모습
m
do
I heard from Mr. Guan that your father wanted to ask for a peace.
What?
You know that Guan Huai returned to the Guan family
and got the importance of Mr. Guan.
You can't hold it anymore?
Yes.
Are you willing to give him a chance?
I don't deserve any pity.
It seems that our Mr. Guan won't ask for help.
I was too impulsive before.
For the sake of the two families,
you don't remember the past.
Don't argue with me.
Why do you think
I would want a shirky shoe that has a green hat?
You are full of words.
I don't think you deserve it.
You can't even count the hats on my head.
Your shoe is broken into pieces.
How dare you talk to me about it?
At least I'm different from you.
I'm not as dirty as you.
Who are you looking for?
Why do you have to be with that bastard?
Don't you want the shares of the Guan family?
After marriage,
I will transfer all the shares to you.
I can also pay off the debts of the Qin family.
Are you serious?
You really want to do it?
Kneel down.
Let me see your sincerity.
You and I show sincerity.
Let me kneel down.
Kneel down.
Hands up.
We are family now.
From now on, mine is yours.
I'm sorry.
Drink a glass of wine to celebrate.
During the online meeting,
Mr. Kuan doesn't allow you to drink.
I know
you must have hidden the wine.
I didn't expect that a person
could fall twice in one place.
I don't know if it's simple or stupid.
You want to withdraw the money in advance?
Mrs. Lan, didn't we agree in advance?
The meeting will last five days.
How can we cancel it in a short time?
Mr. Kuan,
I'm really sorry.
There is a reason for that.
The hidden goods must be withdrawn before six o'clock.
Mrs. Lan,
we can talk about it.
We like to talk about the country.
I want to communicate with you.
And it's not safe to withdraw the money in such a short time.
No need.
I made the contract first.
I will pay the deposit according to the contract.
Goodbye.
Mrs. Lan,
if you have any conditions, just ask me.
Mrs. Lan, Mrs. Lan.
He's really determined.
What should we do next?
I'm really trying to make him do that.
Peter.
There is still time before six o'clock in the afternoon.
You prepare to act in advance.
I'm afraid it's too late.
It's a few days earlier than our original plan.
Our people haven't reached the real thing yet.
We don't have enough people.
And Xin Yi,
is she done?
How's the progress?
Almost.
We still need to complete the last detail.
Good.
You know Lan and Sheng Yu Lan.
Xin Yi,
you don't lose your father.
I'm also doing his last work for my father.
Put this painting
and the exhibition hall's one together.
It's exactly the same.
Who can tell the difference?
Can the rest of the parts
be completed before sunset?
Why did you change it suddenly?
The plan has changed.
It must be completed before six o'clock this afternoon.
Dad.
Lan Ke suddenly started to move things.
They're going to withdraw.
I don't know if he made a mistake.
It's a mess.
We have to plan ahead of schedule.
But then
it's too late to do the workshop and deal with it.
I suspect
Lan Ke must have noticed something.
If we miss this opportunity...
It's going to be a day of dusk.
Guan Huai,
you and Shi Tou will act together later.
Don't let me down again this time.
Lan Ke has sent people
to pack the painting of the White Bird and the Spring.
They will use the goods train to transport the Lian Shui Town.
After arriving at the airport,
they will board the train and leave the city.
There are people in their team.
It's convenient for us
to make a move on the way out of town.
I'm going to go to the city.
I've prepared a car.
From the outside to the car park,
it's like the two birds that transport the truth.
By then,
you will drive this car
and put the new painting
behind the car.
There will be a intersection
on the hillside.
You will exchange
at this intersection.
Mr. Huo, I'm here.
Brother Qing.
Put it here.
What a beautiful pearl.
It's a picture of a bird caught in the night.
I, Guan Shanhai, am so happy
to have this painting.
Others may not see it,
but they can't ignore
Mr. Guan's words.
You deliberately drew the deepest part of the painting
with blue and gold.
Such a secret painting,
as long as you look carefully,
you can still see the difference between the times.
How could it be blue and gold?
It should be green and gold.
Mr. Guan is really sharp.
He can see my flaws every time.
This is a fake.
Where is the real thing?
The real thing was taken away by Mrs. Lan.
It should be on the plane.
How could it be?
I drove the car that sent the real thing.
After changing the car,
no one touched it again.
How could it be a fake?
Brother Shi Tou,
is it possible that
the painting you started to move
is a fake?
And the one I moved on the car
is the real pearl of the white bird.
Thanks to our mutual understanding,
I can successfully
send the real thing to the airport.
There are already people like me in the car team.
How did you do it?
I informed Mrs. Lan in advance.
Tell her all your plans.
We have all the evidence
of what you did.
We have already called the police.
The police will be here soon.
No wonder she left the house in advance.
Why did you do this?
What's the use of doing this to you?
Dad,
we don't want you to make another mistake.
Mistake?
What mistake did I make?
I just want the painting of the white bird.
This is not only my obsession,
but also your mother's favorite thing.
Is it wrong for me to do this?
What I want is
as long as it exists in this world,
it can only be mine.
Dad,
this painting is also mine.
Gu Wenxiang,
since the beginning,
you have always wanted this painting.
How can you still fight for my mother's life?
That covers your own personal feelings.
What she wants
is never the painting of the white bird.
What she wants is to leave you.
It's freedom.
It's you.
You trapped her with your fake, disgusting love.
You forced her to die.
Why did mom kill herself?
Why?
Yun,
this is the gift I gave you.
This is not mine.
It's not for me.
This is a gift for you to satisfy your desire.
How could it be?
We all like Ma Qingshan very much.
You forgot.
We were in love because of Ma Qingshan.
You also want to see the white bird picture?
I have fulfilled your wish.
Ma Qingshan
The factory you made up for my senior
is to complete this painting, right?
Ten years.
I have been looking for this white bird picture.
But I didn't find it.
Maybe it is not in this world.
So I asked the factory to imitate this painting.
Your senior will pick a beautiful pearl and ask for help.
Look, that red one.
It is made of your blood.
Isn't it very beautiful?
Only a beautiful person like you can make such a beautiful pearl.
My senior.
Where is he now?
Where is he?
He had an accident in the factory.
It is a pity that if he were still alive,
this painting would have been completed long ago.
Guanshan.
You are too scary.
Do you still have a heart?
It's okay, Yun.
I will find the painter and complete this painting.
You promised me.
I will give you blood, you will divorce me.
Yun.
I love you.
Why do you want to leave?
I will not let you go.
We will be together forever.
I love you.
Guan Dong.
I really don't understand.
I love him so much.
Why did he do this?
Why did he use death to leave me?
Yun, you are too stupid.
Dad.
I hit this punch for my mother.
You are still so stubborn.
You built the factory to imitate this painting.
I have nothing to do with that factory.
I am just their client.
I wanted to paint.
That factory did not have a suitable painter.
I recommended your father.
I didn't expect your father to be deceived by them.
The factory's power was already under surveillance.
When the capital was destroyed, they transferred the painting to me.
I am the victim.
I paid half of the price.
You are not the mastermind of the factory.
But you are the most evil accomplice.
What are you doing?
No.
Stop.
This is my father's last mistake.
It is also his most hateful act.
It is also the nightmare of Mrs. Ming Yu.
It should not exist.
Stop.
Dad.
Dad, please.
Wake up.
I am sorry.