=The Penthouse 3=
(All characters, organizations, places,
and events are fictional.)
Previously on The Penthouse 3.
We're all here to punish Joo Dan Tae
and Cheon Seo Jin.
First, we need to turn the two
against each other completely.
Nothing's better than money.
Two hundred million dollars.
-I want 500 million dollars.
-Are you kidding me?
I plan to dry up
all of Joo Dan Tae's funds.
It's a picture of Dan Tae
following Oh Yoon Hee's car in his.
Circulate this to every media company.
Move as quickly as possible
so it can be breaking news.
I'll kill you, Seo Jin.
I've looked up a boat
that smuggles people to China.
They're all gone.
The final winner is you, Cheon Seo Jin.
I'll erase all your bad memories.
I've been saving all my pills
just for you.
=Episode 11=
We're leaving soon, so stay in here.
In here?
Yes.
Darn it.
He'll rot there for the rest of his life.
He'll pay for what he's done.
I don't know how long he'll live,
but he'll wish he was dead, for sure.
What?
What is this?
Let's go.
Let's get going.
Hey, you.
Where am I?
What is this place?
Hey.
Are you awake,
Mr. Baek Jun Ki?
Baek... Baek Jun Ki?
What...
Baek Jun Ki.
What is this place?
Why am I here?
What is this?
Hey! Unlock this!
Hey.
Seok Kyung?
Was it you?
To get revenge?
You really are Su Ryeon's daughter.
Is this how you repay me for raising you?
Is that what your mom taught you?
I learned it from you.
You know I'm your Mini-Me.
You locked me up and dumped me
because I didn't share your genes.
What could I have learned from you?
How does it feel?
Don't tell me...
you want to treat me like a daughter
now that you're locked up.
I don't care what people say.
I'm not ashamed.
I raised my enemy's child
to the best of my ability for 20 years.
I even decided to kill Ro Na
so that you'd win the Grand Prize...
at the Cheong A Art Festival.
That's not all.
I had your competition eliminated
one after another...
since you were too dumb
to get into SNU on your own.
For you!
Did you forget?
Even your birth dad
couldn't have done all that.
What more do you want from me?
I never asked for that.
You're the one
who turned me into a monster.
Because of you, I killed my twin sister
and harassed and hated my mom.
I can't even go to my mom because of you.
What?
I despise you so much.
If you hated me so much,
you should've abandoned me.
Why did you live like that? Why?
I don't have time to chit-chat with you.
Get me out of here now.
I have a lot of work to do in Seoul.
I can't do that.
I wasn't the one who sent you here.
It was Logan.
He doesn't know I'm here.
I happened to find out, so I followed you.
Logan?
What do you mean, Logan?
That's right. I guess you don't know yet.
Logan is alive.
Mom's just fine too.
I bet they're back in the penthouse
by now.
Su Ryeon came back?
How is that woman alive? How?
How could she die?
She'd be too angry to die.
Her husband, daughter,
and friend all died by your hands.
I came to say bye.
I thought it was my duty as your daughter.
Goodbye forever.
Seok Kyung. Wait.
Don't do this. Please don't.
We were close.
I must've lost my mind for a minute.
I sent you there not because I hated you,
but because I was mad at your mom.
So I took it out on you, that's all.
You know how much Daddy loves you.
I always liked you
and looked out for you...
more than Seok Hoon, my flesh and blood.
Seok Kyung. Please get me out of here.
I'm sorry for everything.
Seok Hoon, you,
and I can go back to the way things were.
I'll make it happen.
I'll fix everything.
Absolutely everything. Seok Kyung.
How pathetic.
Do you think I came here just to see that?
You've lost. Give up.
In both Korea and Japan,
you're a murderer and a fugitive.
It's probably more comfortable
to stay in there.
I won't come by again.
Live the rest of your life as Baek Jun Ki.
Seok Kyung!
You can't just go!
You have to get me out of here!
Seok Kyung! Seok Kyung!
Seok Kyung!
Hey, Logan.
You really want me to take care
of Baek Jun Ki and Jin Bun Hong...
just like you said to?
Baek Jun Ki betrayed me
and joined Seo Jin,
but he's a victim too.
Dan Tae killed his parents.
He was locked up in a mental hospital
and gave up on life for 27 years.
So?
I may give him another chance...
once he loses his gambling addiction.
Step aside. I need to talk to Logan.
Logan! Please!
Don't send me to my husband.
I'd rather die by your hands
right here and now.
I don't want to be beaten to death
in the house where my daughter died.
I'm begging you.
I won't do anything to Eun Byeol.
I'll just watch from afar. I swear.
Eun Byeol is my life.
I'll die if I can't see her.
I may have lost Michelle,
but I can make Eun Byeol happy.
I can't send her to that woman Seo Jin.
Look.
Get psychiatric treatment first.
And you can never go near Eun Byeol
ever again.
I'll decide what to do with you
after you complete your treatment.
-No.
-Mr. Hong.
No. Please, I'm begging you.
Logan! No.
No. Logan!
-I feel sorry for her too.
-Logan!
She left home
to escape from her abusive husband.
Her daughter, Michelle,
waited for her to come home...
and froze to death.
Michelle...
looked a lot like Eun Byeol.
Alex.
Yes?
I need you to do something
before you go back to the US.
My goodness.
Did you prepare all this yourself?
You did a beautiful job.
Do you like it?
Of course, I love it.
I can't believe this.
Mom, shall we drink?
Sounds good.
You made a good choice.
It's so sweet.
This is...
the happiest day of my life.
I feel terribly bad for Ro Na's mom
who saved my life,
but don't remember anything.
If you forget all the bad memories,
you can be happy too, Mom.
Then you won't have to do
any more bad things for me,
and you won't feel tormented.
I'll make that happen.
By the way,
how's your headache? Has it gone?
It's gone away completely.
That's a relief.
Who's that?
I'll go and see.
Mom, it's our photo.
Our portrait?
Let's see.
-My gosh.
-Don't we look lovely?
Eun Byeol, how come you're so pretty?
You might not remember even me one day.
When that day comes, I'll look after you.
I'll be your mom.
I won't ever leave you.
I promise.
You look so happy.
You bet I am.
I was sitting with you.
Where should we hang this?
Well...
Secretary Do, I'm chatting with Eun Byeol.
Unless it's urgent...
Rumours are spreading that
Cheong A Constructions will go bankrupt.
Financiers heard
of the financial problems.
Stop it somehow.
Stall the banks and media
for as long as you can.
Alex called
about buying Cheong A Constructions.
What shall I do?
Alex?
I didn't know you were interested
in buying Cheong A Constructions.
Yeah. I've been in contact
with Mr. Joo for a while.
Didn't you know?
I guess there's no business talk
between the two of you...
under the same roof.
My husband was in charge
of the construction business.
It's the perfect opportunity
for your father to enter Korea.
Cheong A Constructions
is quite hot right now.
Because of Cheonsoo District.
That may be true, but unfortunately,
Mr. Joo Dan Tae has been involved
with some unwanted attention.
So I don't know if I should go through
with this contract anymore.
The Cheonsoo District project
has huge merit.
You'll regret losing out on it.
Yeah?
Well, if it's such a sweet business,
then why are you trying to sell?
Because I want to focus
on culture and arts.
I don't have the energy
to run a construction business too.
The Cheonsoo District project
has already broken ground.
If they can take on the existing team,
many people other than you
would want to buy the company.
One.
I do have one condition.
If for any reason,
you happen to be involved
in any form of crime,
you best know this contract is dead.
What crime?
Don't worry. That'll never happen.
Well, good, then. Name your price.
Three billion dollars.
I don't think that's a bad price.
If you think so.
So the Cheong A Group presidential
inauguration is coming up, right?
So why don't we announce
the takeover of Cheong A Constructions...
on the same day?
Can you give me a 30-percent
down payment?
Whatever you want.
Goodbye.
You did well.
We'll go bankrupt
if we don't pay the bills this week.
I think we can get through it.
Logan helped me in many ways.
Things will get sorted out
easier than I thought.
Logan Lee was actually a benefactor.
You still haven't located Dan Tae?
Even the police are looking for him.
You'd better stay in hiding, Joo Dan Tae.
Don't suddenly show up and ruin it for me.
Now, am I left
with just one more problem?
Bae Ro Na.
Can you open the door?
I'd like to interview you, Ms. Bae.
Ms. Bae, come outside.
We just want to confirm something.
Is it true you bribed the pianist
at the arts center audition?
We got a report that those
who auditioned were all connected.
Comment on that.
There's also talk that
you threatened Ms. Cheon.
What's the truth?
-Ms. Bae.
-Is it true?
-Say something.
-Did you threaten...
-Come outside and talk.
-Shoot.
-You people!
What are you all doing here?
Why are you yelling at a door
with no one behind it?
Who let you in? How did you come inside?
Since when did Hera Palace's security
become this useless?
This is an invasion of privacy.
So what, if you're reporters?
Can you torture someone
about groundless rumours?
Shall I report you to the police?
Jenny, did you call security?
What's taking them so long?
-Here they come.
-Get this lot out of here!
How are we gonna live in peace
with security this lax?
I apologize.
Get out of here, okay?
Get out, now!
Come on, drag them out!
-Come along.
-Wait.
-Get out of here!
-Just a moment!
How did you come in? Get out!
-Let go.
-Move!
Get out now.
-Okay.
-Walk!
I swear Cheon Seo Jin called them.
She thinks she can do what she wants
because you're not around.
She must've lost her mind.
How else could she even think
of going after that little girl?
It looks like Seo Jin went too far.
I'll let Ro Na take care of the reporters.
Mom.
She checked out already.
Where did she vanish to?
Do you have any guesses?
I'll track the phone and credit card
I gave her.
Why did you ask to see me?
I saw on the news
what Joo Dan Tae did to your mom.
You must be in shock.
I was very worried.
Thank you for worrying about me.
Sure.
I asked to see you to discuss a detail
in the artist in residence contract.
I'll send you abroad to study.
This is a great and special benefit.
Italy or the US.
Where will you go?
Why are you trying to send me away?
What do you want to hide?
You sent the reporters to my house,
didn't you?
You act like you're being generous,
but you want me to back off, do you?
You want to disparage my name...
to block me from working in this industry,
is that it?
Misunderstanding one's intent.
You're just like your mom.
I have no intention
of going abroad to study.
There's something I must stay here and do.
Something you must do?
Clear my mom's name.
-Wait.
-No, you can't go inside.
I called them.
Thank you for coming.
You seemed to be curious about me.
I thought it best I explain,
so I asked you all to come here.
Where Center Director Cheon is too.
What do you think you're doing?
Today, I will reveal
the last moments of my mom...
who was called the Admissions Murderer.
-What do you mean?
-Is there a video?
-What is this about?
-Show their face. Ms. Cheon?
Three people appear in this video.
My mom, Chairman Joo Dan Tae, and...
Center Director Cheon.
-What?
-No way.
-Is that true?
What happened?
I reached the location
after Oh Yoon Hee fell.
I didn't see anything.
That's a lie.
Center Director Cheon was there
when my mom was alive.
And she stayed silent until now.
My mom was called an abductor...
and Admissions Murderer,
and you said nothing.
Why was that?
Were you
working with the murderer, Joo Dan Tae?
Or did you help him murder my mom?
What are you...
What are you talking about?
It's not true.
I'm a victim.
Joo Dan Tae did everything on his own.
Really? Are you sure?
Yoon Hee!
-Hey, get that!
-Film it!
Hurry up!
-She was trying to save Eun Byeol.
-Make sure you get everything.
-I'm getting everything.
-Oh, my.
Oh, no!
There is a car standing precariously
over the edge of a cliff.
It looks like it's about to fall off
at any moment.
This is the dashboard cam footage...
from the Ha Eun Byeol Abduction Case
which became the talk of the town.
Stop it!
Eun Byeol is in the car!
Eun Byeol!
-Get Eun Byeol out first!
-Oh Yoon Hee!
Eun Byeol! Eun Byeol!
Get her out!
I'll move when you get her out,
so do it now!
Hold on a second!
Eun Byeol, wake up!
Oh, no. Eun Byeol...
The dashcam footage from the case
where Oh Yoon Hee was suspected...
to have abducted her daughter's friend
has been revealed.
In the footage, after Chairman Joo Dan Tae
of Cheong A Group...
is seen pushing Oh and disappearing,
we are able to see that
Oh was still alive...
thus causing controversy.
Ms. Oh Yoon Hee has gone
from an assailant to a victim,
and until the moments before her death,
she did everything she could
to help her daughter's friend...
shocking many people.
As it turns out, the person
who was with Oh until the end...
was Chairman Joo Dan Tae's wife,
Center Director Cheon Seo Jin.
With the reveal that
she was a witness in the case,
the fact that she had taken
a passive stance regarding Oh,
who saved her daughter's life,
has turned into suspicion.
-Eun Byeol.
-After the fact that Oh Yoon Hee...
was falsely charged
had been brought to light,
people have begun to raise their voices
for an investigation.
-Why are you watching this?
-Some say...
The dashcam video
doesn't show you pushing Ro Na's mom.
-Thank goodness. Right?
-What?
You know that I remember everything.
I was just pretending to have forgotten.
Don't you dare say that to anyone.
The culprit has been revealed anyway.
It's Joo Dan Tae.
But reporters will still harass you.
See? People are already calling.
Turn off your phone too.
There's no need to create trouble.
The best thing to do right now
is to ignore it.
Once the Cheong A Group Chairman
Inauguration ceremony ends,
-I can handle everything.
-How?
I told you! The culprit is Chairman Joo.
So don't worry about anything
and just trust me.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Why isn't the medicine working?
She needs to lose her memory
before the investigation.
What happened?
How did Ro Na get her hands
on the dashboard camera footage?
You said it was broken,
so how did they fix it?
The police received a tip
under the name Jin Bun Hong.
It seems that they recovered it
through digital forensics.
Jin Bun Hong, that witch!
How much of it was filmed?
Was what was covered on the news
everything? What about after that?
The moment when Oh Yoon Hee fell
wasn't on it.
The footage seems to have been edited,
but the edge of the cliff can't be seen
from the angle of the camera.
They may have chosen
not to reveal that part of it.
If that's the case,
they would've called you in already.
Seeing as to how nobody has called,
what you saw was probably all of it.
You can relax.
Jin Bun Hong's about to ruin...
my plan to make Joo Dan Tae
take the fall for everything.
Why did this happen now?
What about Jin Bun Hong?
She went totally off the grid
after the press conference.
I gave her 500 million dollars,
but she stabbed me in the back?
Do you think...
she gave Joo Dan Tae that footage too?
And received money from both sides?
She's a conniving woman.
I wouldn't put it past her.
What if Joo Dan Tae has the latter half...
of that footage?
What if he took it and ran?
He'll come back.
I'm sure of it.
Joo Dan Tae.
Cheon Seo Jin...
will do anything she can to hold out
until the inauguration ceremony.
She is deluded enough to think that
as the leader of Cheong A Group,
she will have the power
to cover this whole thing up.
Since she believes that Su Ryeon and I
are gone for good,
I'm sure she will do that.
Come tomorrow, Cheon Seo Jin...
will also find out the truth.
That Yoon Hee didn't just die.
That killing Yoon Hee...
was the biggest mistake in her life.
I've told the reporters that...
you will hold a press conference
after the inauguration ceremony.
Good job. What about the sale
of Cheong A Constructions?
I set a meeting for 10:00 AM.
You have to sign the promissory note
within the day, so it's urgent.
Pay back the loan
as soon as the down payment comes in.
Once we get the three billion dollars,
our financial difficulties
will be resolved immediately.
What about Eun Byeol?
She'll be going to the ceremony
straight from the practice room.
Make sure she has bodyguards with her.
Joo Dan Tae might show up.
We need to finish the deal
before the ceremony.
Make sure there are no issues.
Yes, ma'am.
I just need to get through today. If I do,
everything will go back
into place perfectly.
How annoying. Give me the keys.
There's a hole in the tire!
What's going on?
Dad?
Alex? I'm about to leave right now.
Did you check the contract?
I am so disappointed in you.
Unfortunately, I'm going to have to go
and cancel this contract.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean
you're going to cancel the contract?
I specifically said in my terms...
that the owner
should not have any criminal background.
But it just so happens to be...
that the person who
was keeping my brother, Logan, captive...
happened to be you.
Who on earth would say such nonsense?
It's not true.
It's nothing but a baseless rumour!
-It was all Shim Su Ryeon's...
-Yes, well...
We'll see if it's a rumour or not
pretty darn soon,
but until then, this contract is on hold.
Goodbye.
Got you.
Alex?
What on earth did he hear?
No, this can't happen.
Without that money,
I can't become the chairman.
Why are you in such a rush?
Move. I don't have time for this.
Were you on your way
to the inauguration ceremony?
The ceremony got cancelled.
You can't go.
Nonsense. Why would it be cancelled?
You want to know why? I'll tell you.
Oh Yoon Hee. You killed her, didn't you?
Why?
Why did you kill an innocent woman?
You're being ridiculous!
Where do you think you're going?
Let go of me!
(Cheong A Group)
-Why isn't she here yet?
-What's going on?
-When is she coming?
-What do we do?
(Cheong A Group)
(Inauguration Ceremony
of Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin)
(Chairwoman Cheon Seo Jin)
Where am I?
Who are you?
Shim Su Ryeon?
Why are you still alive?
Did you run away?
You remember this place, don't you?
It must be quite familiar to you.
You set up this place yourself
to torture Logan.
Here, you gave the order...
to keep him barely alive.
Save Logan,
no matter what.
I'm not expecting him
to properly function like a human being.
I just need him alive.
Let me go. Now!
This is impressive.
But your luck ends here.
You'll soon get caught
and torn into pieces.
You shouldn't underestimate
James's family.
Just worry about yourself.
How far were you willing to go?
In addition to killing Yoon Hee,
you even tried to get rid of me and Logan?
Did you think, if you got rid of everyone,
everything would be yours?
I didn't do it.
Joo Dan Tae
is the one who killed Oh Yoon Hee.
He is also the one
who blew up Logan's car.
You're insane.
Let me go!
Eun Byeol!
Oh Yoon Hee.
Our ill-fated relationship ends here.
Goodbye.
It's not true.
No, it's not true. That footage is fake.
Look me in the eyes. That demon is you.
Yoon Hee was trying to save your daughter,
and you pushed her off the cliff.
Why did you do that?
What did she do so wrong?
I don't know!
It has nothing to do with me!
I knew you'd deny it.
It doesn't matter.
In the end,
your daughter will pay
for everything you've done.
What? Not my daughter.
Where is Eun Byeol now?
Leave her alone, or I'll kill you!
Let me go!
If your daughter's life
is so precious to you,
how could you do that to Yoon Hee?
You'll lose everything.
From money,
which you value more than anything,
to Cheong A Group, Cheong A Foundation,
and Cheong A Arts Center... All of it.
On top of that,
the person you love more than anyone else,
your daughter, Ha Eun Byeol.
No!
I'll kill you, Shim Su Ryeon!
Bring my daughter to me.
She didn't do anything wrong!
Let me go! Now!
Let me go!
Eun Byeol... Bring her to me!
One more thing.
I'll take away your voice
so you can stop lying so shamelessly.
No. Don't do that.
Please. Don't.
Su Ryeon, please.
Don't do that. Please.
No! Don't!
No! Please...
What?
Is it painful?
Is the pain too much to bear?
Didn't you know that...
when you made others suffer?
Feel the pain thoroughly.
Realize what you've done to others.
Stop that.
Min Hyuk, isn't this place wonderful?
It's paradise.
Do you want to go shopping?
Or should we get something to eat?
No. Let's just have something delivered
to our hotel room.
It seems like suite guests
can order special meals.
When are we going home?
We're not going to live here forever,
are we?
We are leaving.
For the next country.
I've already booked everything.
In Hawaii, we'll relax in a villa
with a private pool.
In Switzerland, we'll go skiing.
In Paris, we'll see fashion shows.
In Italy...
Son, should I buy you an opera house?
Mom, aren't you even worried about Dad?
I feel so bad being here without him.
Why would I worry about him?
I know he can survive anywhere
in the world.
You're right.
Anyway, let's order a little food first.
Excuse me.
-What?
Are you Ms. Ko Sang A,
CEO of Bon-bi Holdings?
-What?
-What is he saying?
-I don't know.
-You're under arrest...
for embezzling Cheong A Group's funds.
What?
I embezzled their funds? I didn't!
Let's take her away.
-Mom.
-Son!
Min Hyuk!
Let go of me!
My goodness.
I must have been out of my mind.
I shouldn't have stolen
Chairman Joo's money.
Before I could even touch it...
Gosh, I'm starving.
This is driving me crazy.
(Detective)
Oh, dear.
How did the mighty Lee Kyu Jin
end up like this?
(Ant Real Estate)
I'm in a bit of a situation.
I need to sell the 55th floor
of Hera Palace...
in Samseong-dong immediately.
Hera Palace is in Samseong-dong.
Why did you come to Namyangju?
I had no choice.
I know all realtors
are connected in a network.
At such a cheap price,
it'll be sold in no time.
And I want the down payment in cash.
Please.
-Oh, my.
-Lee Kyu Jin.
You're under arrest
for embezzling Cheong A Group's funds.
Move! Go away!
Cuff him.
You have the right to remain silent...
-and the right to an attorney...
-I'm an attorney myself!
My salary used to be paid
by taxpayers too!
Mr. Baek Jun Ki.
It's time for your medicine.
Who says I'm Baek Jun Ki?
I'm Joo Dan Tae!
After everything I did...
to abandon that name,
to break free from it...
How...
How did you...
Where's my money?
Give me my money,
and I'll spare your life.
You're not even worth killing.
Okay. I'll give it to you.
I'll give you the money,
the house, everything.
Don't do this, Jun Ki.
This isn't you.
You're a good kid.
I don't need to be good.
Just give me my money!
Hey!
I took in a worthless bum,
fed and clothed him,
and made a decent person out of him,
and you want money?
This is why
you shouldn't be kind to orphan rats.
You ingrate.
I don't owe you anything.
You sucked the life out of me.
How could you steal from me...
of all people?
You built this nice house
and want to live in luxury by yourself?
Give me my money now!
You can just save up again.
That chick Na Ae Gyo is good at begging.
You two were an amazing pair.
You'll be millionaires in no time.
Please, I'm begging you.
I didn't eat or buy anything I wanted...
and saved every cent I made
from begging...
since I was ten years old
and gave it all to you.
You said you'd buy me
a house in the middle of Seoul.
You said you'd let me...
build a house
on the land where my mom died!
What is this annoying loser
babbling about?
Where's my money?
Where is poor Ae Gyo's money?
Shut it, jerk.
Hey.
Wash your sneakers, will you?
Seeing these dirty sneakers
kills my appetite.
How many times must I tell you that?
Don't spread your disease
and get lost, you jerk.
Open the safe now!
You freak.
Open the safe!
You scumbag.
I can't go down like this.
I did nothing wrong.
All I did was work hard.
I built Hera Palace
by working my fingers to the bone.
I won't let jerks like Su Ryeon
and Logan taint it.
I need to get out of here.
I must get out of here somehow.
Hurry! Please send help!
-Stop it!
-Bring it.
Stop it!
Let go of me.
You people are dead.
Let go of me!
I want to go back!
Let go.
She's fine?
Yes. Look.
Her MRI and brainwave scans
all came back normal.
How about early-stage dementia
or anything unusual?
No, nothing.
You're worried for nothing.
Are you sure she took that drug?
I didn't take the drug.
I didn't take the drug
that erases memories.
So don't worry.
Then why did you take them from Bun Hong?
It must have been at least 100 pills.
I was going to take them,
but I threw them out.
Did you bug me all day long
just to check that?
Are you done? May I go now?
It's Mom's inauguration. I'm late.
You need to live with me now.
You can't live with Mom.
No. Why should I?
Mom needs me.
How much worse do you want to get?
If you didn't take that drug,
it means you remember.
You know what your mom did
to Ro Na's mom on the cliff!
You know everything.
So why won't you say anything?
Don't you feel bad for Ro Na?
Exactly. So forget this terrible daughter.
I'm a monster who can't be reformed!
Eun Byeol.
Go to Ro Na.
Don't worry about Mom and me.
Go be a dad to Ro Na.
She has...
no one else but you now.
You knew too?
When Ro Na's mom...
risked her life to save me.
That's when I realized.
That was the only reasonable explanation.
Because I was your daughter.
She liked you a lot.
So go. Just go!
I'm sorry to Ro Na's mom,
but I can't leave Mom.
I have to protect her.
If I leave her too,
I'd feel so sorry for Mom.
She did it for me.
So how can I hate her?
I'm going to live with Mom,
just the two of us.
So don't come to me ever again.
Eun Byeol.
(Cheong A Medical Center)
I'm supposed to meet her
at the inauguration.
What's wrong with her?
Hey...
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol. Where are you?
Eun Byeol...
Logan?
How are you...
I wondered...
who had taken me just to torment me.
You manipulated Jun Ki
into betraying me...
and got Ha Yoon Chul out
to prolong my life?
I never even imagined
it would've been you.
And then you dumped all the blame
on Su Ryeon?
How could you do that?
That's not true. You've been lied to.
Su Ryeon did all of this.
That woman...
tried to kill you
to avenge her daughter's death.
It wasn't me.
Do you still not get it?
You're dumber than I thought.
I'm disappointed.
What's going on?
Did you two conspire together
and pretend to be dead?
Was I,
Cheon Seo Jin, fooled?
I saw you.
You injected poison into my arm.
Fortunately, Ha Yoon Chul saved me.
Ha Yoon Chul?
Cheon Seo Jin.
You...
You were the person
behind the altered voice.
I realized that a little too late.
If I'd known,
even if it meant rotting in prison,
I wouldn't have accepted your help.
I didn't get to kill you
before Yoon Hee died.
That's my only regret. Do you know that?
The purchase of Cheong A Constructions
is off the table.
I don't have to explain, do I?
I don't do business with criminals.
Oh, and you provided the cause
for the deal to fall through.
Be prepared to pay the penalty.
No.
I can't go down like this.
You're already ruined.
You failed to repay...
the promissory notes by today.
You planned this from the start,
didn't you?
To bring me down.
You brought in Jin Bun Hong
and Baek Jun Ki...
to set all this up, didn't you?
I don't want to ruin the likes of you.
Because I will kill you.
The board of directors fired you today.
Don't be too upset.
The company's not even worth
a piece of paper now.
I was fired?
I will take over Cheong A Arts Center.
The 20 percent of shares
that Yoon Hee had...
were in my company's name.
The owner's back.
It's only right you return it to me.
Shut your mouth.
I'm the chairwoman of Cheong A Group!
The arts center and foundation
are all mine!
I waited for this day for so long!
I will never fall.
Secretary Do. Where is he?
Summon the directors now!
I'll have the inauguration ceremony!
Secretary Do!
You finally show yourself,
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin.
Who are you people?
You're Joo Dan Tae's wife, aren't you?
I'm here
for the money he borrowed from us.
He looked so desperate,
so I lent him 50 million dollars.
He shouldn't vanish
without repaying his debt.
Why should I give you the money
he borrowed?
I have nothing to do with him.
If his wife has nothing to do with him,
then who does have something to do
with him?
Give me that.
Look at this.
(Bond of Debt)
(Debtor: Joo Dan Tae,
Guarantor: Cheon Seo Jin)
Don't you see you're the guarantor?
That's your seal.
I don't know about this.
I never affixed it on this.
You didn't lend the money to me,
so get lost!
Move. Get out of my way!
Secretary Do!
Cheon Seo Jin. We're the police.
We must question you about Joo Dan Tae,
who's hiding now.
Come with us.
I don't even know where he is.
He's behind all this!
Why are you all doing this to me?
I must get my daughter.
I have no time to waste.
We must force you to come with us, then.
Take her.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
I said let go of me!
They're the worst of the worst
among the loan sharks.
They never give up.
With Joo Dan Tae missing,
Cheon Seo Jin will have to repay his debt
for the rest of her life.
-The interest will snowball.
-I'll kill you all!
It's a depressing amount.
She won't even have the freedom
to choose death.
If she dies,
Eun Byeol will end up inheriting the debt.
Whether she spends the rest of her life
as a fugitive or a debtor,
she'll live in extreme poverty.
Until the moment she dies.
Don't get Eun Byeol involved.
I'll persuade her somehow
to get her to leave.
Our plans don't involve the kids.
I made them promise.
We can trust them.
Cheon Seo Jin had so much money
she could never spend it all.
Now she has a debt so big...
she can never pay it off.
I can't let her
spend the rest of her life...
sitting in a cell in comfort.
Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin...
must experience
what living in torment is like.
The deeds for the penthouse
and Cheonsoo District lot 27.
Dan Tae failed to repay the debt on time,
so legally,
they belong to you now, Ms. Shim.
Thank you, ma'am.
I didn't do anything.
They got what they had coming.
Thank you so much.
I don't know how I can ever repay you.
You saved my life, Ms. Jincheon.
How can I not do this much for you?
Oh, I have to go. I stayed too long.
Will you let me treat you
to a meal one day?
If you have the time to do that,
go and check in on your husband.
I did hire him a good lawyer,
but we'll have to see how things go.
Why is this so special...
that everyone's fighting to keep this?
Don't you feel dizzy
if you're up this high?
People must live closer to the ground.
So that there's no more fighting,
we must end this place too.
(Seized)
Take everything worth anything.
My gosh. This is worthless trash.
(Grand Award)
Get out the way.
Nice.
-Not bad.
-That was nothing.
-Was that nice?
-Yes.
-You must have it in you.
-Try again.
Get out of the way.
(Prosecutors' Office)
What are my charges?
Why did you bring me here?
You're the fugitive
Joo Dan Tae's accomplice.
That's why you're here.
Accomplice?
He and I are total strangers.
We're divorced.
We didn't tell
because we were sworn to secrecy,
but the papers were signed.
You didn't know?
The court didn't approve your divorce.
Someone said you were faking a divorce
to avoid repaying debts.
Here.
(Prosecutors' Office)
The petition.
What?
(Applicant and witness Shim Su Ryeon)
Shim Su Ryeon. To the very end...
Your husband embezzled 500 million
from the company...
and borrowed from loan sharks.
You knew about that, didn't you?
He owes over one billion dollars.
There's no way
he spent all that on his own.
Where did you hide it?
You two.
Aren't you perfect business partners
before being a married couple?
Joo Dan Tae, that lunatic.
Sir.
Will you please let me see Eun Byeol?
That mad woman Shim Su Ryeon
kidnapped her.
Don't change the subject.
Tell me where Joo Dan Tae is.
There's no way
you two are getting out of this.
I really don't know!
I never saw or touched the money.
Ms. Cheon.
You can't even run away.
You're banned from leaving the country.
Did you know
that Cheong A Constructions...
filed for bankruptcy?
What?
Bankruptcy?
How could you do that to Yoon Hee?
You'll lose everything.
From money,
which you value more than anything,
to Cheong A Group, Cheong A Foundation,
and Cheong A Arts Center... All of it.
Everyone that lent Joo Dan Tae money
has filed a lawsuit against you.
There are over ten people
including Haeyeon Group's Chairman Song.
Ms. Cheon. Are you listening to me?
Stop putting on an act
and cooperate with the investigation.
Listen here, Ms. Cheon.
Ms. Cheon!
It seems like a temporary state of shock.
Her respiration is very unstable too.
She should try to get some rest.
Getting questioned
in this state is impossible.
Let's call it a day.
Once she gets better,
she will cooperate the best she can.
She can't leave the country anyway.
When you receive a call from us,
you have to come right away.
I make sure of it.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Director Cheon. Are you okay?
Where am I?
You're in the hospital.
You collapsed during your questioning.
Don't you remember?
What about Eun Byeol? Where's Eun Byeol?
Mom.
Eun Byeol!
My dear daughter. Where did you go?
Do you know how worried I was?
Is everything okay? Did you get hurt?
No. I'm fine.
What about you?
How did you end up at the hospital?
Are you sick?
No. I must have had a headache.
Secretary Do made a fuss for no reason.
You don't have to worry.
Let's go home.
The thing is...
I don't think you can go home
for the time being?
What do you mean? Why?
Loan sharks came charging into our house
and caused a scene.
It was so scary,
and I couldn't pack anything.
We can't go home right now.
I got a place for you to stay
for the time being.
I'll take care of Eun Byeol
and bring her some place safe.
I thought you might get caught easily
if you were together.
How can I live in a place like this?
You want me to sleep
in this smelly, tiny room...
on those dirty blankets?
Get me a room at a hotel.
Hotels are easy to track,
so it's dangerous.
This place is on the outskirts
of the city, so it'll be safer.
They're tenacious people,
so keep your cell phone off too.
Eun Byeol can never live
in a place like this.
Make sure you take care of her.
Don't worry about Eun Byeol
and bear with it for the time being.
My accounts have all been frozen as well,
so I couldn't get any money.
I'm sorry. This is all I could get.
Thanks.
Then get some rest.
Oh Yoon Hee!
Oh Yoon Hee! Please don't do this!
Go away!
Don't do this. Oh Yoon Hee!
Go away, please.
I really had no idea.
My husband is the CEO
of Cheong A Industries,
and I'm just a housewife.
What could I possibly know?
I just trusted my husband
who told me to take a trip,
and I went on vacation with my son.
How could a housewife embezzle funds?
Five hundred million dollars at that?
How does this make sense?
Lee Kyu Jin, that jerk,
committed the crime alone,
unbeknownst to me!
Ko Sang A!
Hey. How could you do this to me?
I heard people went crazy
in front of money,
but how could you betray me and run away?
You even took the only son
of the Lee Clan with you!
This woman knew about everything!
Even still,
you and I really loved each other.
I wanted to buy you a nice house!
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it, woman?
Did you think
I would go with you willingly?
I got married into the Lee family,
and for 20 years,
I lived like a slave for your family.
But you want me to go abroad
and do it some more?
Five hundred million dollars?
I wouldn't even do that
for five billion dollars!
Even if it's a paradise nicer than Hawaii,
I refuse to live with your family!
You go ahead and live with your mo
and your sisters!
I'm going to live with my son.
Hey, Lee Min Hyuk. Be straight with me.
If your mom and I get a divorce,
who do you want to live with?
It's me, right?
What are you talking about?
Please stop this already.
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't want to live with either of you.
I'm going to live alone.
Darn it.
What are you doing?
I should try to sell these
to make some money.
Figure out a way to send Eun Byeol abroad.
She can't move around
and stay with other people forever.
Eun Byeol will refuse to go.
She keeps demanding that
she wants to be with you...
and refuses to eat or sleep.
All she does is cry.
Don't bring her here.
She can't come here.
I'm willing to sell my heart
if it means I can get her flight.
I need to send her abroad at all costs.
She just needs to do...
one thing before she goes.
That's all.
My final wish is to see Eun Byeol succeed.
If we wait, Eun Byeol will be able
to get back Cheong A Foundation...
left for us by my father.
Where should I take you?
Where do you want to go?
What?
Where was I planning to go?
Ma'am.
Hera Palace.
Take me to Hera Palace in Samseong-dong.
Mom.
Seok Kyung...
Where is she right now?
Well...
I did it all by myself.
I don't have a family.
My mom is dead, and it's been a while
since I cut ties with my brother.
So just send me to prison.
I did it all by myself, I swear.
Seok Kyung.
What was it?
(Calling)
Hello?
Are you there?
(Seized)
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol, are you there?
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! Can you hear me?
Where did she go?
Eun Byeol!
I don't have time for this.
-Eun Byeol!
-What?
Is it okay for her to be here?
The loan sharks are everywhere.
Eun Byeol!
Oh, my goodness.
-Eun Byeol!
-Oh, dear.
Eun Byeol!
Ms. Cheon!
Where is she? Eun Byeol!
Dr. Ha, it's me.
Seo Jin showed up at Hera Palace.
But there's something off about her.
Something doesn't feel right.
You should come over right now.
Eun Byeol.
Where is she?
There you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Ms. Cheon.
We have no time to lose.
It's my inauguration ceremony today.
Our outfits are ready.
Come. We'll be late.
Ms. Cheon, let go of me.
I'm not Eun Byeol.
Why won't you listen to me?
Do as I say!
You're my daughter.
You must attend the ceremony.
Everything I have will be yours. Come now.
Come! Hurry!
Listen to me!
-Ms. Cheon, why are you...
-Come!
-Come, Eun Byeol.
-I'm not Eun Byeol.
Hurry. Come.
Stop it, Seo Jin.
Why are you here?
Are you here
to take Eun Byeol away from me?
You can't! I'll never let that happen!
What are you doing?
She's not your daughter!
Yes, she is! You can't take her away!
Move!
Eun Byeol, come to your mom.
Ro Na, run, now!
No! Eun Byeol!
-Get it together, Seo Jin!
-Eun Byeol!
Ro Na, are you okay?
Are you out of your mind?
Where are you taking her?
She's my daughter!
Ro Na!
Mr. Ha, are you okay?
Eun Byeol!
We don't have time for this.
Come with me now.
Why are you so stubborn?
-Eun Byeol!
-Ms. Cheon.
Come with me.
Eun Byeol!
=The Penthouse 3=
I can't let it end like this.
I'll go back by all means.
He's coming back to kill me.
Your life isn't just yours. I love you.
I'm getting engaged to Logan next week.
If I can't have it, no one can, okay?
There will be too many victims.
I'll chase him
to the ends of the earth and destroy him.
Shim Su Ryeon, I miss you.
Come here quickly.