Meng
Qian Mo finally took the bait.
Zhou Xuetong's medical expenses have been increasing lately.
The two of them are doing livestream sales.
Business hasn't been good recently.
It's exactly when they need money.
Give him a little benefit first.
Let him get completely drawn in.
Alright.
Honey.
Are you feeling better today?
Look.
What's this?
A magnetic therapy device.
And also,
I have some good news for you.
I've also made an appointment with the hospital.
Tomorrow,
we'll go get the nusinersen injection.
It's thirty thousand yuan per shot.
You...
Where did you get the money?
Didn't I tell you before?
As long as you cooperate with the treatment,
money
will never be a problem.
Meng
You called me?
How much has Qian Mo paid so far?
It's already over a hundred thousand.
Starting today,
we'll bleed him slowly.
Sister Meng
Qian Mo has already sold his house.
The previous six hundred thousand
has all been paid back.
The remaining five hundred thousand
he also lost to us.
And
he keeps losing.
Continue.
Raise his credit limit.
But Sister Meng,
look at how broke Qian Mo is.
How could he have any money left?
What do you know?
Qian Mo may not have money,
but he has a good wife.
Zhou Xuetong's accident insurance is three million.
Qian Mo is listed as the beneficiary.
That's a big payout.
By the way,
send the loan sharks to Qian Mo's house.
It's time to put some pressure on him.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
What do you want?
We're here to collect money from you.
Smash it for me.
Big brother.
Boss
You owe our boss three million.
When are you going to pay it back?
Boss
Two days.
Can I definitely pay you back within two days?
Qiangzi
What does that chick look like?
Take off the mask.
Let’s see her face.
Pretty good-looking.
Bro.
I'm in love.
Let her go.
It's just a shame she's in a wheelchair.
Let go.
Is this going to get violent?
Come on, hurry up and continue.
Didn't get a drag.
You animal.
I'll kill you!
Let go.
Go.
If you want to beg, beg over there.
Show some sincerity.
I suspect you're faking your paralysis.
Come on, get up.
Then we'll let that guy go.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on, get up.
Come, follow me, come on.
Come on, stand up, come on.
Follow me, come on.
Come on, come on.
Honey.
A m-miracle, did you see that?
Don't move, don't come over here!
She peed.
She peed, she peed.
Come here.
Give a close-up.
Look at that little face, even I feel sorry for you.
Let go.
It reeks of urine.
Honey.
Come here.
I'll give you two three days.
If you still can't pay back the money,
I'll make sure you two can't survive in Xinhai.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Honey, I'm sorry.
Honey.
Don't be mad.
I swear.
I'll never touch this stuff again.
I won't gamble anymore either.
Can you forgive me this once?
Money.
Honey
Honey, it's okay.
Honey, I was wrong.
You lied to me.
Meng
This Zhou Xuetong
She won't die anytime soon.
Our three million
When can we actually get it?
Do you think
I'm waiting for her to die naturally?
Are you saying
Qian Mo should kill his wife
and then claim the insurance money?
Sis
That's a big move.
If we pull this off
Tian can see for himself
the true strength of our team.
Get the face-swapping software ready.
Once Zhou Xuetong dies
we'll fake evidence of him killing his wife
and force him to transfer the insurance money.
Okay.
Honey
I bought your favorite noodles.
Don't worry anymore.
I'll figure something out.
Isn't this our big internet celebrity?
Just one more day until you pay back the money.
What,
you still have the nerve to eat without paying back?
Sorry.
Um...
I'll pay you back in the next couple of days.
Actually,
you don't have to rush to pay back the money.
But next time we come to your house,
it won't just be smashing things.
Your wife will have to let the guys have some fun.
Even though your wife smells like urine,
and can't move,
it's fine.
The guys like to help others.
We can move for her.
To be honest,
your wife actually looks pretty good.
After a wash, you can still use her.
If you don't pay back for a day,
the guys will go "help" for a day.
Until the day you pay back.
You still dare to call me?
Three million.
How am I supposed to pay that back?
Mr. Qian,
why are you so impatient?
A temporary win or loss means nothing.
As long as you still trust me,
I’ll definitely help you turn things around.
One hundred percent.
Nonsense!
You’re still lying to me even now.
I’m lying to you?
You’re the one lying to yourself.
You know full well that your wife’s illness
can’t be cured at all.
Yet you keep pouring money into it.
Is that my fault too?
All of this
should come to an end.
But I...
I have nothing left now.
Doesn’t your wife still have a large insurance policy?