Thank you.
Hello, dear passengers.
The cruise heading from Xinhai to Mikede
Golden No. 2 cruise is preparing for security check.
Passengers taking the Golden No. 2 cruise
please organize your luggage and belongings.
Proceed to the security checkpoint.
Hello, Master.
Where are you?
At the dock.
Going to Mikede.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Qin Lang is being reckless.
And you're following along with him.
Come back right now.
I can't go back.
I'm already getting ready to board.
Do you understand the nature of what you're doing?
I know.
He doesn't want to wear his police uniform anymore.
You don't want to wear it either.
Master.
It's not that I don't want to wear this uniform.
It's just that now Qin Lang and I are partners.
Since we're partners,
we should share honor and disgrace, advance and retreat together.
That's what you've always taught me.
Golden No. 2.
So I'm sorry, Master.
Ticket checking has started.
Please line up.
Come on, come on.
Ticket checking over here.
Enter.
Your ticket.
Let go of me.
What are you doing?
Going to Mickde.
I know you're trying to stop me this way.
But I'm telling you, it won't work.
Don't waste your effort, just go back.
I'm not trying to stop you.
I want to go with you.
Do you know what this counts as?
Without approval from superiors, it's acting without authorization.
You know the consequences.
You're being so fussy.
Gaoman.
Hasn't it been your dream since childhood to be a police officer?
Once you cross this gate,
it will affect your whole life.
Finding your father
isn't that something you've always wanted to do too?
Yes.
So this is my own business.
I'll go by myself.
Qin Lang, let me tell you,
we're partners now.
So this isn't just your business anymore.
I'm not going.
I remember in our junior year,
when we interned at the station,
that time,
you insisted on catching that drug dealer by yourself.
Back then,
I didn't know the whole story.
I thought you just wanted to show off.
So,
I remember now.
You mean reporting it to the station?
That wasn't your fault.
I was also to blame for acting on my own.
Besides,
that drug dealer was pretty dangerous too.
If you hadn't reported it,
and the station hadn't sent someone to escort me back,
I might have been hurt even worse.
But I really didn't expect
that you would get punished because of it.
And even have to repeat a year.
Repeating a year wasn't just because of you.
But about that incident,
I don't really have any regrets.
It's just that
if back then
I had known about your father's situation,
I would have understood
why catching that drug dealer
was so important to you.
I heard from my mentor
that your father
went missing while trying to capture Wei Qiang.
I remember the year my dad had his accident,
I had just started middle school.
It was just an ordinary afternoon.
My mom was still preparing
a change of clothes for my dad.
Suddenly, we got a phone call.
On the call, they said
that while my dad was chasing drug dealers,
he went missing along with them.
At that time, I didn't realize
how serious the situation was.
But then, the waiting
lasted ten years.
Ever since my mom got that call,
she fell ill.
And after she got sick,
as you know,
medical bills became a bottomless pit.
The team donated some money,
but we couldn't rely on others forever.
Uncle Hao and Captain Jiang had no other choice
but to declare my dad as having died in the line of duty.
That way, I could receive compensation.
But you know,
when I signed the papers,
it was the most humiliating moment
of my life.
For the sake of money,
I had to sign my dad's death certificate.
But my mom was saved.
Although her health was never the same as before,
she always felt
she would never hear any news about my dad again.
But I told myself,
no matter if he's dead or alive,
I have to bring him back.
Don't worry.
No matter how difficult it gets,
I'll be with you.
We'll bring your dad back.
Meng,
If you ask me,
you've done so much to help Tian.
But now Zhao is gone.
And Lao Gou has quickly pulled the people from Group Three
over to his side.
Why does it seem like
he's determined to win this?
Look how arrogant Lao Gou has been these days.
He's almost walking all over us.
What should we do?
Let's wait for Tian to come back and then decide.
Tian,
you're back!
You've had a tough time.
Tian,
Tian.
As expected, Sister Zhao is really gone.
Brother Gou was the farsighted one after all.
He made his move early.
Um, Brother Tian.
Where is Sister Zhao?
Did something happen to her?
If anything's wrong, you can tell me.
Why didn't you stop him?
Look at how smug he is.
He’s just relying on someone powerful.
At such a critical moment,
the higher you jump,
the harder you fall.
Brother Tian.
Stop hitting me, Brother Tian, please.
I've been away for so long,
and this is all you've accomplished?
I was wrong, Brother Tian.
I know I was wrong, Brother Tian.
Congratulations to Sister Meng for taking over Group Three.
Keep it low-key.
Brother Tian hasn't officially announced it yet.
Once Brother Tian announces it,
it's just a matter of time.
Cheers!
Sister Meng.
Brother Tian asks you to come to the office.
Okay.
Brother Tian
About Sister Zhao
My condolences
When a person is gone, the light goes out
What's the use of condolences
Let's talk about the company
Xiao Zhao is gone
Her Group Three is now leaderless
I know you two are both fighting for it
Competition is a good thing
But I don't want our own people
to fight each other to the bitter end
Brother Tian
But some people keep picking fights
How do you want to arrange it
We'll do whatever you say, Brother Tian
Of course
Who doesn't listen to Brother Tian
Then this cup of tea
is for Lao Gou
Thank you, Brother Tian
Jiming
Captain Jiang
Later, go over the Yafeng Club
and re-interrogate the other suspects
See if you can get any useful information out of them
Okay, I'll go now
Captain Jiang
What about the two of us
You two write a self-criticism
What?
Don't you know what you two did
Write a self-criticism
Three thousand words
Make it thorough
Reflective
From the heart
That's not really fair
Qin Lang
How am I being unfair?
It's not unfair to me.
It's unfair to Gao Man.
I acted on my own, so I'll write a self-criticism.
That's how it should be.
But everything Gao Man did
was to persuade me to come back.
Why should she have to write a self-criticism?
Fine.
Gao Man.
You go interrogate Lin Sanpeng in a bit.
You
keep writing your self-criticism.
Six thousand words.
Doesn't anyone else have work to do?
Rewrite it.
Qin Lang
Go buy me a cup of coffee.
Aren't you supposed to be writing a self-reflection?
Let me see.
No.
So this is the so-called top student in the whole school,
and this is your self-reflection?
You'd better just go buy me coffee.
When you get back,
I'll help you think about it.
Really.
Hurry up.
Four coffees.
Make one of them a latte.
Less coffee, more milk.
Xiaoxi, you don't remember me?
I'm Gao Man's friend.
That day, I was sitting right
Why are there so many more cameras in your shop now?
The area near our police station isn't very safe.
What happened to your arm?
I'm not in a good mood.
It's fine, I'll do it myself.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Witch.