[English subtitles are available]
[Unchained Love]
[Episode 18]
Godfather, Her Highness is fine.
What are you worried about?
Yuwen Liangshi has noticed
that I treat Bu Yinlou differently.
What you reminded me of earlier
is right.
Just because we are far from the Imperial City,
I became greedy
and reckless.
I almost caused her harm.
Godfather,
you and Her Highness
have no future to start with.
How about
let's just end it here?
That Bu Yinlou has always
been a smart alec since she was a kid.
Even my father
was fooled by her.
Your Highness,
please give me another chance.
I will prove
the relationship between her and Xiao Duo...
Don't you think you were embarrassing enough?
I was careless
and believed your nonsense.
Xiao Duo is so powerful
and there are so many beauties
who have been sent to him.
How could he like
your ridiculous sister?
Maybe...
Maybe he has a unique taste.
Guards.
Escort Concubine Rong to the ancestral hall to reflect on her mistakes.
Find some disciplinary madams
to teach her
the rules of my residence.
Your Highness.
Take her away.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Rongbao.
Send some capable men
to keep an eye on Xiao Duo.
Surely
he has a weak point somewhere.
Yes.
Cool down.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Why are you here?
Your Highness, you're forgetful.
You might have forgotten.
Your Highness ordered me
to play the zither for you today.
I waited in the Flower Garden for a whole day.
Without your order,
I dare not leave.
There's no need today.
You may leave.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Queen Rong'an
sent a secret letter.
Give it to me.
Your Highness.
[This girl, Qiu Yuebai, was Xiao Duo's lover]
I didn't expect it.
Rong'an is still quite useful.
I was just worried there wasn't anyone
who could spy on Xiao Duo for me,
and now she has sent me
Xiao Duo's lover.
Xiao Duo has a lover?
Rongbao.
Yes.
Take this lady
to Mingding Tower,
give her some concessions,
then send her to Xiao Duo.
Yes.
[Mingding Tower]
[Doing as One Pleases]
Mistress.
We've been walking the whole morning.
Even Eunuch Ba can't walk anymore.
Let's go back.
Let's walk a little more.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
Xiao–
According to the information
from the military camp,
there is indeed something problematic
with the Prince of Nanyuan's cash flow.
We must find out the truth.
Got it.
Chief.
Her Highness has been looking at you.
Do you want–
Why did you jostle me?
Stop it.
Cao Chun'ang,
you don't have to go this time round.
Take good care of Her Highness over the next few days.
If Her Highness asks...
Keep your mouth sealed.
He's ignoring me?
Did you see that?
He just
walked past like that.
Your Highness,
what do you want?
What else do you want to play?
We'll go with you, okay?
I want to drink some wine.
[Mingding Tower]
Mistress.
No.
This is...
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
Did he bully you?
What happened then?
We haven't seen
Chief Xiao in a few days.
Mistress thinks
Chief Xiao is avoiding her.
I knew it was him.
How could someone like him
be a good man?
Cousin.
Don't speak ill of him.
I'll get angry.
I have something to tell you.
I know what you want to say.
What do you understand?
He's lying to you.
He actually has another...
Tell me.
Why do people want
more and more things?
When I was with him,
I only wanted a little bit.
But the longer
I am with him,
the more I want.
I know
this is all unrealistic
and absurd.
Maybe he understands now
and doesn't want to get involved with me anymore.
But I can't stop,
and keep falling deeper and deeper.
What will you do
if he has deceived you?
Make him cry.
Your Highness,
we can't stay here for long.
Let's go back.
Didn't you just get here?
What's the rush?
You are not in a hurry but someone else is.
Cousin,
I'll leave first.
Your Highness.
What's wrong?
Since we're here,
why not buy a bottle of wine?
What now?
I don't feel like drinking anymore.
Let's go back.
Mistress.
Young Master,
buy a box of rouge
for the girl you love.
Sending rouge during the festival
is like giving her spring's scenery
and the best of the seasons.
She will understand your feelings.
[Mengyun Pavilion]
I kept feeling like
Chief Xiao was following us today.
My silly mistress.
He's already avoiding you,
but you are still dreaming.
Listen to me.
There's no point chasing him.
You should have some backbone.
Then tell me,
why is he avoiding me?
It doesn't make sense.
What do you mean?
Maybe he was just playing with you.
But you really fell for it, so he got scared.
Didn't you say today
that he has realized?
I just think
he’s following me.
I think he might even be
standing at the door now.
Is that possible?
Let's sleep.
Go to sleep.
I don't want to talk to you.
I'm leaving then.
Godfather.
Bad news!
She's waiting outside.
But with Qilang guarding,
I don’t know how she found her way here.
Chief?
She's been waiting for you all day long.
Duo,
I finally found you.
This...
Chief,
what should we do?
Clear out a room to hide her in
and ask a doctor to come take a look.
Don't let anyone find out.
Yes.
Cao Chun'ang, help.
Okay.
[Mengyun Pavilion]
Here.
Godfather.
The doctor has checked. She's fine.
She said that in the past few years,
she had been living a tough life
so her body's weak.
She got too emotional
so she passed out.
Chief,
I’ve investigated it.
Her name is Qiu Yuebai.
She used to be a palace maid.
She offended
a matron in the palace
and was kicked out of the palace.
There was no trace of her after that.
But
it's indeed strange
for her to look for you at this time.
Was she really Second Master's woman?
Duo told me
there was a girl in the palace
and they were lovers.
Maybe it's her.
She has been missing for years.
Why does she have to show up
just as you are
going to West Shu?
There must be something wrong.
When will she wake up?
Chief Xiao.
You're here, Chief Xiao.
You got up early.
I haven’t seen you in days.
We finally meet today.
Why are you three
just standing here?
Your Highness
hasn't had breakfast yet, right?
Cao Chun'ang,
take Her Highness to have breakfast.
No need.
Why don’t you accompany me
to the Huashen Temple Festival
today?
It's just that the sun has just risen
and it's still early.
Let's just wait then.
I have something important to do.
Chief Xiao.
I’m the Consort Dowager.
Isn't it your duty
to listen to me?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Godfather.
You scared me.
How long
do you plan on shopping for?
I like shopping.
I can shop
for as long as I want.
How's this sachet?
Five wen for one.
It's too noisy here.
Let's rest somewhere else.
What for?
No.
I like it here.
It was my wishful thinking
I waited for you day and night,
but your heart is as steel, as iron.
Drink some.
Waiter.
Serve us wine.
Coming.
You have let me down,
like a poison that takes my life.
Enjoy.
Let's go back.
No.
Did I upset you
somehow?
Why are you suddenly ignoring me?
Your Highness.
You're drunk.
Don't call me Your Highness.
Stop pretending.
You're following me around.
You're obviously worried about me.
♫ The long night is like yesterday's ♫
You were hiding outside my room
♫ The night breeze scattered into a song ♫
the entire night.
Why do you have to
pretend to be
♫ Under the moon ♫
so cold
♫ What am I sighing about ♫
when you see me?
You know everything.
♫ Laughing at the moon, so lonely ♫
♫ Laughing that the stories are too tumultuous ♫
♫ What is love ♫
♫ I still don't understand ♫
Your Highness.
♫ The palace is as it was yesterday ♫
There are things we can't say.
♫ Whose soul has it trapped ♫
I want to say it.
Don't say it.
♫ Fate is unpredictable ♫
♫ No one can escape ♫
You're being mean.
Why are you being mean to me?
♫ Like bubbles, like fireworks ♫
Isn't it just because I like you?
♫ Fate has too many twists and turns ♫
You were the one who tugged on my heart strings first.
♫ You're me ♫
You flirted with me first.
♫ The persistence of my lifetime ♫
Yet now, you don't want me anymore.
Have you never
liked me?
♫ Don't dodge ♫
♫ My love for you is never cowardly ♫
♫ This is ♫
It's fine if you don't like me.
♫ The promise of my lifetime ♫
I don't want it.
[Lanxi Pavilion]
♫ Let this ♫
♫ Fire burn away the entanglements of the past life ♫
♫ For the rest of my life ♫
♫ I'll stay with you ♫
Miss! Miss! Miss!
Don't run around.
Please go back to your room.
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Well,
there are so many stars tonight.
Right?
Yes.
Your Highness, your room is over there.
Let me send you back.
Rest early.
Someone is inside.
No, no.
Move!
It's really empty.
No one is here.
Move!
Your Highness.
You are...
Cao Chun'ang.
Are you hiding a woman?
No, it's not...
It's me.
What happened?
Duo.
Miss Yuebai, right?
For our Chief Xiao
to meet an old friend,
is a happy occasion.
Go back to your room first,
I'll find you after I'm done.
It's no problem.
It's more important
for Chief Xiao to catch up with Miss Yuebai.
I have
nothing much to do anyway.
I'll go to bed
after washing up.
There's no need for Chief Xiao to come.
Duo, Yuebai.
What matching names!
Her Highness didn't even do anything,
Why do I feel
she's scarier
than the tortures in the imperial prison?
Godfather.
What are you going to do
about Miss Yuebai?
Let's ask first.
Playboy. Philanderer.
No wonder he's been cold to me these days.
Turns out he's brought his old lover here!
He's a man.
It's inevitable that he's fickle.
Although Chief Xiao
is not a complete man,
but they are all the same deep down.
Take it easy.
Why?
Bastard!
He wishes!
Eunuch Ba,
you will be a dog without a father from now on.
Let's just live a carefree life.
Tongyun,
if he dares to come again,
just say I don't want to see him.
Forget it.
I'd better not stay here
and be an eyesore.
I'm going back to the capital.
Let him and Qiu Yuebai
live their blissful life.
Why do I have to go back to the capital?
I've won so much dowry
from Bu Yin'ge,
and those dozen boxes of
valuable things.
It's better to find a place
where no one knows me,
and live a carefree life
far far away with that money.
How are you going to live that carefree life?
He's not the only player here.
Who doesn't know how to play?
Your Ladyship,
let me sing a song for you.
let me massage your shoulders.
You the one who said
we will be together forver.
Now you've replaced me with new people.
Y-you hate me now.
Have you forgotten
our affection in the past?
Enough.
Take it easy.
Just tolerate what you can.
If you can't,
then just pack up.
Get out!
This is domestic abuse!
Fan me harder.
I can't live like this!
That's not bad.
Stop thinking about these stupid ideas.
You want to leave,
will Chief Xiao let you leave?
Don’t you remember he said
he brought you along
under the command of the emperor?
If you run away,
he will be implicated.
He treated me like this.
Why would I still care about him?
You're right.
In my opinion,
Chief Xiao is blind.
That Qiu Yuebai
is nothing compared to our mistress.
Of course.
But
Chief Xiao's
attitude is clear.
He wants to break up cleanly with you.
In my opinion,
it's a good thing...
I should be the one who breaks up with him!
How dare he
do it without thinking?
Qiu Yuebai is nothing.
I have to ask him.
Let's go!
How many years haven't we met?
Six years.
I remember it clearly.
When I was kicked out of the palace,
I was only 15 years old.
I have no family outside the palace.
I couldn't find any place to stay.
You said you would put me up.
You asked me to wait for you at the west of the city
on the seventh of the sixth month.
You said you would come.
When the time came,
I waited and waited,
day after day.
Even after my tears have dried up,
you still haven't come.
Why didn't you come to me after that?
I—
I waited until it was dark that day.
I was kidnapped by human traffickers
and sold to Hedong.
Over these years,
I've been wandering around
many places.
Talking about it now
brings back only painful memories.
Duo,
after all these years,
I just want to ask you one thing.
Why didn't you come that day?
Something happened suddenly
and I was late.
A few days ago,
I begged my the way back to the capital.
It was then that I heard my Duo
has became a high official.
So I came to West Shu.
Why didn't you look for me?
Did you forget me?
How did you know I was in West Shu?
I...
I heard it from someone.
You said you begged your way
back to the capital.
But this outfit
doesn't look like it.
The fabric of your clothes
is a new product from a quality store in the capital, right?
Jinguan City is far from the capital.
Where did you get the money for travelling?
Someone sent you here?
Who is it?
Did they ask you
about my past?
Duo.
Are you
unhappy that I came to look for you?
From now on,
don't go out to see anyone from outside anymore.
I'll send someone
to take care of your necessities.
Without my permission,
you're not allowed to leave this house.
Duo.
Don't go.
I heard you're looking for me
to register the reward
the capital sent to the Prince of Nanyuan's residence.
I was about to talk to you about it.
Shall we?
[Doing as One Pleases]
Let go!
Does it hurt?
None of your business.
Don't get close to Qiu Yuebai anymore.
All I did was
show up in front of her
and you're already worried about her.
Who do you think you are?
No one cares!
Godfather.
Miss Yuebai is crying in her room.
Do you want to
go take a look?
Go take a look. Hurry up.
Do you still want to take a look?
Let her cry.
It seems like this reunion
is not that happy.
Tongyun, come in.
Your godfather is a bastard.
You're no good either.
[Doing as One Pleases]
It's none of my business.
This...
Godfather.
Are you alright?
Qiu Yuebai is hiding something.
I think someone
sent her to me on purpose.
Could someone be suspicious
of your identity,
and is using her to probe you?
Not necessarily.
If they were already suspicious,
I'm afraid I won't be
standing here right now.
Send some men to check out
who she has met
along the way.
I want to see
who is behind this.
Yes.
But Qiu Yuebai is a hidden danger.
If she finds out that you're not Second Master,
it will be a big problem.
Do you want to...
No.
Just confine her.
She is Duo's woman.
She is the only person
who was sincere towards him in the palace.
No matter how dangerous she is,
I can't kill her.
But Her Highness doesn't know
the reason behind this.
I think Her Highness
was really angry just now.
When a woman gets angry,
it's dangerous.
This matter involves too much.
We can't let her get involved.
Tell our men
to keep an eye on Qiu Yuebai.
Don't let anyone near her.
Especially Her Highness.
Yes.
Mistress,
eat something.
It won't interfere with you losing your temper.
I'm not eating.
I'm so angry, it's killed my appetite.
Why should I eat?
He even sent someone
to guard Qiu Yuebai's room.
Who is he guarding her from?
Shameless vixen.
Yes.
Qiu Yuebai
is obviously
a shameless vixen.
Xiao Duo.
I was talking about Xiao Duo.
Xiao Duo is a vixen.
I quit. I'm breaking it off.
I'll set him free to philander around.
Even if he comes to cajole me,
it won't work.
It won't work even if he kneels down to beg.
I don't want to be fooled by him.
Mistress, you finally figured it out.
Why hasn't he come to cajole me?
Godfather,
go in if you want to.
If not, go back and rest.
What's the point of
hanging around here?
I heard she was angry
and didn't eat well.
So what should I say
when I go in?
Actually,
it's not such a bad thing
to you and Her Highness
that Qiu Yuebai showed up.
Why don't we let Her Highness
go on misunderstanding you,
and let her give up on you?
It's better for her to feel sad for a while
than for her to waste a lifetime.
Tell her you sent it
and ask her to eat well.
He's really not coming?
I can't be cajoled.
He's not going to be able to cajole me ever again.
Has she eaten?
Are you still thinking about
whether Her Highness has eaten?
Miss Yuebai fainted again.
Get her a doctor.
I did.
The doctor has seen her,
but she refuses to take medicine.
She's making a fuss, saying she wants to see you.
Since she's a troublemaker,
let her wait.
Where is Ah Duo?
Godfather is busy today.
He asked me to talk some sense into you.
If you don't feel well,
you should listen to the doctor
and take your medicine.
Is he with Her Highness?
Miss Yuebai,
you shouldn't ask
what you shouldn't ask.
Duo,
has your heart really changed?
What about me?
What should I do?
How is Qiu Yuebai doing?
She has been sent to Xiao Duo.
But according to our spies,
Xiao Duo has been
treating her rather coldly.
He's only keeping her in the residence.
Your Highness.
Can such a woman
really be of help?
Xiao Duo
is such a powerful character.
How could he still have eyes for his old lover
from when he was down and out?
It's fine if he neglects her.
When a woman is desperate,
she will do anything.
Rongbao,
ask her to find a chance
to put this
into Xiao Duo's food.
Your Highness.
What is this?
Snow mugwort.
Fatal when ingested.
Your Highness.
If Xiao Duo dies in West Shu,
the capital will hold us responsible.
The Emperor
might take the opportunity to send troops.
How could Xiao Duo die in West Shu?
By the time his body
is found,
it must be in the cold river, on its way to the capital,
well outside of West Shu territory.
Because
his ship crashed into a reef,
it was destroyed and he was killed.
Not a single person was left alive.
Your Highness is wise.
Qiu Yuebai is sick?
Yes.
I happened to see when I walked past.
When the wind blew,
she fell to the ground
like a leaf.
Don’t expect Chief Xiao
to come here.
He must be in her room now.
Maybe he's cajoling her right now.
How dare he!
Chief Xiao sent someone to watch over her.
He said
no one is allowed to see Qiu Yuebai.
Don't do this.
I'm scared.
Bad news.
My mistress wants to cook spicy chicken
for Chief Xiao.
That chicken didn't cooperate,
so they're fighting now.
Her Highness is fighting with a chicken?
It's just a chicken.
I'll do it.
Take a look.
What are you waiting for? Go help.
Your Highness, please forgive me.
I've been wanting to pay you a visit.
It's just that
Duo is worried for my health,
and wouldn't let me.
He has always been like this.
Whenever it involves me,
he is extra cautious,
and wouldn't take no for an answer.
But the rules are the rules.
How can he be so willful?
Please be magnanimous.
Don't blame him.
If you're tired,
you can stand up yourself.
Are you waiting for me to help you?
I know you don't like me.
It's all my fault.
It has nothing to do with Duo.
If you are angry, come at me.
You applied powder well.
It's hiding the rosiness of your skin perfectly.
You do look ill,
yet you exude a beauty like Xi Shi's.
Unfortunately,
Xiao Duo doesn’t buy it.
He hasn't been here,
right?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Was this woman
really Xiao Duo’s lover?
Xiao Duo
doesn't treat her
like she's his old flame.
But why didn't he deny it?
You are his brother?
He's lucky now.
You're rich and powerful,
you can buy him
as many lanterns as he wants.
Where is he?
Why don't you ask him
to come out and have fun too?
He's dead.
Two brothers.
Which one of them died?
Is Xiao Duo really Xiao Duo?
Switch a tactic,
and try harder.
I’m leaving.
Qilang, where are they?
Your Highness, no!
I was wrong, Your Highness.
This is...
If you do this,
I won't hesitate either.
I hit her.
Are you okay?
I didn't get hit,
of course I'm okay.
I'm just being jealous.
I'm doing great.
Chief Xiao,
if you’re hiding something from me,
you'd better come clean now.
If you do it too late,
I might not want to listen anymore.
I'll tell you in the future.
Don't bother.
Duo.
Her Highness didn't mean it.
Qiu Yuebai.
Listen carefully.
If you behave yourself,
I'll protect you for the rest of your life.
But if you dare
play tricks on Her Highness again,
I won't show mercy.
Do you understand?
It's just killing a chicken.
Why are you two here?
Too many cooks spoil-
Chief Xiao.
Keep an eye on her.
If she dares to make trouble again,
make her mute.