[English subtitles are available]
[Unchained Love]
[Episode 33]
It's wrong!
It's all wrong!
That's not how you should be acting!
That...
That eunuch.
Yes, yes, you...
Come here.
Come on.
It's okay. Kneel down.
Consort Duan.
Are you enjoying this show?
I had it arranged specially for you.
You're not?
If you're not enjoying it,
then they should be punished.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, no!
So in this play,
you two are the main characters after all!
Sharing the same fates, and being together with each other.
What about me then?
Who am I?
What am I?
I...
am a eunuch.
This is...
Consort Duan has moved into Deer's Reed Residence for too long.
It's time to return to the palace.
All of you carry on singing.
But Consort Duan can't die.
Chief Xiao,
I’m under orders to arrest you.
This place is under the jurisdiction of Zhaoding Bureau.
Arresting Chief Xiao...
who gave you the authority to?
I apologize.
Chief Xiao, please cooperate with us.
I’ll go with you.
[Yongze Palace]
Under His Majesty's orders,
from now on,
I, Baozhu, will take care of you.
No matter where Your Highness goes,
I'm not allowed to leave your side.
Don't worry and just stay in the palace.
If there is nothing important,
don’t go around outside.
I heard Chief Xiao went against His Majesty,
and was thrown into prison by His Majesty.
Even his residence was raided.
You blind wenches,
leave right now!
Your Highness.
[Yongze Palace]
His Majesty has ordered that
you are not allowed to leave Yongze Palace.
Your Highness!
You can't go in, Your Highness.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness!
You can't go in, Your Highness.
Leave us.
Bu Yinge? Why are you here?
Didn't you get imprisoned because of
the Prince of Nanyuan?
Well, His Majesty loves me so much that
even if I committed a serious crime,
he still wants to keep me in the palace.
He favors me more and more each day,
and sleeps with me every night.
He sleeps with you every night?
Then I guess I have to congratulate you
for rising up the ranks again.
Your Majesty, Yinlou wishes to see you.
Don't waste your energy.
His Majesty won't see you.
He’s not in Shangqiong Palace.
You can't leave.
What do you want now?
Bu Yinlou,
what's there for you to be proud about?
Who are you to look down on me?
Do you think I want to
live on shamelessly like this?
I ended up like this because of you.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have been married off to West Shu.
I wouldn't have been given to
His Majesty like a plaything
just because I look somewhat similar
to you.
And I wouldn't have ended up losing at the last moment
and having my family torn apart.
Now you ask me what I want?
If you had
married in my place back then,
or died in the imperial mausoleum,
none of this would have happened.
I would still have been
the precious legitimate daughter of the Bu Residence,
and I would still have my father and mother
who dote on me and love me.
I would have had a noble life.
It's all because of you.
Give me back my life!
Bu Yinge.
You don't think you'll be happy
as long as I'm not happy?
Don't be silly.
I was never the one
who hurt you.
Father was the one who gave up on you and used you.
The ones who bullied you and humiliated you
are the Prince of Nanyuan
and Murong Gaogong.
You dare not
confront the real culprits and get even with them,
but instead you're making things difficult for me.
Don't you think
you're a joke?
You're the one who's a joke.
You abandoned His Majesty
just so you could cosy up with a lowly servant?
You chose to be lowly,
and ruined everything.
If you're willing to be
a plaything that is used by others,
then that's your business.
I'm following my own desires
to love the person I want to love,
to go on the path I want to go on,
and do what I want to do.
If we compare with each other,
which one of us is the one choosing to be lowly?
You-
Was this what His Majesty ordered people to do to you
when you were locked in the temporary palace in Weichang?
After he treated you like this,
do you really still believe
he's keeping you around
because he loves you?
He dotes on me, loves me, and can't leave me.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't want to keep me
at the expense of offending everybody.
Bu Yinge, stop being silly.
Even if you keep on giving in to those
who hurt you and insulted you,
you still won't recover your dignity.
You'll only sink deeper and deeper.
and lose everything in the end.
While it's still not too late,
ask to leave the palace now.
Why should I leave the palace?
Are you jealous that I can make a comeback?
I'll be honest with you.
I will be the empress soon.
I will become the most respected
woman in Daye.
Bu Yinge.
You're still dreaming aren't you?
Her Highness is here too.
Bu Yinge, receive the decree.
Summoning Bu Yinge
to the Hall of Imperial Supremacy immediately.
Yes.
Your Highness.
I was just about to
go to Yongze Palace to invite you too.
Please go with us then.
I'll let you see for yourself
if I'm telling the truth.
Bu Yinge is a rebel's concubine!
She can't be the empress!
Please withdraw your order.
Bu Yinge.
Come here.
This bunch of people just don't understand.
I said I would make you the Empress.
They all opposed it.
They're crying and making a scene as if their father died.
What do you think I should do?
I'll heed whatever Your Majesty says.
Then you need to
do your part to contribute.
Perform a dance in the palace,
and show them
the overflowing charms of my future empress,
to see if you're worthy of being
called the mother of the nation.
Yes.
So ridiculous.
How inappropriate!
What is this?
How could this be?
This is ridiculous.
Yes.
Are you kidding me?
How utterly embarrassing!
Indeed.
This...
I've never heard
such a ridiculous thing.
Brilliant!
Your Majesty.
The Hall of Imperial Supremacy is where matters of the state are discussed.
How can you let a witch behave immorally?
Your Majesty!
Have you gone mad?
Your Majesty.
T- This is really...
rather inappropriate.
Come.
You danced so well.
The Empress Dowager has arrived!
Greetings, Mother.
Arrest this witch!
Your Majesty.
It's my fault for
alarming the Empress Dowager.
I'm not against
you wanting to appoint an empress.
But the Empress is the mother of the nation,
and a role model for all the women of the land.
How could you choose her of all people?
A wicked, impure woman
who even committed treason.
It's already absurd to allow you to keep her in the palace.
And you still want to appoint her as Empress?
Out of all of the
many virtuous and respectable ladies in the harem,
do none of them compare to her?
I dare not accept these words of yours, Mother.
It was unfilial of me,
and I made you upset.
But you are absolutely right, Mother.
All of my concubines in the harem,
as long as they can enter the palace,
they must all be good candidates who are
virtuous and respectable.
So in your opinion,
the Empress should be
chosen from these people?
That's right.
Aside from Bu Yinge,
which one of them isn't a good candidate?
Do all the ministers
think so too?
Your Majesty, we agree.
Fine.
Then I...
Then I'll do
as you wish.
Sun Taiqing.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Relay my order.
Relaying His Majesty's order.
I have quested after the rules of the world,
and a successful man needs a woman behind him.
Consort Duan of Yongze Palace
is filial and modest;
virtuous and honorable;
refined and dutiful.
She is befitting of the position of Empress.
By the grace of the Empress Dowager,
With this decree and seal,
I hereby appoint you as Empress.
How can you treat
appointing an empress like child's play!
Child's play?
Mother, everything you just said,
which part of it did I not follow?
Even so, it cannot be her!
I am undeserving,
and dare not accept Your Majesty's grace.
I was originally part of the former Emperor's harem,
and only had the chance to return to the palace
after receiving Your Majesty's grace.
I am already greatly favored.
If I am appointed Empress now,
I will become a sinner for generations to come,
and I will be too ashamed to face my ancestors after I die.
I implore Your Majesty to choose another candidate.
I've given the decree.
Since time immemorial,
the words of the Emperor are absolute.
Besides, Mother has given her word,
and all the ministers agreed to it.
You want me to withdraw my order?
Thank me for my grace,
my Empress.
I...
thank Your Majesty for your grace.
Escort Consort Duan to Fengyi Palace at once.
Ask the Imperial Astronomical Bureau to pick an auspicious date
to hold the coronation ceremony.
First, he acted all absurd
and used Bu Yinge as a cover.
Then, he set up a decoy
and shut everyone up.
He planned this all in advance.
No matter how unsuitable I am to be Empress,
I have no choice now.
This is not him favoring me.
This is revenge.
He wants to trap me for good
in the Imperial City.
Your Majesty, slow down.
Your Majesty.
What you said earlier in the court
is not true, right?
How dare a witch guilty of treason like you
come to me begging for dignity?
The position of Empress is one of such honor.
Even if I really give it to you,
do you dare to take it?
Do you deserve it?
I was wrong.
I beg Your Majesty
to spare my life for the sake of
our previous relationship with each other.
Your Majesty, don't you like
this face of mine?
I will destroy this face of yours right now!
Your Majesty!
This lowly wench deserves to die.
You're the almighty Emperor.
She's not worth getting blood on your hands.
Leave it to me.
I'll handle it for you.
You're right.
She doesn't deserve me getting blood on my hands.
But I don't
want her to
die comfortably either.
I want her to live in pain.
How about this?
Banish her to the Laundry Bureau, and make sure
she can never get out for the rest of her life.
Yes, take her away quickly.
Bu Yinlou was right.
I'm such a joke.
You, Father, and Yuwen Liangshi!
You all used me
and trampled all over on me!
You all ruined me!
Murong Gaogong!
You will be punished!
My sister won't be as stupid as me,
she'll make sure you suffer!
What else can she do
to make me suffer?
Let's go.
Come with me to see my new Empress.
Your Majesty, be careful.
Be careful, Your Majesty.
Those who stand in my way
must be kicked out.
Your Highness, congratulations on being appointed Empress
[Fengyi Palace]
and becoming the mother of the nation.
Shut up.
How unlucky.
Yinlou.
I miss you.
I'm here to see you.
Come on.
I heard that you like pear blossoms,
and that Chief Xiao's residence has beautiful pear trees,
which still thrive
even after they've been moved.
I believe
they'll thrive too after being moved here.
Trees are like people.
They can adapt to some places,
but not to others.
You know that.
You just don't want to let it live.
Yinlou.
Why are you so hard to please?
I've already banished
your most hated Bu Yinge
to the Laundry Bureau.
She has already become the lowest
of the low in the Imperial City.
And you will soon become
the most respected woman in the land.
Are you happy?
You were once all intimate with her too.
How could you have the heart to do that?
Look.
You always misunderstand me.
I've said it hundreds of times.
The only one I love is you.
You are also my only Empress.
Once you stand at the top,
naturally everyone in the Imperial City will have their eyes on you,
and everyone in Great Ye
will help me trap you.
And you will be trapped in this position
as the Empress,
forever lonely.
Since you hurt me,
it's only fair that you share the pain
with me.
Oh right.
You must personally tell
this great news to the person
you care about the most.
Get changed.
Do you hear that?
Someone has been waiting for you for ages.
No!
Xiao Duo!
Don't hurt him.
Zhuo Ying.
I heard that
the 72 tortures of Zhaoding Bureau
are mostly created
by you, Chief Xiao.
I’ll let you try all of them
one by one then.
How's that?
I was wrong.
I didn't know better, and my sins are unforgivable.
I beg you to spare him.
Zhuo Ying, get up.
Get up.
Are you...
begging me right now?
For what?
You're begging me to give him something good,
aren't you?
No!
No.
Get out of the way.
Move!
Use whatever method of torture
you want on me.
I know I was in the wrong.
I'm the one that likes him,
I'm the one that seduced him.
If you want to vent your anger,
I'll bear it on his behalf.
What should we do then?
It's fine, it's fine.
There are rules for everything.
How about this? With every plea from you,
and with every extra tear you shed for him.
I,
shall administer one more
punishment on him,
until he becomes a piece of
unrecognizable flesh.
No!
Don't hurt him.
Please don't hurt him.
I beg you.
Murong Gaogong.
If you're unhappy, come at me.
Let her go.
Why should I let her go?
She is my woman.
And very soon,
she will be the Empress,
and my wife.
I still have plenty of
love and care
♫ Wind sweeps through the bottom of my heart ♫
that awaits her enjoyment.
Take your time.
♫ Blowing ripples into our past ♫
One by one.
The whole world will see her and I
♫ Sighing and lamenting ♫
♫ We can't escape parting ♫
as a loving couple that will be celebrated through the ages.
♫ How can ripples form in a mirror ♫
A hundred years later,
♫ The wind cannot dispel my loneliness ♫
in my grave,
there will also be a spot for you.
You must...
♫ But the sorrows and joys of this world ♫
♫ Look upon desolation and recklessness ♫
You must...
♫ Not knowing when I can return ♫
look after me,
for generations and years to come.
♫ How can we be calculating in this ephemeral world ♫
♫ The wind has risen in the smoke and rain ♫
Murong Gaogong.
Let her go!
♫ Even if the road ahead is rough ♫
♫ The wind has risen and can hardly continue ♫
♫ I'll pledge my life to you ♫
Princess!
[Shangqiong Palace]
Princess, you can't go in.
You can't go in!
Brother,
Xiao Duo and Bu Yinlou are unforgivable.
We can't appease them
and let them stay in the Imperial City.
We should deprive their positions,
confiscate their property and expel them from the palace.
Sun Taiqing, you may leave first.
Yes.
Are you questioning me
or pleading for them?
I haven't blamed you yet.
You are already here
to play a trick on me.
Wan Wan.
You and I are siblings
who grew up relying on each other.
Indeed.
After that, in order to protect yourself,
you stayed close to the Empress Dowager
and went to Tanxi Temple,
leaving me alone in the palace
to be humiliated.
But I
have never blamed you.
Because you're my only sister.
My only family
and the only person I trust.
Shouldn't you
be wholehearted to me?
You knew
they had an affair.
But you helped them to deceive me.
How could you betray
your only family?
I want to know
the true colors of your heart.
When I first knew
about this,
I wanted to tell you.
But, Brother,
I couldn't say it.
Why?
Because I envy Yinlou.
Bu Yinlou is disloyal and unfaithful.
You're the Princess Hede.
Why do you envy her?
I envy her because she doesn't
take her fate lying down.
She tries her best to protect
her innocence in her bones.
Everyone in the Imperial City
has a title
and identity.
They own luxurious clothing
but they are
barely living.
Only Yinlou
is always herself.
Brother,
please let her go.
Nonsense!
I lied to you.
I'm sorry.
Every day, I ask myself
whether I was right or wrong.
Now I've figured it out.
I think I understand Yinlou now.
You keep saying that you like her,
but she has things that she is
willing and unwilling to do,
and her own likes and dislikes.
Have you ever cared about that?
Just because of
your wishful thinking,
you forced her with your power.
In your eyes,
is she still a human being?
Do you really like her?
I am the Emperor.
If I want a woman,
why would I bother to care so much?
Brother.
How did you become like this?
We used to be tortured
by power.
Our mother died because of that.
Now you have
the supreme power,
yet you trampled on others.
You treat a woman
as if she is your belonging and take this for granted.
Brother,
you have become
the person we hated the most.
You betrayed us.
Times have changed.
You're the one who doesn't know
your place.
You betrayed me for other people.
As your brother,
I have to take the responsibility
to educate you.
I want you to know,
in this world,
power is the only truth.
Brother.
The Yuwen family
has lost their power and influence.
They can only kneel on the ground
and bear my humiliation.
Please don't. Brother.
Wan Wan.
You are an adult.
Why are you still
being childish?
You're too greedy.
You begged me to spare Xiao Duo and Yinlou.
Now you beg me to let him go.
You can only choose either one.
Make a choice.
Wan Wan.
-Wan Wan. -Don't you care?
Leave me alone.
Please don't. Brother.
I will make a choice.
Brother,
please spare Yuwen Liangxu.
Love is selfish.
Wan Wan, look.
Even you can't do it yourself.
How can you ask me
to be magnanimous?
But I promise
to fulfill your request.
From now on,
please remember who you are.
Don't do anything
to let me down again.
Princess Hede.
Your sister
obeys.
Liangxu.
I have bribed
the guards here.
You leave immediately.
Go as far as you can.
Come with me.
When I first came to the capital,
I found everything newfangled and interesting.
After staying here for a long time,
I realize the people here
have ugly and horrible desires.
My brother was buried here.
I don't want to lose you too.
I don't care about the grudges anymore.
I just want us to be fine.
Let's go.
I am the Princess.
I can't leave my brother behind.
Does he still regard you as his sister?
He's gone crazy.
If you stay here,
you'll be abused by him.
Wan Wan,
come with me.
Follow me to West Shu,
back to my home.
From now on,
let's just be an ordinary couple.
We can live freely.
You don't have to worry about
the tricky world in the Imperial City anymore.
OK?
OK.
I'll go with you.
We fell into their trap. Quickly leave!
Let's go together.
Don't be so dramatic.
Go quickly!
Who dares to go there
will be the first to be sacrificed for my sword.
Wan Wan, you lied to me again.
Brother.
Are you testing me?
If not,
how would I know
you would betray me?
You all
either want to leave me
or beg me to spare others.
I really hate it.
Tell me.
How should I punish you?
I have
a good suggestion.
Since you like him so much,
I'll invite him back
and cut off his arms and legs
and put them in a jar.
Let him be with you forever.
Sun Taiqing.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Pass on my decree.
Arrest Yuwen Liangxu.
Don't care if he's dead or alive.
Yes.
Let's go.
His Majesty gave an order.
It has been chaotic outside recently.
He wants you to move here
so that you won't be disturbed by irrelevant people.
[Hill Outside the Imperial City]
Go!
Fool.
[Fengyi Palace]
You have a home.
I'll take you home.
Your Highness, you're awake.
I want to go home.
What are you talking about?
The Imperial City is your home.
How's Zhaoding Bureau lately?
Nothing unusual has happened.
Zhaoding Bureau has been with Xiao Duo for many years.
They must only follow Xiao Duo,
not the Emperor.
I took Xiao Duo down.
How could they sit still?
What?
Do they think I can't touch them?
Pass my order.
Zhaoding Bureau colluded with
Yuwen Liangxu from West Shu
and attempted to rebel.
From now on, disband Zhaoding Bureau.
Leave no one alive.
But Your Majesty,
Chief Xiao and Zhaoding Bureau
have contributed a lot to pacifying the rebellion.
What?
Now even you dare to disobey me?
I dare not.
If it weren't for Consort Jing,
I would have been dead long ago.
Your Majesty is
the child of Consort Jing.
Your Majesty's will
is my will.
I will obey your orders.
Then what are you waiting for?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Where is the herbal soup?
Your Majesty, you shouldn't drink too much of
potent herbal soups like these
made from deer and tiger penises.
Shut up.
Serve me another bowl. Hurry.