I think this is fine.
Let’s just go with this.
Let’s boldly sing along this time.
Is that okay?
We didn’t sing earlier.
Let’s listen and sing along with him.
No problem, right?
Let him melt into colorful ice cream.
We’re not walking Roman Avenue today.
Destiny has drifted off course.
Love and joy are the little lucks on the journey.
All fell into the coffee cup.
The swirling wine glass is my true happiness.
This line is mine.
Let’s focus on C1, this part is super interesting.
The folds of a fun life hide secrets.
The pitch went so high.
Love and joy gone astray are the little luck on the way.
Clouds fell into the coffee cup.
Even the swirling wine glasses are truly mine.
Of.
The world is interesting.
Life hides secrets.
The world is so interesting.
Secrets are hidden in the world’s lilies.
This world is super interesting.
Like wanting to bungee jump at the world’s end.
The world is so interesting.
Want to be in your world.
Just go with the feeling.
Just feel it.
This really can’t be pushed.
Right hand, left leg, right?
Left hand, right leg.
Is there really a better way?
Who are you struggling for?
Only a phone number is left.
Never willing to give in.
I heard you once fell in love.
Once couldn’t help yourself either.
Bro.
You do it once.
Sure.
Any problem?
No.
Separate.
Now you have to win back with true love.
Love isn’t something you can buy.
You can’t buy it just because you want to.
Let go.
Let them understand.
Love that lets go.
Go around.
See a flower on your body.
Makes me want to write for you every day.
A love song.
A romantic chorus.
Gently echoing along.
It’s also the choice of the determined.
Why does everything feel like tears?
Tears.
What did my big bro say?
Flowers.
Two six.
Those days are gone.
Go dig for shells.
Capture the northern suburbs alive.
Sister.
Beautiful sister.
Sister, sis.
Red bud sister.
Lovely sister.
Sister.
Beauty in my heart.
Dad.
I’ll show a bit more.
Change a bit so I can really see.
By the novel’s grace, I’ll stay with you for countless days.
Let me willingly love you.
Yuning.
Liu Yuning.
I want to ask if you’ve ever lost.
I haven’t lost in this show.
Let's piece together a story with countless short videos like this.
One day, I caught a glimpse of you.
This is your unexpected journey together.
Let's film it line by line.
It's not simple at all.
If it were simple, I'd know what to shoot next.
Film your hand.
He gave an example.
If I were the cameraman,
I'd film his hand.
Start with the hand.
A hand holding him.
Holding your hand.
Maybe looking at your face.
Hold hands.
Then follow the hand to film him turning to look at you.
A glance back.
A smile.
You travel together.
Then do it in slow motion.
It's fine.
I'll show up later.
Next, a hand-holding shot.
Hand-holding starts here.
Let's try one take, start with three, then move forward.
Look at the camera.
Oh no.
I'm speechless.
From your hand.
Start from your hand?
Once I grab the hand, I film him.
Alright, let's go.
Ready, one, two, three.
Look up at the camera.
Don't run here.
Run forward.
I'm speechless.
The camera catches me first.
Look at me first.
Then pull back.
Then the two of them appear.
Then you put your hand on.
My hand goes like this, then I speak.
Right.
It's just lip-syncing, right.
So we want something super fun with the camera.
Da di da di da.
That's what I mean.
Just like this.
Wave hello upwards.
Then look like this.
Film this first.
You're at this height.
Then pull out.
The three of us appear.
Then continue to the right side.
So let's vote out two or three people we don't trust.
Let him stand in the middle.
Let him block.
But he can't block it.
Let this break, okay?
We lost this round.
Right?
But we have to vote now, right?
Any doubts left?
This round.
Because I saw everything.
I saw you doing something weird in the back.
I want to ask you.
How did you walk?
Can you jump in like that?
You have to walk like this.
The easiest way is
Let these two bros go in front.
Because the two of them won't
They can.
They can walk normally.
They won't have any of that tripping stuff.
It's hard for two people to trip each other.
Yeah, we can't trip each other.
Bro.
I still want to play a game with you.
If it's not me.
Would you play if you lived in Room 8?
I'm already in Room 8.
I'm not inside with him.
How do I pull from inside?
I pull like this.
Yeah, think about it.
If it breaks here, maybe someone over there is pulling hard.
Your arm length isn't the same as ours.
Like this, bro.
Herniated disc.
How come I...
Why am I the most suspicious?
I just want a reason.
Today I can float.
Because you're too handsome.
Alright?
Just admit it.
This one I can admit.
Bro