Next, we'll do an activity.
We've prepared some classic movie scenes.
Everyone will take the lines from them
and turn them into Shaanxi dialect.
Okay.
Let's watch the clip first.
This is Titanic.
The one with the raised glass.
Rose
So cool.
That legendary glance back then.
Mouth opens, dodges.
Liu Yuning, you play Rose.
You, just like that.
There aren't any lines.
How do you act this out?
There's no Xi'an dialect here.
Where's the Xi'an dialect?
Do we even need lines for this?
We gave you one line.
Rose, give me your hand.
No, that's not right.
Rose
Give me your mouth.
This one needs Naiwen to act.
Naiwen has to do this.
This has to be Naiwen's.
Quick, add that special effect for me.
The effect where the mouth disappears.
I don't want this mouth.
I don't want it.
So who plays Jack?
How do we act that?
Wait, Ning will do one.
Ning, do that one.
Give us your magnetic voice.
Go ahead.
I want to hear it.
I want to hear the Suzhou version.
Rose
Give me your hand.
Bro, just give it to her.
Or not.
It's like I want to give it
but also feel gross about it.
This is just too...
I feel uncomfortable after hearing that.
Lin Yi
Lin Yi, you do one.
Make it deeper.
Do a Northeast China version.
Just to compare with the bossy type.
Sure.
Rose
Give me your hand.
That was too timid.
Rose
Roast, give me your hand.
Give me your hand.
Roast
Just kidding.
It's just Rose.
Fuzhou dialect
Rose
Give me your hand.
Are you sure that's Chinese?
Which word means "hand"?
It means "hand."
Tianjin dialect
Do a Tianjin version.
Rose
Give me your hand.
Right?
What are you doing?
Give me your hand.
It should be "sister."
Sister, right.
Sister
Sister, where's your hand?
Give me your hand.
Darn it, Xingxu can't show off now.
I'm the same as him.
They're both from Shenyang.
They're the same.
Rose, give me your hand.
What about Wuhan?
Suan Niao, Suan Niao
Suan Niao, just don't give it.
Suan Niao
Rose, give me your hand.
They're all a bit different.
Let's do Harbin Avenue's version.
That's the same.
Harbin Mandarin
This really is Mandarin.
We're so standard in Harbin.
Standard Mandarin.
We can't join in on this one.
Harbin dialect
Do a bossy Mandarin version.
Just the normal kind, bro.
Rose
Please give me your hand.
Announcer's tone
Harbin isn't like that.
Rose, I want to see Honglei and...
Ordering food, you're here.
How do you act this out?
Cheating the angle.
You want to...
Then I...
You be Rose.
Okay, I'll be Rose.
You two go ahead, or do one.
I'm getting a little feeling.
Rose
Give me your hand.
A hug will do.
Come on, give me a hug.
Hug me, quick.
Hug.
Didi.
I just like it.
Didi, what's up with you?
What's up with me?
What's up, really?
I'm losing it.
How do you say "Whatcha up to?"
Say it in Xi'an dialect.
Whatcha up to?
Who's with me?
You pick yourself.
He-ge.
Come on, He-ge.
Then He-ge it is.
Let's go.
HER LADYSHIP HAS ARRIVED!
Everybody, clear the way!
Clear the way!
You're Jack, bro.
I don't know.
I don't know which one I am.
You turn around.
I turn around.
Then you're Jack.
Mighty fine!
Give me your hand.
Silly.
You do one.
Your turn.
You just have to play abstract.
You play abstract with him.
You startled me.
You gotta see how fine he is.
Give me your hand.
This round is all about abstract.
Let's go, have a drink.
Your cheeks are still a bit warm.
Love to watch, act more.
Your turn, hurry up.
Come on.
You love watching, right?
Love watching you act.
Do something awesome, go on.
Come on, Junjun.
You two switch back and forth, later.
Give your hand to each other.
What's that about?
Come.
Junjun.
Get yourself mentally ready.
As an actor, you need ethics.
What did you see when you turned?
Everything.
You gotta act out that feeling.
Block it out.
Yeah, block it.
Block.
Block me.
Let's go.
Rose.
Give me your hand.
I'll help you.
Want to add a scene.
Why is it so tight?
I'll help you.
Let's pull together.
Quick.
Can't get it off.
Give me your hand.
This is a robbery!
How about you do it, give it to me.
Okay.
That Rose just now was really...
Give me your hand.
Got anxious, you know?
Come on.
You little Rose.
Give me your hand.
Close your eyes.
Bro.
Give me my ring back.
What are you doing?
Whatcha up to?
You little Rose.
Close your eyes, you didn't get it, huh?
I heard "BA" instead.
Security.
Honglei-ge and Wen, do one.
I'll do one with Wen.
Wen, do one.
Honglei-ge.
Let's do a proper one.
There should be a camera here.
Follow from behind.
Then spin around.
Honglei-ge, give me your phone.
I'll film a clip for you.
I'll take it.
Take Didi's.
I'll film a clip for you.
You start subjective.
Of course.
Subjective turns to two people.
Right.
Then you have to pass theirs.
Us.
Right.
You're the last one, right?
A big show.
Block him first.
Director Liu.
Continued from Spain.
Everyone, get into character.
Get into character.
Cue the music.
Three, two, one, go.
Honglei-ge, you're up.
Go in.
Rose.
Give me your hand.
Give it to him.
Thank you, everyone.
Perfect.
This year we'll use this scene
to submit for awards.
Enter the competition.
Compete.
The title is "Give Me Your Hand".
"Give Me Your Hand"
"Give Him Your Hand"
Next, we'll fully showcase
everyone's learning results.
So, the task is
we'll provide some film scenes.
The first member
will learn the Shaanxi dialect lines.
Others must wear noise-canceling headphones.
The last member
just needs to repeat
over half the dialect lines.
That's a win.
Come on, bro.
You go first.
You start the relay.
Come on.
Ning bro.
You're second.
I'm second.
I'm second, but I'm not reliable.
I'm not reliable either.
The one with good memory is third.
My memory's not bad.
Then you go up front.
I'll go up front.
Okay, you come here.
I'll sit in the middle, right here.
So, is the last one reliable?
He's fine.
He can make up for it.
Who's last?
The last one needs to summarize.
I'll sit here.
Let Didi be last.
Didi, you're last.
You'll be fine as the last.
Alright, good.
Darn it, we're unstoppable.
Victory is ours.
Everyone, focus.
Right.
To win a girl's heart,
you must rely on your gaze.
Look at me.
Sexy or not?
Hahaha.
Not sexy, just funny.
How is that possible?
Look more closely.
Hahahahaha.
Not helping you anymore.
Come on, bro.
Let's teach you the Xi'an dialect version.
To win a girl's heart,
you must rely on your gaze.
Look at me, sexy or not?
Hahaha.
Not sexy, just funny.
How could that be?
Look a bit closer.
Hahahahaha.
Not helping you.
That's really how it is.
To win a girl's heart,
you must rely on your gaze.
Look at me.
Sexy or not?
Hahaha.
Not sexy, just funny.
Right?
Yeah.
Then, next.
How could that be?
Look a bit closer.
Hahahahaha.
Not helping you.
That's what we said.
Yeah.
Okay, time's up.
Bro, only one minute.
Once you're ready,
just tap Yun Ning.
Then we'll start timing.
No glasses for this.
That's tough.
I think it's risky.
A bit risky.
It's fine.
We need to deliver on time.
Accurate, let's go.
Three, two, one, go.
To win a girl's heart,
you've got to use your eyes.
Look at me.
Sexy or not?
Got it. Come on.
Then you say,
Heh heh heh.
Not sexy, just funny.
It's funny.
How's that possible?
Look closer.
Heh heh heh heh heh.
Not helping you.
Not helping anymore.
Okay, time's up.
Okay, I know.
That's from "East Meets West," right?
The one with Tony Leung and Jacky Cheung.
This one's awesome.
Come on.
Let's start. Come on.
Okay, let's begin.
To win a girl's heart,
you need your eyes.
Sexy or not?
Then the other person...
Ha ha ha.
Not sexy, just funny.
To win a girl's heart,
you need your eyes.
Sexy or not?
East Meets West.
How could that be?
Look carefully.
Sexy or not?
Looks like two fat sausages
hanging on your face.
Not teaching you anymore.
That's it.
East Meets West.
Come on.
Under Xi'an's city wall,
is Xi'an's train.
Look at me.
He might not have seen it.
Start.
If you want to win a girl's
heart,
you need a sexy look.
Look at me.
Second person.
There are two people.
Ha ha ha.
Is this the start?
It's started.
First person.
Thirty seconds left.
If you want to win a girl's heart,
you need a sexy look.
To tempt you.
Look at me.
Second person.
Ha ha ha.
Why are you laughing?
Sexy or not?
Second person.
Not sexy.
It's funny.
Really not sexy.
Nine.
Eight.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Seven.
Remember.
Not teaching you.
Wait, I haven't memorized it.
Again.
If you want to win a girl's heart,
you need to be sexy.
Okay, time's up.
Last one.
Not teaching anymore, that's it.
It's over, that's it.
It's actually pretty short.
Let me think.
Not teaching.
See if anyone in the back can recover it.
He needs to know this.
If he knows, it's easy.
I think...
I think He can do it.
Pretty much.
He can make up for it.
He must've seen it.
Definitely seen it.
Like this.
If you want to win a girl's heart,
you need to look at me with tempting eyes.
Second person.
This is the first person.
What did the second person say?
Ha ha, don't forget.
Just keep laughing.
Laugh more.
Why are you laughing?
Sexy or not?
Tempting or not?
Not sexy.
Not tempting.
Was there something else?
I'm not teaching you anymore.
Ten seconds left.
If you want to win a girl's heart,
you need to give me a sexy look.
Hahaha.
Why are you laughing?
Sexy or not?
Not sexy, not tempting.
I'm done teaching you.
Okay, time's up.
Come on.
That's enough.
Actually, that's enough.
You want to win a girl's heart,
then you have to give me a sexy look.
"East Meets West"
Hahaha.
Sexy or not?
So, is it sexy or not?
Not sexy.
Looks like two sausages hanging from your mouth.
Well, I have no idea then.
Because they didn't pass it to me.
Go on.
Uh, what was it...
It's about the heart.
You need to give me a sexy look.
Sexy or not?
Not sexy.
Tempting or not?
Tempting or not? Maybe a little.
Right, keep going.
So, not tempting, right?
I'm not teaching you anymore.
That's it.
I've seen this part.
The part with Tony Leung and Jacky Cheung.
Won.
Okay.
Two people.
I'll teach you.
That's it.
Is this the phrase?
Yeah.
How do you win a girl's heart?
A girl's heart.
Look into my eyes.
Then turn around.
Turn your head.
How do you win a girl's heart?
Look into my eyes. Sexy or not?
Turn around, turn your head, turn.
Sexy or not?
I turn, you laugh.
Wait a sec.
Act it out one by one.
Twenty-five seconds left.
Okay, just remember the lines.
How do you win a girl's heart?
Look into my eyes.
Sexy or not?
Tempting or not?
Over there.
How many laughs?
Keep laughing.
Laugh a hundred times.
Right.
Forget it, I'm not teaching you.
Okay.
How do you win a girl's heart?
Look into my eyes.
Sexy or not?
Tempting or not?
Laugh a hundred times.
Then the other person laughs.
That's not respecting him.
Then he won't teach you.
Won't teach you.
That's it.
Yeah.
Alright, come on.
Come on.
Hurry.
Bro, hurry.
How?
Calm down.
The phrase.
How do you win a girl's heart?
Look into my eyes.
Sexy—
Sexy or not?
Tempting or not?
Laugh a hundred times, later.
Let the last person laugh a hundred times.
A hundred times.
We don't need to laugh.
Laugh a hundred times.
Then...
What was the phrase?
Yeah.
It's just...
His last part...
How do you win a girl's heart?
Look into my eyes.
Sexy or not? Tempting or not?
Laugh a hundred times.
Let the girl laugh a hundred times.
And then, just...
I forgot the last four words.
Why don't you improvise?
That's too abstract.
Too abstract.
It's fine, the last four words don't matter.
You've seen this.
The last four words don't matter.
They said it is...
Seen it.
Think about it.
Definitely seen it.
Am I handsome?
Forget it, you say it.
That line is just for him.
Forget it.
Not giving it.
He Ge knows.
I know which one.
But I don't remember the phrase.
I can think of it.
But I don't really remember the phrase.
Say the meaning.
Like, the specific action.
I'll teach you how to win
a girl's heart.
I'll teach you.
How to win a girl's heart.
Look at my lips.
Irresistible or not?
Handsome or not?
Laugh a hundred times later.
Laugh a hundred times.
About thirty times should be enough.
No problem.
Look at me.
Ain't I mighty handsome?
Mighty handsome.
Mighty fine!
Can you do it again?
Look at my lips. Sexy or not?
Handsome or not?
Pretty or not?
Irresistible or not?
Ha ha ha.
Yeah, just like that.
Yeah, that's it.
Alright, laugh a hundred times.
Anything else?
No problem.
No.
That's enough, we can win this round.
That's enough.
Enough, definitely enough.
Ain't I really handsome?
Stuff like that.
I'll teach you.
How to win a girl's heart.
Check out my lips.
Sexy or not?
Handsome or not?
Irresistible or not?
Ha ha ha.
This is like when I pad my essays.
Hahaha.
Nice.
That's enough.
A hundred is plenty.
This is just essay padding.
It's "East Meets West," right?
Yeah.
"East Meets West."
Good thing you all watched it.
Because it came from Brother Honglei.
It wasn't "hahaha."
Brother Honglei passed on "hehehe."
Hehehe.
Almost.
Yeah.
Out of forty-eight words total,
you got
twenty-five right.
Good.
Nice.
Alright, congrats everyone!