Why are you staring at me like that?
Don’t think you can—
You can like me.
Hmm.
What’s that called again?
That waiter said about me—
Don’t think I don’t know what you’re thinking.
How could a pheasant pair with a phoenix? Even thinking about it is wrong.
Oh.
That’s right.
Which movie is this?
It’s East Meets West.
Yeah, East Meets West.
That one.
He could guess it’s East Meets West.
That’s already impressive.
You keep staring at me.
Don’t fall for me.
Even though I’m approachable,
and naturally beautiful,
and easygoing,
Where’s a real phoenix with a true heart?
If you let me do this part,
I can recite it word for word.
Go ahead.
Let me do it.
What are you doing?
Staring at me.
Though I’m naturally beautiful,
and easygoing,
but how could a pheasant ever fly with a phoenix?
Me—
You, what about you?
You’re just a mere waiter.
Why would I even notice you?
Don’t—
Don’t think I don’t know what you’re thinking.
You think just because I’m staying here,
you have a chance?
Even thinking about it is a sin.
This is—
That’s right.
I have both beauty and brains.
The embodiment of heroism and chivalry.
Tang Bohu.
You know who now, right?
Qiu Xiang.
That’s right.
Second line.
Right, isn’t it?
Third line, more—
Just brushing you off.
Yeah, that’s me.
Thanks.
Yeah, that’s it.
It’s basically Mandarin, right?
Me and you—
I’m not the same age as you.
Not the same, just different.
Ah.
Why bother?
Why use knives and guns?
Knives and guns.
Hmm.
Are you begging me?
Begging me?
You’re—
Trying to control me?
Is there a difference?
Yes.
Sky.
Of.
Ah.
I can't kill you this year.
Today, I killed your
son.
I killed your son.
Son.
Right?
When you just asked if I speak Cantonese,
Now let me ask you back,
Do you speak Cantonese?
It's fine.
No problem.
Describe it properly.
It's just a name plus an action.
Right?
How many characters?
12345677 characters.
OK.
Are the first three characters a name?
The first 123455 are names.
Left hand, left hand, right hand, right hand, combine together.
Put it down.
Down, down.
Stop your leg.
Right leg, yes.
Stand up straight.
No, no, no, no.
Stand, stand.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
The wind is coming.
Who are you?
There's wind.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
There's wind.
What's this for?
Butt.
Stick your butt out.
Yes.
Spasming.
Mermaid.
Are you messing with me?
You're messing with me.
Yes.
The last two.
Right hand.
Left hand.
Alright.
Hey.
Make a fist.
Punch forward.
Boxer.
Open.
Hold.
OK.
67344 sports troublemaker.
Olympic.
Machine.
1234567
12345, someone's left hand, right hand, what, reach out, hands, hands
Put your hands together
What are you putting together?
Put them together
Palms facing up
Palms facing down
Down, keep going down, down, down
Right leg
Legs
Oh no
Stretch it out, stretch it out
This, oh no
This is getting abstract
Not flying
Blowing wind
Wind, wind, wind
There's wind
Rukawa Kaede
Whose is this?
That's weird
Who is this?
Do you know?
I don't know either
You don't know the right move either
Are you messing with me?
He doesn't know
No no no
You don't know?
Having "wind" is correct, right?
There's the word "wind"
Right
There's wind
OK
Six, seven
Hands
Spread out
Spread out, then clench
Mechanical
Mechanical six, seven, fencing
Right
And before that, it's three, four, three, five
Let me try to imitate it
Let's see if he can guess it, okay?
Like this
Everyone, think about it
There's wind, right?
There's the word "wind," wind blowing
Alright
Time's up
Reveal
Please say the correct answer
This one is hard
Actually, you did it pretty close
But you missed the main idea
It's already that person
Wrong
The main idea is similar to this move
Who does it look like?
It already is
Right
It's exactly the same
Come on
Brother He
Please say answer three
And blowing wind
Blowing wind
There's wind
Marilyn Monroe
Me
I couldn't remember