The task for swapping roles is called
Dance
Dance is my weakest skill.
Everyone dances to the music.
After getting the prompt,
use dance moves to describe the prompt.
Everyone at the table
can join in guessing and answering.
The first team to guess right gets a point.
The losing team becomes the new challenge givers.
Let’s try a round first.
Sun Honglei, show us your moves!
How many words?
Four words.
Eagle
Eagle catches chicks.
Dragon and lion dance.
Correct!
Yes.
Impressive!
Amazing, Didi!
Next prompt.
Knock out with one punch.
How many words?
Are they all four words?
Five words.
Punch you once.
An enemy in the past may be a friend in the future.
Say the number of words first.
Four words, okay.
Cut ties completely.
Bullfight.
How many words? Four words.
Full of bullish energy.
Strike the ox over the mountain.
So impressive!
No.
Why are all the answers from the other team?
An enemy in the past may be a friend in the future.
Strike the ox over the mountain.
No.
I won a round!
No, you do that even when they get it right.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Start dancing!
Nice.
They really dance better than us.
Energetic!
Okay, give the prompt.
Alright, ready.
How many words?
Four words.
Bro.
Sun Honglei eating.
Bao, security captain.
No, the first two words are right.
Security.
What’s the last part?
Security what?
Security patrol.
Correct.
Who said it?
He did.
Shidi.
This really isn’t my strength.
Don’t get too excited.
Okay.
Just a bit.
Calm down a little.
Next one.
Go, Didi.
Jump up!
Three words.
Straw battle.
Straw king.
How do you guess this?
Five words.
Tiger.
A fox borrowing the tiger’s might.
Eyeing like a tiger.
Tiger roars, dragon sings.
Colosseum, Roman Colosseum
Correct.
What?
Roman Colosseum.
Five characters.
How do you guess five characters from four?
At the beginning,
A fox borrowing the tiger’s might, eyeing like a tiger.
Tiger roars, dragon sings.
How many characters now?
Four characters.
Tarzan.
He goes first.
He said it first.
Then let’s do it this way.
Lead dancer.
Yes, just be cute.
Go dance with them.
Don’t fall for it.
Three characters.
Tai Chi.
It’s this song.
Five characters.
Stewed Chicken with Mushrooms.
The five characters are...
No idea.
How do we do this?
How do you guess this?
Five characters.
Fly.
I want to fly higher.
The last two characters are...
The last two characters.
Swan Lake.
Eagle.
How do you act this out?
You fly.
Titanic.
The first two characters.
Fishing.
Correct.
The first two characters are fishing.
Definitely not.
He’s just acting randomly, don’t dance.
Don’t look, he’s misleading us.
Can’t see.
This is a song title, right?
You quietly covered my eyes.
Quietly cover your eyes.
Quietly cover my eyes.
Cover his eyes.
Quietly cover.
Cover you.
Pass.
Passed, pass.
What?
Invisible Wings.
How do you act invisible?
I don’t think so.
It’s not our problem.
I don’t get them.
Invisible Wings means the wings are invisible.
It’s not that you’re blind.
Act invisible.
I’ll do it.
Like this.
Come.
Look.
The wings are gone.
Can you guess this?
Can’t guess it.
Seems kind of right.
Invisible is hard to act out.
Everything we ate and drank today
was produced right here in this estate.
Really nice.
So delicious.
Amazing.
After tasting here,
we’ll invite our professor
to say a few words.
Alright, thank you.
Okay, everyone.
Dear teachers,
We’ve arrived at
a very beautiful
Italian town.
Right next to Naples.
Behind us now
the background is
the Bay of Naples.
And right next is the Mediterranean Sea.
In the distance, there's Mount Vesuvius.
Back in the year 79 AD,
it buried Pompeii, Rome's second largest ancient city.
The whole city was engulfed.
Sorrento.
It's also called Sorrento.
Facing Mount Vesuvius,
you realize how small life is.
Nature's power is truly fierce.
It can instantly
swallow an entire civilized city.
Everything gets consumed.
So often Italians feel
they should enjoy the moment.
They want to enjoy this sea.
So I think
this is what Sorrento
gives us—a sense of strength.
So we should stay here
and enjoy life in the moment.
Amazing.
Wonderful.
Thank you, teacher.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
A good day starts in the morning.
Mediterranean mornings
often begin with exercise.
It's how they start a great day.
We chose three local
specialty foods
lemon, seafood, and pizza
to design a warm-up routine.
You need to follow our instructions
and do three set movements.
If you hear a repeated command,
then you can't move.
Got it.
If you mess up, you're out.
There are three rounds.
Last one standing each round gets a point.
Highest score wins in the end.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
No.
Lemon.
Bro, it's like this.
You need to use your foot too, not just your hand.
Lemon.
Left foot.
Seafood.
Then,
then pizza.
Too easy.
Naiwen.
Naiwen, show us.
Way too easy.
Why is it getting easier every day?
Let me say it once.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Impressive.
Alright, go ahead.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Lemon, seafood.
Pizza.
Wait a second.
So easy.
Why is it getting easier every day?
Seafood.
Hold on.
Out.
I didn't get the question.
Uncle Nai is out.
You have to do all the moves.
Go out.
Come on.
You're up next round.
Next round.
You're next.
I haven't joined yet.
Next.
Naiwen.
I think Sun Honglei is sneaky enough.
You're even sneakier than him.
That's enough, let's go.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Pizza.
What does this mean?
Look, Naiwen.
If you lose, you step down.
I want to play.
Not bad at all.
No struggle.
Worth learning from.
Here we go.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
So fast!
Seafood, pizza.
Darn it.
That was quick!
Almost got it wrong.
Let's not fight among ourselves.
Three are already trailing, it's fine.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Lemon, pizza.
Seafood.
Pizza.
Lemon, pizza.
Seafood.
We're basically AI now.
It's too easy, kind of.
Way too easy.
Is it easy?
Let's call it out.
Okay.
You call it.
I'll call.
Go.
Ready, go.
Seafood, pizza, lemon.
Lemon, seafood.
Was that wrong?
Lemon, lemons are together.
No, you said pizza.
You got it wrong, minus another point.
You still don't get the rules.
Minus another point for you.
Naiwen, we can't even punish this.
Bro, you're totally out.
Totally out.
You call it, go ahead.
I'll call.
I'll do it.
Seafood.
Lemon, pizza, seafood.
Pizza, seafood.
Seafood.
Lemon.
I messed up.
I did this one.
I’m doing this.
You distracted her.
Actually, you distracted her.
You did it like this.
Lemon.
You can do it like this.
Really.
Makes sense.
That’s really good.
Yeah.
Final round now.
Final round, everyone.
Seafood, pizza, lemon.
Wait, how about this?
Let’s give three of us a point first.
Stop messing around.
Right.
I’m a bit tired.
Why didn’t you say that when I was up?
Say that line.
Four is a bit much.
Shidi, step down.
Basically, only a few left.
We’ve already won.
Yeah, so let’s do this.
Then just three people.
Add one point first.
Add a point.
Yes.
Okay.
Come on.
Let’s go.
This is great.
This way is much better.
Look at this family, right?
Get a point and you’re family, huh?
Yeah, family.
Family.
Let’s go.
Everyone’s ready to go.
You’re not going to be the first in the center, right?
Three, two, one.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Seafood pizza.
Seafood, pizza.
Darn it, I lost.
I’m out.
It’s all your fault.
How is it my fault? Look.
Let’s do it, come on.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Seafood, pizza.
Pizza.
You messed up.
He did pizza, pizza.
You’re using a one-on-one strategy.
Let’s go.
Uncle Nai is playing with confidence now.
Come on.
Uncle Nai is confident now.
Three, two, one.
Pizza, lemon, seafood.
Bro
Come on, get ready
Three, two, one
Lemon, seafood, pizza
Seafood, pizza
Lemon, pizza
What kind of pizza?
You two are out
You’re out too, no pizza for you
These two get points
Come on, add points
Wait, but there are three left
You all got it wrong just now
Step down
Here comes round three
Only one person can score in the end
Come on
Let’s go
Earth is so hard to adapt to
Earth is super unpredictable
Get ready
Ready, three, two, one
Seafood, lemon, pizza
Lemon, pizza
It’s reversed
Three, two, one
Pizza, lemon, seafood
Lemon, seafood
I got it wrong
So nervous
Seafood
Lemon
Bro
What do you mean?
Go down
I'm exhausted
Let's finally shine, bro
Come on!
So nervous
Three, two, one
Seafood, lemon, pizza
Seafood
Bro, this won't work
The quality is too poor
This one can go down
Here we go, the real finals begin
Alright, bro
Come on
Let's go
Must mirror
It's hard for us to mirror like this
You know?
Don't distract each other, I'm telling you
It's tough
Alright, get ready
Three, two, one
Seafood, lemon, pizza
Awesome, Liu Yuning
Nothing more to say
Impressive
Let's congratulate Yuning for this round
Congrats
What's this called?
Seafood Pizza Lemon King
Yeah, rivals the Straw King
Lemon Seafood Pizza King
Do we have anyone with zero points?
Yes
I'm proud
You three with no points, do this
Or decide who's the worst among you
Can we deduct one more point from them?
Okay
Wait, isn't this just a warm-up?
That's it
We're deciding this
Decide who's the worst
This is
The battle of shame
This isn't a battle of glory
This is the last one to advance in the group
Come on
First eliminated gets minus one point
Okay
Alright
Get ready
Three, two, one
Wait
So nervous
A bit scared
You encouraged me
Senior
Come on
Seafood, lemon, pizza
Seafood, pizza
Lemon, pizza
Seafood, lemon, pizza
Lemon, seafood
We won.
So embarrassing.
No, you two can compete for one more spot.
Minus one, the two of us.
Just decide who’s the second worst.
We don’t need to compete.
Two zero scores shouldn’t be a tie.
With so few people, we still have a tie.
I think minus 0.5 points.
Okay.
Let’s do the mirror.
Lemon, seafood, pizza, go.
Get ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Lemon, seafood, pizza.
Seafood, pizza.
Lemon, pizza.
Seafood, lemon.
Lemon.
Bro, you’re out.
What are you doing?
No.
Seafood, lemon.
You should come over.
You’re in the middle, lemon.
This is unacceptable.
Then I win.
Yes, let’s congratulate Junjun.
The best among the worst.
Second to last, not bad.
Third to last.
Still okay.
Before we go diving,
let’s do a quick warm-up.
Who’s the foreign language whiz?
First, split into two teams.
Send one person to express in English.
No acting allowed.
Within the time limit.
The team with the most answers wins.
Let’s do a practice round first.
Three characters.
Is three characters okay?
Three, okay.
It’s a boy.
Another one.
Chen Xingxu.
Great.
My turn.
Darn it.
How many characters?
Rabbit.
Three.
Yours was too hard.
Okay, rabbit spirit.
Spirit.
No.
White rabbit spirit.
Jade rabbit spirit.
Right.
Quick.
How did you guess that?
I might never guess this in my life.
How do you describe this?
How many characters?
Four.
Shoes.
No acting.
Just talk.
You can’t.
No acting.
Just say it.
Take off your shoes and get on the bed.
Red Foot, Red Sole
Red Foot
Name
Another name
Red
No
Not red
Dance
Another name
White
Red
Red shoes
Sun Honglei will be on stage later
Another shoe
No
No shoes
Ballet
Barefoot Immortal
Quick
Four
Spirit
Color
Gold
Lion King
Golden Lion
Golden Lion Award
Golden Lion, Golden-haired Lion King
Okay
Come quickly
Ox
She is
Queen
Three characters
The first character means strength
Kung Fu, Chinese Kung Fu
Michelle Yeoh
No
The first character
Queen
The last one
Who is the queen?
Wu Zetian
Yes
Three characters
The first character is
Actor or singer?
From a movie
Movie title
Movie
White
White Dragon Horse
No
That's his name in the show
His name is in
Just say it's in a play or movie
In a play or in
In a movie
Okay
White what?
The last character
Candy
This
This is
Two characters
The first is "understand"
Do you know?
Understand
Right
Forever
Come on, go for it.
We give up.
Please welcome.
Come.
Three, two, one, start!
What does she do?
I really don't know.
No.
Because she saw the answer.
Stand there, don't move.
I'll do it.
Four characters.
Wears glasses.
Famous female singer.
Four characters.
Ouyang.
No.
Four characters.
The third character is "Gao".
Gao.
The fourth character is "Wa".
I know! Siqin Gaowa.
That's right.
Three characters.
Male.
Singer.
Okay.
First character.
Liu Yuning.
Vegetable.
Cai Guoqing.
Correct.
Alright.
A very, very famous actor.
Another person.
On the Spring Festival Gala.
Very.
Spring Festival Gala.
A well-known actor.
Three characters.
The second and third characters are the same.
Spring Festival Gala.
The last two characters are the same.
Then.
Three characters.
The first character is "Song".
Give.
Li.
Is it Li?
Is it the "Li" from "gift"?
Li, Song.
I know this lady.
Famous singer.
Phoenix Legend.
Listen to me.
One.
If it doesn't work, try one character at a time.
Okay.
How many characters?
Three characters.
Let's break it down one by one.
Explain it step by step.
Go through it one by one.
Give it a try.
The middle character.
Person.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
Just a second.
Make it abstract.
Now they're singing.
Is it a show or a drama?
The middle character is "person".
Arrange "person".
What's wrong?
What word is making it so hard for you?
Let me see.
It's too hard.
A famous game.
A four-character game.
PUBG.
No.
Game.
King person.
Honor of Kings.
Names in it.
What are the characters called?
Has the character "person" in it.
Hurry, think!
I don't play that game.
Don't you play all kinds of games?
I don't play mobile games.
A long, long time ago.
Yes.
Professional player.
"Killer".
Chinese.
Judge Bao.
Similar.
You go.
Hege, you definitely know this one.
Help her out.
And I think Wenzi
described it really well.
Someone said "police".
Can we change the question?
I saw it.
Let's skip this one.
Okay.
Can we skip one question?
This one's tough.
Three characters.
Three characters, male singer.
Male singer.
Liu Yuning.
First character: "understand".
Understand.
No.
First character.
Pain.
That's right.
Tengger.
Wow, you guessed "pain".
It's really hard, can't help it.