So I'm here by myself.
The three of us can't be together.
Being together would freak out the mood.
Just wow.
This bag is really nice.
This bag looks amazing.
Does it look good?
I'm such a lemon.
The ultimate lemon bought it.
Is the blue one better or...
Oh wow.
Is the blue or the white one better?
What about the yellow one?
I'm the ultimate lemon.
Hello.
Ah.
Which one is good?
For me.
This one.
Lemon for me, okay?
The best.
Best.
OK.
Do you have another one?
This one.
Maybe this one.
Good.
This color is better.
Looks classy.
I'll buy two.
One for my wife.
One for myself.
The ultimate lemon is here.
So pretty.
These fabric bags.
These little pouches are all quite nice.
I'll get a tote bag.
Hey.
It's pretty convenient to carry like this.
Alright.
I'll buy it later.
Letting a guy shop alone...
It's honestly so awkward.
I have no idea what to buy.
Let me see if there are any little trinkets.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
That scared me to death.
Where's Xingxu?
I thought he was the hunter.
We're the prey.
Darn it.
What about the prey?
The prey is going after the hunter.
Now you can't tell who's the hunter.
I really think they're being too obvious.
First Chen He talks to him alone.
Then,
Sun Honglei talks to him alone.
If it were me,
I would've thought something was up long ago.
Go.
I'll go find him.
Here's how he's thinking.
He has Chen He,
Sun Honglei,
and me, the three least suspicious people, passing it along.
I bought two super cute dolls.
They're for my two daughters. So adorable.
Really cute.
Look, isn't this one really nice?
And the texture is great.
It's heavy.
Yeah, really heavy.
But I have to buy two.
One for each of my daughters.
Each must have one.
And I also bought two more.
I think they're from an artist, but I'm not sure.
They're not his photography.
Look at this photo.
It's really good.
It's someone fishing.
With lots of cats behind.
There's a signature on the back.
What's this about?
It's from this photographer.
Yeah, it's the photographer's.
Yeah, look at this one, this is mine.
I really like this one.
This is from 2007.
Yeah, he took it in 2007.
There are some smaller ones too.
Sorry.
I spent quite a bit.
These are two little cups I bought.
Lemon-themed cups.
And a plate for fruit, perfect for summer vibes.
But these two photos,
I really like them.
This photo just feels so nice.
Someone's fishing in the front.
A bunch of cats lined up behind.
It's like we're doing something,
with others waiting for someone to take the bait.
It's about the fish,
and the cats.
One person fishing, so many cats.
It's really interesting, you know?
And also, it's kind of lonely.
Right?
But it's not lonely either.
You're lonely too.
Use the wide-angle to get the whole view.
Got it, taking a panorama.
Everyone's in the shot.
Everyone's in.
Nineteen.
Eighty-seven.
Six.
Fifty-four.
Three.
Let me tell you.
Hide behind Liu Yuning.
You can't lose that way.
Come on.
I'll do it.
Let me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Why do I feel so uncomfortable?
Come on.
Sixty-five.
Forty-three.
Twenty-one.
Zero.
Let's do it again.
One more time.
Again.
No more.
Can you get a lot of people from this angle?
Feels like a security camera.
Guys.
Just like surveillance.
This height though.
Come on.
Let's stand still.
Okay.
Let's try the surveillance angle.
Come on.
Surveillance scans like this.
That's really good.
Totally still.
Let's go.
Come on.
Nineteen.
Eighty-seven.
Six, go.
Five, go, go, go.
Four, three, go, go.
Two, one, go, go.
Nice move.
Beautiful.
Oh no.
Let's just do it.
Walk over here.
Turn your head this way.
Let's do it like this.
This music is great.
Come on.
Wait, like this.
After putting it on your back, do this.
Ah.
This one, this one, this one—let's lift your veil.
I don't get it.
You missed out on a fortune.
What about up?
Then let's do up and down.
What about left?
Let's do this one on the left.
This one.
Isn't this the right side, not left?
This is right, on the right.
I thought I'd already done this one.
Right, left.
What about left?
Left.
Left is good too.
Up, down, left, right, right.
The world feels so fresh.
I'm losing my mind.
No way.
I can't win.
They can suspect me.
But I can't give them fake clues.
I definitely can't be the winner.
You have to think in reverse.
Normally, you'd be afraid if they got the clue.
Right?
I think I'll just give them the clue.
For now,
they trust me.
The more okay it is,
the less I try to compete.
Or do anything aggressive.
I'll hold back my actions for now.
Stay steady no matter what happens.
Right?
Well,
He Ge said it himself.
He wrote down ten families.
Everyone wants to write more.
So everyone gets more funding.
That's normal.
So I think it's basically around 80.
With help from Honglei Ge and He Ge,
I feel like I can definitely win.
So what should I do?
He's basically me.
The question is so weird, making someone touch the same muscle three times.
Right?
That's so creepy.
It's really hard.
How did everyone end up together?
Yeah.
Let them go first.
I still need to hide myself.
Honglei Ge helped me because of He Ge.
He Ge was the first one I passed it to.
I forced you, you were forced by me.
I lost because I was forced.
Alright then.
Now you feel at ease.
How can there be a man who's 1.79 meters tall?
Why does everyone usually say they're 1.8 meters?
If a guy is 1.79 meters,
he'll definitely say he's 1.8.
Exactly.
Who would ever say
they're 1.79 meters?
Alright.
The world's first 1.79-meter man has appeared.
You should be more precise.
Is your 1.79 meters with or without shoes?
With or without shoes?
What do you mean?
Soles and hair.
Actual height.
I'm talking about actual height.
Actual height is 1.79 meters.
Bare height, bare height.
With shoes, it's over 1.8 meters.
OK.
I'm 1.79.
Hey.
The second one showed up.
Take off your shoes.
Take everything off, no extras.
Advisor.
Take out the insoles from your socks too.
What about you?
I'm 90 Ge.
How can you even ask that?
Didn't you notice when you pointed at him, how tall are you?
No, I didn't just now.
I don't think I did just now.
I should've asked like this.
Like this.
Me.
So, Xingxu, you're 185 or 185.5, what about you?
We're using the info we found on Tencent Yuanbao.
180.
Do I really have to say it?
Turns out, there's no man who's 1.79 meters.
Just write down the amount.
It doesn't matter to us.
We don't need to care.
Because our goal is to let
him win this round successfully.
So,
if he comes to ask me later,
I will
be super nice so he thinks I'm a good sister
and tell him everything.
But actually, I'm not that nice.
Let's enjoy shopping.
I'm afraid if I talk,
it might suddenly show up.
And then I'll get really scared.
This one is pretty cute.
This TV is so colorful.
Take a look, take a look.
This really has that
local vibe.
I want to take a look.
Is this a ring or...
There are too many.
I can't decide.
Maybe I just won't pick any.