Welcome everyone to "Earth Super Fresh"
This is our first stop of filming
Before the journey officially begins
we'll have a
small activity to share food together
to help everyone get to know each other better
First, let's pick two team captains
You definitely deserve to be a captain, bro
Captain
Agreed?
Okay
Now we have two captains
In a moment, the two captains
will each pick their team members
One team is called "Solo Joy Team"
The other is "Shared Joy Team"
Soon
we'll bring out various foods
The two teams will
say whether they want to eat it
or
don't want to eat it
For the Solo Joy Team
the captain can choose anyone
including themselves, to eat the food
For the Shared Joy Team
everyone must share the food
The two captains,
now you need to decide
who will be the captain of the Solo Fun team
and who will be the captain of the Group Fun team.
You choose first, Yuning.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Whoever wins gets to choose first.
Alright.
To make it fair.
Rock, paper,
scissors!
I'll choose first.
Then I'll pick
Group Fun.
Alright, we eat together.
Then I have to be Solo Fun.
Right.
You decided the team type first.
Then Honglei gets to pick team members first.
I choose Xingxu.
He really cares about looks.
Look at me,
I looked at him so affectionately,
and he still didn't pick me.
Bro, I choose you.
Come on.
Thank you.
Bro, you fit in any team.
Right?
Then what was the point of winking at him just now?
I don't know either.
Let's continue.
Gong Jun.
Okay, bro.
Then
Wen.
Alright.
There's one more.
There's still one person left unchosen.
I
Everyone enjoys together, or enjoy alone
Enjoying alone
Is this also
a natural process?
I think we should have He Ge blindfolded
and let him eat first
Then
He Ge has to eat it himself
and show us as an example
and say, "This one is okay"
Then make a face for us
I think He Ge can do it
Then you guys are done for
I'm telling you
Come on
Go
Get a point for eating something good
Lose a point for eating something bad
Whether it's tasty or not
He Ge decides
Okay
Like this
Whoever loses gets punished
Make them stand guard at our door
I think
Wash everyone's socks
That's going too far
You're too ruthless, bro
Washing socks is a bit gross
Cooking is fine too
Cooking
No
It's just washing socks, cooking, or standing guard
There are exactly three of us
Not a single good idea.
Bro, you can't do this.
You think we've got this in the bag, don't you?
Bro.
What about me?
Then how about this.
I'll even act it out for you.
I have to be on the winning team, no matter what.
Alright.
Come on, let's go.
Watch closely the whole time.
What's that expression?
Hege showed a look of asking for help.
Why do I feel like I don't get it?
Definitely this one.
Can you eat this thing?
It's over.
Not eating it.
He can act it out in reverse, bro.
Makes sense.
Scoop it up with a spoon.
You can't pick it up with your hands.
I saw your micro-expression.
It's really sour, isn't it?
It's okay.
Very sour.
Such a complicated expression.
Definitely not tasty.
I really don't think it'll work.
It's definitely a condiment.
Let me tell you guys.
Naiwen bro.
What do you think of this?
I think it's pretty bad.
I think so too.
He, your turn.
Can I smell your mouth?
Stay away from me.
This is just a small part.
Don't go overboard.
Went to smell the spoon.
This is getting a bit more intense.
Not bad.
You smell it.
I'll smell it.
It's fine.
Right?
I'm sure this is fine.
We won't choose.
Then let him eat it.
Not choosing.
We'll eat.
Lift the lid.
What's the big deal?
Rice with lard.
Right?
Yeah.
Tasty.
It's one to zero now.
Second dish.
I ate it.
The taste is very strong.
You seem to suffer with every bite.
Are you a picky eater, bro?
Why does it feel a bit like seafood?
I'll go smell it.
I smell it.
I know what it is now.
You smelled it?
Yeah.
I don't want it.
I smell stinky tofu.
A whiff of Chen He.
I think this time should be fine.
That's Uncle Nai.
Wait a moment.
Kids,
do you want to eat?
Yes.
Go ahead, then.
Eat.
Let them have it.
You guys eat.
Wait a second.
So eager?
Stinky tofu.
It smells so bad.
Cover it.
This is the really smelly kind of stinky tofu.
For people from the south,
this is hard to accept.
Yeah.
I'm from the south.
I can eat it.
I'll eat it, bro.
You'll smell bad after eating it.
You can't lose, Junjun.
Junjun.
Eat it all in one bite.
This is really salty.
Don't eat it.
I'm already used to the smell.
Eat half.
Half.
But I think for someone from the south,
being able to enjoy this flavor is already quite something.
Here, let me spread it for you.
Just spread it like this, that's enough.
Here.
Right?
Spread it on the steamed bun, right?
Yes.
Just spread it on half.
It's not about how much.
The main thing is to enjoy the flavor.
This is...
That's too much.
This stinky tofu...
That's a lot.
One bite is enough.
Half.
Okay.
It's so delicious.
A kid from the south
can actually eat this stinky tofu.
I think he
It's too smelly.
No,
it's really smelly.
I think
what kind of stinky tofu is this?
How can there be this kind of stinky tofu?
Gong Jun, go to that group.
Jun Jun, go undercover.
This is something that will lose you points.
What counts as losing points?
Stinky tofu is really delicious.
When we were kids,
this was the tastiest thing.
It stinks.
It's too smelly.
It's really way too smelly.
I want to eat it like it's the most delicious thing in the world.
What should I do?
I'll give it to you, your acting is good.
That makes sense.
That's pretty good.
I'll sit here.
Hurry up.
I don't dare sit there.
Why?
You don't like Mr. Chen He, right?
Or are you...
Are you...
If you think Brother Honglei
makes you uncomfortable,
you can just tell me directly.
I just don't like Chen He.
Can achieve great things
Take a look
Serve the dishes
Because today
we have people from all over the country
so we have seafood from Fujian
Mapo tofu from Sichuan
and dumplings from the Northeast
Thank you
Okay
Yuwen
As someone from Hubei
we've prepared a dish
called "Suan Niao"
"Suan Niao"
Okay
What's that?
What is "Suan Niao"?
"Suan Niao" is what people from Hubei
say when trying to break up a fight
They say
"Suan Niao"
It means "let it go, let it go"
Forget it
Where is the "Suan Niao"?
This is it
Where's the bird?
I'm the bird, right?
I'm "Suan Niao"
I think we should just enjoy this meal
It might be tough after this
No wonder they set up a long table like this
This is the last supper
That's right
Is that what you mean?
Let's eat
Delicious
So tasty
This is so delicious.
Thanks, bro.
Here, with the skin.
Give me a piece.
Yeah, definitely.
Here you go, darling.
Thanks, bro.
Do you want a piece?
With the skin.
Let’s have this one.
This lamb feels
really tasty.
Delicious.
This lamb is so tender.
Bro, do you eat crab?
I’ll get one for you.
I’ll pass.
No, thanks.
Okay.
Do you guys eat this?
Should I get some for you?
No.
We’ll just go get it ourselves.
It’s fine, don’t worry about us.
You guys eat.
Thanks.
The kid is so considerate.
Let’s just pass the dishes around.
The dishes.
On your side.
We’ll go over and get some.
Get it while standing.
Eat while standing.
Yuning, you’re really so tall.
You even hunched over when you came over just now.
It felt like a pillar was coming over.
Right?
Yuning, when I just walked in,
I said, we haven’t seen each other for a few hours,
how come it feels like you’ve grown taller again?
Let's do this.
Let's play a game.
How do we play?
Let's play this one.
Accent King.
It must have something to do with accents.
The rules are very simple.
In a moment, I have a stack of lines here.
For example, I give you five characters now.
Then you say it once, emphasizing the first character.
Then say it again, emphasizing the second character.
Then say it again, emphasizing the third character.
Then say it again, emphasizing the fourth character.
Then say it again, emphasizing the fifth character.
Keep going until you finish the sentence.
You have a total of 90 seconds.
If anyone makes a mistake in the middle,
you go back to the first person.
We're all actors, after all.
Director.
We've practiced accenting our lines.
Logical emphasis, emotional emphasis—
We can do all kinds of accents.
Right.
Isn't it? Should be fine.
This is too easy.
Then "garlic bird" goes to that girl.
Give him the dumplings.
I'll eat the dumplings.
Here, you guys split the rest.
I'm fine with anything.
I'm easy.
The young lady has arrived.
Give it to him.
Let's see who dares touch him.
Who goes first?
I'm fine with anything.
I'll do it.
Give him the dumpling.
Okay, give him the dumpling.
Sounds like Spanish.
Give him the dumpling.
Here it comes.
Start.
Awesome.
Is it moving?
Restart the timer.
I'll admit defeat this round.
Lost.
How about restarting the timer?
Okay, three, two, one.
That's good.
Perfect.
Okay.
Continue.
Honglei.
This loss...
Yeah.
Yeah, just a few lines.
This is a bit...
Messed up.
Really messed up.
You're confused, man.
I'm confused.
Let me try again.
This time it's correct.
This one is right.
Let's do another one.
I think this round should start with them.
Is that okay?
Otherwise, we might not get to play tonight.
How about we go around from this side?
Otherwise, you guys won't get the experience.
Seriously, bro.
Right? Gong Jun, go ahead.
Gong Jun, you start.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
Then I'll start from here. Let's go.
There's also no "no" character.
You're right.
Start from that side.
Yuning.
Let them play for a while.
Let's eat for a bit first.
Come on, have some food.
Eat for a while.
Why?
Then how should it be said?
Can't do it.
The emphasis should be varied.
There should be a big contrast.
It's about how we actors understand this line.
Emphasis doesn't have to mean shouting.
It could be...
Being soft is also a kind of emphasis.
This is the kind of emphasis used in variety shows.
What he wants isn't necessarily pitch.
He wants volume.
Naiwen, you start.
Like this.
He'll go last.
Is that okay?
Let him take a break for a bit.
This way, he has a round to rest.
Otherwise, our He...
And Yuwen haven't played yet either.
Seriously.
This thing.
Eat a bit more.
Eat for a while.
Come on, I'll start.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Hurry.
No one said anything.
Oh no, there are so many mistakes.
Oh no.
We can handle all kinds of accents.
Wait, are you sure?
This is too easy.
Oops.
I just had it in my head.
No problem at all.
Don't let me rub off on you.
I don't want to speak Wuhan dialect anymore.
Then let's switch.
Let's change to a new set.
Switch it up.
Change to a new set.
Right.
Wait, why are we switching?
We didn't even figure out the last one.
Why are we switching?
We didn't get the last one.
It's just that it might be a bit hard.
Let's pick an easier one.
This one only has five characters.
Okay.
Starting from me.
Alright, I'll pass it to you, bro.
Here we go.
Stop hitting.
Alright, get ready.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
Keep going.
Feeling the pressure now.
Keep going, hurry.
Alright.
Keep going.
Okay.
Alright.
One minute and four seconds.
Piece of cake.
Isn't it really easy?
We have to give you some footage for the show.
We can't say we passed on the first try.
Yeah.
We have to look a bit clumsy at first.
It's all for the show's effect.
This is actually pretty easy.
Yeah, very easy.
Next time when designing it,
Do your best.
We all make a living by delivering lines.
And you couldn't even tell we made a mistake in our performance.
There were traces of mistakes, right?
Right.
You couldn't tell at all.
It was very lively.
And we even coordinated with each other.
Look, come over here.
You come over here.
Catch your breath over here.
Then you go again.
Actually, Yuníng was controlling the whole rhythm.
Not really.
Right?
That's not what I meant.
Just saying.
That's really all there is to it.
Yeah.
I didn't mean that.
After spending a day together and getting to know each other,
I believe everyone has already established
a basic understanding before the trip.
Usually, everyone comes up with a slogan for the show.
So you guys think of a slogan.
Yeah, let's brainstorm together.
Let's come up with one together.
Earth is super fresh.
If we can't think of it today, we'll think about it tomorrow.
I think what you said is right.
We can't decide everything on the first day,
especially something this important.
That makes sense.
This is a big deal.
We need to have three group meetings about it.
Let's assign some homework.
Everyone should come up with a few ideas.
Yes, you all should think of a few too.
We'll come up with some as well.
Let's really think about it seriously.
Then together,
let's shout out our show's slogan.
Earth Super Fresh!
Everyone together
Come on
Okay, come
Come
Cover your mouth
Is it real or fake?
Are you guys for real?
We can just come up with one for now
Shouldn't we do this gesture?
Earth is super fresh
That's fine
This one, bro
And this one
This one
Earth is super fresh
Let's start with this one
That works
Earth is super fresh
And then?
Then cover your mouth
Is it real or fake?
Okay
Earth is super fresh
Maybe there won't be one at the end
We'll just use this one directly
This will be the last one
It's this one
Alright
Let's go
Ready
Earth is super fresh
What a loud slogan
Everyone probably looked really unsure just now