Everyone needs to complete three rounds of tasks
and have Xingxu perform the designated actions
to pass good luck on to you.
At least four people must receive it from him.
But we can't let him know
that we know he's the "Chili Spirit."
If it doesn't work, we can just sacrifice ourselves.
What we just saw was
this spot
has absolutely no body fat.
Do it like this.
Hold your fingers like this.
Trust me.
I've never seen muscles like this before.
What are you doing?
Wait a second.
Come on.
What is this?
Final round
He just needs to find one more person.
One more from among us.
Xiao Xu seems especially shy and reserved.
I feel like he's too embarrassed to bring it up.
Based on your
understanding of Xingxu,
is he nervous?
He's already falling apart.
Isn't that nervous?
I just saw him, he's already falling apart.
But I think he's enjoying it.
He thinks it's nice to have someone include him.
He's really happy.
What should I do, brother?
Brother locked me in.
What should I do?
Acted cute.
So annoying, brother locked me in.
But it's really cute.
At that moment, I was
Just right.
Chen Xingxu's group has three people in their car.
I really did feel Xingxu's figure.
It's so delicate.
It's so slender.
I touched him.
He's full and springy.
To be honest,
because
since you just arrived and have jet lag and all,
I really didn't think of you.
No,
I truly didn't know.
I really drew the "lemon essence."
You drew it.
No,
It wasn't assigned to me.
I really did.
You drew it yourself.
You personally drew the "chili essence."
This is what they call the variety show god.
showing favor.
I said, are you guys messing with me?
Then when I took those out, they were all blanks.
I said,
that's it.
That was a good game.
No, I couldn't help it.
We have to—
You're so sly and cunning.
If I draw the undercover role next time,
I'll be the undercover.
Like this.
Actually, now you know who to suspect.
That's more normal.
Is that normal?
Yuning.
You guys can target me.
Yes.
I really seem like the bad guy.
Don't just accuse one person.
The four of us are all suspicious of each other.
Let's all target each other a bit.
Yes, okay.
Is it really that pretty?
So beautiful.
Let's take a selfie together.
Okay.
Alright.
So beautiful.
Let's take a selfie.
Three, two, one.
Nice.
Perfect.
How is it, Xu?
You’ve been running around with us all day since you arrived.
You’re sweating all over.
Are you tired?
Can you still keep up physically?
I always carry my energy booster with me.
Mizone.
You should have a bottle too.
Take a sip when you’re tired.
It’s refreshing and quenches your thirst.
You’ll feel recharged right away.
Here.
Get your energy back.
It really is different.
Let me tell you,
after drinking Mizone,
I can even guess who the undercover is now.
I’ve figured it out.
I’m super sharp now too.
Let’s go.
They look so relaxed.
Hello.
What did you buy?
I bought two really cute dolls.
For my two daughters.
So cute.
Really cute.
This is really cute.
So cute.
This one is really cute.
It really is. Hold it for a second.
You'll see.
The texture is really nice.
This doll.
Thank you, Hehe.
I think this is real.
Taking this back is so meaningful.
The kids will be so happy.
Kids will definitely love it.
Also,
I bought two of these photography prints.
Let me see.
This is very memorable.
Yeah.
This photo is especially nice.
Someone is fishing in the front.
There are lots of cats lined up behind.
It feels lonely.
Right?
But he's not really alone.
You're lonely.
I think coming to this place called "Lajiao Jing"
I have to buy a chili pepper.
This chili pepper has "Good Luck" written on it.
It means "very spicy." So spicy.
So spicy.
It's really spicy.
You understand English.
So spicy.
Honglei gave me a bag.
This bag right here.
Because I think
when I saw him buy this bag,
it looked really nice.
Then the two of us
also have a very meaningful
mug.
A partner set.
We even bought matching couple mugs.
Because we both love coffee.
Yeah.
So we bought ones with the same pattern.
But the brushwork is different.
I also want to buy that mug.
So whenever I pick it up, I think of
the Earth group,
think of Xingxu,
and think of Naiwen, whom I don't want to see.
I bought it myself.
I have a bunch of these.
Little keychains.
This one is Junjun's.
Yeah, she gave it to us too.
This one is my Lemon's.
And I'll give this one to "Spicy Pepper" later.
Let's show off the four of us.
The straw bags we bought.
Straw bags.
Four straw bags.
Let's do a little runway show for them, come on.
Walk a bit, do a turn.
These models here.
Their looks are great.
Ready.
Okay, sure.
Alright, thank you.
This is your only trophy.
What did you buy at first?
I gave it to him.
This one.
Very kind.
He, you’re always relying on everyone.
We’re all brothers.
When you’re out, you rely on friends, right?
He.
Wherever you go, you ask if you can buy something for your brother.
Can you spend some money on me?
I don’t have any money.
I really don’t have money.
Brother should spend money on us.
Sure.
I’ll buy it for you outside the show.
Alright, that works.
And also that one.
The one we saw at Naiwen’s sock washing place.
This really nice-looking soap.
Yeah.
Are you giving it to me?
No, bro.
Of course not.
Then why did you mention the sock washing place?
What did you mean by that?
I just saw it.
I kept looking for that nice-looking thing.
Who’s washing socks now?
It’s still you, sorry.
It’s still me.
That was an unnecessary question.
What’s up, Naiwen?
I bought one.
What is it?
A spinning top.
Wine cork
Also, Naiwen just wouldn't spend a single cent no matter what.
I really saved a lot.
Then I bought this.
It's also a straw bag.
Bought a bag.
And this straw hat.
Straw bag and straw hat.
The "straw bag" wears a straw hat.
Okay.
Didn't spend much else.
Just treated them to that.
Those fries.
Chicken nuggets.
Hot dog.
Everyone,
"Chili Essence" has already passed his good luck
on to someone else.
So he already knows, right?
Yes.
That means there’s more than one bad guy among us.
It's possible.
Come on.
The clue about the real "Chili Essence".
Who will get it?
The total number of people before is
fifty-seven.
Who is it?
I won.
Fifty.
Ning won.
If he is the "Chili Essence",
I think we've already lost.
And look, why did he
spend exactly fifty yuan so perfectly?
Now it's very clear.
Everyone,
now it's very clear.
Naiwen, how tall are you?
One meter seventy-nine.
How can there be
a man who is one meter seventy-nine?
Really.
Why?
If a man is one meter seventy-nine,
he would definitely say he's one meter eighty.
Right.
Okay.
The world's first
one meter seventy-nine man has appeared.
That proves I'm telling the truth.
Be more precise.
Is your one meter seventy-nine with or without skin?
With or without skin?
Foot skin.
After removing the foot skin.
How thick must that foot skin be?
I'm talking about height without shoes.
Okay.
This keyword actually
is pretty accurate.
This "spicy guy"
is over 1.80 meters tall.
You just happen to be exactly that height.
How tall is Honglei?
With shoes, 1.81 meters.
I'm 1.79 meters.
Here's the second one.
Are you really 1.79 meters?
Really 1.79 meters.
Wait a second.
He's 1.79 meters.
You two stand up and compare your heights.
As long as you're taller than him.
Take off your shoes.
Come on.
Take out the height insoles from your socks too.
Stand up straight.
Your legs.
What are you doing?
Straighten them.
Feels like airport security.
You three together, bro.
Excuse me, what's Sun Honglei's height?
Bro, is that how you ask?
I just looked it up.
Top ten most handsome tough guy actors.
I'm on the list.
And I'm ranked fourth.
These three 1.79-meter-tall actors
are all here.
He, you're a bit taller.
He really is a bit taller.
Not taller than Honglei.
Look at the level of the chin.
Look at the forehead.
Look.
That's just his hairline, it doesn't count.
That thing.
You can't measure by the hairline.
Someone definitely lied about their height.
Stand back to back and compare like this.
Why do I feel like He...
He might be a bit taller.
He, he's definitely over 1.8 meters.
No need to think, he's 1.82 meters.
I'm his fan, I've looked him up.
I know his stats.
Then he's more than 1.79 meters.
Then I think he's suspicious.
He's suspicious.
How tall are you?
I'm 1.85 meters.
And you?
I'm 1.90 meters, bro.
How can you even ask that?
Didn't you notice when you pointed at him...
How tall are you?
I'm 1.90 meters, bro.
No, just now I should've... no.
Xingxu, how tall are you?
1.85 meters.
And you?
I'm 1.90 meters, bro.
How tall is Didi?
Didi.
We checked on Tencent Yuanbao.
According to the information we found.
Naiwen's height
is 1.80 meters.
Do you really have to say it?
As expected, there are no men who are 1.79 meters tall.
No, at crucial moments
I'm 1.79 meters.
Got it.
No need to mention Honglei.
He's 1.80 meters.
Really?
Yes.
He is 1.82 meters.
They're all there.
Really?
All are suspects.
Except me.
Who do you think?
Me.
It should be Yuning.
What about me?
Yuning
It's because he's just too
amazing.
He performed exceptionally well today.
So I think his suspicion
is also quite high.
If he gets this,
I would find him especially dangerous.
So Yuning, you're very suspicious.
You're accusing me, aren't you?
Alright.
You're really flustered, man.
You're so flustered.
Just confess already.
Then who do you think it is?
I think it's you.
Why didn't you say someone over 1.9 meters?
I'm just waiting to see who accuses me.
It's him, I'm telling you.
And this 1.8 meter information
might not even be accurate.
Xingxu
Do you think what I said makes sense?
It actually does make sense.
Yeah.
Although I'm a bit confused right now,
I still think
he's really the only one I can choose.
Why?
Because I
have interacted with
Brother He
at the very beginning,
and I ran into Brother Naiwen.
I was paired with Brother Honglei.
No one told me I was passed on.
And just now there was another clue:
over 1.80 meters tall.
Then,
so
do you think the two of us are accomplices, is that what you mean?
He thinks the four of us have already
all been passed on.
I don't know, because I
I really don't know.
Anyway,
I can understand his point.
Because he really hasn't seen us.
Yeah.
Look, you're blushing.
Even your ears are red.
"Chili powder"
Right, Xingxu?
Yeah.
You...
It can't really be you, right?
Shut up.
I said shut up.
I'll explain in a minute.
You sit down first.
Your heart is beating really fast.
About to self-destruct.
Xingxu is laughing.
Laughing so hard.
Liu Yuning.
There are two possibilities here.
If everyone is stepping on it,
if it's Yuning,
where did the person being passed to go?
Bro, it's you.
You're also a suspect.
When eating ice cream,
you two sat too close.
First of all, from my perspective,
the two ladies must be good people, right?
Why?
Because over 1.8 meters tall.
One, two, three, four.
Actually, the four of us are relatively tied together.
If the two of them accuse me,
it means I didn't pass it to her.
First, this is definite proof.
So the four of us must be innocent.
So, do you believe me?
This "chili essence" is really playing very well.
Then it's him.
Vote for him in a bit.
This round.
Okay, whatever, fine.
I promise, like this.
Vote for Naiwen this round.
Next round, vote for me, okay?
No, that's not okay.
Why?
We just can't let you survive.
Vote.
Three, two, one.
"Chili Extract"
Let's do it together
Yuning's initial role is
a good person
I'm really impressed
I'm really impressed, guys
That's kind of interesting
This is a bit of a brain teaser
Not interesting
Not interesting at all
That's so interesting
Not interesting in the slightest
The pacing here
Kind of interesting
We're really bad at this.
How come we still can't figure it out?
This "chili extract" is really spicy.
Next, we'll do the last one for today.
It's a task where we can get clues.
It's called "Earth Super Fresh."
The members design four
each representing
dance moves for up, down, left, and right.
All members stand in a line.
One member steps forward.
and takes on the "Earth Super Fresh" challenge.
They stand in front of each member in turn and shout
"Earth Super Fresh!"
and make a different move
from the defending member.
Direction.
If the direction is different, the challenge is successful.
If you pass all seven people in one go, the task is complete.
The member who finishes the task fastest wins.
Seaweed, seaweed.
Right?
Look here, look there.
Yes.
Seaweed, just do the opposite anyway.
Let's decide on a set of moves.
This one needs to be...
What's this?
Head covering.
Red head covering.
This.
Lift up your head covering.
Down is this one.
I don't understand.
You missed out on a fortune.
This is down.
Right.
What about up?
Then let's do up and down.
Down.
What about left?
Left.
Right.
This one, I guess.
Left, this one.
Isn't this right?
This is right.
I thought I even missed this one.
Right.
What about left?
Left is also this one.
Left, this one.
Right, this one.
Up, down, left, right.
You're mixing up left and right again.
Left, right.
This whole left-right confusion thing.
It's another show again.
What are all these things?
This is the Tai Chi we learned.
Hung Gar Kung Fu.
You even learned this?
Taught by an Italian.
Hung Gar Kung Fu taught by an Italian.
Are you kidding me?
An Italian performed a lion dance in front of us.
Come on, challenge time.
I'm taking the challenge.
Three, two, one.
The Earth is super fresh.
Can't get through
Earth is super fresh
Let's go eat
Congratulations
One minute and six seconds
So fast
Six
It's your turn
Okay
Earth is super fresh
Impressive
The last one
No problem
Quick
The last one
Earth is super fresh
The rhythm is messed up, you messed it up
This day, it's a perfect match
Earth is super fresh
Perfect match
Can't get through
Earth is super fresh
Help Didi
I can't help her right now
Try again, come on
Earth is super fresh
Come on
Sorry
Earth is super fresh
I'm laughing so hard my head hurts
That scared me to death
Earth
This of mine
Alright, Earth is super fresh
Are you the gatekeeper?
You go do it with him first.
Yes, you go do it with him first.
Go do it with him first.
Come with me first.
I was the first, I'm pretty tired too.
Actually,
Come on.
Earth is super fresh.
Okay.
Four minutes and forty-nine seconds.
Wow.
Come on.
You start from there.
Why?
You start from there, I'm the last one.
I don't want to.
No.
Yes.
I'll listen to her.
I'll start from this side.
Okay.
This kid really holds a grudge against me.
Come on.
This feud is settled now.
You're done for.
Come, from this side.
Earth is super fresh.
It's all the same, that's amazing.
You don't even need me.
Come.
Earth is super fresh.
You're still too slow, you...
No.
Ning.
So you do it like this first.
Then after he does it like this,
You follow like this.
Right.
Fresh.
Wait a second.
Let me do it.
Earth is super fresh.
You didn't do it.
What do you mean?
Okay.
Earth is super fresh.
Come on!
Alright, let's go.
Earth is super fresh.
Are you in or not?
You guys, stop fighting.
Stop fighting.
You're having another dance battle, huh?
Let's play something advanced, come on.
How do we play?
Just like this.
I'm behind you.
Alright.
I definitely won't cheat.
I'll turn my back to you too, okay?
Alright.
The two of us will turn our backs to you, come on.
Three, two, one.
Earth is super new.
Earth is super fresh
Okay
Awesome, come on
Passed, he passed
I passed, come on
Bro, do you know what I'm going to play?
I know
If you know, that might not work
You can't know
I don't know, come on
Earth is super fresh
Wow
Earth
Wait a second
Okay, I can wait
Make a call, call someone
Hello
I'm going to play left
Top, bottom, or right?
You know now, right?
Someone told you the secret, didn't they?
Of course
If I lose this time
I'll jump into the sea from here
Play
That intense?
Don't forget what happened in Room 6
Right
Blood feud
It's become a blood feud
These are two big families
The blood feud between the Elves and Vegeta
Your sister is great
Of course
Which side are you going to play?
I'm going to play top
Okay
Super fresh
Wow
Not bad
A few minutes
Five minutes and one second
The first person to go over five minutes
Hello
Three, two, one
Earth is super fresh
I've already learned it.
Earth is super fresh.
What are you doing? If you didn't do it, it doesn't count.
Both of us did the downward move.
It's this.
It's really like overcoming many obstacles.
Getting serious.
Earth is super fresh.
Earth.
Two minutes and twenty-one seconds.
Okay.
Come on.
Earth is super fresh.
Defense is broken.
Wait a moment.
What are you doing?
I'm going to interrupt your spell.
Okay, go ahead.
Earth is super new.
Earth is super fresh.
One minute and forty-nine seconds.
Awesome.
Go for it, big sis.
Earth is super fresh
Okay, I'll play seriously
Okay
Earth is super fresh
Be a bit more serious
I'll be even more serious
Earth is super fresh
It's really hard
Not necessarily, you might not be able to guess
Come on
Earth is super fresh
What is this thing you're doing?
What are you making?
Go
Earth is super fresh
I think I still have to go up.
You can't put it at the back.
Earth is super fresh.
You're really good at this.
How much?
One minute and nineteen seconds.
That's good.
That's really fast.
You're still the best.
Naiwen is awesome.
Brother, please.
It's my turn.
Please.
Easy.
Earth is super fresh.
Earth is super new.
Impressive.
That was easy.
Fifteen seconds.
Impressive.
So impressive.
That was amazing.
Come.
Come on, bro.
I think you should take care of them a bit.
Okay.
Sure.
Give them some hospitality.
Treat them well.
Alright.
Earth is super fresh.
Master.
The lines are really nice.
Hurry up, bro.
It's really good.
Hurry up.
The rhythm is already broken.
Did you guys touch it today?
No.
Hurry up.
Haven't you felt it before?
Come on, hurry up.
Let me tell you, this is the master I acknowledge.
It's really different.
You—hurry, don't—
How many seconds has it been for me?
Hurry up.
Hurry up, bro.
You work out, come over here.
And there's one more thing.
No.
Show it.
Hurry up, bro.
Hurry up.
I'm only looking at this one spot.
Look.
Don't move yet.
Look, like this—hold it down.
What are you doing? What are you guys doing?
Hold it down.
Look, press here.
Press this spot.
And look at this part.
He really practiced well.
Check out this edge.
Hurry up.
He really did a good job.
Because it sinks in.
It's really good, the lines are good.
The lines are pretty nice.
Bro.
Big bro from the family.
Quick.
The Earth is super fresh.
Go back.
He practiced well, right?
Not bad.
Pretty good.
Practiced quite well.
Earth is super fresh
How can someone get their muscles like that
He Ge
And also, Yu Ning
There's something you don't know
What
He trained to get them like this
And he only has five abs
No, five? I don't believe it
Five
I actually felt them today
Who has five? Isn't it six or eight?
Five, look
One, two, three, four
And he's not even flexing
No, I only felt four
Show him the fifth one
The fifth one
Not allowed to touch
You can't touch the fifth one
We're really curious.
How about this? Or maybe like this?
With muscles like yours,
you must have a strong resistance to hits.
Let each of us punch you three times.
How about it?
We'll let you pass all of them, okay?
Each person gets three punches.
What are you doing? Where should we hit?
Hit the abs.
Hit here.
Feel this part, it's like a tank.
Come on, stand up.
How about each of us gives three punches?
Will that count as passing?
Because it's already been over five minutes.
I'll go.
You go.
You better not.
Alright, it's done.
Okay.
Can you still keep going?
I can.
He can.
I definitely can.
Earth is super fresh.
Are you ready?
I'm talking, it's fine.
You...
I'm talking.
It's fine, we're normal.
We're normal.
Like this.
Come on.
I'll turn my back to you, come on.
Three, two, one.
Earth is super fresh.
Not easy.
Five minutes and twenty-nine seconds.
Congratulations to the members of the five-minute club.
That's awesome.
So this is how you welcome me.
We only have the final round of voting left.
Then let's go back to the guesthouse.
We'll do the final round of voting at the guesthouse.
Okay.
Alright.
Let's go.
Mizone, save me.
Naiwen.
I'm thirsty and tired.
Then wait for me a moment.
Okay.
Have a Mizone.
Get your energy back.
As expected,
the energy savior.
The lime-flavored Mizone is really refreshing.
My energy came back right away.
I can keep going.
Do you believe it?
Can you really keep going?
Full of energy.
Bring it on.
Let's try something even harder.
Energy dropping.
So thirsty and tired, I'm about to collapse.
Join the "Unstoppable Energy" Mizone comeback challenge.
Stay energized on your journey.
Succeed and win a Mizone comeback supply pack.
Haven't you had enough to drink?
Have some more.
Please ask Sun Honglei to give Li Naiwen
a Pulse comeback supply pack.
Stay energized with the Pulse lifesaver.
Get ready to face more challenges on your journey.
I'll try again.
Take your time with the challenge.
I'll go back and grab a bite first.
Looks great.
The sunset is so beautiful.
The sunset.
So beautiful.
This light.
The afterglow shines on our faces.
Go over there and take some photos for me.
Over here.
Then I'll take some wide shots.
I'll take another wide shot.
I don't want wide shots.
I want beautiful people in the photo.
We've got beautiful people.
Okay.
Come over, let's take a selfie.
You hold it.
Like that.
Which way?
Horizontal? No.
Like that.
Like this.
Right.
Come on.
Let's make it into a nine-grid collage.
Ready, one, two, three.
Let's go home and eat.
Go home, go home.
Come on, get in the car.
Congratulations on winning the competition.
Amazing, really.
Now it's completely safe.
Totally safe.
Won everything.
If, just now, while playing that game,
did you already forget
what you were supposed to do?
I remember.
But it wasn't good.
So what should you do?
It's hard to make a move.
If I hadn't acted just now,
you wouldn't have had much of a chance.
Because I was planning to look for that person—
Wen'er.
Because I'm more familiar with Wen'er.
Just now, he
while you were standing there chatting,
he came over and let me touch.
He said even though he's been on set lately,
he's still been working out pretty well.
Still been working out pretty well.
What's wrong?
Even though he hasn't really been working out,
it's still okay.
It's fine.
I touched three times.
That's fine.
I didn't squeeze.
It would be weird if I squeezed.
Squeezing would be too fake.
Yeah, squeezing three times right away
would be exactly what he wanted.
So I just touched once.
Are you sending it to me now?
Send it over, I'll pick some.
Wait a moment.
Then I'll edit them tomorrow.
Who else?
It's on the phone.
Liu Yuning has it on his phone, right?
I don't have it.
I look really bad in photos.
Not as bad as Chen Xingxu (his photos are worse).
I just asked him to
take a few photos for me nearby.
The scenery is so big,
but I'm just a tiny part of the photo.
And it started from here.
Just my head in the bottom corner.
It made me so mad.
Let me see.
I'll show you, I'm so annoyed.
This is the first one, this composition.
The next ones are...
I'll show you, the later compositions are even crazier.
What is this supposed to be?
The later compositions are even more exaggerated.
Look.
Tourist photo.
It's all just mountains.
The main thing is, it's so ugly.
What is this?
Look at the ones I took for him.
Not bad.
I'm so frustrated.
Not bad, looks good.
You didn't even say anything.
You should've asked your sister to take them for you.
We're here.
Come on, Xingxu.
Come on.
Come.
Honored homeowner, welcome home.
Welcome home.
You haven't been here before, right?
No, I haven't.
Take a good look.
Come on, move forward.
I'm your security guard.
Really?
Follow me.
This is our foot-washing guy.
Foot washing.
No.
Sock washing.
Foot washing.
Foot-washing guy.
Sorry.
You switched to foot massage, right?
Uncle Naiwen will wash your feet.
Uncle, all of this is...
It's so cool today.
This feels amazing.
With a gentle breeze blowing,
it's so comfortable.
It feels like a sea breeze.
Ning, are you tired today?
Ning,
I'm okay.
My shoulders are a bit tight.
Your shoulders?
Alright.
The pool.
Is it an infinity pool?
Perfect chance for you to show off your muscles.
No need, I don't have any muscles.
Let me show you the "Number One Suite."
Are you sleeping with me tonight?
I don't know.
Right, we need to give everyone a pillow.
Seriously.
We don't have to be this close, do we?
There's a private bathroom.
And a balcony too.
It's beautiful.
Come on, let's eat.
This is great.
Thank you.
Sure.
Look, my three plates, bro.
Bro.
Hurry, eat while it's hot.
It's delicious.
You don't eat cheese, do you?
This cheese is really tasty.
Just this cheese.
I don't like cheese.
Then how did you grow so tall?
Born beautiful.
How did you get so tall?
I don't know.
Why don't you two go outside?
Even 1.82 meters feels short here.
Did you know that?
That's normal.
I want to know.
Was there a clue in the last round just now?
Yes.
Honglei
Let's go to the side, I'll tell you the clue.
Clue.
Lots of leg hair.
This clue is making me dizzy.
What clue?
This "chili powder."
This clue is almost
a giveaway.
It's basically giving it away.
It's like forcing this person into a corner.
The clue is that the surname is Sun.
Likes to wash socks.
You have to tell the truth.
The clue I just got was
has a lot of leg hair.
Then Naiwen is cleared of suspicion.
At least make it as hard as mine.
"Chili extract"
Everyone has to pull out a leg hair or something.
Yours is so sparse.
Because I play this game a lot.
Is my leg hair the longest?
Let me tell you,
Those of us with the surname Chen,
you all basically come with built-in wool pants.
Is my leg hair the longest?
It must be He.
He has a ton of leg hair.
A few months ago,
when I got a hair transplant,
there was some extra of this stuff.
Hair follicles.
A whole batch ended up on my leg.
Xingxu also has thick leg hair.
My leg hair is thick too.
Let me see whose is thicker.
You like this...
Didn't you notice today?
I didn't really pay attention.
There's nothing after that.
There is, too.
I forgot.
Really?
I have to see this for myself. Come on.
So I said,
After my hair transplant, before and after,
I got a whole patch.
Even the back of my knees grew hair.
Bro, you have hair behind your knees too.
What's it to you?
"Chili extract"
Choose one of two.
Me and Xingxu
And then, that brother and big brother
None of us have been tested.
Actually, that's right.
Actually, I think
the content of this clue
is about fifty percent true, in my opinion.
There's one more person
who hasn't said a word this round.
The person sitting across from me.
What did you do to my mussels?
Let me tell you,
No matter how much I eat, it's still not as much as your leg hair.
I think it must be He.
Yeah, bro.
He really has a ton of leg hair.
His leg hair is as much as his scheming.
Honglei might be lying.
I believe he's telling the truth.
Then you two should team up.
Then Naiwen,
You just wouldn't come up and let me check your leg hair.
I think there's something wrong with your hair.
There's something wrong with your hair.
What does that mean?
A problem.
Wearing glasses without lenses.
Legs without hair.
A brain that doesn't think.
You're "chili sauce" now.
Okay.
I'm done arguing, guys.
I'm done arguing.
If you vote for me,
you won't have a chance.
For my "chili" boss,
I'm willing to sacrifice.
I've been blessed.
I accept it.
Vote for me.
You only have one chance.
Wait a moment, Chen He.
Wait a moment.
Come on.
Chen He.
Do you dare to say that?
You've been blessed, right?
I've been blessed.
Okay.
I've been blessed too.
See?
Bet you didn't expect that.
Jumped.
Wait, let me be honest.
You've confused me.
What are you trying to do?
Alright.
Actually, it's just for an effect.
I'm being serious now.
Anyway, I'll tell you.
Sit down.
Let me tell you humans.
You only have one chance.
Vote for me.
All the big beds
belong to us, the "Chili Clan".
You sit too. Bro, sit down first.
To make a long story short,
but actually, it's a long story.
I've already said a lot just now.
If there's anything,
talk to my mom.
Is it you?
I think it's Xingxu.
Xingxu, who do you think it is?
Yes.
Me.
Take your time.
Take your time, no rush.
Make sure you speak slowly.
I definitely have to suspect Honglei.
It's because...
Is it possible...
He tied me up...
...here.
He didn't hurt me.
He left you here to protect him.
Xingxu, I'm going to cry.
A pair of innocent eyes just looks at you like this.
Alright, shall we vote?
Let's do it.
Three, two, one.
Raise your hand if you vote for Xingxu.
None.
One.
One vote.
Okay.
Raise your hand if you vote for He Ge.
Three votes.
Wow.
Raise your hand if you vote for Honglei Ge.
Honglei Ge, four votes.
Honglei Ge's initial role is
a good person.
Thank you.
That's enough, bro.
That's you.
We are the "Chili Clan."
Come on, let's applaud.
Come on, applause.
You rascal.
"Chili"
Thank you.
"Chili King"
You guys are in cahoots with him.
I'm telling you, the four of us are together.
Come on, let's have Xingxu say a few words.
Xingxu, go ahead and say something.
I won't give a speech.
I'll just briefly talk about what happened.
After I found out my identity,
I completely broke down at that moment.
Honestly, my first reaction was thinking
maybe I should just lose and be done with it.
It would be nice to just go live alone in that tent.
Already broken down.
Almost at my breaking point.
But I never expected
that at this very moment, I would run into
my first "chili sauce."
They came to me on their own.
They delivered themselves to me.
A "chili sauce" that came right to my door.
There's even something like this?
How could I have expected that?
Who could have expected that?
Bro, tell me,
how did you end up breaking this rule?
Why?
I wanted to work out.
I ran right into trouble.
The "chili sauce" came straight to me.
So I just went along with it and talked about it.
Then my task was done.
I was really shocked at the time.
You were right to be shocked, let me tell you.
The second "chili sauce"—
I never expected that at all.
Because—
Again, I totally didn't see it coming.
Ran into trouble again.
Yeah.
No one told me
that the first "chili sauce" had already been informed
that they'd been made into "chili sauce."
So at that time, I was
with my second "chili sauce."
He just kept me there.
I was totally confused.
I was like, what do I do now?
Honglei is really
so smart.
I really had no way
to do anything right under his nose
at such close range
to do it,
to make a "chili sauce."
Then
No one expected
the first bottle of "chili sauce"
the first bottle of "chili sauce" was notified
I was totally confused when he came in
I didn't even know he had already been notified
"chili sauce"
After coming up
he started
When he said his first sentence
Master
This is my master, now
When he said "master," I said
Then
my second bottle of "chili sauce" appeared
I was still confused
Right after my first bottle of "chili sauce"
and the second bottle of "chili sauce"
led me to finish my
third bottle of "chili sauce"
I was forced to make "chili sauce"
Come on, let's reenact it
Let's reenact it, come on
Honestly, for me
it felt like two bottles of "chili sauce" had already
smeared all over me
I had no choice
so I went straight for the "chili essence"
That's how it was
Naiwen, this side is the shop
You act it out
I'm watching
Yeah, I said, what are you doing
What are you doing
I just turned into "chili sauce"
I was the most guilty at first.
But there was no choice, it was for the mission.
I also paid the price.
That was part of the mission too.
Right?
I haven't received a single cent yet.
The two of us also
exchanged gifts.
Yeah, cups.
Alright, it was worth it.
So mine was the least valuable.
No.
It's like drinking tea.
The first brew, the second brew,
by the third brew, it's weak.
No flavor left.
We can definitely make up for it.
We can make up for it.
Okay.
We'll make up for it later.
Make up for it later.
Because the situation was urgent at the time.
Right?
We don't feel guilty toward ourselves.
Not a bit guilty toward you.
A toast to the losers.
Come on.
That smug little look.
Today, besides the best player,
which is Xingxu,
we also have
Best Planner,
Best Director,
Best Actor,
Best Action Director,
and this one.
They are, respectively,
Gong Jun, Liu Yuning,
Chen He, Sun Honglei,
Wang Yuwen, Ouyang Didi,
Li Naiwen.
That's awesome.
Wait a second.
Welcome to
"Earth Super Fresh."
Welcome to "Earth Super Fresh."
Xingxu, how about this—
Can you go over it again?
Are you guys messing with me?
Is every single one of them—
I don't believe it.
How come you never suspected me?
This can't be right.
What's not right?
Isn't it? Why does it feel so weird?
I don't need to go over it again.
I'm just going to be dizzy for a bit.
I have a feeling right now.
Let me say a few words—
There is no worse.
Only the worst.
I just like the bad ones.
Impossible to guard against.
When the three old guys
turned into "chili sauce,"
Xingxu immediately relaxed.
Yeah.
The difference in him was obvious.
It was
when he first arrived
and when he saw us again later.
He was like a completely different person.
This is what you call
feeling secure.
He suddenly felt safe.
I don't have it now.
Now it's completely gone.
Not even a little bit left.
Even less than when I first came.
Feels like he doesn't even know us anymore.
Right?
You guys really
matured so quickly.
This is the crash course I signed you up for.
Alright.
Today really was
a rollercoaster of life.
Thinking back on it is just too funny.
Xingxu.
Xingxu is such a pure kid.
Brother.
Brothers.
Love you.
Welcome home, owner.
Cheers
Always remember the city of Sorrento
This is a city that makes me
both love and hate it
Let's take a group photo
We don't have this here
No, I want to stand here today
Okay, that's fine, come on
Then move forward
This side looks better, little brother
Three, two, one
Okay
Great
Just a little closer, just a bit more
My heart
Have we thought of a name?
Have you figured it out?
Earth is super fresh
The world is right in front of us
The second gesture is this
This one, with both hands
"The world is right in front of us," right?
The world is right in front of us
Okay
Earth is super fresh
The world is right in front of us
See you in Sicily
Yuning is the main focus today.
We're all your assistants today.
My voice is hoarse, bro.
Xingxu.
If you don't want to be the "spicy pepper",
then just sing one song.
The one from Les Misérables.
"Stars".
"Stars" is the hardest song
to sing in Les Misérables.
Xingxu.
Please stop randomly
showing off your charm.
Welcome everyone to Earth 808.
I like how unique you are.
I have eighty-eight concerts this year.
Teacher Gong, I'm your fan.
Just teasing you.
First, tell us where you're from.
Hello, students.
I'm from...
Why do I feel
like the atmosphere is a bit off now?
You can tell who looks more like a mentor, right?
Teacher Ouyang.
Whichever team you join,
we'll join that team too.
Just switching sides directly.
Give yourself a hand.
On your body.
Like this.
They'll always remember
their left shoulder and left hem.
Let's go over it.
Here we come.
Okay, right here.
Solo performance.
You're pretty good at blocking.
Go away.
Get out of the way.
He winked at me.
He's distracting me.
Jun Jun, do a solo performance.
Music, start.
Since I can't stay in your embrace,
Friends walk together for a lifetime.
Walk together for a lifetime.
You reckless guy.
Jumping so high.
Just like that, I'm conquered by you.
I'm too embarrassed to watch.
Way out.
Let's have some dignity.
Elephant Square.
In this kind of atmosphere,
I love China.
Thank you.
Today, the eight siblings of the Earth family
are discussing the family business merger plan.
But everyone has serious disagreements about the merger plan.
We will have three rounds of voting
to identify the two people who oppose the merger.
Control your expressions.
Naiwen looks a bit suspicious.
Number Six,
why aren't you saying anything?
My throat just isn't feeling well today.
You're overacting a bit.
Eighth Sister,
what's written on your sign?
I choose not to say.
Today's situation will be tough.
You can also choose
the most trusted leader
and let them take two people in to vote.
I'll be the captain.
Why are you suddenly so energetic?
Because I've never played this game before.
Weren't you just quiet a moment ago?
You've never played?
Why are you trying to be the captain?
You'll probably get us all sunk.
Revolution, rotation.
Spin up and down.
Spring.
Trampoline.
Go!
So many people.
What are you doing?
Up.
Down.
Left.
Right.
Me.
Marilyn Monroe
How did you know that?
Older people are wiser.
Which two do you think are the bad guys?
I suspected him from the start.
The captain said it was you.
It's me.
Who's the second one?
It's you.
It's me.
Has this song been passed down all along?
What?
Was this song passed down directly?
Let me see.
You cried and told me
In fairy tales
Beautiful heavenly voice
Not this one.
Girl across from me, look over here
Look over here
This is killing me.
I've seen heavy rain in the desert
I've seen the ocean
Wait, put it back on.
You've seen too much.
I praised you for nothing.
This is really a bit hard.
Look at my expression.
I won't say anything.
I won't sing.
Yes.
I know
I know that song
I've seen rain pour down in the desert
I've seen the ocean kiss a shark
Go ahead, charge
I've seen dusk chase after dawn
So who are the two wolves in your mind?
Just vote
One hundred percent
He isn't
I'm an old "killer"
Danger
Very dangerous
Take responsibility yourself
Just say it once
Don't say more than that
Otherwise, you two admit defeat
Do we even need to admit losing?
He was always the uncle
I'm planning to leave this show
Naiwen
Stop acting, that's enough
A little bit
Not even a little bit
That performance
Under what circumstances
What's your pivot point?
A long time ago
A little bit
Even just a little bit
Is this the Lemon Family's dance?
We're both crickets
Cricket duo
Do you know
I've been waiting for you for a long time
Do you really think
you're so stunningly beautiful
that you can fool me
It's definitely in the rhythm
What rhythm did you give him
Even Liu Yuning can match it
It's so hard to guess, this of his
Even if we're really clueless
we still have to vote for you this round
Yeah, I think it might be wrong, but