[주제곡] [Machine Translate by www.kisskh.la]
[rattling sound]
- [Giggles] - [Painful groans]
[Minyoung’s heavy breathing]
- [Continued creaking sound] - [Painful moaning]
[Minyoung] Oh, fuck!
Fuck you, be quiet!
Shut up!
[Minyoung sobs]
[Sooyoung] Min Young-ah
are you okay?
[Rough breathing]
shut up
This is not my sister!
Minyoungah
are you okay?
[Sobbing] No, I don&#39;t want to wake up!
[Loud cackling sound]
[Minyoung’s painful scream]
[Minyoung continues to sob]
- [Sounds around you become muffled] - [Mysterious sound effects]
- My sister is - [dark music]
my sister
[Minyoung] My thoughts
worry
I don&#39;t do that
She&#39;s the type of sister who only knows herself.
[Sooyoung] Min Young-ah
are you okay?
[Minyoung] I need to be that kind of sister
[Minyoung sobs]
- [Emphasized sound effects] - [Dark music]
[Mysterious sound effect]
[Crying] Min Young-ah
are you okay?
What about your sister?
[Minyoung] Even if I look like this
Even if I keep tormenting my sister
Even if my sister has a hard time because of me
Are you okay?
[Sooyoung] Min Young-ah
are you okay
That&#39;s right
my sister
[Sound of lock opening]
[dark music]
Then it&#39;s okay with me too
[Interesting and suspenseful music]
[Elevator operation sound]
[Music stops]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[nervous music]
[Elevator arrival sound]
- [Dark music] - [Sooyoung] What about Minyoung?
I&#39;m fine, whatever.
[Geonwoo] Oh, I’ll send you a photo.
Wait
[camera shutter sound]
- [Switch operation sound] - [Door opening sound]
[rattling sound]
[Sound of door closing]
[Meaningful music]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Minyoung’s moans]
[crow crying]
[ECG alarm sound]
- [Sound of falling] - [Minyoung’s groan]
[nervous music]
[Minyoung’s sound of pain]
[Heavy breathing]
[Sound of mountain birds]
[Squeaking door]
[Minyoung’s surprised gasp]
[Minyoung’s sound of pain]
[Frightened breathing]
[Grunting sound]
[Lock operation sound]
- [Rattling sound] - [Minyoung’s frightened breathing]
[rustling sound]
- [Sound of birds flapping] - [Sound of dogs barking in the distance]
[Switch operation sound]
- [Grass bugs crying] - [ECG beeping sound]
[intense music]
[creaking sound]
[Sound of door slamming]
[rattling sound]
- [Card key recognition sound] - [Door lock operation sound]
[Door lock operating sound]
[Switch operation sound]
[Heejin] Kids say that these days?
If I stay close with you, I will study well.
I need to hang out with you
[Sooyoung] You talk about all sorts of things.
[Heejin] So I did that
Eunseo Lee, she
Something sucks
There&#39;s definitely something
[Puts it down]
[Suyeong] What&#39;s wrong and what&#39;s there?
I&#39;m figuring it out
As soon as I find out
I&#39;m going to expel you from school right away.
[Heejin] But before that, I’ll give you a warning.
next midterm exam
Don&#39;t even touch that
My body is really a matter of life
[Sound of opening a book]
[snort]
Is your life so fucking easy?
Do you think you can do anything you want?
Don&#39;t be mistaken
Because if I make up my mind, there&#39;s nothing like you
[heavy music]
You&#39;ll hear good news soon
[Jinwoo] Seo Ho-soo
uh?
Your aunt says she has something to ask you?
What?
[Aunt] Student, it’s been a while
I saw it in the laundry room then.
yes
What do you want to ask?
[Call connection tone]
[snort]
[Call end sound]
[Aunt] I guess the chef is having trouble talking on the phone right now?
[nervous music]
[Jinwoo, aunt’s laughter]
Um, can you explain?
Last Saturday, replacement Lee Eun-seo
Why are customers visiting students&#39; homes?
Did you call me?
Why at that timing?
What kind of timing is that?
[Soaring music]
[tapping sound]
[Imo] Timing when the chef is in crisis
What on earth are you talking about?
Eunseo tells customers
You even sent a picture of the lake student?
[Aunt] The text says to take the student out of the house.
uh?
[Laughter leaking out]
[Jinwoo] Oh, but aunt
No matter how much I think about it, it doesn&#39;t make sense.
Is this guy a chef?
Lee Eun-seo knows the identity of the chef.
Is he alive and well?
Plus, we eat lunch together.
We also take classes together
[Meaningful music]
Sticking around?
[The angry breathing of the lake]
[Lake] Let’s go
But I think you need to be careful what you say.
If the chef finds out you&#39;re doing this
I think it&#39;s dangerous
- [Card key recognition sound] - [Door lock operation sound]
[Sound of door slamming]
[Door lock operating sound]
[light sigh]
[sigh]
[uneasy music]
[Hosu Mo] Let go of this!
long time no see
[People sound surprised]
[Meaningful sound effects]
- [Lake&#39;s heavy breathing] - [Skipping sound]
[Ecstatic laughter]
[Jihye] Please be pretty
[Laughter of the lake]
[The sound of the lake&#39;s strength]
[Emphasized sound effect]
- [Thumping sound effect] - [Music stops]
[sigh]
[sound of banging]
[Hosu] I solved the workbook yesterday.
I got just one question right
What did you think?
[Sooyoung] ‘Failed’?
&#39;thank god&#39;
It&#39;s positive
[Lake] You said it
Don&#39;t give up
help me
of course
[Sooyoung] I already have a method in mind.
[Chasing the sound of rain]
[Hosu] Are you going to find Yoo Seong-pil?
[heavy music]
The consultant Yoo Seong-pil, played by Choi Gun-woo?
[Sooyoung] Yes
Because that will be Choi Gun-woo’s decisive weakness.
[sigh]
What and how do you find that person?
I don&#39;t know if he&#39;s dead or alive
dead
[Sooyoung] To be exact, I killed him.
Choi Geon-woo
[Lake] How do you know that?
Are you sure?
I found it
[Sooyoung] Witnesses who secured decisive evidence
[Meaningful music]
[Sooyoung] Please share one weakness.
[Geonwoo] What does that mean?
[Suyeong] Seohosu is in full swing
I need it to get him out of school.
I&#39;ll say I found it
But there&#39;s just one thing I regret
I guess I should go out in person
I&#39;m going to say I need to find out.
[Geon-woo] Will he come out obediently?
what
It will depend on how critical the weakness is.
So, pass over my weaknesses?
[Swimming] No
It can be fake
There are plausible circumstances
If only I could fool you
[laughter]
[Hosu] But the timing is a little too good.
I suddenly have a student who offers to give me information.
[Meaningful music]
[Suyeong] Why?
Are you anxious?
If you don&#39;t believe me
I can go out alone
no
How can I go alone?
Let&#39;s go together
Anyway, if it stays like this
Even if I stay still, I die
I should try something
of course
[Lake] I should try it
You&#39;re trying to protect me
[Sooyoung] I’ll go first
- I&#39;ll stop by the bathroom and then go. - [Hosu] Yes.
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Steps moving away]
[Geonwoo] Did the West Lake go over?
[Swimming] Yes, it was easy?
[Geonwoo] It looks like you trust Sooyoung a lot.
Then, as soon as you hand over Seo Ho-su,
I will tell you the address where Minyoung is located.
[Sooyoung] But before that
Let me make one thing clear.
This is the place where Minyoung is.
What if I go and it’s not there?
How can you believe that?
[dark music]
[snort]
Why do I lie?
Use me again or whatever you do
You can threaten me with Minyoung.
[Meaningful music]
Ah, um
[Geonwoo sighs] Let’s think about it.
What value is Sooyoung without a chef?
Should I take advantage of your weaknesses?
- [Interesting and suspenseful music] - Minyoung?
It&#39;s just a burden to me
The moment I catch the chef, I won&#39;t have him around anymore.
There is no need or reason
Isn&#39;t it?
Yes
[Geonwoo] What value is Sooyoung without a chef?
Should I take advantage of your weaknesses?
[heavy music]
[Kyunglim] Oh, Eunseo.
Would you like to see the teacher for a moment?
[Kyunglim] I heard it
I heard you told teacher Seongpil that you were still thinking about it?
So
[Suyeong] Does that mean I can go to all the universities here?
[Kyunglim] Then, of course
Is there a university that top students from Jeonghan High School can&#39;t go to?
So let me know
Not only all students
The teachers and parents here are all curious.
Eunseo you are now
What university and department are you studying for?
Anywhere
[Suyeong] I want to go somewhere
If you can go
[Meaningful music]
There&#39;s no need to hesitate anymore
To get Minyoung back
You have to be cool
[Swimming in the mirror] As if the lake was deceiving you
You&#39;re just fooling him too.
There&#39;s no need to feel guilty
that&#39;s right
No matter what you had at school
That&#39;s not more important than Minyoung.
[Swimming in the mirror] You are Minyoung’s older sister.
You&#39;re the only family
just
I&#39;m going back to my familiar daily life, but...
still
[Calm music]
There were some good things too
[Crying] Nineteen
3rd year of high school
It was your first time, right?
don&#39;t say more
[Sooyoung] Don’t cry
Don&#39;t show it
are you okay
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Sooyoung laughs slightly]
Smile, just
[Laughs slightly]
[Sound of students talking]
[Dahyun] Eunseo!
어디 갔었어? Where have you been? 전화도 안 받고 Not even answering the phone
[Sooyoung clears her throat]
[수영] 왜? [Suyeong] Why? 무슨 일인데? What&#39;s going on?
[Dahyun] After our midterm exams
On the 200th day left before the CSAT
Do you want to go take a friendship photo?
- [Student 1] That&#39;s right, let&#39;s go together - [Students respond]
- [Students] Let&#39;s go together - [Dahyun] In front of the school
I heard there&#39;s a place that does really good retouching, so I&#39;m thinking of making a reservation.
[Student 1 laughs]
[Dahyun] Wait a minute
Eunseo, did you cry?
[학생2] 뭐야? [Student 2] What is it? 진짜 울었어? Did you really cry?
[Students] What, what is it?
- [학생2] 야, 왜 울어? - [Student 2] Hey, why are you crying? - [다현] 무슨 일이야? - [Dahyun] What&#39;s going on?
아니, 누구야! No, who is it! 누가 우리 은서 울렸어? Who made our Eunseo cry?
- [Student 1] No - [Student 2] Why are you crying?
- [학생3] 괜찮아? - [Student 3] Are you okay? - [학생4] 울지 마 - [Student 4] Don’t cry
[Sooyoung sniffles]
[Calm music]
If you
If you say you die tomorrow
- [Coughing] - [Suyeong] What are you going to do today?
why?
Well, why don&#39;t you tell the neighborhood that you have an incurable disease?
sorry
[sigh]
[Jinwoo] Well
Dream about eating cookies
Wouldn’t you try to achieve as much as possible in reality?
[sigh]
But to do that
What if the situation is a bit complicated?
What does the situation matter?
I die tomorrow
[Sooyoung] Isn’t that too mean?
i still remember
[Jinwoo] What is your dream?
wear nice clothes
Eat something delicious
Make friends, date, and study
Are you saying we&#39;re just going to live like we do now?
What&#39;s wrong with that?
To other kids, it&#39;s just everyday life.
[Students laughing]
[Sooyoung] Let’s take a picture of friendship today
The weather is nice too
- [Upbeat music] - [Students] Smile, smile
[Jinwoo] Take a picture
One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
[Dahyun] It&#39;s captured, let&#39;s do V V, V
[Students] V, V
[Jinwoo] One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
- 됐지? -Okay? - [학생1] 야, 빨리 와, 빨리 와 - [Student 1] Hey, come quickly, come quickly
Quick, come to work, come to work
[Sooyoung and Dahyun’s excited screams]
[함께] 야, 우리 뭐 해? [Together] Hey, what are we doing? 뭐 해? What are you doing?
- [학생들] 곰돌이? - [Students] Bear? - [진우] 자, 마지막이다 - [Jinwoo] Okay, this is the last time.
One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
[Sooyoung’s laughter]
[Student 2] I’m here, I’m here, quickly
[Dahyun’s scream]
[Students laughing]
One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
[Dahyun] You two are dating
How about taking a sweet photo like a couple?
Ah, ah, no, no, it&#39;s over.
Let’s just take a quick picture and get into it [laughter]
[Jinwoo] Hey, who is doing V?
Look at me
I have to do it like this
your left hand, me right hand
[Sooyoung laughs] What are you saying?
[Sooyoung clears her throat]
[Dahyun] Filming?
[camera shutter sound]
Okay, now it&#39;s the last time
One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
[Heejin] Eunseo Lee, what on earth is she doing?
[Lake] I think you are taking a picture?
Are you asking because I don&#39;t know that?
[Heejin] No, why are you acting like that when it’s raining?
[Hosu] I guess my friends asked me to take a picture.
[Heejin] If you just look
Do you know that she&#39;s secretly suffering from princess disease?
I just stand in the center because it’s pretty
Is that a compliment?
no it&#39;s not
[nervous music]
[Geonwoo] Are you doing well?
[Tap sound]
Why is the teacher here…
[Laughing] Hey
Why are you here, teacher? Huh?
[Geonwoo] It’s a classroom.
Ah, guys
Well, something happened suddenly today.
There was a consulting class in the 5th period.
It was changed to Korean
Why don&#39;t you talk to your friends who aren&#39;t in class?
- [Students] Yes - [Geonwoo] Yes
[Geonwoo laughs slightly]
Lake, see you again
[Suyeong] If possible, please come to the classroom.
The lake must be blinded by revenge right away.
I will try to get out of school somehow.
[Geonwoo] Do you think you have a lot of resentment towards the chef?
but
It was too much to lie that I could wake Minyoung up.
You&#39;re lucky
[Suyeong] I wish it was a little later
I might not have been able to get past Seo Lake back then.
- [Dark music] - [Chairman] It&#39;s a shame.
I wanted to kill you in front of you
I
I guess I couldn&#39;t control the water.
I died too easily
Like the flowers planted in the flower garden last time
Can you please check?
[Chairman] Check it out.
Because the smell is so bad
&#39;Cause I just can&#39;t go
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Chief Heo] If our Geon-woo waits, well, we should wait.
[Chairman] And this
This is the cell phone he used.
I brought it separately to give it to you.
Because it&#39;s locked
- I didn&#39;t open it separately - [Meaningful music]
now
Please hand over the chef.
[dark music]
[Birdsong]
- [Screaming sound in the video] - [Kiseok in the video] What&#39;s wrong?
[Kiseok’s moans in the video]
니가… you… 건우야! Geonwoo!
왜 그러는 거야… Why are you doing this... [신음] [moaning]
[Call connection tone]
yes
I even checked my phone
The chef
I will take you there myself tomorrow evening.
[Washing machine operating sound]
[Aunt] Perhaps
What will you do if you find out who the chef is?
[aunt’s laughter]
Just like you did to me
- 요 칼이라도 들이대려나? - Are you going to point me at me with a knife? - [어두운 음악] - [Dark Music]
worse
as much as possible
I need to take revenge more cruelly.
[Aunt] Eating together or going to class…
시간을 보내는 건 좀 오버지? Is it a bit too much to waste time on? 그지? Right?
Isn&#39;t it obvious?
As long as I don&#39;t go crazy
[breathing in relief]
[Suyeong] But for about a day
today
If it&#39;s the same day
I think the chef would be grateful.
[Aunt] You know that?
Have you almost reached your sales target number of customers?
[Sooyoung] Already?
[Aunt] Oh
I&#39;m thinking of talking to the chef today.
Now wake Choi Minyoung up.
How about sending you out of school too?
The timing is just right.
What happened
[Meaningful music]
[Sooyoung] Min Young-ah
Today in my heart
I called your name a thousand times, ten thousand times
[rattling sound]
[heavy music]
[Sooyoung] I had to keep remembering
- I&#39;m your older sister - [Sigh]
you are my younger brother
It&#39;s obvious that I have to save you
[sigh]
i want that
To say the obvious
This place is too much for me
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Lake] Where are you going at this time?
What&#39;s going on?
today
I got caught in too much rain
[Sooyoung] So
Will you come to my sister’s dream today?
please
[Mysterious sound effect]
Will you be my dream again?
[Music increases and then stops]
[Lake] I barely slept a wink last night.
I can&#39;t sleep
[Suyeong] Why?
Well, I&#39;m nervous too
I&#39;m looking forward to it, so
[Calm music]
[Exhales a long breath]
What do you expect?
[Lake] Of course I’m looking forward to it.
If only this thing goes well
Choi Gun-woo is also completely finished.
We are finally liberated
Why are you so naive?
[Lake] Huh?
[Suyeong] Is it the end? Is it liberation?
Isn&#39;t that too easy to say?
[Laughs slightly]
[nervous music]
[The sound of the lake clearing its throat]
[The lake is gurgling]
[The lake sniffles]
[The sound of the lake clearing its throat]
[The lake is gurgling]
[Sooyoung] This
[호수] 어? [Lake] Huh? 어 uh
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Sooyoung] It’s strange, this is definitely the right place
Let’s at least give it a call. Are you sure you came to the right place?
[Meaningful music]
[Sooyoung] Uh
I&#39;ll call you
- [Lake] Yes - [Sound of zipper opening]
[Call connection tone]
[Sooyoung] Ah, I have now arrived at the place you mentioned.
Oh, you&#39;re almost there?
[Heavy sound effect]
[Emphasis sound]
[eerie sound effect]
What is this?
- [Call end tone] - Sorry
you…
[Heavy sound effect]
[The lake&#39;s laborious groans]
[dark music]
I couldn&#39;t help it either
If we want to save our Minyoung
How can you do this to me?
[The sound of the lake&#39;s heavy breathing]
[Mysterious sound effect]
I know you can’t save Minyoung anyway.
[Sooyoung] There’s no reason to protect it
[Sound of car door closing]
[Geonwoo] That’s right
[Heavy sound effect]
I&#39;ll send you the address.
[intense music]
[Continued intense music]