[Translate by AI Provided by www.kisskh.la]
[You can send your subtitle to us we will put your credit on it]
-= The place names, characters, organs, events, etc. of this TV series have nothing to do with real =-
Feed Song Zhenyu running legs
Song Zhenyu Heel Mask
Is there any two of them?
Should the two of them be associated?
No
There is definitely no Minying follow me
I haven't said that to me
What is it?
Where did they go?
What new employee
ah
Newly selected by chefs
To deal with intra -school monitoring and cope with various situations
okay
Why don't you answer my phone before?
SMS does not return
I'm going to take a vacation
Is it on vacation?
One person died
But what is killed is our cookie customers
The killing method is also cookie
But even the police are not away from me throughout the weekend ...
Otherwise
Really
Hey according to what you said
Our customers killed someone with our cookies
Then what ingredients can our cookies detect
New drug?
No
Not detected in the end
Although today there was a crisis due to the police
But things have been solved
Because of the good performance of our new employees
Do so well
What will the police do this
You take care of Park Wisdom
I will clean up the police
May I
Does the invasion of the residential case?
Is the boss in the workplace entered the subordinate employee's home?
What is the identity of the victim and the victim
First...
Cui Minying Cui Xiuying?
elder brother
What about the victim
I will call you back right away
What are you doing
What
I ask what you are doing
Is this a police officer, is your car?
Because I fell off
here
police officer
Be careful
Let you drive carefully
so
The song that the woman gave me ...
I ate Xiu Ying's cookies that Xiuying gave me
Everyone looks delicate and tender in my eyes
I am still fighting spirit
Really 淦
Then
Did you have a deep coma?
wisdom
right
Police officer, do you believe in me?
How to say the results of the hospital's examination
So what is annoying is this
There is no abnormality
It is said that it has not been checked what's special
that is
Can't prove that there is such a cookie existing this fact
No one believes me
so
In order to get a bit of cooking, you leave the hospital
Go to the victim's house
right
but
No cookies
Said it was given by her sister
Her sister's words
Cui Minying?
right
I did not see it
Xiu Ying
She is a simple person
The woman of her sister is not an ordinary person
就 If I go out, I will go directly to her ...
If that thing is anesthetic, don’t I take it?
Eat so much
I'm a police officer, right?
I am Kim Yun Fan Wei, a Zhenghan Police Department
Can I go in because Cui Minying came in?
no
For the recent Wen Kui Nan case, the case
I want to ask you a few questions
Didn't you just say that because of Min Ying, did you come?
I because they came
You know this
Survey results show
This is an ordinary cookie
This is what I just bought in a convenience store just now
Gulan
Because it can be bought everywhere, it can be sold everywhere
So it is difficult to distinguish
so what
So it can be very convenient to deceive people to replace
There is a student who died in Zheng Han High School
Because I ate cookies
How could it be so the same
Whether it was before or now
Regardless of him at that time
still you
What
you
These policemen
I heard you faint
Will you only manage your strength in this year when you are in high school?
Parents
sorry
Your dad is also scared because he was scared
Say it yourself
Aren't you often showing off to friends around you
Say my daughter is studying at Zheng Han High School S
next time
Manage your physical strength
Ask what she needs
Try to satisfy her
Look, Mom said it
As long as you go to class S, everything will be solved
Two cases related to cookies
Also included Cui Minying, classmate Cui Minying
I am not very clear about the case of the school
It should be okay
But Wen Kui Nan's case is determined
It has nothing to do with her
Obviously what you said
That cookie is a unilateral claim of the victim
After the investigation, I found that there is no abnormal ordinary cookies
I told you that it can be very convenient to deceive people to replace
I know you should be difficult to accept
But if this is a new type of drug
See you
Do you know what kind of guy Wen Kui Nan is
I
us
Do you know what we almost turned that day?
Do you know what he usually looks like in the company
But that pervert
Find an excuse that is unwavering
What does my sister who is obviously the victim?
It is a character that is commonly included in two cases
this...
Have you ever seen Wen Kuinan just now?
Because the guy said that you came, did you suddenly come over?
That's why I doubt my sister?
sorry
I
Can't fully take care of the victim's mood
But something is urgent
I'm not shocked anymore
You were like this four years ago
Xiuying girl
I heard you usually make up
School uniform skirts are still short
I also heard that you will be coquettish with your father
There's none
And why you have not called the police so far
If you don’t want to, you should call the police a long time ago
Just take a sip not to sleep, it is also very energetic
Thanks to this for a long time
If you eat half of the cookies
There will be a mood of flying sky
If you eat a whole whole, you will be fluttering
The fantasy in dreams will be displayed in front of you
get out
But if you eat more than one
I asked you to get rolled, otherwise I would call the police
-= My sister, my sister, I and Haoxiu because I have to go back to the party later because of learning.
sister
I have to go back later because of learning
Open it after the party
-= Guard Jin Yunfan =-
I have to go back to school first
I put the business card
If you change your mind, you must contact me
If not
What do you plan to do
I have confidence
Can you apologize to us
I can still kneel and apologize
What do I need to do
How do I prove
Who is Min Ying's boyfriend
sister
I have to go back later because of learning
Open it after the party
here
Did you go home immediately after school today?
Yes
But what's the matter
Come to my house
Nothing
Tomorrow will move into the dormitory
Before that, I want to see you
After that happened, I cared about it
I'm fine
Wait a moment
correct
When do you learn to make cookies
What
nothing
I just want to learn how to do it
Go to see him to confirm it
Whether it is
It's really the cookies he made
wisdom
Can you chat?
What's wrong
wisdom
What happened to you wisdom
Dad
Help
What
I tell you honestly
I fainted today
It is because of this police uncle
He said that I was blinded in class S
Kill Xu Rujing
Does this look like
I've been entangled these days
Wisdom you
I haven't said that kind of words
wisdom
Not why
how's it going
Very clear how to make biscuits
I heard that her father used to be a bakers before
Yeah
Park Wisdom
Did you say what to say
I will contact you again later
I will sleep well
Ready to kneel
I told the younger generation
Learn
Don't have to worry about
I heard that madman
Has been warned several times by the police
-= Park Xizhen =-
-= Cui Minying =-
-= Xu Haoxiu =-
-= Wisdom. I am like you are waiting for you on the roof. =-
Are you crazy
I let you not intervene in Zheng Han High School
- = Director =-
Now say something inexplicable
Also investigate schools
Do you know how many people call me?
Director, I also plan to let go today
but
That's why you can't promote the official to step in place
You will be transferred to know
Come to report in the Department tomorrow morning
Director
-= Spring water that can be drunk =-
My sister suddenly told me to go today
Ask me how to make biscuits
What's wrong
Praying information of the daughter of the factory director
What is this called?
what happened
What's going on
- = []]] Park Shangji's eldest daughter Park smart position: Zhenghan Hospital Funeral Hall 803 Time: March 8, 2023 at 14 pm =-
This is how to do ah
What is this called?
-= Jin Yunfan criminal police =-
Hello
Is it Jin Yunfan's criminal mobile phone?
There is something wrong with the mobile phone machine
Traffic accident
I can't answer the phone seriously
May I have your name
As soon as he wakes up, let him call back to you
Cui Xiuying?
What is the teacher's suicide
Do Park Smart jump off the building and commit suicide?
It's too bad, right?
Recently, S class will be missing
Will stay in nine people
Now you know
Be sure to keep spiritual concentration
Do you understand
Put your luggage in the dormitory in the first lesson
Lesson 2 starts to class normally
Everyone must come to class on time
Min Ying
Want me to help you transport your luggage to the dormitory
Min Ying, where are you going
The luggage brought by the mask herself
Two men helped move
Is it a bit over
yes
I said I am here myself
Haoxiu, you're a little over
That's because my relationship with Min Ying is the best
Let's put here here
Put it inside
Not so good outside
Go slowly
Vast
Do you like Park Xizhen
How can it be
no
Like it in the future
What
-I liked -I like Cui Minying
So you like Park Xizhen in the future
I'll give you money
OK
Don't hinder me
Hello teacher
-The teacher -Hello, hello
Teacher Liu, come here
This is coming to our school to investigate
-Pura Police Officer -Hello
I am the admission exam consultant Liu Chengzheng
Nice to meet you
Chat
Teacher Liu together
No
I have something else
how's it going
I will deal with it, there will be no problems
The investigation is over
I know Jin Yunfan's lunatic
I have always liked to make things bigger
Why is our school always happened
Can't leave a bad impression
yes
That's why I will come over
-D toast -dry toast
Dry coffee
Is the chef finally crazy?
It's not that if it's not crazy enough to be discovered
How can you deal with things like this
Criminal Police's traffic accident Park smart committing suicide
Is it crazy enough to want to make things big?
Don't be stubborn
Dare to be dissatisfied with the chef
The chef is different from our position
We don't know his identity
If he is found to hide it
But what about us
In case of discovery
Give my chef's mobile phone number
I want to say it in person
There is no way to do this again
It's better not to contact
Give me a mobile phone number
Chef knows everything
Your sister’s factory happened because of a biscuit
Why didn't you tell us
that is because
I have done it all
Yeah
Didn't you leave a doubt?
Yes
I don't know there will be any problems
You know the criminal police in a traffic accident
Have you ever been looking for your sister?
Real
Didn’t my sister tell you?
Do you not change clothes? What do you do?
Change
In the evening, everyone will go to the funeral home together
Do you have to go too
Um
Have you been brewing your feelings?
Mourning for the death of the daughter of the factory
Don't be too much
You are already a formal staff member
No need for this
What has something to do with you?
If it is related
What should I do
How to do how to do
Sorry you are okay, right?
Um
What can I do?
-= Cui Xiuying =-
Thanks