Don't go.
Don't meet him.
I don't want you to see him.
Do you know what you're saying?
I do.
I'm stopping you.
You said your dating life
sucked because of me
and you couldn't like anyone else but me.
So you were unhappy.
I feel responsible for
what you went through.
You shouldn't just date anyone
when you don't even like--
Who says I don't like him?
He's not just anyone.
He's a good man.
I think I can learn to like him.
So…
you don't have the right
to feel responsible
or to tell me who I should
or should not date.
We're just…
friends, right?
He still has that habit.
He still confuses me.
PROSECUTOR HAN JIN-JU
YOU ARE INVITED TO
SHIN DONG-HUN AND JUNG JI-YUN'S WEDDING
How dare he send me a wedding invitation?
Why not?
I'll be blunt. You guys weren't dating.
It wasn't even a fling.
It wasn't because of my lack of trying.
It's not some amusement ride
I can ride alone.
I need permission to go on it.
Right. Why are you so worked up?
You just had a crush on him.
I'm angry only for one reason.
Everyone else is actively dating
and getting married.
But how come I'm still single?
Why am I always alone?
Dating a lot of men
isn't so special, either.
Look at me. I'm alone right now.
Then since we're both alone,
let's grab a drink.
Now?
Yes. Should I pick you up?
Are you outside?
Well,
I have plans tonight.
With who?
I see. Your CEO?
Yes.
Do you want to call Yeong-hui?
No. Have fun on your date.
Okay.
She said she was alone.
Why are you out here?
To do this.
You must be hungry.
Let's go and get some delicious food.
I've always had bad relationships.
I just dated anyone even though
I didn't have feelings for them.
Since I started liking you,
I couldn't like anyone else.
It's too hard for me.
I feel responsible for
what you went through.
You don't have the right to feel
responsible or to tell me
who I should or should not date.
We're just
friends, right?
GIRL WITH THE CURSE OF THE NINTH
Come on, what is she doing?
Why isn't she answering her phone?
-Hello.
-The receiver cannot be reached.
-Please leave a message.
-Fine. Just hang up on me.
-Have a drink. Let's raise our glasses.
-Sure.
By the way, how come
you never fight with your boyfriend?
We had a fight recently.
But you don't seem bothered.
Aren't you nervous?
We dated for ten years.
So our patterns are fixed now.
"She's probably cooled off by now.
I should give her a signal
that I want to make up.
I should let this go now."
You know, things like that.
Ms. Kim, did you have a fight
with your boyfriend?
No.
I have ears, too.
I heard you say you had a fight.
You have good hearing for no good reason.
This is a compliment.
-Right. I have good hearing, don't I?
-Yes.
By the way, you should apologize, Ms. Kim.
You can't date other guys now.
You dated him for ten years.
What do you mean by that?
Let's be honest.
Unofficially, you're a married woman
who went all the way.
No men will accept it.
Only pushovers will accept your history.
Don't you agree?
Sir, let me pour you a drink.
-My glass is filled.
-Can you pour me a drink, then?
All right. Let's stop drinking.
Do you not like the food?
No. It's good.
Why don't we do something
that will lift your mood after dinner?
What do you like, Ms. Gyeong?
You're a nice guy.
I hope that changes to "the guy I like."
If I met you a long time ago,
I would have caved in and dated you.
I don't dislike you.
And I would have hoped
that I might grow to like you.
Why don't you cave in
and hope that you will?
That hope has always betrayed me.
I don't want to be
in another bad relationship.
It might turn out differently.
I don't think I could be
in a good relationship.
Then, why don't we test this out?
Let's see if you could be
in a good relationship or not.
I'll be your test subject.
I don't want to do that.
But you don't dislike me.
You said you could have hoped
it would be different.
If you're turning it down for my sake,
you don't have to.
You turned me down,
but despite that,
I'm still hanging onto you.
So I'll be responsible for my own pain.
There's no need to think so hard about it.
When I ask you out with a decent excuse,
please say yes like today.
When you do, you will end up liking me.
I'll make sure you do.
You're quite confident.
You do sound trustworthy.
It's all an act,
so you can trust me.
-Let's eat.
-Okay.
Can you get something from the backseat?
Sure.
It's a bribe for brownie points.
TONIGHT
Goodness. What is it this time?
It's obvious that
you have something on your mind.
Come on, lighten up.
Just tell me what's bothering you.
Am I that unattractive?
-Am I that lacking?
-Oh, my.
So many guys like Woo-yeon.
And Hyeon-jae is crazy about Yeong-hui.
But why am I alone?
Why am I always alone?
Why are you blaming yourself?
You just haven't met the right person.
It's not your fault.
Besides, being single is awesome.
How?
You have a lot of time and money.
Oh, right. That's why you deserve to drink
this high-quality traditional liquor.
I was just about to say
you don't have to if you don't want to.
Why are you always so angry?
Perfect timing. If it weren't for you,
I would've been dead.
You're coming here often.
Is ignoring me a trend with you girls?
-It's a long tradition.
-Is ignoring me your habit?
You just realized that now?
-You punk.
-Beer, please.
You don't get a beer.
Aren't you going back to Jeju Island?
Are you leaving? You should go somewhere.
-Does she hate me?
-You just realized that now?
I wonder if Woo-yeon's date is going well.
Is she dating again?
He's a really nice guy.
He's hot, rich,
and totally straightforward.
"Totally straightforward"?
On top of that, he's so gentle.
They're like a match made in heaven.
You call yourself a prosecutor.
But where's your sense of justice?
Save that guy. Tell him to run away.
-Where are you going?
-To the restroom.
-What's his job?
-I don't know.
What? You guys must think
you can walk all over me.
-You just realized that now?
-You little…
What did you mean
by "totally straightforward"?
TONIGHT
Oh, right. I don't smoke.
All right. Wait.
Has anyone here bought
concert tickets online?
Have you done that?
I…
-What is it?
-The moment they find out you're capable,
that will always be your job.
I see.
Sir, didn't you say you went to
Red Velvet's concert the other day?
You need serious skills
to buy their tickets.
Totally.
-You're amazing.
-You're so amazing.
-You're so good.
-You're amazing.
-Really? Then help me out.
-Amazing.
My daughter has been pestering me
to buy tickets for NCT's concert.
Sure. Tell me the date
of the concert she wants.
-Sure. Let's have a drink, everyone.
-Nice.
JIN-JU
-Hello.
-Hey, girl. You've got to come over here.
Hey!
Our Cultured Pearl is totally wasted.
It's a huge mess here.
-Jin-ju? Why?
-Hey, stop that.
-No.
-Beats me.
She told Su not to make you cry
and won't let him go.
-Okay. I'll be there quickly.
-Okay. Don't move. Hurry.
What's wrong?
I need to stop by somewhere.
Sure.
I can drive into the alley.
No. It's a narrow alley.
It's better if I walk.
I'll wait if it won't take long.
No. My friend probably drove here.
I thought we were getting close.
Don't you think you're refusing me
a bit too often?
-Drive safe.
-Bye.
When will she stop being so distant?
Sir. Get home safely.
-Bye.
Wait. Hold on. Wait.
Guys, we should go for round three.
Round three.
-Round three.
-You almost made me sad.
-Let's go.
-Round three.
-Let's go, round three.
-Let's go.
-Over there?
-Yes.
When are you going to go home?
Did you drink a lot?
How did you know I was here?
You texted me to come here.
You go to Pretty Pig's
for company dinners.
Afterward, you always go to this karaoke.
My gosh, what a clever lady.
It wasn't my intention.
I'm sorry. I regret what I did.
-How much?
-Enough to not do it again.
I'm going to let it slide just this once.
Okay.
-Sweetie.
-Yes?
Should I have ramyeon
at your place tonight?
-Tonight?
-Yes.
Will you?
-What?
-Let's go.
Seriously. When did you get here?
I know everything.
What took you so long?
Where's Jin-ju?
Hey! Jin-ju.
Jin-ju.
Why did you let her drink this much?
Her? She drinks like a fish.
How can a prosecutor be so violent?
Su got beaten up pretty good.
See it for yourself when he comes back.
There he is.
Tell your friend that she'll be
a defendant tomorrow, not a prosecutor.
There's no need to be that harsh.
Jin-ju, wake up.
You…
If you break Woo-yeon's heart
one more time, you're dead meat.
If you make Woo-yeon cry again,
as the prosecutor of this country
and as her friend, I won't forgive you!
What? Is she Sailor Moon?
Have you gone mad? Hey, wake up.
Woo-yeon means so much to me.
My gosh, she's a goner.
Hey, put her on my back.
-Jin-ju.
-Put her on my back.
-Get her cell phone and her bag.
-Okay.
Goodness.
Move.
Watch your head.
I cannot leave the restaurant unmanned.
I'm going back in.
Get home safely.
-Call me.
-Okay.
Let me come with you.
-Why?
-To sue Jin-ju.
Did the date go well?
Yes.
-Woo-yeon.
-Yes?
Did I make you cry?
Yes.
-What?
-Did you cry because of me?
That's what Jin-ju said earlier.
She'll kill me if I make you cry again.
Seriously?
Why would you listen to a drunk girl?
Some use alcohol to tell the truth.
Drunk people tend to say things
by mistake more often.
That's how they are.
What the heck is Su thinking?
Didn't Su talk about Woo-yeon?
No.
That's Su. He always keeps
a straight face and doesn't say anything.
I have no idea what he's thinking.
I'd never date a guy like him.
I'd be frustrated.
Here.
Don't worry.
I'll be the last guy you'll ever date.
But you're like that, too.
You don't talk about yourself, either.
I've dated you for ten years,
but there's a lot I don't know about you.
You didn't know? That's my thing.
I want to be a mysterious woman.
So you could be even more attractive?
-By the way,
-Yes.
are we just going to eat ramyeon?
No additional activity?
Can't we finish this?
It's a waste of food.
Hello, ma'am.
Thank you for looking out for her.
Not at all. This is nothing.
My gosh. She only ends up drinking
because she can't date.
She's rich, has a nice job,
is well-educated, and pretty.
Why can't she date?
It's because of you, ma'am.
My mom told me once I go to college,
I could date men
like Gang Dong-won and Zo In-sung.
Dating is harder than getting into SNU
and passing the bar exam for her.
My gosh. But she doesn't want to
go on blind dates.
She's so stubborn.
She drives me crazy
when she's all grown up.
It was you who caused this.
My mom said I could meet Hyun Bin
and Lee Min-ho once I passed the bar exam.
I'll get going, then.
Okay. Get home safe. It's late.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
What took you so long?
What could you possibly talk about
with a drunk girl?
You're still here.
How could I go?
Why are you asking me? Get a cab.
The transportation wasn't the problem.
How can I leave without you?
It's dangerous at night.
What if something happens to you?
I don't want to feel guilty
because of you.
You don't care about
anyone else but yourself.
Do you think
the world centers around you, too?
Of course.
Let's go.
If you break Woo-yeon's heart
one more time, you're dead meat.
He's a good man.
I think I can learn to like him.
Oh, right. My flowers.
Wait.
Pass me my flowers.
Do you have selective memory?
Why did you remember this?
I'm using my memory to the fullest
after forgetting you.
Thank you.
Gosh, it's so chilly.
How long have you been out here?
Are you a two-timer?
Or did you break up with him already?
It's not what you think.
Did you manage to see his face
when it's so dark?
It's dark, but his face was
shining like a star.
You have a bad taste in men.
What? No.
You and I have a similar taste in men.
This was all your fault.
She always takes everything out on me.
My goodness.
Unbelievable.
I'm going to put them on soon.
Why fold them?
I don't want your clothes to get wrinkled.
My gosh, you're so nice. You're amazing.
Then why won't you marry me?
I don't want you to suffer.
I'm kind of serious.
I don't want a serious conversation.
You won't marry me?
If I get married, I'll marry you.
And I'll get married.
Then why do you always avoid the topic?
I'm not avoiding it. I'm 29 years old
this year, the curse of the ninth. Okay?
I'm a total idiot if I ever drink again.
Prosecutor Han.
Hey.
Did you drink a lot?
A bit. No. I drank a lot.
Drink this.
Did you also drink a lot last night?
No. I had one with me.
And it looked like you needed it.
Thank you.
Don't drink too much.
Your liver won't last.
How could the bottle be green, too?
It's a green light, right?
He's a really nice guy.
What is it? Why aren't you talking?
You're the one who drank last night.
But I'm the one who's feeling sick.
Are you sick? How?
My body's aching all over.
Did you go to the hospital?
The only thing I can do is talk.
What about your parents?
Woo-yeon, we're going to Namhae.
Oh, no. What should we do?
I have to work late today.
-Why don't you call Yeong-hui--
-No.
I'm sure she's busy as well.
I'm sure
I'll be fine after I get some rest.
Okay.
JIN-JU
What about this week's shoot?
METAPHOR PUBLISHING HOUSE
-Mr. On.
-Yes?
Do you want to go
to the school reunion together?
I can't make it.
Why is that?
I'm on a test.
I see. All right, then.
WHAT ABOUT THIS WEEK'S SHOOT?
She's ignoring my text?
Woo-yeon called in sick today.
She says she's aching all over.
I see.
Okay. Thank you.
You're not the only one asking for her.
I mean, a handsome guy came by
earlier and asked about her.
I thought he was her boyfriend.
He's not her boyfriend.
Hello?
I heard you're sick.
Did you go to the hospital?
It's late.
I bet you didn't eat or take any medicine.
I've been sleeping.
Come out. Let's go to the hospital.
What?
I'm at your house.
No way. You can't be.
No.
I know women don't like it when
men suddenly show up
and ask to meet without a heads-up.
But you need to go to the hospital
and have some food, too.
No, I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
I'm not okay with this.
I'm not okay with this, either.
I won't look at you.
I'll keep my eyes on the road.
Let me drive you to the hospital.
Wait until she comes out.
She said she was coming out.
I'm here because she's taking too long.
What will you do if she collapsed?
I will take care of everything.
-Woo-yeon.
-Ms. Gyeong.
Are you okay?
What are you two doing here?
-Let's go to the hospital.
-Let's go.
Can't you see the driver is waiting?
So take the taxi back and go home.
I was here first.
Ms. Gyeong, are you okay?
-Come with me.
My gosh.
I just want both of you to go home.
I'm taking the taxi.
You can't go all by yourself.
Right. Come with me.
She said she wants to take the taxi.
-She doesn't want to take it with you.
-Gosh, come on.
Can you two…
Can you just go?
I have a really bad headache.
Ms. Gyeong.
Jin-ju.
Get your hands off her.
You're the CEO.
She told me so much about you.
I'm On Jun-su.
I'm sorry,
but I'll take her with me today.
Then please take good care of her.
What's going on here?
Why are they both here?
I don't know.
Why are you sick?
You're breaking my heart.
Because you can't brag?
Yes. Today is a historical day.
Why did you get sick?
Gosh. My ears are ringing.
You know what?
I don't even know
why I'm asking this, but…
Then don't.
You guys aren't dating right now.
It's rude to come to her house like this.
There's no need to worry about that.
We're more than just colleagues.
In my opinion,
you're the one who's being rude
when you're just her friend.
Or
do you like Woo-yeon?
As if. I told you. We're just friends.
That's great. I hope you will keep
your word and your friendship.
Bye, then.
-Are you feeling better?
-Yes, totally.
But how are you here?
I thought you had to work late today.
I finished quickly because I was worried.
-I'm the best, aren't I?
-You showed up at the perfect timing.
Right. Why did you hesitate?
You could have just gone with the CEO.
I wasn't hesitant.
I was too sick to think.
Tangerines.
They must be from your CEO.
He's so considerate.
Tangerines are your favorite.
And this is porridge.
I'll heat this up for you.
You should eat this.
Thank you for the porridge.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I showed up unannounced
and made a scene there.
Don't show up
without a heads-up like that.
I'm sorry.
Because I was worried,
I let my emotions take over.
I don't want you to see me
when I'm not ready.
You looked pretty earlier.
You said you wouldn't look.
I couldn't stop looking at you
because you're pretty.
Oh, right. How did you know
that I like tangerines?
-Tangerines?
-Yes.
Tangerines are my favorite.
The tangerines
were from someone else.
-What are you doing?
-These are from Su.
Don't eat them.
They are just tangerines.
By the way, I really don't understand him.
The way he looked at you.
It looked like he had feelings for you.
You're way off base again.
That's what you said ten years ago.
You said he liked me.
I mean, the things he did…
You're right.
No one knows what he's thinking.
Right.
Whatever. Let's stop.
Let's just stop talking about him.
Hey. You're the one who started it.
How is it going with your CEO?
Are you seeing him, then?
-For now?
-What does that mean?
What? Why are you smiling like that?
You know, he told me
to test him out.
-Do what?
-Test him out.
I told him all my relationships were bad.
He told me to test him to see
if he can help me
have a good relationship.
He's weird, isn't he?
He's the perfect guy.
He does seem like a really nice guy.
Right. Just forget about Su.
Anyway, he'll probably leave soon.
I'll only work with him
if nothing happens.
How can she not give me a call
after leaving me like that?
Who parked in front of my house?
Hi.
Get in.
What's this car?
-I bought it.
-You're staying in Korea?
-For now.
-Why?
I just wanted to.
What's today's theme?
We're going to Euljiro and Haebangchon.
For Euljiro…
Old printing shops there
are still operational.
And there are old restaurants.
Next to these shops,
retro cafes and restaurants sprang up.
This area got popular because of them.
It's the same with Haebangchon.
So the theme is a place
where the past and present coexist.
What do you think?
It's good.
No messing with me today.
I put effort into my makeup today.
I wanted to get this off your hat.
I wasn't trying anything.
I just thought
you were going to cover my face again.
-When did I ever do that?
-What?
My gosh. The old sayings are all true.
The one who did wrong
can't even remember it.
-What?
-You said that I was ugly
and that you should only look
at beautiful things.
That's why you put my hoodie over my face
and pulled my drawstrings.
You did that ten years ago.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Stop it.
What was that all about?
You look ugly.
I must only look at beautiful things.
Hey, that was…
You should only look at good things.
I didn't want you to get hurt.
You totally misinterpreted my kindness.
Why do you have so many
misunderstandings against me?
Then you shouldn't have
let me misunderstand you.
Nothing over 20,000 won. Let's go.
He must not want to buy a toy for him.
He could really not have enough money.
No way. Every toy here is over 20,000 won.
I'm sure he knows that.
He really might not know
how much they cost
if he doesn't buy toys often.
Is that so?
We can't possibly know everyone's story.
Please have a sample.
I'm sorry.
You always eat unhealthy food.
Look who's talking.
You're a picky eater, too.
I'm a reasonable picky eater.
You think you're always right.
If you keep it up, I'll scold you.
I'm serious.
Is this the wrong way?
If we circle around again,
it'll be our tenth time.
Already?
What?
Isn't that the place?
Yes, it is.
It's good news. Why are you mad?
I feel cheated. We went around the block
ten times, but it was here.
It's your fault for not spotting it.
It's not the cafe's fault.
Him and his temper.
EULJIRO
"Just like how the feelings
you didn't notice suddenly appear…"
EULJIRO WILL APPEAR WHEN YOU ARE LOST
How can you not notice your own feelings?
Shut it.
Give it back.
Or what?
Take it.
I must use violence when words don't work.
Hey.
This used to be a real printing shop.
Interesting.
By the way, that day…
"That day"? When?
If Jin-ju didn't show up,
who were you going to pick?
You?
Why?
I heard you and the CEO are dating.
Exactly, my point.
I can't let him see me like that.
You saw me that day, right?
I hid my face because I couldn't wash up.
And I was wearing an old hoodie.
I'd never let him see me like that.
Was that it?
What else could it be?
My gosh. You are…
Why won't you answer me?
Forget it.
What's gotten into him?
Wait up.
What do you want for dinner?
Pasta?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes?
Yes.
Yes, I got it. Okay.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I have to get going now.
What is it?
It's nothing. I'll call you later.
If it's nothing, tell me.
Please talk to me.
Later.
I'll call you later.
Get in. I won't ask any questions.
No need to tell me anything.
I'll go alone today.
I'm sorry. I'll call you later.
How tight-lipped she is.
Write everything down.
I want him to be punished. Okay?
-I'm sorry.
-Yeong-hui, I didn't do anything wrong.
This was the first time I hit him first.
He bullied me first.
He bullied me since middle school
because I was poor and fatherless.
-How come only I--
-Cheol-su, shut it.
I'm so sorry.
Do you think he can get away
with your apology?
How will you fix this?
Look at my son. What are you going to do?
I'm so sorry.
Bring five million won
if you want to settle.
Without that,
your brother is going to jail.
I'm sorry, Yeong-hui.
I want to tell you not to worry
and say something nice to you.
I want to buy you a bowl of rice soup
to reassure you it's okay.
But I don't think I can when
I'm about to pay her five million won.
Someone once said
in real life, poverty
doesn't mean
small, worn-down houses with bugs
or shabby clothes.
It's getting a call in the morning
about your credit card debt,
not being able to go to a dentist
when your teeth ache,
feeling guilty for failing
to take care of your loved ones,
and feeling pathetic
and scared that I have to
ask my friend for money.
JIN-JU, CAN I BORROW SOME MONEY?
That's what poverty means.
Unless you experience it, you never know.
There's no point telling anyone about it.
What are you staring at?
Namsan Tower.
Come to think of it,
I've never been to that tower.
-Not even once?
-No.
I was saving it for a special day
with someone special.
But I never went there.
Why not?
No one I met so far was that special.
You could go there with the CEO.
With the CEO?
Why does he keep going without me?
You walk like a baby giraffe.
Do you know why it's called Haebangchon?
I'm not sure.
After Korea was liberated,
people who came back from abroad
and North Koreans who fled from religious
persecution stayed here.
Hence the name.
Haebang, as in "liberation."
Isn't it sad?
Everyone wanted to be liberated,
but it didn't come in a shape
everyone was happy with.
I find that sad.
Right.
God can be mean at times.
God is mean by nature.
So you should only trust yourself.
Don't lose the talisman.
-The talisman?
-How's the compass I gave you?
I threw it away.
What?
Why did you throw it away?
It'd be ridiculous for me to hold onto it
after what happened that day.
I'm not stupid.
Why do you always hold onto bad memories?
Why do you ruin good memories?
Do you think they're beautiful memories?
To me, those memories
are painful.
I got the wrong idea.
And I got my hopes up.
Then, I got my heart broken.
Am I responsible for your feelings?
Right.
I'm a fool
who liked and hated you by myself.
I am stupid.
I didn't ask you to like me.
You're making me feel bad.
HAEBANGCHON
A PLACE WHERE THE PAST
AND THE PRESENT COEXIST
You can't just leave me like that.
Go. I have plans tonight.
You do? With who?
Are you seeing the CEO again?
Why do you care?
Goodbye, then.
We meet again.
Right. We're meeting way too often.
Move.
Can you buy me a meal?
I haven't eaten anything
because I was working all day, Mr. On.
What?
Sure.
My gosh. You don't have to.
Aren't you coming? I'll go alone, then.
Don't say anything weird to Mr. On.
That depends on you.
My gosh, that jerk.
How long have you been friends?
We're not really friends.
We just went to the same high school.
That's it. Nothing more.
I doubt that was the whole story.
We were pretty close.
Don't let your imagination run wild.
He went to the States for his studies
when he was 18.
-And we barely saw each other after that.
-But those few meetings were intense.
Woo-yeon and I have
a pretty special relationship.
Well,
I don't think it's that special.
Really?
I liked you.
I liked you as a friend.
I hope your special friendship
will continue for a long time.
Let's eat.
Take your time.
If you pull this stunt again,
you're done for.
Does everything I do
seem like a joke?
-I know it is.
-Says who?
Can't you listen to
what I have to say as it is?
No. I can't.
It's a defense mechanism.
I don't want a misunderstanding
or get hurt from false hope.
That's why I'm bound
to suspect your intention
and interpret your words differently.
This happens when you're always rejected.
What if I really have feelings for you?
Answer my question.
What if I'm serious?
What will you do?
Objects are closer than they seem
in the mirror.
So we must always prepare ourselves
for unexpected accidents.
Don't toy with me.
How would you feel
if your first love came back?
I'd be tempted.
Your first love is hard to forget.
You're only nice
when something's happened to me.
-What are you talking about?
-You haven't changed at all.
I'm not the impatient type.
But I always get impatient
in front of you.
Let's watch a musical this Saturday.
-Mom, are you crazy?
-He's not just anyone. You'll marry him.
Are you the only one in love?
Don't make me be your burden.
I don't want someone I love to suffer.
You can rely on me.
Let's not see each other after work.
I don't want to hurt him.
Why are you here?
You told me
if nothing happens, you'll date him.
Something has happened now.
Go on a date with me tomorrow.