A missed chance will turn into regret.
If I have no more chances to miss,
I should make one myself.
I'll be the one with a crush on you now.
Just like you liked me.
I'll like you longer,
and I'll like you more.
I'll be just like you.
And you can be like me.
Then just like I came to like you,
you should come to like me again.
If that's the cycle we're in,
I'll wait.
You're still so arrogant.
You are always so sure of yourself
and do whatever you want.
I'm doing that for you.
I have to be sure of myself
to win you back.
Don't.
Don't try to win me over.
I was telling you all this
not because I'll be with you,
but because I won't be.
It's already in the past.
And it's too late.
You're just giving me a headache now.
Bye.
What should I do?
You were late. You don't deserve me.
It's no big deal.
It's nothing.
But why am I crying?
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the beep.
GYEONG WOO-YEON
I couldn't reach you.
I turned my phone off.
It's okay.
How could you be okay
with something like this?
Because it's you.
If you're angry, act angry.
If you're upset, tell me about it.
Show me your feelings.
If you don't,
it will only make me feel sorry.
Everything gets better over time,
even feelings like that.
And once those feelings fade away,
other feelings will be clearer for you.
I'll try harder.
How could you try harder than this?
What are you looking for? It's late.
I can't sleep.
I want to have a cup of tea.
Sit down. I'll make it for you.
-I'll--
-Sit down. You'll only make a mess.
What's wrong?
Can you tell?
You said you couldn't sleep.
You wanted a cup of tea at this hour.
I just thought something must be wrong.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Can time make everything okay?
Will effort make things better?
Is it about work?
It could be about work or feelings.
Anything.
Effort won't betray you
except for a few things.
What's on your mind?
"This is good. I'm jealous.
I wish I was this good."
One-dimensional thoughts like that.
Someone else will be
standing in your spot soon.
In front of your pieces.
That's too far in the future for me.
I doubt it will be that far.
Metaphor Publishing House
publishes good books.
And they sell books well.
The top publishing house in the industry.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
I really like today's weather.
Then, I'll be the weather.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you slammed at work nowadays?
No. Why do you ask?
You look a bit tired.
Your face looks a bit haggard.
Or is it your liver?
Is that so?
Should I take some supplements?
Actually, my friend works
at a really good pharmaceutical company.
This supplement contains Chinese
matrimony vines, oriental raisin trees,
bee-bee trees, gardenias, turmeric,
kudzu, mugwort, and so on.
This has all the ingredients
that are good for your liver.
-Never mind.
-What?
It looks like I'm trying to sell you
this supplement.
It's okay. I'm sure you brought it
because it's good for me.
No. Pretend you didn't hear that.
I don't want to give the wrong idea
to the woman I like.
I'm almost done with the book.
Already?
I worked on it whenever I could.
I only have one area left.
But that doesn't mean I didn't do my best.
I worked so hard, my wrist hurts.
Look at this. I can't even hold my fork.
You should file a claim.
Did you pick a title?
Oh, right. Come to think of it,
I didn't pick a title yet.
Take your time.
I'm not the kind of CEO
who nags a writer who hurt her wrist.
We should pick a title for the book.
You're reading a book.
Do you like that book?
Let's only talk about work.
Okay.
It's from the last shoot.
What about the title?
Did you give it some thought?
What about you?
One Day, Seoul Becomes
a Travel Destination.
Seoul can be a travel destination
even if it's familiar to us.
Seoul is too pretty of a city
to just overlook.
Yes, it is. Very pretty.
So people can't leave.
What about you?
Any ideas for the title?
Everyday Life to You, a Trip to Me.
To you, Seoul is part of your
everyday life, but to me, it was a trip.
I like that title. I should
include this in the foreword, then.
"The moment
our everyday life feels foreign,
that foreign feeling becomes
a pleasant feeling in Seoul."
Why are you staring at me?
How can you be fine?
Do you want to be friends?
-What?
-Or
am I supposed to say okay
and start dating you
when I don't even like you?
Sounds familiar, doesn't it?
It sucks to be
on the receiving end, right?
That hurt, but I'm okay.
What choice do I have?
I know what I told you.
Treat me how I treated you.
Do you want us to be friends?
Or should I let you toy with me?
You're free to do whatever you want.
You can beat me or curse at me.
I'll do as you want.
Don't make me deal with your feelings.
They're yours. Deal with them.
And look where that got me.
Every decision I made about you was wrong.
So I'm asking you this time.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
I'm dealing with my one-sided love
as best as I can.
I'll reject all of the above.
That includes your effort and your promise
that you'll do anything I want.
I don't want to do what you did to me.
I like your title. Let's go with that.
We're done. So I'm leaving.
Will you answer my calls?
No.
You won't see me if I go see you, right?
I'll report you.
What about coincidences?
Is it okay if we meet by chance?
Coincidences are coincidences.
I don't care about you enough
to get mad at coincidences.
I guess I won't need coincidences.
A HARMLESS PERSON
-Are you okay?
-This is uncomfortable.
Not that. I was asking
about getting rejected.
It's possible for me
to not realize how I feel.
I'm such a bad guy.
Hey. Ending it like this whenever
you want isn't fair. Don't you think so?
From now on, I'll do right by you.
Can you give me one more chance?
How…
How can your one-sided love
end that quickly?
You're crazy.
I'm your father. Bye.
I knew something was odd.
She answered my call.
Did you get rejected?
-I wouldn't want to date you, either.
-Why not?
I thought he had multiple personalities.
He yelled, begged,
and suddenly tried
to convince me rationally.
Dad.
Is that why you're here?
No. I want the three of us to have
a meal before you leave Korea.
And I wanted to talk to you.
-I'm not leaving.
-You're not?
Why? Because of that girl?
Not you too, Mom.
What is it about?
You're mad whenever you see us,
aren't you?
Then yell at us whenever you see us.
As you said, it's something that happened
in the past, but it still happened.
You were deeply hurt
and you're still angry about it.
Get it off your chest.
It wasn't a big deal.
Right.
We're the ones who did wrong,
but you're paying the price.
We're sorry
for not taking care of you back then.
Why are you bringing that up now?
I don't want you to use that pain.
I'm worried that
you might pretend to be cold and mean
and turn into an awful man
to cover up the wound.
I want you to be happy.
You should also yell
and curse at me whenever you see me.
What?
You can vent out all your
bottled-up feelings about the past.
What's wrong with you?
I'm bothered that
I might turn into an awful man.
I made a lot of mistakes.
You can resent me and blame me for them.
-Come on, pay more attention.
-Am I stupid?
-Must you talk to me like that?
-How else should I do it, then?
Do I have to take care of
every little thing here?
You said you'd do everything for me.
-Why are you pissed at me?
-Because you piss me off!
What if you become like him?
-What do you mean?
-He used to run to a pharmacy
even when she got a small scratch.
But he's always irritated after marriage.
Is that what you think of me?
Relationships and love don't
start off like that.
But marriage starts off as a fairytale
and ends up like some gossip story.
What's wrong with that?
Someone I know peels shrimps
for his wife even when they're fighting.
And the wife badmouths him and says
she hates him, but she buys his underwear.
That's how they live.
I like that story.
I wish we could live like that, too.
I love you, Yeong-hui.
How much?
As much as the value of a house in Seoul.
That's way too much.
HE CAME TO THE BAKERY SINCE
HE DIDN'T HAVE ANYONE TO EAT WITH
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY FEELINGS FOR ME
IT'S RARE FOR FEELINGS TO BE MUTUAL
HE COULD HURT HER
WITHOUT EVEN LIFTING A FINGER
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT MEANT TO LOVE
I DIDN'T HAVE THE COURAGE
TO BREAK OUT OF MY SHELL
I opened this book
so I could get to know you more,
but I ended up finding my faults.
WANTING TO PROTECT SOMETHING
JUST LIKE HOW THE FEELINGS
YOU DIDN'T NOTICE SUDDENLY APPEAR…
EVERYDAY LIFE TO YOU…
You are invited to a tasting
of my new dish on Wednesday.
I'm busy.
Office workers don't make plans
on weekdays.
I'll go if Yeong-hui is coming.
Why can't anyone just say yes?
I'll see if I can make it.
This is a coincidence.
She said that was okay.
MOM
Shouldn't you be working now?
I'm taking a break.
-When are you coming home?
-I'll be late. Why?
I just wanted to know
when you were coming.
-Do you have something to say?
-Gosh, no.
Okay. Don't be too late.
Okay.
-Gosh.
-What's that?
This supplement contains Chinese
matrimony vines, oriental raisin trees,
bee-bee trees, gardenias, turmeric,
kudzu, mugwort, and so on.
These are liver supplements
that have all the good stuff.
What are you up to?
Don't take them, then.
-I was thinking about your--
-No. I'll take them.
Are they approved by the KFDA?
Sweetie, take them.
-I'm okay. Give them to your mom.
-No, you take them.
-It's okay.
-I can get some more.
What? Yes. That would be nice.
I'll be back.
What's going on with her?
-That's cool.
-Yes.
That was pretty cool.
You look pretty good right now.
I'm hanging out with my friends.
Did you eat?
Do you smell something burning?
My heart?
It's not that.
It's something else.
Hey. Fire!
-Gosh.
-There's a fire.
-Fire!
-Oh, no! What do we do?
-Open the window.
-What should we do?
-Open the window. Hurry.
-Open it.
-I'll call you later. What is it?
-Hurry.
Gosh, we almost died.
Exactly. What you did was so silly.
I wasn't being silly.
It was a cool technique.
You invited out exhausted workers
on a weekday
and made them inhale smoke?
Cut him some slack.
I'm sure he meant well.
Having good intentions is useless.
Look at what he did.
You're so mean.
Don't act so rude!
You startled me.
Where did Woo-yeon and Su go?
I'm stopping by Tonight.
Sang-hyeok asked us to taste his new dish.
-All of your friends?
-Yes.
I'm on my way to a book reading.
I won't be available during the reading,
so I wanted to listen to your voice.
I'll pick you up later. See you soon.
Okay.
Do you need to talk to me?
Yes, I have a lot to tell you.
You just won't give me the time for it.
No. I won't have time
for that again today.
I thought about why
I always made the wrong choices.
And I figured it out.
Doing my best is torturing you.
It happened in the past,
but it still happened.
Bad memories
must still be fresh in your mind.
I'm sorry for acting
like nothing happened.
I'm sorry I always made
a joke out of everything.
And I'm sorry that I'm making an effort
for my own benefit.
I just thought I should tell you that.
Maybe telling you this
is also being selfish.
Can't you just live your life?
You said you'd do what I tell you to do.
Just live a good life.
Don't let the past hold you back.
Don't try to piece back together
what's already broken.
And don't hang onto a lost cause.
I'm going to be happy from now on.
I'll pretend to do that,
but I can't promise anything.
Missed opportunities bring regrets.
And I have so many regrets.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
But at least, in front of you,
I'll pretend to be happy and doing okay.
So you should just assume that I'm happy
and doing okay.
TONIGHT
Why didn't you come in?
Just because.
Want to talk? Or should I go inside
and pretend I don't know anything?
Su likes me.
He's the one who likes you,
but why are you out here,
looking like that?
How do I look?
Like you've lost everything.
I was so sure
that this would never happen.
It was something I only wished for,
for a long time.
But not anymore?
I like Jun-su now.
Right.
Then that's great.
But why does it sound like
you're chanting a spell?
"Like him. Please learn to like him."
That's what it sounds like.
Diseases and feelings grow
when you try to cover them up.
-I got a discount, too.
-Really?
-What? What about Su?
-He left.
He didn't even say bye.
He's always like that.
He doesn't tell us anything.
He just comes and goes whenever he wants.
He does whatever he wants to do.
What happened?
Later.
Are you awake?
We're in front of your house.
Why are you here, Jun-su?
I said I'd pick you up.
Right.
Do you not remember that?
No.
Good.
Why?
If you do, you'll be embarrassed.
-Did I do something?
-You were snoring.
I was joking.
It's late. Go home and get some sleep.
You can snore all you want.
Come on.
Get home safe, Jun-su.
I love you.
I love you, Woo-yeon.
Thank you for today.
-I'm almost there.
-You're selfish to the end.
Even to this day,
you've only been thinking about yourself.
I don't care if you like me or not.
I don't care if you'll wait for me or not.
I don't care if you're happy or not.
Hey, this is Yeong-hui.
She's very drunk right now.
JUN-SU
Have you gone mad?
Woo-yeon. You…
Mr. On.
Woo-yeon is quite drunk right now.
Hey, wake up now. Wake up.
PHOTOGRAPHER LEE SU
I guess you're not confident.
When will this exhibition end?
The last day is the 17th of this month.
The photo book is scheduled
to be released next month, correct?
Yes, that's right.
-The book event hasn't been decided?
-No, sir.
Good.
Thank you.
I heard you've been seeing someone.
How did you find out?
I'll give you some privacy.
How did she know?
Don't be hard on Sang-sik.
I asked him about it.
Good. I was dying to brag about her.
-So have you changed?
-What?
You always play it safe.
You always take a step back
and wait until you get what you want.
Or hold back to protect something.
That's how you were.
I'm the same in some ways,
but different in some ways.
But I'm not sure which one is right.
The more desperate I am,
the harder it gets.
I think the exhibition is closed.
Can we come in here?
Guess the name of the building.
Metaphor Art Museum.
I'm the CEO, remember?
Gosh. You suddenly feel
so far away from me.
That's not the reaction I wanted.
"Gosh, my boyfriend is rich.
Which handbag should I ask for?"
I want you to think like that.
Should we meet at a department store
on our next date?
When should we meet tomorrow?
I was joking.
But why are we here?
Before you pick your bag,
you can pick something else first.
How long do you think
you'll need to finish the book?
Not much.
We'll be able to publish the book
next month as scheduled.
Good.
This is the best spot at this gallery.
Which piece do you want to hang
right here next month?
Why are you asking me?
Start thinking about it.
Next month, it will be your piece
that will be hung here.
For the book launch, we're going
to hold a calligraphy and photo exhibit.
I will pave the path
if your path gets rocky.
And if what you want is too far,
I will bring it to you.
I want you to take an easy path.
Am I Cinderella?
Do you want to be Aladdin? I'm your Genie.
Genie is cooler than
the silly prince who can't even recognize
the woman he loves.
Yeong-hui.
Hey. Have you worked on
wedding invitations too?
They need to be mass-produced,
so I haven't done any.
I've made a lot of postcards and cards.
Why do you ask?
Is someone getting married?
What? No. Just asking.
Anyway, I bet you had a huge fight
with your boyfriend.
With Jun-su? Why would I?
He didn't tell you?
You called your boyfriend, thought
he was Su, and said some stupid things.
What?
Is your boyfriend that kind?
Or does he not care?
How could he say nothing
after hearing all that?
I'll call you later, Yeong-hui.
Okay.
Go in.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
No.
Okay. Thank you for dropping me off.
Goodnight.
You, too.
I want to like what you like.
I should like the same things.
I'm okay. Because it's you.
There's no need to do that.
If you need anything, I'll give it to you.
I'm your Genie.
Will effort make things better?
Effort won't betray you
except for a few things.
When it comes to one's feelings
or sudden misfortunes,
effort won't be able to do anything.
Hello?
Let's meet tomorrow.
I want to talk to you.
Okay.
What kind of ring do you want?
Well, I'm going to propose
to my boyfriend.
Can I take a look at that one?
Effort won't betray us,
but
there are things that need our effort
and things that don't.
HAPJEON UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
It's gastric cancer.
For instance,
misfortunes that we cannot avoid
or one's feelings.
I could've come to you.
I thought
I should be the one coming to you.
I ordered coffee for us.
There are too many reasons
why I should like you.
But even when I think about those reasons,
I can't fall in love.
Is it you who's unable to love?
Or are you just unable to love me?
It hurts to be considerate.
I'm sorry.
Your words hurt me even more.
And holding back doesn't?
Why won't you tell me
what's going on, Jun-su?
Why do you always hold back?
You should have gotten mad when I
called you, mistaking you for another man.
You should've resented me.
You should've criticized me.
How could I do that? I was worried
that you'd leave me if I did.
I knew that you didn't love me
and that you hadn't gotten over him.
So I tried my best.
I thought I could be patient
and you would eventually love me
if I wait for you.
Couldn't you have considered my feelings?
You could have given me time to think.
I needed time to consider
what could happen in the future.
Why would you need to do that?
Why torture yourself
over something so obvious?
No matter how hard you try,
you feel insecure,
so you hold back your feelings.
You'd lose yourself in this relationship.
That's not a good relationship.
So
let's break up.
I'm sorry.
The lethargy that comes from
realizing that your effort was futile
destroys us in the end.
The downside of making an effort.
Will you hold back again?
But you have the right to be mad.
I'll try harder.
How could you try harder than this?
What? Did Woo-yeon say that she likes me?
You…
You won't get a pass the second time.
I don't care how she feels.
You can't date her.
She can date anyone but you.
You have no right to decide that!
You made her cry for ten years.
You don't even know
how to appreciate love like that.
Now, I do.
So I'll start liking her back from now on.
Excuse me.
What are you two doing?
-Woo-yeon.
I don't even feel bad for you anymore.
What is this?
You guys aren't kids anymore.
Your lips are busted.
Jun-su, you've been sparring
for ten years.
You can't beat people up.
Gosh. A boxer beat me up?
So this wasn't just an assault.
This is a special case.
My dad is a lawyer.
It's my fault.
Hey, I'm hurt, too.
But you can move your lips fine.
Talk about playing favorites.
Don't you have a conscience?
You and Jun-su aren't the same.
You're not him.
It hurts.
I want to stop being in bad relationships.
Either I get hurt
or end up hurting someone else.
Being in such relationships
isn't good for me.
It's too painful. I can't do it.
So I can't date either of you.
I mean, I won't.
You can call me a bitch
or resent me for being selfish.
I don't care.
Do you remember what I said?
I'm responsible for my own feelings.
I'll aggressively cling onto you
or come see you with excuses.
I will go to you.
I'll wait.
As long as you come back to me,
I'll wait without any complaints.
Suit yourselves.
I'm done with both of you.
I cherish myself more than anyone.
ONE MONTH LATER
A PLACE WHERE THE PAST
AND THE PRESENT COEXIST
WE STILL SURVIVE
EVERYDAY LIFE TO YOU, TRIP TO ME
WANTING TO PROTECT SOMETHING
JUST LIKE FEELINGS YOU DIDN'T NOTICE
SUDDENLY APPEARING
YOU FIND THEM
WHEN YOU FOCUS ON YOUR JOURNEY
How beautiful.
What did you buy this time?
My book will be published soon.
So I'm giving myself a present.
BE SUCCESSFUL, GYEONG WOO-YEON
My gosh. This is amazing.
Aren't you going to date anyone?
You've only been working these days.
No, I'm not.
Did you break up with them both?
I broke up with one.
I wasn't dating the other one.
What about the love letter guy?
He said he'd wait. Did he give up?
It's only been a month.
I told him not to wait.
Did you go through my room?
You should've cleaned it yourself, then.
Do you want to eat, sleep, and work
in that mess of yours?
Yes. I'll eat, sleep, work, and die there.
Gosh. Men will stop chasing her
once they see that nasty temper of hers.
You don't get to say that.
She reminds me of you when you were young.
A HARMLESS PERSON
I'LL BE TRAVELING FOR A WHILE
I ALWAYS THOUGHT PEOPLE DISAPPOINTED ME
BUT I DISAPPOINTED THEM
BEING AN EMPTY SHELL MADE
PEOPLE WHO LOVE ME TURN AWAY
I'll be traveling for a while.
I'll be somewhere in Korea.
I'll only be a phone call away.
If I stay here, I might bother you again.
I said I'd wait, so I'll wait quietly.
You can drunk dial me
or call me because you miss me.
She hasn't called me once for a month.
It feels like it's really over.
I opened this book
so I could get to know you more,
but I ended up finding my faults.
The sentences I underlined
have also been mistakes.
Mr. On. I informed the photographer
and the writer about
the calligraphy and photo exhibit.
As you said, we made
ample space for the calligraphy
so all the attention
doesn't go to the photos.
What's bothering you?
I don't want to work with a foolish CEO.
Bring me your resignation letter, then.
Hey, aren't you even mad?
Why go out of your way for your ex?
We didn't break up.
She said it was over
and won't answer your calls.
You can't even ask how she's doing.
That's called a breakup.
When writers are stuck,
they pause or start over.
They take a break.
That's what this is.
If she starts over,
would it be the same story?
Yes, as long as the intention is the same.
EVERYDAY LIFE TO YOU, TRIP TO ME
Whatever.
Give this to her.
And bring her news back?
You can't change jobs.
-Why?
-You know me so well.
You're incredibly frustrating. Gosh.
Mr. On wanted me to give you this.
I see.
EVERYDAY LIFE TO YOU, TRIP TO ME
Did you get the text about the exhibit?
-Yes.
-You're coming, right?
Will Mr. On be there, too?
That was the whole purpose.
You should still come.
I should go. It's work.
You must think I'm brazen.
As an editor,
I'm grateful for your attitude.
But as his friend, I kind of hate you.
He's a mess right now.
I know you're not to blame.
Sorry for being nosy.
It's okay.
I'm done here. So I'll get going.
See you at the exhibit.
EVERYDAY LIFE TO YOU, TRIP TO ME
WRITTEN AND CALLIGRAPHED
BY GYEONG WOO-YEON
Gosh. Now that the exhibit is set up,
I can see that the photos and calligraphy
go really well together.
-It's nice.
-You really have discerning eyes.
SEONGSU-DONG
WANTING TO PROTECT SOMETHING
WE STILL SURVIVE
You must feel awkward
since we haven't talked for a month.
A bit.
Congratulations on your first exhibit.
Thank you.
It took me a month to find an excuse.
What do you think?
HAEBANGCHON, SEOCHON
WE STILL SURVIVE
AS A PHASE ENDS, ANOTHER PHASE BEGINS
YOU CAN START OVER WHEN ABANDONED
Effort won't betrays us,
but
there are things that need an effort
and things that don't.
Our feelings
would be one example.
-You're here, Mr. Lee.
-Hi. Thank you for your help.
What will happen to us
when we're faced with
the result of futile effort?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
Pardon? What do you mean?
Oh, that?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT TO WOO-YEON?
People can't see things
that are too close.
Look. If you look at a mirror like this,
you can't see anything.
Plus, you're the closest to yourself.
I misunderstood my own feelings.
There are no misunderstandings now.
BUT THAT SHIP HAS SAILED
If Woo-yeon is a ship that has already
sailed, I'll swim until I catch up.
SAY SOMETHING TO HER
Woo-yeon,
you are bound to come back to me.
-So you'll keep liking Woo-yeon?
-Of course!
Mr. On!
She'd better come back to me.
I let it slide last night
because you two were totally wasted.
This better be the last time.
-Woo-yeon.
Something is off.
He won't answer my calls.
And he quit the cafe, too.
Of course. You're my everything…
Why would you pine over someone like him?
You're too good for him.
You know nothing.
Hello. I'm Gyeong Woo-yeon.
-Who is she?
-The girl I like.