♪Fly high, spread your wings♪
♪I'm no longer who I was♪
♪Who isn't♪
♪Wishing to break free?♪
♪No surrender in the flames♪
♪Burn me♪
♪Flowers shining in the sky♪
♪At 68 degrees♪
♪Watch me fiercely take the streets♪
♪The hummers moving forward♪
♪Never turns back♪
♪Running like a bullet♪
♪Every second, smiling and saying♪
♪Get ready♪
♪The retreating hummers♪
♪Prefers to break at dawn♪
♪If needed, then they will♪
♪Fly very high♪
♪Confronting the earth-shaking♪
♪Sweeping beams of light♪
♪The battle rages on♪
=Sisters in Arms=
=Episode 23=
Captain Zhu, the result of
Fenghuang Village case is out.
Lu Xiaoying's drugs
are purer than Zhou Yan's.
The composition is similar,
but the quality is better.
Okay, I got it.
Dajun.
Captain Zhu,
we've searched the beauty salon.
A large amount of drugs were found.
They hid the drugs
inside the boxes of beauty products.
Everything was seized.
But Captain Zhu,
the front desk told me
Ai Lian went out of town
two days ago.
Did you alarm her?
No.
I had them talk on the phone.
She said everything
was operating normally.
She might come back in a few days.
Okay.
Captain Zhu.
Chen Yan spoke.
Let's go.
Wish I could stay another day.
I didn't stay long enough.
Stay one more day,
and you'll eat all the chicken
and duck of their house.
Still hasn't had it enough.
You ate too much.
After breakfast,
go to the basement.
I'll be leaving soon too.
During this time,
be careful.
Don't use that secret passage.
It doesn't feel safe.
I've thought about it.
We can't stay long in Binjiang.
When we have enough money,
we'll leave together.
Really?
You've figured it out?
I have.
For Yun'er,
I can't be so willful.
That's right.
Why are you going against money?
Isn't that right?
Besides, in my line of work,
it's always dangerous.
If I die,
my money
will be your money.
What are you trying to say?
Ai Lian.
Only I in this world
know your dark past.
So if I die,
you can take my money
and live a carefree life
with your beloved Yun'er.
Isn't that what you want?
I'm not wrong, am I?
It's simple.
As long as I
drink this cup of milk,
it will come true.
This is what I found in your bag.
Don't tell me this is white sugar.
Yun'er,
turn your head a little.
Looks great.
Even has a beauty filter.
Really beautiful.
You have no right
to decide when it ends.
If it's going to end,
it will end in my hands.
Drink it.
This is your punishment.
Ai Lian,
I've only loved you in my whole life.
If you die,
I...
You taught me
don't put all the eggs in one basket.
Did you
ever
love me?
People like us
don't deserve to talk about love.
You're right.
People like us
don't
deserve it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I think I saw my mom.
(Yun'er)
Mom.
Mom, are you inside?
- Mom.
- Yun'er.
- Ai Lian.
- Captain Ye.
Officer An.
What are you doing here?
We were just passing by.
Tata and the others went out to play,
and brought me along.
Mom, why are you here?
This is my friend's home.
Came to check it out.
Don't stand outside.
Come in for some water, and we can chat
or eat something.
Thank you for taking
such good care of Yun'er.
Come in, come in.
No, no need.
It's getting late,
we should head down the mountain.
Yun'er, are you staying with your mom
or coming with us?
You guys go ahead, Tata.
I'll stay and keep my mom company.
Alright, we'll go first.
Okay, take it easy on the way.
- Alright, alright.
- Bye.
Bye.
Alright, see you.
- Text me when you arrive.
- Okay.
- Bye, Tata.
- Bye.
Bye.
Mom, it's so good to see you here.
Mom, why are your hands so cold?
Are you cold?
Let's go inside.
It's cold outside.
Mom.
Whose house is this?
Why have I never been here before?
Yun'er.
Mom.
Who is he?
Why is he lying there?
He's a friend of mine.
A friend of yours?
Yun'er.
Let's go home.
We'll come back another day.
Yun'er.
Don't shout.
Mom.
What happened to him?
Don't lie to me.
What happened?
It was me.
I killed him.
Yun'er.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid. Don't worry.
Don't ask anything right now.
I will explain it to you later.
Don't be afraid.
I need to think of a way
to get rid of him.
Yun'er.
Go away.
Mom.
You can't move him by yourself.
Ai Lian said that,
selling out this batch of goods,
they won't supply anymore.
(Interrogation Room)
But not long after,
she contacted me again
and told me they had enough supply.
I knew they must have a place
for making drugs.
Where is the production site?
How could I know?
I know
Ai Lian goes to a place
every so often.
I followed her once.
She drove all the way
to Feiyun Mountain.
But she was very cautious.
When the car reached
halfway of the mountain,
it stopped for over an hour.
I thought,
she must have noticed me.
What happened next?
I feared her revenge.
So I stopped following her.
Where is that place exactly?
It's near Fengwu Village.
Fengwu Village?
Director Zhou.
There is probably
a drug manufacturing den
in Fengwu Village, Feiyun Mountain.
We are leaving immediately.
I request police support.
Yes.
Captain.
I feel like something's not right.
What's wrong?
Yun'er said her mom
was on a business.
How could she be at Feiyun Mountain?
Director Zhou.
Are you still at Fengwu Village?
We're heading down the mountain.
Don't leave.
Huaiyang suspects
there's a drug manufacturing den.
They are on their way up the mountain.
You can join forces
with the Anti-narcotics Brigade.
The break is over.
Vehicles and equipment
are already on their way.
Yes, Hummer Commandos is on it.
Tang Xin, turn around.
Yes.
(Ai Lian, suspected of
drug manufacturing and trafficking)
Captain.
What happened?
Chen Yun'er's mother
is under drug investigation.
We need to assist in the arrest.
Fengwu Village may also have
a drug manufacturing den.
Let's go back to where
we dropped off Chen Yun'er.
Yes.
Get ready for action.
- Yes.
Yes.
Yun'er.
I knew
this day was bound to come.
What I fear the most
is this day.
I even wake up from my dreams.
It must be God
punishing me.
Yun'er.
What I fear the most
is you seeing all of this.
I'm not a good person.
I opened the beauty salon,
but it's just a cover.
It was just to make it easier for him
to traffic drugs.
I've done too many bad things.
I'm beyond saving.
But Yun'er,
I really want to
give you a clean life.
I wanted to take you abroad
to get away from all of this.
But he,
he has been
pressuring me these days.
He won't let us leave.
He even threatened me with your safety.
So I killed him.
I couldn't let him destroy you too.
I had to do this.
I could only do this.
Yun'er,
this is the path I chose.
I don't have the right to regret.
I'm just worried about you.
No.
I have to send you away.
Get in the car.
It's Ai Lian.
Captain, what should we do?
It's fine, she won't escape.
Roadblocks everywhere.
What's the situation?
We've already located Ai Lian.
On our way.
Go.
Leave Binjiang.
That's what I was thinking.
No one will ever know
what I've done.
But now,
it's too late.
You've known
and you've been dragged into this.
How could I let you
bear my sins?
I can't watch my daughter
worrying for me.
I can't let that happen.
Absolutely not.
Report, report.
(Command Center)
Suspicious vehicle pivoted
at village entrance, headed uphill.
It turned east.
Captain Ye.
The suspicious vehicle is heading east.
Alright, we got it.
Let's drive east.
Yes.
Yun'er.
Listen to me.
This happened too suddenly.
I don't have any other plans now.
I just want to send you away.
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow I'll turn myself in.
You are innocent.
You don't need to worry.
In the future,
cut off all contact with me.
Change your name
and start a new life.
Yes.
Just like that.
Yun'er.
Did you hear me?
Did you hear
what I just said to you?
Yun'er.
Did you hear me?
So fast.
(Yun'er)
(Tata)
Captain.
Do you think Yun'er knows
about what Ai Lian did?
If she didn't know,
she wouldn't be acting like this now.
Tata.
You must remember,
you are a police officer.
You can't be swayed
by personal emotions.
Understood.
Captain.
This is in the direction
of the second floor.
We'll be there soon.
What do they want?
They probably know they can't escape,
so they're trying to stall for time.
- Hello.
- Captain Ye.
The needed equipment
arrived at the assigned site.
We'll join Anti-narcotics Brigade
to arrest drug dealers.
We won't wait for you.
Alright, thank you.
Mom.
If the police catch you,
will you die?
If I die, I die.
You can't get involved.
But I've already been dragged into this.
(Hummer Commandos)
(Police)
What is this?
A bomb.
In this situation,
we can only escape.
Take the secret passage.
If the police catch up,
we have a bomb.
That gives us a chance.
How long to exit
through the secret passage?
At most half an hour.
(Surveillance)
It's too late.
Yun'er, Yun'er.
What are you doing?
Mom, you go first.
I'll buy some time.
No way.
We either go together,
or I'll turn myself in.
Mom.
You either leave now,
or
I'll detonate the bomb.
We'll die together.
(Sniffer Dog)
Open the car.
How's inside?
Captain Zhu, we checked.
They're not inside.
There's no back door.
I think there should be a secret door.
Otherwise, they wouldn't
disappear like this.
Do you think
the drug manufacturing den is here?
Even if it's not here,
we still have to check everywhere.
Dajun,
take the sniffer dog to recheck.
Yes, Captain Zhu. Let's go.
Oh, by the way,
we saw two servings of breakfast
on the table earlier.
But Chen Yun'er
had breakfast with us.
So that means
- there was a third person.
- Yes.
Captain.
We found something.
There's a man's clothing under the bed.
It should be Wu's.
Wu?
Yes.
Wu's real name
is Gao Jianwu.
We've been investigating him.
After finding
Ai Lian was a drug trafficker,
all the details matched.
You mean
they know each other?
Yes, they used to date.
Later, Wu went out to work,
and never came back.
Ai Lian married Chen Yuanhang then.
Life was always tough for her.
But after the divorce,
she received a large sum of money
and opened a beauty salon.
The drugs she sold
were Wu's.
There are two bombs here.
One is real,
and one is fake.
Do you know which one is real?
We're running out of time, Mom.
Just put one on me.
Hurry and leave.
Hurry, Mom, there's really no time left.
Mom, hurry up.
They're coming.
Captain Zhu,
the sniffer dog didn't react.
This shouldn't be the drug den
we're looking for.
Alright.
This is on you. Let's go.
Okay.
Captain, there's a situation.
(Policewoman's Mini-Class)
(Methamphetamine)
One year.
(3 grams)
Seven years.
(10 grams)
15 years.
(50 grams)
Life sentence.
(100 grams)
(200 grams)
Death sentence.
♪Wear a smile to hide sorrow♪
♪Everyone's life is a tale of weariness♪
♪Tears that won't flow,
dust that won't clear♪
♪Every story has its imperfections♪
♪Chasing the wind,
soaring high without regrets♪
♪In the end, earning an invisible trophy♪
♪Living freely, living purely♪
♪Life is but a dance of asking and giving♪
♪If you face it bravely,
there's no need for shame♪
♪Everyone has their own shining moment♪
♪The scenery is intriguing,
but the end is the same♪
♪Waiting is truly precious♪
♪Face it bravely,
and regrets will naturally fade♪
♪Embrace the gifts of time♪
♪Why not journey together
through the ups and downs?♪
♪Together, enjoy
the gentle breeze and soft clouds♪