♪Fly high, spread your wings♪
♪I'm no longer who I was♪
♪Who isn't♪
♪Wishing to break free?♪
♪No surrender in the flames♪
♪Burn me♪
♪Flowers shining in the sky♪
♪At 68 degrees♪
♪Watch me fiercely take the streets♪
♪The hummers moving forward♪
♪Never turns back♪
♪Running like a bullet♪
♪Every second, smiling and saying♪
♪Get ready♪
♪The retreating hummers♪
♪Prefers to break at dawn♪
♪If needed, then they will♪
♪Fly very high♪
♪Confronting the earth-shaking♪
♪Sweeping beams of light♪
♪The battle rages on♪
=Sisters in Arms=
=Episode 13=
Why does he look so familiar?
What's going on here?
Sorry, I didn't know it was you.
I thought you were a bad person.
- It's fine.
- Who is it?
Isn't this the guy you hit that day?
The blind date?
The blank sheet of paper.
Do you remember?
(Emergency Response Training Base)
This is for you.
What is this?
Peach blossoms.
The peach tree beams so red,
how brilliant are its flowers!
Stop.
Wait a moment.
You don't like the Book of Songs?
Let me put it more simply then.
Miss Liu Danyang,
since we last met,
my mom has
introduced me to many other girls.
But every time I meet with them,
your image keeps popping up in my mind.
I just can't stop thinking about you.
After seriously thinking it through,
I realized
the person I'm looking for
has to be someone like you.
Pure,
straightforward, with principles.
So,
after endless thinking,
I think
you can be with me.
No, no.
Uh...
Your name is...
Eric.
Mr. Eric,
I think
you seem to have
a misunderstanding about us.
Yes, there's a misunderstanding.
No,
to be precise,
it's my fault.
Your emergency response
was no problem.
It actually proves
your high moral standards.
You won't easily let others
take advantage of you.
Why do I always want to hit you
as soon as I see you?
Danyang.
I oppose violence,
but I can accept diversity in things.
Maybe,
this is just your way
of expressing emotions.
If you want to
express emotions this way,
I can exercise
and spar with you.
Come, hit me.
Hit me.
Danyang, hit me.
Danyang, come on.
- Okay, I will.
- Hit me.
- Calm down.
- Is there a problem?
Song Tiancheng.
Tiancheng.
We are colleagues.
Do me a favor.
No.
You guys...
He...
My boyfriend.
No way.
You're so violent.
Who else
could accept you except me?
Good girls are like this.
They're fierce to boys
who don't concern them,
but sweet to
their boyfriends.
Understand?
Really sweet.
Danyang.
If you don't want to be with me,
you don't have to find
someone like this to anger me.
He dislikes you.
We're getting married.
Stop bothering Danyang.
Leave.
No way.
I don't believe it.
A quick rescue, thanks.
Mission complete. See you.
Let me treat you to a meal, bye.
- Nice job, Danyang.
- Come clean.
- Tying the knot?
- What's your relationship?
What?
It's fake.
- What?
- You were holding hands.
Take it away, take it away.
We're getting married.
I think it's not bad.
I can't take it anymore.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Who wants it?
I don't want it.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
You're early. Good.
Thank you for coming today.
Yun'er will be very happy to know.
That's very kind of you.
We rarely come to watch
dance performances.
It's really an honor.
She must be dumbfounded this time.
She didn't even get a ranking.
How embarrassing.
You underestimate Chen Yun'er too much.
What's the big deal?
She's not just anyone.
Fang Fang.
Forget it, don't tell Yun'er.
This way.
Okay.
Yun'er, look who's here.
Mom, Fang Fang, Sister, you're all here.
Yun'er.
You're amazing.
You danced so well.
You danced great.
Thank you, Tata.
We all think you danced really well.
But your leg injury isn't healed yet.
Mom, you don't have to comfort me.
I lost. Don't worry.
I'm okay with it.
In life, there are many things
worth thinking about.
I shouldn't dwell on the past.
I should look forward.
That's the right thing to do.
That's the right way to think.
- Keep it up.
- Keep it up, keep it up.
♪Give me care and concern♪
♪Let me learn to believe♪
♪Everything we have is hard-earned♪
♪Love is selfless giving♪
♪Let me continue my dream♪
♪Life is full of adventure♪
♪I won't hesitate♪
♪The tears the years take away♪
♪Leave endless beauty♪
♪I'll always survive and be grateful♪
- Hello.
Huaiyang.
Are you coming home today?
Yes.
Then tell me where you are.
I'll pick you up on the way.
No need.
Go back by yourself.
Rest first. Don't wait for me.
I'll be back soon.
Alright.
I'll wait for you at home.
Okay, see you then.
Bye.
- Take care.
- Okay.
You don't need to see us off.
Okay, take care.
- Bye, bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Goodbye, Tata.
Take care of your leg.
Okay, I will. Bye.
You seem to really admire Officer An.
After I left,
did you change your mind?
What, is that not okay?
Of course, it's not okay.
I want to become a strong,
brave girl like her.
Luckily, Song Tiancheng
showed up in time.
Otherwise,
Danyang would be off the market today.
I was scared.
Does this count as a hero
saving the beauty?
I'm not sure about the beauty part.
But the hero part,
he's definitely heroic.
Danyang, don't be humble.
You're so beautiful.
I'm trying to be.
But becoming beautiful
is so troublesome.
It isn't troublesome.
Do you really like Song Tiancheng?
Nonsense.
Don't move, don't move.
♪Get used to wearing a smile♪
♪To cover up the sorrow♪
♪Whose life is not♪
♪Full of exhaustion♪
♪Tears that can't flow♪
♪Dust that can't be wiped away♪
♪Every story♪
♪Isn't perfect♪
♪If we can face it bravely♪
♪There's no need to feel ashamed♪
♪Everyone has their
own unique brilliance♪
♪Scenery that's worth pondering♪
♪But different paths
lead to the same destination♪
♪Waiting is precious♪
Nana.
Nana!
I know I was wrong this time.
Please give me another chance, okay?
Please open the door.
Luo Zhongliang,
sign the divorce agreement.
Stop bothering me.
Nana.
This time I was out of my mind, but...
But a child can't grow up
without a father.
Now you realize you're the father?
You had to wait for a paternity test
and for this to escalate to a divorce.
It's all because of you.
Nana, please give me
another chance, okay?
Nana, I beg you, Nana.
We can't go back.
Go.
Babe.
Nana.
Nana, what's wrong with the baby?
Is he crying?
Nana.
Nana, Nana.
Don't come closer.
Nana.
It's all my fault.
I was wrong.
Please forgive me, Nana.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Enough, enough. Get up.
Have you forgiven me?
Don't do this.
Nana.
Have you forgiven me?
Now that it's come to this,
we can't go back.
For the sake of the baby,
let's part on good terms.
Isn't that better?
For the sake of the baby,
we shouldn't separate.
We should stay together as a family.
Do you think my dad
opposed us being together
because you were poor?
It's because your overthinking.
You're insecure.
You're mentally unhealthy.
I know
you've been good to me.
But that kind of goodness
puts so much pressure on me.
A normal marriage
shouldn't be like this.
I can change.
I really can.
I know I shouldn't have
treated you like that.
This is the end for us.
Nana.
Can I hold the baby one more time?
This should be
the last time I hold him.
Okay?
Babe.
Do you know who I am?
I'm your dad.
Babe.
Do you miss me?
I promise you,
I'll never leave you
this lifetime.
Zhongliang.
Give me the baby.
Don't...
Zhongliang.
Don't make me hate you forever.
Nana.
Without the baby
and you,
what's the point of my life?
You
and the baby,
that's what makes a complete family.
Give him to me, Zhongliang.
Please, Zhongliang.
Give me the baby.
I can't live without the baby.
- Give him to me, please.
- Nana.
Nana, get up, Nana.
Give me the baby.
Nana.
Get up, Nana.
The baby.
Give me the baby.
Luo Zhongliang!
- Nana, we've come to get you.
- Mom, Dad.
He's going to take my baby.
- Don't come closer. Don't push me.
- Luo Zhongliang, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- I'd rather we die together!
Don't come closer.
Dad!
Luo, don't. You'll scare the baby.
Luo Zhongliang, calm down.
Give me the baby.
He can't live without a father.
But he also can't live without a mother!
You're right.
He can't live without a mother.
That's what makes a complete family.
Let's go, let's go.
- Nana, Nana.
- Dad.
- Luo Zhongliang.
- Hurry, Nana.
- What are you doing?
- Nana.
Dad!
Mom!
Hurry.
Nana! Luo Zhongliang,
what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Nana.
- Stop, stop.
- Luo Zhongliang, stop.
- Nana.
- Stop, stop.
Hurry, call the police.
Hummer Commandos, attention.
A knife conflict has occurred
in Building 2, Tiantian Village.
The suspect has taken
a woman and child hostage.
They got into a Hyundai sedan.
Plate number: HAC64570.
They're currently heading east
on Yingbin Avenue.
Please proceed.
Copy that.
Nana, don't be afraid.
Don't touch me!
Follow the car ahead.
Nana, hold on tight, Nana.
Captain, should we intercept?
There's a child in the car.
Don't get too close.
I'm afraid the suspect
might act aggressively.
Just follow it.
Got it.
Get out of the way!
He's losing control of his emotions.
He might hurt the baby.
Discontinue pursuit.
Keep a safe distance.
Execute Plan B.
Keep a distance. Don't disturb him.
Got it.
Attention, all departments.
Suspect's identity confirmed.
(Personal Information)
He's Luo Zhongliang.
No criminal record.
He was suspicious
that the child wasn't his,
and is currently in a divorce
with his wife, Li Na.
Luo Zhongliang?
Not that Luo Zhongliang, right?
It really is him.
The records show
they've already done a paternity test.
The child is indeed Luo Zhongliang's.
He is now seeking reconciliation,
but hasn't succeeded.
Xin, go faster.
The signal is lost.
Okay.
Nana.
Don't touch me.
Nana, you don't have to be afraid of me.
How could I hurt you and the baby?
You two are my life.
Back then, I pointed a knife at you
because I had no choice.
I had no choice.
They wouldn't let you
and the baby go with me.
How did it come to this?
I only made one mistake.
Can't you give me another chance?
Luo Zhongliang?
This is Captain Ye Zhen
from Hummer Commandos.
Do you remember me?
Captain Ye, I'm Nana.
Nana.
Put the speaker on.
I need to talk to Luo Zhongliang.
Luo Zhongliang.
From what I remember,
you were very considerate towards Li Na.
You were a good husband.
Why are you doing this?
They forced me.
They want to tear our family apart.
Do you really care about your son?
Of course, he's my child,
my own flesh and blood.
He has my blood running through him.
Babe.
Babe, stop crying.
Why is the baby crying so much?
Is he hungry?
Did you feed him?
No.
The bottle is at home.
He was born not long ago, right?
What's his name?
His name is Luo Tianyou.
We all call him Babe.
Tianyou, that's a good name.
Luo Zhongliang, how about
you pull over for a moment.
I'll send someone with some formula.
He can't go hungry for too long.
I'm not stopping!
Officer Ye, do you think I'm stupid?
If I stop the car,
you'll take me away,
and I'll never see Nana
and the baby again.
You're mistaken.
I'm thinking for the baby's sake.
Listen to how hard he is crying.
His throat is nearly hoarse.
I'm not listening.
I'm not listening. I'm not listening.
- Go away!
- Luo Zhongliang.
Captain, they've turned
onto a small road.
Nana.
Let go of me!
Zhongliang, please.
Let us go.
Nana.
Do you still not believe me?
In your heart, I'm no longer
part of your family, right?
Am I that terrifying?
I don't know.
You've changed.
I don't even recognize you anymore.
What did I do wrong?
Huh?
Why does everyone treat me like this?
Why?
All I wanted was a family.
I just wanted us to be together forever.
Why is it so hard?
Why is it so difficult?
You want to take care of us
and make it up to us.
But the reality is,
the police car is chasing us,
and the baby hasn't even been fed.
Is this the life you wanted?
According to the info,
Luo Zhongliang is an abandoned child.
He grew up in an orphanage
and has a low education.
He dropped out of high school
and has worked in
various car repair shops.
Never stayed in one place
for more than a year.
Three years ago, he married Li Na,
and has staying at a car repair shop
until now.
Looking at it now,
Binjiang must be the place
he's stayed the longest in recent years.
How could parents
abandon their own child?
Children like him
must grow up feeling insecure.
That's why, he's so insecure
with Li Na
and reacts so extremely.
Tata, haven't you found them yet?
Not yet.
There's still some obstruction.
Captain, I've found them.
Xin, turn right
at the intersection ahead.
Okay.
Where are you taking us?
I'm taking you away from here
to start over.
Where exactly are you taking us?
I'm taking you both
back home.
Captain.
Nothing.
We've checked the surroundings.
No suspicious leads found.
Captain.
Information from the welfare house.
(Binjiang Police System)
Luo Zhongliang was adopted twice
between the ages of 7 and 13.
But for some reason, he secretly ran back
to the welfare house
within six months each time.
The first time he ran back
from the adoptive family,
he wasn't taken back.
But the second time he ran back,
he was taken back
by the adoptive family.
Could it be that he went
to the welfare house?
No way.
The second year after
Luo Zhongliang was adopted,
the welfare house
had already relocated.
The original location
had been abandoned.
Luo Zhongliang's spent his whole life
searching for a home.
He can't go back to the home
in Binjiang anymore.
Luo, check the surveillance
near the old site
of Sunshine Welfare House.
I suspect he went back there.
Okay.
Two adoptions,
and he ran away both times.
Luo Zhongliang's adoption experiences
must have been really unhappy.
Maybe so.
Let's go.
(Binjiang Armed Patrol)
(Liucheng Bus Stop)
(Integrated Police Communication System)
Captain Ye, you were right.
Luo Zhongliang did go
to the welfare house.
He got off the bus with Li Na
and the child at Liucheng Bus Stop.
That's only 400 meters away
from old Sunshine Welfare House site.
(Police, Binjiang)
Director Chen from
the welfare house is on the line.
I remember Luo Zhongliang.
He was a very kind child
but also an extremely sensitive one.
Has he gotten into any trouble?
Director,
I'm not free to discuss the case.
But could you tell me more
about Luo Zhongliang's background?
You know that
he ran away from his
adoptive families twice, right?
Yes.
Was it because they treated him badly?
Of course not.
Every child
hopes in their heart
that one day their real family
will come to find them,
and then everything will be okay again.
But
Luo Zhongliang never had such hopes.
He never believed
that anyone could truly love him.
He kept denying himself,
while constantly trying
to comfort himself.
Again and again,
tormenting himself.
(Sunshine Children's Welfare House)
(Do Not Enter)
Where is this place?
This is the place where I grew up.
(Do Not Enter)
(Eagle Soars, Heart Runs Free)
(Sunshine Children's Welfare House)
Welcome home.
Before I met you,
this was my home.
It was small and shabby,
but it was warm.
(Kindergarten Health Education Bulletin)
Especially Director Chen,
she was like my mother.
She gave me my name.
So, how is it, Nana?
Do you like it?
When I was a child,
there was a voice kept telling me
that I had to live the way others liked,
so I wouldn't be abandoned
and disliked.
But I was so worthless.
I didn't know how to
get along with others
until I met you.
The first time I saw you,
I just knew you were my family.
Really.
Every day I spent with you,
I felt so at ease.
I even felt like
I could be like normal people,
having a happy family.
I didn't expect
you would really agree to marry me.
That moment, I was really so happy.
I felt like I was
the happiest person in the world.
Even if I had to die right now,
I'd still feel it was worth it.
Babe,
I hope so much
that you will be luckier than me.
I hope you have a happy family.
But like me,
you have a painful childhood.
You have such a terrible father.
Nana,
I am truly happy now.
I have you.
I also have someone
who is blood-related to me.
(Eagle Soars, Heart Runs Free)
(Binjiang Armed Patrol)
(Police)
Everyone, pay attention.
We cannot yet determine
Luo Zhongliang's mental state.
The child is our primary safety concern.
Do not act rashly.
Prepare for both possibilities.
Tata, find a sniper position
and focus on observation.
Report any updates to me.
Yes.
(Policewoman's Mini-Class)
Love and control
sometimes seem indistinguishable.
Both want to completely
occupy the other
and never be apart.
Once lost,
there's a piercing pain.
Whether it's kinship,
love, or friendship,
when you put someone above all else
and see them as your entire life,
living only for them,
extreme choices will keep happening.
Love is not obsession.
♪Wear a smile to hide sorrow♪
♪Everyone's life is a tale of weariness♪
♪Tears that won't flow,
dust that won't clear♪
♪Every story has its imperfections♪
♪Chasing the wind,
soaring high without regrets♪
♪In the end, earning an invisible trophy♪
♪Living freely, living purely♪
♪Life is but a dance of asking and giving♪
♪If you face it bravely,
there's no need for shame♪
♪Everyone has their own shining moment♪
♪The scenery is intriguing,
but the end is the same♪
♪Waiting is truly precious♪
♪Face it bravely,
and regrets will naturally fade♪
♪Embrace the gifts of time♪
♪Why not journey together
through the ups and downs?♪
♪Together, enjoy
the gentle breeze and soft clouds♪