♪Fly high, spread your wings♪
♪I'm no longer who I was♪
♪Who isn't♪
♪Wishing to break free?♪
♪No surrender in the flames♪
♪Burn me♪
♪Flowers shining in the sky♪
♪At 68 degrees♪
♪Watch me fiercely take the streets♪
♪The hummers moving forward♪
♪Never turns back♪
♪Running like a bullet♪
♪Every second, smiling and saying♪
♪Get ready♪
♪The retreating hummers♪
♪Prefers to break at dawn♪
♪If needed, then they will♪
♪Fly very high♪
♪Confronting the earth-shaking♪
♪Sweeping beams of light♪
♪The battle rages on♪
=Sisters in Arms=
=Episode 18=
Wu, Ms. Wang,
come give me a hand.
Why are you so late?
(Monitor)
There's too much cargo.
My back is about to break.
Alright, be careful.
Don't fall down.
Sorry about that.
Don't move.
Listen up,
do as I say
and no one will get hurt.
What do you want?
Take me to the finance office
and give me 500,000 yuan in cash.
If you dare lie to me,
I'll shoot you dead.
Young man,
500,000 in cash?
Everything is digital now.
This supermarket
doesn't keep that kind of cash.
Doesn't a model team get selected monthly
with bonuses distributed to everyone?
When it's payday,
the bonuses are given in red envelopes
in cash, to each model employee.
Tomorrow is payday.
You must have prepared it already,
so I know you've got cash here.
Now that I'm here,
I'm not leaving empty-handed, okay?
How do you know so much about this?
No, no.
Didn't I already tell you?
Do what I say
and no one gets hurt.
Why did you lie to me?
- I didn't! I swear!
- You lied.
Lying makes me angry.
And if I'm angry, someone will die, got it?
I understand.
What matters more, money or life?
Think carefully, okay?
I will, I will.
I will.
Manager Zhou,
what's the matter?
Hu,
put... put the cash
in the bag.
Cash?
What cash?
The cash for the red envelopes!
Red envelopes? But...
Are you even listening to me?
Do you understand?
Cash!
Alright, alright, Manager!
I'll do it now, don't get mad!
Open the safe!
Open it, open it!
- Okay, okay.
- Open the safe!
There's no cash.
Really, no cash.
To motivate the staff,
we've already gave them
the red envelopes early.
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Everyone get down!
Take cover!
Move!
Where? Where to?
Hurry up!
Move!
The keys!
What keys?
To the door! Hurry!
Where are they?
Police! Help! Help! Help!
Police, help!
Help! Police!
(Binjiang Armed Patrol)
Any surveillance of the suspect?
No.
Security linked to the police station
was deliberately cut off.
Cameras and phones are disabled too.
Looks like it was well planned.
He's probably experienced
to act alone like this.
Most troubling is that he's armed.
(Binjiang Armed Patrol)
Don't move!
Tell them
what they should do.
Don't move! Don't move!
Do as he says!
Don't move!
(Market Entrance)
(Police)
(Hummer Commandos)
Tata, find a sniper position.
Got it.
Everyone else, follow me.
You wouldn't believe me anyway.
Shut up!
Why didn't you tell me?
There's no money in the safe.
I told you, I told you!
- Relax.
- You didn't trust me.
Don't hurt innocent people.
We can talk about your demands.
I'm Captain Ye Zhen
from Hummer Commandos.
- Shut up!
- If you...
I don't care who you are.
Listen up!
In two hours,
I want you to prepare
500,000 yuan in cash,
with no sequential serial numbers.
Did you hear me?
500,000 is a big sum,
and it has to be in cash.
Two hours isn't enough.
Even with police help,
it won't get it that fast.
Figure out the situation.
You don't have the right
to negotiate with me, got it?
Look here!
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven!
Seven people!
If you don't care
whether they live or die,
fine!
Keep stalling!
Don't be so worked up.
I'm here to
listen to your demands.
Whatever it is,
we can talk it out.
Just don't hurt the hostages.
That depends on how well you cooperate.
Now listen carefully!
I need a car.
Fill it up with petrol.
And park it at the supermarket entrance,
engine running.
Also,
tell your people
to evacuate through the rear exit.
Once I get the money,
I'll only take him with me.
The rest will be released.
Is that clear?
Two hours is really too short.
One minute late,
and we die together.
Did you hear me?
Calm down first.
We'll do our best to meet your demands.
Just ensure the hostages are safe.
(Main Entrance for Customers)
This road gets jammed a lot.
He won't escape by car.
There's a metro station
200 meters from here.
He can drive to the station.
To use the hostage as cover,
then he gets on the subway.
So the car is just a decoy
to draw away us.
His real target is the metro station.
He won't escape from the metro either.
He won't even get inside.
His plan looks calculated,
but it won't work at all.
Are the money and car ready or not?
He's not as experienced as we thought.
He's trying to act professional,
but it's overdone.
Captain, you can tell that?
So far,
none of the hostages have been harmed.
That proves
he's not a professional criminal.
We've passed your request
to the superiors.
We're taking it seriously.
Now,
can you show some sincerity too?
What do you mean?
You want me to release a hostage?
Do you think I'm that stupid?
No, you're not stupid at all.
You're very professional.
I think
you've planned this all out.
And our response
is all standard procedure, right?
Good that you know.
I guess
once you get the car and money,
you'll escape via the subway.
Am I right?
So I'm telling you,
you don't have any other choice!
If I get away,
you'll still have a chance to catch me.
But if I don't get
the money in two hours,
they will
all die!
You're very confident.
Of course I have to
plan such a big thing
carefully.
You're right.
Young man,
you're already surrounded.
There's no way out.
Shut up.
I'm warning you all!
No more tricks!
Only two hours!
One penny short,
and we'll all die together!
Li,
are you feeling unwell?
I need to use the toilet.
Young man,
it's been a long time.
We all need to go to the toilet.
So what?
We're all human
with dignity.
You can't make us go on the floor.
Zhou Tianshui,
anyone can talk to me about dignity,
except you.
You better figure this out
who's being stepped on here?
Me or you?
You... You...
Do you know me?
One more word!
I won't, I won't, I swear!
Mom.
I want some water.
The child is thirsty.
Shut up!
I won't say anything!
Ma'am,
are you okay?
I think she's having a heart attack.
Young man.
Shut up!
I'm in charge here!
What if she dies from a heart attack?
Shut up!
I'll stop, I'll stop!
Move forward.
Slowly.
She should have medicine on her.
Ask her where it is.
- Quick!
- Where's the medicine?
Where is it?
This one?
Are you stupid?
Get some water!
Water, water!
- Ma'am.
- You'll be fine now.
Feeling better?
She should be okay now.
Run!
- Run!
Hurry!
- Go!
Run!
Freeze!
Don't move!
Help me!
Don't move! Stay still!
Step back!
Calm down. Don't hurt the hostage.
- Don't move!
- We're getting your money ready.
How about
you let Manager Zhou go?
I'll go with you.
I'm a woman.
It's easier to control, right?
I only want him!
Back off.
Captain.
There's an obstacle.
I lost the target.
Captain,
the gun is fake.
Mai,
check if surveillance is back.
Yes.
- Danyang stays.
- Yes.
I'll fight you to the end!
Why is it you?
The surveillance is back online.
Isn't that Yuan?
You know him?
Yes.
His name is Yuan Bin,
used to work in our finance department.
He quit?
He was fired by Manager Zhou
six months ago.
Yuan Bin, 26 years old,
convicted of theft at age 15,
spent one year in juvenile correction.
He taught himself to get
an accounting certificate.
Records show he has
(Police Dispatch)
a two-year finance role
at Jipincang Supermarket.
He was fired six months ago
and has been jobless since.
Zhou Tianshui.
You ruined me.
I didn't! I didn't!
Why
did you always target me?
Why did you always target me?
I don't know what you think
about this month's sales performance.
Yuan Bin.
Don't you know the company rules?
My family had some issues recently.
Only your family has problems?
Only yours is special?
It's happened several times.
Your bonus this month is docked.
Yuan Bin.
Please, let me go.
While you still can,
turn yourself in now.
From now on,
you shut up.
Got it?
Got it.
I really didn't expect it
to be Yuan Bin.
What was he like before?
I joined later,
so I don't know him well.
He was quiet,
but hardworking.
He was just a bit withdrawn.
Our performance
hasn't been great these years.
Last year Manager Zhou came,
and said to downsize
to cut costs.
That's why there were layoffs.
What do you all think of Manager Zhou?
Manager Zhou's strict,
but very capable.
Our performance has improved a lot.
You're being too euphemistic.
He has no compassion.
We call him "Slave Driver".
Am I right?
Yes.
Before he came,
the performance was poor,
but at least we got along.
After he came,
he started some
reward competition scheme,
and made us all fight like roosters.
No one dared to take leave.
Even five minutes late was a big deal.
Why was Yuan Bin fired?
I heard
he came out of a juvenile center.
Maybe that's why.
So it's true?
What do you mean "true"?
Of course that's why.
Zhou Tianshui can't tolerate flaws.
This Zhou Tianshui
was so harsh on staff.
Is it possible that
he fired Yuan Bin
for having a record?
Isn't Manager Zhou in real danger now?
Zhou Tianshui,
why aren't you so arrogant now?
You never thought
that you'd end up like this, right?
Yuan Bin.
What exactly are you trying to do?
I'm Ye Zhen.
Can you hear me,
Yuan Bin?
Don't be nervous.
I've read your file.
To be honest,
I felt relieved.
You're not a heinous criminal.
You're just upset
about being fired,
and want revenge.
You don't want to hurt anyone,
right?
(Supermarket Warehouse)
Stop underestimating me, okay?
Stop analyzing me!
My money
and the car!
Are they ready?
I'm not underestimating you.
I just want you to know
the gun is fake,
and no one's been hurt.
That works in your favor.
But your people came in.
I don't trust you anymore.
There was still over an hour,
(Supermarket Warehouse)
but now I'm upset.
You've got half an hour left!
Did you hear that?
Half an hour is too short.
It's too short.
Too short?
If you're venting,
- Ouch!
- you've made your point.
I think Manager Zhou
fully understands how you feel now.
Okay, I promise you.
Help!
Captain.
Yuan Bin is losing control.
What do we do now?
Luo,
contact Yuan Bin's mother for me.
Yuan Bin,
you can't do this.
This will really get you into trouble.
I'm not afraid of anything now.
Getting into trouble?
Even less afraid.
Didn't you always think
I was beyond saving?
I never thought that.
Zhou Tianshui,
think about what you did to me before.
Whatever I do to you today
isn't too much, is it?
I...
What did I ever do to you?
Have you ever thought
why he treated you that way?
Why?
Because
he knew
that when I was a kid,
I was in juvenile detention.
(Supermarket Warehouse)
So he always had it out for me.
Given the chance,
he'd fire me.
Juvenile detention?
I didn't know about that.
How would I know
about your childhood?
Stop pretending, will you?
It's all there,
written in my file.
So all I ever wanted
was to work hard,
without saying one more word.
I told myself
to work hard
and make all of you managers
(Supermarket Warehouse)
forget about my past mistakes.
I did everything
I should do
around you.
Even things I shouldn't,
I still tried my best.
But why
did you still fire me?
I really didn't know
you were in juvenile detention.
Please, believe me.
I truly didn't know.
(Supermarket Warehouse)
Yuan Bin.
Aren't you overthinking this?
Mistakes from your youth are long past.
You don't have to dwell on them.
You tell Captain Ye,
why was I fired?
Who to keep and who to let go
was decided by the head office.
I was just following orders.
Captain Ye!
Did you hear that?
Even now,
this guy
(Supermarket Warehouse)
is still shifting all the blame!
I'm not shifting anything!
I really am not.
Yuan Bin,
to be fair,
I can't take sides.
But have you thought
that Zhou Tianshui
is just a store manager?
He has bosses too,
and his own struggles.
He makes so much money.
- I...
- Can someone like you
understand people like us
who can't even afford
hospital bills?
What money have I made?
Have I made any at all?
If I had, would I be in this state?
Everyone has their difficulties.
Yuan Bin,
do you really know him?
Do you know why he did what he did?
I don't care
what kind of person he is.
All I know is
I ended up like this today
because of him.
(Supermarket Warehouse)
Why do you keep saying it's my fault?
All I ever wanted was to do my job well.
I have no personal grudge against you.
Why blame me for your crimes?
You think my life is easy?
You all say behind my back
that I'm harsh
and heartless.
I know you called me "Slave Driver".
Have I ever said a word back?
I'm always first to arrive,
last to leave.
Did anyone see that?
Do any of you know
what I've given?
When I first came here,
the head office had already
decided to shut us down.
Do you know what that means?
It means
everyone would be out of a job.
32 people, including myself.
So I pushed everyone to work harder
because that's the only way
to keep our jobs.
I'm 47 years old this year.
I've never fought this hard in my life.
Then why did you ruin my job?
I really tried my best.
I truly did.
Later, the head office sent inspectors.
They gave us a verdict
to let go at least five people.
Only then could we
keep the store running.
I'm sorry, you were one of them.
But
I honestly didn't know
about your past.
I'm sorry.
I only focused on
doing my job well,
and neglected how you all felt.
I deserve this, okay?
I deserve it.
Just kill me.
Captain Ye, we found
Yuan Bin's mother, Chen Lijun, has
severe kidney failure.
She's currently hospitalized
at Second People's Hospital.
Yuan Bin's mother
still has unpaid medical bills.
Yuan Bin,
I want to confirm something with you.
Your mother, Chen Lijun,
has severe kidney disease.
Her life is in danger.
She urgently needs expensive treatment
to stay alive.
That's why you wanted 500,000,
right?
My mom
is the only one in this world
who still believes in me.
I can't just sit back and watch her
leave like this.
You're a filial son.
You care about your mother.
If it weren't for this situation,
you wouldn't have made this choice.
Actually,
I already found a bookkeeping job.
But later...
Later,
they found out I had been fired
and let me go again.
Every time,
(Supermarket Warehouse)
it's the same.
In
this world,
no one is willing to trust me anymore.
No one gives me another chance.
Yuan Bin,
we understand your situation.
Let us help you, alright?
Can you give me that 500,000?
500,000 really isn't that much.
It'll be gone in a few treatments.
I am my mother's
only son in this world.
I have to do something for her.
But your road ahead is long.
There's still so much
you can do for her.
But my mom
can't wait any longer.
Hello?
Mom.
Bin.
Where are you?
Mom,
I'm at work, at the office.
How are you today?
Everything's fine?
Same as usual.
Don't worry about me.
I just miss you.
Why haven't you visited me
these past days?
Mom,
things are super busy at work.
But tomorrow,
I'll get the day off.
I'll come visit you tomorrow morning.
Bin,
don't overwork yourself.
Work will never be finished.
Take care of your health.
Don't worry about me.
I'm okay.
Mom.
What is it, Bin?
I just feel
I'm very happy to be
your son in this life.
I feel the same.
Alright, Mom, I...
I gotta go now.
Work is still quite busy.
Tomorrow,
I'll come see you.
Okay.
Get back to work.
Don't forget to come tomorrow.
I miss you.
I miss you too, Mom.
I'm hanging up now.
Don't be afraid.
As long as you help me,
even if I don't get the money,
I won't hurt you.
How...
How can I help you?
You'll find out soon.
(No Signal)
Yuan Bin.
You still have a chance.
Please don't act recklessly.
When the door opens,
they'll start shooting.
Remember this,
if you stay down, you'll be fine.
No, no.
Don't do it.
Get down.
(Restricted Warehouse Area)
Time's up.
You didn't keep your promise.
I'm going to kill him!
Don't shoot!
Yuan Bin.
Even if you get
the 500,000 yuan,
you won't be able to spend it.
Before things go from bad to worse,
just let it go.
I'll help explain everything
to the police
and ask our colleagues
to raise money for your mom.
Everything will be alright.
It won't be alright anymore.
It's not just my mother's illness.
I'm in debt too.
There's no way
to start over
without ending it entirely.
What do you mean by ending it?
If I got the money,
I could pay off debts and treat my mom.
Everything would be resolved.
My mother's illness
still needs a lot of money.
Please.
Help me act this scene out, okay?
It's over, it's over.
You're safe now.
Officer.
Will he go to jail?
It's still a serious case.
But with a letter of understanding,
things might be better.
Actually,
no one was hurt.
This time,
I will definitely help him.
You were very brave just now.
Thank you.
Yuan Bin.
I didn't help you before.
This time, I won't stop until I do!
Actually,
I think Yuan Bin was just overthinking.
No one
looked down on him for being in juvie.
He probably wanted
too badly to erase that stain.
The more insecure he is,
the stronger his pride grows.
That's why communication
matters so much.
If Zhou Tianshui had talked with him
before letting him go,
and if Yuan Bin had gone
to ask Zhou Tianshui
why he was fired,
maybe this whole misunderstanding
could've been avoided.
Yeah.
Communication's crucial.
Otherwise, misunderstandings happen
and we never know why.
Right, Captain?
Right.
But sometimes,
the one involved can't see clearly.
Right, Danyang?
(Policewoman's Mini-Class)
Please remember these important numbers.
Police emergency number, 110.
Fire emergency number, 119.
Medical emergency number, 120.
Traffic accident hotline, 122.
Highway emergency hotline, 12122.
And there's another number
you might receive calls from,
96110.
This is a number used by police
specifically for
telecom fraud prevention.
Please make sure to remember them well.
♪Wear a smile to hide sorrow♪
♪Everyone's life is a tale of weariness♪
♪Tears that won't flow,
dust that won't clear♪
♪Every story has its imperfections♪
♪Chasing the wind,
soaring high without regrets♪
♪In the end, earning an invisible trophy♪
♪Living freely, living purely♪
♪Life is but a dance of asking and giving♪
♪If you face it bravely,
there's no need for shame♪
♪Everyone has their own shining moment♪
♪The scenery is intriguing,
but the end is the same♪
♪Waiting is truly precious♪
♪Face it bravely,
and regrets will naturally fade♪
♪Embrace the gifts of time♪
♪Why not journey together
through the ups and downs?♪
♪Together, enjoy
the gentle breeze and soft clouds♪