♪Fly high, spread your wings♪
♪I'm no longer who I was♪
♪Who isn't♪
♪Wishing to break free?♪
♪No surrender in the flames♪
♪Burn me♪
♪Flowers shining in the sky♪
♪At 68 degrees♪
♪Watch me fiercely take the streets♪
♪The hummers moving forward♪
♪Never turns back♪
♪Running like a bullet♪
♪Every second, smiling and saying♪
♪Get ready♪
♪The retreating hummers♪
♪Prefers to break at dawn♪
♪If needed, then they will♪
♪Fly very high♪
♪Confronting the earth-shaking♪
♪Sweeping beams of light♪
♪The battle rages on♪
=Sisters in Arms=
=Episode 19=
I heard you're doing extra training.
Are you meditating here?
Yes.
Why are you talking to me now?
Are we not in a cold war anymore?
What's going on with you?
Why are you upset?
We could just talk it through, right?
You don't know
how frustrating this is for me.
You really think
I'm upset with you
because my grades
are worse than yours?
I don't think so.
After all, you're not that ambitious.
What's really going on?
Tell me.
Come on.
Mai.
We're such good friends
that we even have the same taste.
Isn't it annoying?
What do you mean?
Mai.
You're beautiful,
with high emotional intelligence,
great abilities,
and you even know medicine.
You're better than me at everything.
If it were me,
I would pick you.
What are you saying?
I know who you have a crush on.
It's Song Tiancheng, right?
Song Tiancheng?
You also like Song Tiancheng?
You do like Song Tiancheng.
Liu Danyang, even you have a crush!
A once-in-a-moon event!
Why can't I like someone?
I'm good enough too, you know?
Yes, that's true.
You are indeed very excellent.
But unfortunately,
you don't have a chance anymore.
(Song Tiancheng)
Song Tiancheng got married?
Yes.
The bride isn't us.
I was just alone
thinking about this matter.
My bestie,
you have to share the pain together.
You keep it for meditation.
I'm feeling better.
Thanks, bye.
- Liu Danyang has a crush!
- Mai Jialing, get back here!
Come back here!
I'm telling you, if anything happens,
don't tell me!
Yuan Bin.
All criminals
find an excuse for themselves.
It's all because of your greed
that this happened.
If everyone in society
walked to extremes like you
and broke the law,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
I hope you can truly repent
and reform
to get out soon.
Can I go see my mom again?
I've been a burden to you.
Now let's talk about
the hostage situation the other day.
Danyang.
I remember criminology talked about
the psychology of hostage-takers.
It's either in uncontrollable rage
or scornful of everything.
So we need to use humanitarianism
to change their mindset.
Very well.
But it's all just theory.
We need to adjust
based on the actual situation.
Yuan Bin was a juvenile offender.
After rehabilitation, he worked hard
and became an accountant.
He was fired
because of his past blemish,
so he must hate those
who deny his efforts.
So
we need to shift Yuan Bin's attention
away from Manager Zhou.
Pretty good.
Remember,
during the negotiation process,
we must always be aware
of the suspect's state of mind.
Once our words
don't resonate with him,
the suspect will easily
lose patience
and cease communication.
This could lead to mission failure.
By the way,
the donations for Yuan Bin's mother
have all been given to the hospital.
And I heard the donations
are still coming in.
Great.
Captain, goodbye.
Yuan Bin,
I'm here to tell you
Manager Zhou has signed
a letter of understanding
and has been writing to the court.
They are still working for your case.
Here's some good news.
The hospital has received donations
from all sectors of society.
Your mother's medical fees
are no longer an issue.
Don't worry.
This is a recent video of your mom.
Drink slowly. Don't choke.
Her health is stable.
Thank you.
It's no problem.
I'll peel an orange for you.
Where's Bin?
Bin?
He went on a business trip.
He told me to come
and help take care of you.
Bin is really impressive now.
Our boss at the head office
saw him once.
He said
that Bin is very hardworking,
and they are preparing to send him
for training at the head office.
Thanks for their care.
It's no problem.
It's because Bin did well.
Get more Vitamin C.
It's good for your health, right?
And your medical fees
have been taken concern.
No worries now.
You don't need to worry.
Right.
Thanks for your help.
It's the least we could do.
Here, have another one.
Okay, thank you.
Sorry.
I'm leaving.
Pass.
Quick, quick, quick.
What happened?
What place is this?
Hello, where's my bestie outfit?
It's ready.
Here.
Tata.
How about this dress?
It looks pretty good.
It suits you.
Too bad it's a bestie outfit.
Fang Fang isn't here.
Otherwise, she could wear it with me.
How about...
- This looks so good, Tata.
- You're killing me.
It looks great.
Here.
It's so ugly.
Delete it, delete it.
I'll go pay.
No.
Don't waste money.
I won't wear it.
Doesn't it look good?
I'll pick a few more for you.
No!
Hello, Mom. What's wrong?
Tata.
Coming back this week?
I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm out shopping with a friend.
Okay.
What's wrong, Mom?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing serious.
I just came to the hospital
to visit a friend.
And I saw your dad.
He was still in a hospital gown.
I don't know
what illness he has.
Do you think...
Mom.
I'll be home tomorrow at noon.
Want something to eat?
I'll bring it home for you, okay?
Anything's fine.
Go back to your things.
Come back early tomorrow.
Okay.
These drugs were all
found in the trash bins.
(Binjiang Anti-narcotics Brigade)
According to those we arrested,
no one has ever contacted them directly.
They just set up meeting spots online,
and those spots are random.
Then they use a black plastic bag
to wrap the drugs
and leave them in the trash bins.
The composition of this batch
is exactly the same as
what we found with Xiahou Xiong.
Even the trafficking methods
are identical.
I also believe this batch
is the same batch
that Wu took previously.
So if it's Wu,
why has he been active again
after such a long time?
Because the supply is sufficient.
Or maybe
he found new sources.
It's possible.
No way.
I've blocked all his
foreign routes.
Is it possible they found someone
who can make the drugs
and set up a self-sustaining
production chain?
Is it possible that
Mad Dog is with him?
I think
the one who saved Mad Dog
must be Wu.
The goods are ready.
The purity absolutely reaches
the sample level you gave me.
Are the goods prepared?
Dove,
didn't you give out
a little trial sample?
Wu,
don't you trust me?
How could I not?
Well done.
Mad Dog.
His real name is Li Donghan.
Ten years ago, he entered
the Chemistry Department
at Ocean University
with top grades.
(Suspect Info: Li Donghan)
His professor mentioned
Li Donghan was very talented.
He was supposed to get into
graduate school through recommendation.
But they said
he had some personality issues.
While in college,
he got into a fight over
a small matter with his roommate
and injured his eye.
He was sent to detention,
then he fought with another inmate.
I think there are some issues with him.
According to testimonies
from people close to him
and the information we have,
we can confirm that he and Wu
are working together.
So,
our immediate priority
is to move quickly
and locate their hideout.
- Yes.
(Surveillance, Basement, Living Room)
(Fairy)
(Miss you)
(Police, Binjiang)
HAF45562.
Stop, stop!
Mom.
Kid.
Are you okay?
Come on, get up.
Where else does it hurt?
Let me see.
Okay, don't cry.
Does it hurt here?
Does your hand hurt?
Where does it hurt?
You guys are too careless.
We're really sorry.
- Thanks, officer.
- Thank you.
A child should always be in a car seat.
- Sure, sure.
- Okay, okay.
Thank you, thank you.
Be careful next time.
- Okay.
It's okay.
Return to the base.
I've never seen such careless parents.
They don't put their kid
in the car seat,
and they don't buckle up,
even leaving the car windows open.
There are parents
who are even more careless.
Remember last time?
We saw a young couple go out for a meal,
and they forgot their child
in the back seat.
The child cried loudly.
I'm quite speechless.
Who's born knowing how to be a parent?
It's their first time.
They're still young,
haven't gotten in the role yet.
Look, even our Tang Xin
knows this principle.
It's not about age.
Some people live their whole lives
and still don't know
what responsibility is.
How does she have so much energy?
Do you think
she doesn't get tired?
I don't understand.
The canteen has braised pork tonight.
Let's go.
Tata, keep practicing.
We're going to eat.
We're going for the meat.
Get me a portion.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
I really envy them.
They are always so happy.
It's like they never have any worries.
They definitely have worries,
but you know,
they have a gift
that we don't have.
What?
A big heart.
People should have
fast self-response abilities,
strong self-healing powers,
and selective forgetting abilities.
Not one less.
So,
those who only remember the good
and forget the bad
are the ones who are happiest.
Tell me.
What are you struggling with?
Nothing.
Actually, I've recently
figured a few things out.
I realized
as long as I can
let go of the criticism,
I will feel a sense of relief.
Try it.
Why are you still
playing on your phone?
Have you done your homework?
Xu Zifeng, I'm talking to you.
Can you hear me?
What are you doing? I'm playing!
Go do your homework first.
I have my own plans and schedule.
Don't try to manage me.
I'm your mom.
If I don't manage you, who will?
- What's that attitude?
- You can see.
Where are you going?
Stifling in here.
I'm stepping out.
Don't go!
(Honey)
Hello?
You'd better not come back.
None of them are easy to deal with.
Qiang, let's go.
Let's go.
We said, it's all fake.
How many times do I have to say?
We're helping her.
You also need to help me.
We've grown up together.
After it's done,
I won't treat you unfairly.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
- Help!
- Don't shout.
What are you guys doing?
Who are you?
Shut your mouth.
Get in the car.
- Get in the car.
- Hurry up.
Officers.
- Something's wrong.
- What's going on?
They've kidnapped people!
Don't worry. Take your time.
I... I just saw a mother and daughter
being dragged into a car.
One of them was holding a knife.
Wanru, Mai, stay here
and find out what's going on.
Tang Xin, head to the crossroads.
Everyone else follow me.
- Yes.
Attention, all departments.
At Shimen No. 1 Alley,
two people were kidnapped.
They were forced into a white van.
We only saw part of the license plate.
The first three letters are HAF.
The last digit is 4.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Don't move.
Behave yourselves.
Behave.
Tie her up.
Hurry up.
Just do as you're told,
we won't hurt you.
Let her go.
She's just a child.
Please.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
Come.
Captain.
According to the information provided,
the two people who were kidnapped
are mother and daughter.
The mother's name is Chen Lin,
the daughter's is Xu Zifeng.
It seems that the kidnappers
planned this.
Notify their family quickly.
And search their house.
Got it.
Yes.
(Integrated Police Communication System)
Captain Ye, we've spotted
the suspected vehicle.
The license plate is HAF22034.
It's heading south
on Libo Road in the east.
Captain, I remember that
south of Libo Road
is still under construction.
The surveillance system
isn't fully installed yet.
Requesting reinforcements.
Please send nearby
police quickly.
Okay.
Hey.
It feels like things are getting worse.
How about
we let them go?
Fine.
We can let them go.
Let me ask you,
do you still want money?
Don't worry.
I have it under control.
Is anyone there?
Captain Ye, we've sent reinforcements
to surround the last known location
of the suspect's vehicle.
Their whereabouts now are still unclear.
Could they have left the area?
Given the time,
they shouldn't have driven too fast.
Where could they have gone?
Wanru,
do you have any updates?
Captain,
from what I know,
Chen Lin is unemployed.
Her husband works
as a technician in a factory.
Their income is low.
But from the site visit,
the house conditions seem decent.
It's cozy and warm.
We're still waiting for
her husband to come back.
What are you doing?
You must be Xu Zheng, right?
The main road without cameras
has already been blocked.
There are also police cars
searching nearby.
If they
haven't left this area,
where could they go?
Is it possible they have
abandoned the car
or switched vehicles and hidden?
But the car can't just disappear.
(Parking Lot)
Stop the car.
Xīn,
how many public parking lots are here?
Four.
Which one can avoid cameras completely?
The one in Sinan Parking Lot.
Let's go.
(Police, Binjiang)
(Vehicle Identification, Slow Down)
Listen.
We'll get out of the car soon.
If you dare run,
I'll stab her.
Got it?
Take her
to the front car.
Go.
Get out.
All units, attention.
The suspect's vehicle
has entered Sinan Parking Lot.
You... You mean
my wife and child have been kidnapped?
Have you offended anyone recently?
Offended anyone?
No, we haven't.
Have you noticed anything unusual?
Any strangers or
unfamiliar vehicles around?
No.
Has your daughter
made any new friends lately?
Or maybe
someone she met online?
Zifeng...
You know, when a girl grows up,
she doesn't tell
her father everything.
Didn't your wife tell you anything?
I've been busy lately.
I haven't had much time
to talk to my wife.
Is there any problem
with your relationship?
Our relationship is fine.
Have my wife and child
really been kidnapped?
How is it?
No suspicious clues found.
The suspect's vehicle was found
in Sinan Parking Lot.
The car is empty.
The suspect might have
switched vehicles here
to evade pursuit.
Looking at their financial situation,
this is not a typical target
for kidnappers.
Doesn't seem to be about money.
Captain Ye,
we've checked
all the vehicles
that entered your area.
Only a black SUV
with the license plate HAB22176
matches the information.
The vehicle is still being tracked.
We've sent people
to block the road.
Continue to pursue south of Libo Road.
- Go.
- Yes.
Hey.
Are you sure you're not lying to me?
Qiang,
when have I ever lied to you?
Right?
Don't worry.
This plan may be extreme,
but when the truth comes out,
they'll thank you for it.
Trust me.
Hey,
aren't we going that way?
Too many cameras
on the main road.
It's not safe.
Hello.
This is the 110 emergency hotline.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Calling the police?
Hello?
Please speak.
Is it
inconvenient to talk?
Captain Ye, Chen Lin
called us.
But no one spoke.
Put me through.
Track the location of the call.
Yes, tracking now.
Chen Lin,
this is Ye Zhen, captain
of Hummer Commandos.
Are you safe?
Lower your voice!
I will kill you.
Don't scream.
I know you can't talk right now.
Don't panic.
I'll ask the questions now.
If you can hear me,
just press any key.
Good.
Is the call safe?
If yes, press once.
If not,
don't press.
Are you Chen Lin?
You're not hurt, right?
There are two suspects?
What are you hiding?
What exactly are you hiding?
Get away, get away.
- Don't move.
- What is it?
Hey,
they called the police, the police!
Throw the phone away, hurry.
You...
Behave!
You two want to die?
What should we do?
Captain Ye, the phone's
no longer moving.
Can you track the location?
It's on the county road
in Hedong Town, Baiyun Village.
(Hexi Town, Hedong Town)
Location will be sent.
Okay, thanks.
Captain, we've learned something.
Xu Zheng's family is very average.
But Chen Lin's mother is very rich.
Her father passed away early.
Chen Lin's mother has been living abroad
and running a company.
When they got married,
Chen's mother strongly
opposed her marrying Xu Zheng
because Xu's family was poor.
In a fit of anger,
Chen Lin severed ties with her mother.
They've been apart
for over a decade.
Who else knows
Chen Lin's mother is very rich?
We asked Xu Zheng,
but he said
he and Chen Lin never talk about
her parents.
Even Xu Zifeng doesn't know
who her grandmother is.
(Policewoman's Mini-Class)
Officer, I get a query.
Why do you sound the alarm
every time you respond to a call?
Don't you worry about
the criminals escaping?
We don't always sound the alarm
when responding to calls.
But when it's a major case,
we won't hesitate to sound the alarm.
The goal is to deter the criminals.
But what if the criminals escape?
Preventing the crime is more important
than capturing the criminals.
♪Wear a smile to hide sorrow♪
♪Everyone's life is a tale of weariness♪
♪Tears that won't flow,
dust that won't clear♪
♪Every story has its imperfections♪
♪Chasing the wind,
soaring high without regrets♪
♪In the end, earning an invisible trophy♪
♪Living freely, living purely♪
♪Life is but a dance of asking and giving♪
♪If you face it bravely,
there's no need for shame♪
♪Everyone has their own shining moment♪
♪The scenery is intriguing,
but the end is the same♪
♪Waiting is truly precious♪
♪Face it bravely,
and regrets will naturally fade♪
♪Embrace the gifts of time♪
♪Why not journey together
through the ups and downs?♪
♪Together, enjoy
the gentle breeze and soft clouds♪