♪Fly high, spread your wings♪
♪I'm no longer who I was♪
♪Who isn't♪
♪Wishing to break free?♪
♪No surrender in the flames♪
♪Burn me♪
♪Flowers shining in the sky♪
♪At 68 degrees♪
♪Watch me fiercely take the streets♪
♪The hummers moving forward♪
♪Never turns back♪
♪Running like a bullet♪
♪Every second, smiling and saying♪
♪Get ready♪
♪The retreating hummers♪
♪Prefers to break at dawn♪
♪If needed, then they will♪
♪Fly very high♪
♪Confronting the earth-shaking♪
♪Sweeping beams of light♪
♪The battle rages on♪
=Sisters in Arms=
=Episode 20=
What's wrong bro?
Cops know now,
we have to change the plan.
Change the plan?
This woman is in our way.
Let's do this.
Kill her?
Are you insane?
What else can we do?
Nabbed by the cops.
And we'll both go to jail!
Jail does beat a bullet!
Are you in or not?
I'm out.
If you want to do it, do it yourself.
Wu Qiang!
Wu Qiang.
I'm telling you,
either she dies here today
or
you die here instead.
Ma Tianze.
I've always seen you as a brother.
Now you're pointing a knife at me?
Were you lying to me all along?
All that stuff about the abused kid,
her family paying us
to stage a kidnapping,
is a lie, right?
And I actually trusted you.
Qiang,
I did all this for your own good.
Think about it.
Jail means our lives are over.
But with this money,
we can do whatever we want.
Better than being nobodies forever!
That's nonsense!
This is murder!
You'll eat a bullet!
Bullet! Do you even get that?
You've lost your mind!
You're not doing it?
Fine.
First,
you get nothing.
And also,
if I go to jail,
you're not getting away either.
Are you in?
Get out.
Out.
Move.
Go.
Hello?
Give me the phone.
Oh, okay!
I found it.
Where?
Just right here.
I saw a light flashing here,
so I came down to check.
How long since we got the call?
16 minutes.
Captain.
Ahead is mountain road.
No cameras there.
Use the drone.
Got it.
Hello, Auntie.
Don't worry, I'll take good care of her.
Stay inside the hotel
and wait for my call.
Okay.
Got it. Don't worry.
I gotta go.
She's dead?
One million.
You promised me one million.
Ma Tianze.
If you lie to me again,
I'll kill you too, do you believe me?
Relax,
man.
I'll keep my promise. Don't worry.
Calm down, calm down.
Take it easy.
Let's get in the car
and leave this place.
Go.
The only passable road
runs north-south.
We came from the south to intercept.
The phone was dumped here.
So they must've headed north.
There are two options north.
One is National Road 375,
the other is the coastal highway.
There's a toll station
at the highway entrance.
Traffic police will be there.
He probably won't take that route.
Then he'll use the national road.
Hurry up.
Think carefully again.
How could Chen Lin
not contact her mother at all?
I remember once
she sent a New Year's card
to her mother.
It had a photo of Zifeng inside.
But she never got a reply.
So she lost all hope.
There was no point in staying in touch.
Attention, all units.
We just found through
the ticketing system
that Chen Lin's mother, Tian Fang,
arrived in Binjiang two days ago.
She's currently staying
at Dinghao Hotel.
These incidents must be connected.
A wealthy old lady, alone
suddenly arrived in Binjiang
and days later, her daughter
and granddaughter are kidnapped.
Could that be a coincidence?
Chen Lin's mother
is the perfect extortion target.
(Police)
Hello, Auntie, it's me.
Tianze, where are you?
When are you coming back?
Auntie.
Something went wrong.
What happened?
Is my granddaughter okay?
For now, she's fine.
What do you mean, for now?
What exactly happened?
Auntie.
Zifeng might be in danger.
What?
What kind of danger?
What's going on exactly?
The guy I partnered with
is my childhood friend.
We rescued Zifeng together,
but he suddenly turned on me.
What do you mean?
He wants a lot of money.
Otherwise he'll kill her.
Didn't I already give you a big sum?
Give it to him first.
As long as he lets Zifeng go.
He says it's not enough.
Also,
he recorded a video
and let me send it.
Hold on.
(Photos and Videos)
(Auntie)
Zifeng.
Zifeng!
No,
we have to call the police!
No, Auntie.
You can't call the police!
Think about it.
Even if you're her grandma,
this is still kidnapping.
Wait.
Just think, the police will
send Zifeng back home.
And her dad will keep abusing her.
That guy just wants money.
Trust me.
Once he gets the money,
I swear I'll get Zifeng out.
Did he name a price?
Five million.
Alright. I'll give it.
As long as he lets my granddaughter go.
Go to the foreign bank
across from the hotel
to withdraw the money.
- Got that?
- Okay, okay!
I'll go now!
Well, Tianze,
can you guarantee Zifeng's safety?
Don't worry.
She's safe for now.
Once we have the money,
I'll immediately find a way
to get her out.
I'll send your phone the account.
Be quick, understand?
Okay okay, I'll go now!
Hey.
Well,
the money's coming soon!
Please don't hurt her!
Alright, alright.
Tianze, what's wrong?
Well,
how much longer do we wait?
What's the rush? The money's coming.
Hello.
Are you Ms. Tian Fang?
There's nothing out here.
My daughter and granddaughter
have been kidnapped?
Ms. Tian, has anyone
contacted you recently,
demanding ransom?
No.
Even if they did,
why would they come to me?
Right?
I haven't spoken to my daughter
Chen Lin for over ten years.
I didn't even know I had a granddaughter.
I'm sorry.
I have something to do today.
I can't talk with you for long.
Ms. Tian.
We just have a few questions.
Please sit down.
Go ahead.
What brought you
to Binjiang this time?
I heard the scenery is nice here.
I'm here to clear my mind.
So where do you plan to go sightseeing?
Well...
My secretary arranged all that.
I can't remember everything.
Just now you said you had to go out.
Go out?
Did I say that?
Oh right, yes I did.
I have something to do.
I have to go now.
Ms. Tian.
I hope you can cooperate with us.
This involves
the safety of your daughter
and granddaughter.
Look, officer,
didn't I already tell you?
Lin
and Zifeng
have nothing to do with me anymore.
You mean Xu Zifeng, right?
Yes.
But earlier you told us
you didn't know you had a granddaughter.
So how do you know
her name is Xu Zifeng?
How do you explain that?
Didn't one of you just mention it?
No, we didn't.
Wanru.
Did you speak with Tian Fang?
Yes, Captain.
It's very likely
she's gotten a ransom call.
We asked a few questions
but she lied to all of them.
There's something else strange.
I feel like Tian Fang
isn't mentally clear.
She speaks very slowly
and forgets things in a second.
Doesn't seem like she's faking.
She might have Alzheimer's,
cognitive disorder,
or memory gaps.
Captain.
The drone is nearly out of range.
Nothing found so far.
You have no right to touch my things!
Ms. Tian,
we're trying to help you.
Please don't obstruct our investigation.
That's my personal property!
Give it back!
Ms. Tian.
Why do you have their photos?
I care about my granddaughter.
Is that so wrong?
It's just human nature.
Ms. Tian.
Your granddaughter and daughter
are in grave danger.
If you know where they are,
who kidnapped them,
or why
they were kidnapped,
you have to tell us.
What are you doing?
Trying to run?
Try that again
and I'll send you to your mom,
you hear me?
You won't.
You won't kill me.
Dare you try me?
Could it be that
we're going about this the wrong way?
After they ditched the phone,
maybe they didn't move forward
but turn back.
Sometimes the most dangerous place
is also the safest.
Tata.
Try the opposite direction.
Roger that.
Something off
about the photos.
Look.
Xu Zifeng's head and body
look out of proportion.
And the lighting in this one is off too.
See?
The shadow on her face doesn't
match the light source above.
This photo might have
been digitally altered.
What?
It might be computer-generated.
It means they're fake.
We'll send them to technical unit
and have them confirm it.
And from what we know,
Xu Zheng was actually good
to his wife and daughter.
It was Chen Lin who was
stricter with the girl.
There were more conflicts
between mother and daughter.
But...
But the photos suggest otherwise.
Right?
Did someone say
Xu Zheng was abusing your granddaughter?
Yes.
Who gave you these photos?
My nephew.
What's his name?
Ma Tianze.
(Ma Tianze)
(Ma Tianze abused his role
to embezzle over 3.5 million yuan)
(for personal use,
stock grading and gambling)
Captain! Found them!
Help!
Help me!
- Officer!
- Are you Chen Lin?
Yes, I called the police.
You're injured.
Don't worry about me.
Please save my daughter.
Get her bandaged up.
Please save my daughter!
Don't worry. We'll find her.
Yes, get her treated first.
This way, please.
Ma Tianze, male, 30 years old.
He's the deputy manager
of your mainland branch.
Can you confirm that?
Ma Tianze embezzled company funds
and accounting found out.
Now he's facing prosecution.
So he desperately needs money
to fill the hole.
What?
You didn't know about this?
No, I had no idea!
I've been in poor health.
I rarely handle
business matters.
How could he do this?
I trusted him so much!
Auntie.
Didn't you just take your medicine?
Why are you taking more?
I already took them?
Yes, you did.
I forgot.
Auntie.
Let me massage you.
Okay.
Tianze.
I don't have children by my side.
Thank you for flying back and forth
to care for me.
Auntie,
we're family after all.
Just treat me like your own son.
This time I came back to China,
I don't want to leave again.
I miss Lin.
I can't go on never seeing her again.
Tianze.
When are we
going to see Lin?
Auntie.
I already told you.
Did you forget?
- You told me?
- Yes.
What did you say?
This...
What happened?
That's Zifeng.
And that's her father.
I've seen her before.
Where did you get the photos?
Auntie, don't worry.
I originally went to visit Lin.
But she didn't recognize me.
Then I happened to see
her husband abusing Zifeng.
I told her to get a divorce,
but she refused.
You know how stubborn she is.
Back then, because of this man,
she even
cut ties with you.
Yeah.
So what do we do now?
What should we do, Tianze?
Auntie.
You once told me
you wanted to bring Zifeng back.
Do you remember?
I said that?
That's right.
But there's one problem.
Zifeng is underage.
She needs a guardian's consent.
Do you think Lin would agree?
So,
I came up with a plan.
What plan, Tianze?
Auntie.
First I will
bring Zifeng to stay with me.
Then I'll talk to Lin.
She's suffered so much
out there all these years.
I believe
she'll definitely agree.
I don't know where they'd go.
Those two
don't always agree.
For example?
For example...
Go.
Don't shout. I'm letting you go.
Wait till we've left, you can run.
But to convince him,
you'll have to suffer a bit.
Bear with it.
Lie down.
Don't scream.
He said this has to be done
behind my daughter's back.
I've been in poor health.
I get
confused a lot.
So I handed all company matters
over to him completely.
How could he be like this?
(Tianze)
Ma Tianze.
Answer it.
Keep him talking
and drag it out as long as possible.
(Tianze)
Hello, Auntie.
Tianze.
Are you alright over there?
Have you transferred the money?
Oh, right.
Transfer the money, right?
Oh dear.
I totally forgot about that.
What...
You haven't sent the money yet?
Auntie.
Listen to me.
I can still keep him calm for now.
But you need to go downstairs right now
to transfer the money.
Got it?
Okay okay, I'm going now!
I'm going!
Tianze.
What did you just tell me to do?
Why can't I remember it again?
Go to the bank across from the hotel.
Bring your bag.
Your ID is in there.
Got it?
Oh, to the bank downstairs, right?
- Right.
- Okay, okay.
How much am I transferring?
Five million.
Remember? Five million.
Okay, okay.
I'll transfer five million now.
I'm going now.
Okay, okay.
Auntie.
Is someone next to you?
Yes.
No.
I'm alone in the hotel.
There's no one else here.
I...
He hung up.
Captain Ye, the phone location shows
near Taoyuan Fourth Road.
(Abandoned Factory)
A barely populated area.
There's an abandoned factory there.
What's wrong?
Why are you holding a knife?
I'm gonna kill her.
- No! Calm down!
- Move!
- Move! I'll kill her!
- Calm down!
Calm down!
Why?
If she lives,
we both will die!
Move!
Listen to me!
I've already killed one.
We can't kill this one.
If she dies, what about the money?
We won't get the money.
Right.
If she's alive,
we still can get money.
Either way, we're doomed.
Might as well go all in.
Get her in the car.
We'll go somewhere else.
No, listen.
If we move now,
we're easier to spot.
Maybe staying here is safer.
Please.
As long as she's with us,
we still have a chance.
Watch her.
Watch her closely.
I'll go check outside.
It was my mom
who told Ma Tianze to do this?
Your mom probably
just wanted to protect Xu Zifeng.
But she has Alzheimer's disease,
also known as dementia.
Her memory and cognition
are both impaired.
Ma Tianze took advantage of that
and of your mom's trust in him.
From what my colleague saw,
your mom still cares deeply about you.
Shh.
Hey.
How's it looking outside?
All good. Nothing suspicious.
Wait, bro.
What?
There's something
I've wanted to tell you.
What do you want to say?
Thank you
for giving me this chance to make money
so I could pay off my debts.
Not in the mood.
Hey bro, listen to me!
Bro.
I...
Bro! Bro! Bro!
- Stop it!
- Get out of the way!
Come here!
Come here! Now!
Let me go!
Calm down! She's just a kid, bro!
Bro!
If you don't behave,
I'll kill you first.
Let me go!
Move!
- Wait!
- Let go!
- Move!
- Wait!
Let her go, bro!
- Please!
- Shut up!
Let go of me!
- Come here!
- Hey!
- Let me go!
- Tianze!
- Bro!
- Let me go!
Bro!
Let the kid go!
- Come here!
- Help!
Let the kid go!
Get lost!
Come here! Come to me!
Let the kid go!
You're surrounded!
Let me go!
Get down!
- Stay back!
- Let me go!
I have a hostage!
Bro,
it's all police.
Let's turn ourselves in.
Shut up!
Go.
Bring the car here.
Or I'll stab her!
Now!
Hurry up!
Stay back!
Come here!
Move!
Come on, quick!
Get in.
Get in!
- In!
- Move aside!
Go after them!
Zifeng!
Hurry!
Bro,
what now?
Just drive!
Xin, follow them.
Yes!
The cops are catching up, bro!
- Bro!
- Step on it! Now!
- Help!
- Shut up!
Faster!
I'm going as fast as I can!
Don't move!
Run! Get out!
Protect the girl.
We'll chase the suspects.
There's an injured person.
Get him to the hospital.
Mom!
Zifeng.
Are you alright?
Be careful.
(Policewoman's Mini-Class)
Some people get their weaknesses
exploited by bad guys,
turning their help into harm.
No matter how sincere our intentions,
we must understand
the truth of the matter.
We can genuinely support those in need
only within legal and reasonable limits,
and with their consent,
without harming others' interests.
♪Wear a smile to hide sorrow♪
♪Everyone's life is a tale of weariness♪
♪Tears that won't flow,
dust that won't clear♪
♪Every story has its imperfections♪
♪Chasing the wind,
soaring high without regrets♪
♪In the end, earning an invisible trophy♪
♪Living freely, living purely♪
♪Life is but a dance of asking and giving♪
♪If you face it bravely,
there's no need for shame♪
♪Everyone has their own shining moment♪
♪The scenery is intriguing,
but the end is the same♪
♪Waiting is truly precious♪
♪Face it bravely,
and regrets will naturally fade♪
♪Embrace the gifts of time♪
♪Why not journey together
through the ups and downs?♪
♪Together, enjoy
the gentle breeze and soft clouds♪