CHARACTERS AND PLACES ASSOCIATED
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Platoon One and Two, prepare immediately.
Platoon Three, stand by after dinner.
This is Platoon One. Roger that.
This is Platoon Two. Roger that.
Be mindful of safety
so no unexpected events occur.
This is the situation room reporting
the progress of today's rally.
The participants of the rally
are increasing rapidly
and are gathering at Bosingak Pavilion.
Enjoy your meal.
EPISODE 1
Sir.
Aren't you going home?
We're closed, sir.
Hey, yelling at them won't wake them up.
Just shake them harder.
Sir.
Hey,
you know that I'm taking this week off,
so So-jeong is coming instead, right?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Why aren't you answering?
These two drank fifteen bottles.
They won't wake up.
Just shake them harder.
Sir.
Is this the police station?
I'm calling from Hyuna Intersection
in Seongbin-dong.
There are drunk people sitting
on the streets where there are cars.
Yes. Hyuna Intersection.
What are you doing?
I'm just rinsing rice. Just go to bed.
Just sleep.
Mom, sorry. I'm so sorry.
Does it hurt a lot?
-Ouch!
-Gosh, seriously.
I NEVER GAVE UP. I DON'T WANT
YOUR SUPPORT. JUST DON'T LAUGH AT ME.
DON'T GIVE UP! NEVER!
Mom, are you up?
You should get more sleep.
Mom, I made soybean paste stew.
Have breakfast.
Mom.
Mom, are you listening to me?
Gosh.
Are you going somewhere?
A client of mine wants to see me
before I go to work.
To buy an insurance plan?
I'll find out when I get there.
Don't get annoyed.
I can't help it.
Did you take your medicine?
Why would I? My panic disorder
will never get better anyways.
Take it.
You should have breakfast.
I have to go whenever my clients
want to see me.
How could an insurance agent
expect to eat on time?
What's this smell?
The stew!
Give me 50,000 won.
I told you I'm going to Seoul
for the job expo.
I'll pay you back when I get paid.
Just give me the money.
Why are you staring at me?
What do you want me to do?
Damn it.
My life is a mess.
Yeong-ji, hurry!
-Hey, where are you going?
-The bathroom!
You idiot, there are bathrooms
at the job fair!
You should've told me!
Sorry! I'm sorry.
2014 SMALL BUSINESS
RECRUITMENT INFORMATION EXPO
RECRUITMENT NOTICE BOARD
BLIND RECRUITMENT
-I studied in Canada...
-Through a wide range of volunteer work,
I learned how to get along with everyone
and how to be a good leader.
Regardless of region and...
I worked on developing my language skills.
-If an opportunity is...
-Through cultural exchanges...
-Working in an international sales team
-My experience as an exchange student
-allowed me to build a wide scope of...
-taught me how to communicate with...
Every year, Minhwa Corporation invests
over ten percent of its net profit in R&D.
Petrochemistry... No.
Petrochemistry... No, wake up.
In addition to the petrochemical industry,
the continued advancement
in macromolecule science...
-My gosh!
-Oh, no!
Oh, gosh.
Her shirt is completely ruined.
-What is she going to do?
-She has an interview too.
I feel so bad for her.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me?
You need to come up with a solution.
This is obviously your fault.
Why do I have to think up a solution?
Aren't I right?
Take off your shirt.
My interview is in ten minutes.
I'll give it back when I'm done.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, take off your undershirt. You too.
Okay.
Everyone, don't walk around
with your coffee.
Get rid of your coffee now.
Let's not ruin each other's life, okay?
-Ms. Lee Jeong-mi?
-Yes.
-Ms. Kim Yeong-ji?
I thought you might be tired.
I cannot accept things like this.
Of course I'll keep working
even after I get married.
That's a sexist remark...
What about you Ms. Han Jeong-o?
I don't want to get married. I'd like
to contribute to your macromolecule...
What will you do
if a senior member of your team
asks you to take care of
a personal matter?
Like picking up groceries
or babysitting, for example.
I'll consider even that as interest.
I'll help them with such personal matters
and ask about work-related rules
or know-hows...
I didn't go to an elite school,
but my GPA is high.
I'd love an opportunity to learn
at your company even as an intern...
We don't have an internship program.
-You graduated from Gayeon University.
-Yes, that's correct.
On your website, you advertise
that you accept all applicants
regardless of their academic background,
but during the actual interviews,
-you ask every applicant...
-Did you go to the military?
-Yes, sir.
-Which division?
Getting points for that
violates the constitution...
I was just asking,
out of my personal curiosity.
-I served in Blue Dragon Division.
-"Blue Dragon Division."
Sir, you're not here as yourself.
You're sitting there
as a representative of the company.
If this interview was for
your personal questions,
there would be no need for
job seekers like me to be here.
What an obnoxious asshole.
-What the hell?
-Are you blind?
I'll write everything I experienced,
on the Ministry of Employment
and Labor's website.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, let me verify the order with you.
You ordered 20 jugs of 10L spring water.
Yes, the order has been received.
Thank you.
This has been
Yeom Sang-su in Marketing Team One
of Serai Water,
proven safe and effective by the FDA.
-Please review and approve this.
-Okay.
Have a good day.
Yes, I remember. Mr. Lee Jae-min, you said
you are interested in investing, right?
Serai Water has been patented.
We'll revolutionize the water industry,
and we're preparing to go public.
This is Yeom Sang-su in Marketing Team One
of Serai Water, approved by the FDA.
Thank you for calling Serai Water.
Our water was developed by Doctor Yang...
Hello, this is...
Thank you for calling...
This is Yeom Sang-su
in Marketing Team One of Serai Water.
-Yes, I remember. You wanted to invest...
-Thank you for calling...
How many shares will you buy?
A hundred. What about you?
My mom and my brother are pitching in.
I should buy at least a hundred
if that's the requirement.
It's so hard to become
a full-time employee.
We pull an all-nighter every day
and we even have to buy stock shares.
But we'll make 2,000,000 won every month
and become shareholders.
Then we'll be able
to join the successful bunch!
Let's stay positive, okay?
Hey.
-Fuck. My nose is bleeding again.
-Are you okay?
I work so hard, don't I?
Do you have tissues?
Stop talking about discrimination.
These days, men are often
put at a disadvantage.
That's right. Due to the policy
on women's employment,
companies must hire a set percentage
of women.
Let's be honest.
Isn't that reverse discrimination?
How is that reverse discrimination?
Korea's rate of female employment
ranked seventh
from the bottom
out of all OECD member countries.
Men earn seven times more than women.
Don't you read the news, you pea-brain?
Just do as you're told.
Just like the military,
society wants you to obey.
-Bullshit.
The military and society
are two different things.
Men start with a higher salary
as compensation for the service
men provided for the government.
I agree that our country
used you against your will.
But
the country should pay you back,
not individual companies.
Ask for more pay for the time served
or demand a reunification.
Vote for someone who's willing
to change the national policy.
You didn't vote, did you?
Give me the money
and order as much as you want.
I'll pay the difference.
I won't say no to that.
-What's the occasion?
-The bill, please.
He got job offers from
Winner and Real today.
Really?
Why?
Jeong-o had an interview with Winner too.
But why didn't she get an offer?
Men are easier to order around.
-Congrats.
-Thanks.
I don't know why they chose me over you.
You scored higher than me in
TOEIC and Speaking.
I don't know why they didn't choose me,
but I also don't want to know
why they chose you.
So I came up with two reasons.
One reason is that I'm strong, since I'm
a man and I learned patience in the army.
Women have more patience.
We deal with bone-crushing
menstrual pain once a month.
Would you like to experience it?
It's just as painful as
guerilla training in the army.
I don't want to talk about gender
discrimination. It's useless anyways.
What really bugs me
is the fact that men who hold
the power in our society
only see the world from a narrow viewpoint
based on their own experience.
They judge women
saying that
we are impatient and opinionated
and have been ruining my future.
I'm too jealous to drink with you.
You see, I'm petty.
Women aren't petty, but I am.
Jeong-o, wait.
Hey, stop sending messages.
HWIGANG R&D EMPLOYMENT ANNOUNCEMENT
I want to ace the interview tomorrow.
-How many interviews do you have tomorrow?
-Four, but I'm open to more.
Hi, Mom. Are you home?
A coffee shop?
Are you drinking again?
Did you sign any new clients today?
No?
What?
You're buying what?
Come on in.
The cafe isn't that big,
but I've been here for two hours
and it seems like business is going well.
Jeong-o,
should we ask your dad for some money?
If we managed one of these...
I don't have a dad.
I don't even know his face.
Sharing DNA doesn't make him one.
Of course I'm annoyed.
When I was in high school,
we asked him to pay my tuition
and that man called you a leech.
I haven't forgotten that.
Don't go to him. Don't you dare.
How was the job interview?
Was it successful?
Of course. I'll be getting an offer.
Sorry. I wish I could tell you
good news like that.
What is the matter with you?
What now?
Why did you hang up on me like that?
You're upsetting me.
It's not just you. I'm upset too.
Why can't you get a job
like everyone else?
Fine, I'm a loser.
Your daughter is a loser.
Do you want me to say that
and be discouraged?
I'm trying really hard
not to break down in front of you.
I tell myself hundreds of times a day
that I can do it if I give it my all.
I tell myself I'm not a loser
that I just didn't have
enough opportunities.
That's what I tell myself.
You idiot.
So why won't you let me
talk to your rich father?
With that coffee shop...
I was born out of wedlock!
You don't have to see him.
I'm willing to beg for the both of us.
You and I are the same.
If you beg, it's like I am too.
What's the difference?
Same, my ass.
When were we ever the same?
I had a child out of wedlock
while you have a college diploma.
How are we the same?
Anyone can tell that
you're far better than I am!
---
Did you wire the money?
How much?
I was only able to send eight million won.
That's all that I have.
What more can I do?
Do you want me to steal?
If you like money so much,
why don't you just sell me?
I'm not deliberately holding back.
I don't have any money to give.
Darn it.
Didn't your brother give you money too?
Why am I angry?
Why don't you cancel
your installment savings account
you opened to buy a new home?
See if it makes you happy.
Goodbye.
Damn it.
Every time I save up
some money he takes it
as if it is rightfully his.
That little brat.
I wired seven million won.
Yes, I canceled my savings bond
and wired it in your name.
Are you certain about this though?
Is your intel reliable?
It is. I promise.
-How many times must I say it?
-Sang-jun,
sort out the storage too.
Sure thing.
I better go.
I want to finish early and see Jin-hui.
Are you at the pharmacy again?
Why do they keep asking
a pharmaceutical sales rep
to clean their storage?
It's why you should work for yourself.
Okay, bye.
Jin-hui, I'll be there soon.
Just wait a little...
What do you mean you can't meet?
A blind date?
Why are you crying?
Didn't you agree to it
because of your parents?
You made the right choice.
Are you doubting me?
You idiot.
Wire me the money and come to the club.
Sure.
Sir, is the stock buying
until 10 p.m. tomorrow?
My friend bought some too.
Sure, I'll do my best.
Where are you? I'm on my way.
Seo-yeong? I broke up with her ages ago.
What do you think?
We just had nothing in common.
So how are the ladies at the club?
Who's the DJ?
X-Men?
No way. Fuck,
I'm going die if it's really him.
X-Men.
-How about this place? They prefer women.
-You in sales with that temper?
It would be a stretch, right?
Indeed.
Looking good.
Where are you going, Sang-su?
Hey. It's the bar across
the street, right?
Yes. See you soon.
-What was that?
-Did you nab them?
-Nice, right?
-Totally.
We're going for round two.
-Sang-su, Sang-su...
Why a bar and not a roadside snack cart?
This won't be enough.
We'll each pitch in 50,000 first
and 30,000 more if that's not enough.
What about you?
I'm on emergency duty tomorrow.
I'm just going to go home.
I can tell they're heavy drinkers
just by looking at them.
You'll just end up wasting money.
He's right. Are you crazy about women?
Must we give up what little cash we have
to fawn over them?
Hey, are we easy prey?
It's been a while since...
Stop lusting after women.
I have to go study. Give me my money.
You can't study while you're drunk.
I have a test tomorrow. I want my money.
They don't want to pitch in. Give it back.
-Give it back.
-We won't stay for long. Just...
Just a little...
What's your problem?
You're such a loser.
Let's just go home.
Hey.
Yes, I want a woman.
Stop it.
You bastard.
I worked any job I could for three years
and nothing worked out.
And two months ago,
my girlfriend dumped me.
-You said you had nothing in common.
-You believed that?
She dumped me because I have nothing.
You jackass.
I worked two months,
mostly overtime without a day off.
Without women...
What would I have to laugh about
without women?
Can't I just hang out with girls
and have a good time?
Can't I? Is that what you think?
You're an intern at least.
I don't even have a job.
I know your situation...
That's why I'm trying to let you have fun.
You said you liked the girl
in the red blouse.
Forget it. I don't need your pity.
You have an inferiority complex.
What? "An inferiority complex"?
You asshole.
Hey, hey, stop it.
-He called me inferior.
-Don't.
Let go of me.
Nice one.
Don't. Are you crazy?
-That's hilarious.
-My supervisor. Give me a minute.
It's work.
Can we order more drinks?
Sure. Excuse me, can we have two more?
Yes, sir.
What great timing.
Good on you. Talk to you later.
Hyeong-uk.
What's wrong with you?
I don't think I can get
a job this time around.
Say that after you take the test.
The girls drink too much.
I could end up penniless paying for them.
Let's run.
Don't forget about this.
Let's find some nice girls
at a club next time.
They were too outgoing and not our type.
I'd love to find a woman
who's willing to pay half the bill.
Hi, Mom.
Your ankle? Call my brother.
He's not picking up?
Hyeong-uk's drunk off his ass.
Call a taxi.
Mom.
I...
Hello.
Why are you carrying Hyeong-uk?
He's drunk.
You're all so useless.
You're her son?
The pharmaceutical sales rep
or the water vendor?
The water vendor.
Oh.
Sang-su, come along.
Hello, son.
Over here.
My colleague. Say hi.
-Hello.
-And her son.
Hello.
My son's a civil servant.
He works at a borough office.
He picks me up every night
saying it's dangerous for me to walk home.
-Take care.
-Bye.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Why did you come? You must be tired.
-Take care.
-Bye.
See you.
Why call me when
you could just take the bus?
How can I carry my bag
when I'm on crutches?
Are you jealous of that lady?
Are you jealous because her son is
a civil servant? Live with him, then.
What are you looking at?
She is...
going to get her employee card soon.
You know, the one you have around
your neck. She's getting a raise too.
By 120,000 won.
They can fire me,
but they can't fire her easily now.
Because she's full-time.
Civil servants never get fired either.
I won't either.
I'll be made full-time soon.
The moon's so pretty.
You're prettier.
You scumbag,
how could you just leave me and Hyeong-uk?
I have a job too.
I have to go back to work
in just three hours.
What do you mean?
You won't invest?
"An illegal pyramid scheme"?
That's just nonsense.
That's Chang-min's company. Mine isn't...
Don't invest, then.
I talked you up to my superiors
to get you a chance
to invest in us first.
My company isn't illegal.
My mom and brother put all their savings
in, so why would our...
What?
Why is our company
an illegal pyramid scheme?
I get paid.
Where's my money?
You jerk. Where's my money?
Where's your boss?
Where's my money?
-I don't know. We're victims too.
-Pay me back!
Where's my money?
You're one of them, right?
What is the matter?
What is going on?
I invested 500 million won in it.
Those bastards ate up 10 billion won.
No, I'm sure it's actually
way over 20 billion won.
-Next.
-For the last two to three months,
even their office...
We got paid 1.1 million won a month
for 2 months.
I invested 23 million won.
That was my rent deposit.
Goodness.
You should've done thorough research.
How can you just trust
their words and ads...
Right. From the doctorate certificate
to the patent certificate,
they forged everything so meticulously.
What about you?
I invested 35 million won in stocks,
and my friend invested 20 million won.
But why did they pay us
if they were going to scam us?
You morons,
didn't you guys say you're interns?
They were trying to copy
what big companies do. Can't you tell?
Then why did you get scammed?
-You little... Shall I teach you a lesson?
-Sit down!
-Gosh, it's so chaotic here.
-All right.
You obnoxious asshole.
Please sit down.
May I answer this call?
Sure, just leave your ID with us.
-We can't worry about being embarrassed!
-Where were we?
-I said my friend invested 20 million won.
-What?
-I'm speechless.
-Calm down.
Is there any way we can get it back?
Can you catch them?
Hey, where are you now?
Home?
Are you going to work in the afternoon?
Hey.
The thing is, I actually...
What? You're going to Australia? Why?
"A working holiday"?
I applied for it just in case
when I used to look for jobs,
and my application got approved.
Those at a wheat farm want me to come.
Sang-su...
Jin-hui had a blind date
with a guy who works for a big company,
and I think she likes him.
She wants to break up with me.
I know that I won't let her go
if I stay here.
Sang-su, I need to be away
for a little while.
Then when will you come back?
Why aren't you answering?
Will you never come back?
Are you abandoning us?
Why would I abandon you?
Leaving like that
is no different from abandoning us.
It's the same thing as
throwing us in the garbage can.
Tell Mom for me.
Sang-su, I'm...
sick of this country and Seoul.
Even my job where
I have to work over 20 hours a day.
I'm too exhausted.
I'm not leaving of my own accord.
It feels as if this country wants me gone.
So, I should leave.
Sang-jun.
I'll call you again soon.
Sang-jun...
The customer you're calling is unavailable
at the moment. Please leave a message
after the tone.
But I must say, he's a big guy.
Don't even get me started.
His arms are huge.
I barely managed to cuff him.
I wouldn't even have been
able to cuff him. Great work.
2015 OPEN RECRUITMENT FOR POLICE OFFICERS
-Did you see him? The newbie.
-What about him?
2015 OPEN RECRUITMENT FOR POLICE OFFICERS
Don't even think about it.
You'll have to prepare for the exam.
It'll be competitive too.
I'm not going to apply.
But civil servants are hired
solely based on their exam scores.
They don't look at other qualifications.
And even women get promotions.
2015 OPEN RECRUITMENT FOR POLICE OFFICERS
Sang-su.
Sang-su!
Why do you want to join the police force?
Just work at a company.
It'll take years for you to become
a civil servant!
Sang-su!
Hello?
I'm Han Jeong-o,
Ms. Lee Sun-yeong's daughter.
I don't know who that is.
Make sure you eat.
Take your medication too.
CRIMINAL PROCEDURE CODE
What do you want?
I guess you do know who I am.
You said you didn't know...
What do you want from me?
I'm struggling to find a job,
-so I want to...
-Cut to the chase.
I need money to study for the police exam.
Give me 20 million won.
Give me your account number.
Mr. Oh, send 20 million to this account.
Send me your account number.
I'll pay you back.
If you waste your time chatting
with friends and dating guys,
your life will be doomed.
You must keep that in mind...
I studied the study guide 30 times.
STUDY THE GUIDE 30 TIMES
I did everything
my professor told me to do.
I obeyed his every order.
IT'S A BATTLE AGAINST YOURSELF!
NOTHING IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN BECOMING A POLICE OFFICER.
Sang-jun abandoned Mom.
Yeom Sang-su, will you abandon Mom too?
-One extra-large serving to go, please.
-Sure.
I must focus only on eating now
to focus better when I study later.
Begin the roll call.
-One.
-Two.
-Eight.
-Nine.
-Ten.
-That's everyone.
Let me know if you need anything
or have any complaints.
We don't have any.
-Keep up the good work. You can do it!
-We can do it!
Have a good night.
HAN JEONG-O, LEE YE-JI,
PARK YE-JIN, JEONG YE-JIN
STUDY ROOM
POLICE
APPLICANT: HAN JEONG-O
APPLICANT: YEOM SANG-SU
I made it!
-I made it into the police academy.
-I see.
I made it...
I'm sorry, please carry on.
Sang-jun.
Call me as soon as
you get my message.
Why?
I'm made it into
the fucking police academy.
Was I not clear?
Your brother became a police officer!
A police officer!
I'm a police officer!
Here and here.
You're all done. Thank you.
Thank you so much every time.
I'll give you a call sometime soon.
Hey!
My baby!
Mom!
CENTRAL POLICE ACADEMY
-One, two, three, four.
-One, two.
-Three, four.
-One, two, three, four.
-One, two.
-Three, four.
Instead of going home tonight,
we're all going out for drinks.
Are you in?
Of course.
I'm going to get wasted tonight.
How much longer do we have to run?
I hear that the new martial arts trainer
is a hard-ass.
How much are we pitching in?
Are we only drinking
one bottle each like last time?
-Let's drink at least three each.
-You bet.
We might cause trouble if we get excited.
-Do you want to get penalty points?
-Who cares?
We'll make up for it elsewhere.
Who is this trainer anyway?
Why is he making us run the track?
I want to be out in the field already.
I'm applying for the police squad.
What about you?
Patrol division.
I'll roam the streets with a gun.
-What about you?
-The same. What about you?
Patrol division.
Finally, we're getting a break.
Please let this be the end.
Starting today,
he will train you all in martial arts.
He is the pride and legend
of the Violent Crime Unit.
This is Captain Oh Yang-chon.
Look at his face.
Someone might think he's a culprit.
Steady...
And rest.
Don't think about resting and run!
What? "Don't think about resting and run"?
Just because you passed the exam
and made it to the police academy,
you might think it's over,
and that you're a civil servant now.
You might've relaxed
and let your guards down.
As of this moment,
put that thought into the trash can.
Each month,
I will kick out at least one person
if they lose their focus.
What's he talking about?
He's kicking at least one of us out? Why?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What do we do now?
No one knows which one of you
will get the boot.
From this day forward,
you will learn
the sense of duty of a police officer.
The exam...
Aren't we done since we passed
the police academy exam?
Aren't we civil servants?
Civil servants...
It's a scare tactic.
Who is he to kick us out?
I studied like a mad woman
for two years just to get in.
We're not leaving just because he said so.
Don't be intimidated.
I will kick you out.
There's something scary about him though.
Steady!
Keep running in the same spot!
Do you think you're a civil servant?
Do you think
you're already a police officer?
I didn't say anything.
Since you didn't say anything,
does that mean I can't ask?
-Is that it?
-No, sir!
You don't seem to have a sense of duty.
You're wrong.
I do, sir.
In what way?
I'll do my best!
That means you joined
the academy empty-handed.
You didn't bring your sense of duty.
Run again!
-One, two, three.
-To your place.
-One, two, three, four.
To your place!
No, wait!
Please, I'm scared of heights.
One penalty point.
-One, two, three.
I...
Get ready!
I am a police officer!
I have a sense of duty!
-Descend.
-Descend!
No, wait!
Two penalty points.
Three penalty points.
-Four penalty points.
-Next.
Take your places.
Any complaints?
She studied hard
for three years to get here.
I think it's harsh to give her four
penalty points for one rappel exercise.
So it's okay to have an acrophobic cop
when someone's life is on the line?
The citizens we serve would
just love that.
One penalty point for being thoughtless.
Ready?
I am a police officer.
I have a sense of duty.
-Descend.
-Descend!
You with four penalty points.
Come back up.
Come up in 10 seconds,
or you get 5 penalty points.
We shall begin the slow fire exercise.
Load your guns.
-Loading guns.
We're all tired out from martial arts
training, and they want us to shoot?
Shooters, take aim.
-Take aim!
For your lack of discipline
in report repeat,
you each get one penalty point.
Shooters, take aim.
-Take aim!
Pull the hammer back.
-Pulling hammer back!
Begin.
Stop.
None kept your arm still.
You each get one penalty point.
Attention!
Raise your shields!
-Shields up!
Just because you passed the exam
and made it to the police academy,
you might think it's over,
and that you're a civil servant now.
You might've relaxed
and let your guards down.
As of this moment,
put that thought into the trash can.
Each month,
I will kick out at least one person
if they lose their focus.
I desperately want my juniors
to become police officers someday.
If you waste taxpayers' money,
you can't become a police officer.
You can't become a police officer.
I desperately want my juniors
to become police officers someday.
Withstand the force! Stand your ground!
-I am a proud police officer!
Here.
A bit lower.
-Here?
-Yes.
-You do it.
-Massage me.
Do you feel better?
That's enough.
Let go.
Grab onto him.
Damn it. Let go.
Freeze.
Stand up.
Cuff me.
Three penalty points
for doing a crappy job cuffing me.
for allowing a surprise attack.
For not securing your
weapon which could threaten your life,
out of pity for you,
I'll be merciful and award seven points.
A total of 13 points.
The total penalty of your training
so far is 21 points.
Doesn't 30 equal expulsion?
You have one month to go.
-What'll happen?
-I'll put my life on the line.
You, for playing easy to get
for a female trainee.
Five penalty points.
Block-off formation!
-Block-off formation!
Protesters, charge!
-Defense formation!
Three steps forward.
-Forward!
One, two, three. One.
One, two, three. Two.
-One, two, three. Three.
-Get out the way.
-Stand your ground!
-Move!
-Stay!
-You can't come through.
-I can.
Keep formation!
You didn't hold your shield properly.
You broke formation.
Two penalty points each. Recover!
-Recover!
-Jackass.
-Recover.
Han Jeong-o.
-Han Jeong-o.
-Over here.
You're being moody.
Do you want to be penalized?
Why aren't you in bed?
I don't mind being expelled.
Are you crazy?
You got this far. Why give up now?
You have to graduate.
Go back inside. You'll get
penalty points if you get caught.
If I don't cool down now,
I'll go mad before
I graduate or get expelled.
That, or I'll run up to Oh Yang-chon
and take a bite out of his neck.
I like your tenacity.
I will graduate for sure.
I don't doubt that.
CENTRAL POLICE ACADEMY
Isn't that Oh Yang-chon's car?
Where's he going?
Who cares where he's going?
You two.
Are you dropping out? Goodness.
I've been called out
into the field as of today.
I see you didn't know.
Didn't I mention it?
You should've held out a little longer.
Why are you leaving
when you have no penalty points?
You and this place
are both irrational and unfair.
CENTRAL POLICE ACADEMY
You're right.
This field and I are quite unfair.
You made the right choice.
But out in the field as a police officer,
you'll encounter situations
that are more unfair.
Those who are guilty
get drunk, curse at us, kick us, hit us,
and even stab us.
But if we suppress them,
they'll file a civil complaint.
We get shot at too.
What part of the world is fair though?
Anyway, good luck!
I miss you, I love you,
it's been a while, my dear wife.
I'm sorry though.
I'm getting called back to the precinct,
so I can't make it home tonight.
When did you ever come home?
Check the video I sent you
and call me back.
I'm a husband just dying to see his wife.
Why would you send me a video
of a scumbag police officer
I'm a husband just dying to see his wife.
Why would you send me a video
of a scumbag police officer
harassing the people?
How about hangover soup?
I found the footage
while looking into another case.
There wasn't a civil complaint.
Loser pays. Rock-paper-scissors!
He's an officer on my team
who goes by the name of Dong-kyu.
He'll be transferred to
a cushy job in Human Resources soon.
He's a decent cop and a single father
who takes care of
his mother along with his child.
My stint at this patrol division
ends in two weeks.
Should I let it slide?
I can if I quietly erase the footage.
A complaint wasn't made.
Should I let it go?
Dong-kyu's a really fine police officer.
That's all the more reason
not to let it slide.
No matter how good he is,
he shouldn't neglect citizens.
In midwinter too.
What if he froze to death?
Report him.
How are you always so lucky?
Dong-kyu.
-Can I get a cup of tea?
-Sure.
What will I do without you here?
I don't know.
I'll miss you too.
People are watching.
Crazy bastard.
He sings and dances
after ruining others' lives,
What a psycho.
He should've told us
that he was going to leave.
He just let them quit.
Sense of duty, my ass.
He left without completing our training.
I'm pretty sure he doesn't know
what sense of duty is, either.
Crazy psycho.
Anyway, we're doomed.
Why is that?
Oh Yang-chon is gone,
and we graduate in two weeks.
We're going out in the field
starting tomorrow.
The trainees who went out
in the field last year
dropped out one by one after every class.
Oh Yang-chon only left because he knows
we'll be quitting anyway.
Why are our lives so complicated?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you sure about that?
Is field training that tough?
It is. I heard it from a reliable source.
At protests, the academy students
always form the front line.
Our seniors will only care
for those who survive it.
Fine. Bring it on.
I'll show you how feisty I can be.
Let's promise not to whine in the field.
We have to be tougher than the boys
and stay in formation.
-I agree.
-Bring it on.
I'll never break formation no matter what!
This smells like ass.
You heard the rumors.
They say field training at protests
are meant to kill us.
-Let's survive it.
-That's right!
Be careful until we make it
to our desired positions.
-We can survive this.
-Good luck.
-We can do this.
-We'll make it.
-Let's survive.
-Let's make it as police officers!
-Let's do this!
-Let's survive.
-Let's do this.
-We can survive this.
-We'll become police officers!
I heard how it can be, but I'm scared
now that I have this on.
This isn't the 90s.
The police don't have
water cannons or tear gas.
Protesters don't throw firebombs either.
The building is the base of
a pseudo-religious cult.
I hear that there's a corpse.
We're going there to scout the place.
Hey, aren't you scared at all?
My goal is
to make it to the patrol division.
I won't be intimidated.
You shouldn't be either.
CENTRAL POLICE ACADEMY
POLICE
Is everyone seated?
-Yes.
Let's go.
Attention.
Pass your batons to the front.
-To the front!
Since they are taking our batons
it must not be that bad.
It must not be dangerous.
I couldn't sleep thinking that
I had to hit people with it.
Be quiet, or we'll get a penalty point.
I'm three points away from expulsion.
I want to make it too.
Put your helmets on.
-Helmets on.
You will repeat loudly what I say.
Today...
-"Today..."
We won't take action.
-"We won't take action."
Again! Be alert and repeat what I say.
Today, we won't take action.
-"Today, we won't take action."
Not taking action means
we won't budge even if we get hit.
-"Not taking action means
-we won't budge even if we get hit."
Get your head straight!
Repeat after me again.
Not taking action means
we won't budge even if we get it.
-"Not taking action means
-we won't budge even if we get hit."
We won't be shoved
even if the protesters push hard.
"We won't be shoved
even if the protesters push hard."
We won't help our comrades
even if they get hit.
"We won't help our comrades
even if they get hit."
We will only move forward in formation.
"We will only focus on
moving forward in formation."
We will get five penalty points
if we break formation.
"We will get five penalty points
if we break formation."
We will be dismissed immediately
if we lose our shield to the protesters.
"We will be dismissed immediately
if we lose our shield to the protesters."
We will also be dismissed immediately
if we lose our helmet.
"We will also be dismissed immediately
if we lose our helmet."
Today...
-"Today..."
We won't take action.
-"We won't take action."
We won't be shoved
even if the protesters push hard.
"We won't be shoved
even if the protesters push hard."
We won't help our comrades
even if they get hit.
"We won't help our comrades
even if they get hit."
Today, we won't take action.
-"Today, we won't take action."
Let's report it to the police.
Are you saying we should let him die?
I have a job.
I'm not a loser anymore!
-I'm Probationary Officer Yeom Sang-su.
-Probationary Patrol Officers aren't cops.
Instant noodles should be
regulated by law.
You work for me. Remember that.
It feels creepy. Take your hand off me.
-Jang-mi.
-Just get out.
JANG-MI
Don't talk to me.
-Idiots!
-Let him get inspected.
Just do as you're told
if you're not going to quit.
A case like this
is rare, right?
Subtitle translation by Lexi Lee