CHARACTERS AND PLACES ASSOCIATED
IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
This is cancer.
My girl, you look so beautiful.
-Whose daughter is this?
-Yours.
You look so pretty.
You look beautiful.
I'm going to work.
See you.
Hey.
His businesses failed
10 years ago, and 3 years ago.
How can you be so sure
he'll succeed this time?
You used all our savings
for our daughter's wedding.
Now you want to mortgage our house
for your brother's business?
What would we do after retirement?
Do you want to be
forced out onto the streets?
What are you going to do?
You'll work for another
7 to 8 years as a cop.
We can always make more.
How would you know
if I'd work for another 7 or 8 years
or just quit in a couple of days?
What if I get sick and die tomorrow?
Are you a god or something?
You silly woman.
Goodness.
Why would you get sick?C
EPISODE 13
KIM KYEONG-JIN, BAE SU-JEONG,
MOON JIN-YEONG, LEE JI-MIN
Well...
I'd like to know the names
of victims of the rape cases
near Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong.
It turns out you were right about that.
Why? Did you find anything?
We just verified the identity
of the suspect
of the rape cases
from the judo association.
His name is Cho Seol-tae.
He's 35 years old.
He was a member of the national team.
He ran a judo gym until a few months ago.
The time frame of
when he shut down his gym,
and when the first case took place
are similar.
It was about 1 year and 2 months ago.
He shut down his gym
because of diabetic complications.
Kyeong-jin testified
that he had bad breath.
We compared his montage
with a photo from the list.
There are many similarities.
And
a woman just called the police
saying her husband might be the suspect.
His name is Cho Seol-tae.
He's the same man
Lieutenant Oh was talking about.
She found some name tags
in his possession.
The name tags are from
the victims of the murder and rape cases.
You said I was right.
Does that mean he is a store owner?
Yes. It's 112 Somyeong-gil,
Happy Outdoor.
I'm going there now.
I'll see you guys there.
Drive safely.
Suspect in rape and murder case
is in a white tracksuit.
Suspect headed to Jeongbal Intersection
near Chayeong Building.
I spotted the suspect!
Stop right there!
The suspect stole a scooter and fled!
It's a red scooter!
License plate number...
I can't see the number.
Suspect in rape and murder case
is in a white tracksuit.
Han-pyo, there's a trail between Mount
Baekun and Mount Somyeong around here.
-Report it.
-Got it.
Patrol 24, Patrol 24.
Chasing suspect in rape and murder case.
Suspect is heading to the trail between
Mount Baekun and Somyeong.
Patrol 24, Patrol 24.
Heading to Mount Baekun.
Requesting backup from patrol cars
in the vicinity.
It's the one turning right.
-How are you sure?
-The tracksuit is different.
And his shoes look different,
but I'm not sure.
Han-pyo, prepare for the worst.
Patrol 24, Patrol 24.
Chasing suspect in rape and murder case.
Another suspected bike spotted.
A red bike with a man
in a white tracksuit.
Seoul 40 N 7891.
Requesting backup from patrol cars...
Are you all right?
My gosh.
What did you just do to a cop?
Show me your IDs.
You may go.
What happened? Isn't he the suspect?
No, he's not.
We ran his ID. He's an ordinary citizen.
Code Zero. Code Zero.
We have tracked and located the position
of the rape and murder suspect's phone.
He's headed toward the entrance
of Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong.
at Hongil 2-dong.
Dispatch patrol cars in the vicinity
Code Zero. Code Zero.
We have tracked and located the position
of the rape and murder suspect's phone.
He's headed toward the entrance
of Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong.
That's right. This is him.
That's the perp.
We're tracking his phone.
Yeom Sang-su.
-Take care of it and request backup.
-Okay.
Patrol 24. Patrol 24.
Chasing Cho Seol-tae,
suspect in rape and murder case.
He is headed up the mountain using
the access road
between Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong
at Hongil 2-dong, 16.
Requesting backup from patrol cars.
Choi Myeong-ho,
what do you think you should do now?
We should assemble
all personnel around Mount Baekun
and Mount Somyeong.
While it's a residential area
with one entrance point,
but we can't exclude the possibility
of him going into a restricted area.
So, the more people the better.
The suspect ditched
the phone and the scooter he stole.
He went this way.
I have the suspect's phone.
Track its location.
I'm following Sang-su for backup.
-Until the other personnel arrive--
-We may not be able to wait.
You must wait. He's an athlete,
and we can't be certain that he's unarmed.
Do not arrest him alone.
Officers are gathering at the foot
of the mountain
and blocking off all escape routes.
Sang-su and you will just drive him
down the mountain.
I'll say this again.
Don't arrest him without backup.
Wait until you know for sure
that we can overpower him--
But what if he runs away?
Just let him run away!
I've made myself clear.
Don't catch him without backup.
We've already confirmed his address,
and backup is on the way.
What if he commits another crime?
I'm hanging up.
Hey, Myeong-ho!
Damn it.
Officers and patrol cars in the vicinity,
this is Lieutenant Oh
from the serial rape task force.
Officer Yeom and Senior Officer Choi
are chasing the suspect.
All detectives in the team,
except for Detective Jang and Cho,
will head towards
Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong.
They'll lead the team,
so you stay out of it.
Patrol cars in the vicinity,
keep monitoring the GPS tracking updates
provided by the situation room.
Also, block all possible
escape routes near the mountains
and support Senior Officer Choi
and Officer Yeom.
Senior Officer Choi and Officer Yeom
are chasing the suspect at the moment.
This is Captain An from the task force.
I repeat.
Patrol cars in the vicinity,
block all possible escape routes
near Mount Baekun and Mount Somyeong
and support Senior Officer Choi Myeong-ho
and Officer Yeom Sang-su. That's it.
I'm sure you want to be at the scene,
but we have a job to do here.
Patrol 22 from Hongil Patrol Division,
Patrol 22.
We're at Trail Nine of Mount Baekun.
This is Patrol 21, Patrol 21.
We arrived at the entrance
of Trail Seven of Mount Somyeong.
This is Patrol 34, Patrol 34.
We're at Trail Eight of Mount Somyeong.
This is Patrol 41, Patrol 41.
We're at Trail Two of Mount Baekun.
This is Patrol 31, Patrol 31.
We're at Trail Four of Mount Baekun.
This is Patrol 43, Patrol 43.
We're at Trail 11 of Mount Baekun.
-You should surrender.
-Listen to him.
Surrender.
My daughters are safe
because I'll protect them.
My dad tried to hit Kyeong-mi.
My mom
had no choice.
That's enough.
He might try to hurt himself.
PRESCRIPTION
He is Cho Seol-tae.
This prick needs to hear you
reciting his Miranda rights.
Too bad he passed out.
The Miranda rights aren't important.
You have to get a life sentence
no matter what, you psycho.
I hear a lot of footsteps.
Backup must be here.
The suspect is... I mean,
we caught the wanted criminal!
We caught Cho Seol-tae!
The wanted criminal has been caught!
Code Zero!
The situation is over!
The suspect has been caught!
Great work!
-Good job, guys.
-Great job!
The suspect, Cho Seol-tae,
has been caught!
-Senior Officer Choi and Officer Yeom
-It's over.
arrested Cho Seol-tae.
Cho Seol-tae has been arrested
-Cho Seol-tae has been caught!
-near Trail Seven of Mount Baekun.
Code Zero.
The situation is over now.
I repeat. Senior Officer Choi
and Officer Yeom of Hongil Patrol Division
caught Cho Seol-tae
near Trail Seven of Mount Baekun...
The rape and murder suspect,
Cho Seol-tae, has been arrested
in the restricted area
near Trail Seven of Mount Baekun.
The rape and murder suspect,
Cho Seol-tae, has been arrested.
The search is over.
The rape and murder suspect,
Cho Seol-tae, has been arrested.
The search is over.
All officers who are searching
the areas near the mountains,
please return to your positions.
All officers who are searching
the areas near the mountains,
please return to your positions.
Senior Officer Choi and Officer Yeom,
great work.
Thank you, sir.
-Let's all go out for drinks soon.
-Sure.
Hey, we'll see the ambulance go
and head back after.
-See you guys at the station.
-Yes, sir.
See you.
Hey.
Good work.
You too, sir.
-Hello, how can we help...
-Where's everyone?
At the cafeteria upstairs.
No one has left for the day.
Everyone is so excited.
Isn't it so good?
-Yes, it is.
-It's delicious.
Are we just getting fried chicken
for catching a serial rapist?
This is wrong.
Then give it to me!
We got you sandwiches and fried chicken.
-What more do you want?
-Hey, then what should we do?
-Should we sell the pillars to
-buy you ribs
-or a steak?
-or a steak? You punk.
-My gosh, you're an adorable kid,
-You're an adorable kid,
-a good kid, and a lanky kid.
You guys did a great job,
but that was very dangerous.
You should've just shot him.
Why did you fight unarmed?
What if you got hit in the eye
with the baton?
Then you would've gone blind on the spot.
Just like Senior Officer Song at Mapo.
-But we should refrain from using guns.
-Yes, I agree.
When a cop uses a gun,
it's not the suspect who dies,
we'll die from the penalty.
"Why did you shoot him
when he was unarmed?"
Have we ever gotten away
with shooting a suspect?
The citizens always
expect cops to fight without weapons.
The children of the people
who say such things
should all become cops.
-Why are you cursing them?
-You know it's a curse.
Just congratulate them on a job well done.
Why say anything more?
Sam-bo, were you there today?
Yes.
My words exactly.
They're jealous that I caught the bastard.
Besides, it's me who got hurt.
Hey, that's not true.
I see your confidence is through the roof.
Yeom Sang-su, what was that again?
Well?
I knew you'd get an earful.
Yang-chon, go on and lecture him.
You should consider yourself lucky
that you weren't badly injured.
The suspect was skilled in judo.
Is your life just your own?
In Seoul alone,
a single field officer,
not including those on desk duty,
is responsible for 1000 civilians.
If you factor in breaks,
vacation, and shifts,
that number goes up
to about 4,000 civilians.
Even so, you fought against him
just so that you could cuff him!
Good job. Congratulations!
-Nice!
-You too, Myeong-ho.
Well done, you two.
Lucky him.
I'm green with envy.
You'll be on big cases started next month.
As if I'd get the chance.
Once I retire,
you'll be teamed up with a younger,
more sprightly mentor.
But sir...
I didn't mean it like that.
Why aren't you heading home?
After I retire,
I'm going to operate an excavator.
Leave. I need to study.
What about something else?
Operating an excavator is hard.
"You shift gears
using oil pressure."
You
were very brave. Good job.
Your description of the suspect
was crucial.
What you told us about the strange scent
coming from his breath...
That gave us a clue
and helped us figure out he was ill.
That's how we spotted him at a hospital.
You're the one who caught him.
Your mom is being let out.
Tomorrow morning,
she'll come to the center.
Your dad won't forgive your mom,
but he apologized to you two.
Until you forgive him,
he'll let you have some space.
The hard part is all over now.
It's all over.
Are you heading home?
We should go for a drink.
Should we?
Myeong-ho, why the long face?
It's still depressing, that's all.
We may have caught the bastard,
but that doesn't erase
what happened to the victims.
Take a page out of his book and grow up,
Sang-su.
Unlike him, you were lighting up
with glee over catching the perp.
We can be happy about catching the perp.
What more is there to it?
So what if I'm in high spirits today?
We should drink at my place.
The rule of our division is that
we drink one round
to guarantee the safety of the people.
Unfortunately,
one round won't cut it today.
Let's go to my place.
Hye-ri and Jeong-o can join us.
-Okay?
-I can't today.
You two go ahead.
Actually,
I'd rather drink alone at home.
See you tomorrow.
Didn't you just agree to drinks?
-Is it because I mentioned Jeong-o?
-Yes.
I'd rather spend time with her alone.
Not in a group but alone.
I'll get going then.
It seems like
Myeong-ho just sucker punched you.
It's not like she's his girlfriend.
Let's go and get a drink.
I'm sending off my mother tomorrow.
Where?
Are you changing hospitals?
That's just it.
You're right.
She's changing hospitals.
It's easier to think of it that way.
Be careful next time though.
You could die.
Who are you becoming like?
You're so reckless.
Who do you think I'm becoming like?
I'm becoming like you.
Me?
Me? Is that so?
Am I your friend?
Because it sounded like
you were addressing me as one.
Don't be such an ass!
God, I want a drink.
Hey.
Can't you see that we're sleeping here?
I'm sorry.
An overseas resident officer?
It's what I'm leaning towards.
Rather than working domestically,
I want to work overseas.
What about you? Violent Crime Unit?
I don't know. I'll think about it later.
Right now,
I want to celebrate catching
that son of bitch, Cho Seol-tae.
Do you also think
that my spirits are too high?
Yes.
I caught the bastard, so who cares
-if I enjoy the moment?
-Who said you can't?
Yang-chon and Myeong-ho.
They said that catching the suspect
doesn't change the world.
The victims were still attacked,
and they have to live with it forever.
That's right too.
But
there's something more important.
"Something more important"?
What's that?
The fact that I caught the perpetrator.
Therefore,
he won't be able to abuse
any more victims.
5th, 6th,
7th possible victims.
We.
I.
You.
We stopped that. We saved them.
That's why I...
You, me, us...
We have to celebrate this moment.
So, we must stay strong
and catch more bad guys.
Am I wrong?
You're right.
I caught the criminal!
I caught the lunatic
who's worse than an animal.
I caught the fucking bastard myself!
Kyeong-jin said...
Kyeong-jin and her mom said that
they're grateful to us.
What?
Kyeong-jin said...
Kyeong-jin and her mom said that
they're grateful to us.
What?
They're grateful.
I'm grateful too.
That you caught him.
This will go on my sense of duty list.
Look at this.
JU-YEON
The internet cafe kid I saved.
He's at a shelter,
and his mom visits sometimes.
And this.
POLICE ADMINISTRATION
The kid who cut the side of my face
sent me this saying
he wants to be a cop like me.
And...
RECORDING 001
I'm grateful too. That you caught him.
Now I have this too.
I'll save it in my sense of duty folder.
As life goes on,
one day
-A bright day will finally greet us
-Even on cloudy days
-When a new day comes
-The sun will come out and shine
I love you.
We're fortunate
I'm drunk.
To be young
That's just stupid. What's wrong with you?
-So don't be stingy
-And straighten yourself up
-The sun will come out tomorrow
SENIOR CHOI MYEONG-HO
Lift your chin. Look up.
I can do it.
You don't do it properly.
You always miss a bit.
That's only because my eyes are dim.
If your eyes are dim, be more thorough.
Use your hands
to feel your chin and cheeks as you go.
-Dad.
-What?
Let's think that Mom
is moving from the nursing home to heaven.
Think of it that way.
I think it's done.
Your suit's so old.
We should've bought one.
Your mom bought me that.
A new suit would feel strange.
Would it?
Would a new suit feel strange?
You wear this. It would make her happy.
Okay.
You becoming a cop
was the best thing you did for your mom.
Think about it that way.
Don't just look into the fridge.
Drink if you want to.
Your team caught a serial criminal.
Go to bed.
Drink or don't drink,
just go to bed early.
You don't want to look puffy
at your daughter's wedding.
There's an opening for police corporal
at Bomun in Chungcheong Province.
TEAM LEADER KIM
Hi.
Yes, I got the text.
Really?
There's an opening for police corporal
at Bomun in Chungcheong Province?
That's great.
Everyone knows
that's a cushy title.
Yes.
A senior of mine worked there.
Is it true that it'll open up soon?
No, there are no problems at Hongil.
I have some personal issues.
I know that this is all you can do.
I can't ask for favors.
Yes, I know that. I know.
-Hi, Sam-bo.
-Hi. Is everyone here?
-Not yet.
-Okay.
When we worked in Gangnam,
he was Han-sol's and my senior.
I should go inside first.
Sure, go ahead.
He walks with a limp.
That's Min Su-man.
He was a traffic cop,
and a drunk driver hit him.
He visited our division once.
Didn't you see him?
He works as a security guard in our area.
I don't know.
But doesn't he receive a pension?
Why does he work as a security guard?
Seven years ago,
when he was interrogating
a hit-and-run driver who killed a family,
he lost his temper and punched the guy
because he was so shameless.
But unfortunately, he fell
and ended up injuring his spine.
So Su-man got fired for excessive force,
and he's still paying back the loan
he took out to pay for the damages.
Goodness.
You still have a few days before
you retire. You should be careful too.
Yes, I should. See you later.
CONTACTS
CAPTAIN AN JANG-MI
Hey, are you going to come?
You shouldn't.
People will understand.
I should be there.
Chief Ki's only child is getting married.
How's Yang-chon? Is he okay?
Ask me directly from now on, will you?
Come out. I'm going to drink some water.
Yang-chon always talks like that,
you know.
I have a blind date, so I can't go
to the hospital this afternoon.
You know how stubborn my mother is.
I heard that she's a divorcée,
who used to be a doctor.
She has no kids.
You should meet her.
Who knows? You might like her.
Don't you worry. I'm going to meet her.
You said you don't like me,
and it's not like
I want to be single forever.
But what I'm saying is,
why does it have to be today?
Well, I guess I'll see you here anyway,
but explain my situation
to Yang-chon for me.
Yes.
All right.
-Gyeong-mo.
-Han-sol.
Gosh, please wear your uniform properly.
The guests will see this. Goodness.
Hey, I heard Yang-chon
decided not to have a funeral.
Yes, it was his father's decision.
His sister, who lives on an island,
visited last week,
and she's too ill to come.
They want to keep it quiet.
Right.
She lived like a dead person
for a long time,
so a funeral might be unnecessary.
By the way, why are you sweating so much?
Are you nervous about this wedding?
This is so unlike you.
Well, I am a little nervous.
You look dashing.
Let's go.
Gyeong-mo.
I'm sorry
I made you come
to our patrol division.
At least you know.
Will you be able to smile
at the wedding today?
I have to smile.
I can't ruin someone else's wedding.
Let's go.
Come in, guys.
My, you look stunning.
Gosh, who's this beautiful lady?
-How gorgeous.
-My gosh.
-She looks so beautiful.
-My, is she an angel or what?
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
Are you okay, sir?
Yes, of course.
-How beautiful.
-She's stunning!
She's beautiful.
Of course!
She obviously got her looks from us.
My wife and I worked very hard
to have our beautiful daughter.
My daughter is very popular,
so she won't have time
to take photos later.
Everyone, gather around and sit.
Honey, let's sit down.
All right. Let's sit, everyone.
Let's take a photo, everyone.
Mentors, stand behind the bride.
Mentees, sit in front of her.
Everyone, gather!
She looks so beautiful.
Sit here.
Congratulations on arresting the suspect.
We should go out for drinks soon.
Okay.
Sit down.
My gosh, hey.
-Be quiet!
-They want us to sit.
Yes, please be quiet.
-The tall gentleman, more to your right.
-Me?
-That looks great.
-Move over.
Hey, can you...
My daughter.
You have to live well, okay?
Be happy.
You've said that over a hundred times
this week alone.
Did I?
All right, I'll take your picture now.
Everyone, look at the camera.
Guys, let's shout our slogan together.
Everyone, one, two, three!
-Go Hongil!
I'll take another shot.
Everyone, look at the camera.
One, two, three!
-Go Hongil!
Just leave it if you can't do it.
You said you wanted to wear a tie
for the first time in your life.
You should wear it.
I'll figure it out.
I'll do it.
Father, I guess you want to look good
when you say your last goodbye to Mother.
I can see that you even
took a bath and shaved.
She'll be able to leave this world happily
after seeing how handsome you are.
The team members are here.
Out of all the mentees,
Captain Eun only told me.
He said I should know.
I should know, don't you think?
I should because I'm your partner.
I'll go in first.
It's done. You look very nice.
Thanks for everything you've done.
I didn't even do much.
All right. If you're ready,
please say your last goodbye to her.
Father.
Say goodbye to Mother.
I don't even deserve
to say anything to her.
I'm sorry.
See you soon on the other side.
You should say goodbye to her too.
Yang-chon, say goodbye.
Mother.
Mom.
I know that
you went through a lot
to raise a bad son like me.
Rest in peace.
You guys should wish her well too.
-Grandma.
-Rest in peace.
Mother.
Thank you for everything.
You can rest in peace now.
Then,
we'll now take Ms. Geum Mi-ja
off the ventilator.
Ms. Geum Mi-ja
has passed away.
Time of death, April 21, 2:33 p.m.
Boys, let's all salute her.
As you were.
Thank you.
Sure.
-Thank you for coming.
-Thank you all for coming.
-Please don't mention it.
-We're doing what we must.
Why did you come
on such a good day for you?
Jeez.
Old age has made you soft.
Please don't cry.
It's your daughter's wedding day.
Don't cry.
Once he takes the test next month,
he'll be promoted.
We don't expect you to bring anything.
Once you pass the test,
will you be joining
the National Police Agency
-and leave the patrol division?
-Yes, of course!
One of his brothers is a judge,
and the other is a diplomat.
He didn't join the patrol division
because that's all he's cut out to do.
He just wanted to serve
the entire police community.
Just so you know, he's ambitious.
Yes, I can see that.
I think there's a misunderstanding,
but it's all police work
no matter where you're stationed.
I just love being an officer.
Will you excuse me?
Didn't you say you were 40?
You do not look your age.
Mom, I have to leave. Something came up.
THE LATE GEUM MI-JA
I was jealous to see you cry
if I'm being honest.
These days,
I worry that
I won't be sad when my parents die.
What if I don't shed a tear?
That's what I've been thinking.
Do your parents and your brothers
still hate that you became a cop?
It's not that per se.
They hate I'm at a patrol division.
It's not worth bragging about.
You're taking the promotion exam.
Work at the agency.
Working the field is more
my style than yours.
The problem is...
Annoyingly enough,
being in the field is growing on me.
Regardless, I'm going to go to the agency.
Did Sang-su and the rest leave?
Yes, they called a taxi.
Song-yi works part-time,
and Sang-su should go home too.
What's with the alcohol?
Let's have a drink.
The kids nag me.
They want us to reconcile.
They're worried about their grandpa
and about you too.
Dad likes it here.
And
wanting us to reconcile
is just the kids talking.
Don't mind them.
To be honest, I like what we have now.
Separate but together.
But if it's what you and the kids want...
No, let's stay apart.
I need to be punished a little more.
While I was crying
because of my mom today,
I thought about
how your parents passed away
at the same time.
I wondered, "What did I do then?"
When you had a miscarriage at 26
for being overworked...
You were at a crime scene.
I could've come to you.
But I couldn't face you.
I didn't know what to do if you cried.
Then and even now.
Even still, I should've gone.
As always, I ran away.
To the field, into a crime scene.
When I saw the kids when I came home,
I thought,
"When did they get so big?"
Then when I think about it,
the answer is clear.
You raised them yourself.
I don't deserve to be with you.
When I got violent over Ju-hyeong's case,
and when I dealt with Song-yi's boyfriend,
I saw myself clearly.
I'm still emotional, violent,
and dangerous.
You must've had a hard time facing me.
You must've been uneasy.
I wasn't reliable.
Oh Yang-chon.
Do me a favor.
Don't go too far.
Having you in my life
is a huge support.
If I were to lose you too,
I think I'd be really sad.
I mean that.
I am
always
near you.
Whether I'm here in Paju or a crime scene,
I'm close enough
that I can come running whenever you call.
Did you know?
You're the only woman in my life.
It's true.
Now my mom's gone.
I love you.
Me too.
Where are the security cameras?
There, there and...
Code Zero, Code Zero.
Someone posted a notice of a future
sexual assault on social media.
It says a schoolgirl
leaving Mahyeon High School
will be kidnapped and sexually assaulted.
We're off on patrol.
Those patrolling the area...
Take a break. You said you feel sick.
You don't look well.
Those patrolling the area,
convene at Mahyeon High School.
Code Zero, Code Zero.
Someone posted of a future
sexual assault on social media.
It says a schoolgirl
leaving Mahyeon High School
will be kidnapped and sexually assaulted.
Those patrolling the area,
convene at Mahyeon High School.
Code Zero, Code Zero.
Patrol 20, Patrol 20.
We'll respond to the Mahyeon High
sexual assault.
Heading over right now.
Patrol 24, Patrol 24.
We'll respond to the Mahyeon High
sexual assault.
Heading to Mahyeon High. Last call.
Patrol 23, Patrol 23.
We'll respond to the Mahyeon High
sexual assault.
Heading over right now.
A school is the one place I hate to go to.
It happened a long time ago,
but once...
In the trash of a girls'
high school toilet,
we found a newborn
a student had given birth to.
That traumatized me.
I shudder when I think of schools.
We have nothing better to do.
This is newsworthy.
That's enough.
We have so much to do.
There's a sexual assault case
at Mahyeon High.
There's not a case. There was a warning.
It's the same thing.
Don't we have guts?
Why should we protect the family
of a rapist and murderer?
They're being harassed by their neighbors?
Then tell them to move.
They got wearable devices.
Why should we waste
taxpayers' money to patrol their house?
-We even filled our tanks--
-Gosh, you don't stop, do you?
Damn it.
I'd do that if I lived here.
What's wrong with throwing trash
and spray-painting?
A girl died,
and six other girls were raped.
-Raping them because he was frustrated--
- Sexual assault.
Murder. Did his kids do it?
They put their house and store
on the market, so they can move.
The wife's mother
won't take them in
because the kids are of his blood.
The wife's not eating
and won't leave the store.
Those poor kids.
See the scratches on their faces?
It must be from the neighborhood kids.
Why don't you tell them
what you just said to me?
Fine, we'll go by the book.
We'll patrol the area
and then head to Mahyeon High.
MURDERER! LEAVE
OR YOU'LL SUFFER THE SAME FATE
Kids, that's dirty.
Don't touch it. Stop.
What are you looking for?
Mom threw away the doll
my dad bought for me.
My robot too.
A doll and a robot?
MURDERER! LEAVE
OR YOU'LL SUFFER THE SAME FATE
-Their dad's a murderer.
-He's a bad man.
Do it again and I'll arrest you.
Tell me what the doll looks like.
Is it a girl?
Are you looking for this?
Yes.
I'll help you look.
Where could the doll be?
-My God.
-Thank you for your help.
Are you kidding me?
Parents, please.
Why did this have to happen on a day
of a PTA meeting?
Captain, what should we do?
Are all the students accounted for?
Yes, the teachers are checking.
Now, we wait.
Teachers without classes
will gather at the teachers' room
and make sure no one leaves the school.
Yes, ma'am.
Detective Jang,
did we get the warrant
to track the IP address?
Put Prosecutor Kim on the phone.
Where's my warrant?
What do you mean it's not enough?
What more do you need?
Do you need definitive proof
that a girl was raped or killed?
Is that what you need?
This is why I can't accept the fact that
only the prosecution can issue warrants.
Mr. Kim.
You're new on the job,
so you don't know better.
Meanwhile, I do, so you listen to me.
Give me my warrant!
Potential Rape Case at Mahyeon High.
Aiding officers, be advised.
I have asked to track
the culprit's IP address.
We will provide protection
until the threat is eliminated.
Classes end in an hour.
We will contact the guardians
of all the students
and make sure they get home safely.
Check the library, gym,
music room, science lab,
and even the garbage dump.
Check all locations that can be
an entry point thoroughly.
-Lock down the school.
-Excuse me, sir.
Check all suspicious
passersby and vehicles in the vicinity.
Detective, please help.
A student from my class is missing.
She was at the science lab,
but now she's missing.
She's Park Eun-bi in
class three of year three.
She's about 160cm tall and has curly hair
with fair skin.
Officers, be advised.
Park Eun-bi in class three of year three
has been missing since her science class.
Officers, be advised.
Park Eun-bi in class three of year three
has been missing since her science class.
-She's about 160cm and has curly hair.
-What?
She also has fair skin.
Jeong-o,
I'll aid you here
since it's the ladies' room.
-Call for me if you see something.
-Yes, sir!
What now?
I'm busy, so keep it short.
Is anyone in there?
I know you're in there.
Answer me.
Who's in there?
Sergeant Kang. Sergeant Kang!
Please open up.
Open up! Come on!
I didn't do anything wrong
that I need to apologize for.
How are Jeong-o's living conditions?
Will she be okay if she gets fired?
Yesterday and today,
after hearing my story,
you haven't said anything
or tried to comfort me.
Hye-ri!
Why am I the only one
getting disciplinary action?
I want to tell you that I'm proud of you,
that I'm proud of
how you handled yourself.
But I'm too sad to say anything.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park