You're foolish.
Your Highness,
I'll be back late.
And you come to look for death.
Your Highness.
Guess what I have for you.
Second brother, you came to me late at night.
What's important?
Second brother, you are...
Third Brother.
Hand over the soul of Master Bai Zaizai.
Take the Tiger Tally.
Second brother,
If you and me join hands,
we can take down the nation.
At that time, you will be your Carefree King.
Won't you be happy?
Third brother.
I hope you won't forget
when I was in the military power,
I didn't kill them.
Because I don't want to see you and me fighting each other.
Your Highness,
I am going to escort Liu Chang Ge.
Shen Yi,
are you really going to die with me?
Five years ago, Xing Yue died and
we can only stop if we don't die.
Master.
It's here.
You've been through a lot.
Master,
tell me how to save you.
I have already died.
And I'm powerless.
When you help me out of the cage,
that's to help me get free.
It's here.
I've turned you into a human.
We've only been together for a few years.
Know a lot of things.
To teach you these things.
♪ You should remember ♪
Don't be blinded by hatred.
Your Uncle has gone astray.
He will reap what he sow.
Don't avenge me.
Can you promise me that?
Good child,
In the future,
you have to go by yourself.
Just do whatever
whatever you want.
Don't leave yourself regrets.
And don't disappoint yourself.
Such a difficult world.
It's
see yourself,
and see the world.
And see all living beings.
Master.
What should I do?
I don't have any teacher.
I don't have a teacher.
Who would use the folding fan?
I smile and ask who owns the folding fan.
After several years of reunion,
♪ I ask if this hatred is strong ♪
♪ Hold on to the past, remember to treasure it ♪
♫ Every word is short ♫
♪ A good dream against my will ♪
♪ It's a long journey ♪
In this life
melt with this love
If wind into the sky,
looking for the deep night light
a dazed and confused sleep. I can't feel the chill.
Why would I fear the pain? I'm not afraid of this calm.
I told Zicheng that I would live and die to make a fortune
but those are ancient legends.
♪ Hold your hand and grow old with you ♪
♫ Mottled in the memories ♫
Intertwined with each other
♫ How can we face passing by ♫
♪ Holding hands and looking at each other with tears, I can't even say a word ♪
♪ From the pen, I won't live ♪