Obey god's will
and the emperor's command:
The Demon Hunters are destroying lives.
His party was put on death row.
And the eldest prince, Changhe, rebelled.
Now he is dead.
Let bygones be bygones
your Highness,
you can't tell right from wrong.
And lost his popularity.
To abolish the Duke from now on
that's all.
I hope you'll remember that lesson today.
It's the talent I gave you that
you can't steal it.
If the next time,
will be killed without amnesty.
Yes
I accept the imperial edict.
Brother.
I've told you that
I came from another world.
I know that.
You said that
It seems that
not all time travel
can be the protagonist.
I'm not capable.
Maybe I can only be an extra.
Need some soy sauce.
Qing'er, I thought you have me.
Brother.
As long as you're here,
that's why I don't feel like the most miserable person.
Qing'er,
don't think too much.
Now the northern barbarians are ready to attack.
It's time for us to accomplish great things.
Alright.
We will get ready
set out to the border.
Come on.
Please.
Greetings, Father.
Ge'er.
Don't be so formal.
The antidote to Shen Yi.
The Imperial Hospital has studied it for days.
To find out the ingredients.
Will be produced in batches in a few days.
Wang Xia and his officials
and other officials.
I didn't expect Shen Yi
would do such vicious things.
Luckily, I've been on guard.
Jie'er brought back the fake Tiger Tally last time.
You said we went along with his trick.
Just let them use the real Tiger Tally to rebel.
To find out the spy in the imperial guards.
Now it seems
you were right.
I'd like to thank you for pretending to be ill.
To force Shen Yi and the others to rebel.
Ge'er!
Your clever tricks
so that Shen Yi walked into your trap.
Your achievement is no less than
Is no less than when you helped me ascend the throne a few years ago.
I dare not take any great achievements for myself.
I only hope that you will
promise me two things.
What you promised me.
First, Wang Xia is free
he was greedy,
he's loyal to the Liu family.
Father, please take back the late emperor's order
summon him back to the Imperial Palace.
As the Palace Steward.
Got it.
The second is
I hope you can let me and Bai Zaizai
to live in seclusion in the mountains.
Ge'er,
the investigation shows
bai Zaizai is indeed a demon.
You'll be the emperor in the future.
When two human beings and monsters fall in love,
how will the people
think of you?
Father,
the moment I handed over the Tiger Tally,
I knew I'm not fit to be an emperor.
I can't take on such an important position.
Enough.
You can leave now.
Your Majesty.
That's a yes?
I don't want to
I don't want to be bothered by you.
Exactly.
Thank you, Father Emperor.
Go on.
What is it?
My life is short.
Will have no joy without you.
You are the only person I ever met.
I was born with no joy.
Come on.
Mind your words.
From today on,
you own me?
Your Highness,
do you want to?
I have a request.
You can only eat carrots with me.
Will you
It's a deal
stop!
Stop!
Let's see where you run to.
Got you, right?
Liu Chang Ge.
Put me down.
Who would use the folding fan?
I smile and ask who owns the folding fan.
After several years of reunion,
♪ I ask if this hatred is strong ♪
♪ Hold on to the past, remember to treasure it ♪
♫ Every word is short ♫
♪ A good dream against my will ♪
♪ It's a long journey ♪
In this life
melt with this love
If wind into the sky,
looking for the deep night light
a dazed and confused sleep. I can't feel the chill.
Why would I fear the pain? I'm not afraid of this calm.
I told Zicheng that I would live and die to make a fortune
but those are ancient legends.
♪ Hold your hand and grow old with you ♪
♫ Mottled in the memories ♫
Intertwined with each other
♫ How can we face passing by ♫
♪ Holding hands and looking at each other with tears, I can't even say a word ♪
♪ And that sentence, "He refuses to live." ♪
Your Majesty.
What caused you to panic?
Something's wrong.
The northern barbarians have invaded our borders.
Our army has captured 11 cities of Zhao.
Our army suffered heavy casualties.
Zhao has been at war with the barbarians for a long time.
It won't be a big deal as long as we don't attack Yongcheng.
Your Majesty.
Yongcheng reported that
after Queen Jing heard that the eldest prince had died,
her sanity was approaching insanity.
And escaped from the prison.
Three thousand iron armors couldn't stop her.
What?
Hurry.
Summon Sixth Prince immediately.
Yes, Your Highness.