Steward Wang.
My Lady Yuzhan,
you are the prince's most trusted person.
Then please
give this document
to the prince.
The document.
Don't bother.
Lady Yuzhan's business is my business.
Share a carriage.
Fancy!
Ideas?
Gong Sun Qing is really clever and extraordinary.
Eh, Chief Wang.
I'd like to see this outstanding talent.
Gong Sun Qing.
Yes, Your Highness.
I'll make the arrangements for you now.
Last night the stars went by last night.
East of Gui Hall by the side of Painting Tower.
Without wings of colorful phoenixes,
mind acts upon mind
that's great.
You are indeed the most talented girl of the dynasty.
She was quick-witted and outspoken.
Once this poem spreads,
It'll become a famous poem forever.
That's too kind of you.
Although I'm the daughter of a general,
I like to write poems as my enemy.
And even a little fascinated.
So she focuses more on these things.
It's like some foodies
If they like turnips, they think only of turnip all day long.
My white sister,
am I right?
Just show off
just show off your stuff.
Why did you call me a foodie?
Your Majesty.
I didn't call your name.
That you are a foodie.
You
If you're so great,
let me test you.
Don't be presumptuous.
Your Highness.
It's fine now.
Alright.
Make a poem out of radish then.
I'm screwed.
You've never memorized this before.
Furthermore,
who could be so bored and write poetry to carrot?
You don't look so confident anymore?
So talented girl can't do anything.
You don't have the right
how I am.
Don't be anxious.
Since composing poem is not good,
let's sing a song then.
It's also about turnips.
You
what?
Don't tell me you can't even sing the song.
What do you know?
Your Highness.
I'm not feeling well today.
I will discuss the implementation plan of horse-drawn carriage with you the other day.
Alright.
You two.
Sister. Sister.
What's wrong? Why are you so angry?
The guards at Second Prince's Mansion bullied me.
Will you care about them?
What?
Have some water.
Cool down.
I won't drink.
Don't worry.
He'll get the justice back for you.
I won't cheat you
how would I lie to you?
Brother.
You are the best!
Now, calm down.
Alright?
Sit down.
She's Shen Xing.
She is not
who would use the folding fan?
I smile and ask who owns the folding fan.
After several years of reunion,
♪ I ask if this hatred is strong ♪
♪ Hold on to the past, remember to treasure it ♪
♫ Every word is short ♫
♪ A good dream against my will ♪
♪ It's a long journey ♪
In this life
melt with this love
If wind into the sky,
looking for the deep night light
a dazed and confused sleep. I can't feel the chill.
Why would I fear the pain? I'm not afraid of this calm.
I told Zicheng that I would live and die to make a fortune
but those are ancient legends.
♪ Hold your hand and grow old with you ♪
♫ Mottled in the memories ♫
Intertwined with each other
♫ How can we face passing by ♫
♪ Holding hands and looking at each other with tears, I can't even say a word ♪
♪ From the pen, I won't live ♪