White Zaizai.
I don't want your master to be destroyed.
Within half a month,
give me the Tiger Tally
and the head of Liu Chang Ge.
Your Highness.
The queen is back.
I am tired.
Your Highness.
The queen is back.
She hasn't gone out for three days.
Would you like to talk to her?
Let her be alone again?
Yes
It's here.
Come in.
You don't need the antidote.
It's a deal
It's here.
Are you going to kill me?
You fool.
You don't want your sword anymore.
Your Highness.
It has been three days.
At least have a bite.
His Highness is really stuck in love.
Steward Wang, wait a second.
I have something to tell you.
Well
guard Bai.
Guard Bai.
The prince risked his life
and risked his life.
What did you say
he took the Tiger Tally
and went to Third Prince's Mansion.
When did he go there?
Two hours ago,
he said
he went to get back your most important thing.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You forced me to swear a serious oath.
Say it after two hours.
He said he couldn't return for two hours,
he would leave with Guard Bai.
And never return to the capital.
The prince has never loved someone so before.
Shen Xing loved you at that time.
He just treats her like his sister.
I can see that.
The prince is only truly happy
Is he really happy?
Now, for you,
the Tiger Tally is abandoned.
You don't want the throne?
And now I don't want to die.
Guard Bai, where are you going?
It's my fault.
I'm going to find him.
Silly girl.
Who would use the folding fan?
I smile and ask who owns the folding fan.
After several years of reunion,
♪ I ask if this hatred is strong ♪
♪ Hold on to the past, remember to treasure it ♪
♫ Every word is short ♫
♪ A good dream against my will ♪
♪ It's a long journey ♪
In this life
melt with this love
If wind into the sky,
looking for the deep night light
a dazed and confused sleep. I can't feel the chill.
Why would I fear the pain? I'm not afraid of this calm.
I told Zicheng that I would live and die to make a fortune
but those are ancient legends.
♪ Hold your hand and grow old with you ♪
♫ Mottled in the memories ♫
Intertwined with each other
♫ How can we face passing by ♫
♪ Holding hands and looking at each other with tears, I can't even say a word ♪
♪ From the pen, I won't live ♪