FINAL EPISODE
The past president Tae-joon Jang
has denied the charges of collusion
with Moojin Group
during his term in office.
However, the prosecutor states
that because Moojin Group's past chairman
Moo-il Park's testimony is very detailed
and they have supporting evidence,
they believe it will not be difficult
to prove their case.
The one who tied the knot must untie it.
I got us into this mess,
so I must get us out of it.
Don't get any stupid ideas.
Help your uncle
and take care of the company.
Of course. That's what I always do.
Also, don't bother trying to win over
people in the government
to get a special pardon
before the change in power.
Once I receive my sentence, I'll serve
my time and get out once I'm done.
-Father.
-I kissed up to jerks in power
and broke the law now and then
while doing business.
That's how I became rich.
I won't try to play games now.
I am not angry at the world,
and I don't blame anyone.
I committed these sins,
so I will carry them with me.
Gun-woo.
This wasn't easy for me to say.
Please do it for me.
I will.
It's about Bong-soo's daughter.
Don't fight with her.
The bad blood ended with the fathers.
That's enough.
I can't promise you that.
Gun-woo.
Your generation may be done,
but we are not.
It's supposed to get chilly.
Don't catch a cold.
You can't find a path in books.
When you walk, the path is behind you.
I'm not in the mood
to play word games with you.
I'm not here to argue with you, either.
Don't you want to catch Yi-kyung Seo?
I have a couple of plans.
It won't hurt for you to listen.
I don't know. Just because I'm after her,
doesn't mean I need to work with you.
That allowed her to get both you and me.
We'll have to do it right this time.
You seem confident.
All I have left is my will.
So, how will you do it right?
If you want to capture the general,
you must shoot his horse.
That's the beginning.
How long have you been following me?
Rest assured. We're not here to harm you.
You expect me to believe that?
Chairman Son requested Ms. Seo's help.
We will help you flee the country safely.
Three people replied saying
they will take on the mission.
That's all?
They tend to do their own thing.
-When are we meeting them?
-Well...
No one will come in person.
They all want to do it online.
Connect them right away.
UNKNOWN ZERO
I'm Unknown Zero,
the one who invited you to this mission.
I heard you are all skilled hackers,
so I have high expectations.
If you work together
and fulfill the mission,
you will each receive
the promised compensation.
I'll leave the details of
how you attack the target to you.
-Who's the target?
Gallery S' system.
How severely should we attack?
Unrecoverable utter destruction.
Who are you?
How dare you snoop around in my computer?
I'll track you and teach you a lesson.
Father.
Our company can do it too,
but it's in case the prosecutor finds out.
Don't make any mistakes.
That's what Ms. Seo said, too.
I'm sorry, Father.
Don't talk.
When you get to Japan,
live quietly and stay hidden.
Can we trust Yi-kyung?
If not? Will you turn yourself in?
What?
Stay out of trouble until things
quiet down. Don't come to Korea.
Before I go,
I'd like to say bye to Ma-ri.
If you wanted to be a good father...
Go quietly.
That's best for her.
Father.
Okay. Tell Tak to stay with Gi-tae Son.
You can come back.
Ms. Kim, my laptop is acting up.
Just a minute. One minute.
Ms. Kim.
I'm almost done stopping him.
It's okay now.
Done.
What's going on?
Some punks who don't know better
start trouble now and then.
The system I created must trigger
their competitive spirit.
Did you resolve it?
Yes. It was a little difficult,
but I kicked him out.
What's wrong with you?
Ms. Kim.
The earlier one was bait.
He must've been messing around
in order to see my response pattern.
What is this? How many are attacking?
What?
No way.
This can't be.
What is this?
-Ms. Kim.
-It's okay. I can...
I can recover it in no time.
I'll handle it.
Look at me.
Slow down. Calm down.
I trust your abilities.
Okay.
Hey.
I've repaid my debt with this.
What?
Making it look like TJ Foundation
made an illegal investment
was a trap your computer expert set.
It'll be difficult to recover. It'll be
better to create again from scratch.
-You worked hard and racked your brain.
-Thanks.
And I won't touch the gallery's accounts.
I'm not into stealing.
But I'll have to freeze your assets,
so you don't get ideas.
The money you see isn't everything.
Even freezing the money I see
is a great success.
I didn't know you hated me this much.
Wrong.
I like you.
It would be less tiring for us both
if you'd give up now.
I guess I'm asking for too much.
You must've prepared the next step, too.
I'll be waiting.
-Ms. Kim.
-Don't talk to me. I'm almost done.
Please work. Please.
It'll take longer than expected.
Don't rush her. She'll take care of it.
Are you moving Gi-tae Son tomorrow?
Yes. The preparations are almost done.
Once that's taken care of,
let's take care of the funding issue.
Even if we revive the system later,
we need to move the funds.
Was this Gun-woo Park's doing?
I think what old feelings remained
are gone now.
Now, our only option is to knock him down.
Did you pack everything?
Mr. Jo will be here soon.
Let's go down to the garage.
Behind you!
Let go, you jerk!
Do you know who I am? Mr. Jo!
Tak! Get Mr. Son!
Mr. Jo, wake up! Mr. Jo!
I've restored 50% so far.
If I work quickly, I should be able to...
What's wrong?
Mr. Jo...
They just began the surgery.
There was internal bleeding
in his abdomen.
Go to the gallery.
-I'll wait, too.
-Ms. Kim is working alone.
Go stay with her.
Go on.
Okay.
Where's Mr. Son?
I can't let someone like that in here.
He's being kept somewhere safe.
I've spoken with the prosecutor.
If Mr. Son agrees to the deal--
That won't be easy.
It was a pain bringing him, too.
What do you mean?
Yi-kyung Seo almost took him away.
What do you mean, it was a pain?
Did someone get hurt?
-Mr. Nam.
-Mr. Park.
There is no beautiful loss
or a valuable loss.
I know.
Once the fight has begun,
win no matter what.
I'm sure that's your philosophy.
I have bet everything on this fight.
Didn't you have the same conviction?
Just keep in mind
that our mutual target is Yi-kyung Seo.
You're the one who needs to remember
just what kind of a person
you are going up against.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
We stopped the bleeding. Any later,
and it would've been dangerous.
Thank you.
But it'll take quite a while
before he is fully recovered.
Seriously...
Ms. Seo left the hospital.
I'm going to take her place.
Do you want to go, too?
I do,
but I can't.
My job is to build the gallery's system
as soon as possible.
I'm sure that's
what Mr. Jo would want as well.
What happened to my son?
It was either Gun-woo Park, Jong-gyu Nam,
or perhaps a collaboration
between the two.
How dare they...
It's obvious what they're up to.
They'll threaten him
and hand him over to the prosecutor,
and tie me to his crimes.
But he knows nothing.
He knows nothing,
so it's easy to make it up.
If a past president's right-hand man
teams up with a corporate heir,
they can create crimes that don't exist.
Don't worry.
We'll get your son out
before he's handed over to the prosecutor,
and we'll pay them back one by one.
How can I help?
I'll take care of both the planning
and the execution.
I stopped by in case you'd be concerned.
Yi-kyung. Be careful.
He's staying in the recovery room today
and moving to a general ward tomorrow.
Okay. What about Ms. Kim?
She's still working. But I think
it's been stabilized a lot.
Okay. Call me if anything happens.
Are you going to the gallery?
No. I need to see someone.
Yi-kyung Seo made you do it, correct?
Big Love Bank's illegal loans.
She created the bank to begin with,
and controlled you behind the scenes.
Correct?
No.
I did that on my own.
That's not right.
Try to remember, okay?
Yi-kyung Seo made you do it,
and you couldn't resist her threats,
so you did as she instructed.
That's not what happened.
I'll be back in half an hour. Show him
some exercises good for his memory.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Nam!
I mean...
I...
Sorry.
Mr. Nam was rougher than I expected.
No need to apologize.
He's been through much worse in Japan.
He'll be fine.
Gi-tae Son will turn himself in soon
to the prosecutor.
He'll confess that you ordered
Big Love Bank's illegal loans.
You have no way out.
I'm disappointed. I was looking forward
to a more creative attack.
This isn't a game.
If you keep resisting,
you'll end up losing everything.
Stop on your own and go back,
before it becomes the worst-case scenario.
-Gun-woo.
-I told you,
I like you.
This is the last bit of consideration
I can show you.
Do you think it'll be over
if my money is frozen
and I'm taken in by the prosecutor?
What?
Everyone I like is here.
Se-jin.
May I have a seat, Ms. Seo?
I heard about what happened
at the gallery.
Why did you do it?
That's not for the company, either.
It's not something
you should involve yourself with.
Sorry,
but I've been way too involved already.
Se-jin.
He says I'll lose everything,
and that I should stop and go back.
What do you think?
Should I do that?
Really?
Do you mean it?
Who knows?
I guess not, because of Gun-woo.
No matter what you do,
this fight will not end.
No. I'll end it.
It's good to see you again,
but you shouldn't have come.
I agreed to run right over
if she ever called.
Didn't I tell you before
that Se-jin is my savior?
Yeah, I think so.
Give me the car keys.
You look tired. I'll drive.
It's okay.
Give them to me.
Please?
I moved the funds in Japan
as soon as I received your instructions.
They were all scared when I said
I was there in your place.
Once Ms. Kim gets the system running,
the funding issue will be resolved, right?
It'll take some time.
We'll take it one at a time.
How was Japan?
It was a total disaster.
Everything was a complete mess.
That's how it was overall, but it was fun.
Did you miss me?
I think you should look forward.
Hey...
How could you do that?
I thought we were friends.
You should say if you're coming or going.
Couldn't you at least text?
Sorry.
I'll take you out somewhere nice.
Is Mr. Jo okay?
I heard the surgery went well.
Yeah.
Stand straight.
-It wasn't your fault.
-No.
I was stupid.
I could've covered him.
It'll become a habit if you
keep regretting and blaming yourself.
-What?
-That's Ms. Seo's line.
Is it?
Anyway, chin up.
It's no fun
seeing the complainer like this.
We have a lot to do for Ms. Seo.
Seriously...
My back.
Ms. Kim, I'm back.
Se-jin.
This should be enough
to shake them up a little.
They created an entire task force
just for me.
I should show my respect.
I'll get the remaining documents
from Ms. Kim.
The system is running well again,
so it won't take long.
But what about Ma-ri's dad?
-What about him?
-If he lies to the prosecutor,
you'll have to go in for questioning.
We need to find something before then.
I doubt Gun-woo did it.
I'm sure it was Jong-gyu Nam.
You said Gun-woo has a lot of fear,
remember?
At first, he tried to stick to the rules,
even as he was betraying someone.
But as things got tougher, he kept finding
new excuses and rationalizing to himself.
Eventually, he'll come to believe
that those reasons and goals are real.
So? Do you feel sorry for him?
Yes.
In my eyes,
you are the same.
Is making someone President
and becoming the wealthiest person
in the country
the top that you want to reach?
It isn't.
When you get there, there will be stairs
to somewhere higher.
I can worry about that once I'm there.
I know.
You'll keep climbing without worrying
since you don't want to live
a single second if you're dead.
And that...
makes me sad.
-Se-jin.
-Mr. Jo is unconscious
and Ms. Kim has no one to lean on,
but you will not stop.
You'll keep climbing up
and stand alone at the top.
You, up there,
seem beautiful
yet sad at the same time.
Tak and I will figure out the problem
regarding Ma-ri's dad.
I'm sure we can come up with something.
What's going on with Yi-kyung?
Is it going as planned?
We're taking our first step
for the Neo City Project today.
Don't worry about that.
It'll just give you a headache.
Make sure it doesn't hurt the company.
What happened with Mr. Son?
He's resisting,
but he won't last much longer.
Are you done with your part?
The task force is gathering documents
that may appear to be illegal loans.
Gallery S and Chunha Financing had
so many transactions,
it'll be a piece of cake.
It's our first and last time
working together. Let's do this right.
Over the past 15 days,
the Neo City Project completed
receiving outside investments,
and on the first of next month,
we will be breaking ground.
The project is being hailed as the biggest
construction since the founding of Korea.
It'll be the best opportunity
for Moojin Group
to prove our potential and capabilities.
They'll have to rush
before the business gets held up.
They want to get the business running
before the licensing corruption
that Chairman Moo-il Park was involved in.
They can rush, but it'll be useless.
If these internal deals that were involved
in obtaining the land get out,
the Neo City Project will come to
a complete halt.
I went to the site,
and there isn't even an office there.
That isn't all.
Most of these companies
are paper companies.
They bought land using the names
of paper companies,
and bought them for much more
once the project was announced.
It's so easy for the rich to make money
in this country.
And the money they made from it
probably went into their slush fund.
Do you think Gun-woo knows as well?
I'm half sure.
It was before he took over the project,
so he may not know.
Ms. Kim, you can do
the additional investigation.
Tak and Se-jin, mark Ma-ri.
It'll be a pain if we lose Gi-tae Son.
Okay.
But Se-jin, are you back at the gallery?
I'm not back
and I'm not working part-time either.
I'm just here to help for free.
That's not right.
You're thorough when it comes
to calculations. You can't do that.
Meeting adjourned.
Goodness.
Why are you doing this to yourself?
You have to pay for your sins anyway.
All you need to do is take someone
with you as a companion.
You must...
keep your promise.
Just make sure to get Yi-kyung Seo
on the hook.
Gun-woo Park and I will take care
of the rest.
Then...
Go ahead.
Let me see my daughter
before I turn myself in.
She has quite the temper.
If I turn myself in
without telling her first,
my daughter will disown me.
I think she noticed.
Pull up behind her.
-Se-jin.
-Go on.
Se-jin, were you following me?
I was.
Why?
To find your dad.
If we don't, our boss will be in trouble.
Where are you going?
To see my dad.
But I can't go if you follow me.
Se-jin.
I can't stand him and he's pathetic,
but he's still my dad.
Help me see my dad.
Se-jin.
The roads are slippery.
Drive carefully.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
What are you doing? Get in!
Don't go after her.
What...
I'll explain to Ms. Seo.
She's...
my friend.
There's nothing wrong
with the transactions between us.
Can they frame you with these?
Moojin's Special Team is on par
with secret government agencies.
They can fix what's there
or create what isn't.
Plus, I'm sure they've been working
with a prosecutor already.
And they want to use my son
as a witness in that production.
They'll regret it if they aren't careful.
The moment they throw a jab,
I'll counter with a final blow.
-Hi.
-I'm sorry.
Dad. Dad.
It's okay, Ma-ri.
I'm okay.
What happened to your face?
Did those jerks hit you?
No, they didn't.
I told you not to be greedy.
I don't need to go to Europe
and I don't need a sports car.
I just need you to stay, please?
I raised my daughter well.
Don't worry.
I'm turning myself in.
-Really?
-Of course. You can trust me.
See? You're not a bad person.
No one else knows.
Grandpa doesn't know, but I do.
Okay, okay.
As long as you know.
Gi-tae Son just went
to the Seoul District Prosecutor's Office.
Will he get the story straight?
Of course.
Once your task force
submits the documents,
Yi-kyung Seo won't be able
to find a way out.
Okay. We'll talk later.
Gi-tae Son turned himself in.
I heard.
If you had followed her,
Tak would've been able to handle it.
I insisted...
that we let her see her dad.
They'll come after us now.
In other words, your friendship created
annoying complications.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me.
Tell that to Gun-woo.
If Gun-woo uses Gi-tae Son
to cause trouble,
he'll have to enter a fight,
which he will obviously lose.
You pushed him into a corner
that he could've avoided.
I was thinking of Ma-ri...
Just because you have the best intentions
doesn't mean the results are beautiful.
You may go.
Forget what she said.
At least Ma-ri got to see her dad.
If they collide like this,
neither Ms. Seo nor Gun-woo
will win this fight.
They'll both be damaged,
but there will be a winner.
What if they can resolve it
without fighting?
Dream on.
Do you want to get scolded again?
I know. I can't change Ms. Seo on my own.
But I can get Gun-woo to stop.
Gun-woo Park?
No matter what you say,
he won't believe you that easily.
Well,
I won't know until I try.
Hey, Se-jin.
Did Yi-kyung declare war against me
or something?
I came to say something
you both know well.
In all honesty,
you don't want to fight Ms. Seo, do you?
Making Ma-ri's dad lie
and forging documents
is not the method you wanted, is it?
-Se-jin.
-Please stop.
Then neither of you will be hurt.
It isn't that simple.
No, it is extremely simple.
Even without a big incident
or a great opportunity,
all you have to do is tell yourself,
"Let's stop here." That's all.
I wanted something I didn't have,
and you didn't want to lose what you had.
I'm not saying that greed is bad.
I'm just saying you don't need
to use a method you do not like.
Are you saying
you found the method that you like?
I'm still searching.
But I don't plan to give up.
You and I both like Ms. Seo.
That's why we hate her,
and that's why we get angry.
It'll become much easier if you're true
to your feelings toward her.
You've changed somehow.
Is that a compliment?
Should I tell you something
you don't know?
Corruption behind
Moojin's Neo City's land purchases.
That is how Ms. Seo will attack you.
Yes, Ms. Moon.
It's a Special Team emergency meeting.
Call them in right away.
I'm on my way as well.
You and I both like Ms. Seo.
That's why we hate her,
and that's why we get angry.
It'll become much easier if you're true
to your feelings toward her.
Please stop.
Then neither of you will be hurt.
I'm going to start writing
my own music, too.
It's a gift.
Will you come watch us practice sometime?
Do you have any hobbies?
You don't even have friends, do you?
Hey, hey, hey.
Listen to some music
and make some friends.
People smell much sweeter than money.
Want me to be your friend?
I don't need it.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
It was bad luck.
Thank goodness it wasn't worse.
Gi-tae Son...
He went to the prosecutor.
I'll probably get a subpoena
in a day or two.
Would Gun-woo Park go that far?
I remembered something from the past
while I was lying here.
If we hadn't entrapped him back then,
you may have led
a completely different life.
You say useless things at times, too.
I must be getting old.
Mr. Park, the meeting will begin
in ten minutes.
Ms. Moon.
If my late uncle saw me now,
what do you think he would've said?
MOOJIN NEO CITY PROJECT EXPANSION MEETING
Before we begin our meeting today,
I have an important announcement to make.
Based on the Special Team's discrete
internal investigation,
we found illegal transactions
that exceed our imagination
during the land purchasing process.
-Gun-woo.
-This is something
that I, being in charge of the project,
cannot look past.
It is a corruption that must be exposed
for the sake of Moojin Group.
What are you saying?
I plan to punish everyone involved
and hold them accountable,
and there will be
legal ramifications as well.
Moreover, I plan to ask the public
for forgiveness
for failing to fulfill our duties
to society.
Moojin... I mean, Gun-woo Park
announced that they will stop
the Neo City Project.
Are you out of your mind?
Are you trying to destroy the company?
Were you involved, too?
I'm saying this as the chairman
because I'm worried about the company!
That's good.
As a manager,
I made this decision for the company.
Gun-woo.
"There is no need to be angry
at the world. Do not blame others,
and carry the sins
you committed yourself."
Okay, I've heard your story now.
Let's hear the other story.
Big Love Bank's illegal loans
were ordered by Yi-kyung Seo,
weren't they?
See?
You're not a bad person.
No one else knows.
Grandpa doesn't know, but I do.
No.
What?
I was solely responsible
for the illegal loans.
No one else was involved,
not Yi-kyung Seo or anyone else.
Gi-tae Son flipped his testimony on us.
He played us.
-Is that right?
-Let's push forward
with the documents you prepared.
I destroyed them all.
Mr. Park.
There may be no valuable loss,
but there must be a less embarrassing one.
That's enough for me.
I still have the rebate documents
on Chairman Moo-sam Park.
You should take that up with my uncle.
It's gotten cold.
Don't waste your energy,
and tend to Mr. Jang in prison.
Just what did Se-jin say to you?
Something so obvious that I had forgotten.
Just how much I liked you.
She made me remember that.
She shared a simple know-how with me, too.
That even without any reason or incident,
the moment I say I'll stop,
it'll all come to an end.
But you know, I knew all along,
that if we took this fight all the way,
you would win,
although I hate to admit it.
Accept it. That's a fact I know, too.
My phone has been ringing nonstop
ever since the announcement.
I should go.
So, have you let it all go, now?
What do you mean?
Like Mr. Nam would sit still?
If anything happens to my uncle,
I'll have to fill in as chairman.
If I'm lucky,
I may just become the chairman, too.
You're quite greedy. It's good to see.
I remember the joke you made
when we were with Se-jin.
Even though it was momentary,
you wanted to stop too.
Right?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Is it Mr. Jo?
No, Ms. Seo...
What about her?
What did you say to her?
-What?
-What did you say,
that she's folding everything
and returning to Japan?
-Ms. Seo.
-Hi.
You're going to Japan?
Why so suddenly?
It's no fun anymore.
There's no one to fight anymore, either.
I'm kidding. Laugh.
It isn't funny.
What is this?
Why are you suddenly leaving?
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Ms. Kim will bring Mr. Jo back
once he's recovered.
Please visit him regularly.
Tak seems seriously pissed off.
Although I'm sure he'll come too,
once he gets over it.
You still haven't told me the reason.
It's what you wanted. My stopping.
Don't be too smug.
It isn't completely because of you.
I've already seen everything
I needed to see here.
I remembered a few things
I need to do there, too.
Ms. Seo.
Stopping when you can reach the top.
That's true power.
Don't go.
Even if you start over, do it here.
Se-jin.
You said you never lose something
you once wanted.
So how could you leave like this?
I never lost it, and I never let it go.
Because Se-jin you are my mirror.
-Se-jin.
-I...
won't go with you.
I know.
I will
climb my way up
on my own here.
You should. That's why I taught you.
I need your help with one last thing.
Everything in Gallery S is
in these numbers.
Once I make the initial calculations,
you check them.
I'm warning you, it is more boring
than you can imagine.
I'm prepared.
Shall we begin?
For just one hour,
I want you to be me, Se-jin.
Can I really act...
like you?
Ask yourself, Se-jin.
Even if it's very brief,
even if it's a lie,
do you want to be like me?
You sent me there
knowing what will happen.
So? How did it feel to be me?
What did I do wrong?
Is being poor a sin?
Is it my fault I was born poor?
Of course. Being poor is a sin.
Can you really make me...
like you?
If your ambition is real,
do not be afraid of money.
If you fear the weapon you possess,
you can't win the fight.
I want all those lights.
You will become me someday.
What meaning would that spot
on top of the world have?
I'm not climbing up there
to find any meaning.
The desire to climb up.
That itself is the meaning.
I'm done.
-Any errors?
-It's perfect.
Are you sure?
Shall we do it again?
Good job.
I'll look forward
to seeing the kingdom you'll build.
It won't take long.
Every coin is a god and a life.
You lost your mind.
Find every single one.
Something so obvious that I had forgotten.
Just how much I liked you.
She made me remember that.
And...
that even without any reason or incident,
the moment I say I'll stop,
it'll all come to an end.
You wanted to stop too.
Right?
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee