You insist
on disobeying me?
The Korean market has a bright future.
Compared to the forerunners,
it's already too late to join the race.
Everything is ready.
And
Mr. Jo and Ms. Kim will be going with me.
You brat.
How dare you! Without my permission!
I'm way too old to need your permission
to do business.
Yi-kyung.
Don't go
to Korea.
It isn't
a place where we belong.
Moo-il Park and Tae-joon Jang.
Because of them?
I found this in the safe room.
I heard what happened from Mr. Jo.
The trauma of being betrayed
by friends of 30 years.
I understand how you feel.
Not at all.
They're scumbags not worth
even taking revenge on.
I never said I'd take revenge.
I'm still thinking about it.
A cruel revenge
or a useful tool.
Which would be more helpful
in creating my own kingdom?
Yi-kyung Seo, the CEO of Gallery S
has arrived.
Yes. I'll send her in.
EPISODE 6
Hello.
Oh.
You've met before, haven't you?
We've met.
Thanks to you.
You even gave him
our gallery's transaction details.
Mr. Jang is waiting.
I thought I'd be seeing him
quietly, alone.
Isn't it quiet?
We lit the Olympic cauldron,
and the doves there caught on fire too.
Gosh, it was just...
"Switch the cameras to another scene!
Silence the foreign press."
The planners were all freaking out,
and then Moo-il says,
"Tae-joon, Bong-soo,
grilled doves go very well with soju."
Whether it was money or people,
the 88 Olympics
would not have been a success
without the three of us.
Seeing the two of you here
is making me emotional.
It seems like yesterday that Moo-il,
Bong-soo and I banded together.
Before I knew it, it became time
for the next generation to take over.
From now on,
be my right-hand men.
Sir.
Moojin Group has a special place
in Mr. Jang's heart.
Ms. Seo,
if you'd like to be of help to him,
you'll have to help Mr. Gun-woo Park
become the group's leader.
I'm not sure.
There's a better option for Moojin's sake.
I know.
Mr. Moo-sam Park is the nuisance.
You'll have to give in and cut him off--
That's fine.
I came to pull Mr. Jang's sleigh.
I don't want to run with another sled dog.
I can't
give in either.
If you want me to do great things,
please trust my judgment.
I'm sure you know with what determination
I came here.
The choice is yours to make.
Why don't you cut off my uncle
and stick to Mr. Jang?
Wasn't that your objective anyway?
He's the next chairman of Moojin Group.
You don't throw out a card like that
so carelessly.
Sure.
Yi-kyung Seo wouldn't just run
backdoor art deals.
You'll make my uncle chairman
and increase the pot.
You'll carry Mr. Jang on your back
and raise the bet.
That was
the plan you mentioned
to climb to the top.
Sorry,
but your name isn't in that plan.
I said I won't join you.
I feel the same.
-Mr. Gun-woo Park.
-I showed my hand.
Mr. Jang will decide
whether or not to call.
Around this time, two years ago,
the prosecutor investigated
Moojin Produce.
Internal transactions by subsidiaries,
rebates from subcontractors,
and Foreign Exchange Law violations.
I'm sure you know very well
just what Mr. Moo-sam Park is like.
That's why he's useful.
I don't work with people
who aren't greedy.
What about someone
who sells out his brother?
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
Hi.
How have you been?
-Have a seat.
-Okay.
Mr. Park, who obtained
internal information
approached the prosecutor for a deal.
In exchange for letting him go,
he sold out the big fish, Chairman Park.
Do you get it now?
The reason Mr. Jang doesn't trust
Mr. Moo-sam Park.
I guess
Gun-woo doesn't know about it.
If he did,
Moojin Group would've fallen apart.
Mr. Jang doesn't want that, either.
You should work with Gun-woo Park
for your sake.
You should convince Mr. Jang.
The person who will make his dream
of becoming the king's father
is me.
Yes, Ma'am.
Where's Mr. Jo?
He took Se-jin to the office in Yeoksam.
Tell him to come in. Tell Tak, too.
I didn't know we had a building
in a place like this.
Moving funds, investments.
Normal business is conducted here.
You'll be coming here often, too.
That's the entrance to the annex.
This way.
Hello, Ms. Kim. We just arrived.
An emergency?
Even if it's a single tree,
if you plant it on top of a mountain,
you can make it look down
on a thousand roads.
Is that a saying in Han Feizi?
I must choose one or the other.
Which tree
should I plant on my mountain?
Gun-woo?
Or the other child?
If you consider
only ambition and abilities,
wouldn't Ms. Seo be better?
A knife that is overly sharp
may cut its master.
Today,
I wish I could have some soju
with my old friends.
Don't give me that bull.
Moo-il, Gun-woo threatened me.
He threatened me.
Mr. Jang...
He said he'll work with him
to kick me out.
Moo-sam.
Watch what you say!
Gun-woo will cause a big trouble
if you don't do something.
You need to call him in
and give him a big scolding--
Aren't you the one who caused trouble?
Did you forget about being stabbed
and putting on an act?
Moo-il, that was...
Do you think I kicked out Gun-woo
because I like you?
I did that so that you can live,
feeding your greed,
and leave my child alone.
But what? Tae-joon Jang?
Moo-il.
Are you okay? Moo-il.
I know my own child.
No matter what kind of treats
Tae-joon offers him,
Gun-woo wouldn't fall for it.
I understand.
I'll come to Seongbuk soon.
You should go home early.
Be ready to work like crazy
starting tomorrow.
Sir.
I'm sure the chairman
will be disappointed.
When I left Japan
to say goodbye to my uncle,
this may have already been planned.
This fight
may be unavoidable.
Aren't we worrying for nothing?
It's Gun-woo Park, of all people.
He'd never.
It's too soon to relax.
Mr. Moo-sam Park may be the target,
but we may be hurt as well.
Everyone listen.
First, Ms. Kim,
obtain Moojin Group's data.
Yes, ma'am.
We need everything you can obtain
through the network.
Tak. Stay on Gun-woo Park.
Note where he goes, whom he sees,
round the clock.
That's not a problem.
If Mr. Jang gets involved,
the prosecutor's office or the FSS
may make a move.
We'll be ready.
What about me?
Be on standby in the office.
I never called you.
I'm learning the basics of financing
from Mr. Jo.
When Ms. Kim updates profiles,
I memorize them again,
and am learning how to use the computer.
Tak taught me a few self-defense moves.
They may seem like nothing to you,
but I'm trying hard.
I know you're stressed and upset
about Gun-woo Park.
Have me do anything.
I'll do well in your place.
In my place?
-I never did that.
-Sorry?
I never worried about someone
from the past,
and I don't wait for someone
to give me an order.
But what will you do in my place?
I was just worried about you.
From now on,
the real fight will begin.
The opponents are Tae-joon Jang
and Gun-woo Park.
Even I don't know
the power they hold.
Are you afraid?
Do you have a hard time sleeping
before a picnic
because you're afraid?
Don't be nervous.
Don't be anxious.
You are the universal key
that I kept hidden,
and the mirror that reflects me.
Chairman.
They say the position makes the person.
Even the great and mighty Chairman Son
is a powerless old man.
I wonder who will become the new chairman.
Don't tell me
you got a call from Mr. Jang.
No way.
Let's go.
Father.
Do you want to go golfing?
A few swings on the field
will make you feel much better.
Would it be a little cold?
Maybe a hot spring would be better.
We can soak in hot water and eat good food
for a few days.
Maybe we'll just go to Guam
or Hawaii, instead.
We can take Ma-ri, too.
Just hit me.
I blew the association's money
and disgraced your name.
It's all my fault this happened to you,
so beat me until you feel better!
Father.
Gosh.
Remember the guys who went to the shed
to take care of those Taiwanese guys?
Call them in.
What the crap are you trying to pull?
Rebates?
Who dares defame me?
The 2011 contract with Myungjin Logics.
The 2012 company system replacement
by Sungil Networks.
-There's something from 2013 too, correct?
-Yes.
Take the ledgers and computers
of everyone involved.
Pay attention. Don't miss a thing.
Let's finish up and go.
Gun-woo, you punk.
You covered up my flaw for the sake
of the company's reputation.
I'll return the favor.
Let's take care of it quietly internally.
Let's not ruin the company name.
Don't tell me...
Did Mr. Jang tipped you off?
Sorry, but the woman who said
she'd make you chairman
failed in the preliminaries.
My poor brother.
He trusts wholeheartedly in his son.
Goodness.
He failed at managing his brother.
He can't expect much from his child.
It's too late for me anyway,
so I'll give up on being a good son.
I'll pursue being a good employee instead.
Oh, it looks like the personnel committee
plans to reconsider
my reassignment.
Word gets out quickly.
Maybe they heard about Mr. Jang already.
I should redecorate this place.
I've never been this humiliated before
in my life.
Gun-woo brought the Auditing Team
and emptied out my office
and the secretaries' offices.
-What a relief.
-What?
You wouldn't be able to call like this
if the prosecutor got involved.
Gun-woo must care a great deal
about his uncle.
Look here, Yi-kyung!
You're partly to blame in this!
You said it would be smooth sailing
once you met Mr. Jang!
That's when I didn't know you completely.
What?
What do you mean?
You handle your own family matters.
I'm busy looking after my company.
Rude brat.
Moojin Group Chairman Moo-Il Park
Indicted for Tax Evasion
You need to go to the office in Yeoksam.
The Financial Supervisory Service
is doing a special on-site audit.
You craft each line of codes to get in.
It takes creativity in its own way.
That's why people say I'm a writer.
Can you get in anywhere you want?
What? Yes. No.
Well, you can't do everything.
I'm the CEO of Gallery S, Yi-kyung Seo.
I'm Woo-sung Choi, auditing team manager
of the Financial Supervisory Service
Sorry to interfere with business,
but we'd appreciate your cooperation.
-Mr. Jo.
-Yes?
Move them into a larger room and give them
every document they request.
It looks like it won't end that quickly.
Gun-woo.
He's being harsh from the start.
Don't you think Mr. Jang got involved?
It doesn't matter who it is.
Call Chief Heo
from the Financial Supervisory Service.
Yes, ma'am. I'll find out what's going on.
The interview is running long.
Why don't you come another time?
Did you instruct them to strike Gallery S?
Oh, that.
The director of
the auditing team is my old friend.
You shouldn't do that all by yourself.
I said let's tie up my uncle first,
since that is the proper step.
Mr. Park.
We are not competing in the Olympics.
Wait for the whistle and fight
fair and square by the rules?
There is no such thing
as a beautiful loss.
Once the fight has begun,
you must win, no matter what.
That's your style.
I'll go with my pace.
From now on,
don't attack Yi-kyung
without my permission.
Gun-woo Park speaking.
Hold on. Hold on.
Hey, you. Will you go to
the office in Yeoksam?
I need to know what's going on,
so that I'll be less nervous.
Don't worry. Ms. Seo will handle it.
Look at this girl.
The Financial Supervisory Service auditors
are like the angel of death to us.
Gosh.
No one in this world is spotless.
Ms. Seo is.
She is, thorough and thorough.
How can you be reading right now?
They're documents on Moojin Group
and Gun-woo Park.
Tak said,
"know the enemy, know yourself
and you will never lose."
Enemy?
I'm sure the audit has something to do
with Gun-woo Park.
That means he's Ms. Seo's enemy.
-Hello?
-We're police officers.
Excuse me?
It's freezing cold.
I said let's meet at a nice bar.
What is it?
What do you have on my uncle?
Put your fangs away.
We may end up helping each other.
Recently,
I got a very good reason,
so I'm getting back at Yi-kyung.
To start it off,
I cut off one of her subordinates.
The police?
Se-jin? Why?
There was a record on his phone
of a call with our company.
Those Taiwanese guys.
Se-jin is on the line. I'll connect you.
Ma'am, it's me.
She followed them since they said
they just need a few statements.
Se-jin said not to call you
because you'll worry,
but my heart is racing so much right now.
Call the police and find out
which detective is in charge.
Send our attorney straight there
as soon as you reach him.
More auditors came.
I think they plan to investigate
all through the night.
What did Chief Heo say?
He said it's out of his hands.
The director ordered it himself.
Ma'am.
The documents are clean, right?
We prepared for this, but...
Tell Tak to come in.
On the prior day, you called
to discuss the artwork transaction.
I work at the gallery,
so I do that all the time.
There was another call the next day.
The matter at the hotel didn't work out.
"Let's do better next time."
It was something like that.
But what is this case about?
Those people left the country already.
One did,
but the other one
died.
He died?
A passport and cell phone were found
in the bag with the body.
The tip was right.
It was close to the scene.
The forensics guys just went.
There were burn marks on the body.
There was an explosion
at a storage shed nearby that night.
Do you know anything about it?
Ms. Se-jin Lee.
You were at the shed, weren't you?
What the hell is this?
We even left the gun
where they can see it.
She can't get out of this one.
Anyway, while I was trying to frame
that chick Se-jin Lee,
I remembered.
The Taiwanese guy that Yi-kyung borrowed.
I heard Moo-sam Park
was attacked by a stranger.
And you took the fall for it.
It's obvious, isn't it?
If we tighten the leash around him
for fabricating that incident--
Get out.
-What?
-I said to get out.
My ears are about to rot.
Hey, Gun-woo.
I'm being nice.
Don't treat me like a fool.
I heard Moo-sam Park
was attacked by a stranger.
And you took the fall for it.
Yi-kyung is a cruel woman.
She knew it was a trap,
but she sent a replacement.
Go back before it gets harder, Yi-kyung.
You said this was your dream.
You can't even pursue your own dream,
but what, you'll stop me?
If I were going to let you break me,
I wouldn't have even made it here.
Gun-woo,
you can't win this fight.
A monster can't lose
to a human.
So, you passed out at the hotel,
and you were in that shed?
I told you already.
They mistook me for Ms. Seo.
Chunha Financing.
Investigate them first.
We'll take care of that.
Don't worry about it.
The two Taiwanese men fought among
themselves and then the place exploded.
It wasn't you who shot it?
Shoot if you can!
I told you, I didn't.
The fingerprint identification is
in process, so we'll find out soon.
Ms. Se-jin Lee.
If your fingerprints are found
on that gun,
it'll be murder based on
willful negligence.
It is a serious crime!
So,
tell me the truth, will you?
-Detective.
-That's right.
There could have been
extenuating circumstances.
Other than...
being poor,
I did nothing wrong.
It was Gi-tae Son's doing.
Otherwise, they wouldn't have found
the passport, cell phone and gun.
Keep it down.
She knows already.
Do you know Gun-woo Park
met with Gi-tae Son?
Are you sure?
The camera will prove what I saw.
I have it on camera.
They teamed up in order to get you.
What are you doing?
We need to get the kid out first.
There's a problem in Yeoksam office, too.
-What?
-Remember the account
we received from Chunha?
Some of them are problematic.
Normally, they may let it slide,
but given how targeted this audit is...
Let's take care of them one at a time,
in the order of importance.
I went to the hotel in Ms. Seo's place,
and those people...
Wake up and talk clearly.
I've prepared something.
Please take a look.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
I told you.
I escaped when the fire broke out.
I don't know the rest.
Ma'am?
What are you doing here?
I told you to be on standby at the office.
I know.
I look a bit...
-Right?
-Hold your head up.
Sit up straight.
Much better.
My aunt will be worried.
Ms. Kim already called her.
You're away on business.
I avoided a back slap.
I'm sorry.
The company has been attacked by a bomb
and I'm unable to do anything.
Then get out and get to work.
We should
return that bomb.
There may be fingerprints on the gun.
They say if they find mine on it,
it'll go straight to court.
Will you just sit there and die
like a loser,
while being someone's double?
I couldn't sit there and just die
like a loser,
while being someone's double.
There will be
no fingerprints.
If it fails online, they'll go offline.
Money is the world's strongest eraser.
THE FINGERPRINTS ARE A MATCH.
Whether it's memories or records,
it erases them completely.
MATCH SUCCEEDED
MATCH FAILED
FAILED
NO MATCH FOUND
Even if you don't like it, tough.
That is the best way to get you out.
I can breathe now.
I wondered how I'd escape from prison
if things went south.
I wondered if I should
draw a map on my body
and dig my way out with a spoon
like in the movies.
At most, it'll be 48 hours.
Hang in there.
I'm not afraid at all.
I'm not anxious, either.
I'm not nervous.
You would've been the same
if you were the one in here.
This is
-from before...
-It's my lucky charm.
The one yen
that is more important than my life.
I'll lend it to you interest-free.
Thank you for not charging interest,
but sorry.
You don't lend money without collateral.
Se-jin.
You are my collateral.
Ms. Se-jin Lee.
Huh?
Look at you.
Where's my tofu?
Tofu's only for people
released from prison.
-You brat.
-Ouch.
Hey. Wait. I didn't teach you that
to use on your master.
-Let go.
-No.
-Let go!
-No, you brat.
Hey, let go of me.
-I won't.
-Let go!
My arm hurts.
Se-jin just got out. I'll take her home.
No, ma'am. I'll come to work.
Rest at home today.
See? She says to rest.
I'm fine.
You'll be exhausted starting tomorrow.
Be ready.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Yes?
We don't need tea.
Should I say I'm happy to see you
or shocked?
-Sit.
-Good news, bad news.
Which first?
They say it's better to get the worst
out of the way first,
but I'd rather take it later.
I decided to challenge you properly
starting now.
-And the bad news?
-I plan
to work very hard at it.
You must be upset about the audit.
But luckily, they didn't shut you down.
A few million won in fines is generous.
Why did you drag Se-jin into it?
Who?
Oh, the other Yi-kyung Seo?
What about her?
To start it off,
I cut off one of her subordinates.
-What happened?
-Let's not ask what we know.
Do you think
I was behind it?
-Yi-kyung, this was--
-This is our fight.
Don't touch her.
I'll give you a big gift very soon.
I hope you like it.
Yi-kyung.
I don't know if you want revenge
or business,
but choose your methods wisely.
Even if you lie to yourself
that you're a monster,
you're still human.
Just wait for the gift.
Se-jin Lee.
That's right.
Don't forget
that name.
Hey, it's me.
Really?
Good job. Let's grab soju next time.
Take a cab from here.
-Why?
-I need to meet someone. Go.
-Who?
-You're so annoying.
I'm meeting my girlfriend.
Happy?
A jerk like you has a girlfriend?
Have you ever been in a relationship?
Do you see that car? Please follow it.
It doesn't taste good.
The food doesn't taste good.
Just eat what I buy you.
Have you ever earned money before?
I'm just saying it tasted bad
because it did. What's your problem?
Hey. Ma-ri!
Se-jin.
What are you doing here?
I don't have business with you.
How have you been?
You know I wasn't well, don't you?
You got out somehow.
Did Yi-kyung send you?
Tell her to come herself,
if she has something to say.
Ms. Seo is busy.
Plus, she's on a whole different level
than you.
Hey. Se-jin. Watch it.
I came to warn him.
Do you see our employee in that car?
Those men are also our employees.
-Shit.
-Really?
Girlfriend?
What do you have in your brain?
-Hey.
-Did you want to take my place
and go to prison?
Will you tell Ms. Seo?
Do whatever you want.
I'll just be yelled at.
Still,
I feel
pretty good.
Don't jump to conclusions.
I didn't do it for you.
Huh?
You have a visitor.
Are you
really Bong-soo's daughter?
I heard you were here,
but I didn't know I'd see you like this.
Have a seat.
Sure.
Your eyes and mouth
are just like Bong-soo's.
How is he doing?
How do you think he is doing?
Does he
still resent me a lot?
I did a lot of wrong against him.
Just the word Korea,
probably makes your father sick.
Well,
I guess it's justice.
I think that's why I'm being punished.
A nice single room.
A medical staff standing by
24 hours a day.
Special visitation rights
regular prisoners can't even dream of.
This is a vacation,
not a punishment.
If you really want to repent,
you should do it outside.
What do you mean?
Gun-woo Park
is working under Mr. Jang.
If you leave it this way,
Moojin will be split into two.
As long as Gun-woo
is receiving Mr. Jang's support,
Mr. Moo-sam Park won't sit still.
Why would Gun-woo do such a thing...
Wait.
How do you know so well?
This is all within the group.
I am also operating a tiny shop.
And I've know Mr. Moo-sam Park
for a while, too.
You're the only person who can fix this.
Let go.
Give in and say you'll give up
the Dubai business.
That way, you can get sick bail.
You betrayed a friend
to build Moojin Group.
You can't let it collapse like this.
Leave this place.
That'll be the beginning
of your repentance toward my father.
KOREA-JAPAN CO-OP NIGHT
1988 SEOUL OLYMPICS
Gun-woo Park
is working under Mr. Jang.
KOREA-JAPAN CO-OP NIGHT
1988 SEOUL OLYMPICS
It's my lucky charm.
The one yen
that is more important than my life.
I'll lend it to you interest-free.
Thank you for not charging interest,
but sorry.
You don't lend money without collateral.
Se-jin.
You are my collateral.
Japanese money?
Did you go to Japan for work?
No, I didn't.
I'm right.
Let me see.
Get lost.
Song-mi.
Your exams start next week.
Shouldn't you be studying?
Everyone's always picking on me.
You brat.
I saw Suk's mom this afternoon.
Did you renew?
Yes.
We can finally sleep peacefully now.
Tell your boss
that we are ever so grateful
over and over again.
Okay.
Let's drink to celebrate.
Yes?
Yes.
With seaweed.
Isn't there anything else?
MOOJIN GROUP
Mr. Park!
Moojin Group's chairman
Moo-il Park, who is in custody
while being investigated for charges
including embezzlement and tax evasion,
left the detention center today
and was admitted
into Dongsan Hospital in Seoul.
We will connect to our reporter
on the scene.
Moo-il Park Out on Sick Bail
The Department of Justice
stated that his health worsened
due to his high blood pressure,
pneumonia, depression, and other ailments,
and stated that detention is not required.
Dongsan Hospital's diagnosis
of Chairman Park's condition
will determine whether or not
he will qualify for sick bail.
A spokesperson from the court
stated that Chairman Park
has not been in good health...
Please have a seat.
I want to knock over everything here,
but what?
You want me to sit?
You really don't listen to others.
I asked you
not to drop by here because
people are watching.
Moo-il's sick bail
was your doing, wasn't it?
I just confirmed it.
Shit.
What are you up to?
If you keep disrespecting me,
I can't work with you.
Then what?
Will you run to the prosecutor
and cut a deal again?
You don't even have your brother's
corruption to offer up anymore.
Trust me and follow me.
If you keep suspecting the path,
you'll fall.
I'm just worried that I'm wasting my time.
No.
Chairman Moo-il Park
can't keep his position.
But Gun-woo Park
won't be claiming it either.
Se-jin, come here.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Se-jin Lee.
Whenever I'm away,
she will take my role.
She will be the new hidden card.
Father.
Stop working with Tae-joon!
He just left.
Moo-sam Park...
will betray me someday.
I'm sure he's wary, too,
worrying when he will
get stabbed in his back.
You're on the same side
only while you need each other.
Is that it?
That's right.
So you need to make people
continue to want you.
If you can't,
you'll be discarded right away.
Rest assured.
I won't discard you,
since you're always important to me.
Since we dragged the old lion
out of its cage,
the bloody fight will begin now.
In order to fight,
you must become
absolutely necessary to someone.
Pardon? To whom?
Tae-joon, that punk,
is a monster wearing human skin!
I won't watch my own son
be a pawn in his little game!
It's nice being scolded
on the outside.
You're more energetic
than in the detention center.
Gun-woo!
The Auditing Team
barely stopped Uncle from his rampage.
Both inside the company and out,
I have more people on my side.
I benefited from Mr. Jang
when I needed him.
I can't turn my back on him
because things have changed.
He's just using you
to take over the group!
You have to know.
You were used all your life.
Gun-woo Park.
Steal him.
Do you really not care?
He's just one of the obstacles in my way.
I'd like your help with something.
Did you predict Gun-woo would approach me?
Will you let your life end
just being used by Yi-kyung?
I'm sure she has an axe to grind.
It's meaningless
if she can't realize her real ambition.
It'll be her final test.
Guess.
Whom do you think I'm here to seduce?
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee