EPISODE 9
Are you up already?
Did you not sleep at all?
You have a busy day today.
You should sleep a little.
The documents on the new foundation
are there. Sort them.
When I was in high school, a kid
in my class was top 0.3% in the nation,
and she was just like you.
She was on study mode
whenever she wasn't sleeping or eating.
Eventually, she cut down on sleep time
and studied while eating.
Guess what happened to her.
She was hospitalized
on the day of the college entrance exam.
I'm not trying to jinx you.
I just want you
to consider your health, too.
-Any update on Gun-woo?
-We texted a few times about the earring.
There's been nothing since.
I dropped it in the car on purpose,
since I'll need an excuse
to see him again.
Don't worry.
I'm sure he'll call.
This is the most important time.
Don't miss a thing.
I won't miss anything.
That girl who was hospitalized
went to an ivy league the following year.
I'll become a villain.
I'll climb to the top
and look down on the world.
So that I won't be framed again
or be anyone's prey.
Hi. You're here.
You're early.
I'm here to see Mr. Jang.
I can't be even a second late.
Wow. I haven't been here in a while.
Before he and Moo-il severed ties,
we'd come by time to time
and talk about life and stuff.
Gosh.
You like tea, don't you?
They say this is
Secretary Jin-tao Hu's favorite tea.
Thank you.
It's been about seven
or eight years, right?
I have always been waiting
for you to call me.
It is all thanks to Yi-kyung.
She said if I want to do something great,
it must be you.
She was too stubborn.
She is very talented.
So,
what do you plan to do now?
Pardon?
What do you mean?
Will you stab me in the back
as you did
to Moo-il?
What? Sir...
I...
You even betrayed your own family.
You will probably do
the same thing to me too.
That concerns me about you.
What do you think?
A relationship in which each side's goals
are clear is not severed easily.
Mr. Park will fulfill his duties
that you need him to perform.
Of course. Without a doubt.
She must have made
several plans for you.
You two can handle the details.
And whenever you need my help,
don't hesitate to ask.
Thank you so much for offering such thing.
Thank you, sir.
He blabbed everything to Gun-woo,
but look at him play dumb.
What an old cunning bastard.
It's not like he made it up.
Ms. Seo.
Let's clear away the past.
We have much to do.
Are you sure you can remove Moo-il?
I suppose...
there's a quite old document
in Moojin Group.
Tak!
Hey!
If you came, you should go in. Don't run.
Let go. You'll warp the door.
Let it warp.
-I won't let go.
-Se-jin.
Yes, that's my name.
Let's go in. Hurry. I'll freeze to death.
Seriously.
I brought home the runaway child!
Hi!
Welcome back.
I thought it was time for you to return.
You made me wait for so long.
I just dropped in while passing by.
Sure. Drop in every day
and do some work too.
Okay?
Do you know how worried she was about you?
-I'm sorry.
-Don't be.
How about some hot tea?
-Sounds good. I'll brew it.
-Okay.
Where's...
She went out.
She should be back now.
There she is.
Hello.
Take Se-jin to Chunha Financing.
Stop by the Yeoksam office
and pick up some documents.
Yes, ma'am.
Bring me some tea.
Meet with the punks
who opposed the new city project
and work on them one by one.
Even if they are Tae-joon's people,
no one can resist money in their face.
Finish your breathing exercises.
What? Oh.
About Uncle...
Do you still suspect him?
That was Tae-joon messing with you.
Don't waste your energy
and focus on the new city project.
Uncle
met with Mr. Jang,
along with Yi-kyung Seo.
The head driver for Moojin Produce
is actually one of our people.
He said the three of them met
in Seongbuk today.
It's obvious what they discussed.
"I'll be the new chairman.
I'll back you up."
It must have been pleasant.
What are you talking about?
Uncle...
has been after the chairman's seat,
since the day you were arrested.
Come in here!
-Yes, sir.
-Tell Moo-sam to come right this instant.
Yes, sir.
Wait. But
why would Bong-soo's daughter
work with Tae-joon?
She couldn't do that, considering her dad.
They look good.
I'll report it to Ms. Seo.
She wants to move as quickly as possible
to establish the foundation as well.
You've grown.
You were on your knees, begging and crying
at the hospital.
You're a big shot now, aren't you?
Thank you.
Mr. Jang will be calling you soon.
It is supposed to be good news.
Hello?
Okay. That's good.
Okay.
You'll have to go to Yeoksam without me.
I need to meet with someone.
Drop me off on the way.
Okay.
Gun-woo Park?
Yes.
When will that project end?
I don't know.
It will end when Ms. Seo says I can stop.
Do it right.
Since you're doing it anyway,
make sure he falls for it.
Didn't you want to see me
about my earring?
Earring?
Oh. That's in my office.
I forgot to bring it.
I'll save it as an excuse to meet again.
Then why...
Did you hear anything else since?
Either about Mr. Jang or my company.
Not particularly.
-Hear what?
-When did Moo-sam Park
come to the gallery? Does he come often?
Hold on.
Am I arrested?
I feel like I'm being interrogated.
Let's say you're a witness.
Whatever it is, I don't have
anything worth mentioning.
Last time, I thought you really
need to know.
That's why I went to you.
I appreciate that.
I'm asking something I need to know again.
I am not your spy.
I have no intention of telling
on Ms. Seo, either.
Rather than a deal,
what about a favor?
If you'd help me,
we can end this fight soon.
You may call me a hypocrite,
but I don't want to see Yi-kyung get hurt.
I don't have that power.
Maybe not,
but we have something in common.
Both 12 years ago
and now,
you and I are the only people
to whom she showed
her true emotions.
And you and I
worry only about one person.
He's anxious.
He must've noticed that Moo-sam Park
has started to take action.
So, what did you tell him?
That I'd think it over.
Indeed you should.
It will be suspicious
if you accept it right away.
Leak information to him that are safe
to leak. Mr. Jo will let you know what.
Gun-woo
seems convinced...
that he is trying
to end this fight for you.
Se-jin. What did you do?
-Sorry?
-Did you go on a date?
Or did you meet with him
to hear him preach to you?
-Ms. Seo--
-Get your act together.
That isn't what I meant.
I don't have time
to settle your feelings for you.
If you're going to waver,
just quit now.
You may go.
Moojin Produce just sent this.
BUSINESS CONSENT FORM
FOR RECOVERING FROM IMF CRISIS
I suppose there's a quite old document
in Moojin Group.
Hey. You okay?
Lower your standards.
If you try to follow Ms. Seo's pace,
you'll fail early in the race.
I'm angry.
What can you do? You have to keep it in.
If I had met Ms. Seo sooner,
I'd be much stronger by now.
I'm still too weak.
You're right.
I should do it right,
since I'm doing it anyway.
Calm down. Think of your blood pressure.
You worthless scumbag.
How dare you try to take over the company?
I can't just work for you all my life.
-What?
-That's enough. Please go.
I know what your father's thinking.
If Moo-yi were alive,
he would've made him chairman,
then skipped me
and given it to you.
Is that why you crawled over to Tae-joon?
So that he can make you a chairman?
If I don't do something,
I'd be out in the cold.
Shut your mouth you...
Father.
Okay, so please go.
As long as I'm alive,
there is no way
you'd get the company,
even if Tae-joon has your back.
I have my ways.
Did you forget already?
The consent form we signed
during the IMF crisis.
When we were freaking out
about reorganization and getting funding,
we tried anything and everything
to save the company
and signed a consent form
regarding business management.
I signed without really thinking,
and had forgotten all about it,
but I get to use it 20 years later.
Moo-sam Park owns a third.
Company stock, of course,
and he can also claim the right
to manage the business.
The deceased brother's shares
would be split between them.
Even if we add Mr. Jang's
and my shares in Moojin,
it'll be too close.
But if we announce this consent form
at the shareholders meeting,
we have a very good chance.
The chairman who is old
and is on sick bail.
The younger brother who has the support
of the most powerful figure.
Whose side would the shareholders take?
How did you find such an old document?
When it comes to Moojin Group,
I know down to the number of tiles
in their building.
Because
they were all supposed to be mine.
Whether at the shareholders meeting
or in court,
the consent form will cause a problem.
Don't speak.
I told you, you need to sleep.
Where did he find
that old document?
Gun-woo.
You're talking again.
Moo-sam
admitted it proudly
that he sold me out.
That punk
shouldn't be the chairman.
A punk who sells out his own blood
doesn't deserve to own Moojin.
That won't happen.
Rest assured, and sleep.
Okay.
It shouldn't happen.
What did you just say?
I had a blow-out with my brother
and I told him
that I have the consent form,
so he can try to take me on, if he wants.
We were going to disclose it
during the shareholders meeting anyway.
We should fight head-on.
Goodbye.
Yes, Ms. Seo.
Where are you?
I am on my way home.
Come in right away.
Call Tak, too.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll check A-3.
A-3 Clear.
The Auditing Team doesn't have a copy.
Not a single one?
They said the chairman ordered them
to destroy all the documents
on Moo-sam Park's rebates.
Did you not find it either?
They cleaned out my office
and yours completely.
Who knew we had a thief
in the Park family?
I will look for another weakness
other than the rebate matter.
You give up too quickly.
We're not done.
My brother is very protective
of his little brother.
He said he refused to see me
behind bars as well,
and got rid of the rebate documents.
He must regret it now.
Did you clean out Gun-woo's office, too?
We obtained the documents
and destroyed them.
Thanks to you, my year has turned around.
I'm not interested in your morality.
Whether you sell out your brother
to avoid being investigated yourself
or how much of the company's funds
you have embezzled.
They have nothing to do with me.
However,
I do not like it
if you hinder my plan.
Don't get so mad just because
I made one little mistake.
Do you want the chairman's office
at Moojin Group?
Then don't do anything
without my consent.
You must hide everything out there
and not hide a single thing from me.
If you cannot keep that promise,
our collaboration ends
right then and there.
I'll say that right back to you.
Don't try to trick me.
I need to become chairman
for you and Mr. Jang to benefit from me.
Mr. Jo will see you out.
I'll see you in my office from now on.
We have no reason to worry
about Gun-woo or anyone watching.
Also, change your driver.
What?
Why should I change my driver?
Why, do you suspect something?
You must be extra cautious
during these sensitive times.
Sure.
Where's Se-jin?
I heard the brothers signed a consent
during the IMF crisis
about business management,
and that with that,
he can take the chairman seat.
What?
Is that not very helpful?
No, it was very helpful.
That's right.
I remembered today.
-It's cheap, so you can throw it out.
-Then I'll throw it out.
Did you think a lot about it?
I'm curious if you thought it through
when you asked to see me urgently today.
I respect
Ms. Seo.
I don't want to see her getting hurt.
That means the fight
needs to end soon, as you said.
Thank you for understanding.
Just a minute.
Take the call.
I'm going to use the restroom.
Yes, Ms. Moon. Did you look into it?
Just as you said before,
I am still a cheap mirror,
but I want to reflect...
your true image,
at least a little.
I see why you're special to her.
You have a lot in common.
I'm sorry, but something urgent came up.
I keep doing this.
I know your company is going through
a crisis.
I need to get back too.
Let's grab dinner
once everything is resolved.
Is that okay?
See you.
Thank you.
VOICE RECORD 004
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
I'll forego the pleasantries.
Neither of us wants to talk long,
so let's be brief and get to the point.
Moo-sam Park's rebate documents.
You have a copy, don't you?
Give it to me.
I follow only Mr. Jang's orders.
Mr. Jang has forgotten all about you.
Yi-kyung Seo has taken your spot.
If it's Ms. Seo, I can rest assured.
She is very capable.
I don't care
whether a fired henchman is loyal
or betrays his master.
This has nothing to do with Mr. Jang.
I guess the family feud has begun.
-Right?
-You can read it in the papers.
Hand it over to me.
I don't know.
I've dealt with so many documents.
I can't remember if I have a copy.
I don't think I have it.
It's a shame.
I have another document, you see.
Jong-hyuk Nam.
Professor of Media at Moojin University
since 2005.
His brother, Jong-hyuk Nam.
Corruption behind his appointment,
plagiarism, embezzling research funds.
It's a triple crown.
Okay. That's enough evidence.
I'll go in now.
I guess he will threaten Mr. Nam
to get the rebate document.
How interesting.
Gun-woo Park.
It is an educational corporation
owned by Moojin Group.
But you will still go public
about a professor's corruption?
Is that what you mean?
Why would I worry about a corn on my foot
when I'm about to lose my body.
If you give me the rebate document,
I'll bury this.
This is a fight within the Park family.
You are not betraying Mr. Jang.
Mr. Nam,
give me the document
and save your brother.
Call Mr. Jang. Tell him I'm coming now.
Tell Moo-sam Park to come too.
Yes, ma'am.
Good job.
Okay.
I complimented you.
I wasn't scolding you.
I heard it as a compliment.
What's the problem?
What do you mean?
Conscience, morals, rationality.
Which one of them is bothering you?
Is it the recording
or is it that it's Gun-woo,
that it bothers you?
No.
Nothing is bothering me.
That's good.
Gun-woo is desperate
and doing anything it takes.
Don't be naive and stress out.
That's a waste of time.
Okay.
Call me at any time,
whether it's for company matters
or personal.
I heard you called the directors
during the day.
I told you, you need to rest.
The special shareholders meeting
that Moo-sam called
is coming up, right?
He's going around telling everyone
about the business consent form.
The directors say
it may be bad for us.
Their hobbies are worrying
and stressing out.
Don't take it to heart.
I betrayed my best friend
and made my little brother
die away from home.
I feel like I'm paying
for all my life's sins in one blow.
Stop talking like a weak person.
Don't worry about the meeting.
Uncle won't make it that far.
If you're still worried,
assign me somewhere else.
Moojin's educational corporation.
I need to become the chief director there.
Do you know what it means for him
to become the chief director there?
That corporation owns 5%
of Moojin Group's shares.
If Gun-woo becomes the chief director,
he'll use it all to keep Moo-il in power.
Even if I push with the consent form,
if we can't remove him from office, I...
We'll aim for
the next shareholders meeting
and gather more shares until then.
Do you think Moo-il and Gun-woo
will hibernate during that time?
They'll come on strong, too.
Mr. Park.
Ms. Seo.
I jumped in with two feet.
If I lose here, I'm finished.
But everything is a mess.
Mr. Jang, that old geezer.
He couldn't keep his man in check.
What am I supposed to do?
What's the predicted result?
As he said, it's not very optimistic.
That's what I'm saying.
If Gun-woo becomes chief director,
it'll be over for me.
You're the one who created this mess.
Don't order me to come and go.
It's quite annoying.
Look, I'm sorry, but it was an emergency.
I had no choice.
Gun-woo Park is not a variable,
but a constant.
He is an obstacle that is always there.
We can't look right at it
and trip over it.
Are you saying you have a good idea?
Did you come for a team meeting?
Any good plans came up?
-You look tired.
-I am tired.
I'm not built for working late,
but I made improvements, thanks to you.
Don't work too hard
on the shareholders meeting.
You'll lose anyway.
Whether it's people or methods,
I'll have to look hard.
Don't trust people too much either.
Money isn't so trustworthy, either.
That's right. We have freedom of religion
in this country.
Sorry.
Take good care of the chairman.
Being removed from office
will be traumatizing.
I'm looking for a branch office abroad
to send Uncle to.
Somewhere with no business
and no direct flights.
That will be where you'll be transferred,
so look for one with nice weather.
It's good to see you again.
Take a good look at the office
since you're here anyway,
since you'll never come back here again.
Go back to work. Bye.
Yes, Mr. Jang.
Thank you for your understanding.
I thought you went to Moojin Group.
How does it look?
I don't know much.
The artist is underappreciated.
In one to two years,
everyone will be after him.
You're the same.
Even if it weren't me,
you would've found an opportunity someday.
I may have been the lucky one.
That's obviously not true.
I was the lucky one and you were the one
who gave me the opportunity.
Don't get me wrong.
Gun-woo and I
aren't what you're thinking.
Misery loves company.
It's like people suffering from the same
illness feeling a connection.
Gun-woo and I
worry only about one person.
That's a good approach.
This isn't about work.
What else would we talk about,
if not work?
The weather? Hobbies?
Shopping?
How's this?
I don't know.
I don't know you, either.
Then I should teach you.
Do you remember what I said
when you started?
I said to become absolutely necessary
to Gun-woo.
You'll get that chance soon.
He will need your comforting desperately.
Don't miss that opportunity.
Mr. Park.
We found the Daejin Construction matter.
If you look at the shares here...
It's as you can see.
The most shares Moo-sam Park may obtain
is 43%.
Gun-woo Park's side...
We are leaving now.
I got to come back thanks to you.
I regretted it as soon as I left.
Did you see those girls from my job?
Weren't they cute?
Professor Nam at Moojin University's
media department,
is being investigated for corruption,
plagiarism, embezzlement,
as well as other charges.
Professor Nam was the youngest
professor...
You should cut off a tangled knot.
You seemed confused about your brother's
matter, so I gave you a helping hand.
Did Mr. Jang
agree with that decision?
His objective is
to make Moo-sam Park chairman.
You mean, it's what you want.
Don't worry about your brother anymore,
and wait patiently.
As soon as we find an adequate fall guy,
you'll be released.
Mr. Jang is the only person
for you to return to, anyway.
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
He refuses to see you.
He asked you never to come back.
Hello, ma'am.
-Where are you?
-I'm about to go home.
It's time.
The moment you become a person
Gun-woo needs.
Hello?
Is your friend still at the hospital?
Yes. I was leaving, but thought maybe...
Thank goodness I didn't throw it out.
It isn't cheap at all.
I don't have anything in particular to
discuss, but may I take some of your time?
Have you had dinner yet?
You don't like it?
I wanted to buy you something nicer.
I guess you don't like cheap food.
-I see.
-What? No.
I ate so much kimbap and tteokbokki
when I did part time jobs,
that just looking at them made me sick.
But I see them now
and they actually look good.
Did Yi-kyung discover you
at your part time job?
Something like that.
It's hard to get her attention.
Gun-woo.
Aren't we strange?
All we talk about is Ms. Seo.
Her past and what she's doing now.
You're right.
Let's talk about something else today.
I hear you're busy preparing
for a shareholders meeting.
No. No work talk.
Right...
I'm Yi-kyung Seo of Gallery S.
Does Bong-soo know
that you became Tae-joon's lackey?
I'm sure he doesn't.
He would've flown right over
and caused a scene.
Of all the people to get help from,
how could you join forces with him?
Once the shareholders meeting is held,
you will be forced to step down.
Not a chance.
That stupid consent form?
Keep trying with that.
I won't back down easily.
If I can't do it,
Gun-woo will fight for me.
If he has
the educational corporation's share,
he'll last a little longer.
You may survive
the special shareholders meeting,
but it'll be different at
the annual shareholders meeting.
The result has already been decided.
You'll just be dragging it out.
Forget assigning Gun-woo Park
chief director, sir.
Moo-sam, that punk can never
be a chairman.
He's corrupted to the core.
Gun-woo Park is the same.
This?
Moo-sam faked all of this.
Gun-woo did nothing wrong.
Will people believe his innocence?
His own father removed him from his post
and left him without an appointment.
Truth doesn't matter.
What matters is what the people believe.
Aren't you curious
as to who it was
that produced this show?
You came here
to get revenge for your dad, didn't you?
Revenge.
How stale.
Gun-woo and I
knew each other in Japan.
What?
What? You and Gun-woo
knew each other?
We didn't just know each other.
We even considered running away together
from our fathers.
He almost died because of me.
Eventually,
we broke up.
The bad blood
between my father and you people
pushed us into this mess.
Because
of that greed and betrayal.
Look.
About what happened to Bong-soo--
A respectable business man?
A father who cares
especially a lot for his son.
Look at who you really are.
You betrayed your friend
because of your greed.
You are vile and atrocious.
You are just struggling
not to lose what you have.
Gun-woo is a victim.
Don't let there be another victim
because of your greed.
Remove your son
from this fight.
Sir, sir!
Nurse! Nurse, hurry!
If I add up the cost of all the guitars
my dad smashed,
I'd be a millionaire.
But you somehow escaped to Japan.
I just got on the next available flight
in case they'd come after me.
It would've been more interesting
if you had gone to Africa.
It must've been fate
to meet Ms. Seo.
I saw the CD in her room.
You played for her a lot back then, right?
We're being strange again.
It's a sickness,
for both you and I.
Hello?
Father. Wake up. Father.
What happened?
He has difficulty breathing
and went into shock.
He's stable now, but we need an MRI
to see the extent of the bleeding.
I heard you went to the hospital.
What did you talk about?
How's Chairman Park?
Luckily, there was no brain hemorrhaging.
But he hasn't regained consciousness.
You sent me
for another reason, didn't you?
You wanted Gun-woo out of the room
to meet with the chairman.
What did you say to him?
It's guilt.
Even someone who is completely heartless
would fall apart if they feel guilty.
Remember that.
It's a useful vital point.
He's sick
and he's old.
Attacking someone like that
is wrong.
He isn't an old man
sitting on a park bench.
With one word, he can make
thousands of people lose their jobs.
With one signature,
he can bulldoze an entire town.
He isn't weak enough to warrant pity.
So,
did you go with the intent
to make him collapse?
To stab at his weak pressure point?
There are no rules to this fight.
If I don't knock him down,
I'll be the one attacked.
Even if I resent the victors after I fall,
they do not hear a thing.
Se-jin.
Don't hesitate.
If you truly want to possess
those lights that you saw,
don't hesitate. Just take.
Moojin Group, the subject of
a battle for control,
held a special shareholders meeting
at Samseong headquarters
and voted to remove Chairman Moo-il Park
from office.
The shareholders meeting
which began at 9 a.m.
discussed the health...
Wow. Ms. Seo pulled a big one.
The new chairman...
Good job everyone.
Moojin Produce's president, Moo-sam Park
was voted in on a landslide decision.
Moojin Group had doubled in net worth
during former President
Tae-joon Jang's tenure,
and with the approval
of Moojin's Neo City Project,
Chairman Park's pet project,
many had raised suspicions
of preferential treatment.
Gun-woo.
My parents
passed away in a car accident.
After my mom went to heaven,
my dad was in the ICU for a long time.
I pretty much lived in the hall
outside the ICU.
I'd doze off on the bench,
wake up, stare into space,
and after a while,
I couldn't think at all.
Then I'd stare
at the pattern on the floor.
Time ceased to exist.
I didn't feel hunger or anything.
The pattern here is different.
So hang in there.
No more bad things will happen.
Yi-kyung.
Yi-kyung wouldn't have done that.
What did she say to my father?
Gun-woo.
Excuse me, Gun-woo.
There is
something I couldn't tell you.
The truth is,
Ms. Seo...
Excuse me.
Please come in.
It's okay.
You can just talk.
Where's...
Bong-soo's daughter?
She isn't here. She didn't come.
And the meeting?
How did it go?
Did Moo-sam win?
It all went well.
Don't worry.
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee