Your proposal
will start from here
Miss Nie will come up here from the stairs
This is the place you're gonna propose
After the proposal
we have a very romantic dinner arranged
for you two to have a perfect engagement night
So what do you think of this plan?
Just do it in your way
OK
Are really taking me to the Fantasy Town?
Do you like that?
I'm planning to visit it
But
how could you want to go there too?
I've heard that it is a great place for date
But you are going to
meet Mr. Fu of Yuanyang Corp this afternoon
and the bank...
I've told Director Huang
to rearrange all your work
So the only thing for you to do it to get dressed
and come with me
Yes, Mr. Yan
We will be there in an hour
Let's take the bus
It's not convenient
How come?
We are not in a hurry
You liked taking bus
back in college
Don't you remember?
How long it'll take by bus?
One transfer will be needed
About one hour and a half
OK
You're the boss
We'll be there in one hour and a half
Sorry
I didn't expect the bus would take so long to be here
To be with you
I can always experience
something unforgettable
What's so funny?
I just remember
the last time
when we were here waiting for the bus
Last time you just ran into my arms
All right
Let me make a call
Hello
I'm calling to check on
the bus No. 23 which we've waited
at the station for an hour
I see
Alright
What happened?
Bus No. 23 is out of service
but they haven't change the station sign yet
Why don't we walk there?
It's too far to walk
I know a shortcut
and come with me
Jingzhi
Let me down
Be careful
Watch out
You see
It's so beautiful here
What's so beautiful?
The sun is setting
We didn't make it to the Fantasy Town
but we come across
such a nice place
The surprise along the way
is also memorable
Don't you think it's a pity?
No
As long as I'm with you
I will be happy anywhere
I'm not that into the Fantasy Town actually
You don't have to comfort me
I knew you've done lots of research
That's why you wanna go there with me
Actually I wanna to assess the place
because our company will build
an entertainment complex like that in the future
I'm really not good at
making a surprise
You just ask me
What do you like?
I like you
Nie Xingchen
Since my last proposal failed
I was going to
put this ring on your finger
at the Town
but now,
I don't want to wait anymore
Nie Xingchen
Do you wanna spend the rest of your life with me?
Yes, I do
Wait
I remember that I have a video conference
You go to sleep first
Good morning
Good morning, Xingchen
Xingchen
Look at the ring on her finger
You see
Congratulations, Secretary Nie
You accepted boss's proposal
I kept the secret for several days
Boss asked us for more information
in order to propose to you
But sadly
we didn't do a good job for him
Tell us
how he did it
Well
it's complicated
but the place was beautiful
Look at the dark circles around your eyes
You two must did some
hot stuff for celebration
What are you talking about?
Alright, it's time to work
Let's go to work
Right, let's go
Xingchen
let me see it again
How did he propose?
Mr. Yan
what do you want me for?
OK
I'm on it
What's wrong, Director Huang?
Mr. Yan said he's going to Beijing
and he wants me to go with him
Boss left Xingchen alone
right after he proposed
You don't understand it
He's just afraid he can't control himself
and makes his girlfriend too tired
Like you know everything
Shut up
Go to work
Come on
Surprise
Xingchen
What are you doing here?
Today
Xingchen accepted my proposal
but I just couldn't be close to her
I'm afraid
after I wake up
I may forget her again
How long will it take for me
to get over the damn amnesia?
It's going to drive us crazy
Because I missed you of course!
What's the look?
Are you hiding some girl in here?
Welcome
Then I'm gonna help myself
Yan Jingzhi, what are you doing?
I have work to do
You may have a rest here
Yan Jingzhi
You wake up
How's the sleep?
Fine
How about you?
Very well
My phone is ringing
Wait for me
Hello
Mother Ye
You're coming back to Jinghai?
I'm not busy
I'll pick you up tomorrow morning
OK
See you tomorrow morning
OK, bye
It seems
you have surpassed my place
in Ms. Ye's heart
Sorry
I can't stay here with you
I feel so sad
if
you don't wanna go,
I can ask the drive to pick her up
No
Your mom rarely comes to Jinghai
How can both of us not show up?
I'll go pick her up
Thank you
Breakfast is ready
Let's have it together
Yan Jingzhi
You look nice in this dress
It so fits you
I'll take it then
OK
Have a drink
Thank you
Xingchen
I'm coming to
ask you another favor
What can I do for you?
You see
you and Jingzhi
have already engaged
Should I
meet your parents officially?
I wanna ask you
to have your parents come to Jinghai
so we can have a meal together
and discuss about your wedding
There is no need to rush
There is!
You two get married this year,
then you can have a baby next year
How lovely
I'm getting on board
I'll be home at around 8 o'clock
Mother Ye
Later
What are you calling me?
Mom
Good girl
Let's go
grab a bite
and wait for Jingzhi to have dinner
How does this sound?
I have plans tonight
I'll leave you two alone
Xingchen
I thought you are in the next door
Absence makes the heart grow fonder
How can I leave you here?
Are you drunk?
A little
to encourage myself
What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
You...
You calm down first
Me too
Drinking on an empty stomach is bad for your health
Let me cook something for you
Yan Jingzhi
You don't need to avoid me
I've read your diary
Xingchen
I need more time
But we are going
to do it sooner or later
To be with you
is enough for me
I don't wanna spoil our happiness now
You forgot your proposal the first time you lost your memory
But for this time
I've got a ring on my finger
and you are fine
It means everything is going to a better way
doesn't it?
And
You've always liked high risk, high return investments
Now
do you dare to bet with me?
Yan Jingzhi
I tried so hard
How can you say no to me again?
Who are you?
I'm Xingchen
Your fiancee
Don't you remember me?
I don't care who you are
Get out of here right now
You see
This is your diary
You can't forget your handwriting
This is a picture of us
And this
This is the engagement ring you gave me
Do you remember?
You can't take it off before we get married
Yan Jingzhi
How can you make this kind of joke?
I was too nervous to sleep last night
Now you...
Don't lie to me anymore
Alright
We won, didn't we?
Don't lie to me anymore
It hurts
You hit me too hard
It hurts so much
Get up
You didn't sleep last night
Get more sleep
Yan Jingzhi
This
Here you are
Everything goes where they should be
Let me hang you in here
Darling
Thanks
What?
Let me tie your hair
Why?
Your hair is everywhere
You think it's gross?
I just don't want you to lose all your hair
It's anti-hair loss
Look, how pretty you are
Your face looks smaller
If we have a girl in the future
I will tie her hair like this
It's nice
Very nice
You take your time
I'll go take a nap
Wake me up when it's ready
You bad boy
Dad,
you can take off your coat
Yes
we are about to be family
Comfort matters the most
Ms. Ye,
thank you
Thank you very much
for inviting us to Jinghai
We heard you've been living abroad
Yes
About this,
you two rest assured
After the two get married
they will live their own life
I will not bother them
We didn't mean that
We just want to know you better
since we meet for the first time
I agree
I'm telling you
This time
I come here for a world...
Mom
Uncle and aunt
Let's eat
Let's talk over dinner
OK
Yes
You see
I keep talking
Let's eat
Help yourself
OK
Uncle
It takes just 15 seconds for the meat to be done
Let me help you
Yan
is a careful man
Quite careful
If our Xingxing
does anything improper
on work or life,
please forgive her
Uncle
Xingchen does a good job
I'm the one should be tolerated
This two have experienced so much
It's not easy for them
if you two agree,
we may fix
the wedding day for them
Well...
How about next month?
Next month?
Isn't this a bit rush?
Yes
Uncle
Xingchen and I have missed many years
I wanna be her husband
for a longer time
and take care of her
for you
Yan
Pick up your glass
OK
and drink it
then you will be the son-in-law of my family
As for the wedding day
you may decide for yourself
Thank you, uncle
You silly boy
Uncle?
Thanks, Dad
Thanks, Mom
Let's drink together
Let's cheers!
Come on
Congratulations!
Xingxing
Thanks
Thanks, Mom
Good girl
Sit down
Let's sit
Come on
Let's eat
OK
I'll have something
to drink with
The bigger one's decoration is not good
The smaller one's not fancy enough
Do you have something I want?
Mr. Yan
For the famous hotels in Jinghai
We have to book from half a year to one year in advance
You are in such a hurry
It's hard to find a good one
That's your problem
The hotel can't be far from the downtown
or a noisy region
Mr. Yan
Your wife is here
What happened?
Don't you know me?
What a beauty!
Let's go
We only have three hours
We have a meeting this afternoon
Let's go!
Three hours?
Isn't that too short?
Get ready
Let me get this
Hello
It doesn't matter
Shoot me first
OK
Good, stay still
Sorry, it's emergency
Hello
OK
Sorry
Keep going
OK
Now we don't need the flower
Miss Nie
Your wedding is ten days later
But now the hotel
or the site hasn't got ready yet
We are worried that
we can't get ready
before the wedding
Didn't you start the preparation from a long time ago?
We had enough time
but Mr. Yan is the most demanding customer
we've ever seen
We've 12 visions of plans
just for the site
Here is the design draft
You may have a look
If you think it's good,
could you please help us to persuade Mr. Yan?
OK
Look at the pictures
Thank you for your hard work
That's not gonna work
Can we
take some sweet pictures?
OK, no problem
The pictures we took are not bad
But we
should have taken more pictures
when the sun light was sufficient
You can check the pictures
If there is something unsatisfactory,
we can do it again
Jingzhi
I understand you wanna give me
a perfect wedding
I've seen
the latest version of plan
In fact
it is perfect for me
Could you not be that strict
and allow them to go on with their job
You may not get a perfect wedding
but you are still thinking about others
To be honest
your standard of wedding
is a little too much to me
And we have announced
the date of our wedding
If it's really postponed,
it'll be a trouble for us
A trouble?
That's how you see our wedding?
No
Don't get me wrong
I'm talking about the matter at hand
If you care about my wedding
You wouldn't be so indifferent now
That's because I trust you
Then don't interfere with my decision
Dear Mr. Yan Jingzhi,
may I invite you to dance with me?
You won't go to sleep
just for inviting me to dance with you
Do you remember
why you bought me this ring?
Yes
It's because you like the low-key style
So compared with a fancy wedding,
I prefer the sweet normal life
I did not pay no attention to our wedding
It's because that
I think we already have
what's more important than that
Sorry
I didn't control my emotions properly
I did something wrong too
I shouldn't have left everything to you
How about
we make the decision
about the plan tonight
You're the boss
What did you just see?
These two look alike
but I can't decide which one
This one
You see
We are looking at each other in the eyes
How pretty
You look better in this one
This one is good
Look at you
I think we've made the choice
All of these look nice
Right?
Zhen Nian
Don't you think
the wedding dresses here look pretty?
I'm coming
Xingchen
How is this?
You are so gorgeous in the wedding dress
I can't find another word to describe you
I've heard it's hard to hire
the Italian designer
Aunt Ye must have made great efforts
to make this dress
But it's too tight
I can't breathe
It's OK
You look really pretty in it
It should be a sweet burden
I don't know when I can put on a wedding dress
Today is the day
You two go and get dressed
Let's go!
Is that proper?
Yes, let's go
Let's go and try them on
Go
You are here
I'm coming
Darling
You look so beautiful
Mom has a good taste
I like
the dress she picked very much
Mine's better
My bride is the prettiest
You two think I'm invisible, right?
Where is Zhen Nian?
Where is my Niannian?
You're annoying
Our Niannian
Mr. Zhao's Niannian, please come out
Don't stop me
I'm not touching him
I'm not
Our Niannian is too beautiful
Too beautiful. I'm not stopping you
Our Tong Xin is pretty too
Thank you, Mr. Yan
Thank you, Xingchen
Pretty. Xingchen is the prettiest
It feels so wonderful
to put on a wedding dress
Do you think so?
I wore it once on the set
so I don't feel much
Let's take a picture together
Okay! Come on!
You take for us
OK
Move
Let me help you
Come on
Please take a good one
Three, two, one
Wait
Ready
Three, two, one
I wanna one too
Come on
Three, two, one
Nice
Me too
Come on!
Get ready
Come on
Three, two, one
Cheese
Perfect
Have a look
Come on
One more
Three, two, one
Why is he crying?
He hates to let her go,
so he's crying
No
It's because the love of boss and Xingchen is so moving
It so touching
Don't you think so?
Alright
Which one of the four girls
do you think is the prettiest?
Tong Xin
Yes, she is
But don't you think
my Zhen Nian stands out?
Tong Xin is the most outstanding one
She is
but don't you think my Niannian
looks so charming today?
Yes
Tong Xin is the most charming one
Do you have a power bank with you?
Borrow it to me
No way
Darlings
I'm telling you,
you hold up your tears later
You have to control your emotions
We need to take pictures later
Don't you hear me?
Ailu
I can't help it
I wanna cry right now
What are you crying for?
I've done 20 wedding scenes
Don't cry
It's so shameful
No, that's not what I'm talking about
I mean
don't you think Dr. Han
is so handsome today
Don't you think so?
Anyway, Zhao Yuanfang is the ugliest
Sorry
Sorry to interrupt
What's the name of the crying boy?
Sun Yang
Solo? !
Mr. Yan. Mr. Yan. Mr. Yan
Mr. Yan
Finish the process
as soon as possible
no matter what method you use
I'm gonna go on the honeymoon and get ready for pregnancy
Mr. Yan
I understand your feelings
But it is a matter of life
we can't just cut the necessary process out
Where did you find the wedding MC?
He gets 20 pages of the process
Even so, you can't throw the 20 pages
on his face
You also used your hands
to check the quality of his clothes
You tore his clothes
He was too slow
I may not finish the wedding next year
Mr. Yan
I don't care
You have to finish the wedding
as soon as possible, OK?
Otherwise you may lose your job
Ms. Ye
Are you available tomorrow?
What do you
want from me?
Can you make Xingchen back to Jinghai?
Bros
Are you ready?
Your wife just lives opposite
Why are we so early?
Do you still want your year-end bonus
and that of your girlfriends?
Let's go
Go, go, go
Let's take pictures
Come on
One, two, three
Great
Good day, Mr. Yan
Please, move
Bros
How long will it take to break the door?
From the anatomical viewpoint
You need...
Useless
Zhao Yuanfang, your turn
I've made plans with Zhen Nian
She will open the door in a moment
Good buddy
What happened?
I haven't say yes. You stay back
Where the red envelopes?
Red envelopes. Here you are
Red envelopes
Take them away
Open the door
Give a like to your beauty and wisdom
How can you do this?
He used his fingerprint
Zhao Yuanfang, go
Honey, let's move
I can't let you in
Sun Yang
Do you wanna your girlfriend?
Yes
I'm coming
Who are you?
Go away
Xingxing, come on
Why can't I open this door?
There are five red lines
Only when you pick the one held by the bride
can you get in
If you pick the wrong one
you'll be punished
Piece of cake
Do you have confidence, bros?
Be serious
Do you have confidence?
Yes
We can make it
Do you have confidence?
Yes
Sorry
One, two, three, four, go
There is only one left. So it is the one
Are you messing with me?
Are you?
Darling
Sorry to have kept you waiting
I'm late
Get down on your knees
Get up
Did you do it right?
Darling
Leave with me
Wait
They told me
there is one mission left
Just bring it on
I'm marrying me no matter what
Only one of this tied onto my shoe
Honey, you've changed
Are you marrying me or not?
Yes
Bros
Here
Do you have confidence?
Come back