♫  I’ll remember this moment I’m with you  ♫
♫  I’m crush on your eyes  ♫
[Color Rush]
[Episode 4]
Why am I getting dressed?
Why did you come to my house?
Because I miss you so much.
I can't believe he came to the house. I shouldn't meet him.
But why am I getting dressed?
Get home safe.
Hey, don't hang up.
I wasn't able to show you the rainbow before. So instead, I'm going to show you something else.
What is it?
The night view.
[a.nook]
This is for the better.
I'll tell him no after I see this one last time.
That I don't want to meet with a Probe.
Yeon Woo, today is the last trial lesson.
Yesterday, I came here and saw the night view with sunglasses on.
Sunglasses?
Once I did that, I realized that
it might be better not to teach you colors.
It wouldn't be good if you faint here.
But, I need to show you at least once,
that there are views with color that aren't so beautiful.
What color is this?
Lemon.
Yeon Woo, look all the way in front of you.
That's the night view.
Out of all the night views I saw, the night view here looked the most lonesome.
You're right. It is lonesome.
But why in the world are you showing this to me?
Because you're not trying to learn the colors.
Who said I wasn't going to learn the colors?
You just need to teach me the colors and I just need to help you identify faces, right?
- Yes.
- How do I help?
When I ask you to look at me, just look at me.
Like this?
♫ Oh I will be fine, you don't have to worry ♫
♫  The way you look at me, I think about you, again and again  ♫
So?
Are you going to learn the colors?
Yes.
♫ It feels like the whole world is spreading.
Yeah, just like a picture ♫
♫  Take my hand, I'll let you go ♫
No. No.
No! It can't be!
There's no way I could've said that yesterday without losing my mind.
Like this?
I blame it on how beautiful his eyes were when they went from a shade of gray to a caramel color.
It was for this reason that I responded opposite of what I meant to.
So, are you going to learn colors?
Yes.
I'm doomed. How am I supposed to go to school now?
Oh my goodness!
Are you okay?
Not even my mother hit me,
but I got hit by Yeon Woo.
Oh no. Let me see.
I'm okay.
Let's go to the nurse's office.
The nurse is not here again.
Have a seat here.
Since there is a mirror, do you want to put it on yourself?
You're not going to put it on me?
I'd be more of a nuisance if I faint from a color rush.
No, you wouldn't be.
Then, just a little.
It seems I won't faint from this much exposure.
I can take it off if you tell me to.
I'm going to put it on.
Does it hurt a lot?
Blow on it for me.
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Ye-llow.
[Missing person/Mono, Yoo Yi Ri]
Yeon Woo.
[Nurse's Office]
Are you okay?
What the...
Why am I like this?
You were crying a lot.
You suddenly started writhing in pain and cried
but you looked unconscious.
What exactly did I do?
I don't remember.
I can't...
see color.
Don't you remember... the decoloring?
You wanted to see the color of the headband and didn't want the color to fade.
The experience... already past?
That is something Monos experience as they are adjusting to their Probe.
You can experience an extended color rush, a blackout, delayed fainting spell,
and your subconscious can emerge.
Then, it's a good sign that he's adjusting, right?
Regardless, stop doing this at school.
He's already so thin and pale looking.
I understand.
It's a relief to hear that you're adjusting. I was very surprised.
I'm adjusting? To what?
Me? To the Probe?
To Go Yoo Han?
Yeon Woo.
What happens after I adjust? Obsession?
Kidnapping? Murder?
Look at me.
You need to wash your face.
You look pretty even when you're disheveled, but it's so obvious you cried.
I'm the Mono! Why are you the one keeping me from running away?
Go Yoo Han.
♫ Hug me so  ♫
Why are you crying when I'm the one who blacked out?
Earlier, I thought something bad happened to you...
♫  I won't fall  ♫
and I was so scared.
I understand, so let me go.
I don't want to.
Since it's raining... just for a bit.
What does that have to do with hugging me?
♫ Even if I'm far away ♫
I now know
that what my heart desires is different from what is rational.
It's nice being with my Probe.
I want to see color.
Do you want to see the color I see?
Yes.
What?
This jerk! Can he tell what I'm thinking?
Yeon Woo, look forward.
♫  I'm going to confess to you now  ♫
Since I'm your Probe, the color I know will be the color you know,
and we will be seeing the same colors.
What are you talking about?
So if you say the river is the color of the sea, then it's the color of the sea and if you say it's the color of the water, then it's the color of the water?
Yes, that's how it will be.
That's ridiculous.
♫  These nights shine even more because you're here  ♫
For some reason, I saw my happiness fading away the moment I felt happy.
♫ I'll fall asleep  ♫
Loss. When everything fades,
and I only have moments of happiness in a gray space alone,
that's terrifying and horrible. If only I could stop happiness
from escaping me.
If only I...
Choi Yeon Woo!
Let go of me!
♫ and shine on you ♫
Why are you acting like this?
I had the thought... that I wanted to lock you up.
♫  I'll find you no matter where you are  ♫
♫  I never once forgot any of those days ♫
♫  The words I kept to myself  ♫
[Color Rush]
♫  More than any words
♫  When I close my eyes, I hear your breathing  ♫
♫  I’ll remember all your days  ♫
♫  I’ll wait for you here every day  ♫
♫  These nights shine even more  ♫
♫  Because you’re here, that’s the only reason  ♫
♫  In this quiet moment, I'll fall asleep thinking about you  ♫
♫  You probably won’t know how I feel  ♫
♫  My days filled with you  ♫
♫  Now grab my hand, I'll fly to that sky  ♫
♫  and shine on you ♫