♫ This time, this love ♫
♫ I remember this moment I'm with you ♫
♫ I'm crush on your eyes  ♫
[Color Rush]
[Episode 3]
Show me now.
Wow, you jerk!
The trial lesson ends here. How about it? Want to continue?
I don't need it.
What?
Here, take it.
Don't show me that again.
Choi Yeon Woo! You're pretty even when you're mad!
♫  Oh I will be fine, you don't have to worry  ♫
♫  The way you look at me, I think about you again and again  ♫
♫  When our eyes meet, I am reborn  ♫
♫ Feels like the whole world is spreading out
Yeah, just like a picture ♫
♫ Take my hand, I'll let you go ♫
Oh, right. You're the beneficiary of my life insurance.
Are you going somewhere to die?
I'll be on an island for about a month to cover a story.
- For a month?
- Yeah.
I put enough money for your allowance and living expenses into your account.
- Aunt! Wait a second.
- What?
Be careful.
- I'll come back safe and sound.
- Okay.
I'll be going now.
[Encouragement for the Awkward Youth]
I'm not the class president, I'm a servant.
If they're going to make us do things like this, shouldn't they give us some snacks, at least?
Yesterday, the grandfather told me that you would want a snack.
Oh, thanks.
Yeon Woo, you have one too.
Thanks.
I can't just take this. The milk is on me!
What about mine?
Kkwabegi (twisted donut) becomes the donut, the donut becomes the Kkwabegi.
Macbeth.
Why are you pretending to be indifferent? Is only Jung Joo Haeng your friend?
Why don't you care about me?
You're sucking up to Jung Joo Haeng, because he's the class president, right?
- Aren't you going to practice?
- I already finished practice.
That's for Min Jae...
- This guy doesn't even care for me, his childhood friend, nor Min Jae who's been his friend since last year.
- Thanks.
He only takes care of Yeon Woo!
Yeon Woo is very special, unlike the two of you.
But then again, I'd rather break our friendship than being cared for by you.
Yeon Woo, let's go to the science lab later.
Me? Why?
You'll see when you get there.
[Safety First]
Who did this kind of prank?
Do you have a blood phobia?
Yes.
Since when?
I just get anxious when I'm in the same space as you.
Because I'm a Probe?
No, because I feel like you're going to say nonsense.
I've never said any nonsense. I've always been genuine.
Just trust and follow me.
It's nice and kind of cozy in here. It's like a hideout.
A hideout is a perfect place for secret experiments.
What are you going to do?
First, take a seat here.
Look at me.
Are you...
Are you awake?
I wanted to show you a rainbow,
but it wouldn't rain.
Prism.
Can I touch it?
Me?
It's all yours.
I know what it is in my head, and I've seen a rainbow in gray...
But this was the first time I saw a rainbow in color up close.
Red, orange,
yellow, green,
blue, indigo,
violet...
One side looks longer when you change the angle of the prism because of refraction.
It's pretty.
What are you doing?
Show me again.
Go Yoo Han!
I'm only going to wait until the end of this week.
Was this another trial lesson? Why do you want to make such a deal?
You're looking at my face all you want!
All the colors in the world are yours,
however, let me be the one who teaches you.
♫  Oh I will be ♫
Go Yoo Han.
No. We're not strangers anymore.
A Mono and a Probe.
I'm the Probe, right?
♫  When our eyes meet  ♫
I want to see it.
The trial lesson ends here. How about it? Want to continue?
It's all yours.
♫  Take my hand, I'll let you go  ♫
♫  So you can be even freer ♫
It's pretty.
When a Mono meets their Probe, they become obsessed.
I'm not an exception.
♫  This time, this love. When the whole world shines on me  ♫
♫  I'll find wherever you go ♫
Hello?
Hello? Choi Yeon Woo. The article that was released today is only because of suicide, not because they were Mono.
The person who committed suicide was a Mono, however, the spouse wasn't even a Probe. The article was misreported.
- News?
- Yes.
So don't worry about it.
[Breaking News: The head of the household in their forties, who's a Mono, murders their Probe spouse and their family, and commits suicide]
Where is he?
I want to know, too.
It was misreported. It will take some time for the correction to be reported but don't worry about it.
When did I ever care about this, Aunt?
Turn the TV off.
[Aunt]
Don't you dare look up any article about it. This didn't happen because one of them was a Mono, so don't worry about it.
You don't even have a Probe, so don't worry about cases like this.
[The head of the household in their forties, who's a Mono, murders their family]
[Another Mono involved case]
The truth is, I have a Probe, Aunt.
His name is Go Yoo Han, and he is unpredictable.
Choi Yeon Woo.
Yes?
Also, the part about the spouse cheating is only speculation, so don't worry about it.
Are you okay, Aunt? What about the coverage?
It's good here. I get to eat a lot of delicious food.
Yesterday I had sashimi, and today I had black pork.
Even though she sends me these pictures, I know she's following a lead about mom.
Stop sending me food pictures. Are you teasing me?
On my way back, I'll buy some rice cake. Bye-bye.
If mom is involved in the Mono case, that means Aunt is also in danger.
However, Aunt is only worried about me.
♫  Oh, I will be fine ♫
I'm a Mono. There's no way I'm different than any other Mono.
♫  The way you look at me, I think about you again and again ♫
♫  When our eyes meet ♫
Why aren't you running away?
♫  It feels like the whole world is spreading out ♫
If you met a Mono, you have to run away, you idiot.
♫ Take my hand, I'll let you go. So, you can be freer ♫
♫  This time, this love. I'll remember this moment ♫
This darkness. This boredom.
Living like this...
♫  This time, this love ♫
Hey, Yeon Woo.
What?
Where are you?
Home.
[010-43#2- 2$15]
This number I never saved because I didn't want to get closer.
However, I already memorized who this is. It's Go Yoo Han.
Don't answer it. Reject it. Reject it.
♫  I'll remember that moment  ♫
♫  On meaningless days ♫
I'm in front of your house, Yeon Woo. Can you come out for a bit?
♫  When you're looking at me
It feels like the whole world has stopped, like a movie ♫
[Color Rush]
♫  This time, this love. When the whole world shines on me  ♫
♫  I'll find wherever you go ♫
♫ Take me up, where I want. So I can be even freer ♫
♫  This time, this love. I'll remember this moment I'm with you ♫
♫  Just stay with me  ♫
♫  This time, this love. When the whole world shines on me  ♫