Do you have a girlfriend?
Talking to anyone?
Well... maybe a few.
But no girlfriend.
And you?
Me neither.
But you've had a boyfriend before, right?
Come on, at this age?
It would be crazy to never have had one.
But we broke up a long time ago.
I didn't really have time for him.
Do you think we should exchange numbers?
Why?
Just in case we want to grab coffee sometime.
Coffee like... Just coffee. Nothing more.
No need. I told you, I don't really have time.
Are you hungry?
What do you want to eat?
We've been stuck on this island for days.
Do I even get to choose?
Sure you do.
Just tell me what you want, I'll go find it.
[Rathakarn Tour]
Ten minutes, everyone! Ten minutes!
The boat's leaving. Come quickly!
Beautiful lady, hurry up!
Ten minutes!
She's not awake?
Maybe she's not leaving today?
Can you wait a sec? I'll go get my friend.
Alright, boss!
Quick! Come on, miss. Boat's about to leave!
We're here!
Yay!
Because of the storm, you ended up staying longer.
Was it boring?
Oh no, not at all! I'm coming back in two months!
If you want anything from Bangkok,
just tell me, I'll bring it for you.
Kids, do you want anything from Bangkok?
Donuts! The ones in the green box!
Wait, what color?
Green.
Okay, I'll get some for everyone!
Yay!
And don't forget,
if you ever think about selling your land,
think of me first, okay?
Whoever offers me something...
Just tell you, because you can match it.
Right, just like that.
Boat's leaving!
And please tell the other uncles and aunties too,
okay?
Yeah, yeah, you've been saying this for years.
Everyone in the village knows already.
- Goodbye!
- Bye!
Kids, help with the bags, quick!
Thank you!
Hey, You should go, the boat's leaving.
Yeah. Where are you going?
I forgot something. I'll grab it and catch up.
Don't wait, go ahead.
Bye-bye, Ma. Bye-bye!
Bye!
[Narinda]
Here.
Where's your friend?
He said he was going to get you.
Who?
Oh, there, he's coming.
Hurry!
Quick!
- Boss, the boat's leaving!
- Coming!
Alright, captain, everyone's on board.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
There's this painting by an artist I really love.
It's called Question.
In the painting, there are two moons,
one has a rabbit, the other doesn't.
I think it's meant to show that
there are two kinds of people in the world.
Those who believe there's a rabbit on the moon,
and those who don't.
No way, that's ridiculous.
Rabbits on the moon? Come on.
What else is up there besides craters
and spaceship wrecks?
Maybe it's more about imagination
versus no imagination?
Yeah, maybe.
That's probably why it's called Question.
I guess it's asking what kind of person you are.
So... what kind are you?
Well...
The second kind, obviously.
Rabbits on the moon? There's no air up there.
[Koh Yao Pier]
Did you drive here?
Yeah. What about you?
Someone's picking me up.
Oh, okay.
Drive safe.
Yeah.
It was nice meeting you, Mr. Jira.
Nice meeting you too, Miss Plew.
If we run into each other again,
like, by coincidence...
can we go grab coffee together?
Okay. If it's by coincidence.
Sure.
She's back, Mom.
She should've come back two or three days earlier.
She knew today was an important day, didn't she?
There was a storm, Mom. Boats couldn't leave.
She went for work, not for a vacation.
Selling land as a random freelancer.
You call that work?
And some remote island with a storm,
how can you sell land there anyway?
There's a beautiful plot right by the highway,
fully leveled, and she's not even interested.
I really don't know what she's thinking.
Oh, here we go again,
praising your precious youngest daughter.
Don't talk like that.
You're already late, go get changed.
Are you girls ready yet?
Oh, Cha.
You just got back?
I thought everyone would be ready by now.
Being 30 minutes late isn't a big deal, Dad.
I already prepared everything.
Just give me 15 minutes, everyone.
Alright.
Here.
Can I talk to you for five minutes?
But I'm already late, Mom.
You can talk while you get dressed.
Mom, I know I'm late. I'm hurrying already,
please don't scold me right now.
I'm not here to scold.
I just want to say,
you're going to meet a lot of people today.
Yes.
And if someone happens to ask
what you're doing for work right now,
I'd like you to say you're helping your sister.
Mom...
This whole freelance land-selling thing,
it just sounds...
Mom, just because I'm not like Plearn
doesn't mean I've failed.
What you think in your head
and how others see you is different.
Do you even realize how people see you right now?
I just don't want anyone
thinking of my daughter like...
Like how you're thinking of me now?
I'll wait downstairs.
[Learnplern Tutor]
Congratulations.
Thank you, Dad.
Finally, I've reached my dream.
This is the academy's 100th branch.
I want to thank everyone who believed in me.
Special thanks to Mr. Laks.
Thank you, Uncle Danai,
for always supporting me
and helping select every location.
Lastly, my mom has something to share.
Hello everyone,
thank you so much for being here today.
Since today is such an auspicious occasion,
I have wonderful news to share.
This year, my daughter Plearn will have
the most important event of her life: Her wedding.
So let me invite the groom-to-be,
Mr. Laks Jarulaks, son of Mr. Danai and Mrs. Jear,
to come up and share more details himself.
Please come!
- For you.
- Thank you so much, my love.
- Congratulations.
- Let's take some photos.
Sure.
After they get married,
Laks will give Plearn space in every mall branch
so she can expand her tutoring business.
You should help her too.
Tell them they won't regret it
(In Chinese)
If they invest in a wellness center in Thailand
with me,
because it'll be the best wellness center in Asia.
(In English)
Have you found any interesting local agents?
Yes, Pitchaland Scout and Wonderland Agent.
These two are the most promising, boss.
Just what we're looking for.
Pitchaland is the one managing it all.
Would you like to check it out yourself, boss?
You haven't been back to Thailand
in two years, right?
Alright, reach out to both agencies.
Let's see which one offers the better deal.
Got it, boss.
Oh, one more thing.
The gift you sent to your mom...
No one signed for it, so it was returned.
There was no one home?
There was, but no one signed for it.
In that case, just request a return at the shop.
Got it, boss.
[Mama]
[Learnplern Tutor]
[Tutor Service]
[Learn English for beginner to advanced students]
Hello, Miss Pitcha.
Miss Plearn is waiting for you inside.
This way, please.
- Plearn.
- Yeah?
Wow, every room is full of students, amazing!
I'll need to open two more branches
in time for exam season.
Whoa, can you handle that?
I'll have to. I need help though.
Honestly, I need to open ten more branches.
Every parent wants their kid to be number one.
But only one kid can actually be number one,
right?
Parents are so pressuring.
Kids who are competitive love it though,
there are tons of them.
Kids like you, Plearn.
Look at this.
Look.
Honor rolls, certificates, your room is filled.
It's insane.
And this is exactly why Mom doesn't love you.
So this is why you called me to help, huh?
Well, I'm not helping anymore. I'm annoyed now.
Oh, my dear little sister, sit down.
What now? What do you want?
Actually, I want to do a pre-wedding photo shoot.
Find me a gorgeous, unseen location, please.
I want water flowing in front, mountains behind.
Just like the feng shui master said.
Feng shui for a grave site, maybe?
Hey! Watch it.
Water in front symbolizes peace.
Mountains in the back mean stability.
If this photo hangs in my home,
it'll be the best feng shui ever.
Come on, just find me a place. It won't take long.
But a view like that,
don't we have to go upcountry?
Will Laks be okay with that?
He's fine with anything.
He lets me make all the decisions. He spoils me.
Spoils or ignores you?
Hey!
Jealous much? Or just bitter at life?
I hate having an older sister.
Why?
Too much pressure.
Constant comparisons.
It's like a caste system.
I'm the untouchable.
So your sister's really that good, huh?
Do you have siblings?
I'm the eldest.
- Ah, one of those perfect older siblings.
- Hey now.
Why is that?
That's what Grandma used to say.
Older siblings take care, younger ones whine.
My sibling doesn't love me either.
Probably thinks the same way you do.
Even though I'm not that perfect.
Do you think parents
love all their children equally?
Do you love your parents equally?
You do, but in different ways, right?
Different people, different kinds of love.
I believe they love you.
Just maybe differently
from how they love your sister.
Good evening, listeners.
Off work, where are you heading tonight?
If you're unsure, I've got a recommendation.
The final day of the art exhibition by Kookkie,
a brilliant modern artist for the new generation.
Beautiful, meaningful pieces, only until 9 PM.
Oh right, I almost forgot.
This next song is for the listener
who requested it earlier this afternoon.
"I don't know who that person wants to meet,
but I hope that person meets them."
Here's "Want to See You" by Blue Shade.
I'll be the one
who believes there's a rabbit on the moon.
Rabbits on the moon?
Come on, there's no air on the moon, you know.
[Sold]
Wait, someone already bought this?
[Attasit Pokpong]
[The Presence]
- Hello?
- Hi, I'm Jack. I'm Anita's assistant.
Hello, Jack. I'm Pitcha. How can I help you?
Actually, I can speak Thai.
And so can Anita.
She used to work in Thailand
for nearly four years.
Oh, I see.
I didn't realize Anita still speaks Thai.
She hasn't been to Thailand in about two years.
When we saw your properties, we got interested.
We're currently considering two agents.
So I'd like to get more details.
How many days would it take,
which sites are included,
and how do we travel around?
Sure, I'll send it over shortly.
Tentatively,
the trip would take seven to ten days.
If Anita needs anything else,
don't hesitate to let me know.
I'll take care of everything.
Okay, thank you very much, Pitcha.
I want to rent a car.
But I want to pick it out myself.
My guest is VVIP, okay?
Plew!
Mom!
- Mom...
- What is it?
I did it!
Did what, why are you yelling so loud
the neighbors can hear?
Anita contacted me, Mom!
Who?
Anita! A major investor from China.
She never goes out to view land
with anyone in Thailand.
I thought you'd already given up on selling land.
No, Mom! I'm not giving up.
She's huge, like, huge!
If I close this deal,
I could be looking at hundreds of millions!
So the other day when we talked,
you weren't even thinking about what I said,
were you?
Mom, I have my own life.
I have things I'm passionate about.
I've always tried to understand you.
But nothing ever seems to happen.
How old are you now?
Huh?
People your age already own their own businesses.
And what about you?
Still carrying that canvas bag,
selling stinky plots of land?
Time...
Time is the most valuable thing
a person can waste.
Mom, please listen.
I'll give you just three more months.
If you don't make those hundreds of millions
like you claimed,
you'll stop everything
and go work for your sister.
You're almost 30 now. Time to stop playing around.
This place is really beautiful.
Thailand has so many beautiful islands,
but no one takes care of them properly.
People just build whatever they want.
Wastewater systems are a mess.
That's true. I actually own a small plot myself.
At first, my family wanted to sell it too.
But I refused.
I just couldn't let go of some of the trees.
Silly, right?
Not at all.
Some people buy land
just because they love the trees or soil.
Really?
Honestly, I'm always happy when I meet people
who truly appreciate the value of beautiful land.
It's so important
to preserve the beauty of our planet.
You're awesome.
Keep doing what you're doing.
Not many people think that way anymore.
Are you like, an environmentalist or something?
Are you?
You know,
we really should've exchanged LINE contacts.
Mook, I'll come see you tomorrow.
I want to send this proposal to China
as soon as possible.
Okay, bye.
[Car Loft]
Limousine?
It's just two people,
perfect for a luxurious impression.
I don't think that's practical.
We're heading out of town too.
What about a camper van?
Very trendy, I just finished one.
Someone like her only stays in six-star hotels.
Okay, fine, then it has to be a van.
How many seats do you need?
You're coming too, right?
I have one that seats up to six. Super stylish.
Yeah, a van it is. But get me a good driver, okay?
Got it. I'll take care of it.
When do you need it?
I can't say yet.
I have to wait for her approval first.
If she gives the go-ahead,
then I'll confirm with you.
Wow, complicated.
Are you paying for everything yourself?
If she buys the land, I'll just advance the cost.
If not, maybe she'll cover half.
I'll give you a special rate.
Thank you so much!
Let's go get coffee.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Just a second.
Yes, Jack?
You said I should let you know
if Anita needs anything extra, right?
Yes?
Well, Anita has a small request.
If you can get in touch with a certain person,
she'll be very happy.
Jay, the most famous host in Thailand?
You mean, if I can get Jay,
she'll agree to come view the land?
Yes.
Okay then.
I'll take care of it and get back to you.
Thank you so much, Pitcha.
What the heck?
Anita wants a host to come view the land with me.
Oh my gosh, classy Chinese lady.
Wait, what even is a host?
What? You don't know?
A host, like a bar host. A guy who entertains you.
You buy drinks, he flirts.
You mean a male escort?
No, not like that.
He just entertains you, makes you feel special.
If things go further,
that's between the two people.
These days, it's super trendy.
Women who are bored or lonely go to a host bar.
They pay guys to take care of them,
like boyfriend vibes, then go their separate ways.
Paying men to take care of you like that?
Well, maybe it works
for people who don't have time for love.
It's sweet, dreamy.
The guys are good-looking, clean nails,
oil-free face, super attentive.
- It's relaxing, really.
- Whoa, have you gone before?
No, but a lot of my clients do.
They like to rent my luxury cars
for the hosts to drive.
So who did your VVIP guest request?
A guy named Jay.
He's the most famous host in Thailand.
Only takes VIP clients.
His wait list is a year long.
[Thailand's No.1 Bar Host Jay,
Contact: Tiwa or Smile Bar]
What is this? I'm confused.
There's no photo either?
Just says contact Tiwa or Smile Bar.
So I have to go to a bar host?
No way. I'm not doing this.
If you don't go, someone else will.
Didn't you say that
that Chinese lady only considers two agents?
You'll miss your shot.
You're right.
Go now.
You're on your own for this one,
I'm not coming with you.
[Smile]
Excuse me, I'd like to speak to someone about Jay.
Jay's not in today.
What? He's not working today?
Hey Tiger, someone's asking for Jay.
Hi there! Are you here to book Jay?
Yes. Actually, I'm booking for a friend.
Booking for a friend?
Yes. A friend.
Does anyone have his contact number?
Please wait a moment.
Here, call this number.
[Smile]
[Tiva Teeraboonseth]
That's Tiwa,
the only one who manages Jay's schedule.
If you're lucky and have enough money,
you might get a slot.
But if Jay's not available, I am.
Hi, I'm Gur.
Okay. Thanks.
What the heck? I'm a top host too, you know.
Forget it. Let's keep rehearsing. Go, go!
Hey hey! Keep practicing!
Hey hey!
Tiwa, please help me today, it's my birthday.
I just want to be extra happy today.
I really can't fit you in.
Jay's been booked solid three months in advance.
I'll put you on the waiting list
and ask Jay what he wants to do.
Hello, I'd like to check Jay's availability.
- Oh, Miss Noeywan?
- No, it's Noeyhom this time.
One moment, please.
Hello, Tiwa speaking.
Yes, this is Tiwa.
What can I help you with?
Jay's schedule is completely full
starting next month.
Like, really full.
I'm working through his bookings now,
there are three or four people waiting.
Please try again next time.
- Yes, that's the correct response.
- Okay.
- Twenty... Twenty.
- Twenty, wait...
One moment, please.
Yes.
Coming here doesn't magically
get you a slot with Jay.
If it's a no, it's a no.
I'm sorry.
Everything has been arranged just for today.
- Twenty.
- So please, can you double-check for me?
One moment.
- I'm listening.
- I'm not asking for your guy to spoon-feed me.
He's for a client of mine,
she wants to book ten full days.
Do the math and decide,
are you really going to hang up on me?
Or are you going to tell me where you are
so we can talk business?
All-inclusive.
Ten days.
I'm still waiting.
Okay?
Hold on a sec, a big client just called.
What?
Hello, my dear Jay, what are you doing right now?
Do you have a minute to swing by my café?
I told you, I'm not free today.
I know, but...
Hear me out for a second...
Mrs. Saisamorn Jaikhuenkaew,
please proceed to the exam room.
Your turn.
Your blood sugar levels aren't looking great.
This means you haven't cut down on sweets
like I told you, have you?
And your blood pressure is high.
You should be careful,
it could come as a combo pack.
High blood pressure, diabetes, heart problems.
But it's durian season! My friend sent me some.
Still, don't eat too much of it.
Especially if it's premium Monthong
from Palau forest.
Alright, I'm going to prescribe
one more medication.
But from now on, I'll need you to come in
for blood tests every two weeks, okay?
- What? Every two weeks? That's too much.
- Alright.
Okay, in that case,
I'll go ahead and schedule your next appointment.
These are your blood test results.
- Alright then.
- And don't forget, please cut back on sweets.
Durian isn't a sweet. It's a fruit, doctor.
Thanks, Doc.
Thank you very much.
I think getting blood drawn once a month
is enough.
Why?
The doctor said every two weeks,
so let's stick with that.
I feel bad.
You're not even my kid,
and yet you're the one taking me
to the doctor every month.
I don't even know how to repay you.
Just to be clear, I'm not some rich old lady
with a billion-baht inheritance.
So if you're hoping to get something from me,
forget it.
Wow, then I guess I'll go now.
Goodbye, Aunt Samorn, the inheritance-less one.
Hey!
Thanks, dear. Thank you for taking care of me.
Must be such a hassle.
How many times do I have to tell you
it's not a hassle at all?
If I don't take you, who will?
You don't have any kids.
If you really want to repay me,
cut down on the snacks.
I'll make you some sour curry.
Sour curry again?
Didn't I just say to cut down on sweets?
Do you even listen?
Yes?
I should be done by evening.
If they can wait, let them.
I seriously can't go any faster.
They want to hire you
to take care of a Chinese VIP for ten days.
All first-class travel.
Staying at six-star hotels for the whole trip.
The contact's name is Pitcha.
I've checked the schedule already.
If we shuffle some things around, it could work.
Just say you tested positive for COVID
and it'll be over.
At least talk to her. It's a big payday, man.
Traffic's probably bad.
How long have you managed Jay?
About two years.
Is he really that famous?
I tried looking for his photos
and couldn't find anything.
If he's that famous,
shouldn't there at least be some photos of him?
He's so famous,
he can choose not to have pictures online.
Jay doesn't take jobs lightly.
If family's involved, he says no.
Even if the money is crazy good,
if he doesn't want to do it, he won't.
And... if I call him now, will he pick up?
It's been over three hours.
Just in time.
Jay, this is Pitcha.
Pitcha, this is Jay.
Ma! Ma!
Ma!
Ma's not here.
She went to the pier. Should be back soon.
Oh. She left you to watch the shop?
Yeah, I come here a lot. So Ma has me help out.
I've never seen you before.
I've never seen you either.
Honestly, I don't run into many Thai people here.
Are you a land hunter?
Huh? A what?
Guess not.
I'm just a regular employee.
Name's Jira.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too. And you are...
Plew.
Plew?
Pitcha, shall we begin?
You've been waiting quite a while.
Please have a seat. This is Jay.
Hey ma'am, can you order me a coffee?
Pitcha has been waiting for over three hours.
It's fine. Let him drink his coffee first.
Alright.
So, do I need to go for a medical exam?
Huh?
Any underlying conditions I should know about?
Should we go get checked together?
Should I get checked too?
Gross. I'm just a regular employee.
You didn't tell me what you do, either.
You didn't even tell me your full name.
Why should I?
We're spent ten days together, remember?
So what?
You knowing my full name,
does that suddenly make me
a better person in your eyes?
I don't think
I'll be taking this job, Miss Pitcha.