- Hello.
- Hi.
- Are you here with your boyfriend today?
- Yes.
You look great together.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Have a great day.
Secretary Mo.
What's up with you since yesterday?
Why are you so quiet?
What about me?
Usually,
when I even dare to yawn, you start giving me an endless lecture
that the CEO shouldn't yawn during work hours.
Is there something wrong?
Since when were you so interested in me?
Just act like you usually do.
Is something really up with him?
Assistant Manager Bang Seong Woo: Where are you, Secretary Mo?
Are you at the rooftop again?
It's really over between Ms. Ah Young and me.
♫ It's the end.
Maybe I should have asked her the reason.
Maybe she was in real trouble or something. I was the only one she could turn to.
No, no, that's not right.
What are you saying, Mo Tae Kyung?
Does she count on you? Right.
We aren't even dating or anything.
Get a grip.
You must pull yourself together.
See? I knew he would be here.
Secretary Mo!
What is it?
Why won't you answer my messages?
First, I must apologize.
I should have checked more carefully.
I heard my Ms. Ah Young made a mistake toward you.
My Ms. Ah Young?
I mean, why would he be checking Ms. Ah Young's money?
And why did they come together?
Don't tell me she fell for that womanizer already!
That b*stard, really!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know Ms. Ah Young would go talk to you right away.
Ms. Ah Young, why just stand there?
Apologize to Secretary Mo again.
I'm really sorry.
Hold on, Mr. Bang Seong Woo.
Why did you make Ms. Ah Young apologize to me like this?
Pardon?
Then what should have I done?
If you needed money, you should ask me directly!
Well, that doesn't mean I would have lent you money, but still...
No... Excuse me...
Secretary Mo, I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you pretending you don't get it? What a coward!
But the mistake with this month's paycheck wasn't
made by me but Ms. Ah Young.
Even if you made a mistake with this month's paycheck...
Made a mistake with what?
Your paycheck for this month.
She confused your paycheck with Mr. Mo Ji Woo's from the PR Team.
Didn't you know that there was an error with your paycheck?
I'm really sorry.
Please
give the money back!
Back! Please give the money back!
Here. Please check it. I sent the money back.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry for causing all this trouble.
No! It's nothing. It's fine.
I'm sorry for not hearing you out till the end.
You must have really worried then.
I'm very sorry I misunderstood you.
You were so startled, right?
I'm sorry. I should have double-checked.
Secretary Mo.
Ms. Ah Young,
that date we couldn't go on last week,
let's do it this week.
W-Why?
Is it that you don't... want to?
No. I'd like to.
I like you more!
You're cute.
You're cuter, Secretary Mo.
That sunglasses idea is original.
Should I try it on my Mi So?
I should order one first.
What do you want to do this weekend?
Would you like to go see a movie?
What kind of movie would you like to watch?
How about a horror movie?
H-H-Horror...
From now on, we won't be serving the Ga Du Ri Special here anymore.
Instead, we'll officially open Ga Du Ri Tarot Cards starting next Monday.
To get a tarot reading, please DM (direct message) us with your story!
Wow, this place has great service! The raw fish here is fire, too!
I thought the owner reading tarot cards for customers was just a rumor!
The owner is super cool!
Shall we go there today?
Did anyone get their tarot cards read there? Reviews, please!
Soon Jeong: Yes, I have!
As someone who was there already, I can definitely vouch for it!
Oh? It's Ms. Soon Jeong.
I guess she's doing well.
Woo Bin: The raw halibut here is amazing.
For your information, the owner has a really, really handsome boyfriend.
That's Mr. Woo Bin.
He's so adorable.
One minute before getting off work.
Mr. CEO!
I'll be leaving now. Just so you know, don't contact me this weekend.
Have I ever contacted you first?
Anyway I must go get a skincare treatment for my date on the weekend.
You should get one, too.
You heard of male grooming, right?
Grooming means–
I'm leaving.
You can stay here and talk the night away.
"You can stay here and talk the night away," right?
I'll talk the night away with Ms. Ah Young!
♫  I’ll sweep, sweep everything away. Swept, swept away  ♫
Another bottle of Soju, please!
Yes, just a second!
Yes, coming right up!
♫  The pain is that people’s common love is not real love  ♫
Thanks.
♫  I’ll sweep, sweep away. I'll blow everything away  ♫
Here's the raw fish. Please enjoy!
- Welcome!
- Hello.
Did you see it earlier?
Yes, that guy in the tuxedo was sobbing like crazy.
He seemed normal though.
I know, right?
Let's just order.
I want this one.
No, let's order the wraps.
Since you're paying, I want something expensive.
♫  The end of love  ♫
♫  After a long time  ♫
Du Ri...
I mustered up all my courage to come here for the last time.
What?
I know that I'm thick-skinned to be acting like this,
- but–
- Stop it.
What's your excuse this time?
I'm sorry.
Really...
I'm really, truly sorry.
I wanted to apologize to you sincerely if I ever had a chance.
That's why I came here last time.
But I was too much of a coward to tell you then.
And I dragged it on till today.
In the end...
I get to tell you this now in the end.
You know me well.
I never take responsibility for what I do.
I always blame other people.
But...
I don't want to be a loser and coward to the end.
Please forgive this idiot,
the idiot from the past.
And...
Woo Joo as well.
Why are you apologizing on my behalf?
Woo Joo, no, well...
Is this why you were lurking around here?
I'm really sorry to you, too.
I mean it.
Did we go through all that, just to face this?
I know you're very upset,
but I really wanted to apologize to Du Ri
before it was too late.
Even if it meant
you breaking off the marriage,
I had to.
You could have told me earlier.
What?
If you had told me earlier, then I didn't have to live like this.
I didn't have to pretend I was fine!
Woo Joo.
I've been suffering from a huge inferiority complex,
ever since I was your best friend, until now.
Of course, you always had my back because you had no idea,
not knowing it made me more miserable!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It may seem childish,
but I hated to tell you.
So it has come to this.
I'm sorry.
I ask you,
why are you telling me this now?
What?
Hey, do you know how difficult it was for me?
I didn't even know that.
You should have told me back then.
I'm really sorry.
I'm not sorry.
I'm the b*stard here.
I'm sorry.
Woo Bin, look at this!
It's so pretty!
Do you like fish that much?
I'm getting jealous.
I think you like them more than you like me.
Yes, I love it here.
Yes?
Pretty.
Woo Bin, it just talked to me!
What did it say?
That Ga Du Ri is pretty.
Thanks to our Channel Manager: loulou_98
Thanks to our Chief Segmenter: karasu_006,
Segmenters: gennaowen_497, hesto, alessandrina,
kawaii_2017, nanaosaki81, sweetsunnyday,
kkikikaa, livia_mcluz_910, shms
Thanks to our Editors: worthyromance (Chief Editor),
twinkling (General Editor), hannalee123 (Translation Editor)
Thanks to all our language moderators!
Do you really like fish more than me?
Well... I wonder?
Do you wonder?
But who do you think manages this aquarium?
Do you want me to buy you the whole aquarium?
Yes, please!
Woo Bin, are you really going to do it?
Of course.
Once I make up my mind, I push ahead no matter what.
Du Ri, are you nervous?
No.
It's just this is the first drama actually breaking down the wall.
- Okay, let's do this!
- All right!
Coming up: One order of Ga Du Ri Special.
Ga Du Ri Restaurant was pleased to serve you!
Thanks to all our viewers!
Yes.
See you at the restaurant later.
Why did you laugh?
I'm sorry.
Let's shoot one more time. Please standby.
Cut! Okay!
Good night!
Hold on!
Look here! Oh!
They won't fly all over...
You're the one disrupting my business–
- I'm sorry.
- Okay, let's do it again.
You're the one dis–
Oh, my tongue's twisted now. What should I do?
I'm in trouble.
What? I have hot sauce coming out of my nose.
We can't see the blood. We need to see the blood.
Hey, cut it out!
Why would you pick your nose?
Up here... Here... Over here...
What's... this... scent?
Scent!
Please stop rolling the camera, please.
♫ Love
Oh, I can't...
I'm sorry.
Ga Du Ri Restaurant