Wh- What's going on?
Why is it this thing again?
What is this thing?
A stone figurine.
A stone figurine?
Why is it here?
What's that pale stuff?
It's so disgusting.
Uncle Wang.
Have you seen this thing before?
Of course I have.
Anyway, these stone figurines...
There are plenty on Ailong Mountain.
They're buried inside the mountain.
Whenever there's a landslide...
They roll right down.
It's because of these stone figurines...
That recently on this road...
Who knows how many car accidents happened.
This should be modeled after the Han Dynasty.
Could this be from the King of Dian era?
Following this logic...
Have we already entered...
The King of Dian's territory?
Hard to say.
Let me tell you...
Many people think Ailong Mountain is unlucky.
It's exactly because of this thing.
Anyway, whenever it appears...
Bad things are bound to happen.
Uncle Wang.
You don't need to tell us this.
Feudal superstition.
We don't believe in it.
Superstition is one thing.
But if we want to find local ruins...
It's better to ask around.
Uncle Wang.
What do locals say about this stone figurine?
Many people say...
That this is a kind of ancient humanoid coffin.
A coffin?
That's just a legend.
I don't know what it's actually used for either.
Anyway, that's what everyone passes around.
If you ask me, let's hurry up and leave.
Look, so many big rocks.
Lest they all come crashing down in a bit.
Let's go, Old Lu. Let's go.
What a pity.
It's broken.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Look at these tire tracks.
A car accident might have actually happened here.
Look.
What's that sound?
Someone's there.
Fatty.
Get the rope.
Don't move.
We're coming to save you.
Give it to me. Hurry, hurry.
I'll go down from here.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Hold it tight.
Be careful.
Buddy. Buddy.
Fatty.
Pull it up.
Okay.
Old Lu, Uncle Wang, help out.
Okay, come on.
Come on. One, two.
Be careful.
Come on, slowly.
Old Lu.
He's badly injured.
How are you doing?
Old Chen.
Be careful.
Buddy, wake up.
Wake up.
You're saved.
How is he?
Not too optimistic.
He hit his head and bled a lot.
Is there a hospital nearby?
It's in the county town.
That's too far.
What about the inn? How far is it?
Still a few kilometers away.
Okay, help him to the inn.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, Old Lu.
Let's go.
Come on, hurry up!
Sister Yang.
Someone in that car is injured.
Injured?
Hurry up, hurry up.
Then hurry.
Help him in, help him in.
Let's go, hurry up.
Come, this way.
What are you doing?
What's up?
This is that kid's bag.
Let me see what's inside.
I really found something.
There's a badge here.
I think it represents some organization.
Let me see.
Look, look.
This is a Cambridge University badge.
I think he's just a student.
Don't make a fuss.
Coming, coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Come, come.
Have some bananas.
Here, thanks.
Have some tea.
Sorry for the trouble.
Sister Yang.
How is that young man?
He's fine.
He just stayed by the cliff for too long.
He's a bit dehydrated.
As for his injuries, they're not serious.
Did you chat with him?
What does that young man do?
He said he came here to catch butterflies.
Seems like a college student from abroad.
See? I wasn't wrong.
Going abroad just to see a bridge.
China is his roots.
Sister Yang.
We actually have something.
We want to ask you about something.
Tell me what it is.
How do locals cross this Ailong Mountain?
You want to cross Ailong Mountain?
Why?
We want to go to Guyu behind Ailong Mountain.
Ailong Mountain isn't a place for ordinary people.
I advise you.
You'd better drop this idea.
Sister Yang.
It's like this.
We are archaeologists from the provincial capital.
We just want to find a guide to lead the way.
Do you know what we locals
call Guyu of Ailong Mountain?
We call it evil.
It means evil.
So you should all reconsider.
Whether to go or not.
No wonder the locals
avoid Ailong Mountain whenever it's mentioned.
Brother Liu, you said so much.
You mean you want to lead us over this mountain.
You're risking your life, right?
If I were risking my life to take you there,
I'd charge more than this price.
No.
Then what do you mean?
I know a shortcut.
We don't need to cross over Ailong Mountain.
Instead, we can take a bamboo raft
and follow the water flow through the mountain's Water Cave.
This water flow
crosses this mountain
and eventually flows to the other side of Ailong Mountain.
Which is Serpent's Crawl River.
Because the terrain is flat,
the water flow isn't fast.
Before we set off,
we just need to launch the raft and go downstream.
It will save a lot of effort.
Have you taken this shortcut before?
Of course.
It was discovered by herb gatherers here.
Take us there.
Okay.
I like working with straightforward people.
Then you guys pack up.
We'll set off tonight.
What's wrong?
A rabbit.
This, this.
Everyone, follow me.
In this forest,
there are hunting traps I set.
It'll be trouble if you step on one.
What is that?
I don't know.
Wh-What is this thing?
It's a bamboo rat.
They only come out at night to find food.
They sleep in their holes during the day.
Old Chen.
Turn off the flashlight.
Hurry!
How come it's you?
Are you healed?
Shouldn't you be at the Caiyun Inn right now?
Are you the guys who saved me?
Actually, Sister Yang told me you had already left.
I felt quite regretful.
I haven't been able to thank you in person yet.
My name is Dawei.
And my Chinese friends all call me Dawei.
Alright.
We still have to hit the road.
Let's meet again some other time.
Bro.
Wait a minute. Um...
You guys take this.
For safety. Here.
What is this for?
Just to light up the night road. It's safer.
Here.
Just pull it open to use it.
I'll take it.
Brother.
Now that we're done talking, let's go our separate ways.
Thanks for this thing.
Brother Fatty.
I'm actually heading that way too.
Who's your brother?
You sure act familiar.
Dawei, what's your major?
Are you from abroad too?
I just know how to speak English.
Why did you come here?
I'm a PhD student in zoology.
I came here
for a special kind of butterfly.
Cool.
Consultant He is whispering with someone in the back.
Aren't you going to do something?
What whispering?
Isn't it pretty loud?
What's the use of being loud?
They're speaking English.
Bullying us for being uneducated and not understanding.
That's Consultant He.
She might be testing Ding Dawei.
You came all the way to Nanyun
just for this?
This is the only place in the world
where this butterfly might exist.
Do you want to go see it with me?
Consultant He.
Over here.
Coming.
No, thanks.
I hope you can find it.
Wait.
What's wrong?
My name is Dawei.
Shutong.
Everyone.
Wait for me here for a few minutes.
I'll go get the bamboo raft.
We're almost at the Water Cave.
Okay.
That's great.
We can finally take a break.
Good lord.
I'll go pick some fruits for us to eat.
No problem.
Lord Fatty will pick some for you.
Dummy.
There's plenty.
Here, catch these two first.
Here's another one.
What kind of fruit is this? You're just eating it?
Is it poisonous?
I don't care about that.
Chen Youxi is eating it first anyway.
As long as he doesn't die from poison, I'll take a bite.