What's wrong?
You look so calm.
This pearl must be fake.
Every time I passed out,
it meant the pearl was real.
But you can't really say that.
But you did pass out back in Yunling.
Every time you held this pearl,
your face would contort.
And all that crazy stuff.
You're so calm this time,
which means this divine pearl has no magic.
Alright, alright.
What divine pearl?
You're just talking superstitious nonsense.
Bro,
how about we take this pearl abroad?
The archaeology department at my school
has a team studying such mysterious antiques.
No way.
This is a Chinese artifact.
How can it go abroad?
That's losing our national treasures.
We were too busy celebrating.
We forgot we're sitting on a volcano.
Anyway, we've got the pearl.
Let's go.
Right, right.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Darn it!
Look, the tree sap is melting.
The tree hole will be sealed shut.
Everyone, let's go! Hurry!
Go, go, go! Careful, careful!
Go, go, go! Hurry!
Commander Chen, help!
I can't get out!
Pull hard!
Alright, alright.
Hurry up!
Chen Youxi!
Lao Lu, watch out!
Wh-What do we do, Lao Chen?
Bro!
The ground is cracking again!
The magma is exposed!
Listen to me.
I'll take the lead.
You all follow.
Don't wander off.
If I fall in,
keep moving forward.
Whoever can make it out, make it out.
Pfft!
Don't jinx it!
What do you mean "whoever can make it out"?
We leave together!
Fatty!
Okay, okay, okay.
We'll listen to you.
Let's go!
Lao Lu!
Dawei!
Come on!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Dawei, jump!
Jump, Dawei!
Jump! Hurry!
Just close your eyes and jump! Hurry up!
Come on!
Hurry!
Give me your hand!
Jump! Come on!
Dawei, jump!
Go! Slow down, slow down.
Hurry!
Oh my god.
Alright, alright.
I wonder if this Lingxiao Pearl
can lift the curse on Lao Chen.
Why worry about that now?
Let's just hold onto it.
We still have Director Zhu, right?
Right. When we get back,
we can ask around together.
Right, right, right.
Do you guys remember the murals in the tomb passage?
You mean the ritual?
Yes.
The mural showed abnormal weather,
and people being swept into the air.
We all thought it was a natural phenomenon.
But we overlooked a detail.
The ground beneath the high priest's feet
actually had cracks.
At the time, Lao Chen thought
they were marks left by time.
So no one paid attention to it.
Sis,
are you trying to say
that the year recorded on the mural
is the year when Guyu
experienced crustal movement?
Yes.
The King of Dian had been waiting for the right time to ascend.
But besides the Lingxiao Pearl, the ritual
also required a celestial anomaly.
In modern terms,
it should be a volcanic eruption.
The few times recorded in Guyu
probably only involved crustal movement.
The volcano didn't actually erupt.
That's why this information has been passed down.
They wanted to wait until
the day the volcano truly erupted,
so descendants could use the Lingxiao Pearl to complete the ritual.
Then...
Then didn't we arrive at the exact right time?
That's easy then.
Isn't the altar right over there?
We'll know once we go over and take a look.
Let's go.
Hurry! Hurry!
Lao Lu!
Lao Lu, hurry!
Come on!
Lao Lu!
Jump!
Come on!
No, Bro, Bro!
It's on fire!
Fire, fire, fire!
I'll treat you to a meal when we get back.
Commander Chen is treating.
That's rare.
Mutton hotpot.
I'm treating.
Lao Lu is paying.
Then we'll have to eat for three days straight.
Aren't you afraid of overeating?
What about you, Shutong?
Me?
Wait until we get back safely.
What you owe me,
I'll settle the score with you then.
Commander Chen,
I think the rest of your life is spoken for.
Watch out!
Why is there another big gap here?
We can't cross it this time.
Here's the plan. I'll jump over first.
I'll pull you over with the grappling hook.
Dawei, you go first.
Jump hard!
Come on, come on!
Lao Lu, come over!
One, two, three!
Mr. Lu!
Fatty, jump over quickly!
Advisor He, there's no time!
Jump!
Come on!
One, two, three, go!
Bro.
Half of the Lingxiao Pearl is mine, and half is yours.
No matter what we see or hear,
we split it equally, okay?
Bro,
as long as we go to the altar now,
we can explore the mysteries of the entire universe.
You don't need to throw your life away
for a few other people.
I'm taking the Lingxiao Pearl to break the curse
just to spend a few more years with them.
To hell with your universe!
Bro, Bro!
We are not enemies.
You really don't have to do this.
If you want this pearl,
you just have to ask me for it.
Bro,
if it were just you,
I definitely would have asked you for it.
But those three are different from you.
They came for you.
How could they possibly give me the pearl?
So you killed people?
You killed people?!
Bro,
I had no other choice!
But for the Lingxiao Pearl,
I had to do it.
What exactly do you want?
Do you know Bai Lingling?
I'm in the same organization as her.
Our boss
has been collecting Lingxiao Pearls from all over the world.
They say it's to break the curse.
But I eavesdropped.
It's not just that.
It's said that this Lingxiao Pearl
hides secrets about the universe.
Whoever gets it
can control the whole world.
Crazy.
You're all crazy.
You guys are smart, though.
You knew to lure people to Fucheng.
But you overlooked
how well Bai Lingling knows you.
From the moment Director Zhu left the provincial capital
to look for you in Nanyun,
he was targeted by our people.
As soon as you arrived in Jinghong,
the organization sent me.
Bro,
I'm not the main culprit behind all this.
Give me the Lingxiao Pearl,
and I'll take you to the organization
to get revenge on the boss.
Bro.
Should I give you a hand,
or will you die on your own?
For the sake of our past friendship,
I'll give you a hand.
The world is so beautiful.
Bro.
For the sake of our friendship,
I'll let you enjoy the view for a while.
Bye-bye.
Fatty was right.
Evil knows no age.
I can't believe I didn't trust my brother,
and trusted you instead.