Grandpa
Grandpa, wake up, Grandpa.
You promised me.
Grandpa!
It was the Xieling Sect that harmed your family.
Take your revenge on the right person.
If you want revenge,
make sure you don't find the wrong people.
What Xieling Sect?
It's just a nice-sounding name.
Aren't you all just thieves?
So,
you're not going to let us go?
Who let us go thirty years ago?
Listen.
Look.
It's these hornets again.
Moving in an orderly way.
They must have been specially tamed.
Fatty,
come with me to help Senior Master.
Let's go.
Wait.
There are so many hornets.
Aren't you just going to your deaths?
Ding Dawei,
where is your insect lure?
Insect lure, insect lure...
I say, sister,
people keep pets for fun.
But you,
keeping a bunch of big bees
just to harm people for fun?
Perfect timing.
Saves me the trouble of dealing with you one by one.
She's blocking us and doesn't want us to pass.
Which means
the tomb of the Dian King
is right inside the Heavenly Gate behind these stairs.
I'll count to three,
and we'll charge forward together.
I'll cover the rear. One, two, three!
Go!
Senior Master!
Senior Master! Senior Master!
Lao Lu,
go up first and see if the Heavenly Gate can be opened.
Open, open, open...
Give me the insect lure.
Go up with your Teacher Lu.
Protect him well.
Okay, okay. Lao Lu!
Hurry!
Okay, okay. Let's go.
Shutong, take good care of Senior Master.
Senior Master, let me bandage you up.
Fatty, is your stamina up for this?
Cut the crap.
Teacher Lu,
there's no way here.
Go, go, go.
Go, hurry!
Hurry up!
Finally here.
Apprentice,
we can't be too gentle with this.
We have to learn from the big fatty.
I understand.
Be savage.
One, two, three, go!
Apprentice, how is it?
Are you okay? Did you hit your head?
A bit dizzy. Dizzy.
Fatty!
This thing can move.
A... a mechanism!
Little punk, trying this on me?
Huarong Dao.
What is it?
You don't even know Huarong Dao?
In the late Eastern Han Dynasty, the world was in chaos.
The empire, long divided, must unite; long united, divide.
The eight warlords...
Teacher Lu, Teacher Lu, you're getting off-topic.
This, this...
Right, right.
This thing,
it's just a puzzle game.
As long as we put these boards
together into the right pattern,
and this pattern
is the key to opening the door.
Not this again.
No.
It seems a bit different this time.
What could be different?
More and more hornets are gathering.
She's trying to
gather all the hornets in Guyu here.
If this goes on,
just the few of us
won't be able to hold them off.
It all depends on Lao Lu now.
I wonder if the Heavenly Gate can be opened.
This...
Quick, quick, get out of the way!
Don't get hit when the door opens!
Don't get hit!
Do you know this character?
Yes, it's Jing.
Brilliant, right?
Just wait.
Lao Lu is an intellectual.
He's fine with reading characters,
but asking him to open a mechanism
is just making things difficult for him.
Yeah.
Old Chen,
we still have to rely on you for this.
Lao Lu is unreliable.
What are you hesitating for?
We've got Senior Master covered.
Go quickly!
Okay.
Hurry up and go!
Staff Officer He, take Senior Master and go first.
I'll give her a little gift.
Be careful!
Lao Lu!
Brother!
Lao Lu, how is it?
We just found a couplet.
And then?
Mr. Lu figured out it's the character Jing.
But the door just won't open!
Why must scholars make things hard for scholars?
My talents are unappreciated!
Lao Lu!
Heavens.
Your idea isn't wrong.
Did you miss something?
I didn't miss anything!
Look.
Two shapes in one body.
One two, two twos.
Four branches and eight heads.
Isn't this just a Jing?
Then flying spring flows upward.
Water comes out of the well to drink.
What's that up there?
Which one?
Head resides in one room.
What does that mean?
Why should I care what it means?
I've already pieced together the Jing.
Let it reside in however many rooms it wants! This...
It...
Old Chen,
I might really be wrong.
I missed a little dot.
What little dot?
In Large Seal Script,
the character Jing is
two horizontal and two vertical lines with a dot in the middle.
There's no dot!
How was I supposed to know?
That's why I say they're hooligans!
They didn't give a dot!
Leg!
Have you opened it yet?
Sister!
Go, quickly!
Find the dot! Find the dot!
Hurry and find the dot!
It's open!
The giant hornets are coming! Hurry!
It's open! It's open!
Come on, let's go!
Hurry! Quick, quick!
Hurry! They're catching up!
Hurry up, Fatty!
Hurry, let's go!
Senior Master, let me!
Remember.
Senior Master!
If you get trapped in a maze,
try looking to the sky.
Senior Master!
Chen Youxi!
This is as far as I can go with you.
You must find the Lingxiao Pearl.
Being able to join you on this journey,
I can die without regrets.