Dark Glory
You damn girl
If you want to drop out of school, just do it!
Are you not wrong? Not at all?
Things have come to this point
It means you have problems too, damn it!
Come to me right now and rewrite the reason for dropping out!
(Park Yeon-jin)
Yeonjin
I said
The roof of the abandoned building
Do you remember?
That's when you lost your name tag
Do you remember? Yeonjin
What the fuck are you doing?
Go away
I told you to go away!
However
What are you doing here?
The dead can't be here
No wonder I smelled foul odor
You're covered in burns
The head is still broken like that
The dead can't be here
What do you want to do by mixing among the living?
Mom!
Here
This woman
This woman here
This... this woman
Mom
‎Punishment This is a punishment from the gods!
Dark Glory
Your husband is dead.
Is this it?
Your plan with Wen Dongen
Just to involve my mother
Let her kill your husband?
You're a murderer, you bitch
No wonder
You didn't react when I told you I'd help you kill him
I want you to reconcile with my mother immediately
Do you think I can't find your daughter?
First
I have something to return to your wife.
You bitch!
Why do you threaten my child at every turn?
Aren't you a mother too?
I am here
There are many photos of you
So
Don't mess with me
If you come to me again
No matter what it is, I will pay you back double
Just like today
You bitch
Husband
Wow thank you very much
If you need anything else
Please call me anytime
Are you working for Deputy Superintendent Shin?
He will be going abroad soon
He sold the hotel owned by his sister.
Okay, follow me.
How come you are here?
Who are they?
You have two choices
This is the address of the victim's family.
Although you have forgotten them
Not forgotten yet
You either apologize or take responsibility for your crime
Or end our relationship now.
You have to choose carefully
I will too
Why should I go looking for them?
I didn't kill her
She was just crazy and accidentally stepped on air.
So you are there
At the accident scene
(2911 Seonghan-ro, Jongno-gu)
“We”?
From the moment you met Wen Dongen
There is no "we" anymore
Oh, I see.
Then take care
My choice is this
Lawyer Cui is me
‎(After Park Yeon-jin's school violence scandal
My husband is also going to leave her?)
(Park Yeon-jin's 10-year marriage ends)
(The daughter-in-law of a chaebol family divorces)
(Ha Do-young files for divorce)
Is he the president of Zaiping Construction?
(Search:Park Yeon-jin)
"But Zaiping Construction officials said
As for the recent revelations
Park Yeon-jin is suspected of school violence
Whether it constitutes the main grounds for divorce
The company cannot confirm
And I will not make any statement on this in the future.”
So Ha Do Young is single now?
Cough is really annoying
Dean, what's bothering you?
Oh damn
Didn't you say that he would lose his parental rights?
I know you are familiar with the lawyer of Zaiping Construction.
Go ask him right away.
What are the conditions for divorce?
Why the hell are they getting divorced?
Do you think Jae-joon still loves Yeon-jin?
They won't get back together?
Jaejun said
He would ejaculate very quickly for no apparent reason when he had sex with me
Doesn't this mean that he loves me too?
That's premature ejaculation, go away, idiot
I just wanted to come by and give you money for your clothes.
Are you going to Sun Mingwu's funeral?
How much gift money should I give?
Damn it, I can't stand it
Hello!
Is this the Financial Supervisory Commission?
Don't keep asking me about the gift money.
Yes
It's obvious that Sun Mingwu is gone
He is not the dumbest
You are the stupidest
Hey Sarah Lee!
Do you think saying "fuck" or "fuck" is considered cursing?
No
Insults are also insults
If it wasn't Wen Dongen, it would have to be you
You are the cheapest toy
I was actually going to pay for your clothes.
Don't regret it
No
You must regret it, you poisonous insect
Get lost you idiot
Although we didn't go to the Philippines to eat mangoes
But we still
Arrived at sea
I wore the clothes you picked for me last time
How?
Is it suitable for me?
Don't worry about Shan Ya
Don't forgive me either
I hope you are in the cold sea water
Slowly decaying
Husband
Ms. Jiang Xiannan?
Are you a relative of Lee Seok-jae?
I am the driver's lawyer
She came here in person to reconcile with you.
I don't intend to reconcile
I won't reconcile
Don't be like this.
She also had an accident on a rainy day.
Madam
Oh my god, you must be so flustered.
I know I don't have the face to come and see you
But
I have a daughter and a granddaughter
Please don't be so determined.
Maybe we can calm down and talk about the amount.
I won't reconcile
Please do not contact me
You also know that I am in mourning
Wait, Ms.
What to do? She seems very determined
You ask me how I know?
Do you want me to go to jail?
You want me to go to jail?
That woman
Not ordinary
She can actually laugh even though she is in mourning
Still wearing a floral dress
Settlement Fund
Give her double
Get out of the way
I want to drive in
Hello
I am Wen Dongen, you should have forgotten
Who?
Then I will introduce myself like this
I know you murdered Lee Seok-jae
Did Shin Young-joon send you here?
No
I came here by myself
Since 2004, we have come step by step
Wen Dongen?
Write your name there
Then fill in the reason for dropping out again.
You wouldn't be...
Yes
You seem to remember it, so I'll get to the point.
I don't care if you killed Lee Seok-jae
What I care about is
Park Yeon-jin killed So-hee
And what Shin Young-joon helped her deal with afterwards
What?
You have Yeonjin's brand name, right?
I know you left that with the wizard.
You just need to give me the evidence.
How do you say?
Are you willing to sell out Yeon-jin to save yourself?
This is my number
You either become a murderer.
Or hand over the brand
End this with manslaughter
This should be an easy decision for you.
But you can pretend to be upset
Pretend you need to think
Just like you have motherly love
Once you've made up your mind, call me.
"For the second week in a row, the weather station
Issued a nationwide cold wave warning
The temperature this morning continued to hover around -10 degrees Celsius.
It's minus 10 degrees outside but you're so hot, senior
What? Divorce?
Don't you have internet at home?
You just saw yesterday's news now?
It's not news, it's a video
Newly uploaded bullying video
Are you deaf like your mother?
I told you to take it off, don't talk back to me
I will definitely kill her
Yeonjin is angry
Damn it, put it away!
Sorry
She slipped away
Did I tell you?
I won't die alone
Have a nice day
You bitch
(Revealing Park Yeon-jin's bullying video)
In the previous explosive article
It also mentioned that someone was bullied to death by her, right?
Aren't all the above written facts?
Park Yeon-jin!
What's wrong with you?
How come you always get involved in scandals like this?
What is going on with school violence and murder?
Are they all facts?
Every day really
Too hard
Really Director
(Resignation letter Park Yeon-jin)
Bullying is a fact
But I didn't kill anyone
Your beautiful walls are gone.
You finally stand in the ruins Park Yeonjin
It will be desolate
Pitch black
Welcome, Yanzhen
Take this out.
Don't let Ye-ryul go online
Good Lady
My baby
Mom and Dad had a little quarrel
There are other things to deal with besides that mother
I've already seen them all
Did you bully your classmates?
Did you put anything hot on them?
Seung-ah said she was afraid of me
She asked me if I would bully her like you did
No, ...
Mom can go and tell Shengya's mom
You go out too.
I don’t want to be a weather anchor when I grow up
I'm not proud of you anymore
I admit
When I was still young, I used to commit school violence.
But
I didn't kill anyone
Actually, I am a victim
For several years I have been harassed by the family of the deceased
Because they lost their child
I have to endure everything
But I just
Unilateral claims against the family of the deceased
and malicious comments
Submitted a lawsuit
Me and the Dead
Once a friend
So I didn’t want to reveal this.
However
She was actually pregnant at the time.
Pregnant?
Is it true?
Can you prove it?
This is what the case investigation report says
You can go and confirm
She was pregnant at the time
Choose suicide
But at least I want to protect the reputation of the deceased
So I never said
I'm sorry I have to reveal the truth now
That's how it is
I have to go to another friend's funeral today.
You follow her and I'll take a look at the investigation report.
If what she said is true, she must be wronged
Are you sure? I know.
Park Yeon-jin just said at the press conference
She is going to Sun Mingwu's funeral
Go check where the funeral is held.
What about Guokesou? No news yet?
They said the results will be out the day after tomorrow, so I'll ask again.
Why is the atmosphere like this?
Did you have a fight?
How can someone like me argue with her?
I'm just a cheap toy
You have a big tongue
I don't understand half of what you're saying.
You say "fourteen" and see
"Fourteen"
After you uploaded Yeonjin's bullying video
She held a press conference to refute
So you're in a bad mood?
However
You will find that this moment is like heaven
What are you talking about?
(The dog sent a new video)
The dead sent me a message
It's Sun Mingwu
Why are you talking nonsense?
What is this?
Season 2?
Sarah, isn't this you?
That's not me
What is this? Who sent it?
It can't be a dead person, so who sent it?
And you said it wasn't you
Look at the eyes, it's definitely you
Your lifeless eyes
Why did you choose a word that is difficult to pronounce?
I told you that it wasn't me, why are you still happy?
Turn it off you bitch
LOL
You all laughed when I was being pranked
Why are you so serious when your own affairs are exposed?
Hello
This is you
Who is this guy?
Hey
Hey Sarah Lee
What the hell did you just say?
Oh, yes.
You probably don't remember your dog look.
You crawled on the ground very well that day
- Look here carefully
-It's Sun Mingwu
You slept with Sun Mingwu?
-Wow that bastard
- Stop filming
It turns out that it wasn't just your drugs that he embezzled
-That's not me!
- Look here damn
Who is it?
Who sent it?
You slept with him yourself.
Why did you throw my phone?
Damn
Sarah Lee
I have something to tell you
It can't be you, can it?
What are you talking about?
Come out for a moment
You uploaded my video
We need to talk
It's you
How?
You want to use me to cover up your video again?
Hey are you crazy?
Are you high?
Let go!
I usually act like I'm great.
Look at you two, each of you is revealing your friend's video
Another person tried to cover up the video
To disclose the pregnancy of a dead person
You guys are so noble.
What did you say she disclosed?
It's you
Where are you going, you bitch
What's wrong with me going to your church?
I will play that video in the church lobby
Stay tuned
Your fate is to be killed by the video
I said I'll pay for your clothes
You should have accepted it at that time
You are really...
Satan is the one who rejoices in the suffering of others
A woman like you who enjoys other people's pain
You have to stand trial
Get out of the way, police!
Can't take it out now
Let go of the damn thing!
Do you like my clothes?
Wear it as a shroud
Damn
(Sun Mingwu: male, 37 years old)
(Zhou Ruzheng, Director of Zhou Ruzheng Plastic Surgery Hospital)
I've been giving this to you for a while.
Why are you here now?
You're not here to get a diagnosis certificate, are you?
You weren't seriously injured.
Oh, right.
How is your friend?
Look, you know everything.
You and Wen Dongen are indeed in the same group
Huiting, you don't have to worry about her going to a big hospital in Seoul.
What is your relationship with Wen Dongen?
Go to bed?
Looks like you need to be careful
I'm used to my new car.
So today I might really kill you
As expected, he is a child of a wealthy family.
You really don't know etiquette
Anyway
You are the son of the director of Zhou Hospital, right?
I heard that Yoon So Hee is there
She's been there for a long time
So what?
Can you show me Suxi?
Is the body refrigerated?
So
Do you want an autopsy or something?
What do you think as a doctor?
Autopsy
Can the contents of the stomach also be checked?
So Yoon So Hee
I was pregnant at the time
I don't know much about forensic medicine
And it depends on Yoon So-hee
You are going with her family, not me.
If you want to do injection beauty or treatment
Just make an appointment when you go out
I have to leave town tomorrow
So today's appointments are very full
Wow you almost convinced me to make an appointment when I went out
I don't need
Dean Zhou
Mr. Quan left without paying
It doesn't matter
Before he left, he gave me exactly what I needed.
Go get busy
(When steroid eye drops are instilled
Have experienced symptoms of sudden increase in intraocular pressure)
(Glaucoma monitoring required)
We made a mistake. It's not Sun Mingwu.
It turns out to be Jeon Jae-joon
The bastard you mentioned deserved to die
I didn't notice
I didn't notice that
It really shouldn't be
It turns out that he doesn't just play basketball
What time is it now?
Didn't you ask me to come over quickly?
You said it was urgent
Mom
She is a member of our club
She likes the dumplings sold in the club restaurant.
I was just about to call you
Have you read the news?
I had a little argument with Ye-ryul's dad
It's a bit impulsive to decide to divorce just because of this, right?
"Ye-ryul's dad"?
Oh my god, why did you pick up the putter?
This is the most painful thing.
Don't bother with it,
Who is it? Which bastard?
The Federation of Trade Unions told me
Art Rate
Not Doyoung's child
Are you crazy?
Oh my god, I forgot to tell you
That bastard is me
Ye-ryul is my child
What?
So
Let your son raise my daughter
That's a little weird, isn't it?
So I want to ask
Can you please take my daughter
Removed from your household registration?
You crazy
You bastards
I won't let you go
How dare you lie to my son?
Yoon So Hee?
Yes
I want to pay for the storage of the body from 2004 to now
Oh, I see.
How can I say it? You are a step late.
Someone paid the fee not long ago.
Who paid?
Ha Daoying, President of Zaiping Construction
Thank you
Maybe this is the moment he was waiting for.
Dean Zhou believed that this moment would come.
Are you going on a business trip?
Wait a minute
(Mom)
I will remit your severance pay and salary to you.
Thank you for your hard work during this period.
Three, Four, Five
Ha Ye-ryul
Art Rate
Oh my god he's not...
What is my princess doing?
Dad
Dad, I'm sorry.
No, you have nothing to be sorry about.
These things happening now
None of it is your fault
Do you understand?
Dad
I have something to ask of you
Please give this to Sung Hee
Give this to the school doctor.
Messages that need to be conveyed
I wrote it on the note in the bag
So this is
My last mission?
Yes
Thank you for this time
Now
You can live in the world you want.
There
You don't have to be my helper
You can be yourself
Be your cheerful self
Are there eggs in that bag?
Stop crying
I want to leave with a smile
When you were a kid
What kind of child is it?
I am sometimes curious
Such a beautiful person when smiling
Really?
What was I like as a child?
I don't remember
Wish you
Mrs. Everything Goes Wish
Good
Let's not meet again
Jinglan
Yeah
-Have you had any water?
-Yeah
It's so hot
Let's go there after school today.
- Let's order fried skewers too
-Okay
The karaoke room there is nice, right?
(No laundry)
You can't wash your clothes here
Are you a part-time worker?
Very diligent and good
She is the boss of the real estate agency across the street.
Her son died not long ago.
So she is not in a good mental state now.
Killed by a drunk driver
Let her wash it.
Welcome
She said you were her savior.
The scar on the neck needs further observation
As for the voice?
Let's observe again
What is the use of light observation?
So
Can she speak?
Her vocal cord muscles were severely damaged.
So the vocal cords cannot contract or relax.
It seems unlikely that we can talk at this moment.
But sometimes there is a possibility of recovery
(How many possibilities are there?)
How many possibilities are there?
After all, miracles do exist.
Ms. Cui, you can't use your voice like that.
Oh my god
If you have to rely on miracles, then...
Anyway, I'll pack your stuff and send it to you.
Our Huiting is always strong, so I feel relieved.
If you need anything special, just tell me.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot you can't talk
(You can't do this to me)
The doctor said you can't use your voice
You mean
I can't do this to you?
Why?
Ah
What about the recording?
I deleted that one.
You said the password is 696969
(You bastard)
I know I'm an asshole
You are really a doctor who told you not to talk.
Let me give you a menthol cigarette.
That throat clearing effect is super good
(I'm going to kill you! I'm going to kill you!)
Sarah Lee due to special damage
and attempted murder will be tried
Her father, Pastor Li Jicheng
Also arrested by the police on suspicion of tax evasion
Li Jicheng has embezzled over the past 20 years
Total donations and secret funds
It is expected to exceed tens of billions
I saw the news
It seems that the end is not far away
Congratulations on creating ruins!
Even though I was the one who set up the trap
But the ruins were created by themselves.
And you are the one who makes this 100% successful.
You made this plan perfect.
Turn around and don't look
You just need to look at the good-looking things. This is not good-looking.
No, I have to see
This is the executioner's sword dance you performed for me
I'm coming too
Senior
Under the fingernails of Sun Mingwu
The DNA test results are out
But it's weird
What's weird?
I said 18 years ago
In the case of Yoon So-hee
Lighter found at the crime scene
The DNA detected on it
The DNA detected from Sun Mingwu's fingernails is consistent
What is happening?
Go collect all the information related to the Yin Suxi case.
Bring all the DNA samples here
Good
My special thanks goes to Zhou Ruzheng
I will be home late today
I have to go out of town to go somewhere
Where to go?
To Dr. Zhou Ruzheng
A bit far
See you later tonight
Hello, Dr. Zhou
I am Jiang Yongtian
I can't understand the sadness of losing a family member.
But I want to write a few words with apology
Although our meeting was short
But I remember your father was a good man.
He puts murderers like me
Also treated me as a patient and treated me wholeheartedly
3724 Meeting
We meet again
I want to hear the answer I didn't hear last time
You said you'd show me your hell when we met again
During the trial
You didn't tell me the reason.
Tell me about it
Is this your hell?
It’s not enough
Why you
Killed my father?
Everyone refused to operate on me.
My arm is broken and it hurts like hell
Blood is flowing
They said I was a murderer
So I don't even want to touch me
Then your father came in.
You guys come out first, everyone come out.
I'll do it
Give him an IV and do a CT scan
Please remove the handcuffs. I can't save you.
Dean
Please don't do it. Send him to another hospital.
What should they do? What should the doctors there do?
It is the court's job to question the guilt
We have to hand him over alive to the court
Someone give Ruzheng a call?
We agreed to have dinner together
He should be on his way
Let him go home directly
Tell him not to eat instant noodles
I don't know why he likes instant noodles so much.
I'm dying here
He is actually worried about you eating instant noodles
Isn't this insulting from my perspective?
Hmm?
After the operation begins
I woke up from the anesthesia.
I found that one hand could move
And the scalpel is right next to me
Do you know who I wanted to see?
Yes
The Dean's son who likes instant noodles
That's why I do that.
You will come when your father dies
So I used a scalpel to cut it
To make you
Running to see me so I snapped
I want to carry on my late father's legacy
Serve this society
My father used to say
Since the medical profession is our mission
We should take serving the society as our purpose
Whether it is "cultivating legal order"
Or "Reshaping Hope and Tomorrow"
I think it all starts with a healthy body.
I appreciate your philosophy, Dr. Zhou
But I can't hire the victims' families.
The bottom line
It was you who killed your father, not me.
Come in
Mom
Huh?
Wow who are you?
My mother has lost a lot of weight
I'm a vegetarian just to wear a bikini, but it's too bad
They say surfing suits are in fashion now
The chance to find you a new European dad is gone.
Where in Europe? New dad in Italy?
Did you cry?
Why am I crying? What's there to cry about?
I'm hungry, please treat me to a meal
I asked Zhong Xian which restaurants were good.
Don't move here.
Go get a haircut.
I made you so handsome
Why are you wasting your face like this?
I'm going to grow it longer and braid it
Mr. He is on annual leave
I know
Didn't you and I talk on the phone?
So I know
I know all
But I have no other place to go except here
You don't know?
Your lost name tag
I handed it over to the police station.
I didn't make good use of that brand at that time
But I'm going to make good use of it today.
(Park Yeon-jin)
This was given to me by Director Shin secretly from the police station.
I have kept it here.
Is that ok now?
No
Starting now
Mom
You
How come you are here?
Did you call her?
Yeonjin also needs to know
Your mother betrayed you to save herself
You said
Family members are the biggest perpetrators
You bitch
This is for you, Yeon-jin.
This belongs here
But you know what?
This brand name has no evidentiary value
Because this is not the crime scene.
But it is obtained after a period of time.
From the beginning
I don't need your mother's testimony
I'm just curious
How far will Park Yeon-jin be abandoned?
Now I know the answer
You and I both know it
Mom
What did you do?
How could you do this?
How could you do this to your daughter?
Otherwise, we'll both die?
Things got like this because
You can't even handle someone like her.
That's good.
Go and get along well with your daughter.
I have already failed
Mom
I know some people who have tried to save their own children.
And the mothers who choose hell for themselves
Crazy Woman
How can you do this at someone else's funeral?
Damn
(Demian)
(Lai Mei'an)
So
Don't be at ease and think that this is the end
Don't think you've been punished enough.
After all, funerals are
Only Sun Mingwu
(Sung Hee)
Hmm Sung Hee
Sister, I fainted in Shenghandong.
Did she faint?
Oh my god
Kim Ji-nyeo's Guardian
Here we come
What is your relationship?
I am her acquaintance
She has no family
Sorry, please wait.
What is this?
The remarks column says
Dr. Zhou Ruzheng is her guardian
He should be having dinner with the dean now.
Hello, it's me
What does the note you wrote on the information sheet mean?
When did you come?
Guardian of Suxi's mother
It's you
I asked them
They said that the note
It was written before we met on the train.
Did you know this all along?
Did you know
Did I approach you on purpose?