Dark Glory
71-1, Seonghan-dong, Jongno-gu
An unidentified body was found
I'll say it again
Need to rush to the scene
The first team is on its way
The number you dialed is not available. Please confirm...
Where is it?
Your key to Hawaii
I clearly put it here with my own hands...
Wait a minute
The number you dialed is unavailable...
Damn it!
(Cui Huiting)
What's up?
I just received a call from Aunt Sun Mingwu
She said Sun Mingwu is dead
His body was found last night.
You have a really wide social circle.
Are you still in touch with his aunt?
Shouldn't I keep in touch with you?
Hey
What you said before makes sense
Can friendship alone make us friends?
You have no idea how well I know you
You
It's over, Yeonjin
Thank you for letting me know
I just lost two friends.
Dark Glory
Are you really going to sell the hotel?
Why sell it when the business is going well?
Sell it
It's okay to sell it at a low price
You should go find a real estate agent tomorrow.
Then give me a call
Come on, where have you been?
Have you had lunch?
I saw that the room was almost full last night.
We went to eat instant noodles
Really? Why do you guys always eat instant noodles?
Come and order some soup later
Give
Wow boss you are the best
Are you still working for Yeon-jin?
Yes, you can earn some pocket money
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
Don't pick up minors
It's Big Brother, walk slowly
Good
How often do you drink?
What kind of wine are you drinking?
I never drink alcohol. I can't even drink a glass of wine.
Just ask my daughter.
My daughter is a teacher. She is a teacher.
You were diagnosed with alcohol dependence six years ago
You mean
Have you not had a drink since?
Well, at that time
Just had a drink
Actually, it's not even one cup, just half a cup.
I didn't drink the whole half cup at once.
How much do you usually drink each time?
How many bottles?
I said I don't drink!
What do you, a rookie doctor, know?
I wonder why you brought me here.
You damn girl
‎You two have colluded, right?
‎(Persecutory Paranoia)
‎Why did you set the fire?
What fire are you setting?
The floor is just a little bit burnt.
That was done accidentally.
I just wanted to teach her a lesson.
‎(Intermittent Explosive Disorder)
‎These days, every home has a fire extinguisher
We put out the fire quickly.
‎(Alcohol Use Disorder)
Everything is so convenient now
You can leave after the consultation.
Can we go now?
Really?
(Hospitalization consent form)
(Proof of kinship)
Good information, that's it.
Please come this way
Let go
Get out of here, you bastards
Dong En and his people want to take me away
Say something quick!
Only I can do this, mom
Because
I am
Your only relative
I may not be able to come often
You dead girl
Are you still human?
How could you do this to your mother?
You are more vicious than a poisonous snake.
Let go, you bastards!
Choose this floor
Let me take a look at the wallpaper
What is your relationship?
You and Teacher Wen
Scare me Hello
I clearly made some movement
Have you finished picking?
Not yet
Mid-Century Modern Style in All White
and Bauhaus-style gray
I don't know which one to choose
Oh my monthly rent is good.
Which one is more expensive? Choose the more expensive one
Good
The tenant has only been here for a short time? Has he already moved out?
No
The house is on fire
So the room that caught fire yesterday was yours?
Oh my god, why is there a fire?
Is the tenant willing to pay compensation?
No compensation required
I didn't say anything
The tenant of that room
My lifesaver
What? Really?
Is it her?
Ms. Sarah Li, your father, Pastor Li Jicheng
Is the suspicion of tax evasion regarding the art exhibition true?
He is also suspected of using the name of believers
Buying exhibition works at high prices to avoid gift tax
Have you ever reflected on your drug use?
Miss Sarah Lee, please say something.
Have a drink
Tomatoes help detoxification
Where is Park Yeon-jin?
What happened to that bitch?
You greeted your friend as soon as you saw your mother?
Can't you see that I've lost weight worrying about you?
When should I go to the police station again?
They will probably contact you next week.
You just need to go there when the time comes.
If you actively cooperate with the investigation
Can reduce the sentence
So you better go
Damn! So annoying!
Where's my cell phone? Have you found it?
The one from before?
All in your previous room
What do you want that for?
There are my precious memories in it
A bitch's face
Let's go there
-Where?
-It was delicious last time.
Oh, there? Okay.
I'm so hungry
Rely on couple outfits
Oops, Park Yeon-jin, you must be embarrassed.
Wow, it looks like you two are besties.
This moment needs to be recorded
Shut up, both of you.
Hey!
Take off
-What?
-Are you deaf like your mother?
I told you to take it off, don't talk back to me
Look, she's scared.
Sorry Yeonjin
This set is not real
It's a fake
- She said it was a fake
-I'm really sorry
Oh, she slipped away
Super fast
I will kill that bitch
Yeonjin is angry
Damn it, put it away!
‎(My daughter is a victim of school violence)
‎(They use hair straighteners, cigarette butts, etc.
Brand her)
‎(One of the perpetrators
Is a weather anchor of a radio station)
There is a sentence in the article that broke the news online:
"My daughter who went to cram school
Fell to death from the roof of an abandoned building"
Do you think this is true?
It depends on which way you want to go.
The road to the truth or the road in the opposite direction
Why did you quit your job at school?
Is that also because of Yeonjin?
Not exactly
Anyway
I can't be a good teacher.
This is the address you want
The deceased's family lives there alone
It's her mother
The deceased's name is Yin Suxi
Heard
The body is still in the morgue
Which hospital?
Are you going to remove the body?
If not
So you wanna help me?
In Seoul Chow Hospital
This is the information of the person you asked me to check last time.
The information is inside
Seoul Zhou Hospital is owned by their family
- Really?
-Yes
(10th anniversary, the family of three became colleagues in the hospital)
Why do you protect Yilu?
To make Yeon-jin suffer
Art rate should be the fastest and most effective way
But the path of Yilu
It will also make you suffer.
After this revenge is over
Will you become happy?
I hope so.
Can become happy to death
That's enough
I just hope to be happy to that extent.
Damn you, you're so rude.
(To Ha Do-young: Let's meet)
We have to meet
I have something important to say
Did you get a call from Whiting?
She said Sun Mingwu
Dead
Oh
You should know that you live together.
I heard
I guess the police, apart from his family,
The first person you should contact is you
You are his employer after all.
What do the police say?
Cause of death etc.
Did they tell you?
It is said
They told me
Where was Sun Mingwu's body found?
Where was it found?
The abandoned building
The place where Yoon So-hee fell
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, Yeonjin.
I threw away that clothing.
Okay
Really?
Thank you so much, Yeonjin
You should thank me, what else?
I will never appear in front of you again
That's as it should be. What else?
I just knew it
-You are just trying to fool me
-No
I'm really sorry, Yeonjin.
Is that so?
Then it's not too late to take off your clothes.
But the problem is
I recently bought a very expensive ear file
Is it you? The last person Mingwu saw?
And in the afternoon
Did that bastard really record it that day?
Oh, this is it.
What Choi Hui-jung Knows
What is the content?
A bit shocked
Damn Yeonjin!
So what are you going to do?
I am Ye-sol's mother
Your daughter Ye-sol's mother
Now that you know what to do?
You have to save me
You have to save me and Ye-ryul
You are the only one we can rely on.
You need to tell me clearly
What did you do to Sun Mingwu?
That was an accident
I obviously handled it afterwards.
I don't know why it became like this.
This is definitely
Wen Dongen did it
There is a doctor helping her
He is the son of the director of Seoul Zhou Hospital
Whose body is there?
Zhou Hospital?
I'm in big trouble now
I'll take Ye-ryul to your place.
We will come back to you, Jaejun, okay?
We can't let Ye-sol become the daughter of a murderer, right?
So I said
I was with you that day
Right?
So
Then we must have watched a pornographic movie again
Right?
Ji Hyun
-What about Yi-ryul?
-That
Your friend is here
Wow, you draw really well.
Do you want to be my apprentice?
Ye-ryul Do you like the feeling of floating?
Come with me
Hey, why are you so excited?
I mean "beautiful"
Yi-lu, we agreed on this, right?
Goodbye
You crazy bitch
Fuck
Others will think you are a good mother.
It seems you have hired a lot of lawyers.
How come it came out so quickly?
Look, you did it.
I said that because I care about you. You should be careful.
You are no longer a first-time offender.
Look, I know it's you
Report on my exhibition
Written by that idiot who praised you so much before
Dowon Daily reporter Kang Hyung-jin
What nonsense are you talking about?
There is no logic at all
The day your school violence was exposed
An ordinary person was live-broadcasted taking drugs
Does this make sense?
You actually exposed me to cover up your own scandal
It was you who exposed the tax evasion, right?
Thank you for letting me know
I just lost two friends.
The real body is placed here
Why would I come here to lie to you?
That’s enough!
You'll handle it, right?
Hello
What are you looking at? What?
What are you looking at?
Seriously, I won't die alone, you bitch.
(News)
Where are you?
I'll wait for you outside
A far place
How far?
Do you want me to give you a ride?
You got the wrong person
I already have someone I like
Today's goal is 2 kilometers left.
I feel relieved when I see you. You go first and I'll run back.
Do you run like this often?
You take good care of your body
I said I already have someone I like
Maybe it's because you're a doctor.
No matter what you do, physical strength is the key to success
Who are you competing against?
I said you got the wrong person
I really have someone I like.
She is very beautiful
If you don't get in the car, I'll leave.
I know you won't leave
You're just talking
Hey, Dongen, Junior
Wait!
Owner of car No. 4225
Wen Dongen
Oh my god
This is too sudden
Why are you hugging me?
Because I miss you so much
Did you just miss me?
That was a long time ago.
You run over here like this
What's the point of me being vigilant alone?
Why are you wary of me?
Because you are a very considerate lunatic
Oh yeah
You knew me before
The landlady of Eden Apartment?
- Me?
-Yes
She said you were her savior.
It shouldn't be me
I don't have the spare time to save others
I don't live that kindly.
I can see that
Weird, right?
The "considerate" part has to go.
You are so strict.
See you later. I still have 1 kilometer left.
You mean
After a person has been missing for a period of time
When he was found, he was already a corpse.
You can answer with "yes or no"
Would an autopsy be performed in this case?
If there is no evidence to prove the cause of death was suicide or accident
An autopsy is mandatory
Will it be done even if the family members object?
Even if three generations of the family are against it?
Even so
If the case is suspected of homicide
You can apply for a warrant to compel an autopsy
They will definitely do an autopsy, right?
It seems there is no way to stop this
Don't scare me.
You used to ask about tax evasion.
Why do you keep asking about criminal law recently?
Okay, I'll cut off contact with my mother.
I'm leaving. I'll have a meeting.
Hey, where are you going?
Why did you break up with your mother?
Please sit down. This is a long story.
Would you like a drink too?
Just tell me the point.
Are you the type who would rather be spanked early?
This means you haven't been beaten.
Also
That was the first time I was beaten.
So I don't know how to fight back.
Key Points
Get straight to the point
You almost made me swear when you interrupted me
Okay then
Did you know
This is a very special place for Yeonjin, right?
Don't cross the line
October 19
Sun Mingwu recorded this with his cell phone
Take it and listen to it
Sun Mingwu You Know
You also looked for him
This is where that bastard was last seen
The last person to see him here was Yeonjin
That's what I meant
Oh, there is something more important.
I just discovered that today.
Originally here
It feels good to hold a bottle of expensive wine.
But the bottle just happened to be missing.
Could you please ask Yeon-jin where the bottle is now?
You can start like this
"Yeonjin's murder is very costly."
So you're saying
To me,
Yeonjin is a murderer
Don't talk nonsense
What do you want from me?
Do you want me to call the police?
You seem crazy
If I wanted to call the police, I would have done it long ago.
What we need to do is to be accomplices instead of calling the police
I won't give this to the police.
So you give up parental rights after the divorce.
That's it.
Neither you nor I want
Let the child's mother become a murderer?
No matter what Ye-Sul's last name is
You are
Are you using Yi-ra to threaten me?
A long time ago
I provided Yeon-jin with an alibi
What she said
The classmate who went to the rooftop with her died
But
October 19
Another person died while with her.
How do you want to solve this?
You're testifying for her this time?
Are you giving Yeon-jin an alibi?
Husband
What happened?
Get on the bus quickly or you'll be late
You go to Zhimin's house and I'll be there soon.
Call me when you arrive
(Hong Young-ae)
Hello?
Let's meet today
After all, we have been friends for 40 years.
We have to say goodbye face to face.
What time did you say?
(Park Yeon-jin)
Hello?
I'm calling because
What the lady of Pyeongchang-dong told me
I'll send you the address and we'll meet there.
Am I dreaming?
Dinner is almost ready. Just wait for the soup to boil.
It's damn Qingguo sauce every day
Aren't you tired of it?
Eat more yourself.
Oh, and that one
I may not be able to go home in the next few days
Don't call me, okay?
Where did you say you were?
Opposite?
Just come up a little bit and then come through.
-The bag is heavy, please hurry up.
- Go up there?
OK, I'll come right away.
Where are we going?
You have to at least tell me where to go.
Coming Soon
Where are we almost there?
You used to be very simple
Give you money and you will leave
But it seems I am your last customer
What are you talking about suddenly?
Can a suspended sentence be given for manslaughter?
And it would be more helpful if there were eyewitnesses, right?
How do you drive?
Damn
Is he dead?
Are you sure he's dead?
Damn
Hey this guy
You wouldn't be...
There was a car accident
I hit a person crossing the road
Please come quickly
Damn
Are you crazy?
Why did you call the police?
I didn't drink and drive
Also obeyed the speed limit
The visibility is poor because of the rain
You handle this matter. Obviously you are an eyewitness.
What?
You think I'm an idiot?
You teamed up with that bastard to threaten me.
Do you think I don't know?
What nonsense are you talking about?
What am I colluding with him for?
How would he know if you didn't tell him?
Who else besides you knows what happened so many years ago?
How should I know? It's not me!
Damn, I didn't expect you to be this crazy.
Stop talking nonsense
You can't get away
Whether it's you or not, you have to deal with it.
The evidence that proves we are accomplices
I haven't destroyed it yet
Yeonjin's brand
Fuck you
You're really fucking crazy
Ying Ai is more disadvantageous to you than mine
Are you turning yourself in as the murderer of your daughter?
I am a housewife
What can we do?
Get the evidence received by the police?
The evidence is still in the bag.
The whistleblower, the deceased, Yeon-jin, you or me
At least one of them will have his or her genes tested.
I'm really going crazy
Damn
What are you doing, crazy woman?
I want to take advantage of you before you run away.
I
No matter what, I will stick with you
So you have to deal with this
The two of us
Either die together or live together
It can only be this handsome
Light candles in the temple
Then kill the chicken and bleed it
Yes
However
Did she come with you?
Hmm?
Oh my god, I got scared.
We are closed today and it is so late
You go back
So you only work on the side today?
Is it because she is Yeon-jin's mother?
You agreed to her without hesitation.
Boom!
You
Who is it?
Wow
I didn't expect that I would be
Seeing you again in such an unexpected place
Why didn't you even turn on the light?
What are you doing in a place like this?
I think you're weirder
It seems you came here without knowing it clearly.
And this is the second time
I am the owner of this building
Impossible
I was just looking for the restroom
I was so scared that I couldn't find any other excuses.
(Closed and no entry or exit allowed)
Open the door
Because there are always outsiders coming in and out...
Today too
It seems this is all intentional
What did you do to me that day?
That day when I was doing sleep anesthesia
What did you do to me?
Treatment
Your jawline is definitely more defined.
You have become more beautiful
I don't know what she told you
But don't get involved before you understand the situation.
Did you know I also do skin care?
I can tell by the scars
What kind of pain did the perpetrator want to cause?
It's just a devil
You were just looking for something
Are you looking for this?
You take it.
I don't need anything more
You can open the door yourself
The chain is used to deceive you
Not really locked
I won't charge you for parking.
I think this should be your last luck
Drive carefully
Today's weather
It is easy to hit people crossing the road
(News)
(Mom)
I'm at the police station, come pick me up.
It rained so hard
That person suddenly rushed out of the road again
Alcohol test was done on site
The result is normal, you know that
That person crossed the road without any serious fault.
No criminal record, no hit-and-run
Isn't this the end?
Yes, we fully understand the situation.
The problem is that there are no surveillance cameras on site.
So we're on the phone with the family of the deceased.
The driver needs to wait.
Deputy Chief Inspector, you can go home now
Thank you for your hard work.
Don't worry too much
Manslaughter
The most important thing is to reach a settlement with the family of the deceased
You tell them nicely
Got it
Thank you, Deputy Chief of Police
Okay, let's contact each other later.
Thank you for your hard work
Goodbye
Because it rains
So I didn't see him
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to apologize to me
-No, I'm really sorry.
-Please calm down
We found Sun Mingwu's body
Have you heard?
No
Where was it found?
You don't look surprised
Have you met Park Yeon-jin?
Or
Do you think I'm suspicious?
I have read Sun Mingwu's email
He investigated Yoon So-hee's case
The person who gave him the information
It's you
Is it illegal to do so?
There are many people who are worse than me.
It's so sad
What is going on?
What happened between you?
I've told you everything.
Even though you don't believe me
Is everything you said true?
(Winter 2004)
Do you smoke?
On the list of evidence in the Suxi case
There was a lighter found at the scene
Lighter
Click to open
Won't it leave DNA or something like that?
Mom
Did you drive here?
I'm going to the wizard.
What are you going there for now?
What happened?
I feel more at ease going there
I think it's better to go there than to see a psychiatrist.
Do you have contact information for the deceased's family?
You don't have to worry about that.
I can do it myself
You said someone died, how can I just ignore it?
This is a great opportunity for journalists to attack us.
Park Yeon-jin
Mom told you before
Everyone makes mistakes anyway.
The solution to the problem is not behind
It is always in front
Someone died yesterday.
Today we are going to do what we are going to do today
What are you talking about?
If
That person has the original document
Then you have to make a decision quickly.
If he broke the news first
We will be hit hard here.
Please help me take a look
Which small town in the UK or Ireland is suitable for sending Yilu?
A guardian will go with her.
It's snowing heavily
Be careful
Hello Mr. He, you too
(Kim Jin-hoon: The interview date has been decided)
What about wizards?
A big shaman dance ceremony is about to take place
She's preparing for that
Hello?
I don't know whether I should report this to you.
Kang Hyun-nam's husband
I heard he died yesterday.
He was hit while crossing the road
Is this your husband?
Are you okay?
I'm fine
This person
It's my husband
Yeonjin
Long time no see
How are you doing?
Yeonjin
It's me, Suxi
The transfer student Suxi
Do you remember me?
What are you doing?
Do you want me to take this dress off?
Shall I take it off for you?
I want this clothes
Should I take it off for you?
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
Then it's not too late to take off your clothes.
Yeonjin, please
I didn't wear the same clothes as you this time.
I don't care what you wear
I'm talking to you guys
Why don't you listen to me when I speak nicely?
Are you wearing clothes or a fur ball?
One minute
It's the limit of my patience
I told you to take off your clothes
Stop this, please.
I'm not afraid of you now
You are nothing
What the fuck are you talking about?
Are you filming "Romantic Youth Time"?
I used to be afraid of your money
Think about it, you are pitiful enough
So I will forgive you
Because I am better than you
Wow
I suddenly became a pitiful
And he is not as good as you.
Damn, you're scolding me so much at once?
Is that so?
That
I am a poor person
Can I help you sort out the hair balls?
Didn't you say you are better than me?
So you have to dress appropriately.
What are you doing?
If you move
I will go to your school to see you tomorrow
You keep jumping around.
Help me
You go away
(Withdrawal Application Form)
Mom
Mom, what should I do now?
What should I do now? Mom
Really, what on earth do you want to do?
Why didn't you go to cram school today?
Mom, I seem to be in trouble.
We were playing on the roof and accidentally caught fire
There is a transfer student
She was jumping around and accidentally fell down.
It's true
I just met her for a while.
Mom
Mom, what should I do now?
Hmm?
Hello?
Hello? Mom
Wake up, Park Yeon-jin
First, stay away from that place
Uncle Shen will call you
Don't cry and answer the phone carefully
Were there any witnesses? Did anyone see it?
No
-It seems not
-You have to be sure
- Look around
-No, I'm sure there isn't
(Evidence)
They didn't seem to do a DNA test at the time.
The report said the lighter was used by the deceased.
Where are you going?
Guokesou, please sort those out first before you come back
‎Subtitle translation: Ren Ying