(Lee Jun Young)
(Lee Ju Myoung)
(Jeon Hye Jin, Jin Goo)
(Reborn Rookie)
What's this? Why are you coming out of there?
I moved in.
I got kicked out of my home, thanks to a certain someone.
I get that,
but why did you move here?
Aejeong-dong was the cheapest.
The air is nice, and the view is to die for.
And there's someone I'd like to kill here too.
Sweetheart, come and eat.
Okay, Grandma.
Hey, get out of the way.
- What? - I said, move!
Nice landing.
Let's try to get along,
my dear neighbour.
It's been a while, Mr. Hwang.
You should let me do things like this, ma'am.
- Seriously. - Why are you eating at my house?
I'm anaemic,
and I have malnutrition, which is rare these days.
- I'm all skin and bones. - Oh, you poor thing.
- Look at her. - Just come and sit.
Her mother brought seaweed soup too.
- Would you like to try some? - Oh, yes.
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
This is salty.
Did you scoop this up from the sea? Why is it so salty?
- That can't be right. - Unbelievable.
- Have some water. - To the chef of Hannam-dong?
No wonder you're so skinny. Goodness.
From now on, you'll eat with us.
This is to pay you back for the watch. So don't worry, okay?
With inflation these days, we're adding two more mouths to feed?
An office worker's salary only goes so far.
- Do you think money grows on trees? - Five hundred dollars a month.
I'll pay you for the meals, ma'am.
Please teach me how to cook too. I'd be honoured to be your student.
Looks like Grandma's got a side gig.
That's wonderful.
I'm not eating!
- Oh, my. - Adding two more mouths to feed...
What's with his temper? Why has he changed so much?
- Thank you for the food. - Go on, eat up.
- Oh, thank you so much, ma'am. - Sure.
What are you doing?
Thanks to someone, I had to sell my car,
and now I have to walk everywhere.
A responsible society is a beautiful thing, isn't it?
What? Are you trying to plant a bug in my car or something?
What are you talking about?
I know you moved here to dig something up,
but that's not going to work on me.
Don't waste your time. Move out as soon as you can.
What, are you the landlord or something?
Yes. I bought the place.
- When? - Just now.
Go check with the real estate agency,
then pack your bags and get out.
Hey, that's an abuse of your power. We have a lease agreement, you know?
Sue me if you have the money.
You have two weeks until the end of the month.
- Why that little... - Oh, right.
If you want to catch the subway, run.
Darn it.
It takes over an hour to get to work? Seriously...
Good morning!
Or not.
Ms. Kang Bang Geul, you don't seem to have any sense of urgency.
- And you're the last one to arrive. - You little...
I'll do better.
Where are you going?
I have to get to my desk now to clock in on time.
The Materials Team's offer for returns on defective products,
processing complaints for the Shipping and Customer Service,
collecting bid notices from construction firms...
and organising material inventory slips.
There's a long list of support tasks for other teams.
That's your internal work.
You have separate instructions from the Future Business Team.
You're a new team that isn't even fully furnished.
You have instructions already,
Team Leader Hwang Jun Hyeon?
Darn. This is all for show. I'm not strong at all.
- I've had a bad back for ages. - No whining.
(Choiseong Logistics)
Go!
All right.
(Hwang Jun Hyeon)
Manage the Jungil-dong construction site.
Hey, put your back into it. Come on. You hear me?
This is solid rock.
(Choiseong Construction, Jungil-dong Choiseong Town Site)
Hey, you ever handled a shovel before?
No, this is my first time.
But do you think this is deep enough to bury a person?
Manage the Choiseong Solution shareholders' meeting.
Please place them nicely.
- Excuse me, coming through. - Sure.
Gosh!
- Darn. - You should've been careful.
Gosh, I spent all day delivering packages.
And the next day, I woke up to calls from nightmare customers.
After getting an earful, I just apologised and grovelled.
Then I became a master of the copy machine.
You all know what they call us, right?
The Company-wide Task Resource Management Team.
Or the "Ex-Con Team" for short.
It makes you feel like you've committed a crime or something.
My heart pounds whenever I hear a siren.
Why is life so hard? Goodness.
I miss my wife and kids in Canada.
This is hard for you too, isn't it?
I'm sure this change of environment is tough on Ms. Jo too.
How about you just go back to the US?
I can arrange a place for you there...
No. It's not hard at all.
Oh, honestly.
What? What is it now?
Look.
Support work for the Financial Business Division.
Just thinking about that jerk gives me a surge of energy.
(Credit Union)
- How can I help you? - I'd like to withdraw some money.
This lip tint is a bestseller at Sephora.
Number six, Mauve Cherry.
Buy it, and with a quick swipe,
you'll earn cashback right away.
If you use this debit card, you earn cashback every time you buy coffee.
Can I help you apply for one?
Bang Geul will never give up.
Stop with the nonsense and pressure her more to quit immediately.
And keep Kang Jae Gyeong away from her.
This will just make things worse between the father and daughter.
She looks ready to tear him apart...
whenever she hears Hwang Jun Hyeon's name.
Any new developments with Professor Min Seok Do?
He resigned.
And there are rumours he'll be joining Choiseong Group.
He might as well be advertising that he's an accomplice.
Who are you?
Use this video to get some leverage on Kang Jae Gyeong.
She was the last person to visit the hospital room that day.
It's not proof that she killed me.
This isn't enough.
What about what I asked you to check?
They said the CCTV stopped recording due to a security check,
but the person in charge supposedly mixed up the inspection date.
The hospital didn't make a big deal out of it.
Jae Gyeong must have pulled some strings so they wouldn't.
Where is this guy now?
(Personnel Record Card: Ham Du Ho)
Good.
I have no clue.
He's been on sick leave and hasn't come to work for days.
He asks for a fortune, then disappears.
Find him fast. Before this gets out of hand.
Yes. We're looking into his home, family, and all his contacts.
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
I hear the department heads are complaining about being overworked.
Aren't you working them a little too hard, Team Leader Hwang?
Results are most crucial right after taking office.
Everyone needs to be on their toes.
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
Also, we heard from Taeha.
They want the Daesan Hydrogen Complex deal...
wrapped up by next week.
So they just want to take what's theirs?
Secretary Yeo, you can handle that.
(Chairman Kang Jae Gyeong)
Don't you worry about it, Team Leader Hwang.
Yes, Chairwoman.
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
(Personnel Record Card: Ham Du Ho)
(Lee Sang Jae)
I think Kang Jae Gyeong is trying to get to the security guard.
- We have to get to him first... - I've found him, Chairman.
Do you trust Hwang Jun Hyeon?
Trust him?
He only does things to stay in my good graces.
Kang Bang Geul moved in next door to me.
I think she's trying to find something out.
What do you want me to do?
I told you I was leaving the two of them to you.
Handle it.
As I promised, I'll make sure...
the two of them are sent to the US by the end of the month.
More importantly,
what's making that old man so confident?
Give Taeha a message.
If they don't deliver the money and shares by the end of the week,
they'll never get their hands on our core hydrogen technology.
Please.
Darn it.
(Financial Backer)
You have to light a fire under them before they open their wallets.
Secretary Yeo?
- Darn it! - Oh, dear.
I'm so sorry.
Do you think saying sorry fixes everything?
I'm sorry.
Unbelievable.
Let me pay for your dry cleaning and medical bills. Oh, what a mess.
What, you think money can solve everything?
Plus extra for your trouble.
Excuse me! One bowl of ramyeon over here,
and could you please clean this up?
- Thanks. - My apologies.
Well, then.
Eight, seven,
one, zero, one, two.
(Personnel Record Card)
(Financial Backer)
(Compose New Message)
At 10pm.
The parking lot under Sehwa Bridge.
I want 500,000 dollars.
(Okay)
What's the status?
We've agreed to pay him what he asked for,
so we should wait a little longer.
Still nothing from Taeha?
It seems like they're intentionally avoiding my calls.
And Secretary Jo is ignoring my calls altogether.
I wonder what Chairman Na is banking on.
It couldn't be that, could it?
What's he doing here?
(Financial Backer)
Na Byeong Mo, that scum.
- Anyone here? - No one, sir.
- Head to his house. - Yes, sir.
(Personnel Record Card, Address)
The security guard disappeared?
We were one step behind.
The place was a mess. Nothing to be found.
How could she team up with someone like Na Byeong Mo?
She knew full well how much you. hated him.
No.
No matter how I look at it, this doesn't add up.
Jae Gyeong has no reason to involve Na Byeong Mo...
in something that could be used against her.
Then...
Chairman Na is trying to blackmail Kang Jae Gyeong?
Na Byeong Mo knows.
That Jae Gyeong was the one who killed me.
He was trying to get the CCTV footage from the security guard.
If Chairman Na gets his hands on it,
he'll obviously use it to make a deal for Choiseong.
In that case, wouldn't it be better...
if Kang Jae Gyeong's people got the security guard?
So it's fine for Jae Gyeong to destroy the evidence of her crime?
There's only one thing left to do.
We have to hope this has the proof we need...
to prove that Jae Gyeong is the culprit.
(Suspicious Death of Former Chairman Kang Yong Ho)
(Anonymous Tip)
Hayoung Daily received a tip.
I've stopped them from running the story.
(Kang Yong Ho Died After Kang Jae Gyeong's Visit)
A tip?
That means we're not the only ones who suspect Kang Jae Gyeong.
It also means there's hospital CCTV footage...
from the day of Father's accident.
Proof that Kang Jae Gyeong is the real killer.
What about the source? Isn't the paper's president your best friend?
He said he doesn't know. It was an anonymous tip.
I feel like he's hiding something, though.
You're here, Madam Chairwoman!
(Choiseong C&T, President's Office)
You should have called me. I'm surprised the Chairwoman...
would trouble herself to come all this way.
You.
Did you meet with the president of Hayoung Daily?
Hayoung Daily...
You mean Jeong Hak Hui?
I haven't talked to him in a while. Why?
Don't play dumb.
Everyone knows you two are best friends.
Did he say anything to you?
About what? Did an article get published?
Don't tell me...
If you're plotting something with Kang Bang Geul behind my back,
you'll have to give up your position.
Don't jinx yourself by saying her name. You have big things to do.
You're getting a call.
Answer it. It seems important.
I was looking for you. You weren't in your office.
- About Daesan Hydrogen Complex... - We'll talk later, Mr. Hwang.
I guess they don't let the traitor in on the important stuff.
She took a call and stormed out with a foul look on her face.
- Was it about the tip? - What tip?
I thought you were Kang Jae Gyeong's favourite,
but you're totally out of the loop.
Tell me what you're talking about.
A newspaper got a tip that Kang Jae Gyeong...
is the one who killed my dad.
Kang Jae Gyeong's face was caught clear as day...
on the hospital CCTV that was supposedly broken.
See? You can't get away with murder.
- The truth always comes out. - It was Hayoung Daily, wasn't it?
Did you see the article through Kang Jae Seong?
What exactly was on the CCTV footage?
What picture of Kang Jae Gyeong?
You're not asking the most important question.
You must know who the informant is.
The proof that Kang Jae Gyeong killed my dad...
The informant has it, right?
Hey.
Stop running around playing amateur detective.
There's nothing you can do.
Why that little...
Jae Seong.
It looks like Hwang Jun Hyeon knows who the informant is, right?
Do you think it's someone we know?
(Choiseong C&T, President's Office)
(Entrance)
Look at this one. It's packed with roe.
It's a delicacy when you eat it whole.
You said you had something to say.
You're always in such a hurry.
(Daesan Hydrogen Complex and Tech Transfer Agreement)
The core technology of the Daesan Hydrogen Complex.
You'll transfer it without the final payment. Sign it.
(Daesan Hydrogen Complex and Tech Transfer Agreement)
I never agreed to a contract like this.
Or will you wash your hands of Choiseong altogether?
- And I'll graciously let you go. - Chairman Na!
How dare you raise your voice at me?
You're worse than an animal for killing your own father.
Place an ad for Taeha Energy in the Hayoung Daily.
President Jeong does a fine job.
Yes, Chairman.
Was it you?
- You framed me as the killer? - Frame you? Isn't that the truth?
I should've never gotten involved with scum like you.
At first,
she was going to drug Father with the sleeping pills...
she got from Professor Min so Father wouldn't wake up.
But then Father's eyes suddenly shot open,
so she just grabbed the pillow...
and just smothered him.
So, did he say he did everything I told him to?
Or...
that he only pretended to go along with it?
Your husband is my accomplice.
You want to see whose crime is worse?
A recording like that won't hold up as evidence.
Do you really think people will believe that?
You cremated your father as if you couldn't wait,
manipulated the board, and took over as Chairwoman.
Even your family suspects you.
Do you think the public will believe your side?
Don't slander me.
My father was definitely alive when I left.
Who are you?
Seriously.
You seem to have nine lives.
It wasn't me. I didn't kill him.
Don't tell me...
Did you kill my father?
You didn't care if your father dropped dead or was murdered,
but you finally look curious now.
Kang Yong Ho...
was murdered by his own daughter blinded by greed...
for the chairman's seat
I'm going to make that the truth.
What are you, the Almighty?
- How will you hide the truth? - You can't just hide the truth!
You have to eliminate it.
I heard that guy contacted you too.
He said he'd tell you what really happened that day for a hefty price.
He shouldn't have pushed his luck.
(Eunpo Sashimi House)
(Kang Jae Gyeong)
Yes, ma'am.
Where are you?
(The Late Kang Yong Ho)
Are you hiding something from me?
I came here after reading the tip sent by Secretary Yeo.
Is it really true?
Did you kill him?
Don't be so cocky.
- Your father. - I said, shut it!
If that's a weakness, we need to prepare for it.
Answer me.
It was Na Byeong Mo.
He's trying to frame me for it.
I got completely taken in by Chairman Na.
Chairman Na killed him?
Are you sure?
Unbelievable. The whole world suspects me.
Why would I kill my own father?
He was going to die soon anyway.
I already had Choiseong in my grasp. Why would I?
So you're truly innocent, right?
I am. Not in the slightest.
Then you should request a police investigation right now.
No.
If this blows up, I'll be at a disadvantage.
We just need to find proof...
that Chairman Na is the killer,
and then we can instantly turn the tables on him.
I'll drag Na Byeong Mo to the gutter...
and repay today's humiliation tenfold.
I have to protect Choiseong and get my revenge.
Isn't that the only way for my father to rest in peace?
Is that really what your father would've wanted?
Then what would he have wanted?
If he'd just passed quietly, none of this would've happened.
So selfish, right to the end.
I'm trying to avenge him and give him peace,
so what's the problem?
Should I be the one to find it for you?
The evidence that Na Byeong Mo killed your father.
He already destroyed the hospital's CCTV footage.
He killed the witness too.
If there's no evidence, then we'll create it.
I told you.
I'm with you all the way.
What happened between you and Na Byeong Mo...
Tell me everything.
- You're here, Father. - Yes.
- This way. - Okay.
Why is Chairman Na here?
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
The light in here is amazing. It makes you want it for yourself.
You still have to sign the Daesan Hydrogen Complex deal.
Final payment of 100 million dollars.
Settle it according to the contract, Chairman.
Please, I ask of you.
Should I have played the recording at the executive meeting?
A lot of people there still miss Kang Yong Ho.
I'm just kidding.
But...
it wasn't easy for me to get here either.
And I took some major losses along the way.
You'll have to compensate.
You have that secret stash of money, don't you?
Siren Capital Partners, I believe?
While I'm here, I suppose I'll have a look around Choiseong.
Don't mind me.
Just carry on with your work.
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
I've invited you all here today...
as it's a good chance for us to get acquainted.
In our future with Taeha Group,
there will be many more projects we can do together.
You'll give them the wrong idea.
(Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong)
I'm the one helping.
Having the title of chairwoman doesn't solve everything, does it?
And Choiseong has no adults.
President Hyeon.
The automated logistics and distribution system at Choiseong...
I hear it's running quite well.
(Hyeon Jin, President of Choiseong Distribution)
We're thinking of expanding into that area as well.
It'd be even better if we did it together.
Are you already in discussions with Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong?
Why don't we discuss it over a meal?
Taeha will be hosting today.
Chairman Na and his daughter...
even held a luncheon with the company presidents.
Looks like Na Eun Se is having the time of her life.
(Daesan Hydrogen Complex and Tech Transfer Agreement)
If I provoke him without cause,
he might leak the footage from the hospital room.
Try not to worry so much.
Leverage is only powerful as long as you hold on to it.
What?
I'm saying Na Byeong Mo won't play his card just yet.
So,
whatever happens, hold your ground.
It's better than stepping down,
not after all you did to get that position.
Hwang Jun Hyeon.
If you hand over the core technology without the final payment,
do you think the shareholders will just stand by?
A chairwoman who gets pushed around...
on her first deal since taking over.
What will the employees think of that?
This directly reflects on your capabilities as the Chairwoman.
Stop lecturing me and give me a solution.
So what's your plan?
Chairman Na is blackmailing you with rumours...
and stole the hydrogen technology without making the final payment.
Isn't that enough to throw a jab?
How do you expect to manipulate a snake like him?
You have me, don't you?
The icon of betrayal.
You think Chairman Na will trust you?
He either trusts me, or he's dead.
It'll be one or the other.
You won't lose anything either way.
Secretary Yeo.
From now on, follow Team Leader Hwang's orders.
Give him whatever support he needs.
I'm betting everything on you, Hwang Jun Hyeon.
Chairman Na Byeong Mo.
This is Hwang Jun Hyeon from Future Business Team...
at Choiseong Group.
(Friday, March 20, 11:54am)
(Min Seok Do)
No way.
Kang Jae Gyeong is just letting this happen?
Letting Chairman Na run wild when he hasn't even paid...
the balance for the hydrogen technology?
It's so strange, right?
He's someone who deserves to be thrown out on his ear.
But what's even weirder...
is Kang Jae Gyeong's informant.
You found out? Did he share who it was?
At first, the guy swore he wouldn't talk...
even with a knife to his throat. He played so hard to get.
But two bottles of whiskey later, he caved.
The guy's a lightweight.
But your brother here has an iron liver.
I don't get drunk. I take after our father.
Anyway, the informant...
Who is the informant?
It was someone we know.
- Na Byeong Mo. - What?
- Chairman Na? - That viper...
even offered a multi-million dollar ad deal...
and said absolutely not to publish the article.
He said to just send the tip-off to Kang Jae Gyeong.
So Kang Jae Gyeong is being blackmailed...
by Na Byeong Mo over Dad's murder.
Chairman Na...
likes bonsai trees, right?
This is the bonsai expert. I had a hard time getting her to come.
If the Chairman finds out, he'll have our heads.
Hazard pay.
- Wait... - He won't be back for a while.
Don't worry.
Computer hard drives, external memory drives, USBs...
Find anything that looks like a storage device.
Okay. Hospital CCTV footage...
or the connection between Kang Jae Gyeong and Na Byeong Mo.
I swear, I'll find at least one today.
Seok Do.
Mother.
I hear you haven't been home much lately.
I got a call from Il Jun.
He said there was something he was craving.
Don't do this again.
Or just don't answer his calls.
The kids haven't done anything wrong.
Please leave. I'll give it to them.
You did your best to save your father-in-law.
I know you were sincere.
I...
just want to know the truth of how he died.
For Il Jun's sake, don't do anything else you'll regret.
You're a father too.
I guess I'll get what's coming to me.
(Multiful 5, Trace Element Injection)
He quit his job at the hospital.
Why would he be carrying something like that?
There aren't any golf courses in that direction.
Kang Jae Gyeong, that crazy girl.
(Additional Agreement on Strategic Investment)
That lunatic. Selling our precious hydrogen business for this nonsense?
Let's just take it.
You're dead meat, Kang Jae Gyeong.
The Chairman is arriving!
In one minute!
I'm a bit late, Chairman.
Welcome, Team Leader Hwang Jun Hyeon.
Let's go inside.
Well, if it isn't the traitor of the century.
What are you plotting now, Hwang Jun Hyeon?
I thought you might have lost my card,
so I came to see you in person.
When you said you'd serve me as your third master,
I didn't realise you were being sincere.
The lifeline I'm clinging to feels like it's about to snap.
They're trying to hush it up, but rumours are running rampant.
That Kang Jae Gyeong killed her own father.
How is the company in more of an uproar now...
than when Father passed away?
But we don't know the truth yet, do we?
True or not,
no soldiers will follow a general who's lost their trust.
Isn't knowing when to jump ship a skill in itself?
It looks like you've really got Kang Jae Gyeong...
by the throat, Chairman Na.
Team Leader Hwang.
Do I look like someone you can just sound out?
That's what Kang Jae Gyeong said.
That you're the one who killed her father.
She said you're framing her, but she asked me to help...
since she has no evidence or way to prove her innocence.
It's not that I believe Kang Jae Gyeong,
but why should I?
After everything it took for me to get here.
She has to pay the price for trying to kill me.
Your hit-and-run accident...
Was Kang Jae Gyeong behind that?
She's been trading on her father's name in all sorts of ways.
So, is there any reason I should help Kang Jae Gyeong?
The one who ruined a promising young man's life must be punished.
As an adult, how can I turn a blind eye?
Let him go, and then we'll talk.
About how you plan to get your revenge on Kang Jae Gyeong.
All right, then.
I'll hand over the hydrogen technology first.
There's a lot more I can get besides that...
from Kang Jae Gyeong.
I must say, I'm impressed.
Your judgment and your ability to act quickly.
Now I see why everyone asks for you, Team Leader Hwang.
You're too kind.
You should be careful.
Thank you.
Are you hurt?
The pain is mostly gone,
but it flares up whenever I go down the stairs.
(Hangang University Hospital)
Besides Kang Jae Gyeong, was there really no one else...
who came to the Chairman's room that day?
No, there wasn't.
After Kang Jae Gyeong left,
it wasn't long before that happened to the Chairman.
Was there anything out of the ordinary?
Please try to think carefully one more time.
What was unusual?
Oh, right. The stairs.
The stairs?
It was a bit strange.
The elevator wasn't broken, but she used the emergency stairs.
(Do Not Enter)
(Stairwell)
She took the stairs on purpose.
So she wouldn't run into Kang Jae Gyeong.
Sorry?
There was someone else there that day.
(VIP Ward)
Surely you don't think...
you got to that chair all by yourself?
It was Na Byeong Mo. He's trying to frame me for it.
They're trying to hush it up, but rumours are running rampant.
That Kang Jae Gyeong killed her own father.
But we don't know the truth yet, do we?
(VIP Ward)
Someone with a similar build to Kang Jae Gyeong...
who can easily get things in Kang Jae Gyeong's style.
Na Byeong Mo's daughter, who has a deep-seated...
inferiority complex toward Kang Jae Gyeong.
Na Eun Se.
It was you.
You were the one who killed me.
Come on, you should've gotten a better place.
I'll give you more money, so let's move.
How can an accomplice to a slush fund move to a nice place?
Jae Gyeong would have me arrested the second she finds an excuse.
This place is so tiny. There isn't even room to hide and cry.
How can you live here?
I know you've always found...
a secluded corner to swallow your tears...
like the kitchen, the wine cellar, and the garage.
Kang Jae Gyeong really tormented you.
You played a part in it too, you know.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't a good person.
I can't believe how immature I was.
Listen to you, acting like you're all grown up now.
I may be immature, but I'm handy.
See? When I say I'll do something, I do it.
If we leak this, don't you think we can...
keep the hydrogen business from Taeha?
Taeha is the one at a disadvantage in this secret contract.
Na Byeong Mo won't even bat an eye.
Only Choiseong will be shaken by the contract scandal.
- But still... - Jae Seong's right.
And this isn't even proof that Jae Gyeong is the real culprit.
- Any luck finding that informant? - Well, about that...
- Darn it. - My role here...
is to be malnourished, Mom.
- I've got no strength in my hands. - You really should be more careful.
Let me see if I have some pants you can change into.
What are you doing?
Don't say anything to Mom until we know for sure.
What do you take your brother for?
I was going to make something up anyway.
As if.
- You were itching to say something. - Hide!
- You're just embarrassed. - I said, hide!
What now?
- What? - Kang Jae Gyeong's lackey.
That punk.
Where have you been wandering? You're finally crawling in.
Who did you betray this time?
He must have conspired with Kang Jae Gyeong to get to Chairman Na.
"Betrayal" is a bit much.
Hey, the first betrayal is the hardest.
The next ones are a piece of cake, you know?
- Speaking from experience? - That's it. Why you little...
- Are you okay? - Gosh, baggy pants.
Totally my style. I love them.
Do you want to bet if Hwang Jun Hyeon...
has switched to Taeha's side?
We'll see who's right.
Why would you make such a childish bet?
We can just find out for ourselves.
You're having bread in the middle of the night?
Bang Geul just dropped it off. Do you want to try some?
She was here?
Yes.
(History, No Connected Devices)
Please insert the memory card.
That meticulous jerk.
Grandma.
What do you think? It's nice and fluffy, right?
I haven't eaten it yet.
It's more delicious with milk.
It is tasty.
Oh, right. Today's trash day.
Oh, I'll take it out. Taking out the trash is my hobby.
(Unannounced Fire Inspection)
That calculating jerk.
Oh, my. You scared me.
You scared me, Mom.
Aren't you going to make use of me?
What is it now?
I made some savoury pancakes. I brought them for you, Mr. Hwang.
I don't want any.
How can you say no when it smells this delicious?
- Come on out. - Oh, honestly.
You need to eat. You must be getting hungry by now.
They turned out so delicious.
Right?
(Recycle Bin)
Should I make some more?
- No, that's fine. I'll have that. - Seriously.
No. Goodness me. Here, have this one too.
- Okay. - Have this and then eat some more.
I'll take it inside.
Come over here. It won't take long.
- Grandma, I'm back with groceries. - You've gone to so much trouble.
- Sure. - Jun Hyeon, give her a hand.
Thank you.
Come in.
Oh, I was just taking a selfie.
Just one quick selfie.
First, replace the laptops for the Chemical DX Team...
then move on to the Talent Acquisition Team.
There are departmental meetings this afternoon,
so provide support for those.
Hey.
What's wrong with you two today?
It seems like Hwang Jun Hyeon is plotting something,
but we have no way of knowing what it is.
I can't take it anymore. I'm going to be a man and just...
- No. - Is this the resignation letter?
Is that the resignation letter Hwang Jun Hyeon is dying to see?
"To Jun Hyeon. Heart. Hello. The first time I saw you..."
"They were the things I wouldn't have done before I met you..."
This letter is meant to be touching, you know?
I rewrote it more than ten times.
After all we've been through together,
I doubt he's feeling great about this either.
Jun Hyeon isn't that bad of a guy.
No, he's totally cold-blooded. He's harsh and just ice-cold.
He's kind of like my dad.
Bang Geul.
The Chairman cared for you a lot.
He just wasn't good at showing it.
It's okay. I don't resent my dad. He was busy.
That's not true.
When he heard that you were being bullied in the US,
the Chairman skipped the opening of the Daesan Hydrogen Complex...
which he'd been looking forward to for years...
- and flew straight to the US. - The Chairman did?
Of course.
He tore into them until they were a crying mess.
He even got a written promise from them...
that they would never bully you again.
But even after that, he was still so furious.
So that's why their attitudes suddenly changed.
But why did he leave without seeing me? He went all the way to the US.
Because if he saw you, his heart would soften,
and he wouldn't have been able to leave you there.
But if he brought you back,
you would have had to deal with Jae Gyeong again.
That's why he held back.
He knew everything she was doing?
The Chairman always felt sorry that he couldn't do more for you.
He thought that was how he could protect you.
It wasn't because he didn't love you.
If he was going to die like this anyway,
why did he hide his feelings? Why didn't he say anything?
He always seemed so larger-than-life.
But the Chairman was just a father, after all.
Why are you crying now too?
Goodness. Coffee's on me.
- An iced vanilla latte, right? - An iced vanilla latte.
Just rest here.
Get it from the place right in front of the office.
Ask them for two pumps of syrup.
- Mom. - Bang Geul's mom.
If you're done with the bean sprouts,
bring them here so I can blanch.
Yes, coming.
Hwang Jun Hyeon is going on a business trip today.
A business trip? Where to?
Grandma forgot.
She said it started with Dae-something.
Dae?
Could it be Daesan? You mean the Daesan Hydrogen Complex?
I told you, you didn't have to come all this way.
The Chairman doesn't like variables.
Secretary Jo, are you sure you're not just acting on your own?
Can you really get it out without the staff knowing?
After I disable the CCTVs, I'll set off the fire alarm.
The fire trucks will take five minutes to arrive.
I'll get it out then, so just wait.
Don't worry.
If you're that suspicious,
you can come with me.
- Let's go. - Fire. There's a fire!
- Evacuate. - Evacuate.
Fire!
(Enter Password)
(Transferring File)
Why is it doing this again?
But he's dead.
(Lee Sang Jae)
- I'll call you back when... - Bang Geul is there.
- What? - Manager Park said Ms. Jo told her.
She seems to know that you and Taeha made contact.
I think Bang Geul figured something out.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
- Kang Bang Geul! - You...
Did you really betray Kang Jae Gyeong?
Did you side with Taeha?
I told you to lay low.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
The rule is to get rid of any witnesses.
Young Lady.
- Wake up. Are you okay? - Hey, Jun Hyeon.
Darn it, Jun Hyeon. Wait.
Young Lady, are you all right?
Mr. Park.
I'm okay.
- Bang Geul. - Goodness.
Bang Geul!
Yes, we're at the Daesan Hydrogen Complex.
You should've just gone to the US!
You said you wanted to run away, so why are you still here?
Why did I never once truly appreciate this wonderful girl?
The one who would just smile so brightly when I pushed her away.
Wake up, Bang Geul!
Open your eyes! Can't you hear your dad?
You're still here?
Jae Seong.
This is your last chance.
Make sure my father wakes up. Your life depends on it.
Yes, sir.
Father.
Hang on...
just a little longer.
Help me!
Is anyone there?
I'm trapped in here. Is anyone there?
I'm trapped in here!
I'm Hwang Jun Hyeon!
(Reborn Rookie)
I'm letting you in on my revenge.
So from now on, we do everything together.
I found the original CCTV footage from the hospital.
Let's show the world what kind of man Na Byeong Mo is.
We've secured circumstantial evidence...
pointing to the real culprit.
Get all our connections in the prosecution and the police.
If you don't want to be on the news with Na Byeong Mo,
- then throw him in jail now. - So you're looking for a fight?
Do you think my father will let you get away with this?
Get rid of him. And make sure there's nothing left.
You're really something else, ordering someone to be killed.
How about we take over all of Taeha?
In that case, may I tell you what I want?
My final target is Chairwoman Kang Jae Gyeong.