(Lee Ji-eun)
(Yeo Jin-goo)
(Shin Jung-geun/Bae Hae-sun)
(Pyo Ji-hoon/
Kang Mi-na/Cho Hyun-chul)
(Seo Yi-sook/Kang Hong-suk)
(Hotel Del Luna)
(Episode 10)
You know what this is, don't you?
A potion.
I thought it was strange that
Old Mago suddenly offered it to me.
You asked her to
give it to me, didn't you?
Believe what you want.
But Koo Chan-sung,
I want you to be safe.
No.
I'm going to put myself in danger,
so you'll feel uncomfortable by it.
What?
Koo Chan-sung, do you know
how valuable that is?
Do you know how clingy I had to be
to squeeze that out of her?
Ms. Jang Man-wol!
There's no safe place
for me anymore.
I'm going to continue to get
in your way, and fall in danger.
So you…
…continue to protect me.
Is this your potion?
This potion is yours, isn't it?
Sir…
How could you bring this to me
at a time like this?
It appeared you'd dropped it,
so I fetched it for you.
Thank you.
You brought back
something very precious for us.
Then… we'll leave you to rest.
Isn't this the potion that will
erase your fears?
Yes, that's true, but…
Then drink, and be at peace.
See?
Even he says to drink it
and be at peace.
That divine spirit
just can't take a hint.
That was the advice coming from
someone who found peace
by running away.
So drink.
You must've forgotten,
but spirits who hold a deep grudge
can kill you.
Why, you almost died a few days ago.
By me.
Don't put up with
this and that, and free yourself.
Drink.
But if I drink this,
I won't be able
to see you anymore.
You must've forgotten too,
but I peer into your soul.
If I don’t look after you,
you'll grow even nastier.
So even if I have to
put up with this and that,
I'm going to stop that
from happening.
Because…
I just can't have you
become like that.
So I'm going to continue to
remain by your side,
and watch over you.
Mr… Koo Chan-sung?
What is it now?
What brings you here at
my late father's holiday house?
You'd asked a favor to my father
when he was still alive?
Yes.
I borrowed his pond in his garden.
Did you free one of
your goldfishes, perhaps?
It's something very special,
and you'll benefit from it, too.
When Father was still alive,
he mentioned you several times.
That you had helped him out
quite a lot.
We're here to pack his belongings.
I see.
(Baekgu)
Oh… this is mine.
I spent a lot of time here with
Grandpa when I was little.
- Mom.
- Yes?
I found this in the book.
Gosh, when was this?
Father was still so young.
I miss him, right?
If there's anything
you'd like to say to him,
why don't you write it down?
The hotel I'm currently at is
holding a special event
where you send letters to
your dearly missed ones.
I thought you'd have left already,
but you waited.
Because I hate driving.
If you hate driving,
why did you buy all those cars?
Because they're pretty!
I'm going to buy back
all those cars that you sold off!
With what money?
You said you'll put up with
this and that,
so try putting up with
my pettiness.
I want my Mt. Paektu back.
Do you think
I'll give that back to you?
That's my severance pay.
I only dropped it by accident
at your place. So it's mine!
There's a good restaurant
around here that was featured on TV.
Why don't we go there?
A good restaurant?
You can't believe I'm suggesting
we go to a restaurant
at a time like this, right?
It just makes your blood boil,
doesn't it?
Because that's how I felt.
Let's go.
If we arrive there late, only to
find that it's already closed
because of you,
your Mt. Paektu won't be
going back to you,
ever.
Kim Jun-hyun, your idol,
has also been here.
Right, we need to take
a photo to commemorate.
There's no place around
to go shopping,
nor is there
your favorite cold noodles place.
So why not just
go back to Myeongdong?
It's quite a long way for me
to commute, too.
You can commute to
that other hotel for work.
From what I observed,
it seems like the late president is
quite fond of you.
I'd like my current president
who's sitting in front of me
to think that way instead.
And to do that…
I'll take the challenge!
If I succeed in the one bite
challenge, take me back.
The one bite challenge?
Kim Jun-hyun put everything on
this table in his wrap.
Nice try,
but you'll never get there
even if your mouth rips.
If I succeed,
you're taking me back.
It's no use.
I'm over Kim Jun-hyun now
these days.
You even abandoned Kim Jun-hyun,
your all-time idol?
Yes.
So if you succeed with that,
try Gag Concert instead of
our hotel.
Was it easy getting over him?
It hasn't been easy.
He'd be on every channel
I switch to.
I really hope
this place isn't good,
so I'm not ever
reminded of him again.
(Eat Till You Drop)
I said to just leave the car and go.
Why do you keep following me?
I'm making it difficult for you by
being everywhere you turn to.
But now, I'm here to see
the President.
There's something his granddaughter
wanted me to pass onto him.
Give it, I'll pass it on.
No.
How am I supposed to trust you?
I'm going to deliver it to
our guest himself.
I'm the president here,
and you were fired.
President Jang.
And General Manager Koo,
you also came into work.
He's not the general manager
here anymore.
And he's here on a visit,
not to work.
Go see the President for
whatever your business is.
There is something
I must inform you.
You mean the guests you invited
were all murdered?
Yes, we saw their bodies buried
on a mountain, not in a graveyard.
I reported it to the police
using the public pay phone.
It was on the news, too.
They found multiple bodies,
and everyone is talking about
how it is a serial murder.
And putting together
what our guests have told us,
it does seem like
one man murdered them all.
They've all said
he was a complete stranger,
and all agree that
it was a young man.
It's that man.
I'm sure the owner of that vehicle
is the murderer.
Oh! I wrote down the plate number
so I don't forget.
- We could track him down, and…
- Don't get involved.
Hyun-joong already reported it,
and the media's covered the story
of multiple bodies being found.
So leave it to the human police
to catch the living murderer.
Our job is to make sure
our guests have a comfortable stay
while they watch all that happen,
and depart in peace.
Put TVs in their rooms so they can
follow the news if they wish to.
And give them complimentary
Wi-Fi access for the updates.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you alright?
Don't worry,
the police will get him.
Anyway, if it was Hyun-joong
who reported it to the police
they probably must think
they've been bewitched by now.
The report was made
using this payphone,
but at that exact hour,
no one was captured on the
surveillance camera right there!
Do you think it was a ghost?
How bizarre.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
What surprises me is that
they still have payphones around.
Do you have any coins,
by any chance?
Yes, one second…
Ah, here.
Thank you!
This is to say thank you.
It's alright.
If you lose that,
you won't be getting married.
Never, ever,
not in your life!
You'll never find love.
So don't ever lose that.
Hello, Sis!
Ah, yes.
Uh… excuse me?
What the…
Never, ever,
not in your life!
(Dear Grandfather
whom I miss very much,)
(I'm so happy to be
able to write to you)
Your granddaughter was
extremely sad that
she couldn't be there for
your last moments.
She was studying abroad
at that time.
But at least I get to
see her like this.
I owe it all to you.
So you're a motorcyclist?
It really suits you.
Does it?
I couldn't really go for a ride
because it may look disrespectable.
This I also owe to you, too.
I'm glad to see you
enjoying yourself.
My granddaughter is a beauty,
isn't she?
Yes.
Are you… seeing anyone?
Pardon?
My granddaughter doesn't have
a boyfriend either, so…
Her name is Jeong Ji-eun,
and she's 25 years old.
She's been buried in books
all her life that
she can't tell who's a fine man.
I wanted to match her up with
a righteous fellow, if I could…
Ah, I see.
I'm sure she'll find a good person.
Don't worry.
Then… I better get going.
Koo Chan-sung isn't seeing anyone.
I thought you might be curious about
that righteous fellow over there.
Is that right?
Then shall I tell you more
about Koo Chan-sung?
Should I tell him to take care of
this while he's here?
Ugh.
President Jang! There you are.
What is it?
By your special order,
I managed to make a good
impression on our VIP.
Good work. Any progress?
I said I will take care of
something that's been on his mind
since when he was still alive.
Ah! Well done, Mr. Kim.
As a talent who came first in
the Joseon state exams,
you've always proved
yourself useful.
You see, this President… He has
a granddaughter he dotes on.
His only regret is not having been
able to find a match for her,
so I said I'll be the matchmaker!
Matchmaker?
Right. If it goes well,
that means a new suit for you.
He's a CEO, so I'm sure
he'll be more generous than that.
Of course!
If we find him a grandson-in-law,
the least he could do is
take care of this now, huh?
Your dilemma is over!
I knew I could count on you.
Mr. Kim, you're our ace employee!
And the President really likes
the human I suggested.
Aw, Mr. Kim. When did you find
the time to go out there
and befriend someone, when
you're already busy with your bar?
When do I have the time to
befriend anyone?
There's just one human I know.
Huh?
It's Koo Chan-sung!
You mean, Koo Chan-sung, as in
our general manager?
He's not our general manager
anymore, is he?
I know you've been
feeling bad about him,
so let's help him marry into
a chaebol family!
Once he marries a chaebol,
he couldn't possibly ignore us.
We'll receive a handsome sum from
the President,
and Koo Chan-sung, too!
It's catching two birds
with a stone. Haha!
Has Koo Chan-sung left already?
I need to give him
his granddaughter's number.
You can count on me on this one!
Where did he go?
That bird-head…!
Has Mr. Koo left already?
No, I haven't seen him leave.
So he's still in here, is he?
Ah, alright!
(To: Ms. Jang Man-wol
I love you!)
Lies, she still hasn't
gotten over him.
You're still here.
I was just about to leave.
Mr. Koo? Mr. Koo!
What is it?
Do you think Mr. Koo's in
President Jang's office?
Mr. Koo?
Hmmm, he's not here.
What is it?
Well, uh…
Do you suppose he's in the garden?
What's wrong with him? Jeez.
Do we have to stay like this?
Why do we have to stay like this?
You don't like money, right?
I know you're the frugal type.
Why, instead of flashy colors
you prefer turd…
I mean, you prefer the dull brown.
Right?
Are you threatening me,
because I won't give back
your Mt. Paektu painting?
Ha! So you do.
You do like money.
Yes, I like money.
And I want to make lots, if I can.
Is love for money
something to brag about?
Is that what they taught at Harvard?
Yes, because ultimately, an MBA is
all about learning how to
make money.
Good for you,
you greedy Harvard swindler.
I hope you become a chaebol, then!
Or even a hotel president!
Now get out!
What the…
She's really angry about that
Mt. Paektu painting, isn't she?
Ms. Jang Man-wol.
I'll give you that painting back.
But you hold onto that potion.
Let's leave aside just one
safe option for me,
where I can run away
and abandon you.
I'll be waiting for your call to
reinstate me, then.
And the lunch
we had together earlier…
I enjoyed it.
So let's go again, next time.
My wife hasn't been back home
for several days now.
So that's why I'm calling
all her friends.
If you ever hear from her, uh…
Please tell her that I'm sorry,
and that I really want her to
come back home.
Thank you.
No…
Honey…!
Honey…
What's wrong with you?
Why are you like this?
What happened to you?
Oh what?
I… what? What?
It's as they said. There's a body.
You are under arrest as
a prime suspect for
the murder of your wife,
Ms. Lee Do-yeon.
It wasn't me!
You have the right to remain silent,
and the right to an attorney…
What about the shovel?
You need to take the shovel,
the dirty shovel.
That's right. That's right!
Take away the serial killer.
Goodbye!
Ugh!
Why do you hate
Mr. Seol Ji-won so much?
Did something happen between you two
while you were in the States?
Not two, but three.
Chan-sung's involved, too?
After you went back to Korea,
a Korean girl who'd been studying
in Boston killed herself.
And for some reason, rumors were
rampant that I was to blame.
What? You, Sanchez?
No way, who'd believe that?
Apparently everyone.
Rumors led to more rumors
and suddenly,
I was this rich scumbag
who played with a rich girl and
even had his friends
do some unspeakable things.
And after that…
There was a big bet
on an online community.
On whether I'd kill myself or not.
And the person
who started all this, was…
Seol Ji-won?
It was you, wasn't it?
It was you who spread that rumor
about Je-in.
I only ever said that
I saw you inviting Je-in to
a party hosted by
some rich European guys.
It was a job offer!
As a waitress there.
She said she couldn't afford her
tuition, so I…
But this "job" could've actually
been something else.
Don't lose your cool.
No one believes you anyway.
See, people actually hate you
because you're rich
and you go around
pretending to be nice.
But hang in there.
At least I betted on you
not killing yourself.
(Die 121)
(Live 98)
What are you doing here?
I've been looking for you.
Let's go grab something to eat,
Sanchez.
When I was at my most miserable
that I wanted to kill myself,
Chan-sung came to me.
That day, he went to Ji-won with
that giftbox with a pistol in it,
and not long after that,
Ji-won suddenly went back to Korea.
Why? What did Chan-sung
say or do to him?
That... I don't know.
Anyway, after that…
He came to see me every day,
asking if I wanted to grab a bite.
Until the rumors dissipated.
So that's how
you two became close.
Who put this outside?
Collection day is not today,
but tomorrow!
Sorry.
Chan-sung, I also got some pizza
for you. Go wash your hands.
Ah, thanks.
Remember, recyclables are
on Saturdays.
Don't ever tell Chan-sung about
seeing Seol Ji-won today.
I don't want Chan-sung
getting involved with him again.
Alright, I won’t tell him.
Too bad.
There's no guy like Chan-sung.
I don't think there's a better man
than Mr. Koo Chan-sung.
I understand you very well, but…
You are already deceased,
so how could we possibly
pass this onto your granddaughter?
So I was thinking…
I'd like to use your special service
offered at this hotel.
I heard from Mr. Kim right here.
That there's this
"dream call" service,
where you can appear in
your descendants' dreams.
I also heard payment can be done
through real money.
I just happened to remember
something I'd put aside…
Grandpa!
You got my postcard?
Yes, and I really like the man
who passed this onto me.
You mean, Mr. Koo Chan-sung?
Yes.
I really do wish you'd take him
as your partner for life.
About this young man…
Time's up.
It's a rather short call for
a hefty price.
Then why not make one more call?
Our principle is,
one call per day.
You need to be considerate of
others who are in line.
At least you said
all the things you needed to.
President Jang.
Does this mean Mr. Koo will
marry into a chaebol family?
Do you think kids these days
listen to their elders?
Like she would, when she never did
while he was still alive!
Grandpa appeared in
my dreams last night.
He was extremely happy to
have received my photo.
Really? I'm sure
that made you happy, too.
And…
He also said something else.
I really do wish you'd take him
as your partner for life.
Use this.
Excuse me, could you
clean up this table?
Mr. Koo Chan-sung.
Have you had lunch yet?
I'd like to talk to you
about my grandfather.
Sure, let's go have lunch.
What do you like?
He's here. He's here!
Did you really murder your wife?
Why did you kill all those
other innocent people?
Are there any others
beside those seven?
What was your motive?
What drove you to
murder those people?
Why did you kill your wife?
- Please, just one comment!
- One comment please!
One comment please.
(Husband Who Murdered Wife
Arrested, Motive Yet Unclear)
This isn't him.
I'm sure he was
much smaller than this man.
What is?
I don't think he's the murderer.
All they have to do is find the car
with the plate number, 0963.
0963?
You remember the number?
Yes.
Just forget them, like
how you forget your English vocab.
Hey, come on!
This is my friend's place,
and it's really good.
Hey, it's Mr. Koo.
Sanchez!
- Have you been well?
- Have you?
You know Sanchez?
She's a member of our yacht club.
Oh, really?
Well, this is a coincidence.
- I should join you next time.
- You don't quite make the cut.
Please.
Maybe after you own a hotel.
I was going to tell him about the
0963 when I see him…
But I guess I can't.
Mr. Koo's not
our hotel manager anymore.
What?
He's going to marry into
a chaebol family.
I'll use my experience
as general manager to greet customers
and help with inventory.
- That's nice.
- I can talk to customers too.
(Koo Chan-sung)
I'll be waiting for your call.
President Jang! President Jang!
They met. They met!
The matchmaking is going smoothly!
What? They met?
I saw Mr. Koo with the
chaebol granddaughter today!
It was my first time seeing
Mr. Koo laugh so much!
It turns out Mr. Koo is
quite an ambitious man.
I don't know.
Koo Chan-sung's always nice and
smiles to everyone.
Then why don't you go
and have a look for yourself?
Apparently, they're going to see
each other again.
Mr. Koo invited her to his place.
An invite to his house means…
Meet the parents!
But Mr. Koo's father
already passed away, remember?
Do you think his mother is
still here?
Is Mr. Koo's mother still alive?
Who knows, I'm sure
she's around somewhere.
She never listens, does she?
Anyway, we should be happy for
Koo Chan-sung that
he'll have a new family,
since he's been quite lonely.
After all, he's been so good to
our guests while he was here.
I'm glad to see that
he's now rewarded for it!
Do you think so?
Well, good for him.
Are you cleaning the place since
Ji-eun's coming over tomorrow?
Yes,
I want the place to look tidy.
Right, you need to see someone else
if you want to forget about Man-wol.
But Chan-sung does have
high standards, doesn't he?
He always dates women
who own a hotel.
I hear there's a cursed book
in this library.
There's no such thing as that!
My cousin's a librarian here,
and she said so.
The ghost of the person who donated
the book still haunts it,
so take the book from the shelf,
and you'll see her.
Sounds like fun.
Where is that book?
Let's upload it on social media.
- Is this the book?
- Yes.
Here we go.
- Take it out.
- I'm taking it out.
It won't budge. This is no joke!
- What are you doing?
- It really must be haunted.
What is it?
Seol… Seol!
Are you alright? Seol!
(Time and Existence)
Are you alright? Huh?
Are you alright?
Seol, wake up! Hey!
Hey!
Hey, wake up!
If Koo Chan-sung hasn't
taken the potion,
that means he'll be able to see
an old, lost acquaintance again.
That's one of the downsides of
having an all-seeing eye.
I hear you matched up
two random souls again?
It's quite fun, matching up
old enemies.
They instantly take notice
of each other,
because there's still
something left in their heart!
Oh my.
So beautiful!
- Are you going to get in?
- Yes.
Excuse me.
Does this belong to you?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
What are you going to
do about this now, huh?
This happened because of
your ball-point pen!
And it's my first time
wearing this today, too.
I'm sorry, what should I do?
Compensate me.
Actually, I'm busy today
so give me your number.
Pardon?
But this is…
It's black.
Right. It's black.
Though it's pink on the outside.
Fine, then.
Excuse me.
This is something that's
quite important to me
and since you found it for me,
let me compensate.
Will you give me your number?
Sure. Alright, then.
So your grandfather
founded this library.
Yes.
I guess this was the reason
why my grandfather
appeared in my dreams.
To be honest, I wanted this to
ever since I first met you.
My grandfather will be very happy.
Let's go.
Are you satisfied?
What a fine couple they make!
Then as promised,
I'll take that money.
Why don't you stay and
watch them a little longer?
You're so beautiful now!
- A real princess.
- Really?
I almost didn't recognize you.
How is your mother doing?
She's doing very well,
and in good health.
I see. I should really
come and see her sometime.
This here is Mr. Koo Chan-sung.
Hello.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Koo Chan-sung.
Ms. Jang Man-wol.
Why are you here?
The President said
he wanted to see his granddaughter.
This is a special service for him,
since he paid a hefty fee for
our dream call service.
Don't mind us,
but just be on your way.
Why don't you take a look around
the library since you're here?
They have many fine books
and pictures here.
I'm alright.
I'm leaving.
Don't say that, but stay.
There's a very good painting here.
I sold this painting.
I thought
you might die waiting for
a memorial hall to be built.
I talked it out with
his granddaughter,
and we decided to hang it here.
I came here to sell this,
so what about you?
What was your deal with him,
that involves me?
And what's this about
a dream call service?
You don't have to know.
So you say there are
many great paintings here?
I think I'll take a look,
while I'm here.
What did you rip off of
him this time?
I only ripped him off a little.
I feel a little uncomfortable
about that painting you know,
since it actually belongs to him.
Well, you're a greedy
Harvard swindler, remember?
Swindler?
Stop saying that, and take it back!
- I don't want to.
- You don't want to?
The excuse that you don't want to
just doesn't cut it!
I said, take it back.
So, about this Koo Chan-sung…
He seems like a nice guy.
Are you seeing him, Ji-eun?
I'd hoped so, but…
He says he has someone he likes.
The restaurant here is
really good.
Right?
I used to come here often
with my father,
and it was good then, too.
You lived around here
when you were little?
My father wanted to enroll me
in a primary school in this area.
Though we never ended up
finding a room here
because the rent was so high,
we came here often, because
this place is cheap and good.
So it's always been
just you and your father?
Yes.
The reason why my name is
Chan-sung is because...
Because Dad was the only person
who said yes to me being born.
That's why he gave me
this name that mean agree,
because he felt sorry about that.
But because he didn't know
his Chinese characters so well,
my name ended up meaning
"bright star" instead.
You know, your father sold you off
not to save himself but for you.
He said you'll be all alone
without him.
Of course I know that.
We only had each other.
If you're finished,
let's go check out some books.
Books?
I can't quite do that,
not in this state.
Why not?
This outfit doesn't really
go with books.
What does outfits
have to do with books?
Everything!
Look.
You need to take a picture
to show you read books,
but I'm just not dressed right.
Please…
Koo Chan-sung, order some coffee
and just wait here.
I'll go get changed
and be right back.
No need for that, just sit down.
I wasn't asking you to
read a book together,
but to check out a book
that may be haunted.
The chief librarian here was
quite worried because
there's a rumor that a ghost
haunts the archives.
If there really is one around here,
let's bring her to our hotel.
There's a haunted book?
Yes.
And apparently, she was the
donor of the very book.
She was a headmaster of a primary
school who recently passed away,
and her family donated the book.
It seems like she treasured
that book very much.
I don't know…
Most people easily throw away
what they treasured,
and instead guard with their life
what they want to hide.
That spirit must have
been on edge because of
all those humans coming to
pull that book out.
What could she have been
hiding in that book, though?
I can only think of
some secret stash of cash.
Tsk, tsk.
Only money will make her move,
huh?
You pull it out, since you're
a human. That way, she'll come out.
"Time and Existence"…
That title will make
anyone stay away from it.
I've read it before.
Yes, yes. I'm sure you have.
After all,
you're Mr. Smarty-pants.
Good on you!
Yes, I read it to brag about it,
but it was quite
difficult to understand.
It was me who's been killing
all this time,
having been in existence
for over a thousand years.
And even someone like me
doesn't know what time is,
so how would you know when you've
only been around for 30 years?
Well, let's first see
what "time" exists in this book.
It might not appear if I'm around,
so I'll be at the back.
You can see me?
Yes, I can.
What are you doing here?
I didn't want anyone
seeing this book.
Is there something you treasure
inside the pages?
Or something you're hiding?
Can you get rid of what's inside?
I'll help you.
But to do that,
I'll have to take this book out.
It's a past I've been hiding.
I can't have my family find out.
So please…
Get rid of them.
That woman just now…
I think she may be my mother.
The last time I met her was
when I was still very young,
so I didn't even know
she'd passed away.
I didn't even realize
Father had sent these pictures.
(I'm going to the States
with Chan-sung)
You're right, it wasn't
what she treasured,
it was what she was hiding.
So she really was
against me being born.
I told you you'll have to put up
with this and that.
Well, this is what I meant.
The truth you didn't have to learn,
and was better not knowing.
Why? Am I wrong?
Or are you going to say
it was still nice to see her,
because she was your mother?
You want to play the son
you never could, before she leaves?
Do you think I'd want to?
Thank goodness.
Hand them over,
so I can put them back.
Let her be there forever
and continue to suffer.
But that…
I don't want that, either.
Then what do you want me to do?
You had to go through that
because you started seeing spirits,
and since I'm to blame for that,
shouldn't I do something?
I just…!
I'm just sad that I can't be
happy about meeting my mother
for the first time in my life.
Let me just sulk.
It's nothing. Go.
Did something happen?
Why the long face?
Well…
I'm just feeling blue.
You came to the right place.
I'm here to cheer you up.
Let's go, I'll buy you a drink.
Hey, you have a loose button.
Where did you drop it?
Why do you go around like that?
It's pitiful.
Was she trying to
comfort me back then?
Sanchez!
Mi-ra.
I was just about to
step out with Chan-sung.
Chan-sung's here?
This is not a great time to
ask you to join us,
so I'm sorry we'll have to leave you
to have dinner alone.
Hey, I have company!
I won't be eating alone.
Really?
This really is a nice place.
What's going on?
Chan-sung, say hello.
This is Mr. Park Young-soo.
I found something that's
very important to him,
so he's going to buy me dinner.
But you… killed him.
What?
Oh, right?
Yes, he has killer looks.
My gosh, Mi-ra.
Mr. Park's a detective!
So… it's just you and
Sanchez tonight, is it?
I'll see you later.
What is it? Do you know him?
Not me, but Ms. Jang Man-wol does.
Man-wol?
Then does he know Man-wol, too?
He probably doesn't.
Sanchez, we'll have to have
that drink another time. Sorry.
Alright.
Tell me anything Koo Chan-sung
has told you in private.
Does he have any relatives
he keeps in touch with?
What about his friends?
Anyone other than Sanchez?
No? No-one?
Mr. Koo was almost always…
…with you, President Jang.
Don't you know anything?
I'm his boss, so I'm excused!
But not his colleagues.
How can you be so disinterested
in your colleagues?
Mr. Kim.
You even played matchmaker for him.
You don't know anything?
I only recommended him
because he had good heart.
Hey runt,
wasn't he closest to you?
Well…
As far as I know, Mr. Koo…
Well, he likes brown.
I know that much!
The Grim Reaper is
also here with us.
I think
you've scolded them enough,
when you don't know much
about him yourself.
Then what about you?
Do you know anything?
You've seen him quite often.
Ha!
I know you're all dead and all,
but you can be so cold!
President Jang, if there is
anything you'd like to know,
I suggest you ask him yourself.
There he is, right now.
I thought you'd be
sulking for a long time,
but looks like
you got over it pretty quickly.
I'm not quite done yet
but I came, because of you.
Me?
I think, it's me this time
who probed to deep into
your time and existence.
I met the person
who's your greatest sadness.
An ex-thief…
…is now a police officer.
You're doing well again.
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness, indeed.
Do you want to go and talk to him?
No.
I don't deserve to.
But he was like family to you.
Will you be alright like this?
No, I'm not alright.
I'm a bit sad.
Once again,
I had to bring
an old acquaintance to you.
Thank you, Koo Chan-sung.
- Let me see.
- No.
That serial murder…
The results are out for
that dirt on the shovel, right?
Pardon?
Yes, it's almost an exact match to
the soil from that mountain.
Right?
But why will our suspect
still deny it?
Jeez, he's giving me a big headache.
But, uh…
He would have no motive other than
for his wife's murder.
He's a typical psychopath.
A murder addict.
The end!
Ah!
(Jungseok Moving Service)
I'm telling you, we're missing
something from that delivery.
But the truck delivered
everything without problems.
Uh…
Can you check who made
the reservation?
The person who reserved the
3465 truck that day is
Mr. Koo Chan-sung.
- Who?
- Aren't you Mr. Koo himself?
Koo Chan-sung?
It can't be.
Koo Chan-sung.
Koo Chan-sung…
Why did your name
pop out from there?
Chan-sung,
are you going to be
at home all day, too?
Yes.
You're not even going to
go to Man-wol's hotel?
You kept going there,
hoping to be hired back.
There's something
I need to sort out first.
Unless I do that,
I won't be able to
face the guests there.
(Time and Existence)
Will I find the answer after
reading this difficult book?
On how to comfort a child,
whose existence and the time
he spent with his mother
has just been denied?
Are you worried that
your secret will be exposed?
Don't worry.
Because your child
doesn't want that.
He's very sad right now,
and I want to comfort him.
So I need your hotel.
Let me escort you to my hotel.
You're hired again.
Take line 4 on the subway
and come to Del Luna.
I have a guest here waiting,
whom you need to send off.
A guest I need to send off…
Welcome back, Mr. Koo.
You're back in Myeongdong.
I like this location
much, much better!
I look forward to working
with you, as always.
I thought he'd be marrying
into the chaebol family,
but instead he came back to
this haunted hotel.
He has no ambition, for a man!
President Jang needs Mr. Koo.
Men with ambitions
aren't in these days.
You're really behind the times.
And…
I told you to fix that
outdated speech of yours!
Hey, come on!
I think I've worked
a lot on my language.
Don't you think? Oh, come on.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you for coming.
The photographs from the book…
May I keep them?
Will you do that?
I…
I'm really sorry.
(To Heaven)
Goodbye,
Mother.
Did you see her off?
Yes.
Sorry to bring her here
on my own will.
Thank you, for doing just that
on your own will.
And…
Thank you, for telling me
to come back.
Let's get this straight, though
this hurts my pride as President.
You didn't come back because
I told you to.
You came back, for me.
I could have forced you to
drink that potion and
have you never return,
but I didn't do that.
Every time I gave you
a chance to run away,
I thought it was you
who came back nevertheless,
But in actual truth,
I'd been hoping you'd come back.
It feels nice to
have you clearly say that
I wasn't the only one
clinging onto you.
Koo Chan-sung.
I'm going to use you.
You brought that woman,
and Yeon-woo too,
in front of me.
That means you'll probably…
…bring him, too.
That'll probably be the case, yes.
You will, no matter what.
And I…
…will make sure that
he doesn't pass me by in one piece.
So that's why
you're going to use me?
Yes. I'm evil and cunning.
Because of me,
you'll be used and played by me
until you're bruised and scarred.
Is this another way of…
- threatening to run away…
- No.
Don't run away.
You've already made up your mind.
You said you'll gladly get in
the way, and fall in danger.
Do just that,
and stay next to me
with a heart that's ready to
accept death.
Even if I were ever to
go mad and run wild,
and disappear one day…
Still, stay with me.
No.
I won't ever let you perish.
Trust me.
(Hotel Del Luna)
It must be hard,
missing someone
when you can't see them.
I'm letting you off this time
because you're weak.
I'm sure you saw that
the tree has bloomed.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Brace yourselves, because
we'll have to depart before
President Jang does.
It's so beautiful like this.
So does it have to wilt?
It'd be so sad.
Flowers bloom…
…so they may wilt.