[English subtitles are available]
[My Special Girl]
[Episode 10]
I was drunk last night.
Did I...
Say something?
You not only said things you shouldn't have said
but also did things you shouldn't have done.
However, after sobering up, you should feel regret
for those actions, right?
No?
But I remember
you sent me home.
Yes.
I left you at the door.
Should I tell you the truth?
Letting you know that you've done
so many boring things for a girl
you don't even like
will only make things awkward for both of us.
Tomorrow is the weekend.
Will you go somewhere with me?
So handsome.
His legs are so long.
Is he a teacher in our school?
He has a nice body.
He's so handsome.
Handsome.
Is the person next to him
his girlfriend?
He wore a suit to school.
It's quite formal.
So handsome.
I really want his phone number.
Are you afraid of being seen
walking with me?
No, not at all.
Mr. Gu.
What are we...
I want you to have the home-field advantage.
The factors affecting performance
include subjective
and objective factors.
In terms of subjective factors,
after this period of training,
I think you can achieve
a score of over 100 points.
So today, we're here
to eliminate objective interference.
How?
Where do you usually take exams?
The staircase classroom in the Red Mansion.
Let's go.
What's wrong with you?
You haven't handed in your homework for two days.
All of you are
taller than me.
And you still need me to watch over you?
What a trouble.
Thunderbolt Woman.
Hurry back, be quick.
What's wrong?
My Higher Mathematics teacher.
Are you trying to avoid her?
Hao Liang.
Yes.
It's really you.
How's your review going?
I'm...
I'm reviewing.
Your head teacher came to me two days ago
to plead for you.
But you only got 69 points.
Out of 150 points in total,
you got 69.
If I let you pass
with such a score,
it would be extremely
irresponsible of me.
Yes.
You're right.
Hao Liang.
Math
is a fundamental subject.
If you're not good at math,
it means your logical thinking is weak.
Someone without logic,
when they
encounter a slightly
complex situation
at work,
won't be able to figure it out
and will make mistakes.
By then,
no boss would dare to hire you.
Whoever hires you will be unlucky.
If I don't be strict with you now,
in the future,
you will become
a burden to society.
Hao Liang.
You've completely lost face.
Ma'am.
Can we talk in private?
Who are you?
I'm her family.
-Family?
-Uncle.
Family.
Similar.
Handing me a low score isn't sufficient.
Do you two also need to discuss
my daily foolishness?
Here's the thing.
I'd like to ask
how you view Hao Liang's
math performance.
Let me put it this way.
She lacks a foundation.
Is there any possibility
of other factors?
For example...
For example, being in a romantic relationship.
Romantic relationship?
You
heartless and cruel adults,
have you said enough
bad things about me?
I haven't heard about that.
Hao Liang
seems to be quite close
to a guy from the Economics department.
Boyfriend?
You'll have to ask her about that.
Mr. Gu.
What did Thundering Woman
just tell you?
We were discussing
the issue of your academic performance
not improving.
Because I'm stupid.
She said your mind
isn't on your studies.
My mind isn't on studies?
Did Thunderbolt Woman
find out about
my live-streaming activities
and tell Mr. Gu?
Is that true?
I... I don't know.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Does having a relationship
affect your grades?
No, I'm not in a relationship.
Did Thunderbolt Woman say my mind
isn't on studies
because I'm in a relationship?
So,
is there or isn't there?
There isn't.
I work during the day and review at night.
I don't have time to date.
That makes sense.
So, you usually
take exams here?
The make-up exam is in three days.
Let's do
a simulation exam test.
The duration is 90 minutes.
Are you confident to get 100 points?
I...
Will you be disappointed
if I can't get 100 points?
You lack confidence even before the exam?
Mr. Gu.
Did I pass?
Guess.
Is it less than 100?
I...
I didn't go easy on you.
This is the first time
I've passed Higher Mathematics since I entered college.
I'm so, so happy.
How are you going to thank me?
I...
Excuse me.
Hello?
Not tonight.
I have something to do.
Something?
Does that mean tutoring for me?
Am I holding him back again?
Mr. Gu.
Thank you for
tutoring me during this time.
From now on, you'll be free.
Free?
Yes.
The exam is in three days.
I won't trouble you anymore.
Mr. Gu.
Your mission is completed.
Are you happy?
Your knowledge of multiple integrals and differential equations
is still quite weak.
I'm not trying to get full marks.
I just need to pass.
Mr. Gu,
you have so many things to do.
Don't let me delay
your important tasks.
Please.
I finally made up my mind.
Don't look at me
like that.
I'll really regret it.
Dan, let me tell you.
Big gossip.
The one in the next class
broke up.
Is that the Mr. Gu
you mentioned?
Hello, handsome boss.
My name is Yang Panpan.
Well,
there's a newly opened taro stall
at the gate of the school.
It looks delicious.
Let's try it.
No need.
I have something to do. I have to go.
Dan.
I've been looking for you.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
What's up?
It's not convenient here.
About Dai?
Is he the person you like?
Shut up.
Mr. Gu, we have things to do.
We're leaving.
Is this really the last lesson?
Dan's matters are my matters.
You can come to me if you need anything.
I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Zhu Yi.
I'm Dan's best friend, majoring in economics.
I'm more than capable of tutoring her in Higher Mathematics.
Hao Liang
seems to be quite close
to a guy from the Economics department.
I see.
I have something to do.
I have to go.
Bye.
They're gone.
Just say what you want to say.
I'm speechless.
I just saw the notice board.
She says she will punish you in tomorrow night's live broadcast,
which is eating mustard.
This woman is so disgusting.
You are both singers.
She's intentionally damaging your voice.
I'm talking to you.
Don't just say "Huh".
I'm worried sick
about your situation.
Is your mind
completely occupied by that man now?
What about Cute Mengmeng?
I don't know.
You still don't know?
Do you still want to participate in the Qixiu Grand Ceremony?
Do you want your mom to find out
about your career as a streamer openly?
I really can't do it.
I'm so weak.
I can't do anything right.
I'll only cause you trouble
and make you worry.
I'm such a disappointment.
Alright.
What should we do?
Zhu Yi.
I don't want to be punished.
But it's not good
not to acknowledge defeat.
Zhu Yi.
Why am I so unlucky?
Who is to blame?
During that showdown, you were singing your strongest song,
but you voluntarily admitted defeat.
Enough.
That was a special situation.
Special situation?
I think you were
with your boss.
Let me ask you.
If I ask you to give me a grade,
how many points will you give me?
Do you want to hear the truth or a lie?
Alright, I got it.
Stop talking.
Mr. Gu.
Is this your car?
Our dorm is far away.
Can you give me a ride?
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu.
Well...
He's quite unique.
36 points.
What the hell?
If you want me, I'll give you eight...
Full marks.
Don't comfort me.
This month
is the happiest
of my life.
For the first time,
I met someone I liked.
And I got
a chance
to stay by his side.
At first, I thought
as long as I could see him every day,
I'll be happy.
But gradually,
he started to stand up for me in public,
caring about my subtle feelings
and even helping me with my studies.
So I became greedy,
wondering
if he might
have a tiny bit
of affection for me.
But he was drunk that day.
I took him home.
What he told me
and did to me...
What did he do to you?
Nothing.
You...
Actually,
I misunderstood.
All this time,
When I saw that note,
I came to my senses.
I am someone
who is not pretty, not smart,
and timid.
I even messed up the only thing
I'm good at, live streaming.
Who would like me?
Let me tell you.
He's definitely an abusive man,
stingy,
a Mama's boy,
and lazy.
Maybe he even has athlete's foot.
You should be glad
you've completely avoided a scumbag.
Don't talk about him like that.
He gave you 36 points.
And you're still defending him?
I don't deserve him.
This is my problem.
Zhu Yi.
Being dumped is so painful.
Why do you still
like dating so much?
How would I know?
Then tell me
how your ex-girlfriends
get through this.
I don't know.
Send a message to ask them.
No.
It's okay to ask.
Where's your phone?
Where is it?
It's okay to ask.
Send it via your phone.
Where's your phone?
Are you crazy?
Give it to me.
Send it via your phone.
Please.
No.
You won't even help me with this small favor?
[Han Yijie]
Hello? What's wrong?
Come out.
Is something bothering you?
Lend me money.
I've thought about Xiaojiu's problem.
First, build a cloud server
to connect the network.
The issue of computing power
can be solved using servers.
It should be fine.
Gu Jiuli,
I've been waiting for this statement for ten years.
I'm done.
Let's switch positions.
What?
Is it about making the engine
write its own
program?
There's no precedent for this in the world.
Oh my god.
That's a miracle.
This is the engine of the ages.
Non Human
really has inhumane intelligence.
Okay, everybody, the time is over.
Please take the keyboard off the keyboards.
Thank you.
Congratulations to Infinite Team
for winning the championship of the year.
Thank you.
Good job.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Ten years ago,
we could turn the tide.
Ten years later,
Xiaojiu will surely rise
to prominence.
Do you know?
In this world,
only two and a half people believe you.
The first one.
Master Ka.
He believes in you as a person
but not in your ability,
counting as half.
The other
is me.
And
there's also Hao Liang.
She
seems a little strange today.
What?
What's wrong with you two?
I was tutoring her.
She called it off.
Could she
be falling
for someone else?
The goals I set before
are never impossible to achieve.
But this time, it seems like
Hao Liang might withdraw first.
If the mountain doesn't come to me,
I'll go to the mountain.
Yibai, I like you.
Be my girlfriend.
I'm willing to watch sunrise and sunset with you.
Girls like this?
Of course.
This is my secret weapon
for a successful confession tomorrow.
Watch and learn.
Let me watch it again.
Yibai, I like you.
Be my girlfriend.
I'm willing to watch sunrise and sunset with you.
These
are the budget details of our project.
If you
have no questions,
let's start looking into
the situation of the place of origin.
Isn't this
USB drive yours personally?
This is a department's shared USB drive.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just asking.
Fire corals
contain highly toxic cnidocytes.
Contact with the skin
will cause a burning sensation
and lead to swollen lymph nodes.
During the full moon,
fragments of fire corals
float to the sea surface,
forming...
Yibai, I like you.
Be my girlfriend.
I'm willing to watch sunrise and sunset with you.
What's going on?
I don't know.
The USB drive belongs to Yibai.
Sorry, Mr. Gong.
But I'm not very clear
about the situation today.
What exactly is going on?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You gave the USB drive to Yongkang.
In this video,
somebody confessed to you.
You say you don't know?
Mr. Gong.
You know
what kind of person I am.
There's no way I can't distinguish between professional and personal matters.
But what happened today
is my fault.
I didn't check the materials well.
Okay, stop talking.
I know.
The situation with Dazuo
before your wedding
was a blow to you.
But I hope
you'll be cautious about such important matters as marriage.
Mr. Gong, I really didn't...
It's good
that someone likes you.
But I think this expression
is inappropriate.
Moreover, it happened in front of
such important business partners.
How will they see us now?
Look.
Owen hasn't been
affected by this little incident.
Look at your attitude.
Yes.
Later, apologize to him
in private.
What?
Okay.
Also,
the guy
who confessed to you,
I don't care who he is,
but you need to handle it properly.
I hope
it won't happen again.
Okay.
Owen.
Let's conclude our discussion here for today.
Okay.
Alright.
Owen.
Yibai has some details
to discuss with you.
Sure.
Okay.
You two talk.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
I apologize
because I thought
that the USB drive was your personal one,
not for the content inside.
Okay.
Do you want to know my answer now?
First,
I don't plan to date now.
Second,
I can't be a cradle snatcher.
Third,
I'm not interested in you at all.
Do you hear me?
Need me to elaborate?
Do you want to hear my answer?
First,
I have enough patience to pursue you.
You can take your time to think about it.
Second,
we're only three years apart.
What's the big deal with three years?
Third,
everything can be cultivated.
I'm confident
that I can win you over.
What do you like about me?
I'll change it, okay?
I like both your strengths and weaknesses.
How will you change it?
Strengths and weaknesses?
Do you know me?
Do you know what kind of person I am?
Do you know what I hate?
Do you know if I prefer sweet or savory tofu pudding?
Do I eat tangyuan or dumplings on the Winter Solstice?
Is my staple food rice or steamed buns?
You know nothing.
Yet you're acting like
I'm indispensable.
Han Yijie.
It's funny, you know?
Glutinous rice balls.
Rice.
Sweet.
This is my answer.
I don't know if it's the same as you.
But
it doesn't matter if it's not the same.
Love is not about cloning
an identical version of oneself.
Do you know what love is?
Love is even if our perspectives don't match,
even if I don't fancy your features,
I still insist on being with you.
I may not understand you enough,
but...
But I like
the way you light up
when facing street snacks
that others disdain
when sitting by the roadside.
I like that version of you.
But what I like even more
is the vulnerability you showed
on that rainy night.
Yibai.
I want to protect you.
Give me a chance.
Okay?
I think my answer
has been clear enough.
Sorry.
Chen Yibai.
I won't give up.
M... Mr. Han,
I won't give up on this project.
Yes.
Happy cooperation.
By the way,
are you free later?
I...
Auntie Yibai, you're back.
You're eating that again?
Hello.
Is this Dai's house?
Yes.
Hello.
This is a delivery
from Cute Mengmeng.
Sorry to bother you.
Thank you.
Aunt Yibai.
I don't want to go live later.
Okay.
Call Mr. Niu
saying you want to quit.
Tell him
that you are devastated due to a breakup,
the end of the world is coming,
and you don't want to do anything.
That's not true.
What should I do?
Alright.
I'll mix some green juice for you
with a taste and color
similar to fake wasabi.
Seasonal boyfriend?
Everyone on the team knows
that Yibai's every ex-boyfriend
lasts no more than a hundred days.
So,
she has a curse
of seasonal boyfriends.
Eat more of these river shrimps.
The river shrimps here are very famous.
Okay.
So strange.
Not strange.
Her former boyfriend
also ran away because
he couldn't stand it.
Doesn't she have any other hobbies?
Yi Bai
is a somewhat famous streamer.
Streamer?
Let me show you.
Although we
specialize in nutrition,
she specializes in live streaming dark cuisine.
I was as surprised as you
when I first found out.
Take a look.
Don't mind me. Eat more.
We can order more if it's not enough.
Scroll down. There is a lot behind.
Yes, the basic step of this dish
is like this.
Hello, Dai.
Hello.
Your background is so special today.
Today,
because I wasn't streaming
at a fixed time,
I chose to go live from home
to meet everyone.
My dear fans all know that today,
Dai is challenging herself
with wasabi
as a punishment.
I truly feel sorry for her
because I know wasabi
is very spicy.
I've tried it myself.
But
the fans are very persistent.
Dai.
I'm sorry.
Let's stick to the bet.
Have you received the wasabi
I sent you?
Good.
Now, let me share
a little secret with everyone.
Because
I was worried that Dai might cheat,
I secretly
added a little something
to the wasabi.
Dai.
Can you squeeze some out
and show it to us?
Alright.
I'll mix some green juice
for you with a taste and color
similar to fake wasabi, just to be safe.
If you haven't switched it out...
That one over there.
That one looked the same.
That's right.
Yes, that's the one
I sent.
I was afraid you'd find it too spicy,
so
I added a bit of sugar to it.
So,
I have a small request.
Well,
can you
sing while eating the wasabi?
Sure.
How much should I eat?
Two centimeters.
♫Like raindrops♫
♫Falling in this sea♫
♫Just like you♫
♫Already engraved into my heart by time♫
♫Drifting♫
♫Also longing to land♫
♫Fearing that the more I desire to possess♫
♫The easier it is to lose♫
♫I'm in my own sky♫
♫Waiting for the north wind, a beginning, and an end♫
♫A brief pause♫
♫Just to have it once again♫
♫I am a drifting constellation♫
♫You block me from falling into a black hole♫
♫Embraced in weariness♫
♫Only then is it a good dream♫
Dai
is really amazing.
Come on.
Dear viewers in my livestream,
go to her livestream,
follow her, and give her a like.
That's all
for today's livestream.
See you next time.
Wait.
I have something to say.
Go ahead.
The wasabi just now
is the punishment for losing the battle.
Thank you, Cute Mengmeng.
Your appearance
made me realize who I am.
In the past,
I used to think
I was the queen of Qixiu,
but it turns out
I just didn't encounter
strong opponents.
Your appearance
made me see
my shortcomings.
The second bite
is to apologize to my fans.
Before the livestream,
I wanted to be a deserter.
I even thought
about changing the wasabi Cute Mengmeng gave me.
But I thought of you guys.
For the past two years,
you've...
You've been with me,
supported me,
and transformed me from an unknown
into a somewhat
popular streamer.
I can't let you down.
From now on,
even if only one person
watches my livestream,
I'll continue to sing
and become a better Dai.
Come at me if you dare.
Go easy on Dai.
I will unfollow Cute Mengmeng.
Join me if you think the same.
Cute Mengmeng.
Please disappear immediately.
And in the end,
I want to punish myself.
In the last live competition,
I was distracted
because of something else.
I didn't do my best.
This is disrespect to my opponent,
my fans,
and myself.
From now on,
I won't give up on myself
and won't blame anyone anymore.
I want to cherish
everything I have now
and work harder.
Enough.
No need to eat more. Dai.
It's okay.
Hao Liang must be
someone others look up to.
-Great! Great!
-Aunt Yibai.
I did it.
I'm about to cry. Great.
[Zhu Yi]
Hello?
You're awesome.
I have both good and bad news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Just tell me.
We've overcome all the difficulties.
Okay.
The bad news is
Mr. Niu wants you
to extend
each livestream by thirty minutes.
Why?
Because of the good news.
You set an unprecedented
click-through rate today.
The backstage messages are overflowing.
Thousands of comments are cheering for you.
You've turned adversity into an advantage.
Mr. Niu finally understands
even a great outsider
can't compare to the loyalty of your fans
who have followed you for years