(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed
all guidelines for young actors.)
Do you really think I'm the one
who sent the video...
to Su A?
I think it's a possibility.
- And why is that?
- Because you want Su A...
to believe that I killed Ki Beom.
But you killed Cha Ki Beom.
Honey.
He took his last breath
right after you left.
There was no time to call
911 or anything.
Then why did you lie to me?
You were already blaming yourself
as it was,
and I didn't want to make things
harder on you.
(Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra)
It wasn't your fault.
I'll make sure of it.
I told you to let go of your guilt.
Cha Ki Beom...
It was bound to happen.
What have I done?
I killed Ki Beom.
Oh, no. How can I ever face Su A?
I...
will protect you...
no matter what it takes.
Jin Tae Seok...
knows my every move.
But how?
So Young Chae is plotting something
behind my back?
The nerve of her.
But then again...
Credit where credit is due.
Who cares about the truth, anyway?
What matters is
that Cha Jung Won believes...
Han Hye Ra killed her father.
Anyway, where is
that brat Young Chae?
Young Chae!
Why are you looking for me?
What is it?
Don't you have something
to say to me?
If you want to know something,
just ask.
What's with you?
I'm just going to have a beer
and get some sleep.
Right.
To truly survive,
you must fool even your own mother.
You have to be willing to betray
even your own mother to get ahead.
That's my girl.
(Cha Ki Beom, Born: April 7, 1966,
Date of Death: November 28, 2025)
Ki Beom...
How could you leave me
all alone like this?
I lived only for you.
So what am I supposed to do now?
You were born with a restless heart,
like a girl
with spring fever year-round.
You should have lived
true to your nature.
Why'd you settle down
with a guy like me?
Because just looking at you...
makes me feel like that girl again.
What can I do when you still
make my heart flutter?
I make this vow...
before my father,
who loved his guitar and music...
and was full of laughter and love.
If there's anyone happier than me,
I dare them to step forward!
- I will cast off this life of lies.
- Stop smiling so wide.
- You're going to split your face.
- As his daughter, Cha Jung Won,
in my father's name,
I will make the Kunhyang family pay.
Ki Beom...
On the wings
with which I once yearned to fly,
I will affix
the blade of vengeance...
and plunge it
into Han Hye Ra's heart.
Into her bleeding, dying heart,
I will carve my father's name.
I swear it.
(Cha Ki Beom, Born: April 7, 1966,
Date of Death: November 28, 2025)
(A man of music, laughter, and love)
(Our memories with you
will live on forever.)
(I love you, Dad.)
(Rest in peace, Ki Beom.)
(Cha Ki Beom, Born: April 7, 1966,
Date of Death: November 28, 2025)
Ki Beom.
I know I don't have the right...
to say that I'm sorry.
In the next life,
and the one after that,
if by some chance
you happen to meet me,
act like you don't know me.
(Cha Ki Beom, Born: April 7, 1966,
Date of Death: November 28, 2025)
Or, rather,
don't even remember me.
What was that?
You let Ahn Ji Na
take the memory card from you?
What kind of reporter are you,
Reporter Ma?
You have zero professionalism!
I'm hanging up.
So, being Gong Nan Sook's daughter
gave you some nerve, did it?
Just like your mother?
I've been through a lot, you know.
I had to pretend
that I was Cha Jung Won, then Su A.
During that time,
I figured out how I needed to live.
And how will you live?
This world doesn't play fair.
There are no permanent allies.
I learned to take things first
and crush people...
before they ever had the chance.
Just like you, Chairman.
You've got a lot of nerve.
That girl, Cha Jung Won,
may have nothing,
but she's filled with the shame
of living as a murderer's daughter,
and she carries the scars of being
abandoned by her mother as a child.
What about you?
I have Gong Nan Sook's blood.
What do you want?
- Don't do this, Young Sun!
- Let go of me!
- Young Sun!
- I said to let go!
And?
I sent that video to Jung Won.
Cha Jung Won?
- You sent it to Su A?
- By now, Jung Won...
is convinced Vice Chairman Han
was the one who killed Cha Ki Beom.
So?
You wouldn't want this going public,
would you?
Were you there?
Does that matter?
If this video gets out,
Vice Chairman Han,
the person you love the most,
will be ruined.
And at the same time,
Kunhyang's name will be ruined.
This is blackmail, isn't it?
Let's call it a deal.
I assume I'm buying the video, then.
And what do you want?
Make Vice President Jin Se Hoon
change his mind.
Make him forget that pathetic girl
Cha Jung Won.
Make him accept me,
the real Joo Young Chae,
Kunhyang's rightful daughter-in-law.
Winning Se Hoon is your problem.
How dare you bring this video
and try to pull a stunt like this?
Should I send this to a reporter
for a daily newspaper?
You think you can do that?
Try me.
You'll regret underestimating me.
Mom?
Wasn't I the one
who shot this video?
Haven't you ever heard of copyright?
You can't just use my property
without my permission.
Gong Nan Sook.
You filmed this behind my back?
Behind your back?
I just filmed it and never told you.
Who would do business
that takes a loss?
I feared you wouldn't finish it,
so I prepared to handle it myself.
So, what's it going to be?
Should I send this to the reporter?
I also know
what happened after this.
I know everything
that happened next.
All right. I believe...
you're not only done
with my daughter,
but also with me.
So I guess
I'll leak everything then.
Starting with this first clip.
Chairman Gong, why are you acting
so out of character?
Why are you acting this way?
We're family, aren't we?
That's right.
That's exactly my point.
Family shouldn't use knives
to threaten to stab one another.
It can't get any more dysfunctional.
I couldn’t agree with you more.
Unlike Young Chae, I don't care
if Jin Se Hoon loves her or not.
You want her name to remain
as Se Hoon's wife on paper?
Meaning, Joo Young Chae will remain
as Jin Se Hoon's wife?
See? We're on the same wavelength.
We just click.
(Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra)
(Kunhyang Group)
Should I get rid of the bug?
No, leave the tea.
It tastes better now
that it's cooled off.
Slow down.
Here, have some water.
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
Why are you eating like
you haven't eaten in days?
You don't know what you have
until it's gone.
Thinking that Ki Beom is no longer
with us...
makes me feel so empty,
no matter how much I eat.
You have to be strong.
You've got me.
I'm here for you, too.
We keep the departed in our hearts,
but those of us here have to go on,
right?
I'll reopen this restaurant tonight.
You need to rest.
You'll make yourself sick
at this rate.
Goodness,
I can't tell who the mother is here.
I'm more worried about you.
What are you going to do now?
Live with me now.
Stay away from the Kunhyang house.
(Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra)
It's Joo Ha Neul.
I should have visited you first.
Please, have a seat.
It's simple and neat.
Minimalism?
It's very you, CEO Joo.
Regarding the funeral,
I only did what was right.
A lot of people fail to do
what's right.
And that's not all.
Let's remember who Cha Ki Beom was.
You believe he wasn't the killer,
but your father...
I'd rather...
we not talk about that.
I was just complimenting you
on your ability to forgive.
My apologies
if that made you uncomfortable.
So, why did you ask to see me?
Thank you for honoring
my request that day.
You asked me to help Jung Won
serve as the chief mourner.
Why did you do that?
I wanted the funeral to be quiet,
at the very least.
And...
I felt Su A should at least
see her father off one last time.
That could have been...
a major blow to you, Vice Chairman.
If word had gotten out...
You don't think I considered that?
Su A, or rather,
are you saying you cared more
about Jung Won?
Or...
was it guilt over Ki Beom?
And what about you, CEO Joo?
Do you also believe
that I pushed Ki Beom?
Isn't this your phone,
Vice Chairman Han?
Does Su A...
know?
But she saw the video.
I don't know who sent it,
but that alone proves...
- that you pushed Cha Ki Beom...
- It was an accident.
He was clearly still alive.
I should've stayed to make sure
someone called 911.
Fine.
It is my fault.
I won't deny it.
What do you intend to do now?
What are you asking, exactly?
You know that Jung Won is Su A.
My daughter-in-law
turned out to be my daughter.
Naturally, I'll have to welcome her
into the Kunhyang family.
It'll be difficult for now,
but I'll take it one step at a time.
For now,
are you planning to hide...
the fact that Jung Won
is your daughter?
You seem more concerned
about Su A than I am.
Just giving birth
doesn't make you a parent.
When it comes to my Su A,
I don't deserve to be her mother.
What am I to make of that?
What she needs right now...
is someone she can trust,
more than a mother.
You've been reunited after 25 years.
What Jung Won needs most
right now...
is a sincere apology
and acceptance from you.
What good would that do now?
As if that...
would heal the pain I caused her.
There's nothing I can do for Su A.
It's not like Ki Beom is coming back
from the dead.
Su A...
has to become tougher and stronger.
She has to live as if she never
had a mother to begin with.
CEO Joo.
I was hoping...
you could help.
(Chairman Jin Tae Seok)
(Kunhyang Group)
Gong Nan Sook and her daughter...
dare to threaten me?
Secretary Yoon,
escort the Vice Chairman.
- We have to go, ma'am.
- No.
I'm waiting here
until the ambulance arrives.
Secretary Yoon!
We have to go.
This way, ma'am.
You have to save Ki Beom.
He's Su A's father.
Please, Tae Seok.
I promise. I'll ensure he's saved.
Manager Hwang, find out
if the ambulance is on its way.
Yes, sir.
Absolutely no one can find out.
Especially not...
Hye Ra.
Why did you have to go
and do something I didn't ask?
I thought you told me
to manage my own life.
But there's more to that video
than what I’ve seen, isn't there?
- Am I right?
- More of what?
Look, here is seafood!
That hits the spot.
I'm going to do whatever it takes
to put you by Jin Se Hoon's side,
so don't waste your time
catching feelings.
You do what you have to, Mom.
I'll do what suits me.
What? Why, you little brat!
Because I'm going to win
Jin Se Hoon's heart.
Chef Hong, what's going to happen
between Jin Se Hoon and me?
Call him "Grandma."
That was delicious, Chef Hong.
Honestly.
Grandma,
can you tell me what you see
for Young Chae and Se Hoon?
She'll get one thing,
and won't get the other.
So says Grandma.
What will she get
and what won't she get?
Will Young Chae become
Kunhyang family's daughter-in-law?
Your soup is getting cold.
I'll go heat it up for you.
He always dodges
the important questions.
Darn it.
I heard that wasn't
the full video, right?
I thought you, Manager Gu,
were like a brother
or an uncle to me...
and someone I could count on.
I have to leave myself an out,
you know.
You know how Chairman Gong is.
You should have given me a heads-up.
I'll let the video
sent to Jung Won slide.
But do you know how humiliated I was
in front of Chairman Jin Tae Seok?
What are you talking about?
Young Chae, did you send that video
to Jung Won?
Whatever.
Do you realize what you've done?
You've scarred Jung Won for life.
She believes the mother she met
after 25 years harmed her father.
I was just telling her the truth.
I hear what she saw
wasn't the full video.
- There's more to the story, right?
- I don't know.
Gong Nan Sook knows everything.
So stop asking me.
You're getting on my nerves.
What do you mean, how do I know?
Because I saw it.
I saw what happened
on the gallery steps.
I heard the video Young Chae sent
to Jung Won wasn't the full video.
Is that true?
Are you asking if Han Hye Ra harmed
Cha Ki Beom, and what happened next?
Is that what you're curious about?
Yes.
You're CEO Joo, after all.
The only son of Gong Nan Sook,
and the one to succeed me...
and restore the glory
of the Gong family,
and the one who'll lead
Kunhyang Group.
Just tell me the truth.
Don't even think about lying.
Why were you there?
I got a tip
that Han Hye Ra and Cha Ki Beom met.
You know I can easily
get that kind of intel, don't you?
So you followed them?
To be honest,
I was following Jin Tae Seok.
- What do you mean?
- Jin Tae Seok was tailing them too.
I had a hunch he wouldn't just leave
Cha Ki Beom or Han Hye Ra alone.
So you weren't worried.
You just went to watch the show?
I suppose I did.
There's nothing more entertaining
than watching a good fight.
What did you see?
What you saw in the video.
That's all there was.
They were arguing back and forth
about something,
and then Han Hye Ra suddenly
shoved Cha Ki Beom.
- You saw it with your own eyes?
- I'm telling you I did.
Then you should have stopped her.
I was a little too far away
to intervene.
I was afraid Chairman Jin Tae Seok
would cause a scene, so I hung back,
hiding while I watched.
What happened next?
Then why was Cha Ki Beom alone
when Jung Won and I got there?
Han Hye Ra must've panicked and run.
It looked like no one called 911.
I came straight home
because I didn't want to get involved.
I'm sure Chairman Jin Tae Seok
handled the rest.
- That's everything I know. I swear.
- Madam Gong.
"Madam Gong" again?
What? Do you think I'm lying?
This just makes me more certain
that you're hiding something.
What on earth are you hiding?
I'm sorry.
Did you figure out that I met
with Vice Chairman Han?
I just had a feeling.
Why would she ask
to see you, Ha Neul?
Sorry, I mean, CEO Joo.
Just call me Ha Neul.
I'm back to being Cha Jung Won now.
- But still...
- You can still call me Ha Neul.
Just answer my question.
She has to accept
her daughter-in-law...
as her daughter now,
and I guess that's not easy.
And what about my father's death?
She blames herself for that.
She's overwhelmed with guilt.
- She's too ashamed to face you.
- She'd rather look the other way.
She doesn't want to admit
that she was wrong.
She probably doesn't even care...
why I had to pretend
to be Joo Young Chae...
and become her daughter-in-law
in the first place.
So what do you want to do now?
That woman is responsible
for my father's death.
I'm going to make her pay.
It might not be entirely
Vice Chairman Han's fault.
What are you talking about?
We both saw the video.
But what if there's more
after what we saw?
What if the truth has been
covered up?
Jin Tae Seok.
I guess you'll never be able
to defy me again.
How satisfying.
Young Chae sent me the video?
And Chairman Gong Nan Sook
was the one who filmed it?
There might be more to the story.
Chairman Gong Nan Sook and
Jin Tae Seok might be involved.
I need to find out
exactly what the truth is.
Then I'll decide what to do next.
But one thing won't change.
That woman, Han Hye Ra,
is the reason my father is dead.
And I will never forgive her
for that.
(Jin Se Hoon)
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Transferring to voicemail.
- Young Chae?
- How did you know it was me?
You sound thrilled.
What do you want?
I guess you were expecting Cha Jung Won,
the one impersonating me.
Just get to the point. I'm busy.
Where are you?
Maybe we could get a drink.
With you? Have you lost your mind?
We need to get to know each other,
don't we?
I'm annoyed waiting for my girl
in front of her house.
You think I have time for you?
I don't have time for that.
Wait, Se Hoon.
He's outside Cha Jung Won's house?
Fly!
Fly, Jung Won, fly!
- Fly!
- It really feels like I'm flying.
I still can't believe it.
That my dad is really gone.
Get your hand off her!
Se Hoon,
I know you're having a hard time.
But Jung Won is the one
who's hurting the most right now.
Let's not make things worse for her.
Look at you, trying every trick
to steal her from me.
Cut the considerate act.
Come here.
Don't do this, Se Hoon.
Don't you dare treat her like that!
Stop it, Ha Neul.
I'm still her husband.
Overnight,
the woman I love became my sister.
And you expect me
to just accept that?
What kind of psycho would do that?
I know it hurts,
but this is reality.
So now you think you're free
to move in on my woman...
and put your arm on her shoulder
whenever you want?
I'm just as confused as you are.
But...
from now on, it will be difficult
for her to be your wife,
or even your woman.
- You!
- Stop it!
Se Hoon, talk to me.
What am I supposed to do?
Do you really want
to see me lose my mind?
I'm so sorry, Se Hoon.
Then let's just run away together.
As long as I have you,
I'll give up the Kunhyang family,
Kunhyang Group, and everything.
Se Hoon.
Listen.
To get revenge on Han Hye Ra,
the birth mother who abandoned me,
I used you.
You can...
curse, despise,
and spit on a woman like me.
I can take it all.
No. I can't live without you...
Young Chae.
No, I don't care
if your name is Jung Won or Su A.
All I need is you.
Please...
Don't leave me.
Just the sight of cognac
puts me on edge.
- Honey.
- Stop right there. Don't go there.
I'm not jumping the gun.
What about you?
What do you think we should do
about Su A?
Me? Of course,
I'll go with whatever you want.
She's really Su A this time.
What if we brought her
into the Kunhyang family right now?
Someone as delicate...
and soft-hearted as you?
Even if she is your own daughter,
it's a tragic, ill-fated connection.
You're right.
After she found out
I was her birth mother,
she joined our family on purpose
to get her revenge on me.
She made a mockery of our family.
And that's not all, is it?
It will be hard for her
to forgive you, too.
I killed Su A's father,
Ki Beom.
Tae Seok.
Please send Su A abroad.
So we never have to meet again.
And so she won't get entangled
with Se Hoon again.
Are you serious?
It's the only way...
for both Su A and me to survive.
From now on, I'm Cha Jung Won.
I'm going to live
as Han Hye Ra's daughter.
(A Graceful Liar)
How about you go abroad
for a few years?
Are you afraid your world...
will come crashing down
if people learn who I am?
Jung Won went
to the Kunhyang house uninvited?
Who on earth
does Cha Jung Won take after...
to be so driven and decisive?
I will marry Cha Jung Won.
How can you marry
your own mother's daughter?
Mother, Father,
I need you two to get a divorce.
I know you saw everything happen
in front of the gallery.
I am merely a shadow.
I do not think, judge, or decide.
I came back to the Kunhyang family
to find the truth about my father,
find the real killer,
and make them pay.
Anyone threatening
the Kunhyang family is an enemy.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)