(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed
all guidelines for young actors.)
(Episode 48)
Let's have breakfast.
How is the battery dead already?
(Vice President Jin Se Hoon)
Young Chae? Where are you?
(Naeil Nursing Home)
Se Hoon is...
like a mischievous little boy.
He gets sulky easily,
but he gets over it just as fast.
And he's an amazing cook.
Sometimes he's like a boy,
and other times, he's a man.
He's full of charm.
Now that I think about it,
he really takes after you.
I'm so sorry, Mother.
I don't think I can keep
the promise I made...
to never let Se Hoon feel lonely.
Why can't you keep it?
You're still thinking about divorce?
Not in front of your mother.
Let's talk outside.
You came all the way here
to apologize to my mom?
Are we divorced already?
Just tell me why.
Don't tell me
you have some terminal illness.
Did you rack up a huge debt
behind my back?
How much do you need?
Three million?
Or ten million?
- I'll take care of it.
- That's not it.
Is it...
because of Ha Neul?
I'm Su A.
I've been living as Cha Jung Won
since I was seven.
What?
I'm Vice Chairman Han's
biological daughter.
That's more than enough reason
for us to get a divorce,
isn't it?
That...
makes no sense.
I can't even pretend to believe that.
It's the truth.
Chairman Jin and Vice Chairman Han
both know.
So, you're not Joo Young Chae,
but Cha Jung Won...
No...
You're my mother's daughter, Su A.
You married me while hiding that?
That's right.
I deceived you.
Why?
Why would you tell a lie like that?
At first,
it was a favor for Young Chae.
I was just filling in
the blind date for her.
Did you plan this...
from that moment?
To deceive me?
You saw past me being
Chairman Gong Nan Sook's daughter,
and you saw me for me,
and you believed in my potential
as a future designer...
for Kunhyang Fashion.
I was so grateful for that.
What about the new designer contest
at Kunhyang?
That was
Joo Young Chae's application.
Young Chae stole my design book
and submitted it as her own.
The day she was meant to meet you
for the blind date,
her boyfriend, Park Kyung Shin,
was hospitalized for
an overdose on sleeping pills.
That's how it all started.
So I became Joo Young Chae.
Then, Chairman Gong Nan Sook...
and Ha Neul knew about
this all along?
They believed your marriage
to Young Chae...
was crucial for the future
of both families.
Did that give you the right
to keep lying...
to the guy
who was head over heels for you?
Did you even care
that you were hurting me?
The more you cherished and loved me,
the more guilty I felt.
- That's why I was going to end it.
- Then why...
Why did you let it get this far?
What am I supposed to do now?
As much as I felt guilty
about hurting you,
my need for revenge
against Vice Chairman Han...
for abandoning my dad and me
was stronger.
Then you should've kept it a secret!
You should've stayed as my wife,
the daughter-in-law to Kunhyang,
and taken revenge
on Vice Chairman Han!
I didn't hear anything.
I don't know anything.
- I can't give up on you.
- Denying it won't change the facts.
We're siblings.
How can we stay married?
For what I've done wrong,
I'll spend the rest of my life
atoning for it as your sister.
How can we be brother and sister?
We're not even blood-related.
I know you need time.
There's no other way...
to make things right again.
I don't care
whether you're Young Chae or Su A.
You are my woman. My wife.
That will never change.
What were you thinking,
revealing you're Joo Young Chae?
Have you decided to defy me?
It's my life.
Stop telling me what to do.
I'm sick and tired of this charade.
And...
And?
I'll need to be Joo Young Chae again
to seduce Jin Se Hoon.
You're talking nonsense again.
Se Hoon and Jung Won are married.
Hey. I'll make them get divorced.
Do you think Kunhyang will allow it,
now that they're siblings?
Se Hoon isn't the type
to just do whatever he's told.
Ha Neul, be honest with yourself.
If Jin Se Hoon falls for me,
that's good for you too, right?
- You should be cheering.
- Don't play with people's hearts.
You're meant to fall for each other
and then share your feelings.
Love isn't something
you can just take by force.
Whatever. You're so annoying
that I can't even look at you.
That's enough.
There's no need to overthink this.
Ha Neul,
you like Cha Jung Won, don't you?
Then just go for it.
A win for you, Young Chae, and me.
A win-win-win for all of us.
After Se Hoon gets a divorce,
you'll make him marry Young Chae?
And I have to marry Jung Won?
- Exactly.
- You want to have it all again?
That sounds just like you,
Madam Gong.
That brat...
Hello, Ms. Jo. What's going on?
Mr. Cha is meeting
with Vice Chairman Han?
What are you talking about?
Why is Dad meeting
with Vice Chairman Han?
I snuck a peek at Ki Beom's phone
this morning.
He just couldn't put his phone down
and was so restless and fidgety...
that I knew something was up.
Why did she want to meet him?
She said it was about Su A.
Is it because Dad didn't tell her
I was Su A?
I have a bad feeling about this.
If Jin Tae Seok finds out,
he'll make a fuss.
Maybe I should have followed him.
You can't leave
this place unattended, though.
That's why I asked CEO Joo Ha Neul
to go check on them...
in case I couldn't
get a hold of you.
He just left a moment ago.
Where are Dad
and Vice Chairman Han meeting?
Where did Ha Neul go?
Han Hye Ra and Cha Ki Beom
are meeting today.
Why would Ha Neul go there?
If you're that curious, go find out.
Why should I? No way.
If anyone's going, you should go.
That girl...
She can't do anything on her own.
It's useless to even
give her a chance.
I have a bad feeling Jin Tae Seok
is going to cause a huge mess today.
Manager Gu!
Yes, ma'am. The car is ready.
Where shall I take you, Chairman?
Have I ever told you where to go?
Just drive.
Why did you ask to meet?
Why didn't you tell me who Su A was?
- You found out who she is?
- How could you hide that from me?
Especially when Young Chae was
pretending to be Su A.
You should've told me first.
A real mother...
would've recognized her own child.
How could I guess my daughter-in-law
was my own daughter?
She chose to be my daughter-in-law,
knowing who I was.
And you knew but didn't stop her?
I found out later.
And by then it was
too late to stop her.
No,
you didn't stop her on purpose.
- What?
- You wanted her furious with me...
and to get revenge
on your behalf, didn't you?
That's not true!
I was afraid Jin Tae Seok...
would hurt Jung Won
if he found out she was Su A.
So I couldn't bring myself
to tell you.
Was Su A the one who told you?
She did.
My daughter was right before me,
and I didn't even recognize her.
Even after she became
my daughter-in-law.
Don't abandon...
our Su A again.
Why would I abandon her?
I didn't abandon Su A
25 years ago either.
Stop making excuses.
That story about your accident...
and not being able to get Su A
25 years ago...
was all a lie, wasn't it?
- It's not.
- The accident was a lie,
and your long hospital stay
was probably a lie, too.
No, it wasn't.
And that accident...
was caused on purpose
by Jin Tae Seok...
to keep you with him.
Right?
Am I wrong?
No.
Just because you run from it,
doesn't mean the truth will change.
Mommy!
Ki Beom.
I'm so sorry.
I don't deserve to live.
Don't do this, Hye Ra!
- Don't! It's dangerous.
- Let me go!
Please, don't do this!
Don't do this, Young Sun!
Please, just don't
Let go of me! I said to let go!
Ki Beom.
Ki Beom... No, Ki Beom.
Ki Beom, open your eyes...
Please, Ki Beom...
What do I do? Ki Beom!
Protect...
our Su A...
from Jin Tae Seok.
Please...
No!
Ki Beom?
What do I do? Somebody!
Secretary Yoon!
Ki Beom...
This got easier than expected.
Everyone will think
Hye Ra killed Cha Ki Beom.
Ki Beom...
Are you all right, ma'am?
Save him, please.
I must've lost my mind.
He's still alive.
Call 911!
- Ki Beom.
- I already called 911.
- Why are you here?
- We'll talk about that later.
- Did you really call 911?
- I told you I did.
Call them again! Tell them to hurry!
Hye Ra, calm down.
Secretary Yoon,
escort the Vice Chairman.
- We have to go, ma'am.
- No.
I'm waiting here
until the ambulance arrives.
Secretary Yoon!
We have to go.
This way, ma'am.
You have to save Ki Beom.
He's Su A's father.
Please, Tae Seok.
I promise. I'll ensure he's saved.
Manager Hwang, find out
if the ambulance is on its way.
Yes, sir.
Hey, make sure
you're getting all of this.
Wait a minute.
It wasn't Jin Tae Seok,
but Han Hye Ra
who did that to Cha Ki Beom?
Things didn't have to
get this interesting.
Should we pack it up now?
Not yet. I want to see
how Jin Tae Seok cleans this up.
The game's not over until it's over.
- Such a waste that he's gone.
- You scared me.
Grandma, is that you?
You should have stopped it.
Stop what? I didn't do anything.
The heavens are angry.
My gosh, you really are gifted.
I didn't say a word,
so how did you know
something happened?
You didn't bring any food with you,
did you?
Why do you think I'm here?
How should I know?
You're starting to freak me out.
Since you're here,
you might as well make some dinner.
I believe
you have something to tell me.
Look, Se Hoon.
You seem really upset right now.
Why don't we talk tomorrow
after you've calmed down a little?
I can't even think straight
right now.
Is the woman I married...
really your daughter,
Joo Young Chae?
Why is Young Chae claiming
she's Cha Jung Won,
I mean, Su A,
Vice Chairman Han's child?
Listen.
I don't feel the least bit sorry...
for Han Hye Ra and Jin Tae Seok.
But when it comes to you, Se Hoon,
I do feel a little bad.
I had my reasons.
Whatever your reasons were,
marriage is built on trust
between the two families, isn't it?
How could you, of all people,
do this to me,
the heir to the Kunhyang Group?
Did you take me for a fool?
Of course not. Not to the man
who will soon be...
the owner of Kunhyang Group.
To me, you will always
and forever be my son-in-law.
But you're saying
Young Chae is fake.
How is that even possible?
Then where's the real Young Chae?
Right here.
I'm Joo Young Chae, brother.
Not anymore. From now on,
Se Hoon.
You...
pretended to be Cha Jung Won
and said you were Su A...
Is she really Joo Young Chae?
That's right. She's the real one
this time. And that's final.
She's my daughter, Joo Young Chae,
and your legal wife.
What do you mean, "my wife?"
I just have to take back
my rightful place.
I am your wife, Se Hoon.
We can start getting
to know each other now.
Because I...
really like you, Se Hoon.
Let me make myself clear.
I don't care
if she is the fake Joo Young Chae.
I only have one wife.
So don't get your hopes up.
Hey. It's not going to be easy
to win over Jin Se Hoon.
No.
That just fires me up even more.
I will make Jin Se Hoon mine
no matter what.
Dad.
Dad!
Don't do this, Young Sun!
- Please, just don't!
- Let me go!
Did you see Vice Chairman Han
and Cha Ki Beom meet?
What happened?
I saw everything.
Something huge is about to happen.
Did someone die?
Goodness.
No way. Are you serious?
Was it Han Hye Ra? Or Cha Ki Beom?
- Come on, what happened?
- You'll find out soon enough.
Chairman, we have a serious problem.
I didn't mean to impose,
but now I'm in your debt.
I'll be sure to repay this kindness.
He's furious.
They say a woman makes the man.
You just need to make him like you.
Then his "I'll repay this kindness"
will actually mean something.
Don't worry. I've got this.
Now that's my girl.
Here, drink this.
Where's Ki Beom?
Did you check
if the ambulance arrived?
I'm sorry.
I was busy getting you out of there.
I think I lost my phone.
Call emergency services and find out
which hospital they took Ki Beom to.
Yes, right away.
That won't be necessary.
Ki Beom...
Is Ki Beom okay?
He's alive, isn't he?
Ki Beom...
Did something bad happen?
By the time the paramedics arrived,
he was already gone.
No, that can't be.
I'm sure I saw him breathing.
He was alive.
The paramedics
confirmed it themselves.
They said there was nothing
they could do.
Oh, no...
What do I do? What have I done?
I think I killed Ki Beom.
What do I do, Tae Seok?
- I have to go see for myself.
- Are you out of your mind?
You'll be the prime suspect.
You can't just show up there.
No, I have to go find out myself.
Hye Ra!
(Kunhyang Hospital)
What happened to Ki Beom?
Where is Ki Beom?
(Mortuary)
Honey, why are you here?
Open your eyes.
Let's go home.
I'm here.
The one who's loved you
her entire life,
your Mi Hyang, is here.
Why are you so cold...
Ki Beom. This can't be happening.
This can't be happening, honey...
Honey, no!
No, honey...
(Viewing Room)
Young Sun.
You met with Ki Beom, didn't you?
- Mi Hyang.
- You killed him, didn't you?
Please, calm down.
Young Sun, if he hadn't met you,
this never would have happened
to my Ki Beom.
You're the one who killed him!
What do you think you're doing?
She is suffering right now, too.
Please stop with these accusations.
You're Chairman Jin Tae Seok,
aren't you?
If it wasn't Young Sun,
then maybe it was you.
This won't bring Dad back, Mom.
Ma'am.
You met with my dad...
in front of the gallery, didn't you?
Why would my dad
have an accident there?
Tell me what happened.
She...
spoke with him briefly
and then left.
We just found out ourselves
that Cha Ki Beom fell to his death.
Come on, let's go.
It must be hard for Mom
to be with Dad all alone.
I found this on the stairs
at the gallery.
I feel like I've seen this before.
Someone must have dropped it,
and it looks broken.
If we get it fixed,
we might find out whose it is.
- Don't do this, Young Sun!
- Let go of me!
- Young Sun!
- I said to let go!
It was Han Hye Ra.
I knew it.
Manager Gu is so kind.
Why did you want to meet here?
I was going to the funeral.
You killed him, didn't you?
My dad.
Don't even try to deny it.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
When Ki Beom tried to save me,
he lost his footing.
Did you do it on purpose?
Because I revealed that I'm Su A?
Were you afraid the world would find out
your daughter-in-law was your daughter?
Did you want to hide it?
Is that why you went after my dad,
the one person
who could prove I'm Su A?
He was definitely still alive.
I should have stayed with him
until the paramedics arrived.
He was still alive?
And you just left him there?
Did you really do that?
It's all my fault.
I should have...
stayed with Ki Beom until the end.
How could you do such a thing?
You killed my father.
That's not all.
I abandoned you, too,
Su A.
But you said you didn't abandon me.
You said there was an accident,
and that was why
you couldn't come get me.
You see, I knew.
That Tae Seok...
never wanted you.
That's not true, is it?
- That can't be true, right?
- Su A.
Don't forgive me.
Never.
You should have just died back then!
Then you wouldn't be the mother
who abandoned her seven-year-old,
or driven the father of the daughter
you just found after 25 years...
to his death.
You told me not to forgive you.
Why are you kneeling shamelessly?
I'm not asking for forgiveness.
I've only just realized...
that I chose
my ambition and my desires...
over being a mother.
Even though
you are my daughter, Su A,
this is the only time...
you will ever see me on my knees.
You're not even worth forgiving.
Then hate me to death.
Other than giving birth to you,
there's nothing I've done for you
or can do for you now.
Money?
I can give you as much of that
as you want.
If you want to be my daughter,
I'll give you that too.
But that's it.
Don't you dare try to take
what's mine, what I protect,
any of it.
This is the only way
that Su A and I...
can both survive.
(A Graceful Liar)
Why is no one here?
Where's Jo Mi Hyang and Su A?
Open the door!
You're still Joo Young Chae,
the daughter-in-law of Kunhyang.
How will we handle the fallout
if this gets out to the press?
I can't even pay my last respects?
That's ridiculous.
Someone sent Jung Won a video.
It shows them getting into a scuffle
and him falling down the stairs.
Su A believes I pushed Cha Ki Beom
down the stairs on purpose,
and that my actions
led to his death.
You did kill Cha Ki Beom.
We could've saved Dad.
But Vice Chairman Han abandoned him.
Chairman Jin left Cha Ki Beom
to die.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)