(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed all
guidelines for young actors.)
But what happens if you start
to want it for real?
What if you start wanting
to be the real Young Chae?
What will you do then?
Just because I want something,
doesn't mean I can have it.
Between Young Chae and you,
what chance
does someone like me stand?
You've got a silver tongue,
don't you?
Jung Won, are you in there?
Open the door. Jung Won!
Cha Jung Won!
"Jung Won?"
CEO Joo knows?
Joo Ha Neul, did you
and this tramp conspire...
to ruin Young Chae's marriage
to Jin Se Hoon?
It's the exact opposite.
(Victoria)
It's Young Chae.
- Give it here. I'll get it.
- She's calling for Jung Won.
If you answer, she'll hang up.
Darn it, just answer it! Hurry!
(Victoria)
Jung Won, what am I going to do?
Why? What's wrong?
That jerk, Park Kyung Shin...
He cheated on me
and left me for her.
He faked the overdose too.
That jerk.
I am not letting him
get away with this!
Tell her to get back here. Now.
Come home.
- Stop being hung up on your ex.
- No way. I'm not coming back.
I'm going to find that jerk
and kill him.
Young Chae, calm down.
- Let's talk when you get back...
- I said no!
I'll bury him, and then I'll end...
Young Chae.
Mom?
I'll kill that jerk myself.
So get back here this instant!
Hello? What's wrong with this phone?
- Young Chae. Joo Young Chae!
- You should've been more patient.
Darn it! Try calling her back now.
The number you have called
is currently unavailable...
It says her phone is off.
Darn it.
Book a flight to Paris.
The soonest one available.
Mom's not going to let this slide.
She'll come after me
and Park Kyung Shin.
Unbelievable!
That brat, Young Chae.
Doesn't she know
who the Kunhyang family is?
Does she think she can
actually get away with this?
As a friend, how could you help her
with this stunt?
And you too, CEO Joo!
You need to leave for the airport.
I'll be the one to drag
Young Chae back.
In the meantime, CEO Joo,
you keep a close eye on this one.
I'll watch her.
You.
By the time I get back,
if you get found out,
you're finished.
Mom, tuck me in.
You're still such a baby,
aren't you?
Is this for Joo Young Chae?
The emerald set?
Yes.
But why are there two...
Is one for me?
You're not a big fan of emeralds.
Exactly. I prefer sexy rubies.
You think I don't know my daughter?
I know, right?
It's for me.
- That's not your style.
- Yes, it is.
No, it's not.
Your style is simple, yet elegant.
Your eyes are getting heavy.
Come on, I'll tuck you in.
If I sleep in here with you tonight,
Dad will be mad, won't he?
No, you'll be in trouble with me.
- Come here.
- You're impossible.
Are you still this crazy about him?
My Su A would be...
around 32 by now.
Older than Se Mi,
and the same age as Joo Young Chae.
I wonder how much she resented me
growing up.
Where she is and what she's doing
with her life.
If she's even still alive.
Do you think Young Chae
will be okay?
She'll get the scolding of her life
and be dragged back,
but she'll still live
as Joo Young Chae...
whether she likes it or not.
When Young Chae comes back, you...
I'll have to get off the stage
once the play is over.
You can end this right now.
If you want, I'll help you.
You should just be a good son
and a good brother.
Why are you worried about me?
Because I feel responsible
for not stopping you, though I knew.
And why didn't you stop me?
Was it because you wanted Young Chae
to marry Jin Se Hoon smoothly?
I can't deny that.
But just so my sister
can have a secure marriage,
I have no intention
of supporting your charade.
I'm still trying to figure out
how to resolve this...
without you or Young Chae
getting hurt.
Stay out of it.
Young Chae and I
made this choice together.
If Young Chae comes back,
we'll decide what happens next.
One way or another.
So I'm just supposed to watch?
You're telling me
to just be a bystander?
I'm asking for your respect.
For Young Chae, and for me.
(Paris, France)
I'll search every corner of Paris.
If you'd just rest here,
Chairman Gong...
I'm looking for my daughter.
How can I sit back and do nothing?
This is killing me. Here, take it.
Find her.
- Nothing?
- Over there.
All right.
Excuse me, miss.
Are you from Korea? Korean?
- Yes.
Good. Have you seen this person?
It's my daughter, Joo Young Chae.
- Victoria?
- Yes, Victoria!
They know her. When did you see her?
- I saw her here yesterday.
- Yesterday?
I heard she was leaving for Milan.
Apparently, her ex-boyfriend
is having a fashion show there.
I can't believe that crazy girl!
Why go after the man who dumped her?
I could just...
Sorry. I mean, thank you.
You should come visit sometime.
Darn it.
Young Chae went to Milan?
Do you really not know,
or are you just pretending?
I didn't know.
Have you heard from Young Chae?
No, not yet.
Are you being honest?
You two aren't up
to something again?
That won't happen again.
I'm worried about Young Chae, too.
Worried, my foot.
Are you on edge,
afraid I'll drag her back?
You must enjoy all her perks.
It must be pretty sweet.
Chairman.
This isn't the time to worry
about things like that.
And you have nothing to gain
by upsetting me.
I gave you permission
to be Young Chae for a bit,
and now you think you've become her.
You just keep
talking back to me so boldly.
But I am Young Chae.
At least until you bring her back.
You, of all people,
must treat me like the real Young Chae.
That's the only way
I can face the Kunhyang family...
as the real Young Chae,
not an imposter.
Go ahead, get as cocky as you want.
After I find Young Chae,
I'll decide what to do with you.
It won't be too late.
(Joo Young Chae, the chairman
is heading to Milan from Paris...)
Young Chae, where are you?
Are you in Milan?
Chairman Gong just went
from Paris to Milan.
So please, Young Chae.
Run far away.
Somewhere she can't find you,
and don't ever come back.
That's the only way
my show can go on.
Hi.
This is a first for us, isn't it?
Let's make this work.
I'm surprised you asked
to meet first, Se Mi.
To get on my good side,
you should've reached out first.
To make up for it,
dinner's on me tonight.
Is that supposed to be enough?
What are these flowers for?
This is so random.
Looks like someone's about
to propose to you.
I wonder who.
Could it be Ha Neul?
Joo Ha Neul?
Wait. Are you and my brother dating?
In his dreams.
Even after I said so many times
that I wasn't the marrying type.
It's a curse being this popular.
How romantic.
It really is a surprise proposal.
I'm so jealous.
The star of the show today isn't me.
It's Joo Young Chae.
My future sister-in-law.
I have an appointment,
so I should go.
I'll see you again later.
I know our families arranged this,
but I wanted to tell you
how I truly felt.
Joo Young Chae...
Will you...
marry me?
When Young Chae comes back,
she'll take
her life back mercilessly.
It will feel like it's being stolen.
Even though it was always hers.
Se Hoon?
I'm the real Joo Young Chae.
She's the fake.
I knew it.
She seemed so low-class.
I like it.
What's this reaction?
It doesn't feel like you mean it.
Can you feel it?
My sincerity?
Young Chae.
Joo Young Chae!
(Jin Se Hoon)
It was a magical proposal
I could never have dreamed of...
as Cha Jung Won.
So why am I running away?
Why?
"Go return it right now,
or the wedding is off."
Honestly, if I buy him something,
he should just shut up and wear it.
We'll let our daughter-in-law pick
the other wedding gifts herself.
Yes, ma'am.
Which shoe brand do you think
would suit the couple's taste?
I have selected a few brands
for your consideration.
Right this way.
Hold on, Secretary Yoon.
Jo Mi Hyang?
What do you mean
I can't return this?
I've returned items here before,
so why not these men's shoes?
Please look here.
There are clear signs of wear.
The back leather is creased, too.
That's ridiculous.
It's brand new.
I never even unwrapped them.
I returned them in the same shape.
Who could have possibly worn them?
My goodness, that's just bizarre.
But the only man in my house
is Ki Beom.
Perhaps your husband...
slipped them on for a moment.
He's the last person on earth
who would ever do that.
That scatterbrained woman...
Who said I wanted to wear this crap?
Did I ask to wear this garbage?
Seriously...
What are you doing?
Does posing in new shoes
bring back old memories?
What memories?
Where'd you get these shoes?
Take them back, now! Take them back!
Darn it...
No, that can't be.
It was just a dream.
Ki Beom would never do that.
Of course not.
I have no idea how these new shoes
ended up like this.
I want a refund, period.
Ma'am, please don't
make this difficult.
I'm not taking no for an answer!
What seems to be the problem?
Hello, Vice Chairman.
Vice Chairman?
My apologies for the commotion.
It's just that this customer...
Just give her what she wants.
Right away.
People in her position
really are a different breed.
This can't be.
Her, the Vice Chairman of Kunhyang?
Get real.
Ma'am, we're in a public place.
Your refund has been processed,
ma'am.
Thank you so much. You're an angel.
She's totally different,
but there is a resemblance.
Even if Young Sun's fortunes
completely turned around,
how could she be
Vice Chairman of Kunhyang Group?
Come on. That's crazy talk.
I need to get my eyes checked.
Ma'am.
Excuse me, one moment.
What now? Is there something else?
This way, please.
Why would a person of your stature
want to meet me in private?
Mi Hyang.
It's me,
Han Young Sun.
So it really is you.
Completely transformed,
from head to toe.
You've completely
reinvented yourself.
I only recognize you
because you said you're Young Sun.
No one would ever recognize you.
I've been searching for 25 years,
but you were hidden so well
I could never find you.
Mi Hyang.
Su A.
How is she?
She must have grown
into a beautiful young woman.
So tall,
and lovely.
And her studies?
Did she do well with her studies?
She always used to fall asleep
with her head on my lap.
Even at seven years old,
she could pick a fish clean
all by herself.
She loved riding bikes with her dad
more than anything.
And with her tiny, little hands,
she was such
a talented little artist.
The picture she drew for me
back then...
I treasure it.
- That's enough.
- Mi Hyang.
I...
I know I don't have
the right to ask.
My Su A...
Where is she?
- Tell me, please.
- Please, just stop.
Mi Hyang.
If it's about Su A,
I have nothing to say.
Mi Hyang.
You know where she is, don't you?
Please, help me.
I'm begging you, help me.
Mi Hyang.
She's dead.
What?
Su A...
is no longer with us.
You're lying.
Who would lie about a child's death?
Su A.
She was like a daughter to me, too.
Young Sun.
Leave us alone
and go back to your good life.
Isn't that what you did
when you abandoned her?
- She's not dead.
- Don't come for her now...
and ruin the good life
Ki Beom and I have.
She's not dead!
Tell me again! She's not dead!
- Get off me! Help!
- Vice Chairman, please calm down.
I'm going to lose my mind.
If you cared so much
about your child,
why did you abandon her
and run away?
You're the one who killed Su A,
Young Sun.
It's divine retribution.
If that's not, what is?
No... That's not true.
My Su A... Why?
Why?
No... How could my Su A...
How...
What have I just done?
I just told her Jung Won was dead
when she was perfectly fine.
I'm the one who'll pay for this.
No.
Even if I'm punished a thousand,
ten thousand times for this,
as far as Young Sun is concerned,
her daughter Su A is dead.
And my daughter Jung Won is alive.
That is the real punishment
Young Sun deserves.
(Kunhyang Group,
Chairman Jin Tae Seok)
Just having you, Assemblyman Kang,
attend...
will send Kunhyang's stock price
through the roof.
I'll meet you privately
somewhere quiet before the event.
Yes.
It's not just Assemblyman Kang.
Minister Jeong, Vice Minister Park,
and Assemblyman Song.
They're all chomping at the bit.
I heard Assemblyman Kang has his eye
on the presidency,
and it looks like
the rumors are true.
So he needs Kunhyang
to bankroll him?
And not only that...
Those sly jerks.
As if Kunhyang's money isn't enough
for them,
they want to use Gong Nan Sook
as a lifeline too?
Chairman,
there's an urgent matter...
(Kunhyang Group,
Chairman Jin Tae Seok)
Relax.
- What's so urgent?
- It's about Vice Chairman Han...
My wife? What about her?
She suddenly collapsed
and has been taken to the hospital.
And you're just telling me now?
Clear the rest of my schedule.
A femme fatale? Young Chae?
She's been acting strange
ever since I proposed.
She accepted the ring,
but never actually said...
yes or no. She just bolted.
Did you do something wrong?
I have no idea.
That's the thing.
She seemed so happy at first.
She's a total wild card.
She's impossible to read.
Welcome.
You look different today.
Very different.
This is the real me.
The real you?
This is the real Joo Young Chae?
Yes.
To put it nicely, I'm plain.
- And frankly, a little frumpy.
- You look so innocent.
Breathtakingly so.
I can't believe
you had this side to you.
The innocent type has always been
my ideal.
Exactly like you are right now.
So Young Chae suddenly showed up,
acting all innocent?
You think it's weird too, right?
She's your sister,
but you can't figure her out, right?
But didn't you say
the innocent type was your ideal?
So what's the problem?
A woman's allowed
to change her style.
If only that were all.
Young Chae, are you drunk?
How many bottles of soju
did you even drink?
Hey!
It's Jin Se Hoon.
The Crown Prince of Kunhyang Group.
I'm so honored...
that you came to pick me up.
Is this how you are when you drink?
Let's go.
Stop!
Flaunting your money
in a place like this...
No, it's just tacky
to throw your money around.
Guys like you
probably have no idea...
how much three bottles
of soju cost here, do you?
Jerk.
Joo Young Chae,
what's with the loose cannon act?
"A loose cannon?"
You bet. That's me.
I'm also a great clown.
And I can put on one heck of a show.
The Joo Young Chae you know...
is a fake.
Okay, sure.
My Young Chae is good at everything.
A compliment! I'm so excited.
I feel like dancing!
Young Chae really did all that?
Hard to believe, right?
I don't want to believe it either.
Why on earth
is she acting like this?
She won't even wear the ring
I gave her,
and these days
she just ignores all my calls.
Joo Young Chae is just too much.
She's like a maze.
Why are you here without calling?
Is something wrong?
Why are you being mean to Se Hoon?
I got bored.
You're doing this for fun?
You're engaged to the guy!
Engaged?
You think this is funny?
If you keep this up...
and Se Hoon learns
you're not really Young Chae,
what will you do?
What am I even saying?
It's because I'm scared.
I'm terrified I'll be found out.
At least Cinderella knew
she had until midnight.
I have no idea
when the real Young Chae might appear.
It could be tonight,
tomorrow morning,
or a week from now.
Without any warning, my carriage
will turn back into a pumpkin,
and my gown will turn to rags.
What if they learn
I'm not Joo Young Chae,
Chairwoman Gong's daughter,
but just a nobody
named Cha Jung Won?
Then just stop this now.
And if I do?
Then what?
You just go back to your life
as Cha Jung Won.
Once a fox gets a taste
of a sweet apricot,
it can't stop,
even knowing it's poison.
It gets completely hooked
on the taste.
It says "Just one more bite,"
and ends up eating it all.
Then what is it you really want?
I want...
to become the real Young Chae.
No more fearing
the real one showing up.
No more worrying about
the carriage turning to a pumpkin...
or losing that glass slipper.
I don't want to be afraid anymore.
I want to live...
as the real Joo Young Chae.
(A Graceful Liar)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)