(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed
all guidelines for young actors.)
So, what's on the agenda
for today's board meeting?
The damage
to Kunhyang Group's image,
and what to do about Han Hye Ra,
who was behind the interview.
- That's the discussion...
- No.
We're here to expose
everything you've done...
and how far you've dragged down
Kunhyang Group.
That's what this meeting is about.
So, it's a showdown to see who wins.
I love watching a good fight.
Time to get the popcorn.
It's not just about
former Vice Chairman Han's interview.
Since you held a press conference
as a mere temporary vice chairman,
this is also for your reprimand.
It might be the other way around,
you know.
You think the board
is going to praise...
the former and current Vice Chairmen?
A responsible executive.
Won't they see me as an executive
who really cares about Kunhyang?
They'll just think
you're an outsider...
trying to scheme your way in
and push out the establishment.
Jung Won.
Give me the strength...
to see this through.
(Episode 72)
Hello? Over here.
The nerve of them.
I tried so hard
to get on the same side as them,
and they won't even look at me?
Those ungrateful brats!
Interim Vice Chairman
Joo Ha Neul's press conference.
Former Vice Chairman
Han Hye Ra's interview.
Because of these two incidents,
Kunhyang Group
is facing a major crisis.
This undermines
the entire organization.
And they both went against
Kunhyang Group's official statement.
An official statement
should be based on facts.
There's no proof that Cha Ki Beom
was abusive or had an affair.
It's nothing more than
baseless speculation.
So that allowed you to hold
a press conference...
and drag my name into it?
I made you the Vice Chairman,
and you repay me...
by trying to frame me as a criminal?
This is unacceptable.
Not just Vice Chairman Joo Ha Neul,
but also
former Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra...
has dragged our company's name
through the mud.
How about we determine
who exactly...
dragged Kunhyang through the mud,
shall we?
You're blaming Jin Tae Seok?
An owner who is supposed
to have a long-term vision...
- deliberately distorted the truth.
- Han Hye Ra!
She's right. Times have changed.
If we rush to cover up the truth
and crush the weak and the wronged,
we will never be able to
overcome this crisis.
You've got a lot to say for someone
who made this whole mess worse.
Is telling the truth
what you call making it worse?
Do you really not see
what is making things worse?
This whole thing is
about to blow up.
As long as Chairman Jin Tae Seok
remains in his position,
it will be impossible
to overcome this crisis.
Are you telling me
to step down as chairman?
- That's right.
- I believe it's worth considering.
Hearing all this, it sounds like
Jin Tae Seok is really at fault.
And I bet there's a mountain
of evidence, too.
Evidence? There's no such thing.
How dare you all try to paint me
as a criminal?
Have you all lost your minds?
We'll see who's really crazy
in the end.
Apologize to the Chairman now.
Former Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra,
you will retract your interview.
And Vice Chairman Joo Ha Neul,
you will resign immediately.
(Voice Recording)
You should've taken Gong Nan Sook
down sooner...
if you didn't want to die
like a dog.
He's still alive.
What is this?
Are you saying Chairman Jin Tae Seok
tried to kill someone?
My father,
Joo Sang Cheol, was murdered
by Chairman Jin.
The murderer of Joo Ha Neul's dad,
Joo Sang Cheol,
- is Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
- Cut the nonsense!
Han Hye Ra
and Joo Ha Neul set me up!
Let's hear a little more
of the recording.
No, we don't need to hear any more!
I'm telling you,
Jin Tae Seok fooled me for 25 years.
I actually thought I was the one
who killed Joo Sang Cheol!
Make some sense!
You know Joo Sang Cheol
was my ex-husband, right?
This is an official meeting.
Please use formal language.
Formal tone, my foot.
You clearly don't know who I am.
I'm going to speak my mind.
You can pretend I'm being polite.
Gong Nan Sook! Will you shut up?
You shut your trap, Jin Tae Seok!
And the rest of you
better listen up.
Because I'm only saying this once.
This is the undeniable truth.
That's a lie!
- I didn't do it.
- You didn't, right?
- It's a lie, right?
- Why would I lie...
when I'm dealing with Jin Tae Seok?
You did it.
And that's not all.
You framed Cha Ki Beom for it,
and then you killed him.
And he pushed Cha Jung Won,
the daughter...
of former Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra,
off the rooftop.
Chairman! What is the truth?
Tell us yourself.
A criminal can't remain chairman.
Step down!
Please, don't be swayed by this.
Who has protected Kunhyang Group?
It's Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
You can't use unproven evidence...
to oust the man who is Kunhyang.
Everyone, be quiet!
Shut up and listen to me.
I am Jin Tae Seok!
Who dares to insult me?
Who dares try to drag me down
from the chairmanship?
Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
I'm Lieutenant Lee Dong Han,
Violent Crimes Unit, Seocho Police.
I'm placing you under arrest...
for the attempted murder
of Cha Jung Won.
What?
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to make a statement.
What do you think you're doing?
Attempted murder?
Where's the proof?
I am the proof.
Cha Jung Won.
What's going on here?
Chairman Jin Tae Seok
pushed me off that rooftop.
He tried to kill me.
Please come with us.
There's been a misunderstanding.
I'll be back shortly.
There's nothing to worry about.
Step aside.
(Kunhyang Group)
Hey, did you see the looks
on the directors' faces?
Jin Tae Seok, the unbreakable oak,
started to teeter,
and they all looked like
the sky was falling.
So what do you think will happen
to Chairman Jin Tae Seok?
The statute of limitations expired
on the Joo Sang Cheol case,
and there's not enough evidence
for Cha Ki Beom's death.
Pushing Cha Jung Won off the rooftop
is clearly attempted murder.
And since Jung Won survived
to testify,
he won't be able to
get out of it easily.
You really think so?
We're talking about Jin Tae Seok.
Even if he goes to jail,
he'll walk out like it's a vacation.
He might even come out
looking completely refreshed.
Then we'll just have to
throw him back in.
We'll keep finding more evidence,
so he can never run away again...
or make a mockery
of the law ever again.
That's exactly what I want.
Someone who's powerful
but is a filthy bad guy.
Someone stronger than me
that I'm just dying to crush.
But you know,
that's not something anyone can do.
Somehow, I have a feeling
that if it's you,
you might just be able to
pull it off.
Someone I want to see crushed.
You're on my list.
Sure. I'm always up for it.
Bring it on!
But...
- But what?
- You can't just be reckless.
If you rush in without a plan,
you're sure to lose every time.
You're the one
who should be careful.
You've made Chairman Jin Tae Seok
into an enemy.
You must prepare
for his retaliation.
Wait, you're worried about me?
Oh, you're making my heart flutter.
Don't be ridiculous.
Even though
Jin Tae Seok was the real culprit...
who killed my father,
you must also pay for your crimes.
Fine. I told you
that I'd pay for them.
I will.
But I was fooled for 25 years too.
By the way, where are
Han Hye Ra and Cha Jung Won?
My baby,
you came back to me alive.
It's finally sinking in.
I couldn't believe it at first.
I had a dream.
Don't go any further.
Come to Mom.
I was so exhausted and worn out...
that I thought
I just wanted to rest.
At the end of the forest,
I felt like Dad was calling me.
But then,
you beckoned for me to come back.
I'm so glad you did.
I was so scared
something would go wrong...
that I'd never see my girl again.
I was terrified.
My prayers were answered.
Jung Won's awake?
Jung Won.
Doctor, how is she?
Her own will to live
created a miracle.
The swelling in her brain
is gradually subsiding,
and the hemorrhaging has stabilized.
She'll still need rehabilitation
and observation,
but we believe
she can make a full recovery.
Thank you, Doctor.
As for it not feeling real,
I feel the same way.
When I opened my eyes,
the whole world had changed.
Like you were joined at the hip,
you and Chairman Jin Tae Seok,
who seemed inseparable,
are now turning
on each other publicly.
He did something unforgivable.
While you were in a coma,
I found out the truth.
Now I know for sure
who I need to get my revenge on.
Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
- He was behind every evil deed.
- This is far from over.
Do you really think Jin Tae Seok
is finished just like that?
You may have survived,
but you could be killed again.
Chairman Jin Tae Seok...
will try to kill me again?
You think he won't?
Then,
I guess I'll just have to die again.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Go ahead, investigate all you want!
Is there anyone in the police
or the prosecutors’ office...
who hasn’t taken Kunhyang’s money?
How dare you...
Father, please calm down.
I can walk out of here right away,
can't I?
They say it's going to take a while.
I've retained
Kunhyang's legal counsel.
What did I do wrong?
Why do I need a lawyer?
Father, you have to cooperate
with the investigation.
- It's just protocol.
- What protocol?
Cha Jung Won is awake.
Of course, she reported you.
Watch your mouth.
I had them stop recording.
You don't actually think I'd show up
without handling that first?
So Cha Jung Won reported me?
Yes.
For attempted murder.
A moment of pity
only complicated things.
I should have finished her off then.
What do you mean, you should die?
What are you talking about?
They say, "To seek death is to live,
and to seek life is to die."
I've already died once.
What's to keep me from dying
a second or third time?
Anything that doesn't bend breaks.
It's okay...
to hide behind me now.
You want me to hide?
Kunhyang.
I'm going to take it for myself.
I was wondering why you turned on
Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
Of course, that's just like you.
I thought that now
we could finally...
take down
Chairman Jin Tae Seok together.
Together?
Kunhyang is mine.
You just watch and be happy
with the scraps.
That's your place.
Hiding behind Jin Tae Seok...
and enjoying his wealth and power
wasn't enough for you?
So you're finally
showing your claws.
Did you want me to wake up...
just so you could show me this?
Or did you actually wish
I hadn't woken up?
It's not like that.
Just stay alive.
Don't do anything else.
There's nothing you can do,
Jung Won.
You want me to just breathe?
- So I should just lie low?
- That might be for the best.
What would it take for no one
to ever mess with you again?
I don't know.
We're just on parallel tracks,
aren't we?
You and I, always.
Let me be clear.
You go after what you want.
I'll do what I have to do.
I can't let Jung Won
put herself in more danger.
I have to protect her,
no matter what.
What?
Did Cha Jung Won really show up
at the board meeting?
- And Chairman Jin got arrested?
- That's what I said.
Mom, did you know about this?
Why are you asking me
something so obvious,
as if you're surprised?
It was me
who took him down hard!
Weren't you and Chairman Jin
supposed to be allies?
Alliances are temporary.
It's like boats.
You get on, and then you get off.
That's just how it is.
If you make it to port, you've won.
The destination doesn't change.
Taking over Kunhyang Group?
Of course, and if I can't have it,
I'll burn it all down.
So you're teaming up
with former Vice Chairman Han?
And you backstabbed Chairman Jin?
What are you talking about?
He's the one who betrayed me first!
How is everything, ladies?
The taste of betrayal? It's foul.
I was the one
who was betrayed first, wasn't I?
You'll get played again, sweetie.
Me? Again?
What are you talking about?
Why are you looking at Young Chae?
Young Chae, are you
planning on betraying me?
What are you even asking?
Who sits around planning a betrayal?
You've betrayed me more than once!
Are you taking
Cha Jung Won's side again?
Then what about my Se Hoon?
Oh my.
Seriously...
Grandma, why are you staring
at me like that again?
You know I hate it when you pity me
with your eyes, don't you?
So, is Young Chae
going to betray me?
My mom has no idea, does she?
What are you referring to?
The video you stole
of Cha Ki Beom's death and gave to me.
I did no such thing.
I would never betray Chairman Gong.
Right. I believe you.
If you know how terrifying
Madam Gong can be...
Or rather, you should know
I can be even worse.
Don't you forget it, Manager Gu.
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
Why haven't I heard
from Jung Won at all?
She said she was going to put
Jin Tae Seok in jail today.
Jung Won was going to
tell you this herself.
Jin Tae Seok was arrested...
at the board meeting
for attempted murder.
Really?
Mom!
Why didn't you call me first?
The deities were on our side.
Thank you.
I missed you, Mom.
I was worried sick about you.
My Jung Won,
let me get a good look at you.
Are you okay?
That's a relief.
- A phone?
- You need a new one, don't you?
You're a feisty one.
- Were you recording this?
- My word alone isn't enough.
They will only believe
a confession straight from you.
Jin Tae Seok...
threw my phone off the rooftop.
Because you recorded his confession?
But it's useless now.
They said the phone
was beyond repair.
But we should be able
to recover the data.
I know a guy.
He's the best there is at this.
He can almost certainly do it.
So we could have hard evidence
besides my testimony?
Exactly.
What is it?
To be with you like this again,
to talk with you,
look you in the eye,
and be this close to you.
I can't believe it's real.
When I first opened my eyes...
and saw you, Ha Neul,
I was so happy.
I know we have a tough fight
ahead of us,
but having you by my side
gives me strength.
Of all the people who hoped
I would wake up,
the one who had the warmest heart...
and made my heart flutter...
was you.
I wanted to tell you that.
Even if it's a path of thorns
or a quagmire of mud,
as long as I can be with you...
That alone is reason enough...
for me to open my eyes again.
(15 Days Later)
Hey. You're well enough
to come into the office?
Long time no see.
Seriously?
Giving me the cold shoulder?
And I was kind of hoping
she'd wake up.
Just because I was bored.
The sight of her
just makes my blood boil.
She really has a special talent
for ticking people off.
How has everyone been?
Cha Jung Won, it's been forever.
Are you feeling okay now?
Jung Won, are you really okay?
- I knew you'd pull through.
- Thank you.
You're looking well.
That's a relief.
That's enough of a welcome party.
Don't we have work to do?
Putting on quite a show
for someone who's on suspension.
While you were out,
we got new design samples
for the new collection.
Do you have any good ideas?
What if we tried
changing the buttons?
A single button can add flair.
I like that.
I'll add that right away.
- What do you think?
- I hate all of your ideas.
Wasn't your desk in the break room?
That's right.
And now that Jung Won is back,
you should go back to
where you belong.
Designer Joo Young Chae?
Your suspension has been lifted.
- Really?
- All of a sudden?
Why?
It's Vice President Jin's order.
Since it's an emergency now,
all ongoing disciplinary actions...
have been temporarily suspended.
We'll see if this ends up being
a blessing or a curse for you.
Just you watch.
I'll be the one who wins in the end.
This is Cha Jung Won.
Questioning as a witness?
So are you saying Jin Tae Seok
followed you to the rooftop...
with the intention of murdering you?
Yes, that's correct.
Chairman Jin.
What are you doing here?
It's a beautiful view.
And the weather is perfect.
It's quite high up.
It makes your head spin.
Are you here to stop
my press conference?
Or...
are you here to do something to me?
I can't go easy on you anymore.
This will be your grave.
Why would Jin Tae Seok
try to kill you?
- What was his motive?
- He needed to silence me.
So he wanted to stop the conference
you had scheduled?
That's not all.
I was recording Jin Tae Seok's voice
on my phone.
He realized what I was doing
and pushed me.
A recording?
What was on it?
A recording of me confessing
to murdering Cha Ki Beom?
That's a lie.
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
I don't know why Cha Ki Beom died.
If there's a recording, play it!
The recording is gone.
Chairman Jin Tae Seok
took my phone...
and threw it off the rooftop.
See?
Can you lock me up on her testimony
and no evidence, Prosecutor Kim?
Watch your tone, Mr. Jin Tae Seok.
"Mr. Jin Tae Seok?"
Do you have any idea whose money
put your boss in his seat?
Sometimes,
it's best to know your place.
I'm just biding my time
until this all blows over.
With one call, I can get a rookie
like you fired in an instant.
What? Han Hye Ra,
what did you just say?
I said I was going to become
the chairman of Kunhyang.
Are you out of your mind?
No, I'm perfectly sane.
Gong Nan Sook,
if you'll just help me,
nothing's impossible. Am I wrong?
And why would I help you?
If anyone's to be chairman, it's me.
You think Kunhyang would hand over
the chair to a lowly loan shark?
Be realistic.
Fine.
Then make me a realistic offer.
If I help you become the chairman,
what's in it for me?
Be my shadow, Gong Nan Sook.
(Chairman Jin Tae Seok)
(A Graceful Liar)
You're family and a top shareholder.
Take over as the gallery's director.
Don't think for a second
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
You won't even take my scraps?
How disappointing.
You helped
former Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra...
attack my dad.
Have you abandoned me?
You want to be Kunhyang's Chairman,
don't you?
So which side should you be on?
Jin Tae Seok,
I want to see you fall.
Even lower than you are now.
I took you in and cared for you,
but you bit the hand that fed you.
Snap out of it,
Chairman Jin Tae Seok.
It's already over for you.
I'm taking your seat outright.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)