(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed
all guidelines for young actors.)
Hye Ra.
You can rest now.
Fall asleep here beside me.
Forever.
Your voice...
used to be so comforting and sweet.
There was a time...
when just hearing your voice
made my heart skip a beat.
I love you.
I know.
I know how much you loved me.
But now,
it's time your love ended.
That's right.
I'm telling you I did it.
I took care of
the mother of Jin Se Hoon,
the former Vice Chairman of Kunhyang,
because Jin Tae Seok ordered me to.
Are you saying
you committed the murder yourself?
Come on, Detective.
What century are you living in?
Do you really think people like us
get our hands dirty?
That's what money is for.
- What about Jin Tae Seok?
- He's already gone.
- What do you mean, "gone?"
- Are you deaf, Detective?
He's dead.
Then do you have a witness...
to this murder-for-hire
you're confessing to?
Why do I need a witness?
I'm right here confessing to you.
I was the one trading Kunhyang stock
using a borrowed-name account.
It wasn't Joo Ha Neul.
Why are you trying to take the fall
for him?
"Take the fall?"
What are you talking about?
Come on, I'm turning myself in,
so why won't you take my word for it?
Where did I put it? Hold on.
Here.
Here's your evidence.
It's all in here.
It says I'm the one who traded
the stocks under a borrowed name.
And that David Kay, that's my alias.
What else was there?
The Crown Capital.
The company went through
a massive tax audit a while ago.
Turns out I embezzled
a ton of money.
Chairman Gong...
Don't cry on an empty stomach.
Eat up, then cry all you want.
She's the sweetest girl
in the world,
but I called her a wicked witch
and cursed her out.
For a son that isn't even her own,
and she cherishes
more than her own child,
she sacrificed herself,
for crying out loud.
You've been through so much.
I'm not guilty?
How is that possible?
Chairman Gong Nan Sook...
turned herself in.
So, Jin Tae Seok
is really dead, right?
I still can't believe it.
You just came from his funeral.
Why is it so hard to believe?
He's like an immortal, isn't he?
I'm worried
he might rise from his own grave.
That's not going to happen.
He took my child's life...
and killed Ki Beom.
I can finally put him
out of my mind.
You've suffered so much,
enduring everything to get here.
You have too, Manager Hwang.
I don't know why,
but I'm dying for a drink today.
I'd kill for just one shot
of something strong.
I was hoping we could go elsewhere,
not here.
Would you care to join me?
Rest in peace, my sweet baby.
Mommy will come visit sometimes...
with him.
Ki Beom,
you're smiling now, aren't you?
(Cha Ki Beom, Born: April 7, 1966,
Date of Death: November 28, 2025)
That's right. Go on and smile.
Your name has been cleared,
and Jin Tae Seok has fallen
into the abyss.
He got his just deserts.
Now you can finally
relax and have a drink.
(Kunhyang Group)
Do you really have to step down
as chairman like this?
It wasn't my place to begin with.
I've done what I came to do,
so now it's time
for me to step down.
I feel the same way as Ha Neul.
I'm leaving Kunhyang, too.
I've been thinking
about this for a long time.
All of this misfortune started...
when I became
the matriarch of Kunhyang,
and from my ambition
to reach the very top.
I'm going to entrust Kunhyang
to a professional CEO,
and I'll be leaving as well,
with you, Jung Won.
Oh my...
Good grief.
Why did you come all this way?
There's nothing good to see here.
I heard you decorated
your cell like a hotel room.
Are you staying warm enough?
I'm fine right now.
Manager Gu brings me warm things
from time to time.
I figured as much.
So? Did you have something to say?
I won't be able to visit you
for a while.
I guess you're going somewhere.
I've already booked the flights.
How many tickets did you get? Two?
Or did you get four tickets
for a round trip?
Make sure you go
with the one you love.
And make sure
you come back together.
Please stay healthy, Mother.
Hearing you call me "Mother"...
sounds so nice.
It does.
You know, out of all the times
I've seen you,
you've never looked...
more at peace than this.
I do, don't I?
Go on.
Congratulations,
Chief Director Jin Se Mi.
My congratulations as well.
I've been appointed to a position
of great responsibility.
I'll be counting on all of your help
moving forward.
- I'm counting on you.
- You don't even have to ask.
By the way,
what about Joo Young Chae?
Right. I haven't seen
her face around lately.
Joo Young Chae
has submitted her resignation.
And the company has accepted it.
So Chairman Gong Nan Sook
took the fall for Joo Ha Neul?
He has all the luck.
How are you feeling?
Are you starting to show yet?
Do you really have to wear
something that tight? Goodness.
I never imagined...
you'd end up in prison.
I actually like it.
If I'd known,
I would've turned myself in sooner.
How are things with Jin Se Hoon?
Se Hoon will be the chairman
of Kunhyang Group again soon.
And I'm going to make that happen.
Are you still driven
by that same greed?
How is that greed?
I'm just trying to take
what's rightfully ours.
Young Chae.
Just live a good life.
Don't you worry about me.
- I'll live well and be just fine.
- Please.
Just live a good life, okay?
Of course I will.
I'm finally done being your puppet,
and I've even found true love.
You just worry about yourself, Mom.
And don't get into fights
while you're in prison.
What's wrong?
It's all my fault.
No matter how much my mom doted
on Ha Neul,
I never thought she'd go so far
as to turn herself in.
I never thought...
she was the type
to sacrifice herself for family.
I guess I was wrong about her.
You'll startle A Reum. Calm down.
This is what comes around.
What about us?
What do you mean, "us?"
We've done our share of bad things,
you know.
- What?
- The karma.
You don't think that applies to us?
What more could possibly happen
to us?
We're the victims here.
Maybe...
- we've already faced our karma.
- Young Chae.
My goal was to become the lady
of the Kunhyang Group.
And yet...
to think I'd end up falling for you
when you have nothing...
I guess
this really is my punishment.
Hye Ra.
I'm glad you could make it,
old friend!
What's with the "old friend" act?
You never change, do you,
Gong Nan Sook?
You look like you're on vacation.
Your skin's so clear.
I'm in my element, aren't I?
I'm a total rock star in here.
I guess I was made for the slammer.
I could stay here forever.
What?
You didn't forget what I asked,
did you?
Han Hye Ra.
Come on, darling.
You'll help me, right?
How?
I have two favors to ask.
My two good boys.
Make sure they're set up
for a good life.
I'm guessing one is Joo Ha Neul.
And the other one?
My dear Yeong Soo,
who looks like a cartoon character.
Manager Gu?
- Yes.
- How do I give them a good life?
And the second favor?
It's about my Young Chae.
She's my daughter,
and I'm the one who ruined her.
Turns out she's genuinely in love
with Jin Se Hoon.
- I know.
- Don't pretend you don't.
So, please look after them.
What do you want me to do?
Kick them out of Kunhyang.
That's "looking after them?"
That's kicking them to the curb.
It's the only way for Young Chae
and Jin Se Hoon...
to finally live a normal life.
(Chairman Gu Yeong Soo)
Thank you.
Chairman Gong Nan Sook.
I'm Director Yoon Min Jung,
and I'll be helping you from today.
This is kind of awkward.
There's no need for formalities,
Director Yoon.
Sir, here is your briefing material
for today.
Even if I were a genius,
how could I possibly read all this?
You're succeeding Chairman Gong
as head of The Crown Capital.
Former Advisor Han Hye Ra
also gave me specific instructions.
- Which were?
- "Make a real chairman out of him."
"Min Jung,
I'm holding you responsible."
So you're not my secretary,
but more like my warden?
That's correct, sir.
So Gu Yeong Soo is the new chairman
of Crown Capital?
He'll do a great job.
He may act like a fool,
but he's a real genius.
And as for Young Chae and Se Hoon,
I did exactly as you asked.
Good.
See? I told you we have
some serious chemistry.
And you're not worried
about me at all?
Why would I worry about you?
By the way,
are you really going
to give it all up?
I have to atone...
for the sins I've committed.
I've got to hand it to you.
- You're a tougher woman than I am.
- No.
Gong Nan Sook,
you're the better one.
No, you've definitely got me beat.
But I'm the prettier one.
Let's get that straight, okay?
Fine. You're the great, pretty one,
Gong Nan Sook. You win.
Good grief.
I want you to come with me.
(Incheon to Paris)
The flight's in a week.
I'm heading to Paris for now.
I've given up everything I had.
So I'm sorry to ask you...
to come with me
when I have nothing left.
Now that we can let go
of all our heavy burdens,
I want us to live a simple,
happy life.
I want to share that kind of life
with you.
We can take walks together.
We don't have to eat fancy food.
Just being able to eat with you...
is enough for me.
I want to live a life of happiness,
even if it's just full of smiles,
with you, Jung Won.
Just imagining it
makes my heart flutter.
And it fills me with so much joy.
You more than deserve
that simple happiness.
Come with me.
Mom, what do you want to do now?
I'll just go with the flow
and let nature take its course.
You're leaving...
with Former Chairman Joo Ha Neul, right?
He's a good man.
He truly cherishes...
and loves you.
Why must you leave the Kunhyang house?
Where will we live?
Anywhere we go...
will be more comfortable
than the Kunhyang house.
Then let's go to my mom's house.
It's empty right now.
And you need to make up
with Ha Neul already.
Se Hoon, you're acting...
so petty and small-minded
toward Ha Neul.
What? "Petty?"
Is Ha Neul's success a crime?
He even resigned as chairman
and will move abroad.
I can't face Joo Ha Neul.
No, I'm never seeing him again.
(Joo Ha Neul)
Why would you call to have a drink
when there is nothing left to say?
You must've wanted
an apology from me.
It's such a simple thing,
but I never even managed
to apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Young Chae said...
that I was just jealous of you.
She was right. I admit it.
I was being petty.
I'm glad...
that before I leave,
I got to talk to you one last time.
Here.
What do you want?
Are you here to brag about
leaving with Ha Neul?
You and I...
were always very different,
and we hated each other for it.
"I was wrong,
but you were wrong, too,"
"so let's just call it even?"
I can't stand that kind of talk.
Me neither.
I just...
wanted to sit down with you,
just the two of us,
and have a cup of tea like this.
I've decided...
to go back to studying design.
That way, I won't be tempted
to steal your designs again.
That's a great decision.
And...
you won't be seeing me for a while.
So, it must be true
that you're leaving with Ha Neul.
What a relief.
Just the thought of not having
to see your face...
feels like a ten-year weight
has finally been lifted.
I...
still don't understand
Joo Young Chae.
No, I can't understand her,
and I certainly can't forgive her.
But...
now I have the emotional space...
to look into her troubled heart.
Young Chae must have
been hurting too,
just like I was.
By seeing each other
at our most vulnerable...
and finding compassion
within ourselves,
the story
between Young Chae and me...
can finally come to a pause.
With Ha Neul?
Do I even deserve that?
I'm so sorry to you too.
I have become
the daughter of your enemy.
I can't hate you for
what our parents did.
As if nothing ever happened,
am I allowed to be happy?
Have a safe trip, Jung Won.
You take care too, Se Mi,
until we see each other again.
Call me as soon as you land.
I love you, Mom.
Just how pretty is she
trying to look?
Honestly...
Jung Won will be here any minute.
But it's almost time to board.
Jung Won.
I'm sorry, Ha Neul.
Don't wait for me.
Jung Won.
More than anything,
I wanted to go with you.
Then let's just go together.
But...
I don't think I can.
Why? What's wrong?
Love isn't just about...
being together.
How can you end things
between us like this? No, Jung Won
Let's...
just put things on hold for now.
I...
don't deserve to be happy yet.
To me,
you'll always be my protector.
You're my great, sheltering tree,
my endless sky,
and the roof over my head.
- Jung Won...
- If we're meant to be,
we'll meet again.
And when that time comes,
you and I can start fresh.
I love you, Jung Won.
I...
love you too.
(2 Years Later)
(Somang Childcare Center)
- Hey! Stop it!
- Hey, I want some too!
- Give it to me.
- No!
- Kids, be careful. You'll get hurt.
- All right!
- Toss that one back!
- Hey, what about me?
- Hey!
- Careful, you'll fall!
- Hey, over here!
- Hey, give it to me!
Lunchtime!
Do you see that over there?
That's Kunhyang Group,
and one day, it'll all be yours.
Now you know
why we named you Kun Hyang.
You got another one.
(To Jung Won: Hope you're well)
This time,
it's from London, England.
It says his travel columns
were published as a book.
I'd love to read that.
I'll have to check the bookstore.
By any chance,
are you looking for this?
("The Me I Met on My Travels")
Ha Neul?
How have you been?
Well... Listen.
I'm pretty hungry.
If you haven't eaten lunch,
do you want
to get some spicy rice cakes?
(A Graceful Liar)
(Thank you for your love and support
for "A Graceful Liar.")
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)