(All characters, locations,
organizations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictional.)
(This production followed
all guidelines for young actors.)
They couldn't even tell
two people submitted the same book.
That's how sloppy the hiring
at Kunhyang Group was.
Designer Joo Young Chae,
is this true?
No.
I think
there's been a misunderstanding.
But as for you, Cha Jung Won,
why do you have
such a vendetta against Kunhyang?
What?
Look at this.
Cha Jung Won here even leaked
this story to the press.
("Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra's
Hidden Daughter")
("Her History and Path
to Kunhyang Revealed")
Are you out of your mind?
What do you take Kunhyang Group for?
I believe this kind of corruption
and unfairness has to stop.
Se Mi, what do you think
you're doing?
This isn't
how it was supposed to go...
Are you okay, Cha Jung Won?
I told my boss
that the hiring process was unfair,
and she slapped me.
It would be weirder
if I were okay, right?
Unfair hiring process?
What's this about?
I hope you'll look into it as well,
Vice President Jin.
I can explain, Se Hoon.
I mean, Vice President Jin.
No. I need to hear the explanation
directly from Designer Cha Jung Won.
What are you thinking?
(Episode 62)
Did you put on a suicide vest
to take down Kunhyang with you?
This is a workplace.
Please keep it professional.
The article...
Jung Won, did you...
I mean, you published it,
Designer Cha, right?
- I did.
- What did you think you were doing?
Do you even have a plan?
Charging in headfirst
won't solve anything.
That's not your concern, sir.
Just make sure you properly handle
the fraudulent blind hiring case.
That's all I ask.
She's made up her mind
to reveal the whole truth.
She's dead set on
shaking up Kunhyang.
I think she's telling me to take
responsibility for my choice.
And that she'll take responsibility
for hers.
This implies the Kunhyang family
was involved in Cha Ki Beom's death.
But it's true. I...
No. You killed Cha Ki Beom.
Hye Ra.
You know Gong Nan Sook
has proof, don't you?
(Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra)
There's no proof.
You're suspecting me
based on Gong Nan Sook's lies?
You and Gong Nan Sook
are behind everything.
The two of you conspired
to frame an innocent person,
and you framed me
for Cha Ki Beom's murder.
- That's not true.
- Was that all you did?
You even made Se Hoon believe
that I killed his birth mother.
I told you, that's not true!
If it's not true,
then bring me proof.
I swear I will find proof
that you did it...
no matter what.
Were you two arguing
because of the article?
What is it?
Do you have a report
for Vice Chairman Han?
I've received a report
on an issue...
in the Design Team's
blind recruitment process.
The Design Team is your area.
You handle it.
Who wrote this report?
Cha Jung Won.
What brings you here?
- Are you here to see me?
- I came to see Vice Chairman Han.
Why would you meet her?
It's a matter I must discuss
with her in person.
Go ahead.
We'll talk later.
Why are you meeting
with the Vice Chairman?
At a time like this?
Is it because of the article?
Are you Cha Jung Won's lawyer now?
If my business was with you,
I wouldn't need to see her, would I?
I heard she rejected you.
Love is a luxury,
or so I hear from Jung Won.
You rushed things.
Confessing already?
No, it's been long overdue.
Because I've loved her
since high school.
So now you can cross the line?
Se Hoon.
You're the one crossing
the line right now.
Whoever Jung Won dates or loves,
even if it ends up being me,
it's none of your business anymore.
Have you ever stopped to think
about how I feel?
How upset I must feel.
The woman I love is in front of me,
but I can't have her.
A woman I don't even love
has suddenly become my wife.
Things have become a total mess,
and it was all out of my control.
Get a grip, Jin Se Hoon.
- What?
- I don't have time...
for your whining right now.
The woman I love is standing
at the edge of a cliff.
One little push and she would fall.
And she's rejecting my love.
I'm going crazy worrying
that she'll freeze out there alone.
What on earth is this?
Did you really think
she'd just fall into your arms...
like she was waiting for it
after breaking up with me?
Don't kid yourself!
I don't have time for this.
I saw the article.
You seem less surprised
than you were about the first one.
Because I realized
that I'm the one you're aiming for.
- And I know what you want.
- What is it that I want?
To strip me bare.
As a mother
who abandoned her daughter...
and the wife who betrayed
and killed her husband...
after he'd been framed for murder,
a heartless, cold-blooded woman.
- You want the world to turn on me.
- Are you afraid?
Do you think a few measly articles
are going to accomplish that?
I...
spent 25 years clawing my way...
to be Kunhyang's matriarch
and the Vice Chairman.
I'm wearing armor
that your attacks can never pierce.
So a nobody like me can't beat you,
is that it?
- You're not just up against me.
- I know.
You have Chairman Jin Tae Seok
by your side,
and next to him is someone
with cunning and chilling schemes,
- Chairman Gong Nan Sook.
- That's right.
Unless you have a sharper,
more sophisticated blade,
you'll never be able to beat them.
Forget my heart,
it'll feel like a tickle in my palm.
And that's not all.
You'll be consumed by pain and fear
more terrifying than the fiery pit.
Are you worried about me right now?
Worried?
You naive child.
This proves you don't understand
the world or how people work.
Do you think
however recklessly you act,
I'm going to protect you?
"You're my mother.
Blood is thicker than water."
"You wouldn't dare
do anything to me."
That's what you're thinking,
isn't it?
Do you believe
that as long as you're my daughter,
Chairman Jin Tae Seok
won't harm you?
Or that as long as
he forbids it, Gong Nan Sook,
- won't be able to touch you?
- You're dead wrong.
You have far too much to lose,
so you must be terrified
of the truth coming out.
But I'm different.
I have nothing left to lose.
You should know someone...
with nothing to lose
is the most dangerous.
And don't you expect me...
to show any hesitation...
just because you're my mother.
That's enough, Jung Won.
I expect a thorough investigation
into the blind hiring corruption.
Have a seat.
I apologize
for stopping by unannounced.
Not at all. You’re welcome anytime,
CEO Joo.
(Vice President Jin Se Hoon)
What do you think
you're doing in my chair?
Nice and roomy.
It's about time...
you started preparing to move to
the Vice Chairman's office, right?
Excuse me?
Don't you have any ambition?
Who isn't ambitious?
But what do you mean, Vice Chairman?
With Han Hye Ra in so much trouble,
do you really think the board...
is just going to let her
stay on as Vice Chairman?
But the Chairman strongly backs her.
Then we'll force a majority vote.
But wouldn't
the Chairman's decision matter more?
If he's forced to choose...
between Kunhyang
and the Vice Chairman...
the Chairman would naturally
choose Vice Chairman Han.
Nothing's forever.
Isn't that how the song goes?
It's human to change,
and it's in love's nature to change.
You of all people should know that.
This isn't my decision to make.
So Jung Won hasn't
accepted your feelings,
has she?
You gave me a ring,
but I haven't been able
to give it to her.
Are you going to give up?
No, of course not.
I believe
she feels the same way I do.
She may be pushing me away
right now,
but I know
she'll come around eventually.
She must be going through a lot
right now,
so why is she insisting
on fighting this all on her own?
Did you do something...
so that CEO Joo and Jung Won
wouldn’t end up together?
No.
It's cute that Se Mi
would even think that.
Maybe there's another reason
why Jung Won...
can't bring herself
to accept your feelings.
What do you mean by that?
She probably just doesn't have
the emotional bandwidth for it now.
If you're patient with her, CEO Joo,
she might eventually come
to appreciate your feelings,
don't you think?
You care about Jung Won so deeply,
so why do you hide it?
The more I show how I really feel,
the more danger Jung Won will be in.
What if Chairman Jin
stops trusting me?
What if he starts to believe
I would do anything for Jung Won?
But if you keep hiding
your true intentions like this,
Jung Won's anger and resentment
toward you will only grow.
That's a risk I have to take.
Until I can be the one
to tell Jung Won,
I need you, CEO Joo,
to keep this secret.
I understand.
This latest news article...
could be damaging to you.
How do you plan to respond?
Let's say something were to happen
to my position.
Could you...
step in and take my place?
So Cha Jung Won was the one
who exposed the blind hiring issue?
Yes. Where does she get her nerve?
She's counting on your mother.
Then shouldn't she be buttering up
Mom instead of backstabbing her?
The Vice Chairman was in charge
of the blind hiring process.
Dad.
Call me Chairman.
Yes, Chairman.
Her reputation will take a huge hit.
Is she going to be all right?
Oh, my.
Bless your heart.
Se Mi, you're a devoted daughter.
You showed up unannounced again.
You and my Ha Neul
would make such a great couple.
Thank you.
That's very kind of you to say.
- I'll let you two talk.
- All right, dear.
Goodness, how did she turn out so...
pure and polished,
without a single flaw?
How on earth did you end up
with a daughter like her?
She's the apple of my eye.
I never saw that look on your face.
Let me ask you one thing.
If Han Hye Ra and Se Mi
were drowning,
who would you save first?
What kind of childish question
is that?
You're hesitating.
Of course, I'd save them both.
Are you a good swimmer?
Are you kidding?
Why would I have to jump in myself?
I'd just get two good swimmers
to save both Hye Ra and Se Mi.
What if there are no good swimmers?
What if it's just you and only you?
Are you going to keep
talking nonsense?
Your anger makes me more curious.
I thought your heart was Hye Ra's,
and that she filled it completely,
but I forgot
you’re soft on your daughter.
- Let me ask you one, then.
- What?
If Joo Young Chae and Joo Ha Neul
were drowning, who'd you save first?
Hey, why are you copying me?
Let me guess.
Joo Young Chae, your own daughter?
You're wrong.
Save them?
I'd just see who survives...
while I sit back and watch
with some popcorn.
The only things I care about
are my life and my money.
Kids? What good are they anyway?
Come on. Just get to the point.
What are you talking about?
You want me to become Vice Chairman?
Let's just call it
a contingency plan.
The board of directors
won't just let this situation slide.
That is absolutely not
going to happen.
My influence may be limited,
but as a major shareholder,
I am entitled to a vote.
I will do everything in my power
to protect your position.
This is why I need you, CEO Joo.
You're steadfast,
righteous, and honest.
And your actions match your words.
And...
for my Jung Won,
you'll love her unconditionally.
What exactly are you planning?
Are you planning to
give everything up?
What?
You want to oust the Vice Chairman,
and put Se Hoon in her place?
Believe me,
I wanted to just snatch...
the vice chairman position
for myself,
but I thought better of it.
After all,
the title isn't what matters.
So you can pull Se Hoon's strings
from behind the scenes.
What are you talking about?
You're still calling the shots.
Can I really control all of Kunhyang
with just Se Hoon?
No. I have to protect Hye Ra.
Who said you have to decide now?
Just think about it.
There's nothing to think about.
For your beloved Han Hye Ra,
her daughter, Cha Jung Won,
has just dropped like a bombshell.
That's nothing. A candle in the wind
as long as I'm standing guard.
Did it ever occur to you
that you're the candle in the wind?
- What?
- You’re hopeless in love.
What if Han Hye Ra changes her mind
and gives it all to Cha Jung Won?
Han Hye Ra manages your slush fund,
doesn't she?
Never trust a woman too much.
Stop wagging that venomous tongue
of yours.
The word on the street is
that Han Hye Ra...
is desperate to pair Cha Jung Won
with my Ha Neul.
My heart breaks for poor Se Mi.
What will become of her?
Looks like she'll be left out
in the cold.
Or will she?
The Vice Chairman was in charge
of the blind hiring process?
Yes.
The truth is,
I was the one who made the call.
What?
You can't ignore their education.
Especially for designers.
Besides creativity,
they need some background knowledge
to understand you.
How can I work if I must teach them
every little thing from A to Z?
Se Mi, listen to me very carefully.
The fact
that you made that decision.
Keep it secret from the Chairman
and the Vice Chairman.
- Why?
- You like Ha Neul, don't you?
So who was wronged
by the unfair blind hiring?
Cha Jung Won...
No! If Ha Neul finds out
that I'm the reason...
Cha Jung Won was rejected,
he'll be so disappointed in me.
Just report to me what's happening
in the Design Team.
I'll handle the rest
and make sure you don't get hurt.
What if Mom gets hurt?
We have the Chairman on her side.
Don't worry.
Okay.
You should get going.
Ha Neul should be out of
the Vice Chairman's office by now.
Is Ha Neul here?
Why is Ha Neul
with the Vice Chairman?
(Kunhyang Group)
Ha Neul!
- Se Mi.
- Stay for a cup of tea.
You and Mom...
I didn't know
you two were close enough...
for a private meeting.
We had some business to discuss.
Don't you usually handle business
with Se Hoon?
Stop being so nosy, kiddo.
Seriously...
Were you hurt? Come here.
Let me see. It's not swollen...
Stop messing around.
- You hit me?
- Good grief.
By any chance,
did Dad say anything to you?
Like what?
After hearing you and Cha Jung Won
didn't work out,
I thought Dad might have...
What are you talking about?
I guess not?
Se Mi, what did you tell
Chairman Jin?
What do you want me to do,
my dear Se Mi?
Break apart...
Cha Jung Won and Ha Neul for me.
It's just that I told him
I'm serious about you,
and Dad said that guys don't really
like women who come on too strong.
He told me to slow things down.
Is it true?
What is?
That you stole Cha Jung Won's
design book to get this job.
And you believe her?
I went to
the New York Royal Art School.
You think I'd steal a sloppy design
from a high school graduate?
And how did you get into
the New York Royal Art School?
You stole Jung Won's design book
back in high school, didn't you?
Are you out of your mind?
Kim Sung Hee.
Do you want to be sued
for defamation and false rumors?
That's enough.
The truth will come out.
Ahn Ji Na,
you and I are in the same boat.
Don't you forget it.
I'll have to see for myself
how low you'll sink, Joo Young Chae.
Let's get back to work.
And stop wasting time
on useless speculation.
The nerve of her.
Sung Hee.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I'm going to the restroom
to wash my face.
Joo Young Chae stole
Cha Jung Won's design book?
Not just for the designer position
of Kunhyang Fashion,
but to get into
the New York Royal Art School too?
However, that hasn't been confirmed.
That's the claim from Cha Jung Won
and Kim Sung Hee.
They're not the type
to make up stories.
Did Joo Young Chae
really do such a thing?
There's no way to know.
Not without confirming the truth.
I want you to find out
what the truth is, Ji Na.
- Excuse me?
- Didn't you agree to be on my side?
I'm not quite sure what you want.
Whether you're on Director Jin Se Mi
and Joo Young Chae's side,
or...
if you want to support
Designer Cha Jung Won.
I thought you said
our relationship was the priority.
That's true.
But why should it matter
whose side I'm on?
This is a Kunhyang Family matter.
I'm just worried I'll get in trouble
by getting involved.
I'm sure I've told you before.
Just report the facts.
I know that you were hurt...
after your engagement
with Se Hoon ended...
and that you unwillingly
became competitive...
and are prone to jealousy.
But...
at least as a designer,
I trust that you're a professional.
Whether it's Joo Young Chae
or someone else,
stealing someone else's
design book...
and using it to advance
one's education and career...
is unforgivable, don't you think?
(Damga Charcoal Grill)
- Scooch over a bit so I can sit.
- Of course.
Our handsome CEO Joo
looks so troubled.
Is it because Jung Won
turned you down?
Did you really get rejected?
Even after you sang her
that love song?
Slow down. I know you're upset,
but you'll get sick drinking fast.
Maybe he sang it too well?
- That could be it.
- Why get rejected for singing well?
- It makes you look like a player.
- No, that's not it.
Or...
did you say in front of a big crowd,
"Please accept my love"?
- Kiss her!
May I love you?
- It was something like that.
- And then what?
Jung Won just ran off somewhere.
That's it. She was embarrassed.
I handled that so poorly.
I should have confessed
somewhere quiet and calm.
Enough already!
Jung Won was here yesterday,
moping around too.
Jung Won was?
Even if she's the one who ended it,
she didn't mean it.
I raised her for 25 years.
I know how my daughter feels.
So Jung Won does like me, right?
Even to another man,
you seem so kind and dependable.
There isn't a woman alive
who'd turn you down, CEO Joo.
Cha Jung Won must have
some other reason...
Manager Hwang.
The Chairman Jin Tae Seok
that you know would...
What? You think Jin Tae Seok
interfered again?
I'm not sure. It's just that...
Chairman Jin's daughter, Se Mi...
The one who's the director
of the Design Team?
She's Jin Tae Seok's daughter?
- Then she's Han Hye Ra's daughter?
- That's right.
Miss Jin Se Mi...
has feelings for CEO Joo.
Oh my goodness. Then Jin Tae Seok
must have been scheming.
Knowing Chairman Jin,
for Miss Se Mi's sake,
he's more than capable...
of giving Cha Jung Won
a harsh warning.
Excuse me, I have to go.
(Joo Ha Neul)
(Kunhyang Group
Interim Board Meeting Notice)
(Business Ethics Report
on the Vice Chairman's Scandal)
(Allegations
Regarding Blind Recruitment)
(Kunhyang Group)
(Kunhyang Interim Board Meeting,
Business Ethics)
The Vice Chairman's alleged
involvement in blind hiring...
has been confirmed as true
by the internal audit.
After her child controversy,
the hiring process
is now also an issue.
The company's credibility
has taken a serious hit.
The allegations of blind hiring
are exaggerated.
It's an issue we can easily clear up
with better internal communication.
We have a directive on record
to screen applicants...
by educational background.
This is irrefutable.
Holding the Vice Chairman to account
will only escalate the chaos.
It would basically be admitting
the allegations are true.
After we get a clearer grasp
of the facts...
What's so important about
figuring out if it's true or not?
Frankly, a company lives and dies
by its public image,
Vice Chairman Han Hye Ra's image
built a third of Kunhyang, right?
So whoever destroyed
the company's reputation...
should take responsibility.
Doesn't that only make sense?
- Am I wrong?
- That's right.
I agree.
You all happily rode our coattails
when things were good,
but just because the company's image
is a little tarnished,
you dare to defy me?
That's enough.
Vice President Jin, your opinion?
Kunhyang Group isn't
the personal property...
of the Chairman
and the Vice Chairman.
Our stock price hasn't just dropped.
It's plummeted.
We need to show that Kunhyang
is holding itself accountable.
So I should show them
I'm taking responsibility,
- is that it?
- Yes, that's right.
I object to
Vice President Jin's proposal.
- I'm for it.
- I agree.
I second it.
What do you think you're all doing?
Are you trying to go up against me?
- So you're all in, is that it?
- Calm down, Chairman Jin.
It's not like we're deciding
right this second.
At the next board meeting,
we should discuss...
Vice Chairman Han's resignation
in more depth.
Something along those lines...
That won't be necessary.
I will step down...
from the position of vice chairman.
That is a very wise decision.
So impressive, Han Hye Ra!
Bravo!
(A Graceful Liar)
What are the odds
of two different people...
creating portfolios with the exact
same composition?
A similar layout
is entirely possible.
You'll soon find out
who's telling the truth.
- You have to pay for what you did.
- That's never going to happen.
We should have focused on restoring
the group's reputation first.
But that doesn't mean
you should've just quit!
Watching Han Hye Ra's downfall...
is more entertaining
than making money.
Did you hear something
from Chairman Gong Nan Sook?
Tell him you'll make him
the vice chairman...
only if he loves me.
If Se Hoon becomes
the interim vice chairman,
he'll come for your position.
It's going to be me.
I'm the heir to Kunhyang Group.