THE YEAR 2013
-I want to go to Hong Kong!
-Don't be ridiculous.
You're just thinking of going shopping,
aren't you?
How about Iceland?
The auroras looked really awesome on TV.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Auroras...
-Iceland is good. Or maybe the Himalayas.
The Himalayas? Don't be absurd.
Go by yourself. I'd ruin all my clothes.
Hey. When you face Mother Nature,
you will realize
what an insignificant being you are.
That trip will allow us to look back
on ourselves.
-Turn your head.
-Okay.
Can't you apply lotion yourself?
He'll get dry patches on his face
without his wife.
All right, then...
Let's choose one out of Iceland,
the Himalayas, and Mongolia.
-Okay.
No way. I don't want to. Go there
for your 70th birthday or something.
And why choose where to go
for our 60th birthdays already?
Who knows how long we'll be friends?
We'll be friends
as long as you don't cause any trouble.
-That's right.
-My first pick is Iceland for sure.
-Okay, let's go with that.
-Hey, Geun-sang. Why are you sitting?
-You said you'd make our meals.
-I did. That's it.
No way. Is this really it?
Move aside. You're blocking the fire.
Hyeon-jeong, move.
You're blocking the fire. Move.
It has to look like someone took my photo.
Should we kill this jerk?
-What is it?
-He didn't bring any rice or ramyeon.
-What?
-Really?
You can make noodles when you get home.
Camping is all about the vibe.
You didn't bring meat, either?
-I'm starving!
-No.
-You mean it?
-Yes.
-For real?
-How could you? Are you mad?
-That hurts!
How could you?
What should we do with you?
-You jerk.
-It took us hours to get here.
I didn't come here to starve!
My goodness.
Do you think I came here to starve?
-You didn't even bring ramyeon?
-How?
-How could you do this to us?
-I'm sorry.
Among the countless people in the world,
we build relationships
with certain people and settle down.
I was also blooming like a flower
among the people I was surrounded with.
Hey, go get some water for Dad.
-Go bring some water.
-My goodness.
I CAN'T SEE, SO I REALLY CAN'T WALK THERE
Here.
-Right.
-Looking much younger...
Looking so different...
Hey, Yu-ri!
-Hi!
-Hey!
-Yu-ri!
-It's been so long! How were you?
Hey, it's been such a long time.
-Why were you so late?
-I know, sorry.
I was going to come with Gang-hwa,
but he really couldn't get off work.
I was waiting for him.
We can just eat first.
He'll come and pay for our meals later.
-Really?
-Oh, my gosh!
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
So tell us.
Well, we were just talking...
-I don't know.
-What do you mean, you don't know?
I thought my flower had bloomed
firmly and strongly,
but it disappeared
too quickly.
EPISODE 7:
WHERE FLOWER BLOOMS AND FALLS
Can I do it?
You're keeping a distance from Gang-hwa
because of Min-jeong.
You can't do anything
because Gang-hwa is with Min-jeong.
Hyeon-jeong.
Yes?
I don't belong there anymore.
It's where Min-jeong
should be.
Min-jeong...
is preparing for a divorce.
She wants to divorce Gang-hwa.
What are you talking about?
She's not that kind of person.
There's no way.
I didn't believe it at first, either.
But...
I think it's true.
Yu-ri, don't think about anything else.
Just think about yourself.
What's the reason?
Gang-hwa can't get divorced.
That should never happen.
Why?
-Why can't that happen?
-Well...
Just because...
It just can't happen.
Yu-ri.
Look at me.
Yu-ri, look at me.
What are you hiding?
It's so strange.
I'm sure she's hiding something.
She knew about her drinking limit too.
How does she know so much about Min-jeong?
It's as if she's known her.
Are you feeling anxious?
If it weren't for Dr. Jang,
you would've been fired right away.
Did you win the lottery or something?
How can you be so reckless?
You're not a psychiatrist, dermatologist,
plastic surgeon, or orthopedist.
You're just a thoracic surgeon.
How will you make a living
outside the university hospital?
My goodness.
You're driving me nuts.
Geun-sang.
What is it? You can tell me anything.
You're giving me a headache.
Just go home.
You're so loud.
You talk so much.
Hey. Stop drinking.
Is drinking going to solve everything?
Ask that to the other person
sitting next to you.
Oh, my gosh!
How long have you been sitting there?
-What about the shop?
-I closed it for today.
Why? You were so precise
about closing hours.
Hey, Cho Gang-hwa.
Yes? What is it? Tell me.
You little... Take those out.
Do you know what Min-jeong...
Never mind.
I shouldn't say anything about it.
-You little...
-Don't add to his problems.
He's already going through a lot.
Oh, whatever. I don't know.
Take her home.
Her face will freeze from the cold.
Hey, can't you take her instead?
Okay, fine. Go.
My gosh.
Those two are so annoying.
I told you not to strain yourself.
I told you not to strain
or suppress yourself.
That's not the real you.
Then what is
the real me like?
Go home.
You'll really freeze in this weather.
That punk.
That little...
What did you mean? "Strain yourself"?
The person next to him is lonely
because he's straining himself.
Did Min-jeong say she's lonely?
Why? He's so good to her.
Hey, who do you like more?
Yu-ri or Min-jeong?
That's ridiculous. Is it like,
"Choose Mom or Dad"?
I choose Yu-ri. Definitely.
LOOKING FOR PICK-UP HELPER
SEO-WOO'S MOM
Helping out at the kitchen won't be easy,
but you want to be
Seo-woo's pick-up helper too?
Yes.
The kitchen work ends
before the kindergarten ends,
so I can stay there and get her home.
I don't know about anything else,
but I'm sure it'll be better
for me to do it than anyone else.
How can I know that?
We don't really know each other.
Right.
We don't.
Did you do something wrong behind my back?
Pardon?
Last night at the restaurant,
and now again...
you keep avoiding my eyes.
As if you're feeling guilty
about something.
Oh, did I do that?
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry.
I mean...
about your forehead.
I headbutted you.
I remember what I did.
Oh, it's fine.
It sounded pretty bad,
but my forehead is really firm
so that blow didn't cause much pain.
You look worse than me.
You have two injuries.
It must really hurt.
Seo-woo.
Do you like that kitchen lady?
Yes. I like the pretty lady.
You never smiled like that to me.
I feel kind of sad.
But I like you more.
You dried your hair in the bathroom again.
Yes. I'd drop hair on the floor
if I dry it outside.
I said I don't need vegetable juice.
It'll just be a bother to you.
Seo-woo, are you up? Should we go wash up?
No, it's fine. I'll do it.
All right, let's go wash up.
Gang-hwa.
I have something to talk about.
Is there something going on?
I heard that Seo-woo is a bit different
from other kids,
and that I should get her tested.
So I did.
CHO SEO-WOO
ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT
UNDERDEVELOPED
It seems like she's having some problems.
It's okay, Min-jeong. These places
always make things seem serious.
You don't need to worry.
Kids all develop differently.
Some can be slower than others.
Don't worry about it.
All right.
And I think I'll get busy soon,
I'm thinking
of getting a pick-up helper again.
Right. That would be more convenient.
The new kitchen assistant
at Seo-woo's kindergarten...
What do you think of her?
-Who?
-The kitchen assistant, the young lady.
She said she wants to do it.
Oh, really?
So did you say she could do it?
I told her I'd think about it.
What do you think?
Well...
Well, what about you?
I'll think about it.
Oh, all right.
Do as you like.
I couldn't get any sleep
because of those darned ghosts.
You don't have much time left.
You can't afford to sleep.
We might have to wait a long time
if we take time thinking,
so we're just going to ask
our favor first.
Why are you hiding there like that?
-Well...
-We're on our way out.
Do you know
that everyone's been silent
since your visit?
How can I choose just one favor to ask?
Those ghosts already have a hard time
deciding on anything.
And you said
you'd only accept one favor each.
This is like torture for them.
It's him.
What? Wasn't he unemployed?
Our son's a pilot!
Look at him in his uniform.
Doesn't he look great?
Let's go.
Is he raising a pig?
I'm not doing this. I can't!
-No! Wait!
-You said you would.
Don't you have a conscience?
You want me to clean a place
that's dirtier than a pigpen?
I said I'd do you a favor,
not do manual labor.
You must be crazy.
That was way too harsh!
-What's with you?
-How could you
call someone else's kid a pig?
Why are you suddenly crying?
-How could she call him a pig?
-My son...
How could she call him a pig?
Unbelievable!
Hey, when did I call him a pig?
That was just a metaphor.
-How could you...
-How could you?
How could you say such a thing?
-Hello.
Hi, Seo-woo. Oh, I'll take that.
All right, let's take off your shoes.
Seo-woo, why don't you say hi
to the kitchen lady too?
-Hello.
Oh, hello to you too.
Did the young kitchen assistant
not come to work today?
She took half the day off today.
Is there something you need?
No, it's nothing. I'll be off then.
Seo-woo, I'll see you later.
Bye.
Dad.
KIM PAN-SEOK
Mom and I are here.
Have you been well?
Your other daughter has to work,
so she'll come later.
Why did you come here again?
You must have lots of stuff to do.
And why did you bring so much?
It must have been heavy.
My goodness.
Are you that happy?
Poor people show that they're poor,
whatever they do.
Hello, sir.
What? Did they really bring that
for the memorial?
That dry, cheap-looking fruit?
Even my dog wouldn't touch that.
Right. But it's the heart that counts.
My gosh.
Look. You being right next to me
is ruining my image.
Get rid of those pieces of paper in there.
Those ten-thousand-won bills.
It's so tacky.
Do they want you to earn lots of money
after your death
since you couldn't when you were alive?
What a nice family you have.
I guess they want me
to enjoy spending money now
since I was poor during my life.
You killed an innocent man,
but you're going to enjoy your afterlife?
No, of course not, sir. I'm sorry.
My goodness. That old man is at it again.
If they died at the same time,
their fates are more entwined
than those of spouses.
But he's always bullying him.
He still thinks he's his driver
even after they're dead.
Well, he died when that man was driving.
APPRECIATION PLAQUE
So I can understand how he feels.
BAEK SAM-DONG
-Okay, come again next time.
-All right.
-Be careful of water.
-Okay.
Darn it, you baby ghost.
You really can't see anything?
I can't.
Am I supposed to see the future
or something?
No. If you see them, you should see
a kind of color. Like an aura.
If it's purple,
it's depression or poverty.
If it's red, then it's always
the husband cheating on them.
You can tell right away.
Damn it. This baby ghost
just ruined my work today.
Damn it. Look at this. This is all I got.
Darn it.
Don't touch that!
You didn't even earn enough to eat that!
Spit that back out!
Excuse me?
Welcome.
-Look properly. Come on.
-I can't see anything.
The doctor?
Next time you come here,
make sure to wear that watch.
Yes!
You're right!
How did you know I wear a white gown?
I was sent to get treatment
for my depression,
and he was the doctor.
You wear a white gown,
and your specialty is the mind.
Psychiatry, like depression?
Yes, you're right.
You're right.
You're really good.
Ma'am.
My friend...
You must pay the fee first.
You must pay your respects
to the spirit here.
Who?
-Who's there?
-Doctor, it's me.
Only I can see him.
Don't try to see him, or he'll haunt you.
Haunt me?
That's right. Keep going.
All right, what do you want to know?
My dead friend came back to life.
-What?
-She died five years ago,
and her ashes were put
at the cinerarium here, but she's alive.
Is that possible?
Cha Yu-ri. He's talking about her.
That is possible.
That happens occasionally.
This is possible? Occasionally?
Coming back from the dead
happens occasionally?
Of course. Everyone has a friend
who came back to life.
-You said you have one.
-What?
-Yes.
-I have a friend like that.
-So everyone has that kind of friend.
-You're right. But you know what?
You shouldn't go to other shamans
and talk about something like this
with them.
Okay.
That's lame.
No. Stop it. Don't be lame.
That troublemaker, Yu-ri.
I'll die before my time because of her.
Is he really a doctor?
He's not sharp at all.
What was...
What was his name? Bong? Bin?
Where did he go this time?
What is all this?
I mean, no housekeeper can last a week.
They all quit.
-They are not patient at all.
-A week?
I would have quit after the first day.
This looks like it's been here for ages.
But this didn't go bad.
-I don't see any bugs here, either.
-Of course, not.
-Don't you know who we are?
-Come on.
You guys are unbelievable.
He'll clean this up
when there are bugs all over it.
No way. My son has atopic dermatitis.
Insects will ruin his skin.
But still. I'm glad that
I can still do something for my son.
I don't need 49 days like you.
Just one.
I just want to be human just for one day.
When my son was growing up,
there wasn't anything I could do for him.
It would make me so happy
if I could cook him a meal.
My son, Pil-seung,
has never had a home-cooked meal
that everyone had before.
He wouldn't know since he had never
had it once for more than 20 years.
To others, it's always there
like the air we breathe in.
Only my son couldn't have it.
THE YEAR 1999
Seriously.
Your teacher only complimented you.
Well done. My daughter is great.
I'm so proud of you.
-Oh, Dad.
-What?
Did you know my mom
is the prettiest mom at my school?
Of course, she is the prettiest one.
You know what she did?
She took out all of her outfits
and tried on multiple outfits
for the parent-teacher conference.
She changed her outfit thousands of times.
Pil-seung's school will be over soon.
Let's hurry.
My goodness.
Your mother is kind of cute today.
There's Pil-seung.
I told him to wait there.
Look at him standing there.
He's not even moving an inch.
He's a good boy.
Let's go.
Mom.
Go.
My baby.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I don't want your pity.
We're in the same boat.
Right. Every ghost has a sad story.
But you know what?
You can touch your daughter.
I'm envious of that.
Except for that,
I'm not envious of anything.
If I have to choose
between getting reincarnated for 49 days
as a human before going up
and watching my son for the rest
of his life, I'll choose the latter.
I'm going to watch my son
getting married and becoming a father.
I'll watch him for the rest of his life.
Stop chatting.
Aren't you going to clean his house?
Dr. Cho.
-Yes?
-You'll choke yourself.
What's wrong with you today?
He doesn't seem normal today either.
Hey, guys.
Everyone,
has anyone
that you know of
come back to life from the dead?
-What?
Like Jesus?
What are you doing, you crazy bastard?
No, I heard it occasionally happens.
Apparently, it happens occasionally.
Who said that?
Stop it, you crazy bastard.
A shaman.
A really spiritual shaman.
I went to another shaman because
my go-to shaman's energy got weak.
But that shaman
almost made me wet my pants.
She knows everything. Do you want to go?
-My father is a pastor.
-Right.
What about you guys?
-I'm leaving.
-Me too.
Bye.
Go ahead.
Gosh, they don't know anything. Goodness.
She's really spiritual.
Hey, do you want to go?
Yu-ri wants to be
Seo-woo's pick-up helper.
Okay. Really?
Really? Really...
The pick-up helper?
Hey, the pick-up helper has to
get Seo-woo from the kindergarten
and stay at your house
until you or Min-jeong gets home.
She wants to do that? Stay at the house
where you and Min-jeong live?
Yes.
Yu-ri...
She's...
Then, she should let you
tell the truth to Min-jeong.
But she's putting people around her
through a great deal of trouble.
-She can do everything, but this.
-You got that right.
I'm sure she misses Seo-woo.
I know she wants to see Seo-woo.
Then, she can watch Seo-woo
at the kindergarten.
Why would she? For what?
A local ghost?
There's a local ghost in that house?
Yes.
When I was a ghost,
I kicked him out a few times.
I think he's still there.
You want to be her pick-up helper?
To scare away the ghost?
I got rid of all the ghosts
at the kindergarten.
But I can't enter his house now.
This is my only way.
You're right.
She spends most of her time at home.
If there's a ghost at her house,
your effort will go to nothing.
You know what? Hold on.
I've been listening. And as a man,
I put myself in his shoes
and thought this through, you know.
My gosh, but what you're doing
to your husband is out of the line.
Listen. He's remarried.
All of a sudden, his ex-wife shows up
and is forcing herself into his home.
If I were him, I would have lost it.
I know that.
That's why I gave this a lot of thought.
What can I do?
I'm the only one who can protect Seo-woo.
Stop talking nonsense.
Forget it.
You're in no place to worry about others.
-Your daughter might become a shaman.
-I agree.
You're right. You have a point.
What?
Hello?
It was my day off. I read my flight
schedule wrong and went to work.
Yes.
Hold on. Let me call you back.
What's wrong with my house?
Why is it clean?
Damn it. Those darn ghosts.
I'm done helping you when I get out.
Uncle, we're here. I brought my mom here.
You've been well, right?
Yes.
Goodness. You're here to see me, Sis.
I know you're not well.
Why did you come all the way here?
Gosh.
Goodness.
Look at that boy.
You're not supposed to jump here.
All right.
It's all right. That's fine.
Gosh. Jin-gyeong, you grew a lot.
That's enough.
Did you rent out this cinerarium?
I'm sorry, sir. My older sister
came to see me again.
Only your family comes here to visit you.
You bought the cheapest slot here,
but you get the most visitors.
They should limit the number of visitors
depending on the slots you got.
Don't you agree? Isn't that right?
That's a load of rubbish.
What?
What did that old hag say?
What? "Old hag"?
Did you just call me an old hag,
you old geezer?
People with nothing to show for
are always bad-tempered, you know.
You're an old hag.
How else should I call you?
What? You--
Hey!
What did you just say to my friend?
Why are you butting in, you hag?
"Hag"?
Look here.
You're so young that chewing you
into pieces won't be any use.
What have you been eating
to give you such a big ego like this?
Should I carve out your eye
and flick it with my finger?
Or should I stretch your intestines
and jump rope with them?
You're still wet behind your ears
like a whining baby.
Hey.
If we counted the number of times
we used the bathroom,
my number is way higher than yours.
You stinking jerk.
Hey, do you know who you're talking to?
Do you?
You're a ghost.
Do you think you're still a chairman
of a conglomerate when you're dead?
Can you spend a dime of the money
you piled up?
We're all walking the same path.
What? I revived the economy of Korea.
The whole world acknowledged
my achievement.
But this guy only passed on
his debts to his kids.
What? We're all walking the same path?
Of course, not.
My life is nothing compared to yours.
Please calm down.
How dare you judge someone else's life?
I'll be blunt.
Who can guarantee that King Sejong lived
a more fruitful life than Mr. Kim here?
Who can judge that Mr. Kim left
behind less achievements than Mansour?
You must be your own judge of life.
Forget about the world or whatnot.
What's the point of getting acknowledged
by the world and the others?
Mr. Kim, square your shoulders.
Do you know how much money
I left behind in this world?
How many assets I have?
A trillion won?
That's right.
I have several trillion won.
Goodness. Is that so, Mr. Chairman?
I did not know that.
In that case, why don't you go back
to your spacious altar?
Why don't you hop into that?
What's the point of having so much money?
What? Wait. Where are you going?
We're in the middle of an argument.
Come back here! Come back!
-Sir, calm down.
-Come back!
-Sir, please calm down.
-Calm down.
-Come back here.
BURIAL PAYMENT OVERDUE NOTICE
FAMILY CANNOT BE REACHED
The receiver cannot be reached.
Ma'am, were you able to reach her?
She's not answering her phone.
She just started working here.
I can't believe she skipped her shift
without notice.
Goodness.
BIG AUNT
Isn't it good?
My gosh, this is the real deal.
Seeing you enjoying this food
is breaking my heart.
What? What's wrong with you?
He may look like an independent grown-up,
but he must resent us a lot.
We left him in this big world
all by himself.
My poor baby.
That prick. I bet he can see us. He does.
You little brat.
Don't call your brother that!
Gosh, I'm so full. That was a great meal.
I can't breathe.
Son, clean up
if you're done with your meal.
Clean up first. Where are you going?
-Where are you going?
-Hey.
-No. Not there.
-Don't go in there. No.
-You can't go in there.
Hey, where are you going? You're naked.
What? Why did he take off his clothes?
Let's shower.
He's going to shower. Let's leave
when he goes into the bathroom.
Son, I know why you're looking
at the mirror. You take after me.
Why don't you go in?
-You're not making this easy on her.
-He's about to go in.
Here he goes.
Yu-ri, come out. Come on out.
Now! Come out now!
Now. Hurry and leave.
Go back in!
-Go back in. He said to go back in. Hurry.
-What? Why?
-Hurry. Go back in.
-My gosh.
What's going on?
What? Why? What is it this time?
My gosh, you startled me.
You might scare a ghost to death!
This is dirty. Why is it here?
Why do you think it's there?
It's because you put it there.
My gosh, that's disgusting.
Okay. It's clean.
What is it? Just go and wash up.
Mom! Dad!
-What is it? What?
-What?
Look at this. Look.
Son, this isn't right. Okay?
Put it down. No, don't do it.
This is bad.
Son, that can be dangerous. Put it down.
What are you doing?
What? What is it? What's going on?
-No, no.
-Please don't. Don't do it.
Grab the door! Do it!
-Damn it.
-Grab it!
-Grab it tight!
-Do it!
What are you doing here?
It's okay, Min-jeong.
You don't need to worry.
This is nothing. Don't worry about it.
Why is everything my fault?
You try taking care of the house
and watch the kid too.
I'm hanging up.
My husband says the same thing.
They should try taking care of the kids.
I get that he's disappointed.
But is that the best he could do?
Will they lose a tongue
if they say it's okay?
I know!
My gosh, I'm upset too.
Right?
Pardon?
Yes.
A paternity leave? Why?
Well, just because.
My wife has a lot on her plate.
I wanted to help out at home.
Wouldn't having a dad at home
better than a pick-up helper?
No one takes time off while being reviewed
for disciplinary action.
That just means they are resigning.
Resigning? Right.
There won't be any other way, right?
-Yes.
What?
Because you want to be the pick-up helper?
My gosh, you're so simple-minded.
You should all go home.
If you came here to do the house chores,
you should leave when you finished.
Why did you go in there, ma'am?
Don't call me ma'am.
Okay, lady.
What a small world.
How did you end up cleaning my house
out of all the houses?
And you keep getting a nosebleed.
It's all your fault!
I cooked a meal for you,
but you beat me up in return.
Right. She should have said
she was a housekeeper from the get-go.
Why did you make her hide?
Who would have thought
that he would believe that?
-We didn't.
Right. We didn't.
I'm sorry, Yu-ri. It hurts, right?
I'm sorry.
What is it? What are you looking at?
Is something there? That, again?
Anyway, I'm leaving since I did my work.
-Hey.
-Where are you going?
You should clean up! You're disgusting.
-Excuse me.
-What? What do you want?
Well, you know...
Are you coming back?
I'll tell the guy to pay you handsomely.
I guess you like my food.
I didn't cook that.
Add honey.
-Honey?
-Yes. Honey.
One more drizzle.
Pil-seung loved my salad with honey.
More, more. More!
More finely. He doesn't like onions.
Be gentle. Mix thoroughly.
You need to be gentle with that.
Now! Flip it now!
Hurry!
Son.
What? Did you buy it then?
Is there a store that sells rice pancakes?
I looked everywhere, but there was none.
Anyway, I have nothing to say to you.
I'm glad that you liked it.
Wait. Hey.
Well, it wasn't that good, anyway.
Goodness. Seriously.
Stop following me.
Or I'll tell your son that the food he ate
was cooked by his own mother.
Hey, no!
-He'd be really scared if he knows. Never!
-No.
-We're leaving now.
-You're crazy.
-We'll go.
-We're leaving.
-We're leaving. Bye.
-Bye.
-Let's go.
-We're going.
My goodness. They are so irritating.
Seriously.
You guys are crazy about your son.
Why do you only stay at his house?
I would follow him to work
and everywhere he goes.
My son is a pilot. He drives planes.
-So what?
-What if we follow him there
and end up going up for real?
It's dangerous to go
beyond the stratosphere. It's our rule.
He could have been anything he wanted,
but he became a pilot.
It's scary for ghosts, you know?
Exactly. Since he got good grades,
he should've been
-a doctor, a judge, or a lawyer.
-Right.
Can't he work on the ground?
Exactly. That's what I'm talking about.
-Gosh, they are such cowards.
-Exactly.
SINCE MY BELOVED FAMILY
ISN'T IN THIS WORLD,
I WILL FLY UP TO THEM
That's so funny.
Where were you? You won't pick...
-What's with your nose? Did you get hurt?
-Oh, no.
I had to meet someone.
Coming.
What have you been doing to this hour
without eating anything?
Right.
Someone asked me for a favor,
so I helped them out.
Why did you get a bloody nose?
This? I must've been tired lately.
I'm fine.
If you were so tired that
you got a bloody nose, why did you...
Never mind. Eat up.
Why aren't you eating?
I'll eat. You can eat up.
She's a pick-up helper?
Yes.
Gang-hwa is completely out of it.
What's wrong with her?
You know, Hyeon-jeong,
I'm thrilled
that Yu-ri came back to life. I...
I'm all choked up with excitement.
But she should tell everything
and find a way around this.
Even if they pull their hair out
claiming to be Seo-woo's mom,
Min-jeong should know the facts too.
Yu-ri isn't looking to work things out
with Gang-hwa again,
nor is she trying to be Seo-woo's mom.
What?
Then why does she want to be
a pick-up helper?
-Gang-hwa.
-Yes?
You don't have to mind me so much.
Don't worry about me and go do your thing.
I've been awfully busy every single day.
So you don't have to do this.
For how long?
What?
For how long should I do nothing?
Don't you miss your mom and your daughter?
You miss your mother and Seo-woo.
Why do you always see them in secret? Why?
Let's tell everything to Mother
and to Min-jeong too.
Everyone will be shocked
if we tell them everything.
They'll be in huge shock. But Yu-ri,
I'm sure there's a way. Okay?
You heard that I wanted to work
as a pick-up helper, didn't you?
Yes.
I guess she wants to be by her child.
Can't you
just let her do it?
Hyeon-jeong.
If she becomes a pick-up helper,
Gang-hwa will die of stress.
Think about it.
He's living with his wife.
Yu-ri can't be there.
What kind of lunatic would say yes
to that? No way.
Can I do it?
Work as a pick-up helper?
I really have to do this.
I'm so sorry, Seo-woo.
Please stop crying.
Mommy is sorry.
Okay. Go ahead.
You can do it.
Hey, now that I think about it,
this is pretty awful.
Are you only concerned about your friend?
What about Yu-ri?
Did I do that? Why did I do that?
I mean, you know,
I'm a biological male,
so I can connect more easily
with Gang-hwa. That's all.
Yu-ri...
Of course, I feel bad about her.
Hey, it's Aunt. It's Aunt.
From Sang-dong?
Aunt.
Why won't you pick up your phone?
Hey, I've been really busy
running around trying to catch
a virgin ghost.
What is it?
Ms. Mi-dong? No idea.
Not all shamans know one another.
-Why? Is she good?
-She's excellent.
She even guessed that
I was a neuropsychiatrist.
She is good. No one would think
you're a neuropsychiatrist.
A patient, maybe.
Anyway, where does she live?
Peace Temple?
MS. MI-DONG
Anyway, I told you to stop seeing shamans.
You have the perfect energy
for ghosts to possess.
Tell them to come and possess me.
Hyeon-jeong is stronger than all of them.
Tell them to come!
If a female ghost comes,
she'll pull out her hair,
and if it's a male ghost,
she'll marry him off.
-Hey, you.
-Look at her.
Why are ghosts sitting around
not taking her away?
Do you want to die?
I'm all out of energy,
so I've been freezing to death.
Don't tell your mom
and send me 100,000 won...
-Never mind, make it 200,000 won. Okay?
-Wait.
Aunt, send me your bank account later.
Ms. Mi-dong.
So this woman
is a better shaman than I am?
Here's an update on MI Corporation,
a company causing all kinds of scandals
ever since Chairman Baek Sam-dong's death.
Chairman Baek's children and his siblings
abused and slandered each other verbally
during their general meeting.
Once again,
the problem was the dividend of stocks
-which Chairman Baek had left.
-That mess of a family is at it again.
Who cares how much money
he left his family?
-His kids and siblings are at war.
-Another huge war broke out
-over sharing the dividend.
-He lived his life in vain.
Exactly. Even if I had all of his money,
I wouldn't want to die
after living a life like that.
What did you say, jerk?
You lowlife.
Goodness.
-Let's go.
-There were incidents
such as his first son's power trip,
his second son's recruitment corruption,
and his youngest daughter's violence
against her employees.
His family received criticisms
from the entire nation
while undergoing
the prosecution investigation.
Tomorrow, his first son,
Vice-chairman Baek Jin-hyeon will
undergo a trial for his charges.
BURIAL PAYMENT OVERDUE NOTICE
FAMILY CANNOT BE REACHED
It's raining.
Yes, my house is nearby, so it's great.
Thanks for your concern.
I'll buy you a meal
after I get reinstated.
Okay.
What? It's raining?
I don't have an umbrella.
Oh, this is rain with fine dust,
so you shouldn't be exposed to it.
I see.
Let's walk together.
Right, I...
I was going this way,
and this umbrella is bigger than it looks.
Do you want to use it together?
Then will you share it with me?
Man, it just looks like a shower.
Should I buy an umbrella?
Min-jeong, you're on the phone.
You didn't take an umbrella.
Should I come and pick you up?
What is this? What...
What are you doing?
How far are you going?
What? I'm headed to...
-Aren't you going to that apartment?
-Yes.
May I go with you to that point?
It's obviously a shower,
so it's a waste to get an umbrella.
Don't you think so?
Right, you don't want to waste your money.
So do you live there in my neighborhood?
No, I'll find someone else
once I get there.
I'll transfer and transfer
until I get home.
"Transfer."
Okay, then. Let's go.
Let's go.
Do you always feel self-conscious
around others?
No way. I don't get self-conscious.
No way. You've always
looked self-conscious from the start.
I only do that to you...
Do other mothers at the kindergarten say
how I'm so full of myself,
calling me Put-off?
You know that?
That I'm full of myself?
No, your nickname, Put-off.
Of course, I know.
I'm Put-off because I'm such a put-off.
How immature.
It's okay. I don't care about such things.
People are awfully mean.
Aren't they?
I thought you didn't care.
Yes, it doesn't get on my nerves.
You keep lying to yourself.
Of course, it's concerning
when people insult you.
Everyone stands up for themselves.
We don't pretend like we're okay.
-Really?
-Of course.
Even deities get angry
when they're slandered.
Should we face them and end this together?
No, I don't want to.
You're way too nice.
You're the first one to say I'm nice.
You don't seem to have good discernment.
My gosh. This is the first time
I was attacked after giving a compliment.
Anyway, my shoulder has been
getting wet for a while.
This side of my shoulder
is getting wet too.
You said it's bigger than it looks,
but it's tiny. Let me have a bit more...
This is mine.
Gosh, I take back that I said you're nice.
If you take it back,
I'll have a little more...
Can't you see that
my shoulder is soaking wet?
THE YEAR 2013
Do you want to die?
No one in this world would want to die.
You're joking, right?
I told you time and time again
to make sure you pack it.
No, I...
You better not say you were
too busy watching that drama to hear me.
As you know very well,
yesterday was the last episode
of "Reply 1994."
I needed to know
who Na-jeong's husband was.
I mean, it was the day before our camp.
We had a lot to prepare, right?
Why did they air
their last episode yesterday?
That drama was wrong.
-Right?
-Darn it.
Hey, you idiot.
I can't believe what he's saying.
He'll probably die on the streets
without his wife.
Do you have any leftover hand warmers?
Does it look like I do?
He only brought things to show off.
He didn't bring any hand warmers.
It's so cold.
Stop taking pictures.
It's freezing.
How can we sleep without any hand warmers?
We have hand warmers.
I'm right here. A human hand warmer.
All right, come here.
It won't be cold if we stick together.
-Come here. Come right here.
-My gosh.
-Goodness. Here.
-Oh no.
Gosh, it's so warm. It's warm.
It's not cold at all.
I'm cold and hungry.
You're cold and hungry?
You're like a homeless woman.
Go to sleep, my little homeless
Go to sleep
There is no flower in this world
that blooms without a meaning.
In that place where I bloomed and fell,
other flowers of mine were starting
to bloom.
You told her to do it?
What are you going to do now?
-Should I work in Sri Lanka?
-Call her.
-She won't come.
-You're right. It's because I'm here.
Why not? Does she want a divorce?
The dead child is too concerned
for her mother to leave this world.
She thinks her current mother
is her real mother. What if she finds out?
I miss her so much!
Your life is not only yours
but also your parents'.
Yu-ri.
Even I feel this frustrated!
Seo-woo is sick because of me.
I just need her to be healthy.