(Kawai Momoka)
Tai-chan, good morning!
Good morning.
The summer break was so short.
We got two months off.
Summer breaks are fun.
- Right? You get to travel.
- Mm.
Here. Pictures from
when we were playing sparklers.
Oh, thank you.
- Check them out.
- Really?
Wow, a rare picture of Senior Takara.
Mm.
It was the summer break where
I got a little closer to Senior Takara.
(Hiking Club)
You guys are probably still distracted
now that the new semester began.
Tomorrow we will hike up Mount Takao!
- Yay!
Hiking...
But this time
it's gonna be a relaxing hike.
Freshmen can come.
Think of it as a field trip.
What's the budget for snacks?
Just 500 yen. Not one yen more.
Why are you so strict?
Do bananas qualify as snacks?
They do because
they have nutritional value.
Can you come up with a new joke?
- Sorry. I have to take this call.
- Mm.
So let's get into planning groups.
How is he so cool
just going out to take the call?
He's been getting lots of calls.
Mm, especially lately.
Who's been calling him?
I wouldn't know.
I know who because I overheard them.
Were you eavesdropping?
I just happened to hear a woman's voice.
- A woman?
- Mm.
I think Takara finally
got himself a girlfriend.
Is that so?
Mm.
Is this the person who...
(Kawai Momoka)
called him back then?
Hey, don't speculate.
Yes, because as far as I know,
he doesn't have a girlfriend.
No way he does.
That's what you hope. Think about it.
How could someone
so handsome not have a girlfriend?
If I had to guess, he's probably madly
in love with an older girl off-campus.
No, no way!
Don't tell me his possessive older
girlfriend has been checking in on him.
That's not him being madly in love.
You're overthinking this.
Senior...
has a girlfriend...
"Takara's Treasure"
(Episode 6)
Back there, was he...
missing his girlfriend?
It feels strange in my chest again.
Is the meeting over?
Uh, yes.
We'll meet at the foot
of the mountain tomorrow at nine.
Noted.
What's up?
No, it's just...
It's just...
Bananas are delicious
when we eat them on a mountain.
What's up with you?
- By the way,
- Hmm.
you've been getting
a lot of calls lately.
Who's been calling you?
It's none of your business.
This is bad.
I can't fall asleep.
I actually managed to get close to him.
Did I offend him?
Yes?
What's wrong? You sound angry.
Oh, it's you, Grandpa.
Yes, it's your grandpa.
Did you answer without checking?
Kind of.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Eh?
You sound so down.
I'm not feeling down.
Got into a fight with your friend?
I said no.
Say what you feel, Takara.
This is bad.
I didn't sleep a wink.
I really have to clear things up
with Senior Takara today.
Huh?
Eh?
(Takara: I have a cold.
I'll pass today.)
Did he get a fever?
(Akira: Really?)
(Minami: Can you manage by yourself?)
Will I bother him if I contact him?
But...
if his fever gets high
that he can't move...
Anybody...
If no one's taking care of him...
he might die.
Hello, what's up, Nakano-kun?
- I'll check on Senior Takara.
- Eh?
Hello?
Hello, Nakano-kun?
What happened?
Showing up unannounced.
Will it be okay?
(Taishin: I'm coming to you.)
But...
No.
If I get there too late,
that would be worse.
What do you want?
Hey, Takara...
Is that his girlfriend?
Why are you being so cold?
Because you showed up at my place.
I had no choice.
Because you wouldn't answer
my calls and listen to reason.
Let's be honest.
What else is there to talk about?
Please.
You're all I have!
I'm all you have, my ass.
You left me.
Always.
You're always like this.
Always looking down on other people.
Even if someone's in trouble,
you won't help.
You're so cold-hearted.
That's not true.
Nakano?
Senior Takara isn't cold-hearted.
He's unbelievably kind.
Huh?
Hey, Nakano...
When I was sad and cried,
he was kind to me.
When I sprained my ankle,
he was there for me.
- And he saved me from that crazy uncle.
- Crazy uncle?
He's...
always there when I'm in trouble.
And he doesn't look down on anyone.
For someone who knows nothing,
you shouldn't talk like
you've known him forever.
- Huh?
- And...
he has a cold right now.
I will take care of him.
Are you done here?
Did you hear that?
I understand what you want to say.
But quit hoping.
Don't come here again.
Is that so?
You really are cold-blooded.
What did you say? He's not cold-blooded!
Hey, take it easy.
Who is that woman?
That person...
is my mother.
Eh?
Are you still worried?
Well, I...
was rude to your mother.
Rude?
- I'm gonna apologize to her right now.
- No need.
Why did you come anyway?
You said you had a cold.
So I was worried.
I bought a lot of things.
Vegetables and medicine.
I'm just a little sore.
You're more motherly than my mom.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Because my mother
never once did this for me.
Eh?
It's a boring story.
You don't need to hear it.
I...
want to know everything about you.
My parents...
got a divorce.
This is getting out of hand.
How much more do you need to be happy?!
What did you say?
What if they call me poor?!
They kept fighting over
my mother's lavish spending.
I never said that!
- So their marriage deteriorated.
- Would you stop already?!
But...
I can't take this anymore!
The person who always got me out
of the house was my grandfather.
Come on, drink this.
What is it?
Oh, you've never had this?
- No.
- That won't do.
It's Ramune,
the coolest drink in the world.
Life isn't worth living without it.
Look closely.
Come on, try it.
Yummy.
There's something in the bottle.
That thing? It's a marble.
It won't come out.
Give it here.
In the past, I just broke the bottles.
Here.
It's so shiny.
What is it made of?
It's made of glass.
Glass?
There's an upside-down sky inside.
Really? Upside down?
It's prettier than the ones Mom has.
Is it very expensive?
Mm, expensive things
aren't always beautiful.
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
Let's just say to your mother,
jewelry is beautiful.
But to you, marbles are.
Hm.
There's something I consider beautiful.
Like your grandma in the sky.
The sky.
The stars.
And the mountains.
Mountains?
That's right. Mountains.
Next time I'll take you with me.
Hm.
My grandfather's...
always looking out for me.
But...
Mom.
This is for you.
It's a marble.
It's sparkling and beautiful.
I don't want cheap things like this.
Then they divorced and my father raised me.
But she still shows up like that
to ask me for his money.
Is that so?
I had no idea.
Never mind that.
Because I didn't tell anyone.
I'm sorry for pestering you about it
when it has nothing to do with me.
Sorry about yesterday.
One more thing.
You saved me by talking back
to my mom like that.
Thank you.
There's something...
I have in common with her.
Eh?
So I've always hated it.
What do you two have in common?
I...
Just like my mother...
When we want something, we...
Are you warm?
Eh?
Oh.
There are things
that have been bothering me lately.
So I've been losing sleep.
My brain feels kinda fuzzy.
You've got a fever
over anxiety like a child.
Put these on.
His...
clothes...
Here. Drink this.
There's no need.
I already feel guilty as it is.
Just do it.
Come on, put it on.
Get some sleep.
I'm sorry.
I came to take care of you.
Now I'm the one being taken care of.
Sorry for making you worried.
Uh...
You're a kind person.
What are you talking about?
I...
I'm glad I got to meet you.
I'm glad we met again.
And I'm glad you've been kind to me.
I'm really happy.
But I'm always nervous.
And I've kept causing you trouble.
That's not true.
I find it strange.
You're...
not my friend.
You're certainly not my family.
Even though I saw you as my idol,
it turned out that you weren't.
So...
what it is...
that I'm feeling?
What kind of affection is this?
Nakano.
You really are dumb.
(Next episode)
It's possible.
It wasn't a dream.
I'd like to know more.
You've become the junior
I don't know how to handle
or won't be able to handle.
What should I do?
If I want something,
I'll find a way to have it.
I'm sorry.