[Love Strikes Back]
[Episode 8]
Yan,
we can't stay in this hotel.
Its design is not reasonable
at all, right?
The distance between the room
and the restaurant is too far.
It will be tiring to walk.
Chengjun, what do you
really want to say?
I want to say
that we should change to another hotel.
Isn't this your favorite hotel?
I remembered the last time
you booked this hotel
for the honeymoon after our marriage.
I thought you remembered.
I never thought you would forget it all.
What are you doing?
I think this hotel is good too.
Look at this umbrella in the lobby.
The workmanship is awesome
and exquisite.
I think we can stay here.
You're not listening at all.
How could I forget?
I still remember the first time we met.
You were at the library's front door,
holding a red umbrella.
That was so lovely.
I've finished the room reservation.
I'll take you there.
Okay.
Why is he here?
Xiao Mo is my personal bodyguard.
Of course, he has to
protect me 24 hours.
Don't worry.
We will have
a very memorable holiday.
(Lin Yan and I also came
to this hotel for vacation.)
[Wen Lili]
(You have to leave immediately.)
(Don't let her see you.)
Chengjun,
be quick.
This is your room.
I'm next door.
Just call me anytime
if you need something.
Okay.
You brat did it on purpose, right?
Mr. Ma,
your room is over there.
You brat did it on purpose, right?
I…
I'll deal with you later.
Ma Chengjun, what do you mean by this?
Why did you bring Lin Yan here?
I don't have time
to explain all of this now.
Anyway, you have to leave immediately.
I will explain it to you later.
Ma Chengjun.
Ma…
Why did you agree
to go on vacation with Ma Chengjun?
Is it because you still
have feelings for him?
How could I possibly
still have feelings for him?
I don't really have amnesia.
So, what is your purpose?
Wen Lili is also in this hotel.
So, I think as long as Wen Lili is here,
Ma Chengjun will not
keep forcing me to marry him.
We need to find something for him to do.
This way, we'll have more time
to discover more of his flaws.
Isn't that correct?
[Ma Chengjun]
(Yan, I've prepared a surprise for you.)
(I guarantee you will like it.)
(Meet me downstairs later.)
Yan.
♪I'm coming round, coming back♪
♪Like a volcano♪
♪Flowing down on the track♪
♪Running up, running down,
pull your back, make a sound♪
♪Ready I'm going in♪
♪Freakin' up, freakin' down♪
♪All like that, to the ground,
when I came back within♪
♪I'm coming through the fire♪
♪I'm running through the flame♪
♪But, I'm holding back 'till today♪
♪Here I come again♪
This is for my beloved princess, Yan.
I'm really surprised and overwhelmed.
Don't be too surprised and overwhelmed.
I have a more important gift for you.
Jun, a prince who loves you forever.
Wait.
Yan,
you haven't been willing
to get close to me since you woke up.
How could it be possible?
I'm just thinking
as you carefully designed these,
I need to figure out a way
to keep a memento.
Let's take a picture.
Yes.
Three, two…
[Lin Yan: It's another beautiful day.]
Stupid Ma Chengjun.
You want to dump me
and be lovey-dovey
with Lin Yan, don't you?
Don't ever think about it.
Yan, how about the wedding date
that I mentioned last time?
[Wen Lili]
(Honey, I want to meet you.)
(I'm in the dress you like the most.)
You look very busy.
Who is looking for you?
My subordinate, Li.
All are business-related matters.
No need to worry.
[Wen Lili]
(I am now at your room's front door.)
(I'll go for you if you are not
showing up in five minutes.)
I need to make a phone call.
Enjoy the meal.
I will be back soon.
Wait for me.
Why is Lin Yan also at this hotel?
Do you deliberately want me to leave?
This is just a coincidence.
I also don't know
why Lin Yan booked this hotel.
There are not that many coincidences
in this world.
Ma Chengjun, do you really
fall in love with Lin Yan?
Could you please stop
making trouble for no reason?
Anyway, quickly change to another hotel.
We will be doomed if Lin Yan sees us.
No.
Come on, stop it.
Don't you usually like it when I act up?
It's different now, okay?
Could you please stop undressing me?
Could you please listen?
Chengjun, have you
finished talking to Li?
The steak won't taste good
as it gets cold.
I will be back soon.
Get off.
Pack your things and leave quickly.
What took you so long?
Business is too complicated.
Dig in.
Yes.
Let me feed you.
Delicious, right?
Yes.
The steak will be perfect with red wine.
Cheers.
Finish it.
Okay.
Are you okay?
[Wen Lili]
(I'm in your room. Come right away.)
(If not, I will send this to Lin Yan.)
Is it Li again?
Why is he so annoying today?
I will come back soon.
Wen Lili,
are you deliberately messing with me?
I'll deal with you after vomitting.
I...
Chengjun, it's me.
You're here, right?
Chengjun, I know you are inside.
Why didn't you open the door?
Did something happen?
What are you doing?
I'm not afraid of her.
Keep your voice down.
Hide quietly in the washroom,
don't make any sound.
If Lin Yan sees you today,
I'll cut ties with you.
I'll do what I said.
Did something happen?
Chengjun.
Yan, why are you coming here?
Chengjun, I'm worried about you.
Why did you back here
as the meal was not finished?
I'm back here…
It's because I felt uncomfortable
with my stomach.
I just came out of the toilet.
Now, it's done.
Let's go back to eat.
Yes.
Wait, I found your room
much better than mine.
Isn't the layout the same?
The angle is good.
There's plenty of natural light.
This…
What's good about it?
Let's go back to eat, please.
I see that the furniture here
is newer than that in my room.
Yan.
So, your toilet must be better too.
I would like to see it.
Yan,
I just used the toilet.
So, it must be smelly there.
It's no problem for me.
It looks like the toilet
is about the same as mine.
What's interesting about a restroom?
Let's get back.
Wait, I want to wash my hands first.
Okay.
Yan, don't you think
that the steak is getting cold?
Let's go back to the restaurant quickly.
No need to rush.
Done.
Yes, let's go back.
Actually, I'm already full.
I was just teasing you earlier.
Take a rest earlier today,
I'll go to bed now.
Okay.
Have a good rest.
Lili, are you okay?
Sir, please take her
to the hospital quickly.
Since you're like this,
don't talk anymore.
I cannot accompany you.
I cannot leave,
you have to go by yourself.
Be good.
Drive.
What's the matter with you?
What are you doing?
Let me go.
You let him kiss you.
It's just part of the plan.
Do you really want to take a revenge
or do you still like Ma Chengjun?
It's just a kiss on the cheek,
it doesn't mean anything.
So, it doesn't matter
if anyone kisses you?
Yes, it doesn't matter.
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
♪Feeling like you're trapped inside♪
♪No place you can run and hide♪
♪Looking for a light that'll stay on♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪I can sit in the silence♪
♪Just here to listen♪
♪I'll stay with you♪
♪Till you feel like you again♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll stay with you♪