[Love Strikes Back]
[Episode 12]
Surprise, huh?
Why is he here?
Why are you two living together?
I just saw him fastening his buttons.
Aren't you two already...
Oh, my goodness.
Black and white matching stuff.
What's it with you?
What's your deal with him?
Ma Chengjun.
Ma Chengjun?
You used to call me Jun.
You're not really
cheating on me, are you?
Xiao Mo lives here
because he is my bodyguard.
He needs to be close
to protect me 24/7.
I have told you everything.
If you don't believe me, so be it.
I'm tired and I'll go to bed first.
Sending off the guest.
I've had enough of it.
You must make a choice today.
Either he leaves
or I leave.
You choose.
Chengjun.
I realize I didn't know anything
about you.
In my heart,
Chengjun
is a gentle,
generous,
and understanding person.
He never argues with me
over these small matters.
It seems like
it's time for us to take a closer look
at our relationship.
After all this, you still want me
to be considerate?
What does it mean?
Are you breaking up with me?
Let's calm down for a while.
Yan.
Stop pulling me.
Xiao Mo,
let me tell you.
You can't covet
a married woman.
Being someone's paramour,
you will be in for a rough time.
She seems to have never agreed
to marry you
from the beginning, right?
My Yan is too busy now.
She just doesn't want
to marry me for now.
Actually, when it comes to women,
it's not about wanting
to get married now or not.
It's about wanting to marry you
or not wanting to marry you.
You!
It's getting late.
We need to rest now.
Please leave.
I've never seen
such a shameless paramour in my life.
She actually chose that Xiao Mo.
She actually drove me away.
Ma Chengjun.
Do you only have Lin Yan in your heart?
Absolutely impossible.
How could anyone
in this world refuse me, Ma Chengjun?
I'm such an excellent man.
No one can take what belongs to me.
Lin Yan,
you belong to me.
Are you mad?
You've really lost it over Lin Yan.
Lin Yan.
I will
snatch you back.
Ma Chengjun, how dare you do this to me?
Yan.
I will snatch you back.
Ma Chengjun!
Drink some milk later.
Why did you kiss me just now?
Didn't you say I had overdone it before?
Ma Chengjun wasn't here just now either.
Please calm down.
It's Ma Chengjun who needs to calm down.
I'm very hot now.
I overheard what you two
was talking about
downstairs.
Is there any problem?
I told Ma Chengjun
that we should cool off for a bit
to scare him.
I can't break up with him
until I take over Lin Corporation.
Also
I want to remind you.
We are only
in a professional relationship.
You're just my bodyguard.
You shouldn't get so involved
in my personal life.
Moreover,
the most important thing now
is to reassure Ma Chengjun.
Is your heart made of stone?
Don't you have any feelings for me?
What I'm most concerned about now
is how to retake Lin Corporation.
Other things mean nothing to me.
These are all excuses.
You have feelings for me.
You should know where you stand.
You haven't taken a day off
since you came.
Take two days off
to get a good rest.
Okay, I got it.
I will make sure I know where I stand.
Actually, you're the one
who wants to take a break, right?
Mr. Xiao,
Mr. He asked you to meet him this time,
no matter what.
Okay, I got it.
(Chengjun,)
the assets you transferred
from Lin Corporation over the years
are enough for us to spend
for the rest of our lives.
Even if Lin Yan
snatched Lin Corporation back,
it's just an empty shell.
Why don't we take this money
and go abroad?
You don't understand.
I must get Lin Corporation.
No.
I must marry Lin Yan immediately.
Ma Chengjun,
do you want the Lin Corporation
or Lin Yan?
I want them all.
I, Ma Chengjun, have never lost.
Why do you keep mentioning Lin Yan?
You don't really think you can
replace Lin Yan, do you?
Ma Chengjun,
what do you take me for?
I'm nothing in your eyes.
I'm not even as important as a dog.
Since you said so,
I'll make it clear.
You don't deserve
to be Mrs. Ma.
Ma Chengjun.
If I don't get what I want,
then you won't either.
You'd better behave well,
then our relationship can continue.
If you keep causing trouble
every other day...
Just piss off.
(Lin Yan.)
(Why can you easily have everything?)
(Why am I trying my best
but still get rejected?)
(I want you to taste)
(the grievances I've suffered.)
[Main entrance]
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
♪Feeling like you're trapped inside♪
♪No place you can run and hide♪
♪Looking for a light that'll stay on♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪I can sit in the silence♪
♪Just here to listen♪
♪I'll stay with you♪
♪till you feel like you again♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪