[Love Strikes Back]
[Episode 5]
What are you doing?
Are you…
tired of living?
Who are you?
If you want to die, do it far away.
Isn't he Xiao…
Xiao what?
Just punch him.
There is around one hundred
thousand yuan in this card.
No password.
He is quite sensible.
He starts begging
even before we start.
Bro, it hurts.
Those one hundred thousand yuan
are for medical expenses.
Did you send people to bother Lin Yan?
Who are you?
What do you want?
You've already hurt her many times.
Are you tired of living?
What is your relationship with Lin Yan?
You don't need to know who I am.
You just need to know
that you should stay away from her.
I…
I did not do anything.
Lin Yan is my best friend.
Really?
I warn you.
If you dare to bother Lin Yan again,
you will pay for that.
We have to be extra careful
when doing our mission.
No question when you
are not supposed to ask.
No words when you
are not supposed to say.
No eavesdropping when you
are not supposed to listen.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Close your eyes.
Li!
What are you doing?
Let me down.
Who is that girl?
There was only a crazy female celebrity
who was pursuing Mr. Xiao.
You also said that
it was a one-sided love.
Mr. Xiao never paid her any attention.
I think
she is our real sister-in-law.
Yes.
Let me down.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Do you want to repay
kindness with hatred?
I saved you last night.
Do you remember now?
Put on your slippers. The floor is cold.
Who asked you to bring me here?
You were pretty drunk last night.
I could not send you home.
Or should I take you to a hotel?
You…
Never mind.
I've already forgiven you.
Aren't you curious
about how you changed your clothes?
I don't want to know.
Is this your company?
Yes, this is my company.
You guys aren't from the mafia, are you?
Your imagination is too wild.
This is an international
security consulting company.
A legitimate business.
What happened yesterday
was not an accident.
Since I woke up, I've been feeling like
someone had been trying to harm me.
So, I need somebody to help me.
But now, there is no one I can trust
inside the company.
Do you want me to help you?
Yes.
You trust me now?
You've saved me twice,
so I assume you don't have
any ill intentions.
I'm willing to take a chance.
Let's renegotiate the deal
we discussed earlier.
I'm all ears.
At this moment,
I cannot offer you anything
as a chairwoman with no power.
But
I can give you
15% shares of Lin Corporation
once all done.
What makes you think
I'd agree to that?
It's so different
from what I thought before.
This is the best I can offer.
I still have one condition.
How you helped my dad before,
do the same for me now.
I was Mr. Lin's assistant
and personal bodyguard.
So, what you're saying
is you also want me
to be your 24/7 personal bodyguard?
Is that so?
Mr. Xiao, that female celebrity
came to see you again.
Xiao Mo, why didn't you answer my call?
Who is this woman?
Why is she wearing your shirt?
Xiao Mo,
when are you going to agree
to be my personal bodyguard?
If you agree,
all the assets under my name,
including the company shares
will be yours.
Look,
I've brought
the equity transfer agreement.
Just sign it.
What I want is very simple.
I just want you
to be by my side every day
and take care of me personally.
Guess who's winning,
the female celebrity
or our sister-in-law?
Stupid, we've already
called her sister-in-law.
No need to guess anymore.
Just listen.
Miss Lin,
you also heard it.
How does it compare
to the conditions we discussed earlier?
Whatever she offered you,
I'll double it.
I will go with you
if you can promise me one thing
after everything's settled.
What is that?
I haven't thought about it yet.
Do you dare to promise me?
Yes.
Then you have to do me
one more small favor.
Okay.
Xiao Mo, what do you mean by this?
Sorry.
I just want to be
my sweetheart's bodyguard.
So romantic.
So cheesy.
(Even though I don't like Lin Yan,)
(I won't allow other men to cuckold me.)
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
♪Feeling like you're trapped inside♪
♪No place you can run and hide♪
♪Looking for a light that'll stay on♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪I can sit in the silence♪
♪Just here to listen♪
♪I'll stay with you
till you feel like you again♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪