[Love Strikes Back]
[Episode 3]
Chengjun,
I suddenly woke up today
and realized
I don't remember anything.
You
don't remember anything?
That's right, I don't remember anything.
What happened?
Great! This is wonderful!
Everyone, God must be moved
by my sincere feelings for Yan.
My fiancee, Lin Yan,
who had been in a coma for three years
after an accident,
miraculously
woke up today!
Yan,
this is amazing.
Chengjun, take me home, please.
Home?
Really?
Yan, I've missed you so much.
Give me a hug.
Okay,
I'll take you home soon.
Why did you turn right just now?
I thought we had to
turn left to go home.
I think we should
go back to the hospital
for a thorough check-up.
I'm fine, really.
I just want to go home now.
Yan,
nobody has lived there
in the past three years.
It's musty inside.
I will have someone
to clean it up tomorrow.
Once all are set,
we can move back in.
Chengjun,
you've been urging me
not to go home the whole way.
You really don't want me
to go home, huh?
Are you
hiding another woman
at home or something?
What are you talking about?
How could that be?
You women are...
Just kidding, I know you won't.
In that case, let's go home.
We can clean it up together.
Sounds good.
Chengjun,
has no one lived here
in the past three years?
Of course not.
I was afraid it would remind me of you.
I didn't dare to come here.
But it looks so clean,
just like someone has been living here.
You found out.
I had a cleaning lady take care of it
because I knew this house
meant a lot to you.
What's this?
It's the cleaning lady's rag.
She just scattered things
all over the place.
It's highly absorbent.
I think I've smelled something.
What is it?
It's kind of
a familiar woman's fragrance.
How is that possible?
There can't be another woman
in this house.
But if there is,
it must be the cleaning lady.
Oh, I see.
I missed this place so much.
I want to go upstairs and take a look.
Sure,
let's take a look around.
Chengjun.
Chengjun, where's Lili?
Lili?
I saw her car parked
in the yard from upstairs.
The car I gave her.
(Oh, that stupid Lili.)
Really?
Lili.
You're here.
I...
I couldn't help but worry about you,
so I came to check on you.
With such a great friend like you,
I feel so blessed.
It's the least I could do.
You're not wearing shoes?
I...
I came to see Mr. Ma
for some urgent matters at the company.
I was in such a hurry
that I forgot my shoes.
Where are my shoes?
Chengjun,
the company needs you.
You all can go ahead first.
Sure.
Get off.
I'll drive.
I gave you everything!
Why did you betray me?
There's nothing between Chengjun and me.
Give it back!
Are you crazy?
(Ma Chengjun!)
(We'll be screwed if she doesn't die.)
Help me.
Please help me.
Yan, don't blame me.
(Dad, I was wrong.)
(Lin Corporation
meant the world to you.)
(I won't let Ma Chengjun
destroy what you've built.)
(I will find evidence of their crimes)
(and make them give back
what they stole.)
(I will definitely
reclaim Lin Corporation.)
(Ma Chengjun,)
(Wen Lili,)
(I'm back.)
(I'll make both of you pay tenfold
for all the pain I've endured.)
The chance for a person
in a vegetative state
to wake up is very low,
but there's still a chance.
But if one wants to wake up
like Miss Lin,
he or she must be very lucky.
But why
did she only forget
what had happened that day?
Such a situation
is called selective amnesia
in medical science.
Certain memories
can make patients painful,
so the brain selectively
erases those memories.
Patients, when subjected
to certain stimuli,
can exhibit post-traumatic
stress behaviors
and can make some extreme reactions,
which might help them
recover their memories.
[You received a WeChat message]
Lili, what brings you here?
I want to take you out today
to get some fresh air,
which could be good for your recovery.
Where are we going?
You'll find out soon. Let's go.
Yan,
do you remember this place?
On the day of your wedding,
I prepared a gift for you here.
Do you remember what the gift was?
Why did you end up
on the rooftop that day?
(Did you fall on your own,)
(or did someone push you?)
Do you not remember any of these?
Yan.
Yan, what are you doing?
What are you two doing?
What happened?
Chengjun,
how did I end up here?
What happened?
That's what I wanted to ask you both.
Lili, why are you all wet?
Don't touch me!
Chengjun,
Lili brought me here earlier,
saying she wanted me
to remember things from the past.
I remember that day,
she gave me a room key,
saying
there was a gift for me in the room,
so I went there.
Why was I on the rooftop?
Yan.
Why did I fall?
My head hurts so much, Chengjun.
Yan.
My head hurts!
Stop thinking about it.
Stop trying to remember
if your head hurts.
Stop trying to remember.
Don't think about it.
I'm here.
Stop thinking about it.
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
♪Feeling like you're trapped inside♪
♪No place you can run and hide♪
♪Looking for a light that'll stay on♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
♪I can sit in the silence♪
♪Just here to listen♪
♪I'll stay with you
till you feel like you again♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪Cause I'd walk through the fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪