♪Look at them rapping,
you see them flashing light♪
♪We're about to chase light♪
♪I'm glad you're all present
for this fabulous night♪
♪We're about to chase light♪
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
Calm down.
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
Close your eyes.
Li!
What are you doing?
Let me down.
Who is that girl?
There was only one crazy
female celebrity
who was pursuing Brother Xiao.
You also said that
it's one-sided love.
Brother Xiao never paid her
any attention.
I think
she is our real sister-in-law.
Yes.
Let me down.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Do you want to repay
kindness with hatred?
I saved you last night.
Do you remember now?
Put on your slipper. The floor is cold.
Who asked you to bring me here?
You were pretty drunk last night.
I could not send you home.
Or would you rather
I take you to a hotel?
You…
Never mind.
I forgave you already.
Aren't you curious about
how you changed your clothes?
I don't want to know.
Is this your company?
Yes, this is my company.
You guys aren't from
the mafia, aren't you?
Your imagination is too wild.
This is an international security
advisors company.
A legitimate business.
What happened yesterday
was not an accident.
Since I woke up, I feel
like someone has been trying to hurt me.
So, I need somebody to help me.
But now, there is no one I can trust
inside the company.
Do you want me to help you?
Yes.
You trust me now?
You've saved me twice,
so I assume you don't have
any ill intentions.
I'm willing to take a chance.
Let's renegotiate the deal
we discussed earlier.
How do you want to negotiate?
At this moment,
I cannot offer you anything
as I'm only an empty shell chairwoman.
But,
I can give you
15% shares of Lin's Corporation
once all done.
What makes you think
I'd agree to that?
This is so different
from what I thought before.
This is the biggest offer I can make.
I still have one condition.
How you helped my Dad before,
that's how you should help me now.
I was President Lin's assistant
and personal bodyguard.
So, what you're saying is
you also want me to be
your 24/7 personal bodyguard?
Is that so?
Xiao Mo, what do you mean by this?
Apologize.
I just want to be
my sweetheart's bodyguard.
So romantic.
So cheesy.
So, does that mean it doesn't matter
if anyone kisses you?
Yes, it doesn't matter.
What are you doing, Xiao Mo?
You're just the assistant I hired.
You have no right to interfere
in my personal affairs.
I'm warning you.
If you can't control your emotions
and offend me again like this,
you can just leave.
It's so beautiful.
They really are a match made in heaven.
Which part do they match?
They're just a match.
Open your eyes wide and see clearly.
I'm the fiancée.
He's just a bodyguard.
You're just her fiancée, right?
As long as Miss Lin isn't married,
any man in the world
has the right to pursue her,
including me.
You're dreaming.
From now on,
I'm officially pursuing Lin Yan.
Yan,
you can tell him.
Between the two of us, who do you like?
Who do you choose
between Xiao Mo and me?
I'll go to the restroom.
♪I like my coffee
kinda sweet with love, just the same♪
♪And I'm looking for someone
who can make a simple cake♪
♪I know you're a little too much, but♪
♪What a shame♪
This scene is so beautiful.
You can piss off Ma Chengjun.
Don't overdo the act.
Stop using the word
'acting' all the time.
♪I don't wanna play with each other♪
♪I just wanna be...♪
Be together.
Shut up. Xiao Mo, you too.
What do you want to do?
If you suddenly do this, I...
I'm not ready yet.
Take off.
Isn't this too bold?
Quick.
Don't be like this.
Take it off.
Your wound looks very serious.
Don't you really need
to go to the hospital?
No need.
Compared to this wound,
the wound in my heart
are even more severe.
It hurts.
Were you keep following me?
I'm your personal bodyguard.
Of course,
I have to protect you closely.
I...
Before...
Just now...
I...
Are you trying to thank me?
Since when nodding
is a way to express gratitude?
Thank you.
Only saying thank you
seems insincere, doesn't it?
Then,
if not,
what else do you want?
What do you think?
What are you doing?
Don't ever think about it.
What am I thinking?
Don't think I don't know
what you're thinking.
So, what do you think I'm thinking?
You know what you're thinking about.
Never mind.
What do you mean by never mind?
What do you mean by sighing?
I am thinking whether the nutritious meal
I made for you
is not nutritional.
You are funny.
Where did you see signs of malnutrition?
What do you mean?
Do you think I have a bad figure?
By the way,
I have a question for you.
You said before that I acted
and want to keep
a proper distance from me.
What is the appropriate distance?
Like this?
Or like this?
It's really too much.
It looks delicious.
Wait a minute.
Take your time to eat.
I'll go upstairs.
♪I walked a while♪
♪That's a line stroke♪
♪No word is broken♪
♪Into the storm♪
♪The crack of the fire♪
♪See it will grow♪
♪Don't be mistaken♪
♪Waiting for show♪
♪Ya I pat by it♪
♪That you know it, oh♪
♪You're the man I love♪
♪And I gonna be, gonna be♪
♪When I think that on by♪
♪That's a place to the wild♪
♪And I want you decide♪
♪Yeah I gonna be, gonna be♪
♪You know that I got you♪
♪So, what you're gonna do?♪
♪You know I couldn't let go♪
Take your time.
I'll go to bed.
♪What's yours which is mine♪
♪Don't make a move♪
♪Been wait too long♪
♪Come on now♪
♪There was a time♪
♪Since break♪
♪Was it forsaken♪
♪Whatever it takes♪
♪No more smile♪
♪I won't afraid♪
♪Don't be mistaken♪
♪This is no pain♪
♪Ya I pat by it♪
♪That you know it♪
♪And I made I would♪
♪And I gonna be♪
Have a good sleep.
Don't go.
I promise
I won't let any harm come to you again
in the future.
♪You love me ways I always wanted♪
♪You've got me wrapped up in your arms♪
♪Time slow it down♪
♪Don't let me forget this very moment♪
♪Don't let me forget
that look in his eyes♪
♪Time slow it down♪
♪We've all been lost in the chaos♪
♪Fighting so hard for a way out♪
♪Feeling like you're trapped inside♪
♪No place you can run and hide♪
♪Lookin for a light that'll stay on♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪I'll be right there♪
♪When you're falling down♪
♪Rest your mind♪
♪'Cause I'd walk through fire,
carry the flames♪
♪Even in sorrow and all the pain♪
♪You'll be safe and sound♪
♪Ya I'll be around♪
What are you doing?
Morning.
Do you want to run away?
Me?
No.
You don't want to take responsibility
after having your way with me last night?
Please, isn't it a woman's loss
in such situation?
A man saying these things,
have you no shame?
Why are you laughing?
You...
Stop laughing right away.
Last night,
you were quite enthusiastic.
You shut up.
Shut up.
Let me think.
Who made the first move
last night?
That's because...
you seduced me.
I still prefer the you from last night.
I said stop talking about it.
What's the matter?
I haven't even gotten out of bed yet.
Where are you going?
Xiao, who's in your room?
Who are you talking to?
My
pet.
Tell me who your pet is.
You.
I heard it.
It's sister-in-law.
Xiao,
when did you two get together?
Who is his sister-in-law?
You better hang up the phone.
Did you hear that?
Your sister-in-law is upset.
I have to go cheer her up.
Xiao Mo, what nonsense
are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
I'm stating the facts.
Just wait.
These eyelashes are longer than mine.
The skin is still so good.
Who is he?
He looks even better than a girl.
How did I miss
noticing you before?
What have
you been through?
Feeling sad for me?
When
did you wake up?
Probably
before you woke up.
Did you hear
everything I just said?
Do you like me that much?
I'm very happy.
Are the rumors they said true?
What rumors?
They said
rumors about you.
When I joined the army,
there was a battle.
My comrades
were all trapped
in an abandoned village.
I went alone to save them.
The battle was brutal.
Those weren't villagers,
they were terrorists.
When I defeated all the enemies
and rescued my brothers,
I was also seriously injured.
That's where these scars came from.
You must have felt
a lot of pain at that time, right?
But fortunately,
I managed to make it through.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have met you.
♪I like my coffee kinda sweet,
and you love it just the same♪
♪And I'm looking for someone
who can make a simple cake♪
♪I know you're a little too much, but♪
♪What a shame♪
Are you sure these injuries
don't bother you?
Didn't you check it out
last night?
If you don't see it clearly,
I don't mind if you check it again.
No need.
What do you want to eat?
I'll make you something.
♪I don't think we're right
for each other♪
♪If you don't feel the same♪
Are you sure?
I'm afraid
you might burn the kitchen down.
Don't underestimate me.
I will make you
whatever you want to eat.
I want to eat meat.
Do you eat meat early in the morning?
♪I don't wanna play with each other♪
What are you doing?
You...
Please stop the thoughts in your mind
right now.
I mean braised pork belly.
What were you thinking?
Don't make fun of me.
I know what you're thinking.
We've missed too much time between us.
You need to compensate me well.
But yesterday you lied to me like that,
and I haven't even settled it
with you yet.
You should have compensated me, right?
I can repay my debt with flesh and blood.
Damn rascal, go make your meal.
♪I'm gonna walk away♪
Calm down.
(How you helped my dad before,)
(that's how you should help me now.)
(You also want me to be)
(your all day personal bodyguard?)
Wherever you are,
I'll show up in an instant.
(You asked me
to act alongside with you?)
(Fine.)
(Since it's an act,)
(then let's make it more convincing.)
(You better not regret it later.)
(From now on,)
(I'm officially pursuing Lin Yan.)
(Is your heart made of stone?)
(I don't love you.)
(Leave now.)
(The best things come)
(when you least expect them to.)
(Never frown,)
(even when you are sad,)
(because you never know)
(who is falling in love with your smile.)
(To the world,)
(you may be one person.)
(But to one person,)
(you may be the world.)