But aside from that,
what kind of a guy would hang
the portrait that was drawn
by the woman he killed
in the middle of his office like this?
He doesn't care about that kind of stuff.
What? You know him?
We meet often.
What brings you here this time?
I have something to ask you.
This is Detective Kang Do-chang
who works with me.
Hello. I'm Kang Do-chang
from Violent Crimes Unit
of Incheon Seobu Police Station.
Please sit.
I guess it's not about something personal
since you brought your colleague with you.
Do you happen to know
a woman named Yoon Ji-seon?
She's a college student
who was murdered five years ago.
She was an art student.
I know her. Yoon Ji-seon.
How did you meet her?
She painted my portrait,
and I commissioned her to paint it.
Did you ever meet her in private
while she worked on your portrait?
We did have a meal together
when she finished the work
and brought it to me.
And I never met her after that.
It seems you knew
that Yoon Ji-seon was murdered.
And you know that
the killer has been caught, right?
-Yes.
-Then you should be wondering
why we are asking you about
Yoon Ji-seon again now.
Why should I be wondering about that?
Because Detective Kang is
suspicious of you now.
He thinks you're the real culprit
who killed her.
What makes you think that?
I told him about you.
What about me?
Did you kill her?
Are you seriously
asking me that question?
Yes.
I'd like you to leave now.
Please contact my legal team
if you have further questions.
I have nothing else to say to you.
Let's go.
I'm available
for the lunch appointment again.
You don't need to cancel it.
What is your relationship with him?
He's my cousin.
Then are you suspecting your cousin…
I hope Jong-tae is not the culprit.
But we won't have much choice
if we find solid evidence.
Hang on.
It seems like you're trying
to protect your cousin.
-Why would I?
-Why did you
corner him so abruptly like that,
asking if he killed her?
There's no evidence,
and the motive for the murder
is still unclear.
Asking him a question like that
is like telling him to be prepared
because we're after him.
That's exactly what I intended.
He's never been nervous or worried
after doing something wrong.
He believes there's no one
who can dare to arrest him.
I'm probably the first one
to ever ask him if he killed a person.
So if Oh Jong-tae is provoked
by your words and makes a move…
It means he killed her.
That condescending punk.
INCHEON JEIL INVESTMENT TRUST
The way she looked at me…
She was so pretty.
Yes, I know.
Jin Seo-kyung
for the head of the Legal Affairs Team?
Yes. The position is vacant anyway.
Are you sure it will be okay?
Do you all agree?
Mr. Yoo, I don't think I qualify
for the position yet.
Will the legal teams of other companies
accept this?
They'd lord it over her if she was
a reporter from the countryside.
But now she works at the head office
of Jeonghan Daily.
Who would dare to mess with her?
I'm sure she will pull it off.
I believe in her.
So it was about a month
before the incident.
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT TEAM 2, KANG DO-CHANG
How long did she stay?
Okay.
Did Yoon Ji-seon mention
why she went to New York?
VIOLENT CRIMES UNIT TEAM 2
Really? Did she go alone?
Okay. I'm sorry I keep bothering you.
Bye.
What are you doing?
There's something
I need to look into personally.
Do you think Do-chang is
up to something else
instead of going on vacation?
I don't know.
I don't care what others are up to.
He's not some stranger. He's your partner.
Still, he's not my family or something.
I'm comfortable doing things alone.
I'm going to head out.
Yes. I called you earlier.
Are you Mr. Lee Gyeong-ho?
You recently got assaulted
by Mr. Oh Jong-tae, right?
I was there that day.
I said hello to Mr. Oh.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Did you leave the company?
I make less money now,
but this is much better than working
at that shitty company.
I'm feeling at ease now.
I should've quit sooner.
I looked into the department you were in,
and your tasks were…
It's not like I had any specific tasks.
You can just think
that all the people in the company
are Oh Jong-tae's minions.
Then you must have handled
a lot of his personal affairs.
Jong-tae dates around a lot,
but I guess he was seeing only Ji-seon
around the time of the incident.
He even stopped going to the bar
he used to frequent that time.
How did they meet?
He met her while she was working
part-time for the gallery opening.
I've confirmed that
she did work at the gallery.
I also found out that the gallery is
owned by Jong-tae's acquaintance.
Are you saying they started
dating after that?
Yoon Ji-seon went to New York
six months before the incident.
Apparently, she went there
for some exhibition.
I checked the departure
and arrival records,
and Jong-tae was on the same flight.
They must've been
in a serious relationship.
I bet he made up for the age gap
with his money.
Then did she dump him after that?
Is that why he killed her?
-Maybe.
-Just because he was dumped?
He didn't seem like a lunatic though.
Jong-tae had a dog named Happy
when he was young.
And he beat the dog to death
because it didn't mind well.
Then he put a photo
of the dog and himself on his desk.
He'd look at the photo
and tell me that he missed the dog.
When he was little,
he thought he was allowed to do
anything he wanted at home.
And now he thinks that he owns the world.
What are you doing?
You said we can't be late.
You go on ahead. We'll be right out.
Hurry up.
Hey.
If your relative comes under suspicion,
you are supposed to back out
of the investigation.
You know what I mean, right?
I'm just after the culprit.
I'm not thinking about anything else.
Let's go after the culprit.
LAWYER SO JAE-SEOP
To be honest with you,
you're at a disadvantage.
What should we do then?
I can't live without Jae-ung.
Don't worry. He's a competent lawyer.
He's got a lot of cases from me,
and he didn't lose a single one.
But Detective Kang, I've never
dealt with a custody case before.
What did you always tell me?
You said you became a lawyer
for the less fortunate.
She's totally unfortunate.
You don't have to go far to find one.
I know. I should take the case.
But the thing is…
-By any chance,
-Yes?
do you have anyone in the family
who has a very high social status
or a lot of money?
I see.
Objectively speaking, you really
are at a disadvantage.
Why?
I'm being evaluated for promotion.
I'm going to be a lieutenant.
It's an executive-level officer.
KOREAN JUDICIAL RESEARCH
AND TRAINING INSTITUTE
Mr. So is a competent lawyer.
Let's trust him for now.
It's hopeless.
What do you want me to do then?
Why did you have to get divorced?
It's not like your husband
cheated on you or beat you.
You should've put up with him.
Why did you get divorced?
So this is what
you wanted to say after all.
You're just like him.
You never think
from the woman's point of view.
Of course I tried to do that. I did, but…
If you could be so understanding
of the woman,
then why did you get dumped
by your bride-to-be on your wedding day?
That was a long time ago.
Why would you bring that up?
It's embarrassing.
No wonder you're my brother.
We're just the same.
Wait, Eun-hui.
Don't drink today.
How will I get through the day then?
Don't drink more
than three bottles of soju.
I already have a lot on my mind
without you adding to it.
I can't believe Jin Seo-kyung is
the head of the Legal Affairs Team.
Do you want the position?
Honestly, if you think about
my experience in the head office,
-I deserve it more than she does.
-Jin Seo-kyung.
She had Chief Prosecutor
Kim Gi-tae arrested.
Do you think the prosecutors
will welcome someone
who put their boss in jail?
Why did the PR department
of the Central District Prosecutors'
Office deny your access?
I guess they don't like me.
This isn't just about Ms. Jin.
It means they disregard
our entire company.
We should make an official complaint
to the prosecution.
What do you think, Ms. Jin?
I don't want to be narrow-minded
as they are.
It will only tarnish
Jeonghan Daily's reputation.
We should send someone else.
And if they do the same thing,
we will have to think
about how we should deal with it.
-Gwang-hui.
-Yes.
You go instead.
As Ms. Jin said,
we will see how they react first.
Oh, well…
Why would you send me
for such a sensitive issue?
Try to sort it out.
Mr. Baek, you have a good connection
with the Legal Affairs Team.
I need you to support him.
I will.
Then what will you do with Ms. Jin?
The news beat is full,
so there's nowhere else to send her.
Ms. Jin.
The first hearing for Chief Prosecutor
Kim Gi-tae will be held soon.
I need you to work
on the case on your own.
So are you telling me
to go back to Incheon?
After the first hearing,
the case will probably be sent
to the Seoul High Court.
All right. I'll go back to Incheon.
But I'd like to look into something else
other than Kim Gi-tae's case. Is it okay?
What?
The execution of death sentences
was recently announced.
The death-row inmates on the list.
One of them might be innocent.
-My gosh.
-What?
-Who is it?
-Lee Dae-cheol.
-Lee Dae-cheol?
-My goodness.
Mr. Yoo, if that's true,
the Blue House who confirmed
the execution will panic.
No. It's not just the Blue House.
It will turn the whole nation upside down.
-Are you confident?
-Yes.
I know I can prove it
and I'll take full responsibility.
Then let's just trust her and go for it.
Go ahead and do it.
Okay.
Good luck. You can ask us
for help at any time.
What if she causes trouble?
It would be amazing to prove
Lee Dae-cheol's innocence.
She can't prove anything
without the help
of the police and prosecution.
Do you think the police and prosecutors
are crazy?
Why would they help her
and put themselves in trouble?
It won't be amazing. It will
end up as a miserable failure.
This stop is Dowon Station.
The doors are on your right.
YOO JEONG-SEOK
-Yes, Mr. Yoo.
-Seo-kyung.
I'm sorry I didn't discuss it with you
in advance.
I know it might cause
Assemblyman Yoo Jeong-ryeol trouble.
And I'm not doing this
to earn my spot in the head office.
I just think
this is what I should do as a reporter.
You don't have to worry about my brother.
You should just do your job as a reporter.
Thank you for understanding.
This is quite risky
for our company though.
If things go wrong, I might not be able
to protect you as your superior.
-Keep that in mind.
-Okay.
I'll be prepared for that.
Here.
Nothing was found
other than Jo Seong-dae's prints.
And there's no blood on the blade.
Thank you.
Hey, Dong-uk. What do you think
you're doing?
Well, I'm just…
Detective Oh asked me to do this.
If he asks you to wipe his butt,
will you gladly do so? Will you?
You should ask why
and find out what it has to do
with your job, you fool.
Hey, Jae-hong.
Watch your mouth in the office. Okay?
Detective Oh, we're a team.
We should all know what you are up to.
Why did you arrest Jo Seong-dae?
As a suspect for Park Gun-ho's death.
But I should release him
since Team One confirmed it was a suicide.
Darn it.
Captain Woo.
Do you not have any cases
to work on in Team Two?
-Do you want us to share ours with you?
-What?
Learn to supervise your team.
Don't let your people
interfere with our team's cases.
Darn it.
We wouldn't do this
if you did your job right.
Investigation isn't creative work.
You guys just make up and omit things.
It's just insane.
Hey, Beardy. Watch your mouth.
-Hey!
-He didn't say anything wrong.
If Park Gun-ho killed himself,
all the murder cases
should be considered suicide.
That's just ridiculous.
You idiot. Do you have…
Captain Nam, calm down.
They're out of their minds
with the audit going on.
They've raked off a lot of bribes,
so they need someone to pick on.
-What did you say, you jerk?
-What?
You idiot.
Gosh, stop that.
-You jerk.
-That's enough.
Why should I stop? Come here.
Get off me. Let go!
Stop it!
Captain Nam.
Don't worry about my team.
Just make sure to keep your team members
under control.
Get back to work.
-Yes, sir.
I'm curious.
You must have enough excuses
to put me behind bars.
But why?
Why are you letting me go?
There's no other reason.
It's because you're innocent.
Do you know this guy?
KIM GI-TAE
You dropped this.
It's not mine.
I'll call you if I miss you.
And…
make sure to tell your boss this.
I was very disappointed that I didn't
get to talk to him enough last time.
I'll be sure to go see him
and pick up where we left off.
Do-chang.
Where are you?
Okay.
Oh Jong-tae?
Yes.
Are you talking about Oh Jong-tae
of Incheon Jeil Investment Trust?
Yes, I am.
And it turns out
he's Detective Oh's cousin.
Are you serious?
Tell me more about it.
So Detective Oh thinks
his cousin, Oh Jong-tae
is the real culprit?
Yes. There was this painting
in his office and…
Hey. What was that? It's for me.
Ms. Jin. Is this how you
cover a case all the time?
What did you say?
Do-chang.
Why do you keep dragging
Ms. Jin into this?
We're already in the same boat.
Hang on.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying
I cover cases
by pouring drinks to some officers?
You scumbag.
Ms. Jin. Wait. Ms. Jin.
Gosh, you rude punk.
Why did you tell her about Jong-tae?
Hey. Wake up and look around you.
There's no one who can help us.
Ms. Jin is the only one
who can offer us help.
She's doing this risking her job.
She might change her mind.
Do you think we have time
to size her up now?
Lee Dae-cheol will be executed soon.
Our goal isn't to catch the culprit.
It's to save someone from dying.
You brat.
That darn jerk.
How dare he say that to me?
I apologize.
It was rude of me.
It's cold, right?
Oh Jong-tae asked Yoon Ji-seon
to paint his portrait
right before she was murdered.
And the portrait is still hanging
in Oh Jong-tae's office.
So he had a relationship with her
around the time of the murder.
-Yes.
-Then
why wasn't he on the list
of suspects back then?
I'd like you to find out the reason.
Don't you think the officers in charge
of the case have the records?
The initial investigation of the case
was led by Captain Nam Guk-hyeon.
I see. I'll talk to him.
Do you have a family?
Yes. I have my mother.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why? Why are you asking all that?
I don't think you are
getting involved in this case
for Lee Dae-cheol's sake.
Even if Lee Dae-cheol ends up
getting executed for unfair reasons,
it's not your fault.
But if your family or boyfriend get hurt,
it's your fault.
Are you trying to scare me?
So that I'll stay out of this case.
Then why are you so obsessed
with this case?
I don't see any reason
why you'd want to dig into this case.
I don't have a family or girlfriend.
I don't have a boyfriend either.
And my mom is in a sanatorium.
Her condition can't get any worse
than she is now.
-Happy now?
-I'm glad to hear that.
I don't have a boyfriend
and my mom is sick. And you're glad?
I'm sorry then.
Detective Oh.
You don't know what makes
people happy or sad, do you?
I'll meet with Captain Nam Guk-hyeon
tomorrow and get back to you.
This…
This might come in handy.
Is this for self-defense?
Thank you so much
for your thoughtful gift.
I guess it's better than nothing.
Excuse me.
We did as much as we could.
We'd like to discharge
Ms. Lee Eun-hye now.
The thing is,
she's got nowhere else to go.
But this isn't a refuge.
And there are a lot of patients
waiting to be hospitalized here.
She keeps passing out on the streets.
She didn't need in-hospital
treatment in the first place.
If her guardian takes good care of her,
she can go back to normal life.
But the problem is she has no guardian.
I have nothing more to say to you.
Get her discharged tomorrow.
If you don't,
we will have to force her
to leave the hospital.
But she doesn't have…
Excuse me. Hey.
How many people are we pursuing now?
Jo Seong-dae, Oh Jong-tae,
and Nam Guk-hyeon.
Did you put a tail on Jo Seong-dae?
No.
Should we call our team members
and ask for help?
They still have
many years left in their job.
We shouldn't make things tough for them.
And it's okay for me because I don't?
-You started the whole thing knowing that.
-What about you?
Do you think things will be easy
for you for the rest of your career?
I don't care. My life has never been easy.
That's not it. You have your inheritance,
so you're not afraid of anything.
I'm scared of something, too.
Failing to catch a culprit.
Gosh.
There's a culprit I need to catch
before I die.
Who is it?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Then how are you
going to catch the culprit?
I probably never will.
That's why I'm afraid.
I might
fail to catch the culprit again.
What are you talking about?
There are 119 cameras installed.
The crackdown will continue
until next March,
but about 280 cars were
caught already only in 9 hours.
The car owners must pay
a fine of 250,000 won.
Among the 337 cities in the world,
we are the 16th.
According to the global statistical site…
Hey, I told you to take the blanket
out of the machine
and hang it to dry.
If you hang it at this late hour,
it won't dry anyway.
You can just do it tomorrow morning.
What's all the fuss about?
We're not in a position
to have someone over now.
Stop complaining and do as I say
before I kick you out.
That's what the analysts say.
Has she gone deaf after all the drinking?
A group of burly men are going around.
They bow deeply at the waist
and threaten another gang member
who's down on his knees.
In broad daylight in the heart of Gwangju,
members of Incheon and Gwangju gangs
had a violent fight.
The police believe
that the Yeonan Gang from Incheon
went all the way down
to Gwangju for revenge.
And now they are trying to track
the gang members who ran away.
Those jerks.
The fine dust control system
will come into effect starting from today.
Who are you?
Ji-hyeok, think carefully about it.
Did you see the person
who stabbed your dad?
Do you remember his face?
Try to recall it.
You're the only one who saw it.
I don't remember
anything.
Mom.
Detective Oh.
You don't know what makes
people happy or sad, do you?
INCHEON SEOBU POLICE STATION
Joo Dong-pal from the Yeonan Gang?
Yes. He's the boss of the Yeonan Gang
who caused a mess
in Gwangju yesterday.
We will use this chance to arrest
Joo Dong-pal and his gang members.
Do you think it will be
easy to catch them?
They must've already gone into hiding.
Come in.
-All right. Come on in.
-May I?
Hey.
-Come in.
-Aren't you on your vacation?
Gosh, Captain. I understand it's urgent,
but you can't call in someone
who's on vacation.
Hey, the incident happened in Gwangju,
but this is about our guys.
If we fail to arrest these punks,
it's our station
who will be pilloried by the press.
You're the only one
who can catch Joo Dong-pal.
Do you know a lot about Joo Dong-pal?
I've dealt with him since he was little.
But I'm on vacation now.
Does it have to be me?
Chief.
The guys from Gwangju Station
just asked us for help.
If they catch Joo Dong-pal before we do,
we'll be humiliated.
Joo Dong-pal's case is
under our jurisdiction.
Even if they catch him,
they should hand him over to us.
Who cares about such rules these days?
Whoever cuffs him will take the credit.
The Gwangju District Public Prosecutors'
Office already issued an arrest warrant.
Those mannerless jerks.
Chief, Joo Dong-pal is our fish
that we've been feeding in our farm.
Will you let the guys from Gwangju
scoop it up and take it?
We can't do that.
Are you sure
you've dealt with Joo Dong-pal?
I was going to go to Vietnam
with my friends from high school,
so I bought my flight tickets
and everything.
-I can't cancel it.
-Cancel it.
The cancellation fee isn't a lot.
-It's about 150,000 to 200,000 won though.
-I'm sure he will pay for it.
Then I guess I should make a sacrifice.
Please make sure our team
works on the case on our own.
If you bring in someone else halfway down…
Fine. I get it.
Kang Do-chang.
Good luck.
All right.
You rascal.
Gosh, I was going to rest.
JOO DONG-PAL OF THE YEONAN GANG
This guy.
He grew up in Incheon.
It means he's got connections
everywhere here.
So information could leak easily.
If we lose him this time,
we won't be able to catch him again.
All phone calls regarding this case
should be made outside the office.
Make sure to keep it confidential. Okay?
-Yes, sir.
Ji-ung and Man-gu,
you two take care of Oh Jong-tae.
Whenever he meets someone, take photos.
Dong-uk, you stay here
and keep an eye on Nam Guk-hyeon's team.
Tail them after work
and find out whom they meet.
Give it up immediately
if you think you'll get caught.
-Yes, sir.
-Jae-hong.
I'll tell you the whereabouts
of some of Joo Dong-pal's underlings.
Catch them and interrogate them
so the Chief will think
things are moving along well.
-Okay.
-We're the only ones who can do this.
Let's just think
that we represent the Korean police force
and try our best.
All right then.
Good.
-Ji-ung, let's get moving.
-Okay.
We're going out.
Gosh, we're so busy
because of Joo Dong-pal.
That moron. He's just unbelievable.
Incheon Seobu Police Station,
Nam Guk-hyeon.
What?
What is your call regarding, Ms. Jin?
Okay.
Hey.
Why is Seo-kyung calling Nam Guk-hyeon?
We can't interrogate our colleague.
I got a tip regarding
the death-row convict, Lee Dae-cheol.
Detective Kang was in charge of the case.
If you have questions, go ask him.
It's about Oh Jong-tae, the president
of Incheon Jeil Investment Trust.
I heard you were in charge
of the initial investigation
for Yoon Ji-seon's case.
I heard that Oh Jog-tae was
in a relationship with her
at the time of the murder.
And there's objective evidence.
Then why didn't the police investigate
such an important suspect?
Oh Jong-tae was
on the list of suspects.
Then why did the investigation data
that Detective Kang took over
have no statements about him?
Because Oh Jong-tae had a solid alibi.
Close the office for now.
And until I give you a call,
go somewhere in the countryside
and get some rest.
-Yes, sir.
-Here.
It won't take long. Here.
We will get going then.
Jo Seong-dae speaking. Go ahead.
It doesn't matter.
I don't care whom I'm dealing with.
All right. Thank you.
Aren't we supposed to catch Joo Dong-pal?
We are.
Isn't it too big a deal for a side job?
He's the boss of a gang.
Joo Dong-pal has three women.
One for Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
One for Tuesdays and Thursdays.
And the last one for weekends.
Whenever we want to catch him,
we can always pick a day
and go to one of them.
I'm certain he'll be there.
-Do-chang.
-Yes?
Do you see the guy
in the red shirt with a flower?
He has the biggest mouth.
Let's take him to the station.
-For what?
-He looks like a gangster.
Hey, you red pig.
Hey, you.
What's with the carnation?
Did they figure out
Joo Dong-pal's whereabouts?
They will soon.
What about the guys in Gwangju?
The Criminal Investigation Division
is on the case.
The Criminal Investigation Division?
They want to catch him themselves.
-I think so.
-You better hurry.
Catch him and have the press
cover it when it's still hot.
So the guys in Gwangju can't say anything.
Yes, sir.
Darn it.
Who is he?
He's Joo Dong-pal's underling.
Joo Dong-pal? Who on earth is he?
I don't know him.
You don't know Joo Dong-pal?
What's going on?
I guess he doesn't remember him.
He will recall the name
when we start talking.
Please don't worry. Let's go.
What? I really don't know him.
Fine. Just tell me where he is.
Then I'll say you don't know him.
You know what things are like here.
Do-chang is the best
at dealing with guys like him.
You were charged four times for assault.
He seems to be well qualified
to be a member of Yeonan Gang.
What are you talking about?
According to the Additional Punishment Law
on Specific Crimes,
you will be charged for
forming a criminal group.
You will serve out about two or three
times the sentence you did before.
On what ground?
All we need to do is catch Joo Dong-pal
and take a few photos of you with him.
Even the judge wouldn't
find it strange. Right?
What do you want from me?
We want you to prove
that you work for Jo Seong-dae.
Then you'll be cleared of charges.
I just
work at his office.
I don't even know what he does in detail.
So you just admitted
to working for Jo Seong-dae.
You said I'd be released if I did.
Jo Seong-dae
murdered Park Gun-ho.
If he's proved guilty of murder,
you'll be charged as well.
Damn it.
I don't even know who Park Gun-ho is.
And I have no idea who my boss meets.
I really don't know anything. I'm serious.
I just took some people to him
as I was told.
I didn't do anything.
So who did Jo Seong-dae ask you to bring?
Park Gun-ho?
-No. It was someone else.
-Did Jo Seong-dae kill the person as well?
No. He went back alive.
-I'm sure.
-Really? That's good.
You can talk about him then. Who was he?
DECEMBER 7 2018
Mr. Ko Jun-seop.
I need to talk to him in private.
You guys wait outside.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry. We will just talk.
Are you ready to talk now?
-One more time?
-Gosh, no.
What if we end up taking care of the body?
Hey.
We finished talking.
Drive him home safely.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Ko Jun-seop?
Yes. I'm Ko Jun-seop.
How may I help you?
We're from Incheon Seobu Police Station.
Police?
Is there any place we can talk in private?
Come with me.
All right.
What's going on?
I guess you majored in art.
Yes.
Which college did you go to?
I studied Western paintings
at Seongmun University.
Do you know Yoon Ji-seon
who was murdered five years ago?
We went to school together.
-Then…
-That's it.
We went to the same school,
so of course I knew her.
But I have nothing more to tell you
about her and me.
Are we done?
I'm busy preparing
for a presentation today.
Please excuse me.
But I guess you have a lot
to talk about this guy.
No. I have nothing to say.
That can't be right.
You must have thought of
this guy every night.
And the horrible memory
will keep haunting you every night.
You were a hopeless guy
who couldn't call the police back then.
And that's how you'll live forever.
We will make him pay for what he did.
What does Jo Seong-dae want from you?
What did you tell him
when you were taken to him?
Jo Seong-dae can kill a person
without a blink or qualm.
Then why
do you think
someone like him let you live?
He thought you had a reason
you couldn't call the police.
There's something you want to hide, right?
We can't do this today.
We will come back
with a warrant. Let's go.
Wait.
He thought
I killed Ji-seon.
He urged me to tell him why I killed her.
Why would Jo Seong-dae think that?
I was
Ji-seon's boyfriend.
But I didn't kill her.
I found this in there.
-Oh, that one…
-This belongs to him, right?
-Who?
-The day you came from New York.
Do you know I was waiting at the airport?
You were with some guy.
You went to New York with him, right?
He seemed to be well off.
No wonder he's rich
since he took you to New York.
I didn't know you were so materialistic.
Please don't go.
I don't have any feelings for him.
He said he'd sponsor me
without wanting anything in return.
That's why I trusted him
and went with him.
So?
Nothing happened in New York?
When we got there,
I saw his true face.
But I rejected him until the end.
I really did.
What did that jerk do to you?
Tell me.
Say it!
-What did he do?
-Please.
I'll take care of this myself.
Take care of what?
You said nothing happened.
It's true. Nothing happened.
Please believe me.
Please let me handle this.
I'll be sure to end things. Okay?
The only person I love
is you.
I love you.
That was the last time I saw Ji-seon.
And two days later,
Ji-seon was found dead.
The watch you found
at the studio that day.
Is this the one?
Yes. It looks similar.
The man you saw at the airport.
Right. It was him.
Why did you not say that sooner?
If you had said it back then,
things wouldn't have
gotten so complicated.
She was your girlfriend.
Don't you even feel upset?
Don't you feel sorry for her?
If I talked to the police,
they would've been suspicious of me.
If he's proven innocent,
I'll be the only one left on the list.
I'm the only one with a motive
to kill her.
Is that why you've kept this
to yourself all this time?
I can't believe this.
Don't you even feel guilty about it?
I would've told the police
if they came to me back then.
But no one…
No one came to see me.
I also want to go ask the detective
who was in charge of the case.
Why he didn't come to see me.
Why someone else became the culprit,
instead of the scumbag
who was chasing after Ji-seon,
What haunts me every night
isn't the punk who beat me up.
It's Ji-seon's face that I saw
for the last time
when she told me that she loved me.
Okay. I'll see you there.
Bye.
Do-chang.
Ms. Jin wants to see us.
Okay.
I should go to the hospital
to have Eun-hye discharged.
Will you drive my car then?
No. It's nearby. I'll take a taxi.
Call me. I'll come over
as soon as I'm done.
Okay.
Do-chang.
We don't have much time.
Don't waste your emotions for nothing.
I know that.
No, I'm really fine.
Just take it. Get some soju
on your way home.
It's from my investigation budget.
It's no big deal.
Okay. Thank you, sir. Have a nice day.
Are you ready?
Is that the prescription from your doctor?
We will stop by at the pharmacy
on our way.
Where? I'm not going to a shelter.
No, it's not like that.
We're going home.
My home.
Let's go.
Sir.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean? What did I do?
You're the one
who arrested my dad.
You made him a death-row convict.
Do you think I will like you?
Of course you will hate me.
Keep loathing me.
I feel more comfortable that way.
The hallway of Haesong Hotel in Busan.
It's around the time
when Yoon Ji-seon was murdered.
They went in around 11:30 p.m.
And the woman who was with him
left at 1 a.m. the next day.
And…
Oh Jeong-tae left at 9 a.m.
Because of this footage,
Oh Jeong-tae got off the list of suspects.
Wait.
You should've told me you were coming.
This is it. Just eat.
This is a sumptuous feast.
Why would you grumble
when things are just good?
Eun-hye, let's eat.
-Eun-hye.
-She went out.
What? Where?
She went out to buy
some underwear to change.
Do you think we should change
the direction of investigation?
I think the guy named Ko Jun-seop
is more likely to be the culprit.
You met him. Did he seem like a murderer?
No. He can't be the culprit.
Detective Kang.
I heard you gave up your vacation
to catch Joo Dong-pal.
Well, he's under our jurisdiction.
Someone has to do it.
Then why haven't you caught him?
Don't you have all the gang members
in the palm of your hand?
Mind your own business. I will do mine.
-Detective Oh Ji-hyeok.
-Yes?
-Are you close to Jin Seo-kyung?
-Yes.
We're very close.
I guess a Police University graduate
is no different.
You're becoming just like them.
You're just as shameless
and thoughtless as they are.
I bet you picked it up from them.
What is that punk talking about?
I'm sure Jo Seong-dae found out
about Oh Jong-tae through Ko Jun-seop.
But Jo Seong-dae killed Park Gun-ho
for Oh Jong-tae's sake.
I guess Seong-dae threatened Jong-tae
that he'd frame him for the murder.
Jong-tae covered it up with money,
and after getting a taste for money,
Seong-dae started serving Jong-tae.
Isn't that obvious?
And it's highly possible that Captain Nam
also got the taste of Jong-tae's money.
I think I should look
more into this footage.
Go ahead.
-Call me if you find out anything.
-Okay.
Hey. Is Eun-hye home yet?
-Hello.
-About the footage.
I don't think we should trust it.
It's strange that Captain Nam
gave it to me right away.
I agree.
I'm going to hand it over
to the KCSI for an examination.
You are? That's good. I'll come with you.
You don't have to.
I'll get back to you
as soon as the results are in.
I'm the one who got the footage.
What if you find out something
and go to another reporter?
I can't let you fool me like that.
Do you think I'd do such a thing?
-Yes.
-You can come over then.
This is the original. It's not edited.
I'm sure the time code is
from when it was filmed.
Can I watch it again from
where the woman left the room?
I'm sure about this.
There's nothing suspicious.
All right. She's leaving.
Stop. Right here.
What is this?
I guess there was some dust in the lens.
Rewind it again.
She's leaving the room.
Stop. This.
A bug… Is it a bug?
A bug doesn't hover in the air.
You're right. What could it be?
This is a bug sitting on the screen
for a while and flying off.
The footage playing on the screen
was filmed by another camera.
That's why the time code
in the footage appears to be original.
That sounds plausible.
Now, we need to focus on Jong-tae.
No. I'll pick you up.
It's okay.
I'm the one asking you for a favor.
Yes.
I'll see you then.
Those rude idiots.
Is Eun-hye home yet?
I see.
By the way, where can I buy
women's underwear?
Not a place like that.
Somewhere in the neighborhood.
I see. Do they have underwear?
Okay. Bye.
Goodness.
Eun-hye.
Thank you for coming.
Mr. Park Gun-ho died.
He died because of you.
-That's…
-Why do you keep making others miserable?
I'm sorry.
It'll be all over soon.
You don't have to suffer
because of me anymore.
Bullshit.
-Eun-hye.
-Stop faking it and say it.
That you're innocent.
That you don't want to die
for something you didn't do.
Stop acting pitiful
because I don't pity you at all.
Eun-hye.
Fine.
I lied to you.
I really did kill someone.
I lied to others that I didn't do it
because I wanted to live.
I'm a horrible person.
So don't ever think of me again.
Dad.
Why are you being like this?
Why would you say that?
You didn't kill anyone.
I just said I lied to you, you fool.
Don't ever think of me.
Just think
that I never existed.
You'll feel comfortable that way.
And so will I.
I'm done.
Wait. Hang on.
Just a moment, sir.
I made a mistake.
Eun-hye… Please let me see her.
Let me see her again.
Please go stop her. Please.
Tell her
that her dad
wants to see her once again.
Please.
Please let me see her face one more time.
Please, sir.
Eun-hye.
Eun-hye!
Mr. Yoo, where are you now?
I have something to tell you.
Here's my card.
It's about Lee Dae-cheol's case.
Really?
I'll wait for you in the office then.
Thank you.
JEONGHAN DAILY
Sir.
Hey, you…
It's all right.
Let's go home and talk.
Mr. Kang.
My dad…
Please save my dad.
-Oh Jong-tae's alibi was fabricated.
-Oh Jong-tae wouldn't be the culprit.
It's someone
who's more powerful than he is.
He met him on purpose to prove a point.
I won't have to go to court, right?
Joo Dong-pal!
Do-chang is busy
chasing after Joo Dong-pal now.
The witness that judges trust the most
is the detective who was in charge.
What if that detective testifies in court?
I never asked for a retrial.
Have you visited Lee Dae-cheol recently?
Why are you asking me that?
It's true that Do-chang is
reinvestigating Lee Dae-cheol's case.
I hate that brat. She attracts cops.
I said stop!
Eun-hye is sick.
How could you kick her out?
Do you really think
you can take care of her?
She'll be reminded of her father in jail.