THE GOOD DETECTIVE: SEASON 2
SEOBU POLICE STATION
Chief.
Hold on. Just a little longer.
-Chief.
-Give me a break.
Can I just enjoy a moment of peace?
What in the world?
Turn the car around. Now!
-It's him!
-Wait, Chief!
Chief Moon!
-Stop!
-Give us a comment!
He's getting away!
Why do I have to
jump the walls of my own station?
This is all your guys' fault.
I'm too old for this.
Hear me out.
The case happened in Seoul, not Incheon.
Why would we take a case
under your jurisdiction?
My detectives went unknowingly.
It was a coincidence.
They were simply invited by
Director Cheon Na-na.
No, that's…
Captain!
Darn it.
What did he say?
They're saying we should take the case
because two of our guys were on site.
Simply put, they want us to take
this headache of a case away from them
regardless of jurisdiction.
Do we know why Cheon Na-na collapsed?
According to the hospital,
she seems to have overdosed on insulin,
which caused her to go into shock.
Does that mean whoever gave her the shot
made a mistake?
We don't know if it was a mistake
or intentional yet.
Are you saying there's a chance
someone gave her an overdose on purpose?
According to a forensic pathologist,
there's been a case abroad
where insulin was weaponized.
But why is this case
being compared to an overseas case?
It's because of the interview Ms. Cheon
had with WCN before the incident.
Former Chairman Cheon Seong-dae
was put on trial for corruption
because I actually reported it.
And the crime of
current Chairman Cheon Sang-woo
came to light because
I gave the detectives decisive evidence.
Incheon Seobu Station revealed
Chairman Cheon to be the abettor
and is now in charge of the case.
Incheon Seobu Station is yet to explain
what the decisive evidence
Ms. Cheon gave them was
or how it's related
to Ms. Cheon's current incident.
What kind of answer
are we supposed to give them?
We have no answers yet.
But Cheon Na-na sent us hers.
Do you know why you got prison time?
I sent the documents to the Blue House.
You really want to die at my hands.
I'll be honest with you.
I'm afraid of you.
I fear…
You will actually kill me.
That's the end.
I asked you personally.
My career could've been on the line.
I had no choice.
What about the result?
Did you inform them too?
So by sending us that file,
she's telling us that this was
Cheon Seong-dae's attempt to kill her,
and that she wants us to catch him, right?
Yes, basically.
Detective Oh, do you really believe
he tried to kill his daughter?
No, I think she's using the same method
she used on Woo Tae-ho.
She's charging at him
with another risky play.
It was probably staged by her.
He's right.
Inviting us to the scene must have
also been a part of her plan
to make us witness everything.
She got us involved on purpose.
Let's just say it never happened then.
We can ignore it.
No, we shouldn't throw away this chance
to attack Cheon Seong-dae.
I say we go after him
just like Cheon Na-na wanted us to.
We'll pressure Cheon Seong-dae
to bring him closer to us.
He'll be a great asset to our case.
Are you buddies with Cheon Seong-dae?
Does he seem like a man
we can call over at our convenience?
Chief has a point with this one.
You're saying you want to play him,
but that's just not a realistic plan.
Cheon Seong-dae is
on a different level from his kids.
He's had years to solidify friendships
with the most powerful political figures.
People that would make our jaws drop.
We're no match against
a single one of them.
Once Cheon Seong-dae gets involved,
we'll drop dead like flies.
And it won't just be us flies.
Our families would be exterminated too.
I understand where you're coming from.
We may all end up losing our jobs.
So you agree?
Okay.
Then we have one job.
Do absolutely nothing.
I don't want any of you
coming in to work from now on.
I'll still pay you.
Stay put like a statue at home.
Just sit there and zone out.
Easy, right?
We should carry on investigating
Cheon Na-na's case.
We already have evidence against her.
Hey!
Do-chang.
Violent Crimes Team Two Troublemakers.
I'm begging you.
I don't want anything.
I just want one thing.
It's inner peace.
I'll put the building
I own in Gangnam on the line.
If we all end up getting fired,
we'll split it eight ways.
You don't have to go that far--
There's no way we all get fired.
I'm positive.
How are you so sure?
It might very well be possible.
Don't you think we'll get fired
if we keep pushing it, chief?
If that's the case,
I think it'll be a win for us
regardless of the result.
I agree.
I'm sorry.
I can't accept your proposal, Chairman.
Why not?
I'm not in a position
to get involved and resolve this.
That's your position.
What does McQueen headquarters think
about this situation?
Change of management?
Yes.
"Make Cheon Na-na the new head of TJ."
Why didn't you burn it? Why?
I was curious about what was inside.
That's it?
I told you, Gi-jin.
We won't get paid if that gets revealed.
We may have to cough up
the money we already received.
Do you know why Gi Dong-jae held onto it?
It was to extort money from Cheon Na-na.
Gi Dong-jae is dead.
This is our chance to take his share.
I'll make myself clear.
I've bet my whole life on this.
There are only two ways this can end.
I either die behind bars
or live on a pile of money.
Tell me then.
How do you plan on dealing with
the Incheon Seobu Station guys?
They got the forensic result too.
I came this far because I trusted you.
You must help me through this
until the very end.
TJ is in the hands of Cheon Na-na now.
Cheon Sang-woo is beyond redemption.
Use him one more time.
How?
Reveal everything you found.
Then destroy him with it.
The guys at Traffic Crimes
were hiding these.
It's proof that Cheon Na-na's fingerprints
were on the buckle and steering wheel.
How'd you get these?
I doubt they just handed them over.
They most definitely didn't.
We made a whole scene.
We forcibly rummaged through
all their cabinets.
It got pretty physical.
What if they use it against us later?
What's there to fear?
We can just become landlords.
We took it up a notch on purpose.
I'm counting on them to get us fired.
That's smart. We should've gone with them.
I know right?
Cut the crap, you fools.
Cheon Na-na's blood was found
on Jung Hui-ju's clothes.
We even have her fingerprints
from the car.
Does this mean that
Cheon Na-na murdered both
Jung Hui-ju and Woo Tae-ho?
No, it's not definitive.
It's still just a suspicion.
So she could've murdered both
or just one of them
or neither of them? Is that right?
Shouldn't we decide on one narrative
to focus our time and energy on?
Which one should we run with?
To obtain Jung Hui-ju's belongings,
Jang Gi-jin went as far as harming
her grandpa.
Probably out of fear that
we'd find Cheon Na-na's blood.
He wouldn't have gone that far
if that bloodstain
had nothing to do with
Jung Hui-ju's murder.
-Right.
-I agree.
She killed Gi Dong-jae to rid of evidence
for that same reason too.
If it turns out that Cheon Na-na
killed Jung Hui-ju,
then her motive to murder Woo Tae-ho
becomes very clear.
Woo Tae-ho learned the truth.
So she murdered him to hide it.
Then what was her motive
for murdering Jung Hui-ju?
Simply because she had an affair
with her husband?
Does she look like one to kill for love?
We have evidence, so why not bring
Cheon Na-na in for questioning?
If we do that, we're basically admitting
that Cheon Sang-woo,
the guy we sent to prison
as the abettor is innocent.
If Cheon Na-na killed Jung Hui-ju,
then Gi Dong-jae wasn't the murderer.
If that's the case, Cheon Sang-woo
will be cleared of his charges.
Things will get really complicated.
Darn it. We have enough evidence
but our hands are tied.
Hello?
Okay. We'll be waiting.
Captain. Cheon Na-na is on her way.
-What?
-Why?
I told her lawyer that we need
the victim's statement.
But she wants to personally give it to us.
No way.
POLICE FOR THE PEOPLE JUSTICE IN KOREA
What's her real reason for doing this?
Does she really plan on putting
Cheon Seong-dae behind bars?
I doubt it.
I'm sure she knows that's impossible.
Then why?
It's simple.
One reason is self-preservation
and the other is crisis management.
I see.
Did you expect me to understand that?
Lay it out simply. Don't use big words.
She beat us to the punch.
She wants us on a leash
in case she gets busted.
Much better. I understand now.
She's truly a conniving one.
FAITHFUL WARM AND TRUSTY POLICE
SEOBU POLICE STATION
Do we have your permission to record this?
Yes, go ahead.
Okay then.
Start recording.
-Have you recovered?
-Why is she so confident?
Yes, I'm feeling much better.
We investigated the hospital.
We found nothing suspicious regarding
how the medicine was supplied.
This means the insulin shot was
tampered with
while it was in your possession.
It must've been switched out in my office.
That means someone went in there.
It was most likely one of my employees.
Which leads us to someone powerful enough
to order around an employee like that.
If it was an inside job,
finding the culprit won't be easy.
I think it'll be a quick process
since Detective Oh is in charge.
Is that why you invited me to the event?
"You clearly saw it,
so catch the culprit."
Are you…
suspecting me?
Are you saying
that I purposely injected
a lethal amount of insulin into myself?
We meet all sorts of people
working this job.
We come across people
who are impossible to make sense of
with a normal mindset.
Are you struggling with the investigation?
That's a strange excuse.
Yes, it's an excuse.
We're finding it hard to approach
the suspect due to his high profile.
I will do my best to cooperate.
This person tried to kill me.
You must catch the culprit,
whoever it may be.
Right, but everything is circumstantial.
Unless we find direct evidence--
I have faith.
You put the chairman of
a conglomerate on trial.
I cooperated with your investigation
because of that faith,
fully knowing it was illegal.
I'm talking about the search and seizure.
It was a trick to make
the evidence admissible.
I didn't know.
I found out later.
That there was an issue
with how the evidence was collected.
It might become a problem if that's
revealed in Sang-woo's second trial.
She's here to threaten us.
Should I keep recording?
Yes, let's see how far she goes.
I agree.
Chairman Cheon Sang-woo may
be acquitted on all charges.
That's not ideal for you either.
You're misunderstanding me.
But I understand.
I distorted the truth a little
when I testified to you.
What is it?
I apologize.
I was being selfish.
I think that's why
I tried to direct your investigation
another way.
I deeply regret I failed to stop
my brother from murdering Jung Hui-ju
even though I heard him give the order.
I had Jung Hui-ju come see me
the day she was murdered.
I should have told her.
But I couldn't.
I may…
I may have wanted Jung Hui-ju dead.
She was the one who stole my husband.
I felt tormented.
Jung Hui-ju wouldn't be dead
if I had spoken up.
That guilt was why
I tried to kill myself with Tae-ho.
Tae-ho didn't commit suicide.
I...
I wanted us to die together.
When I survived,
I figured that the only thing I could do
was find out who killed Jung Hui-ju.
That's why…
That's why I helped you, Detective Oh.
So you met Jung Hui-ju
on the day she was murdered?
Nothing happened?
No, nothing.
We just talked and she left.
Is there any chance
you concealed this from us
out of fear you might become a suspect?
That didn't cross my mind.
It was the guilt.
Because I did nothing
to prevent her murder.
That's why I couldn't tell you.
It's not because you don't remember?
It's not.
Memories can be manipulated subconsciously
when you're in shock.
To remember it in a way that
is advantageous to oneself.
Does that happen?
Maybe it did to you, Detective Oh.
You said you saw you killed your father.
But maybe you didn't.
Maybe you were so frightened
that you deluded yourself
into thinking you did.
You're right.
I changed the truth.
I manipulated it to how I wanted it to be.
Just like you.
I'm very busy these days.
The company is in trouble.
Everyone is counting on me.
Today's the last day that
I'll have time to meet with you.
I carved out my precious time to come by.
I hope
I no longer have to
concern myself with this matter.
If I'm being honest,
I agree with everything Cheon Na-na said.
That's how it is at first.
Everything makes perfect sense
because every detail was
prepared to a tee.
It's kind of amazing
if she really was acting.
This won't be easy.
We have no evidence
to refute her testimony.
Her acting will fool every judge.
But she didn't explain why her blood was
found on Jung Hui-ju's clothes.
Maybe we should've cornered her with that.
Jang Gi-jin knows
we got the forensics result.
Naturally, Cheon Na-na will find out.
Did we give them time to
come up with a plan?
It's best to let her believe
she's winning for now.
Cheon Na-na's main goal is
to have TJ all to herself.
She came to tell us
she won't allow anyone to stop her
from fulfilling that goal.
We might end up with another victim.
He's right. The woman even turned
her own father into a murderer.
She would do anything.
Hello. Who is Detective Sim Dong-uk?
-What?
-It's me.
You're under arrest for accepting bribery
and breach of duty.
-What?
-Let go.
-What the hell?
-Don't make this hard.
-You better let go.
-Get your hands off of him.
-Shut up.
-You darn punk.
-Hey, let go of him.
-Wait!
-Calm down.
-Stop, Do-chang.
Sim Dong-il is your brother, correct?
Yes.
What does he do?
How does he make a living?
-Why do you ask?
-He's unemployed, right?
Didn't you drag me here
because you had charges against me?
Then just investigate me.
Why do you keep bringing my brother in?
We found that 300 million won was
deposited into his account.
How did an unemployed man
deposit such a large sum?
What are you talking about?
The money was transferred by TJ.
The company you're investigating.
Your brother has zero connections to TJ.
You used your brother's account.
The plan was to divvy up the money
with your fellow teammates.
What the hell did you just say?
How dare you!
It's you, right?
You're behind all this, aren't you?
What are you doing?
I know it's you, Jang Gi-jin!
Yes, it's me, you little punk.
I saw the money in my account.
Why didn't you tell us?
Didn't you find it suspicious?
You should've told your detective brother.
I thought it was sent by mistake.
You didn't touch the money, right?
Well...
I withdrew it to invest it in stocks...
-Are you mad?
-Seriously?
I was going to put the money back
once I made a profit.
I can do it right now.
Thankfully the stock price rose.
What's wrong with you?
That money wasn't yours to withdraw.
That's a crime!
Your life is still a mess.
Dong-uk's on the verge of
going to jail because of you!
-Calm down.
-Hey, he did nothing wrong.
He got unlucky and fell into the trap.
We should be glad
we can get the principal back.
Quickly take it out
and put it back in the account.
Okay. But will Dong-uk really go to jail
because of me?
No, that will never happen.
We won't let that happen. Don't worry.
How did they find out
your account number though?
Did someone ask for it?
No, nobody.
I rarely used it recently
because I wasn't getting paid
or paying anyone either.
When was the last transaction made?
It was the former Team Director of TJ...
-Choi Yong-geun?
-Yes, him.
He told me to make this account.
I think that was the first
and last time I used it.
This was Choi Yong-geun's idea.
Jang Gi-jin was just the executioner.
Let's catch Jang Gi-jin.
Take Gu Jae-chun's testimony
and request an arrest warrant.
Charge Jang Gi-jin for abetting
the attempted murder of Jung In-beom.
That vile bastard started this.
We need to win this fight first.
We can only get Cheon Na-na that way.
These are the clothes Jung Hui-ju was
wearing when she was murdered.
We seized them
from an undisclosed location.
It's evidence that
the murderer Gi Dong-jae was hiding.
Why has this evidence been found now?
We suspect one of the investigators
kept it hidden on purpose.
For what purpose?
It was to prove
Chairman Cheon Sang-woo's innocence
during the second trial.
There was another bloodstain
that wasn't the victim's.
Whose is it?
I can't reveal that yet.
However, we think the other bloodstain
wasn't present at the time of the incident
but was added on later.
The other blood was likely
fabricated evidence.
On what grounds do you say that?
TJ transferred a large sum of money
to a family member of one of
the detectives from Violent Crimes Unit
who was in charge of Jung's case.
We believe they bribed him
to keep the evidence concealed
so the Chairman can win his second trial.
You mentioned the Violent Crimes Unit.
Do you mean Incheon Seobu Station's
Violent Crimes Unit?
Yes, that's right.
This team you're talking about
played the biggest role in getting
Chairman Cheon Sang-woo
behind bars for abetting murder.
Why would they want him innocent now?
You bring up a good point.
People would've suspected them
of aiding a chairman of a powerful company
if he was found innocent
in the first trial.
It was their goal
to have him lose the first trial
and then win the second one.
This is the scenario that
Incheon Seobu's Violent Crimes Unit
and Chairman Cheon Sang-woo
came up with together.
I thought you said
Jung Hui-ju's clothes were burned.
So why do you have it?
Why? Explain to me.
It's the same reason why
Gi Dong-jae didn't burn the clothes.
I've done too much
for me to get rid of that evidence.
It's as you said.
The moment you claim ignorance,
my life will be over.
I kept it as insurance.
So whose blood was found on her clothes?
I think you know that better than anyone.
Can you really make people believe
what you told the reporters?
That the evidence was fabricated?
I can't do it without your help.
You'll have to manipulate the police,
prosecution, and the press.
Me?
If things go awry one more time,
you and I will be done for.
Do you think you can catch me with
that petty evidence you have?
You can't.
Neither can the detectives.
I decide my fate.
No one can end me beside me.
I will make every decision.
You better wrap this up well
for your sake, not mine.
Gu Jae-chun and Jang Gi-jin
talked using burner cells.
That means they were conspiring
Jung In-beom's murder.
We also have clear evidence that
Jang Gi-jin handed Gi Dong-jae over
to Gu Jae-chun.
Pardon?
Okay.
I'll find corroborative evidence
and get back to you. Bye.
What did he say?
He said it's not enough to prove
they were accomplices.
Do you think he was influenced by
Jang Gi-jin's announcement
about us?
I'm sure he was.
The prosecutor doesn't trust us.
Let's be real,
Seoul Criminal Investigation Division's
claims hold more weight than ours.
We're losing the game to him.
Cheon Na-na probably helped him.
The power of TJ has shifted to her.
I'm sure that played a part.
How should I say this…
The Civil Petition Division
at Headquarters called me.
You've all been summoned
for investigation.
Wait, all of us?
Yes. It's serious.
I think Jang Gi-jin
trapped us good.
They made everything up.
We have no reason to be scared.
We'll just go and tell the truth.
Their goal isn't to arrest us.
They're trying to shorten
the length of our investigation.
There's no need to all go in yet.
I'll go first
and try to get this under control.
INCHEON METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Why does the opponent keep getting bigger?
You overreached. This was greed.
You went too far this time.
It wasn't on purpose.
I was just investigating a murder case.
The big guys happened to be involved.
You should've avoided it then.
It's not only your job on the line.
Your teammates are about to lose
their jobs. What are you going to do?
Stop scaring me. You know that
I'm not one to do that.
A quick look into this could tell you
who's playing tricks.
I don't care.
I know one thing for sure.
The moment I help you,
I'll be hit with
the biggest roadblock of my career.
I'm not asking for your help.
Just give us some time.
Their goal is to waste our time.
Give us time to--
Please, Inspector Yoon Sang-mi.
Once is enough, Do-chang.
You did your part.
What you did was truly admirable.
This is where you stop.
You're not a superhero.
That brat.
Darn it.
That darn brat hasn't changed one bit.
So we're screwed.
Do you know anyone at the main office?
That place is packed with your alumni.
I know a ton.
But I was hated by most of them.
Why did you live that way?
I lived like you.
And I plan on living like you
for the rest of my life.
You little…
What?
Why do you live like that?
What? I'm hanging up if you lecture me.
Why are you always so oblivious?
You should be more discreet
when you're asking for a favor.
How could you ask me
in front of everyone like that?
That's why you can't get promoted.
You're one to run your mouth.
That's how you're going to talk to someone
who outranks you by a mile?
You need to learn some manners.
Just hang up! I'm done with you!
I looked over the charges again.
I'll need another week to review it.
What?
Pardon, ma'am?
Of course.
I admire your thoroughness,
Inspector Yoon Sang-mi.
You should most definitely
review it carefully.
You have one week.
Then I'll proceed by the book.
Understood, ma'am. Salute.
I knew I lived a good life.
Just follow my path.
There's no need to improvise.
Do exactly as I do.
Yes, sir.
We bought some time,
but how will we turn this around?
We need support.
From who?
Someone who is much more powerful than
Cheon Na-na.
You have a huge headache, don't you?
From making up all those stories.
Hey.
You need to come up with stories
that are believable.
This is just too far-fetched.
Didn't you order the fabrication?
I don't share your skill of
conjuring up stories.
It was Dad then.
Yes, it all makes sense now.
Did you really believe it was me?
You're his beloved son.
He'd do anything for you.
He thinks I put you in here.
He'd do anything to kill me and save you.
Then why does everything keep
ending up in your favor?
Why?
Does Father seem that dumb to you?
Reality hasn't sunk in for him yet.
He thinks he still has power.
He doesn't know that
I'm the one with the power now.
That's why he's not thinking straight.
No one else thinks that!
We have never given you any power.
You just think you have it.
This is all just happening
inside your head!
Do you know why I want Dad's place?
He realizes all of his visions.
He can make anything come true.
Doesn't matter if it makes no sense.
If he says it's the truth, then it is.
I'll show you.
A world where my thoughts become reality.
You can't do it.
I told you. You can't beat us.
Look at yourself right now.
I've realized my vision.
Originally, my next step was going to be
to get you out of this place
if you didn't provoke me.
But both you and Dad
keep making me change my mind.
I can't beat you.
I can't go up against a lunatic.
Fine, try to destroy us.
Knock yourself out.
I will keep a close watch on
how you realize your thoughts.
Yes?
You've been summoned to
Incheon Seobu Police Station, sir.
Me? Are you sure?
They summoned me?
Yes, sir.
What are they playing at?
Are they trying to infuriate me?
I'm sorry, sir.
They also sent an attachment.
The content of it
complicates this situation.
DIRECTOR CHOI SANG-HO
I sent the only person
you think of as a family to jail.
I gave the police the evidence.
How could you forgive me,
even if I was your daughter?
You seem quite determined tonight.
You are trying to provoke me
so I won't ignore you.
FAITHFUL WARM AND TRUSTY POLICE
Did Na-na send you that recording?
Yes.
What was her purpose in sending it to you?
As you saw on the news,
we're in charge of Cheon Na-na's case.
It was sent by the victim,
so we have no choice but to call--
I was simply scolding her as a father.
Any father who hears that
would've lost it, don't you agree?
Yes, you're right.
Your reaction was completely valid.
However, I ask that you understand
where we are coming from.
Cheon Na-na's overdose case
coincided perfectly
with what you said to her.
So what?
Must I defend myself to you people?
There's no need for that.
We're sure Cheon Na-na
fabricated everything.
Are you saying…
that I should also claim
that she fabricated this incident
to make me look like the culprit?
We're asking for your cooperation, sir.
We'll be honest with you.
Someone is obstructing our investigation.
We need your help to stop them.
And if I don't cooperate,
you'll release this recording
to the press.
Is that it?
Yes.
My pride
got very hurt just now.
I know I've grown weaker.
But not to the point that
I have to make a deal with you people.
Release the recording to the press.
Those words came out of my mouth.
I must take responsibility.
Your names are
Detectives Kang Do-chang
and Oh Ji-hyeok, right?
Yes, sir.
I only remember the names of people that
did me a great favor
or humiliated me beyond measure.
It's one of those two.
Regardless of why I remember your names,
I doubt I will ever forget them.
-Chairman!
-Stop him.
Chairman, I have something to tell you.
Let him through.
Our investigation is
to prove that Gi Dong-jae
didn't kill Jung Hui-ju.
If we can prove it,
Cheon Sang-woo will be released.
My prediction is about to be correct.
Do you have the results?
Yes, sir.
I looked into the prices of
other properties around the area.
With the current market,
they go for about 45 billion won.
-My gosh.
-Divide that by 8. It's around 4 billion.
Why are you happy, you fool?
But isn't this a little unfair?
Shouldn't the money match the rank?
No, if anything, you and the Chief
should get less money.
Why?
You're both close to retirement.
We still have years left. We deserve more.
-Yes.
-You agree, right?
You boys are single.
The Chief and I are breadwinners.
I have my mom...
Chairman Cheon Seong-dae
has promised to cooperate.
Our investigation is good to go.
We just need to carry on this path.
Darn it.
I'm sorry to bother you
at this hour, Mr. Cha.
It's fine. What is it, sir?
Are you free for dinner?
I am, but why do you want to see me?
I have some people
I want to introduce you to.
-Let's go in.
-All right.
It's good to see you.
-Hello.
-Thank you for calling me.
-I appreciate you coming here.
-It's my pleasure.
I'm glad to be here.
-You're here.
-Hello, Chairman.
-It's great seeing you.
-Yes, likewise.
-Hello, there.
-Gosh, hello.
What a pleasure.
-I'll see you inside.
-Okay.
-Hello.
-Thank you.
Members of the assembly,
Prosecutor General, Commissioner,
and Minister.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
This is a great confidence boost for me.
You have all been on good terms with me,
one way or another.
I have never asked a favor
from any of you.
However, I wished that I had
just one time.
I thought I wasn't a picky eater,
but the food I ate in prison was
really not for my palate.
I'm a little embarrassed
to say this myself,
but I never wanted any of you to feel like
you owed me
for all the support I gave you.
To be completely honest,
I was saving my favor to ask you
in my most dire time of need.
That is now.
Please help me.
-What's he saying?
-What does he want?
-It was good seeing you.
-Yes, thank you for coming.
-Thank you.
-I had a great time.
-I enjoyed the meal.
-Thank you.
-Have a good night.
-I'll see you again.
-Goodnight.
-Goodbye, everyone.
This was a great opportunity for me.
I got to meet with such powerful people.
It was an honor for me.
You grew up in America, right?
Yes, sir.
There's one crucial thing you should know
if you want to do business here.
Unlike America,
you don't do business with money here.
You do it with politics.
Yes, sir.
What the hell are you people doing?
We have a search and seizure warrant.
For what?
You drew this yourself?
Yes.
I thought you only got a glance.
How is this so detailed?
Did someone give you a picture
and you drew based on that?
Can you give me a piece of paper, sir?
Would you mind coming in for a second?
Why did you want to see me, sir?
It's nothing. You can go.
Okay.
I need you to tell me
every single detail of what happened
between you and Captain Jang Gi-jin
at Mr. Jung's store.
Darn it.
What's going on, Captain?
What do you mean?
I saw that you were charged
with murdering Gi Dong-jae
and attempted murder of Jung In-beom
on the warrant.
Do you actually believe that?
They conjured up this nonsense
based on the lies Gu Jae-chun told them.
Captain... Listen, Gi-jin.
Your recent conduct
has been questionable to us too.
Please give us an explanation.
Why are you pushing the investigation
in an odd direction?
Summon Gu Jae-chun
from the detention center.
I'll question him myself
and reveal the truth to you all.
I prefer this over regular tofu.
Thanks for hanging in there. Eat up.
What about my brother?
He got me in this mess, right?
Hey, he did an honorable thing.
We didn't have to track down
the account thanks to his help.
I heard he withdrew the money.
Well, that's because he sensed
something was fishy about that money.
He did it just in case
it could be used against you.
He basically laundered the money.
You're not making any sense, Do-chang.
What? I'm not?
Why'd you say he laundered the money?
There's no need for criminal terminology.
Hey, don't blame your brother.
He was just used by bad people.
Jae-hong's right.
He was worried sick about you.
Not to mention, you got released
because he didn't get greedy
and told the truth.
Okay, I'm sorry.
-Hey, Man-gu.
-Yes?
If you look in my cabinet
-you'll see a bottle of soju.
-Okay.
-Here.
-You looked without my permission?
I won't have a drop of alcohol
until I cuff Jang Gi-jin myself.
I will make sure that
I arrest him myself.
All right.
-Let's have a drink in his stead then.
-Okay.
Yes, Inspector Yoon Sang-mi?
You've learned a lot.
You know how to ask for help.
What?
I got a call
from the Commissioner himself.
He ordered me to shut down
all investigations on
the detectives at Incheon Seobu Station.
How'd you do it?
I'm only one call away from
the Commissioner of the Incheon Division,
so that was a piece of cake.
Not him.
I got a call from the Commissioner
of the Seoul Headquarters.
It's my first time speaking to him too.
What? He called you himself?
Who's good side did you get on?
The Commissioner is not
an easy man to sway.
I can't tell you that.
You see, Sang-mi.
There are many secret connections
in the police force.
Just know that
I'm in the center of it all.
Is that so?
I'll have to hang up now
because I'm about to curse you out.
And don't ever answer my call
while you're drinking on duty
and spew nonsense at me.
You're in a good mood today.
No, I'm not.
I've just gone mad.
I'm losing my mind.
I'm going to pay for my crimes.
I suggest you do the same.
Let's accept our fates.
And stop trying
to come up with useless tricks.
Accepting your fate means
you'll rot in jail for life.
What are you going to tempt me with now?
I've seen your dirty deeds firsthand.
I'm still a cop.
I can easily get you out of this.
Stop with your lies.
Just go pray to whoever you believe in.
And pray you don't get sent to
the same prison as me, you punk.
You better watch your mouth.
Hey, it's me.
I'll put your boss on the phone.
Talk to him.
Here, take it.
It's your brother that you trust the most.
What's up?
Are you sure?
In cash?
Is that so?
All right.
I said I heard you, punk.
You're going to take care of my family?
That's a problem.
I have no family.
They're more like my enemies.
I have no interest in
taking care of my family.
That's too much money
for someone with a life sentence.
I'll probably die before I spend it all.
You wasted your time.
Do you want us both to go down?
Let's live.
You and me both.
I appreciate it. Put it here.
Boss.
Thanks for all your hard work.
This is going to take
longer than I thought.
You should go eat.
No, we're fine.
How's your boss doing?
I'm worried he might be upset with me.
He won't pick up my calls.
Please tell him I'll go see him soon.
Okay.
Is he still drinking
and frequenting karaoke bars?
This morning, murder suspect Gu Jae-chun
was caught on CCTV walking out
dressed in a police uniform
while being investigated at
Seoul Criminal Investigation Division.
Police have set up checkpoints
and are conducting a rigorous search
all across the city to catch
the escapee Gu Jae-chun.
However, they have yet to find
any leads on his whereabouts--
What kind of bullshit situation is this?
Jang Gi-jin is behind this.
That scumbag is not going to stop--
Jang Gi-jin broke him out.
He's probably hiding him somewhere.
Then he'll kill him.
Gu Jae-chun has to die
for his charges to disappear.
We'll find Gu Jae-chun
if we keep hounding Jang Gi-jin.
You think we can catch that sly fox?
Ji-ung is right.
He's probably coming up with a plan
as we speak.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Where have you been?
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
You got us all worried.
Jang Gi-jin is in
the palm of my hands now.
While tailing him,
I've memorized all his everyday routes.
-You're done with this, right?
-Yes, why do you ask?
It may come in handy.
Don't act rashly.
If you make the slightest mistake
while tailing or tracking him,
he'll know right away.
-Then it'll all go down the drain.
-I know.
Like you always say,
it's time to do some fieldwork.
I need to go, his meeting is about to end.
And I want you all to trust me
and be on standby.
I'll let you know if something goes down.
Wait, Dong-uk…
Why is he so confident?
Just trust him.
He's going out to do some fieldwork.
That's what a good detective does.
DANGER
BEWARE OF FALLING
I put it in just in case
someone tries to harm you.
It's loaded. Check for yourself.
Goodbye.
You all have bullets left, right?
-Yes.
Put your gun down.
You too.
Yes, sir!
Arrest them.
Goodness.
Consider yourself lucky.
I almost shot your head off.
You should be grateful.
Hey, hurry up and let him out.
I almost forgot.
-Darn, it's tight.
-What the--
-How long were you in there?
-Damn.
Here.
Throw this out for me.
Gross.
You should have just peed your pants.
This is worse.
-I got you.
-Good job, kid.
I caught him.
-Ji-ung.
-Yes?
Uncuff Captain Jang.
Why?
We should hear him out first.
We might've gotten it wrong.
It's also bad manners
to cuff a fellow detective.
Yes, you're right.
Sit down, you punk.
Sit.
-There.
-Darn it.
Let's start with Captain Jang first.
Why were the two of you
out there together?
He was trying to catch Gu Jae-chun.
You wanted to catch him yourself, right?
How will you explain the bag of money,
the fake passport,
and the gun found on site?
It was a sting operation.
He used to lure Gu in
so he could catch him. Isn't that right?
That makes sense.
Is that what he said?
You saw what happened.
He tried to shoot me.
He was going to kill me
to get rid of the evidence.
No way.
I was just his puppet.
I didn't even think about breaking out.
He ordered one of my men
to take my place in prison.
Then he gave me money and a ticket out
of this country. It was all him.
You punk! That's enough lies!
He's Captain of
the Seoul Criminal Investigation Division!
Why would a man like him do
something so atrocious?
This Captain was the one
who ordered us to kill
Jung Hui-ju's grandpa.
That's why we tried to kill him.
He broke me out of prison
and tried to kill me
to cover up his tracks!
He was also the one
who handed over Gi Dong-jae to us.
He wanted me to kill him!
I won't sit back and let you side with him
because he's a fellow detective.
I'm going to tell every reporter I know.
How you detectives are
trying to frame me for everything!
-Ji-ung.
-Yes?
-Put the handcuffs…
…back on Captain Jang.
Yes, sir.
Did you people take me for a fool?
-No, we didn't.
-Be gentle.
-Okay.
-Two notches.
-Right.
-We didn't take you for a fool.
We never would.
This didn't happen
because Jang Gi-jin made a mistake.
Honorary Chairman Cheon Seong-dae
has the detectives' backs.
If things continue on this path,
Chairman Cheon Sang-woo
might get released.
If he does,
that will give the detectives
the chance to reinvestigate
Jung Hui-ju's murder.
So?
Even if they conduct a reinvestigation,
they won't find any new evidence.
But what's concerning is…
Woo Tae-ho's case.
If they find out that
his case was not an accident,
then they will connect it to
Jung Hui-ju's case.
That'll give the detectives a reason to
keep digging into Jung Hui-ju's case.
There's no need to worry.
The detectives think
I tried to get us both killed.
And that's the truth.
Is it really?
Yes.
4 MONTHS AGO
I'm saying,
I didn't kill Jung Hui-ju.
Then who--
I don't know that either.
Why should I believe you?
Do you know about
the vacation home in Yangpyeong?
I was handed Jung Hui-ju's body
from that place.
From whom?
Captain Choi Yong-geun.
So he killed Jung Hui-ju?
Who knows.
However,
there was no need
for him to murder her himself.
If he waited, I would've done it for him.
So I wondered if it was Cheon Sang-woo
who killed her.
But then Mr. Choi said to me,
"Tell Vice-chairman Cheon
that you killed her."
"Or you won't get paid."
I called Vice-chairman Cheon
after I took the body.
I told him I wasn't
able to kill Jung Hui-ju yet.
Then he told me to hurry up and kill her.
Vice-chairman Cheon
didn't know Jung Hui-ju was dead.
So I realized
it wasn't Cheon Sang-woo.
Then who could it be?
The shadow I saw in the living room
of the vacation room
when I was taking the body.
Who was it?
That's everything I know.
It's your turn now.
I know
you're suspicious of someone.
Tell me.
Who is that person?
101 OCHEON-RI, SEONGSA-MYEON,
YANGPYEONG-GUN, GYEONGGI-DO
What is it?
Why…
were you here that day?
The day Jung Hui-ju was murdered.
Why did you come here?
I don't remember.
What exact date are you talking about?
I went through your car's GPS records.
You came here that day.
I guess I did then.
With whom?
Jung Hui-ju?
Why did you bring her here?
I asked her
why it was.
Why...
she loved you.
Did you love her too?
I'm still confused.
Tae-ho.
Were we ever in love?
Were you in pain…
when she died?
What about today?
I know you know.
How do you feel?
Is it equally as painful?
I never loved you.
If I had,
I would've killed Jung Hui-ju.
But I didn't kill her.
What you're suspecting is wrong.
Cheong Sang-woo killed Jung Hui-ju.
It was my brother who did it.
No.
It wasn't Cheon Sang-woo.
I killed her.
I was scared our relationship
might come to light.
So I killed her.
This all started because of me.
So that's what happened.
You didn't do anything, Na-na.
I'll turn myself in.
The police will agree that
I had a clear motive.
Who are you doing this for?
Jung Hui-ju?
Or me?
It was me.
I killed Jung Hui-ju here.
It was an accident.
About ten years.
I'll get to see you again
in about ten years.
All I ask is…
that you will tell me one thing.
That...
you will forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I still can't…
forgive you.
Let's have Cheon Na-na take
the reins for the time being.
You've already chosen one over the other.
I looked into my brother's trial.
I saw Detective Oh was
a witness for the defense.
You are the killer.
-Won't you regret this?
-I'll prove that I'm right.
It was Cheon Sang-woo, not me!
The killer's scenario is perfect.
But there's one flaw.
Are you talking about Choi Yong-geun?
Has any of your colleagues died?
They're looking all over for me.
Now we have to trust each other.