Boo!
- Morning.
- Hey. Morning.
You're not sleepy?
Okay?
It's cloudy though.
- Look. The sun's out.
- Whoa!
It's out already.
- And there are fewer clouds there.
- Yeah.
It's our last morning.
Yeah. Huh?
That we can spend together.
If we can't spend Day Ten together.
Right.
- Time flies.
- Yeah.
- It's not easy to meet every day.
- No.
We'll go back on that.
- On that.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Rice burgers?
- What is he going to do today?
- Yeah.
Will he wander around the city
and let fate decide for him?
What will he do about lunch with Maho?
YUDAI, 24, MODEL AND ACTOR
Okay.
He got a letter.
Huh? Another letter?
Chicken steak, pork cutlet,
croquette, and shrimp tempura?
DAY NINE, RICE BURGERS
Let's see.
The croquette.
Let's eat.
DAY NINE, 7:00 P.M.
PLEASE COME TO MAISON MARGAUX
- They're gathering.
- What, tonight?
It's tonight.
ARU, 30, DANCER AND CHOREOGRAPHER
Did you read it?
I did.
DAY NINE, 7:00 P.M.
Wait. Do we have the same time?
- It's the same.
- Is it?
- That's good to know.
- Good.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to look for Nanami.
I see.
Whoa!
Good morning. Hey, wait!
- You startled me.
- Morning.
Morning.
That was adorable!
These two are so cute.
- The people of Nice must be all smiles.
- All smiles.
No doubt.
You came from that way?
- Why?
- I went around.
Oh, my.
You're pretty as always.
Huh?
Here.
What are your plans for today, Aru?
If you're going to go search for Nanami,
I'd want to meet Maho.
By the way, you haven't declined
her lunch yet, have you?
I'll go see her later today.
- You'll see her?
- Yeah.
I'll tell her directly.
I see. Where will you meet her?
We're meeting at 12:00 p.m.
at Place Masséna.
She wrote that on the letter.
Okay.
I see.
Good to know.
Is he going to ambush Maho somewhere?
Is that what he plans on doing?
SHO, 22, UNIVERSITY STUDENT AND MODEL
- Good morning.
- Morning. What are these?
The olive oil drink with oat milk.
Wow! May I have one?
I have an iced one and a hot one.
- The hot one.
- Hot?
Thanks.
I wanna try the bun.
Bun?
One, please.
To go?
Yes. To go.
And this, please.
This one. Yes, please.
Merci.
- She's all grown up.
- Yes, she is.
I totally agree.
Two cappuccinos.
- Two cappuccinos?
- Yeah.
- Merci.
- You're welcome.
MAHO, 30, MODEL
Hi, Yudai.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Bonjour.
That looks good on you.
- It's not the same one.
- It's different? I see.
- So, there's something I need to tell you.
- It's a biker jacket.
It suits you.
- Um…
- Isn't it cold?
- I'm fine.
- Are you okay?
- It's just right.
- You're joking.
She doesn't wanna hear it,
and he wants to say it.
She doesn't wanna hear it. Oh, man!
- So…
- Yeah?
Today…
I really want to meet someone
and tell her my feelings.
Okay.
So…
I can't go on a date with you today.
Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Did you take your time
to come here just to tell me that?
I didn't think I should
say this to you through a letter.
I see.
Thank you for coming.
Not at all.
- I'm really sorry.
- It's fine.
I'll go find her.
Okay.
- Oh!
- It's Aru!
We haven't seen
this encounter system in a while.
It's happening!
What? Hey!
Look properly!
- What?
- Look!
Look properly, Aru!
She doesn't seem to be here.
What should I do?
He should take his sunglasses off.
That's true.
- He should.
- I agree.
If he wants to find her.
That's right.
Maho wasn't looking
for anybody so it's fine.
He should've made it easier
for her to recognize him.
That is so true.
It's beautiful.
- We kept looking from above yesterday.
- Yeah.
Um…
- There's something I need to tell you.
- Okay.
Can we sit and talk?
- Of course.
- Okay.
Where are they?
- It's Yudai.
- He's nearing.
- He's coming.
- They might meet.
- Jump!
- Phew.
So, Yudai asked me
if I would be willing to meet him today.
But I told him
I'm going on a date with you.
I told him that, and he said,
"I will look for you."
"If we meet,
can I have some of your time?"
He's desperately looking for her.
He's desperate.
If we happen to see him somewhere,
I will spend some time
with Yudai and talk with him.
I don't mind that at all.
Okay.
I got to see you today.
I really like you, Nanami.
I've told you all of my feelings.
How you feel when you see Yudai
is all up to you.
She might feel more at a loss
if she's told that.
You two spoke
after you got back last night?
Yeah.
That's impressive.
I bet Yudai has a lot on his mind too.
I see.
Hmm?
Oh, no.
- Is he nearing?
- He's close.
Let's eat.
Let's go.
- It's great weather today.
- Yeah.
- We could eat outside.
Could they be at Cours Saleya Market?
- What?
- Really?
Wow.
It's Day Nine.
- This is unexpected.
- It's pretty intense.
It's an unprecedented turn of events.
It's different from before.
It's like a different game started.
Nanami said it clearly.
From what we saw in Day Eight,
Nanami would say,
"Aren't you meeting Tohko?"
and "I have a date with Kensuke."
She was subtly declining Yudai,
but she gave up and said okay in the end
because Yudai was persistent.
That's the impression I got.
- Yeah.
- But she took it seriously.
She's treating it like a rule,
so if he happens to see her,
she will talk with him.
She shared that with Kensuke.
I'm surprised
that she's going fair and square.
- Yudai seems serious about it too.
- Yeah.
- That was unexpected.
He could have lost heart at that point.
- Yeah.
- Nanami and Yudai made that promise.
But Yudai could have just stayed
in his room and relaxed.
I mean, I would do that.
Why? You should go out!
You won't look for her?
I would think,
"I don't think I stand a chance."
You'd realize that.
- I would just stay in my room.
- But why? Go out!
They would never put you on this show.
Does Nanami not want to see Yudai?
Does she or does she not?
It's getting too complicated.
She's close with Tohko as well.
She knows all about Tohko's feelings.
But Yudai's feelings
are directed towards her.
- Yudai and Kensuke are close as well.
- They are.
Nanami might not know
what the correct answer is yet.
- That could be it.
- Yeah.
She had never fallen in love with someone.
But she has come to know
the feeling of love towards Kensuke.
Because of that,
she can now understand the affection
that others direct towards her
more clearly.
That's what I think.
So, the fact that Yudai likes Nanami
is just as important to her
as her own feelings for Kensuke.
Nanami is too kind
to ignore those feelings.
- That might be part of it.
- True.
- How will it go?
- What will happen?
- This chase game.
- It's exciting.
DAY NINE, 7:00 P.M.
PLEASE COME TO MAISON MARGAUX
Whoa!
Wait.
What are you doing?
Same to you. What are you doing?
- Can I sit here?
- Sure.
- You have two?
- Yeah.
I happened to run into Yudai this morning.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Oh. Did he say something?
Yeah. Well…
He told me what he was going to tell you.
I heard about it.
I thought, "Oh."
He said he was gonna meet you
at Place Masséna.
I thought I might see you if I went there.
So I bought us coffee
and went to Place Masséna,
but you weren't there.
Wait, really?
Yeah. So this coffee is for you.
He revealed everything.
He's good at that.
- It's Aru's special technique.
- Like saying he reconned.
Oh. Thanks.
I wanna drink it. Can I?
Yeah, but I was walking around with them,
so they spilled everywhere.
Oh, that's why. I see.
- It got kind of messy. Sorry.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- It's cold, huh?
- Yeah, but it's good.
- Are you okay?
- Huh?
It's a bit weird for me
to be asking if you're okay though.
Hmm. Yeah.
Of course you're not okay, right?
- Yeah.
- What were you reading?
Well, I haven't had lunch yet.
I was thinking of grabbing a bite to eat.
I was wondering where I should go.
- You were searching?
- Yeah.
- I haven't eaten yet. Let's go together.
- Shall we?
- Can we?
- Let's go.
Let's go.
You saw the letter, right?
- We have plenty of time.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
They look so good. Let's eat.
She's alone!
She's alone.
But I bought all those clothes.
It's the perfect weather
to go parachuting.
- Wow.
We can look out over the port.
The Port of Nice.
We're in the shade.
Phew.
GARIBALDI SQUARE
He's getting closer.
- To the port.
- They might all gather at the port.
Are they at a restaurant?
Did you cycle along this road with Yudai?
- Yeah. And we went all the way that way.
- That way.
- There?
- And then, that way.
Did you go to the lighthouse?
- Yeah.
- I see.
PORT OF NICE
- He's at the port.
Oh, no. He's here.
- Should we go to the shop?
- Let's go.
We should go while it's open.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Bye-bye, port.
Will I ever come here again?
That's so sad.
It's the last time on this trip.
Everything we do will be our last time.
- It's so sad.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- He's here!
- What's going to happen?
- It's really sad.
- Yeah.
So true.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- They sell hookahs.
Have you been to a shisha bar?
- I have.
- You have?
At Shimokitazawa.
Au revoir.
Wow!
- Whoa, he was inside the shop?
- Seriously?
Wow!
- It's still early, but I wanna drink.
- Oh.
That sounds nice.
- Yeah? Shall we?
- Shall we?
- One glass couldn't hurt.
- Maybe just one glass.
I wonder what that gathering
at 7:00 p.m. is.
- Was it at seven o'clock tonight?
- Yeah, at 7:00 p.m.
- Where are we?
- Is it here?
- We're here!
- Here?
- Oh!
- Oh, wow.
Oh, my. Wow!
- Do you smell it?
- I can smell the seafood.
- Santé.
- Cheers.
- Haven't seen you since yesterday.
- Yeah.
Since last night.
So, are you okay?
About today.
- Today?
- Yeah.
How are you feeling?
Well, I actually met him yesterday.
For lunch.
But it was like,
I kind of had a feeling.
So, I knew.
- I see.
- Yeah.
- We still have tonight.
- Tonight, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Oh, it's here.
- I'm not looking. Don't look.
I didn't see it yet.
- I didn't see it.
- Wow. Just look.
- Look!
- Wow.
- It's huge.
- Awesome!
Let's dig in.
Wow!
It's delicious.
That's got to be delicious.
Yum!
This is great.
- It's nice that they had lunch together.
- Yeah.
She couldn't have smiled
like this if she were alone.
- Oh. It says, "Japan Soul."
- Wow.
- These are all in Japanese.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Oh!
- What?
- I love her.
Taeko Onuki.
The one I was telling you about.
- You found it?
- I want this!
I want this!
They're not here either.
He wouldn't think
they're at a record shop.
No.
- Yudai must be thinking, "It's Day Nine."
- Yeah.
"Please come
to Maison Margaux at 7:00 p.m."
Should we go back?
- Yeah.
- Let's go to our hotels.
We need to put our stuff away.
You're right.
I'll take the same seat.
- Right.
- I'll go over to the back, then.
Me too.
To the very back.
- The last seat?
- No, the one next to it.
- I'll sit here.
- Here?
- Yudai couldn't find them.
- No.
- He sat far away from Kensuke.
- Yeah.
"Last letter"?
So, you went with Nanami, huh?
- Did you tell her your feelings?
- Yeah.
I told her everything.
Really?
So, did you find her?
I didn't.
- Oh, really?
- I didn't get to see her.
Seriously?
- But you looked for her, right?
- I did search for her.
I went to notable locations.
Places they might go to on Day Nine.
Right. I see.
But it was too difficult to find them.
I don't really want to look
at Kensuke right now.
Well…
Hello!
- Bonsoir.
Bonsoir.
I'll go sit at the back.
- Bonsoir.
- Hey.
- Where should I sit?
Oh?
You can sit anywhere you like.
Don't fret over it.
I can't help it.
- I'll go there.
- Okay, I'll sit here.
- Hi, Sho. We haven't met since we skied.
- Hi.
- Did you lose weight?
- Phew.
- Did I get a tan?
- Did you lose weight?
- Did I? I gained weight.
Who cares, right?
It looks awesome
when they're all together.
- It's different from last time.
- Totally different.
Can we open this?
Yeah. Everybody's here.
Should we read it?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna open mine.
There are two papers.
One's blank.
"We hope you are enjoying your trip."
"Tomorrow is the last day
of this ten-day journey."
That's right!
"Tonight is the last dinner gathering."
"Rules for Day Ten are as written below."
"Please choose one person
that you want to see on Day Ten."
"Please wait for that person at a place
where you want to see them again."
- "You can wait for them until sunset"?!
- What?
"The blank letter is
for you to share your feelings."
"This is the last letter."
"Please write your letter
at the hotel after this dinner gathering."
"If you do not wish to meet anyone,
you can retrieve your devices tomorrow."
- It says, "You can wait until sunset."
- Yeah.
Can we tell them where we'll be waiting?
- Yeah. I think so.
- Right?
So, we can designate the location
in the letter, right?
But even if we send this to each other,
what if we wrote different locations?
- Right?
- That's true.
This is difficult.
It'd be crazy if we chose the same place.
Yeah.
I see. We write the location.
- Yeah.
- Wow. This is difficult.
It says,
"If you don't want to meet anybody…"
Let's forget about this for now.
Tonight might be
the last time we get together.
- It's our last dinner gathering.
- Yeah.
- So, this was the goal of this trip.
- I see.
Tomorrow is Day Ten.
They choose one person
that they want to meet.
They wait for that person at a place
where they want to see them again.
Their time limit is until sunset.
They will go back
to their hotels after dinner tonight,
write their letters, and send them.
Right.
But if they don't wish to meet anyone,
they can retrieve their digital devices
at Maison Margaux
on the morning of Day Ten.
Retrieving their phones
means their trip ends.
- They can do that too.
- That's right.
If they're dying to check their phone,
they can retrieve their devices
without meeting anyone.
- Yeah.
- They can do that, right?
Let's say Person A writes to Person B.
They tell them where they'll be waiting.
But if Person B wrote to Person C,
telling them where they would be waiting,
Person A would find out
that Person B didn't write to them.
It becomes obvious
that their feelings aren't mutual.
- Because B didn't send A a letter.
- Right.
Not receiving the last letter
means they don't have feelings for you.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- But will they wait?
- Will they still wait?
Or, will they give up and go back?
If they received a letter
from someone else, they could go there.
- Yeah.
- I see.
If they both like each other,
and they thought of the same location,
they would be able to meet right away.
If not, it's like what happened
at the beginning of this show.
They need to search
for each other around the city.
If they both go to the other location,
they'll miss each other.
They can't both continue to wait
for the other person to come either.
- That won't work.
- No.
This is fate too.
It's where you want to meet again.
That's nice too.
- It's nice.
- They've been to that place before.
- It could be the ski resort.
- That's too far.
- Way too far.
- The ski resort?
It's over if they can't meet there.
"Oh, no! She's on the advanced slope!"
"Nanami's on the advanced hill!"
Why would you choose the ski slope?
- The dinner gathering seemed awkward.
- That was very awkward.
Aru looked so uncomfortable towards Mimi.
He looked like
he was surprised to see her there.
I mean, of course she would be there.
If he was sheepishly like,
"Hey," I would get it, but…
He was like, "For real?"
- He's just so honest.
- He's endearing.
- Yeah.
- I'm growing to love him.
I agree.
Yudai couldn't meet Nanami.
- That's right.
- He almost ran into her.
- That was really close.
- It was so close.
Such things might be happening
to us in our daily lives.
That's right.
- We may have passed each other somewhere.
- Totally.
- That's possible.
- By some chance.
I need to be more careful.
- I need to be more attentive.
- Yeah.
We should look around more.
If there is a Season Two to this show,
let's bring in a soccer player
with a really broad field of vision.
- Let's do that.
- Let's see if he notices everyone.
Or a long-distance runner.
Someone skilled at orienteering.
The captain of the orienteering club.
- They'll be good with maps.
- That's fun.
Wow, this looks delicious!
Oh, my!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
- Yay!
- Cheers!
- What's that?
- Caprese and sardine.
- What do you want to eat?
- Get me the same as yours.
Okay.
Do you want this one?
Thank you.
- Use your hand.
- Okay. Thanks.
I use my hand?
- Thanks.
- Do you want some, Aru?
- Here.
Yum.
- Which one did you eat?
- This one.
- Right.
- Thank you.
This is good.
- I want to eat the octopus.
- This one?
Let's eat.
NANAMI, 25, ACTOR
- This is delicious.
- This is good.
KENSUKE, 24, COMEDIAN
- Tasty.
- Yes.
MAHO, 30, MODEL
This is good.
Those who aren't doing well
are smiling less than those who are.
Totally.
- We should cut the meat.
- Yeah, we should.
Thanks.
I'll give some to Aru.
I got you some meat. Here.
- Can you hold this?
- Thanks.
What's that?
I'll pass it over to you.
That looks delicious.
I can't even turn my eyes that way.
I can't look that way.
It's the air around them, you know?
He's telling them to bite into it.
I wanna go sit over on the other side.
What did you do today?
I spent the whole day looking for someone.
I see.
- Hmm.
- I won't ask who.
You sound curious.
What did you do today?
I did some binge-eating alone.
- I met Yudai first on this trip.
- Stress eating.
It was the perfect weather
for stress eating.
Yet you chose to sit here.
Yeah.
He says he's happy now.
- Yeah.
- Good.
You look different.
So, the past two days,
I was thinking,
"I have no more time left!"
But I was able to use my time
for that person.
That's good.
- Good.
- I'm really glad I joined this trip.
- Did you meet her today?
- Huh?
- Today? No.
I looked, but I couldn't find her.
I didn't expect it to be easy,
and it sure wasn't.
You want anything?
Should I get something?
- The salmon.
- I'll pass it to you.
Please excuse me.
Dear Yudai,
Thank you for sharing
your honest feelings with me yesterday.
This is a normal letter.
She'll write her last letter separately.
Did you all eat the food at Margaux?
I ate the salad.
- The salad?
- I ate that too.
- The one in the jar?
- I ate that salad.
- Really?
How about the red bean butter toast?
- The toast? That was delicious.
- Did you eat it?
- That was delicious!
- It was super tasty.
That was awesome.
I wish I was the one for you.
I can't give up.
From Riko
I can't cheer you on
because I've fallen in love with you!
I wish I was the one for you.
I don't want to leave any regrets
on this once-in-a-lifetime trip.
I want to be with you.
Do you have
any memories of Maison Margaux?
- I ran into two people here today.
- Hi, Tohko.
- Wow.
- You look pretty today.
Thanks.
- Really?
- Yeah. I met two people.
Today turned out to be
the best day thanks to Margaux.
That's wonderful!
Can we talk outside for a little bit?
Sure.
- Now?
- You can eat first.
I was thinking, "Today is the last day."
- I wanted to talk with you.
- Yeah.
Just the two of us.
We only get to see one person tomorrow.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
But I think
it was really fun overall.
It was, wasn't it?
I don't really…
get it myself either.
But I think I really liked you.
Thanks.
I figured you would go to Nanami.
I wanted to give up.
But
we need to choose who we want to see…
for Day Ten.
And I want to see you, Yudai.
I still want to spend time with you.
I want you to keep me in mind.
Okay.
Please read this after you go back.
- After I go back?
- Yeah.
I will.
I don't know what happened last night.
But you couldn't see her today, right?
That's right.
- I looked, but I couldn't find her.
- Right.
And your feelings?
I couldn't tell her, so I will later on.
I'll tell her my feelings.
I see.
He hasn't told her his feelings yet.
- Things may have been different if he had.
- Right.
Another glass?
I'm not overdrinking.
Why? The milk tea was…
- Can I have a minute?
- Sure.
Right.
I looked all over the place today,
but I couldn't find you.
I want to share with you now
what I wanted to tell you today.
I like you, Nanami.
I've spent much less time with you
than Kensuke has.
But for me,
the day we went cycling together
was so much fun.
I was really nervous and excited.
I think that was
because I like you.
That was why I was excited.
- Can we change seats?
- Of course.
- Are you drinking?
- I'm drunk.
Yeah.
Everyone's talking to him.
Don't you need to talk to him too?
Huh?
- It's your last chance.
- Yeah.
I think it's over.
This is so tough.
Well…
I'm really proud of you.
I said something
pretty irresponsible at the vineyard.
Didn't I?
Irresponsible? Oh, yeah.
- Well…
- I was wondering how things were.
I've told him all of my feelings.
If it doesn't work out after all this,
then it's probably just not meant to be.
It's impressive you've done this much.
Right?
- On this trip.
- Yeah.
Are you worried?
- Well, I mean, it's all up to her.
- Yeah.
But
that cycling trip was really fun.
I'm glad you feel that way.
It was so much fun.
Is it Kensuke?
Wait. Never mind.
I think
I'd rather hold off
on hearing your answer.
- I'll go back.
- Yeah.
See you.
Hey.
- You're not cold?
- No.
- You're okay?
- Yeah.
- You know…
- Yeah?
At the beach today,
you told me about Yudai looking for you.
You said you would go talk with him
if we happened to see him.
I said, "Go ahead. I don't mind."
Right?
I said that,
but I didn't want you to go at all.
I was thinking that way,
but I tried to act cool.
Among all of us,
I'm the one that loves you the most.
Believe me.
Just stick with me.
Yeah.
Have you decided who you'll write to?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
That's good.
No changes?
Hmm.
Have you decided?
I'm still…
I think I'll take time to think about it.
Isn't there a part of you
that wanted to talk with other people?
- No?
- Quite a bit, actually.
Yeah, right?
- Regardless of what's going on now.
- Yeah.
Do you wish you could
redo everything from Day One?
Well, yeah.
If I redid everything from Day One,
things might have turned out
completely differently.
- Go talk with him.
- Huh?
- Don't you need to talk to him?
- No.
No. I'm fine.
- You're fine?
- Yeah.
I wouldn't know
what you're feeling.
I can't read your mind.
Just do what's best for you.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm sorry.
He says they're closing.
We need to finish this.
We are closing soon. Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Merci.
Merci.
I might not see you anymore, Nanami.
- I don't want that.
- Me neither.
This is so sad.
- I'll miss you all.
- Stop it. This is sad.
Don't say that.
Then, Atsushi.
- Who, me?
- Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you all
for these great encounters
over these nine days.
- I wish we could have talked more.
- Yeah.
Tomorrow, we'll only be able to meet
with the person we want to see.
It's kind of cruel, isn't it?
There will be people
we won't be able to see.
- But we made great memories.
- Yeah.
To destiny!
- Yay!
- To destiny!
Thanks for everything.
Till we meet again.
Thank you!
- Thanks.
- See you. Let's all meet up again.
Yeah.
I bet Atsushi went on and on.
- I see. Kensuke did the right thing.
- Well played, Kensuke.
- He did the right thing there.
- The speech probably dragged on.
- Atsushi probably said some good stuff.
- I see.
Kensuke was like, "To destiny!"
- Kensuke was very manly.
- Yeah.
He says the right things when he has to.
Exactly.
Comedians are good
at doing that when they have to.
That's exactly right.
He said, "Believe me. Just stick with me."
- "I'm the one that loves you the most."
- Yeah.
- He made Nanami cry again.
- It's not like he's possessive either.
- Right.
So I think he's good boyfriend material.
He has no money though.
Kensuke doesn't have money.
It's been completely overlooked
on this trip that Kensuke has no money.
That's his weak point.
I'll lend him money.
I'd lend him money if it's for Nanami.
I don't mind lending him money too.
- You'll lend him money too?
- Wow!
Kensuke now has
a humongous sponsor on him.
Kensuke is suddenly rich!
We really don't know what will happen.
Like with Kanaka.
- She'll think about it.
- That was unexpected.
We were saying here
that Sho and Kanaka were a stable couple.
It was only on Day Eight
that Sho told his feelings to Kanaka.
- And it wasn't very direct.
- We thought he would be manly.
We assumed he would be
direct with his words and say,
"I really like you, Kanaka."
But he was like,
"I kinda like you."
- That was cute.
- He turned into a college student.
She might retrieve her phone and leave.
- Yeah.
- Totally.
- That's true!
- She would just disappear.
- It suits her image.
- Yeah.
She'll leave a message saying,
"That was fun."
A message with a lipstick mark.
And she'll write, "Bye, Sho."
"Bye, Sho."
The concept of fate
is the theme of this journey.
Now, when it comes to the decision
of whether to go back or not,
will they ask themselves
that question again?
- "Is this really fate?"
- True.
Nanami didn't know Kensuke's face,
but his mailbox was in the middle,
so she randomly
tossed her letter into his mailbox.
That's actually amazing.
- Exactly!
- Yes.
And look at them now.
I feel a strong sense of fate.
Sho met Mimi at the beach.
- He talked to her from behind.
- Yeah, he did.
- It was an incredibly fate-driven start.
- Yeah.
When they all got together
for the first time,
it just so happened
that Kanaka was next to him.
By chance.
And when they talked, they clicked.
Sho happened to have
the Wish Letter for the next day.
Mimi and Sho
both had Wish Letters for Day Four.
Yeah. They had the same date.
That's why he didn't ask Mimi out.
He announced publicly
that he will ask Kanaka out.
We don't know how
he would've asked Kanaka out
if his Wish Letter wasn't on Day Four.
If he didn't have Day Four,
Mimi may have handed him her Wish Letter.
That would have been a different fate.
It was more like,
"If Sho's doing that, I'll do this."
- But that turned out so well.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Tohko did eeny, meeny, miney, mo.
Nanami chose Kensuke.
- Tohko had chosen Atsushi.
- Right.
This one didn't click at all.
No one even bothered to mention this.
- They went for dinner.
- They had dinner together.
Atsushi was like, "I don't feel
like meeting up with the other three."
But nothing sparked.
We know how innocent Tohko is,
yet she didn't feel a thing.
No, she didn't.
If she had, she wouldn't have
fallen in love with Yudai at first sight.
True.
Atsushi miraculously
didn't spark anything in Tohko.
Then, she fell for Yudai,
who sat next to her
and was exactly her type.
But for Yudai,
it was the cycling date.
His feelings got stronger
on Day Five with his Wish Letter date.
- Yeah.
- It was nice.
Tohko and Yudai
both had Wish Letters for Day Five.
That's right.
What if they had switched letters?
And if Tohko and Yudai
went on the cycling trip together?
He may not have known Nanami so well.
And Maho.
She met Yudai at the church
and felt a sense of fate.
She was drawn to him.
Aru is the same age as her,
but in the end, she liked Yudai.
- That's her story.
- Right.
And Kensuke.
Kensuke had it the best, to be honest.
He ran into Kanaka
and felt a sense of fate.
They went shopping together.
He ended up buying a coat
that Yudai was eyeing.
He did.
- He enjoyed Nice to its fullest.
- Yeah.
And he happened to receive a letter.
That letter came to him from Nanami.
Kensuke didn't really do anything himself.
That's true.
But with Aru,
he fell in love naturally.
It wasn't a fateful love
like on this show.
It's a likely scenario in daily life.
You run into friends
and make a connection with someone.
That was how Aru and Mimi met.
The way that didn't work out
might be because of this trip.
Their encounter was less fate-driven.
It had less impact.
Everyone was sensitive to fate too.
- Yeah.
- Exactly.
We still have the last letter.
Right. Yudai might think,
"Maybe I should give up on Nanami."
He might ask one of the other girls
to spend the last day with him.
- They could choose to leave too.
- Yeah.
Everyone might leave.
- Everyone?
- Everyone.
Why?
"I wanna meet someone,
but I wanna use my smartphone."
- Now that they know.
- They would want their phones.
They thought they had to wait
until the very end.
But now, "Wait, the morning of Day Ten?"
I came on this journey
and fell in love with you.
Meeting you was fate.
I'm happy I got to spend time with you.
I want to be with you.
From Riko
I will be waiting for you
at the white bench.
PLEASE CHOOSE ONE PERSON
THAT YOU WANT TO SEE ON DAY TEN
Dear Nanami,
You're the prettiest girl
in the world. I love you.
I'll be waiting for you
at the gate that was closed.
Dear Kanaka,
I'll be waiting for you
at the place where we painted together.
I hope you feel the same way too.
From Mimi
Thank you for a fantastic time
yesterday and today!
I want to know more about you.
I will be waiting
at Place Masséna on Day Ten.
PLEASE CHOOSE ONE PERSON
THAT YOU WANT TO SEE ON DAY TEN
Subtitle translation by: Remi Miura