CHEMINS DE FER DE PROVENCE STATION
SHO, 22, UNIVERSITY STUDENT AND MODEL
KANAKA, 25, BRAND PRODUCER
- Hey, morning.
- Good morning.
- You're here.
- It's early.
- It is.
- You woke up on time?
- I did.
- Good.
- Sorry it's so early.
- Oh, no. I'm excited.
We go in here.
- I hope it stops raining soon.
- I hope so too.
To the right. This way.
Wow.
Our trip has started.
Yeah. I'm looking forward to this.
I have no clue what we're doing.
I only know what was on the ticket.
Just the time and the name of the station.
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Was this on purpose?
- Yeah, it was.
- I thought I'd escort you.
- I can't wait.
NICE-VILLE STATION
MIMI, 20, PART-TIME WORKER
ATSUSHI, 30,
FORMER NATIONAL WATER POLO MEMBER
- Good morning.
Morning.
Your hand is warm!
- It's cold out.
- Aren't you cold?
- A little.
- Yeah.
It's cold. You smell really nice.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- It's this station, right?
Since we're on a date,
I wanted to share an umbrella.
- And you have an umbrella.
- I'm glad I brought one.
- Can I join you?
- Sure.
Yay.
- That way?
- Yeah.
- Wow, it's pouring.
- You must be cold.
- I thought you always bring the sun.
- I usually do.
Their names are pinned to their locations.
Oh. So that's what they do.
Day Four: I'll be waiting for you
YUDAI, 24, MODEL AND ACTOR
at 8:00 p.m. today at Maison Margaux.
He's going to eat sweets at 12:00 p.m.
Yeah.
It's Nanami.
- Nanami?
- It was Nanami.
HOTEL BRICE GARDEN
TOHKO, 24, ACTOR
Let me eat something.
What do we have today?
Mayonnaise and cod roe toast
and croque madame?
The pizza toast looks delicious.
They look delicious.
- I want the red bean butter toast.
- They serve red bean butter toast?
Let's eat.
Yum.
MAHO, 30, MODEL
Oh?
- Hey, morning.
- Wow! You startled me.
You startled me.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Are you here to write letters?
- Yeah, that's why I'm here.
I'm enjoying my breakfast.
Really? That's nice.
I wanted to try those too.
- I'll go take a look.
- Go ahead.
Bonjour!
How about we go for dinner tonight?
I'll be waiting at Place Masséna
at around 7:00 p.m.
- Aru!
- Aru. Really?
- Nice.
- Good for him.
It looks beautiful.
It would be nice if it were sunny.
- Yeah.
- The river is overflowing.
- The river's current is too strong.
- Yeah.
- We haven't been to these places in Nice.
- No.
It's actually my first time in Europe.
Oh, it is?
It's my first time outside of Japan.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Your first time abroad is Nice?
That's awesome.
- This is so luxurious.
- Yeah.
How much longer will it take?
Allow me to check.
CANNES: FORTY MINUTES ON TRAIN FROM NICE
- It's so sunny.
- The sun is out.
- You brought the sun.
- I brought the sun.
This way.
Oh, wow. This is beautiful.
This is embarrassing.
- They don't have cameras.
- No.
- They don't.
- So doing this isn't cheesy.
They really don't have cameras.
The city is just beautiful.
- It's spectacular wherever you look.
- Yeah, just look.
The cityscape is picturesque.
They're drinking coffee.
- And on a Sunday, right?
- Yeah.
- This is awesome.
And it's warm.
Cannes.
Cannes, Côte d'Azur.
- Wow.
- This is amazing.
- Bonjour.
Wow. It's the red carpet.
- Go walk on it.
- Nah.
Click!
I'll take pictures.
Yay!
Look at that.
They have handprints.
"Akira Kurosawa."
Let's buy something matching.
Oh, that sounds good.
Since we're here.
- Yay.
- Let's see…
Caps?
We could get caps.
Is it too big?
- Nice?
- Looks good.
They have stickers.
Let's get those too.
I want this one.
- This?
- Yeah.
- We can write letters on this.
We have something after this.
In the plan? I don't wanna know.
- I prefer not to see.
- The plan?
We're going to the market.
- The market?
- Forville market.
"Marché Forville."
- Oh, that's nice.
- Yeah.
ENTREVAUX STATION
We're here.
- Wow.
- Oh.
- Oh, wow!
- Wow.
Wow. What is this town?
Merci. Merci beaucoup.
- Wow!
- Just look. Oh, wow!
Wow.
I've never seen a landscape like this.
What is this place?
We're like two people
that were released into this town.
Yeah. It's like it's just the two of us.
Which way do we go? Right?
- I think so.
- Yeah, the right.
It stopped raining.
- It stopped?
- Yeah.
I hope the sun comes out.
I think it's this way.
Wow.
Wait. I'm so excited!
- You know what?
- What?
- We're going to the top.
What's up there?
- We'll aim for the top there.
- I'm so excited.
- Whoa.
- Wow.
- It's so ancient.
- Oh, wow!
- Amazing!
- Let's go in.
- Let's go.
How do I put this in?
There's a groove in the token.
You fit it into the groove?
This is exciting already.
This is the beginning.
Here we go!
Let's go.
- It's moving!
Yay.
What was that?
Wow. It's a hill.
Let's climb this.
The fog is clearing.
Oh, good.
- This is never-ending.
- Yeah.
This place is huge.
But it's there.
Yeah, that one.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Wow!
Whoa!
- Wow!
- Oh, man!
Oh, my.
Wow.
- Amazing.
- Oh, wow.
This is the best.
Wow. This is really worth the climb.
That's the station.
Huh? Oh, right.
We climbed up from there.
- Monaco is that way.
- That's Monaco?
- There?
- Yeah.
And look. Our Nice.
- Ours.
- It's that way.
Wow!
I want to remember this forever.
Oh my gosh.
- I'm sorry!
- Hey.
She's totally in love with him.
She's smitten.
Hey.
- Did I make you wait?
- Not at all.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Do you have somewhere you want to go?
Where should we go?
- Oh, look.
- I've marked a lot of places.
Are you hungry?
- You can be honest.
- I'm hungry.
You are? Okay then.
- Let's go to a café to grab something.
- Okay.
- Then we'll have something sweet after.
- Yeah.
- Which café?
- I like that.
ARU, 30, DANCER AND CHOREOGRAPHER
Dear Aru,
Bonjour!
How about we go for dinner tonight?
I'll be waiting at Place Masséna
at around 7:00 p.m.
From Maho
- He's happy.
- He's like, "Yeah, thanks."
- It's written all over his face.
- He savors it.
So adorable.
- So cute. It looks yummy.
- This looks delicious.
I'd take pictures if I had my phone.
I'll burn it into my memory.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
"Excuse me"?
- It's not cheese. It's yogurt.
- What?
That must be tasty.
- I wanna have some.
- Wait a second.
Let me eat the bottom part.
I should have ordered that.
- You're funny.
- Try it.
You should dig into it.
Wait, are you okay?
- What did I do?
- Here.
You've stained yourself.
That was quick. Thanks.
I'll try this.
- Too much?
- You're eating too much?
Is it good?
- It's good.
- The yogurt is thick.
It's getting dark.
Yeah.
It's started raining.
Umbrella…
Hi.
- Thanks for waiting.
- Oh, no. Here.
Let's use this umbrella.
- It's raining hard.
- Sorry I'm late.
Not at all.
- I made you wait.
- Good to see you.
What should we do?
- Let's go indoors.
- Yeah.
I want to go to a restaurant
called Tigermilk
and a vintage shop called La Fraperie.
Oh! I'm so sorry.
Um, yeah.
Do you want to go anywhere?
No. Let's go to those places.
Tigermilk, then?
- Tigermilk.
- Yeah. Let's go.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's fine.
Thank you. You're getting wet.
I'm okay.
- It's pouring.
- Which way?
- That way?
- That way.
- Let's go that way.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
- Let's go.
Thank you.
- Sorry. It was sunny a minute ago.
- I know.
- These two are adorable.
- They're so cute.
They're so sweet.
Thank you.
Oh, no. I need to thank you.
- For the letter.
- Oh, yeah.
I hadn't met anybody.
I thought I had to do something.
Yours was in the middle.
- That's why?
- So I posted there.
Oh.
I was lucky.
We all gathered last night, right?
- You seemed the most approachable.
- Really?
- That ambience got us nervous, didn't it?
- Yeah.
I knew we should get ourselves talking.
I said I felt comfortable in the silence.
- And you agreed with me.
- Yeah.
- You gave me that letter, right?
- Of course, I was happy and came today.
- Yeah.
Even without that letter,
I would've asked you.
What?
I would have asked you out.
- What? Oh, really? Thank you.
- Yeah.
I felt the same way yesterday.
That makes me happy. Thanks.
- What a relief.
- Yeah.
He's not afraid to speak his mind.
That's true. He does.
- About yesterday…
- Yeah?
That was the first time…
I ever asked somebody on a date.
Seriously?
You're okay with me?
Yeah.
I've never said that to anyone.
Does everyone say it?
- I guess we hardly ever say it.
- Right?
I mean,
if we had our phones,
we could just text and ask people out.
For dinner or to a café.
But to ask someone out
on a date in person?
We don't do that.
I was nervous.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you for coming.
- Did you like it?
- Yeah.
That's good to know.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
"Yeah"?
- You're fast.
- Okay.
I can't help it.
This tiny umbrella is shaped like this.
- Like this.
- I think we go this way.
I have a feeling
that we should go this way.
A feeling?
I'm not even looking at the map.
I can't read maps.
She said it was her first time
asking somebody out on a date.
She did.
That's Tohko's "first-time" tactic.
Did she use it before?
- She said she's never dated anybody.
- Oh, right.
- That might put pressure on some people.
- That's true.
She doesn't necessarily
have to say it's her first time.
- Yudai kind of gives light reactions.
- He does.
- We don't see his true feelings.
- No.
- He gives good responses.
- Yeah.
And Yudai.
Before his date…
- He wrote a letter.
- To Nanami.
- Yes, to Nanami.
- What will happen?
So, Nanami and Kensuke…
Will they come back
and check their mailboxes?
That's true.
Right?
They're on a date.
And Kensuke forgot his umbrella.
- What was that?
- I'm sorry.
But why?
- Plus, he was late.
- Yeah.
- He must have been sleeping.
- He probably was.
I can't think of any other reason.
- Comedians are like that.
- We're impulsive.
"Do you wanna go anywhere?"
"Let's go there.
That way? That way. Let's go."
Comedians are like that.
- But Kensuke told Nanami.
- Yes.
- He would've asked her out.
- He says those things clearly.
- He does.
- He's got talent for a kept man.
- That's true!
That Kensuke.
Also, Kanaka and Sho.
Right. They're good.
- In Provence.
- It's the Wish Letter.
The weather cleared up,
and they climbed to the top.
There's nothing too special,
but they look comfortable.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Comfortable together.
- And Mimi and Atsushi are in Cannes.
- Yes.
- She wanted to share the umbrella.
- Yeah.
She said that to Aru.
Aru.
- The cap and stickers.
- The must-haves.
Mimi loves that.
- She loves local stuff.
- Loves them.
She buys them all.
And today is Day Four.
So the ones
with Wish Letters for Day Five,
meaning Tohko and Yudai,
must hand their letters
or exchange them with somebody today.
- That's the rule.
- Right.
- Exchanging at this time is tough.
- You're right.
The one with this letter
needs to act quickly.
And everybody's out and about.
Oh!
- We're here.
- This, huh?
- Yay!
- Wow.
- Look.
- What?
It's the market.
Oh, this is it.
It's this!
Wow!
This is amazing.
It smells so nice.
- Can I get this paella?
- I wanna eat it too.
- Merci beaucoup.
- See you. Have a nice day.
- Have a nice day.
Have a nice day.
Hey, look. This looks delicious.
- Recommendation?
- Yes, it's very nice.
- I'll take this.
- You want one of these?
Do you want to taste the hummus?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Can I?
- Oh, that looks tasty.
- Yeah.
That's awesome.
Do you smell that?
- Nice smell.
- Yeah, nice smell.
- Mimi's in a good mood.
- Yeah.
- It's great how she enjoys every moment.
- I totally agree.
I'm hungry.
Yeah, me too.
We've been walking all day today.
But I'm not tired at all.
Please take a seat.
Thanks.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Look at that.
That's what we climbed.
- We climbed up to that corner.
- Wow.
Have you found anybody?
- Hmm.
- You met everybody last night, right?
- I did want to talk more with you.
- Oh, really?
We sat next to each other, remember?
- We chatted while we ate.
- Yeah.
I wanted to talk with you more.
- So today was a good chance.
- Oh.
I'm glad I asked.
Your manly behavior really impressed me.
Really?
I thought it was really cool
that you asked me out
in front of everybody.
It's been two years?
No, three years since I had a boyfriend.
Oh, really?
Yeah. During that time,
I went on dates and stuff,
and it almost got serious
with some people too.
But it's really hard to find a guy
that could act as manly as you.
Maybe that's true.
- Manly guys, huh?
- They're an endangered species.
He doesn't say, "Well, I can pull it off."
Sho tends to do that, doesn't he?
He doesn't take that next step.
I'll eat first.
- Let's eat.
This is good.
What was your favorite food in Nice?
The truffle risotto.
My number one.
That was insanely delicious.
I want you to try it.
Yeah. But don't you want to
try other places?
Yeah, let's go find other places.
Let's do that.
- You know what?
- Yeah?
There are people going on trips
with the Wish Letter today.
What day was yours?
Mine was eight. Day Eight.
That's late.
- The last one.
- The last one?
Yeah.
- That's nice.
- How about you?
- Mine was Day Six.
- Oh, Day Six!
- So I need to hand it tomorrow.
- Oh, right.
The travel plan that I have
is a difficult one.
Hmm?
What's it like?
It's, uh…
skiing.
Wow! Really?
That's so nice!
Do you ski?
I've never skied before.
Oh, really?
It's 2,000 meters above sea level.
- It's up on this high mountain.
- Wow.
Can you ski?
I'm from Niigata.
- That's right!
- Yeah.
I grew up in the snow.
Did you go skiing on your field trips?
Yeah. We had ski camps too.
I went skiing every year.
- I see.
- Yeah.
She's from Niigata!
Hikakin is also from Niigata.
He is, but you don't have to mention it.
- Oh, yeah. About today…
- Yeah?
Do you have any plans
after we go to the vintage shop?
No.
I want to go near the beach.
Do you know Castle Hill?
What's that?
If you don't mind,
I want to go while the sun is out.
I want a panoramic view
of the sea around Nice.
I wanna see that.
Are you cold?
A little.
You can wear mine.
- It's fine. You'll be cold.
- No. Just take it.
- You'll be cold.
- I'll be fine.
- But…
- Here.
- It might be small.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- I'm good.
Thank you. This smells nice.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Should we eat?
- Yeah.
- Let's eat.
- How do I eat this? With my hands?
- I'll use my hands.
- It's warm!
- It's warm.
So…
First of all,
I really want to thank you
for asking me out today.
Oh, no. Thank you for coming.
- But we had never even spoken before.
- No.
- Did you think, "Why?"
- I wasn't sure you'd be okay with me.
I wanted it to be you.
But you're 20, right?
You're 20.
- Yeah, 20.
- Right?
What do you think of younger girls?
I prefer girls younger than me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'm ten years older than you.
Isn't that too old for you?
- Not at all.
- Seriously?
I like older men. The older, the better.
I see.
ENTREVAUX STATION
Bonjour.
- It's tiny.
- What?!
- It's so cute though.
- It's so different from that other train.
We've come quite far.
- We've come a long way.
- Yeah.
- It's hard to believe we were by the sea.
I like it this way.
It feels more like a trip.
I had a feeling you would like this view.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I love these kinds of trips.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
We're eating sweet stuff all day.
- I love it.
- Yeah.
There's a lot of people here.
- Myeah. I thought so too.
- "Myeah"?
- Yeah. I thought so too.
- Oh. "Yeah."
You said, "Myeah."
- You wanna sit here?
- Yeah.
Yay. We found a seat.
- There we go.
- Van Gogh.
This is grea-- What?
Gogh, huh?
I'm loving this.
What will you do tomorrow?
TOHKO, 24, ACTOR
- About tomorrow…
- Yeah?
YUDAI, 24, MODEL AND ACTOR
You know I have
the Wish Letter for Day Five, right?
It's only Day Five.
So I'm thinking of going
with someone I don't know much
or haven't talked to yet.
I got to know you today.
So for tomorrow,
I'm thinking of
handing my letter to Nanami today.
I see.
Did you promise to meet her?
Well…
- I went to Margaux this morning.
- Okay.
- I left her a letter.
- Right.
But I don't know if I'll get to meet her.
So I'm kind of thinking
about what I should do.
I see.
And you? How will you spend Day Five?
I would've asked you out
if we didn't have the same day.
Really?
Maybe this is some kind of fate.
He said, "This is fate."
His responses are interesting. He's quick.
- He's quick-witted.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Merci.
- Merci. Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- It's nice.
- Yeah!
Yes!
- I got this.
- It's nice.
Yeah. That's cute.
- It suits you.
- Let's see.
Huh?
It looks fantastic.
- We can't really see us.
- No, not really.
- Should we go to the beach?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Let's go while the sun is out.
- Let's go.
- That way?
- Yeah.
Wow.
Do we climb up?
Nice.
A panoramic view.
It's 21 meters high.
- There are 109 steps.
- Okay.
Whoa.
Look at that.
- Oh?
- This is amazing.
We're climbing up.
Oh! I see the light.
Wait. Should we see this together?
- Ready? Now!
Wow! Huh? Oh, wow!
What? We have a 360-degree view!
- Wow!
It's a view straight out of a movie.
- This is something we can't see in Nice.
- Yeah.
- A 360-degree view.
- Wow.
This is really spectacular.
- It's like a movie.
- This might be the best place in Cannes.
Nice.
Oh, wow.
This is the best.
I don't wanna go back.
- Me neither.
- It makes you feel that way.
- I've never been on a proper date.
- Right.
- I have so many things I want to do.
- Like what?
- A date like this?
- Today's date is great too.
- Like walking along the beach.
- Yeah.
I've never been to a café with a boy.
So you accomplished that today.
- Yeah.
- What else?
- I like sports.
- Oh! Okay.
I want to play sports together.
I guess it's just everything.
Can I suggest something?
I want to propose something.
- Paragliding.
- Yeah.
We can do that
at the Port of Nice or somewhere.
It's around there.
We can't go together on Day Five
because we have the same date.
So it's my turn now.
- How about we go paragliding?
- Yeah.
I'm not sure if it's really a date.
- But how's that?
- I'd love to.
Okay?
- When should we go?
- Yeah, when?
- Day Six?
- Are you okay with that?
Yeah.
So does Yudai
really just want to talk with Nanami?
Yudai seems like the capable type.
- I have the same impression.
- Yeah.
Maybe I'll try exchanging
my letter with someone.
Do you have someone in mind?
Hmm.
Maho?
I saw Maho at Margaux this morning.
Where did she say she was going?
There's a vintage shop around here.
She said the shop was closed
and she couldn't look inside.
- She might be around here.
- Okay.
- Or Old Nice.
- Right.
She might be there.
- We could walk around and look for her.
- Yeah.
I'll do that.
- Wow.
- We're here.
This is just totally unbelievable.
- Isn't this awesome?
- This is different again.
Oh, wow. This is great.
I've only seen a view
like this in picture books.
No kidding.
Just wow.
- Wow.
- This is beautiful.
- The air tastes so good.
- Yeah.
Down there would have been
even more beautiful if it weren't raining.
That's true. What a pity.
- But it's beautiful.
- Yeah.
- This was the plan for this trip.
- Wow!
Where are we now?
Here.
- Wow.
- Verdon River is our final destination.
Can I see the back side?
"A train journey on the railways
of Provence" sounds so nice.
Yeah.
- You wouldn't normally do this.
- You wouldn't.
That's what made it so nice.
Do you want to go eat
truffle risotto tomorrow?
Sure. What time do you wanna go?
- Let's meet at nine at Maison Margaux.
- Okay.
- We could walk around.
- Yeah.
- We'll look at vintage shops.
- Then, we'll eat truffles.
- Let's do that.
- Something like that.
That sounds fun.
- Hmm.
- It's tomorrow.
- Two days in a row.
- They made plans.
Kanaka liked the fact that
Sho handed his Wish Letter
to her in front of everybody.
- She appreciated that.
- She said that was manly.
Sho has a tendency
of almost conveying his feelings
if he took one step forward,
but he pulls back at the last moment.
He was like that with Mimi.
Kanaka was very open with him.
- She talked about the people she dated.
- That's right.
She even mentioned that some people
she dated recently weren't as manly.
But Sho was like, "Oh, yeah."
He's like, "I'm different."
- But he doesn't exactly say it.
- No.
But he instantly answered,
"Truffle risotto."
He answered that immediately.
- So he's capable of answering promptly.
- I see.
It's not like he's slow-witted.
He's choosing his answers.
Maybe he's observing the situation.
- I kind of get that feeling.
- Yeah, that's true.
Mimi and Atsushi.
When Atsushi asked
if she was okay with inviting him
when they had never spoken,
Mimi said, "I wanted it to be you."
She can become a textbook.
- Of some sort, yeah.
- Seriously.
- Nanami and Kensuke.
- Yeah.
They're sweet.
Yes, they're adorable.
You keep talking to them as we watch.
- I'm like, "You bought a bag?"
- Yeah.
- Kensuke is cute.
It's the way she looks at Kensuke.
But it's a bit complicated.
Kensuke and Nanami seem to get along.
And the plan on Kensuke's
Wish Letter on Day Six
was to go skiing.
He told Nanami about it,
and she said, "I can ski."
So they might go together. But!
Yudai wants to meet Nanami.
But Nanami doesn't know that.
She hasn't seen his letter.
Tohko asked Yudai
what he was going to do on that bench.
She would've asked him out
if they didn't have the same day.
When she said that,
Yudai immediately said,
"Maybe this is some kind of fate."
He did.
Compared to Aru, Atsushi, and Sho,
Yudai responds spontaneously.
It's not a favorable situation for him.
Tohko told him she wanted to go with him.
But he said it was fate.
It sounds kind of harsh.
- But he says it so lightheartedly.
- Which is it?
He proposed an alternative date
because they can't go on Day Five.
He quickly suggested that.
- He would do well as a salesman.
- Absolutely.
He would be amazing.
Maybe it's because of all the sugar.
- From the sweets?
- The sugar.
Maybe it's the genius type of sugar.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- It's not enough for him.
- Maybe.
He needs to maintain that speed.
It's this vintage shop here.
Is she here?
- Are there any signs of her?
- I don't know.
There are no signs of her.
Oh?
I might find her at Margaux.
Oh, right.
That's a possibility.
Should we go to Margaux?
The sun is starting to set.
Isn't it just nice?
Wow.
I got water on me. It's salty.
- It's salty?
- Yeah.
Oh, you're right. I do feel it.
So it's that one.
I don't know how to get there.
- Aren't those stairs amazing?
- Do we climb that?
- Do we?
- Wow!
Hey, look at that.
Is it closed?
Really?
Should we go look?
- Hmm?
- Oh?
- Oh.
- What is this?
I can't read it.
We can't read this.
What's this?
- Right now…
- Until six?
- I see.
- Let's go.
- Too bad.
- We'll come some other time.
- Yeah.
- Wow!
- Which seat?
- Which one?
- Take this one.
Thank you.
Wow. Oh, gosh.
This is amazing.
We get to eat
with the ocean right in front of us?
- Wow.
- This is great.
- Wait.
- Wow.
How is this as a sea-lover?
- The best?
- The best.
Are you cold?
It's cold. A little.
I'm warm, so you can use this.
Thanks. Aren't you cold?
- I'm not cold.
- You're okay?
- I was really looking forward to this.
- Is that so?
Yeah, since I first read it.
- On your Wish Letter?
- Yeah.
- Right.
- I'm glad I came here with you.
This is the best.
What type of girls do you like?
You mean by looks?
Anything.
Appearance-wise, I like cute girls.
- I see.
- Yeah.
And you? You kind of told me earlier.
You prefer older guys, right?
Also…
- I like guys with beards.
- Oh.
Then it's not me.
Well, beards aren't everything.
- Yay!
- It's not you.
- It's not?
- It's Aru.
- Oh, Aru.
What makes you feel like,
"Oh, I'm so in love with this person"?
At times like these,
we don't have digital devices, right?
Imagine when night comes.
- After my bath and before I go to bed.
- I see.
I would usually spend that time
on my phone and stuff.
I don't have that time now.
So I look back on the things
that happened that day.
If I miss that person during that time,
I'd think I'm probably in love.
I hope you miss me tonight then.
Yeah.
But I have a feeling I will.
To me, you're…
How do I put it?
I like you the best
of all the girls I've met.
Wow.
I kind of get what you're like.
- You do?
- I do.
Kind of. By spending time together.
You like the sea.
I love the sea. It's in my name.
The kanji characters
for Mimi mean "beautiful sea."
Aru is always at Place Masséna.
He's always waiting.
Aru.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hey there.
- Thanks.
- Did you wait?
- No. I just arrived.
- Oh? Okay.
Where should we go?
I have a place in mind, so let's go there.
- This way. We'll take the tram.
- Okay.
Is this your first time at Place Masséna?
It's not.
- No, right?
- My third time.
- Let's see if anybody's here.
- Yeah.
Please. I hope someone's here.
Will they switch with me though?
Nobody's here.
I guess it's not that easy.
You're right.
What now?
Right.
You need to decide today.
Even if I ask someone
to exchange letters with me now,
it's this late already.
Yeah?
It would just inconvenience them.
I guess you're right.
Maybe I'll ask Kensuke.
- I did want to talk with him more.
- Yeah.
I'll go look for him,
or I'll wait for him at the hotel.
Day Five is the toughest one.
I'm pretty sure
me asking you out on Day Four
made things complicated.
- Everything.
- Is that so?
But I wanted to see you today
if I don't get to see you on Day Five.
Oh, yeah?
"Oh, yeah"?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Oh, right.
What?
We need to decide
what time to meet on Day Six.
- Oh, you're right.
- Yeah.
Absolutely.
So, Day Six.
- Do you wanna ride the train?
- Yeah!
Okay.
Number 15 on page seven.
- We'll meet at this station at 12:00 p.m.
- Okay.
How about here?
Oh, thank you.
Okay.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
I want to live here.
Right now, I live in a 70-year-old house.
- I have two housemates.
- Really?
- My rent is 10,000 yen.
- What?!
- All the floorboards are creaky.
- Right.
I'm usually in this small, wooden house,
but everything's wide open now.
It's stunning.
I'm happy to be here
with such a wonderful lady.
Not at all.
- Thank you.
I'm glad I wrote you… that letter.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- It's fine.
Thank you.
- So cute.
- Yeah.
- Aw, Nanami.
- Nanami.
Looking at this sea
makes me feel kind of sad.
- It's coming to an end.
- Yeah.
- The sun has set.
I'd like to…
Let's go on a date again.
Yeah. I'd like to…
ask you out again.
Please do.
I want to drink coffee.
- I like coffee.
- Okay.
Me too.
- Yeah.
- I have it every day.
Do you like espresso?
I've always wanted to try espresso.
Can I ask you out on a date
for your first-ever espresso?
- Of course.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Okay.
That's a promise.
Yeah.
I'll write it down.
I'll drink my first-ever espresso
with Atsushi.
Okay.
That's Aru's pen!
That pen!
- Don't use Aru's pen!
- That's not your prince.
But then you'll see my whole list.
I won't look.
- You won't look?
- No.
You can look.
I'll excuse myself to the restroom.
- Okay?
- Yeah. Go ahead.
Take your time.
TO-DO LIST
DRINK ESPRESSO
FOR THE FIRST TIME WITH ATSUSHI
Merci beaucoup.
- Sorry for the wait.
- You're back.
- Are you cold?
- I was gazing at the sea.
- I was daydreaming.
- I have something for you.
Hmm?
- Like a present.
- A present?
- It's this. The one I got earlier.
- Oh!
I wrote a message on the back.
- Read it later.
- Later?
Read it later.
- Yay.
- Don't read it yet.
- Thank you.
- Here.
- I don't wanna go back.
- Me neither.
- I mean, this view is amazing.
- Right?
- Are you cold?
- Yeah.
We'll hold hands.
Man, today was the best.
Whee!
I had so much fun.
Your hand is warm.
Is it?
Right.
- All right. They held hands.
- I see.
Things might get complicated.
Atsushi kept lending his coat.
He was constantly lending her his coat.
- I want him to buy her clothes.
- He should do that.
Mimi asked him his type,
and he said he liked cute girls.
I thought Mimi would say something
that hints at Atsushi,
but she said her type is guys with beards.
Atsushi thought Mimi chose him over Aru.
- So why?
- Maybe she was trying to get him fired up.
Tohko and Yudai went to look for Maho.
Tohko wanted to exchange
her Wish Letter with Maho.
- They couldn't find her.
- No.
Tohko wanted to see him today
if she won't see him on Day Five.
Yeah.
When she said that,
Yudai seemed to hesitate.
- Yeah.
- Even that Yudai.
Right. He couldn't respond on the spot.
Well, they did have
that conversation already.
They did make plans already.
Yeah, they did.
He did settle the discussion once.
Yudai is kind and is very thoughtful.
He's been helping Tohko
with the things that she wants to do
and listening to her wishes.
Yeah.
- He helped her look for Maho.
- That was very kind of him.
This is something
Yudai needs to report to Kensuke.
To Kensuke, his bestie.
Nanami and Kensuke.
The park closed at 6:00 p.m.
The park was closed,
but they sat on a bench.
"I'm happy I'm with
such a wonderful lady."
Kensuke shyly said that.
And Nanami said,
"I'm glad I wrote you that letter."
She kind of hesitated when she said that.
I just loved the way she paused.
I'm glad I wrote you… that letter.
I absolutely love that.
They're so sweet.
It makes me feel like
we're watching a young couple.
Yes, it does.
- Maho and Aru went for dinner.
- Yes.
He's Mr. Place Masséna.
The Wizard of Place Masséna.
The people of Nice
might give him that name soon.
"He's here. He's here again."
"He's at Masséna again."
That guy's always at Masséna too.
No, it's someone from the shops nearby.
It's here.
- Here?
- Yeah.
- Hotel Nice.
- That's nice.
- What? Did you just say "nice"?
- Let's try that again.
- Hotel Nice.
It's beautiful.
I'll go get him.
Thanks.
The streetlights are lit up.
- It's beautiful.
NANAMI, 25, ACTOR
KENSUKE, 24, COMEDIAN
- How about here?
- Here?
Looks nice.
- Let's eat here then.
- Yeah.
They're having dinner?
- That'll take time.
- Tohko won't see him.
Oh, no.
He wasn't there.
What should we do?
Then I'll wait for him here.
It's almost eight. Are you okay?
I'm fine with the time.
Let me give you
my coat.
- It's fine!
- Take it!
It'll get cold.
- It's fine.
- I can't.
It's all right. Just take it.
- Okay?
- Thanks.
It's fine. I better get going.
Thanks for today.
- You know what?
- What?
I'm kind of curious about
what Japanese food in Nice tastes like.
I agree.
I sometimes see ramen places
and sushi restaurants.
- Do you like ramen?
- I love ramen.
We need to go then.
Let's do that. I really wanted to go.
But when?
Yeah, when?
DAY FIVE: A SMALL BIKE TRIP
How was yesterday? You met everybody.
I mean, it was fun. Wasn't it?
- I don't really remember.
- You're kidding.
MAHO, 30, MODEL
You didn't seem that way at all.
- I was nervous and flustered.
- Really?
You gave me that letter
right after that dinner.
Yeah.
What kind of impression did I give you?
I thought maybe we could talk easily
since we're the same age.
- You're the easiest to talk to.
- Right?
Yeah, that was why
I asked you out for dinner.
So it's just Yudai
that you went on a date with?
Yeah.
We met at a church.
- Isn't that amazing?
- Wow.
I didn't think I'd meet
anybody in a church.
- Shocking, right?
- Did you feel a sense of fate?
- Did you?
- Hmm.
Yeah, that's true.
- I thought, "This must be fate."
- You did?
What kind of dance do you do?
What genre is it?
Well, I sort of do everything.
From ballet to jazz to hip-hop.
- I do contemporary dances as well.
- Okay.
When I do my own workshops, it's hip-hop.
Wow. When did you start?
It's been over 20 years.
- That's long.
- Since I was in elementary school.
Wow. Dancing, huh?
I can do traditional Japanese dancing.
- What?
- Do you know it?
- Like in Kyoto, right?
- Yeah, the slow dance that maiko do.
But I can't do such intense dances.
- You live in Paris, right?
- Yeah, in Paris.
What made you go there?
- I studied nutrition in college.
- Okay.
- I'm actually a qualified nutritionist.
- You are?
France is famous for its food.
So I've always wanted to go to France.
I also love art and fashion,
so I thought, "I should go,"
and that's why I'm here.
- Fantastic.
- Yeah.
I think my mindset and way of thinking
when taking those kinds of actions
are very similar to yours.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We said, "Let's go together."
- But it's a bit awkward.
- It is.
So if I do find a letter,
I won't tell you
what's written there.
- You won't tell me?
- If I find a letter.
Oh, right! Yes.
We'll go in one by one.
One by one.
And then…
- We won't say anything.
- Okay.
I'll say, "You go first."
- And we pass each other.
- Right.
What are you doing, Kensuke?
Whoa! What?
- It's you, huh?
- What?
- What are you doing?
- You were here?
- Alone?
- I'm here. Alone.
- I came to check my mailbox.
- Oh, yeah?
- See you.
- I'll see you.
Why didn't Kensuke notice him?
He came in this way.
- What's wrong with his field of vision?
- How could that be?
This is really cute.
- Thanks for waiting.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- My turn.
- I'll go inside.
- Yudai was there.
- Yudai? Oh.
- Yeah.
Hello.
- Hello.
- I heard you were here.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, thank you so much.
- "Thank you so much"?
- For coming.
Huh?
- Oh?
- Oh.
- Wait a minute.
Oh? Okay.
Please take a look.
Huh? Okay.
Oh!
Wait.
I'll be waiting for you
at 8:00 p.m. today at Maison Margaux.
I'm so glad you came.
Oh, wow!
- I'm so relieved.
- What?
- Wait. Let me put this inside.
- I'm so relieved.
I'm so surprised.
I just saw the letter.
I'm glad. It was worth the wait.
Oh, no.
Wait, I need to give you this.
Give me a second.
Let's see…
- It's for tomorrow.
- Yes.
- Will you join me?
Thank you.
- I'm so relieved.
- Me too.
Yeah.
- I'm glad I came.
- Yeah.
- See you tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- Good night.
I'm exhausted.
- Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow, yeah.
Are you free at night?
Actually,
just now
I got a ticket.
I don't know what time it will end.
What should we do then?
Tomorrow night, if you can make it.
- Will you come here?
- Okay.
I will.
- I'll be here all night.
- Okay.
I don't know what time it'll be.
But I'll come here.
- Thank you.
- Not at all.
If you're early…
Oh, but you would be tired.
It's okay.
I have confidence in my stamina.
- If it's really early, let's go for ramen.
- Let's do that.
- Have fun.
- I will. Thanks.
Kensuke.
- Huh?
- I was waiting for you.
- For me?
- Yeah.
- Waiting for me?
What?
So, you see…
- My Wish Letter is for Day Five.
- Okay.
Will you join me?
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Let's have fun tomorrow.
- Yes, definitely.
- You waited in this cold?
- It's nothing.
I totally thought
you would hand yours to Yudai.
Yudai also had Day Five.
- Really?
- I can't give it to him.
But I want to get to know you better too.
Thank you. Of course.
I'll be there.
Oh, one more thing.
This is Yudai's.
- Oh?
- Can you give it back to him?
Sure.
SHO, 22, UNIVERSITY STUDENT AND MODEL
Dear Mimi,
- It's Mimi!
- Oh, man.
- So it's Mimi after all?
He's crazy about her.
So it's Mimi!
Is he going to wrap up his date
with Kanaka early to meet Mimi?
We don't know. What will he write?
They were the first to meet.
Maybe the sense of fate is really strong.
- Just like Maho said.
- Right.
With this system, the memory
of first meeting somebody by chance
becomes stronger
the more you talk to other people.
- Maybe.
- That might be true.
- Like meeting at the beach or the church.
- Yeah.
Nanami also sent her letter to Kensuke
because his mailbox was in the middle.
And when she met him,
she was glad she had given him the letter.
- The first encounter really is important.
- True.
- That was unprecedented.
- Yeah?
Kensuke missed Yudai.
Unbelievable. How?
He came in facing this way.
- A predator's field of view.
- How could it be?
- He zeroes in on his prey.
- It's the opposite of zebras.
- It's like this. Just straight ahead.
- It's amazing.
Did they both wait about two hours?
- Yeah, they waited.
- They did.
- The hotel entrance is a hot spot.
- Yeah.
- A hot spot.
- It's the best place to wait for people.
It's better than Margaux.
It's open 24 hours,
and they're more likely to meet.
You know what?
If I were with them,
I'd want to join Kensuke, Yudai,
Tohko, and Nanami.
I want to hang out with the five of us.
Don't do that.
Don't interrupt them.
I want to shuffle the pairs
with some random reason.
But I wonder how things will turn out.
- Hey.
- Whoa.
Hi.
- Hey.
Take a seat.
ARU, 30, DANCER AND CHOREOGRAPHER
- It's cold.
- It's cold?
How was it?
- Well, it was super fun.
- You enjoyed it?
Yeah, I bet.
So, how's it going?
- How's it going?
- Yeah.
Well, to be honest,
it was really good.
But I mean, it would be, right?
Man, this is troublesome.
- It was when I first met her.
- Yeah.
She told me the ages
of the people she had dated.
I knew she liked older guys.
So naturally,
I didn't want you to go for her.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I'll say this because it's you, Aru.
She likes older men.
And men with beards.
She said that.
I don't have a beard.
I'll share that information with you.
I don't think there's any need
for me to hide that.
So that's that.
- Atsushi is a fair man.
- Yeah. He's an athlete.
Good sportsmanship.
And Aru seems so happy again.
MIMI, 20, PART-TIME WORKER
Dear Mimi,
Thank you for a wonderful trip today.
It was the best day.
I want to get to know you better
in the next six days.
Let's go drink espresso.
From Atsushi
Dear Mimi,
I'll be waiting for you at 6:00 p.m.
tomorrow (Day Five) at Maison Margaux.
Let's go for dinner!
From Sho
Subtitle translation by: Remi Miura