MIND
Have you ever been to Fukuoka?
No, I haven't.
There are many good hot-springs...
Also, as I am a barista,
I usually go to coffee places
when I travel.
I'm not very good at taking pictures
but...
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, it is.
I went to Hokkaido this time,
so I want to go Osaka next time.
Have you ever been to Osaka?
Osaka... I haven't been there yet.
I actually didn't
look around Japan properly,
because I just went for
a school field trip when I was young.
Then, where do you usually travel?
Mostly domestic.
Oh, yes.
There are many beautiful places
in Korea, too.
There are so many places
I haven't been yet.
Where is the most memorable place
for you?
Have you ever been to the Sky Park?
There is this huge field
of tall wildgrass,
and it is very pretty during the sunset.
Then we can go there next time we meet.
No. Nothing's wrong.
I didn't know you called. I'm sorry.
Okay. I'll send it right away.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Is it too salty?
No, It's fine.
I think it is.
Should I put more rice in it?
What's wrong?
Is something not going well?
Let me see.
He's nice. He has a good vibe.
Hasn't he?
Maybe just for me.
But I think, he looks fine.
Tae-Gyu.
What.
What do you get out of holding on
like that?
You need to take a break.
How was the person you met today?
He seemed nice and good-looking.
Yeah, He was fine.
I guess he has a lot of money
and he travels often.
Why did you just come?
What do you mean?
You said he was fine.
There's no need to rush.
You should.
You haven't had a sex in a while.
Hey.
What?
I'm not an animal.
Stop.
Good work, everyone.
What are you doing?
Pardon?
What are you doing now?
Don't make a splash.
How many more opportunities
do I have to give you?
I'm sorry.
Take your work more seriously,
or don't start at all.
Did you ever go through
your model profiles?
Are you even going to finish it?
I haven't made up my mind.
Then why don't you seek for a compromise?
Or look through the models
you've worked with before.
Thanks for everything today.
Come to my office before you leave.
Yes. sir.
It's been a while
since you guys broke up.
You should get over it by now
and focus on your work.
I mean it wasn't yesterday.
Well...
It's not like I'm an expert of love.
But pictures don't lie.
Like today.
If your mind is authentic,
it's in the picture.
You're right.
Or are you something like him?
What was his name?
You know the person
who's a professor in Harry Potter.
You know, the one with the bobbed hair
and wearing a tatters thing.
Severus Snape.　-Oh yes, that's him.
He didn't stop loving Harry Potter's mom
until he died.
Are you like him?
A love that will stay with you
until you die?
No way.
Don't you see each other quickly
and get old easily on your age?
I don't know.
What a pity.
You don't get anything else
until you empty it.
Excuse me.
Hey, baby.
No. I just finished.
Then, what do you usually do
when you are not working?
You know.
I don't have many gay friends.
I just go out drinking alone.
Why? Haven't you try online dating?
I don't mean to say I haven't, but...
Once I tried it before.
But after a few moments,
it didn't suit me well.
Were you surprised that
I talked to you at the bar?
You know.
People don't usually come to such place
like that by themselves.
I was...
wondering if you felt the same way
like I did.
It's very good here.
I've never known such place like this
in Seoul.
Then, do you come here often
to take pictures?
Yes. And sometimes I come here
to get some fresh air.
Is it a special place for you?
Special...
Maybe with your ex-boyfriend I guess.
No, It's not.
What is?
No, it really isn't.
It kind of hurts me
to see who is on your mind.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
I don't think it's their first time,
for a couple over there to be here
either.
Hello?
It's been a while.
Oh, did I call you? I'm sorry.
Me?
I'm doing great.
Oh, you mean the ad?
The exhibition is getting closer,
so I'm looking for someone to work with.
Oh really? Thanks.
I'm glad to hear from you anyway.
Hello.
Yes. I just woke up.
Why didn't you tell me
that you're leaving?
On the table?
Okay.
Bye.
According to your profile,
it looked like
you are working on your pictures
in black and white.
Yes. Recently.
Is there a reason?
You loved working in colors.
I don't remember when,
but I suddenly feel like
the colors are a bit too heavy for me.
Suddenly?
Something simple...
That's what I like these days.
Well,
how would you like me to interpret it?
Well.
Just be the way you are.
Ah.
Can I ask you a favor?
Why not?
It's not a big thing.
Can I bring someone
that I know who is a makeup artist?
If you don't mind.
We'd appreciate it if you do that.
Are you seeing someone?
I guess you are.
Well...
Hyun-woo.
Do your best.
The lights will be turned off.
We need to go get some make-up fixed.
Hyun-woo.