♪Getting used to soft light♪
♪And spending the night alone♪
♪When my inner anxiety fades away♪
♪It's easy to curl up my lips♪
♪Wind above the roof confuses my mind♪
♪Counting the hours under the stars♪
♪When my inner expectation
drifts out of sight♪
♪I stand up proudly to exhaustion♪
♪I'm expecting the wind. And future♪
♪When it's gone, it's forever gone♪
♪Someone's back while someone's leaving♪
♪It's always wonderful, dream or reality♪
=Love at Second Sight=
=Episode 22=
Don't waste more money on me.
Mom, what are you talking about?
I know.
I just
can't bear to leave you.
What are you talking about, Mom?
You are fine.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't cry.
It's fine.
Mom.
When you get well,
let's go home and make dumplings,
OK?
OK.
Let's make the filling
with shrimp, pork, and chives.
Mom.
I'm fine.
How I wish
you were my own daughter.
Mom, what are you talking about?
Nan, listen to me.
I
can't be with you anymore.
I can't protect you anymore.
Don't blame me.
That year
when I saw you
smiling so sweetly at me
in the orphanage,
I felt that
you were just my daughter.
I'm so selfish
that I didn't tell you this.
Mom.
I'm always your daughter.
Nan, let me look at you more.
Now, I can't be with you anymore,
I can't protect you anymore, either.
Go find them.
Don't cry.
Mom.
Nan, don't cry.
Nan, do you blame me?
No.
Then I'm relieved.
Mom.
Doctor!
Su Nan,
what are you doing sitting here
in the middle of the night?
Is it because of Gu Yibei?
Jia.
Let me ask you a question.
If you love someone very much,
but he chooses to hurt you,
will you forgive him?
Definitely not.
Me neither.
Yibei.
Do I still have a chance?
In the world of relationships,
I'm willing to play fairly.
Things won't work out between us.
Everything I've ever done is for you.
I am
also the one
who has always been by your side
and devoted myself to you unconditionally.
Because I've met someone before,
I've had to make do
with all the people
who showed up later since then.
But
I don't want to make do.
Nan.
Save me.
Nan!
Su Nan.
Let's break up.
It's alright.
It's alright. It's alright.
It's just a nightmare.
It's alright.
Yaru?
Why are you here?
I'm here to get a file.
Wait for my good news.
Su Nan.
Let's hang out.
Isn't it just a break-up?
You've been like this for days.
Su Nan.
There, there.
Even if you don't have Gu Yibei,
you still have me.
♪Confused and puzzled♪
♪I got a feeling♪
♪Expectant but disappointed♪
♪I forgot to thank you♪
♪Something went off my mind♪
♪Into a carriage♪
♪And grew during the journey♪
♪We kept the promise♪
♪Like romantic stories♪
♪We missed what we had♪
♪Like changes of the moon♪
♪With you in my world♪
♪Coldness disappeared♪
♪Wind stopped by the window♪
♪Telling me to love this world♪
♪Reminding me to love you more♪
♪Keep this feeling in mind♪
♪And in the future♪
♪Feel it harder♪
(The right of communication through network
exclusively belongs to Tencent.)