(Rui Takamiya) Someone has been following me lately.
⟨Underground idol targeted⟩
⟨Mystery of serial murder cases⟩
⟨Unidentified Garden⟩
(Reiko Kawato) I've heard a lot of things.
⟨Old friends and accomplices...⟩
(Izumi) Let's go get it. The top of the idol.
(Thelma) I swear by Yakiniku.
♪～
(Louis) 《That night, after Thelma said the Yakiniku oath →
Baby★Starlight has changed》
《But I can barely keep up...》
(Doi) Why don't you take a photo of me?
(Mochizuki) No, no...I'm... >> No, no, I'm always indebted to you, so please come by.
(Louis) Huh?
(Staff) Yes, please line up, I'll take a photo.→
Yes, cheese. (Shutter sound)
♪～
(Louis) You can throw it away.
>> I wonder how long it has been since I took a photo with Louis.
(Louis) Why are you here? You should have told me not to come.
>> I didn't really come to see the live performance.
I was outside for a long time →
Kubo might show up.
(Louis) As expected, you won't be coming here anymore.
>> It's just in case.
It's too late after something happens.
(Junya Kawato) Sorry, I'm late.
>> Kawato-san? why?
Please. (Kawato) Yes.
Actually, I have a suggestion for you all.
In place of Haura→
I would like you to produce Babysta.
To make your name known to the world →
I want to support you.
Was it a nuisance?
>>Ah, no...it's such a nuisance...
(Thelma) That can't be true! hey? (Louis) Yeah.
(Kawato) Good.
>> But why us?
(Kawato) What made me want to produce you guys →
Is it that prank show?
I want to convey the charm of these three people to as many people as possible.
>> It seems that Mr. Kawato was the one who recommended him for the program.
(Thelma) That's what I did...
(Kawato) If you're going to do something, give it your all. You'll never regret it.
So I want you to come with me.
(Thelma Izumi) Thank you!
(Kawato) Okay! Well, let's get started →
I'd like to hold a 6th anniversary live show next month.
The location is Grand Cat.
Building on the success of this live show →
Let's continue to aim higher.
♪～
(Thelma) It's completely flowing.
>> I might be able to go higher...
(Louis) This chance... I'll definitely take advantage of it.
>> Yeah. (Thelma) Yeah.
♪～
(Louis) 《If Kawato-san is here, we can definitely make it happen...》
recall
Don't you want to play?
What are you listening to? (Louis) Give it back.
Give it back! >> It's dirty. What's this guy? Let's go.
(Kawato) Yes.
Are you okay? Isn't it broken?
(Louis) It's already broken.
(Kawato) You're always here.
(Kawato) Hey, aren't you hungry?
(Louis' voice) 《What attracted me was →
It wasn’t just that kindness.→
Same as me in his eyes →
It was because I felt lonely...→
I don't have a place to live...》 (Kawato) I'm home.
(Louis' voice) 《He rented me a room》
Welcome back.
(Louis) Ah...
(Kawato) I thought it would suit you.
(Louis) Thank you...
(Louis' voice) 《But a year has passed since we met...》
♪～
(Louis' voice) 《It seems I was wrong about the loneliness I saw in his eyes.》
(Louis' voice) 《We can't be together anymore.→
When I tried to withdraw myself...
(Kawato) Louis...are you interested in idols?
(Louis) Huh? (Kawato) In Osaka, my university junior →
I'm trying to form an idol group.
Would you like to audition?
(Louis' voice) 《Getting rid of trouble...That's what I felt...→
but…"
♪～
(Kawato) Good luck then.
(Louis) Thank you for everything.
(Kawato) Welcome.
(Louis) Take care of your wife and baby...
Well then.
♪～
Now
(Kawato) But things have changed, Louis.
(Louis) I've been here for six years now.
(Kawato) That's not true.
We met at a reception the other day and talked about it later.
It's like a different person.
The light behind my eyes became stronger.
It's the face of a determined person.
(Kawato) Did something happen?
(Louis) Maybe it was because I was desperate...
Mr. Haura is gone →
We had to do something ourselves.
But most of all...I think it's all thanks to Thelma and Izumi.
(Kawato) I feel so jealous.
♪～
(Louis) You can trust me, right? (Kawato) Huh?
(Louis) He said he would produce us. (Kawato) Of course.
Maybe it's because it's Louis' group →
First of all, I like people who are working hard.
Exposed to numerous hardships and licking the bittern →
I feel like I'm going to be crushed by the reality of not being rewarded...→
I still love people who are trying their best.
(Kawato) That's why I want to support Babysta.
I'm going to do everything I can.
(Sound of door opening) (Sakamoto) What do you think? →
Do you have a garden? Did you understand something?
(Mochizuki) No, it's on the internet→
No matter how much I search, I can't find a store like that →
It looks like this from my business card...
(Sakamoto) Second victim →
It was also found at Fumi Yoshinogawa's home.
Synthetic drugs→
It's the same one found in Yuki Yamano's home.
Moreover, the autopsy results of the first victim Yuina Nagata →
There appeared to be evidence of drug use.
Is there something... related?
I'm talking about a special synthetic drug that doesn't come around very often.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
In any case, the first thing to do is to catch the escaped Kubo.
yes.
(Sakamoto) Kubo is the culprit in the serial murder case →
I want to make it clear.
📱I'm practicing.
📱16 days until the 6th anniversary live (Louis)! →
Babyista I'll do my best today too!
📱(3 people) Yay!
(Louis) Please. >> Yes.
But Kawato-san is right →
The number of followers is increasing day by day.
(Thelma) With the influencer introduced by Mr. Kawato →
Thanks to the collaboration.
>> Looks like they're going to invite a popular driver this time. (Thelma) Really?
>> That's amazing, Mr. Kawato.
📱…16 days left! (Louis) Babysta I'll do my best today too!
(Haida) What is it?
(Mochizuki) Do you know about this club?
i don't know.
Um... why at home?
I'm going around trying to find out what stores I think are in the same industry.
Have you heard any rumors?
no….
So, does this drug look familiar?
No. (Sound of door opening)
Are you someone who works here?
(Michiru) No, that's not true.
Can I have a moment? >> Eh...｡
Don't know about this club?
No...I don't know.
…is that so.
I'm sorry. Is that enough?
excuse me.
Thank you.
Sorry, do you really not know?
I don't care how trivial the information is...
I'm sorry. I don't have anything.
Where do you work now? >> Huh? →
Well...just a normal part-time job.
is that so….
By the way, does this look familiar?
yeah? I feel like I've seen it somewhere...
Ah, the office...?
Oh no, I was wrong. It was a misunderstanding.
What is an office? >> I used to be an idol.
But it's nothing. Don't worry about it.
(Mochizuki) If you need anything...→
Please contact us here.
(Michiru) Yaho!
(Thelma) Michiru! (Louis) What did you come for?
>> What about Mr. Kawato? You became a producer, right? Please introduce me.
(Louis) Come out. I told you not to show your face.
>> Is it okay? Treat me like that →
I made a friend as a detective.
A cool guy named Mochizuki-san.→
Do you know? Mr. Mochizuki.
(Louis) Why did that person choose you...?
>> Hehe, now? →
But~ I was asked about that medicine.→
Mr. Haura's medicine was in the office.
What should we do!? I was looking into Haura-san.
What? It's okay, I haven't said anything yet.
(Louis) Michiru You haven't forgotten, have you?
You're also an accomplice.
But I only carried it a little...
(Louis) How are you going to prove that? >> Huh...?
(Louis) If you testify that the four of us did it →
What will happen?
>> What are you talking about?
No matter how much you say it behind your back, you'll know it's a lie right away.
(Louis) I don't know about that...
What does it mean that we will be arrested?
Because that's what it is.
If you understand, come out.
>> Why is Mochizuki-san at Michiru's place?
(Thelma) Are you suspicious of me?
♪～
(Mochizuki) Yeah. (Louis) It's okay now.
So it's just in case.
(Louis) It's annoying.
picture….
(Louis) I told you, don't get involved with me anymore.
Well then.
>> Hey.
That person named Kawato... can you trust him?
(Louis) Why?
>> No... somehow...
(Louis) It has nothing to do with you.
《I don't know where the rags will come out.→
I can't let Naoya get any closer than this.
📱See you~｡ 📱Thank you.
(knock)
(Thelma) Who will do it?
(Yazaki) Sorry for the sudden change.My name is Yazaki and I am a lawyer.
(Yazaki) I had a talk with Rui Takamiya.
Could you please give me just a little bit of your time?
Hello Louis.
(Reiko) Thelma and Izumi...
Nice to meet you. I'm Reiko Kawato, Kawato's wife.
♪～
(Yazaki) Let's do this right away.
(Yazaki) Louis and Kawato, right?
What is this...
(Thelma) Louis...what do you mean?
(Louis) Ah, this is...
Mr. Louis, you are having an affair with Mr. Kawato.
(Louis) Eh, no!
>> 7 years ago, in the apartment that Mr. Kawato rented →
I also know that you lived there.
When I was pregnant...
(Yazaki) However, even as his wife, it seems that she has no intention of making matters worse.
I just want you to step back.
That is my only request to you.
I have a daughter.
Please don't get any closer to him.
please.
(Louis) It's a misunderstanding. Kawato-san...→
It's not the relationship you think it is.
So what about this photo?
(Louis) We don't have this kind of relationship. It's true.
That means I don't approve.
Understood. I will make changes after research. →
Let's go.
It's okay...leave it to me.
♪～
(sound of door closing)
(Thelma) What do you mean?
>> Please explain, Louis.
(Louis) It's true that I lived in his apartment in Tokyo...
But now... (Thelma) Really? What about this photo?
No matter how I look at it, it doesn't look like a normal relationship.
(Louis) That's...
>> Maybe Mr. Kawato →
He became a producer for Babysta...
(Thelma) Is it because you had that kind of relationship with Louis?
I think it's strange.
Why are people like Mr. Kawato doing what we're doing? (Louis) No. That's not true.
(Thelma) So what does that mean? (Louis) That's...
Let's say no. This is wrong.
(Thelma) Of course. For such a dubious reason →
It wasn't produced. (Louis) No.
It has nothing to do with Babysta...
(Thelma) What?
(Louis) It's from me.
We met again after a long time and that's it.
(Thelma) Are you serious about that?
(Louis) Yeah.
(Thelma) That's not possible. Still an idol? Is it an affair?
Or rather, with such a half-hearted feeling →
Have you been an idol? Is that the extent?
Louis' feelings towards idols.
Louis...you're lying, aren't you?
(Louis) She's an idol in the first place→
I only started because he recommended it to me.
(Thelma) What is that...?
(Louis) But it's okay. I won't do this again.
(Louis) 《To tell you the truth, the two of you understand my feelings→
He will probably reject Mr. Kawato...》
《I don't care what you think.→
Babysta needs Kawato-san》
♪～
《Actually, that's about it...→
What are my thoughts on idols?→
Different from Thelma and Izumi》
♪～
(Music from earphones)
(Ai Takamiya) [This song will cheer you up] (Louis) [Yeah]
[I want to be... an idol who can sing songs like this]
(Louis) [Love can do it. I'm rooting for you]
♪～
>> Garden? Ah, I've heard the rumors.
You can earn a lot of money.
But there are some scary stories...
There seems to be a rumor that they will recommend medicine.
medicine? Is it an example of a synthetic drug?
I don't know, but probably.
Garden... I think there's something going on with this.
yes.
📱Is Reiko in your office?
(Louis) Yeah. I'm doubting our relationship. I want you to do something about it.
(Kawato) Too bad. She's extremely anxious.
This please.
There's nothing really wrong with you, so you don't have to worry about it.
(Louis) No, but...we also had lawyers involved, and we were doing a lot of research.
(Kawato) Lawyer? ...Oh, Yazaki, right?
(Louis) Eh...that's right, though.
(Kawato) You don't have to worry about Yazaki either.
📱Once you know it's nothing, you'll understand eventually. (Louis) No, but.
(Kawato) There's no need to worry about being investigated, right?
(Kawato) I'll contact you again for now.
(phone disconnected sound)
(Louis) Huh...
(Louis) Congratulations on your discharge from the hospital.
Mr. Shimotani.
(Shitaya) Oh no, I found out.
It seems like things are still not perfect.
(Louis) This was a request from Reiko Kawato, right? There's no point in searching.
Kawato-san and I don't have that kind of relationship.
>> Even if you say that.
Anyway, I want you to investigate thoroughly →
Her lawyer...
Thank you for your help again for a while.
♪～
Does it suit you?
(Louis) Yes, very.It fits perfectly with that naughty face.
Excuse me.
《It’s bad. Mr. Shimotani again...｡→
And that clock
Maybe someday I'll realize it's Haura-san's.
>> I don't understand. >> Thank you.
(Michiru) Thank you.
Um, sorry.
Do you know this club called Garden?
What is it, you?
This is the kind of person I am.
Escort club.
(Michiru) [used to be an idol]
(Mochizuki) [Do you recognize this? 〕 〔office…? ]
(Mochizuki) How come I'm connected to Louis and the others again...
♪～
Can I have a moment?
(Doi) Mr. Louis, what do you mean?
This is Kawato-san, right? →
This is going to be a big deal.
Please let the three of us talk for a moment.
(Thelma) That wife...
>>Let's stop it already.
You should keep your distance from Kawato-san.
If you have an image like this→
This will affect Louis' future as an idol.
(Thelma) I just said this →
Louis is doing idols with half-hearted feelings →
I can't help but think so.
>> I know you're working really hard.
I told you, right? Don't carry it on your back alone.→
Is there something wrong?
(Thelma) We're friends, right? Us.
(Louis) It's okay. You can make any excuse you want.
Louis.
(Louis) I don't intend to cause any trouble to you two.
(Mochizuki) Kubo goes to an escort club called Garden →
I understand that you were using it.
The third victim is Yuki Yamano.→
That's not all.
Second victim Fumi Yoshinogawa →
And the first victim, Yuina Nagata.
(Administrator) At the escort club that Kubo used →
Does that mean all the victims belonged to it?
Yes. (Administrator) Considering the situation→
There is no doubt that Shigeru Kubo is the main culprit.→
Be sure to find him before the fourth victim appears.
(All) Yes.
(phone ringtone)
📱(Answering machine) I can't answer the phone right now...｡
♪～
(Louis) I apologize for causing you trouble this time.
📱The man in the photo is (Louis) a close friend →
This is not Junya Kawato.
(Louis) Mr. Shitaya. It's obvious.
(Kubo) What is this?
Ha ha...
(Louis) Ha ha...｡
Ha ha...wow!
Wow!
Louie Louie Louie!
(Louis) Huh... (Kubo) Louis.
(Louis) Mr. Kubo...stop it.
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you.
Wow! (Mochizuki) Stop it!
Are you okay? (Louis) Naoya.
(Kubo) Wow! (sound of knife cutting)
(Louis) Ah...
(Kubo) Wow! →
Ugh...
(Kubo) Uh...
Don't go wild!
(Kubo) Hmm…｡ (Louis) Huh, hah…｡
>> Are you injured? (Louis) I'm fine.
>> Good.
(Louis) But Naoya...
>> I told you, I'll definitely protect you.
(Louis) Why here?
I have a bad feeling when I look at SNS.
That's why I was broadcasting it from my office.
Just in case.
(Louis) Thank you.
♪～
(knock)
He said you can go home for today. I'll send you back.
(Louis) Ah...okay.
>>It's okay.
(Kawato) Louis!
Doi-san told me that you were attacked. Are you okay?
(Louis) Yeah, I am. (Kawato) Good.
Ah... thank you very much.
home.
(Louis) Well then.
Yeah.
(Kawato) Excuse me.
♪～
(Kawato) I'm glad you're safe. I was worried.
(Louis) More than that... (Kawato) Huh?
(Louis) This.
(Kawato) Ah...I was surprised too.
But who exactly...
(Louis) My wife showed me the exact same photo.
(Kawato) Ah...Is that so?
(Louis) People are talking about whether it's Mr. Kawato.
If this continues, I won't be the only one →
Will it affect your work?
teeth? I? I didn't kill you! →
I have never met this person.
(Sakamoto) There was a photo of the two of you in your room.
That's...→
Because I loved you.
But these guys treat me like a stalker →
I haven't seen him once since I was forced to leave the Garden.
(Sakamoto) Do you recognize this medicine? (Kubo) What is that?
Synthetic drugs. >> Ah...
After all, that woman did it.
Why did you think that?
No...when I was watching over that woman →
I saw you going in and out of a suspicious store.→
Anyway, it doesn't matter to me.
Now, let's change the subject.
(Mochizuki) You were the one who attacked Mr. Shitaya, right?
it is….
Why him?
After all, this guy is Louis's stalker.→
It's been with me for a long time.
So to protect Louis...→
However, Louis is with another man...
Is that why you attacked her?
Well, it will happen.
That's crazy... You're the stalker.
Stalker? I?
What are you saying...→
Louis and I understood each other.→
We had the same eyes.
However, Louis suddenly changed...→
It's all Kawato's fault.
That's why I couldn't really forgive it.
You're late Louis...
Is it still the police?
Should I go pick you up after all?
(Thelma) Why us?
>> As expected, even Louis is insecure.
Let's go and talk properly.
(Louis) I just had it sent to me...
(Thelma) I was worried.
(Louis) Sorry.
(Thelma) It's coming out for a while.
(Izumi) Ah... Thelma.
LOUIS Are you okay?
(Louis) Yeah...｡
After all, you can't rely on me.
📱 Talk to Reiko properly (Kawato) For requests to the research company →
I had it taken down. (Louis) Good.
(Kawato) He's just saying that he wasn't the one who posted it on SNS.
Well, I can't think of anyone else...
(Louis) Yeah.
(Kawato) More importantly, can we meet tonight?
I have something to tell you. 📱Okay.
(Louis) 《It went well...》
《Mr. Kawato is a famous person →
The damage caused by rumors circulating is huge.→
I can't help but move to protect myself...
♪～
(shutter sound)
(Louis) 《I don't mind being sacrificed》
♪～
(Louis) 《If I can protect these two...》
>> Kubo is still denying it.
(Administrator) Didn't anything come out of the confiscated smartphone?
The women I followed →
A large number of stolen images were found →
Nothing related to serial murders...
(Administrator) Kubo is Shiro...
But all the victims
The fact that he is related to the garden is an important clue.→
Wash the garden thoroughly. (All) Yes.
♪～
[I saw him entering and exiting a suspicious store]
(Louis) What are you doing here?
(Kawato) It's my hideout that I keep secret from everyone at work and even my family.
Isn't it good?
(Louis) So?
(Kawato) Haura's corpse has been found.
You guys did it, right?