Are you crazy?
Got a death wish or something?
What are you doing?
No, seriously, what are you doing?
You got my car all dirty.
This is really expensive.
Take me home.
Hurry up, let's go!
Take me home, now!
Drive!
Okay.
[The Perfect Suspect]
[Episode 2]
[Nanying District Sub-bureau
Xinggang City Public Security Bureau]
Everyone, gather the clues.
We're about to have a meeting.
-Got it.
Bro.
What were you two just talking about?
In such a rush
to snitch to my master, huh?
I...
I won't do it again.
We were just curious
why he was there too?
He said we ran into a real expert.
Did he mean the expert was the killer,
or was he talking about himself?
You're way too curious.
Why don't you just call him and ask?
How can I...
Master, phone.
Someone's calling Yang Youmo.
Quiet.
[Unknown Caller]
[Answer] [Hang up]
Don't answer. Track the location.
[Unknown Caller]
[Answer] [Hang up]
[Missed Calls]
Stay silent. Call them back.
[Connecting]
[On the call]
Hello?
Did we lock in the location?
[Map of Xinggang City]
Yes, we did.
Tracking shows
they entered Lingpan Residence.
Zhao Qian's place?
Open the door!
Ms. Zhao.
Police.
[Police]
Ask her to come out.
Zhao Qian!
We're the police.
Please get dressed and come out.
Captain Zheng.
[Police]
We're from the Nanying
Criminal Police Division.
We need your cooperation in a case.
Early yesterday morning,
there was a murder at a construction site.
Was it Yang Youmo?
What's your relationship with Yang Youmo?
Just friends.
Officer.
I was kidnapped.
Someone tried to kill me.
Please tell us
exactly what happened.
That day,
I was accompanying an important client
of Lyuyun Group for a fishing trip.
The client had to leave early,
and just as I was about to go too,
someone attacked me from behind.
When I woke up,
I had already been kidnapped.
My eyes were covered,
so I didn't know where I was.
Then why, when we mentioned the murder,
did you immediately say Yang Youmo?
Because the person who called him that day
was me.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Who are you? Where am I?
The man who kidnapped me
forced me to call Yang Youmo.
If he called the police
or didn't follow instructions,
I would be killed.
Speak.
Youmo,
listen carefully.
Here's the first game command:
Take the car onto the expressway.
Roll down the windows.
Drive at exactly 154 km per hour.
Take a photo
of the dashboard at that speed.
If I hit 154 and take a photo,
I might die.
If you don't do it,
I'll die right now.
Hello? I took the photo.
Tell him to delete the photo.
Now delete the photo.
Delete it?
He made me take it.
I nearly died
just trying to get that shot.
Who is he? I swear I'll kill him!
I'm sorry.
I lost my temper.
Youmo, listen carefully.
Okay.
Here's the second game command:
At the construction site, in a trash bin,
there's a red plastic bag.
Inside, there's an altimeter.
Strap it to your wrist.
Then...
Then climb the tower crane.
You must reach 92 meters.
[Straightening Machine Processing Shed]
[Safety and Civility,
Quality and Efficiency]
Why exactly 92 meters?
I don't know.
Yang Youmo
asked me the same question.
Why 92 meters?
Why?
Because once you reach 92 meters,
the game ends.
I don't know what happened
after that.
He injected me with something.
I passed out again.
When I woke up,
I was at the landfill.
Do you have
any other information
about the suspect's appearance?
No.
Then why didn't you
report to the police right after escaping?
I had to go home.
I had to clean myself up.
You have no idea
what it's like
to crawl out of a pile
of rotting, stinking garbage
when you have
a cleanliness obsession.
Why do you think the perpetrator
mentioned 154 km
and 92 meters to Yang Youmo?
I don't know.
I just said what he told me to say.
I honestly didn't know
he'd die if he climbed up there.
Zhao Qian,
try to calm down.
The next question is important.
It could help us
catch the suspect
as soon as possible.
Have you ever crossed anyone?
Any grudges
left unresolved?
No.
No?
What about Yang Youmo?
I don't know.
You and Yang Youmo...
Are you just friends?
Yes.
I'm not even allowed
to have tea in your office anymore?
I've been busy lately, Master.
Busy?
Busy creating a virtual killer online?
Busy interfering with
Zheng Gang's investigation?
Tell me,
why are you so
focused on Yang Youmo's case?
I don't have time to play guessing games.
We've made a major breakthrough.
Zheng Gang is taking a statement.
Didn't expect
even that person to be involved.
Who?
That...
No. We can't disclose case details to you.
Master.
Are you playing mind games with me?
Like you're not
playing mind games with me.
Don't think I don't know.
You want in on this case.
You want back in,
don't you?
Tell me.
You want back in?
[Crack Down on Criminal Gangs
to Safeguard Local Peace]
[Nanying District Sub-bureau
Xinggang City Public Security Bureau]
You were talking about her, right?
You know her?
Zhao Qian from Lyuyun Group, right?
Stop bothering Zheng Gang.
Take care, Master.
Send my regards to Madam.
Zhao Qian...
How is she even involved in this case?
According to the medical report,
Zhao Qian really
was kidnapped.
There's truth in the lie,
and lies in the truth.
Yang Youmo risked his life for her.
Did everything someone told him to.
Is that what a "just friend" would do?
Keran,
you and Ma
dig deeper into
Yang Youmo's social connections.
Got it.
Looks like the two of us
need to get closer to this big shot.
[Nanying District Sub-bureau
Xinggang City Public Security Bureau]
She's still a suspect?
You think the perpetrator
will come after her again
since the first attempt failed?
A general manager
of such a huge corporation
with no past feuds?
Zhao Qian.
We barely know anything about her.
I'm guessing Yang Youmo is her lover.
They're professional bodyguards,
reliable guys.
From today on,
they'll handle your security.
This guy
isn't someone they can handle.
While I was away,
did anything happen at the company?
There were some rumors.
Our stock price took a hit.
You were supposed
to attend a charity ball tomorrow night.
Shall we...
Don't change the schedule.
If I don't show up soon,
people will think I'm dead.
But attending a ball
at a time like this,
isn't that dangerous?
All the more reason to go.
Now is exactly when
I have to act like nothing's wrong.
Invite Liu Renkai to the ball.
Right away.
[Customers Flock Like Clouds]
Long.
[8,000 Daily
English Conversation Sentences]
Yep, Boss?
[Customers Flock Like Clouds]
Do I look okay?
Almost.
Say it straight.
Almost there.
"Almost" won't cut it.
Zhao Qian invited me
to the charity ball tomorrow night.
I need to look perfect.
Okay.
-Ms. Zhao’s car.
-Ms. Zhao is here.
-Turn the camera.
-Come on.
-Ms. Zhao.
Please look over here.
Look this way, Ms. Zhao.
This way, Ms. Zhao.
Ms. Zhao, please.
Ms. Zhao.
[Lyuyun Group]
[Zhao Qian]
[An Evening of Charity: Supporting
the Elderly and Helping Orphans]
Ms. Zhao.
May I have this dance?
Your name?
Zhong Ning.
Mr. Zhong.
You dance quite well.
Are you a professional?
Just a hobby.
By trade, I'm a divorce lawyer.
I run a small firm.
A divorce lawyer?
Then you must really understand women.
How else could you empathize?
Actually, I understand men too.
Because men are also my clients.
If my friends ever need help,
I'll be sure to send them your way.
Thank you, Ms. Zhao.
But I might be a bit busy these days.
Being busy is good.
The busier you are,
the more people are escaping misery.
But I can't help you escape yours.
What misery do I have?
At this ball tonight,
the person in the most misery is you.
When I danced with you just now,
I could feel you were injured.
Even so,
you're here smiling through it.
Not because you enjoy it, right?
In your high position at Lyuyun Group,
you must have your reasons.
Mr. Zhong,
you might be the one
who understands me best tonight.
I'm honored.
Excuse me for a moment.
Kai, this is champagne.
No need to swirl the glass.
Ms. Zhao,
there's been a lot of gossip lately.
If it's gossip,
then it's not worth hearing.
But when too many mouths talk,
things always turn sour.
If that's made you uncomfortable,
then I've failed at my job.
I'm worried about you.
Kai, I appreciate it.
My father always said you're loyal.
You'd speak up when it counts.
Worried about me, huh?
Are you even qualified to be that?
Ms. Zhao.
I get what you mean.
I'll handle your troubles.
Whoever's upsetting you,
I won't let them get away with it.
I know how to take care of things.
You can rest easy.
Captain Zheng, you dance too?
Didn't know that was one of your skills.
Shouldn't you be home with Xi?
Why are you even here?
You're not qualified
to be involved in this case.
In tango,
the man is supposed to lead.
But when I danced with her,
I felt like she was the one leading.
She has a strong need for control.
I didn't feel like her dance partner,
more like
a puppet on a string.
Finished talking?
Yes.
Then go.
Stop interfering with the investigation.
Murderer! Murderer!
She's no philanthropist!
She's a murderer!
She ruined my son's family!
Zhao Qian!
You murderer!
What, you wanna hit me now too?
No filming!
Stop filming!
She's no philanthropist!
She's not a philanthropist!
She ruined my son's whole family!
Zhao Qian, you're a murderer!
Zhao Qian!
-She’s a murderer.
-Go away!
Stop filming!
Over here! Over here!
Auntie, have you
misunderstood me all along?
Auntie, just say it boldly
what happened to your family.
Don't play innocent with me.
I know exactly what you are.
You're a ghost in human skin.
You killed my whole family.
You're a murderer!
You're not a philanthropist!
We demand an explanation tonight!
You're a murderer!
Say something!
You're not a philanthropist!
You're a murderer!
Stop filming!
No filming! No filming!
She's no philanthropist!
She's a murderer!
Auntie, have you
misunderstood me all along?
Auntie, say it boldly
what happened to your family.
You're a ghost in human skin.
You killed my whole family.
You're a murderer!
A ghost?
A murderer?
Who did Zhao Qian kill?
Yang Youmo?
Probably not.
[This case involves the Marriage
Law, Contract Law, and Civil Law]
Tong, died on the same day; Luo Lijuan,
suicide; Yang Yan, missing / Accident]
Tong?
Luo Lijuan?
But those were accidents.
There were
witness testimonies, material evidence,
and the police report.
Yang Yan?
That's even less likely,
also an accident.
So what did Zhao Qian really do?
I feel like killing her myself...
Ms. Fang, please
calm down. Have some water.
Calm down?
She's practically bewitched
my husband and stolen his soul.
Zhao Qian.
A ghost.
A soul-stealing ghost.
[Xinggang Ningwen Law Firm]
Barbecue in broad daylight?
-Boss.
-Hello, boss.
Uh… Mr. Zhong,
what brings you here all of a sudden?
What do you mean "all of a sudden"?
This is my law firm. Why can't I show up?
No, I mean…
We're all just used to you being absent.
Look up someone named Fang Qinchun for me.
Find out where she's living now.
Send it to my phone later.
Which Fang Qinchun?
If she came to see me,
she probably wants a divorce.
[Mr. Zhong, found
Fang Qinchun’s new address
No. 112, Bungalow, 26 Guangming Avenue,
Jianghai Road, Nanying District, Xinggang]
Ten bucks.
Hold on.
Thanks.
Sir, have one bowl of beef offal.
Ms. Fang.
It's no use looking for me.
I can't pay the debt.
Here,
have some beef offal.
Thanks, but I'm vegetarian.
I'm not here to collect debt.
I'm a divorce lawyer.
We've met before.
You came to my firm
to ask about getting a divorce,
remember?
Still trying to make money off my divorce?
No need.
No more divorce.
My husband's already dead.
Dead?
What happened?
Ms. Fang,
I'd like to ask you again
about Zhao Qian.
Ms. Fang.
It was all a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
I thought Ms. Zhao
was seducing my husband,
but she wasn't.
I wrongfully accused her.
She's a good person.
She's always looked out for me and my son,
sometimes even sends people
to buy from my stall.
A misunderstanding.
Ma'am.
Is it fresh today?
Fresh, very fresh.
Give me a few skewers.
You got it!
That's enough, thanks.
Fang Qinchun's husband
was named Qian Cheng.
He hanged himself a year ago.
Can't you ever get everything in one go
and say it all at once?
You ask, I check. That's my job.
Fine, fine.
It's my fault.
Sorry, Miss Cheng.
So what did
this Qian Cheng do?
Senior executive
at Lyuyun Pharmaceuticals.
Why did he kill himself?
Lots of rumors online.
Most people say
he embezzled company funds.
[Fresh Fruits]
Sir, check please.
What are you doing here?
Why can't I be here?
Sir, the check.
You were shouting
to pay the bill so loudly,
but ended up making me pay. Nice one.
You came to find Zhang Qiaoyun.
Did you ever stop
to think who you are now?
You're no longer a cop.
You have no authority
to investigate anyone.
Aunt Zhang!
There were two
suspicious people downstairs.
Let's split up.
Aunt Zhang!
Hold tight!
It's too dangerous!
Come help!
Hold on tight!
-Help him.
-Pull harder.
Someone get up there and give him a hand!
Hold tight!
Auntie!
Family's here.
Please don't do this.
Hold on tight.
Let me go.
I've lost my whole family.
You're a good person.
Thank you.
Careful!
No! Don't let go!
Hold on! Hold on!
Thank goodness they caught her.
That was close.
She should be okay.
Ms. Zhao.
That situation with Zhang Qiaoyun…
Did you do it?
I promised you,
I'd take care of your troubles.
And that's how you chose to handle it?
Things like this
can't be handled with
your philanthropist methods.
Liu Renkai,
you'd better rein
in your dirty tricks.
Ms. Zhao…
What are you...
What about me?
Lyuyun Group today
isn't the same as before.
And I'm not my father.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The only reason I've kept you around
is out of respect for
the past between you and my father.
But if you've got
so much time on your hands,
why don't you go
find the person who kidnapped me?
Ms. Zhao…
The Chairman wants to know if...
If you could possibly
turn the music down a bit.
[The Perfect Suspect]