That short-lived wretch Xie Wuqiang.
He must have provoked the person
who intended to kill Zhao Qian.
Boss.
Zhao Qian is here.
Do you know what this is?
Yang Youmo and Xie Wuqiang
were both killed by this drug.
Just a tiny bottle of this
is enough to kill both you and me.
I had just given you the clue,
and he ended up dead right after.
Why?
Liu Renkai.
You didn't kill him, did you?
Don't be nervous.
Can't you take a joke?
If you still want to eat meat at my table,
then be a good hound
and find me the prey.
Dad!
I won an award for my essay! Look.
How old are you?
Hello, Auntie.
I'm 11 years old this year.
You're already 11,
and you still have no manners?
Get the hell back home!
I'm sorry, Dad.
Trying to protect her?
It's not like I'm gonna eat her alive.
Kids aren't really my thing.
How many years have you had this dog?
Almost nine years.
Nine years?
It's a veteran then.
You must treat it well.
Long.
Do you know why Zhao Qian's father
gave me this dog?
I... I don't know.
He was trying to remind me that
I, Liu Renkai, am just a dog to
the Zhao family.
Boss, if you're not happy
with the sight of it,
I can take it away and raise it
at my place.
No need.
I like it.
It's more loyal than human beings.
More importantly,
it constantly reminds me that
I'm just a dog.
[I can give him a son.]
Mom, I won an award for my essay.
[Award: Liu Zixuan won the third prize
in the 2017 Little Essay Contest]
Mom, look.
[Award: Liu Zixuan won the third prize
in the 2017 Little Essay Contest]
Why?
Why aren't you a boy?
Why? Why!
[Award: Liu Zixuan won the third prize
in the 2017 Little Essay Contest]
[The Perfect Suspect]
[Episode 5]
[Nanying Hospital of Xinggang City]
Yes, Master.
Xie Wuqiang's entire immediate family
has co-signed the consent
to donate his kidney
to his son, Xie Xiaohua.
Will it affect the investigation
of the case?
No, it won't. Our forensic doctor is
also at the hospital.
Master.
The time window for organ transplantation
from a deceased donor is very tight.
You'll have to make the final decision
on this.
I make the final decision?
If it really comes to that,
I'll take the blame if
anything goes wrong.
What do you mean
you'll take the blame?
If something really goes wrong,
can you handle it?
My personal opinion is that
the child's life is the most important.
If worst comes to worst
and something goes wrong,
I'll take responsibility.
Okay then.
Got it.
Let's go.
[Beware of Scams,
Watch out for Medical Fraudsters]
Okay, got it.
Our leader has specially approved
prioritizing the child's rescue.
Just sit tight and wait.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Please calm down.
-Please, get up and sit down.
-Thank you.
Have a seat.
Just wait for the good news.
Okay.
Director Zhang and Captain Zheng, it's
really heroic of you two
to take all the blame on yourselves.
[Internal Medicine Department
Nanying Hospital of Xinggang City]
You feel sorry for me? Then why don't
you take the blame?
My head isn't as tough as yours.
Smooth talker.
[November 13, 2017]
Doctor!
Doctor, someone's trying to kill me!
Doctor! Doctor!
Help me! Someone's trying to kill me!
Doctor!
[November 13, 2017]
Help...
Doctor! Doctor!
Hurry!
Our forensic doctors still need to conduct
further toxicology tests and analysis.
But what we can confirm now is that
Xie Wuqiang died from the same cause
as Yang Youmo.
Both were injected with
a lethal dose of adrenaline,
with the dosage precisely controlled.
Besides, judging from this video,
Xie Wuqiang probably also
experienced hallucinations
on the brink of death
like Yang Youmo did.
We've basically mapped out Xie Wuqiang's
social network.
He had a terrible character.
He made enemies everywhere,
and at home, he committed
domestic violence
against his wife Wu Ping and
his son Xie Xiaohua.
So when he died,
his parents weren't particularly sad.
This is a surveillance blind
spot. Inspect carefully.
No cameras,
and no street lights.
This is exactly the kind of place
murderers prefer.
Keran, extract it.
There're blood stains on this.
Captain Zheng,
we found residual fingerprints
on the chip.
The suspect's name is Liu Renkai.
We investigated and found that
Xie Wuqiang owed Liu Renkai money,
and someone had seen
Liu Renkai assaulting Xie Wuqiang.
Where is Liu Renkai now?
He returned home last night
and hasn't left the
neighborhood since.
Got it. Let's meet at
Liu Renkai's neighborhood.
Do you think a creditor
would kill someone who owes them money?
Wait!
It's windy outside.
Officer,
my husband is innocent.
You've got the wrong person.
He's been with me every night
these past few days.
We're not arresting him.
We're lawfully summoning him
for police investigation.
As for he's innocent or not,
don't worry, we'll find out the truth.
Don't be afraid. Tell me what
happened to your hand.
Is it injured?
She accidently got injured
while playing downstairs
a couple of days ago.
It's okay, Baby.
I'll apply some more ointment
for you later.
Come here.
Sun Ting.
Thank you for cooperating with
police investigation.
We should head back now.
Sorry for the trouble.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go.
Officer, I've told you that
[Interrogation Room]
I was at home with my wife and child
that night.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Liu Renkai.
Do you think we're just
having a casual chat with you here
for no reason?
Officer.
I have two families to support.
Don't try to pull that streetwise
attitude with us.
What two families?
That's called a mistress!
I admit that
I did lay a hand on Xie Wuqiang that day.
That was because he owed me
a lot of money.
I'd tried to collect it several times,
but never succeeded.
Gambling debt?
No, not a gambling debt.
He borrowed some money from me.
I don't know what he used it for.
You used violence to collect the debt
and ended up beating him to death?
Why would I kill him?
Who'd pay me back if he died?
Think about it,  who's the one person
in the entire world who'd
least want him dead?
Take a good look.
Do you recognize this chip?
I have this type of chip. And?
Your fingerprints were found on this chip,
and it was found near the place
where Xie Wuqiang was killed.
Explain it to me.
I gave him this chip.
Sometimes, when we friends
make small bets,
we'd use these chips to keep track.
Whoever loses would treat
the others to dinner.
It's not illegal, is it, Officer?
There's Xie Wuqiang's blood on the chip.
Why?
It's obvious that someone's
trying to frame me!
Then tell me, who would frame you?
I don't know.
Hello?
Captain Zheng, it's for you.
Go ahead.
Master.
He does have an alibi.
The night before last,
he was having dinner with his mistress,
Xu Lina, at a restaurant.
They got completely drunk
and left very late.
He had no window to commit the crime.
Ms. Zhao, someone's onto us.
Someone tried to frame me for
Xie Wuqiang's death.
There's definitely something
wrong with Liu Renkai.
So is their marital relationship.
How can you tell?
Only half the bed was used,
while the other half was nearly
covered in dust,
which shows Liu Renkai didn't
come home to sleep often.
Also, Sun Ting wasn't nice to their child.
She probably took out the resentment
between her and her husband on the child.
You're truly cut out to make money
as a divorce lawyer.
Let's go to Xie Wuqiang's house.
Now, Wu Ping is our only hope.
Hopefully, we can find a breakthrough.
No wonder she's so hostile.
I think something was burnt here.
Has Xie Wuqiang done anything
abnormal recently?
He's abnormal every day.
He's either gambling
or selling those prohibited drugs of his.
So
you've known all along that
he's been doing these illegal things?
I dared not say.
If I had told anyone,
he would have killed me and Xiaohua.
Wu Ping.
Does Xie Wuqiang really treat his
son so badly?
Then why did he agree to
go through kidney matching for his son?
It was a lie.
He was lying, Officer.
He took that money,
the money he got from the donation,
and he used it for gambling.
I didn't see a single penny of it.
It's true.
You can check it.
Where were you the night
Xie Wuqiang was killed?
I was at work.
After work,
I... I just went home to cook for Xiaohua.
Did you go straight home after work?
I...
I bought some things outside
the neighborhood.
What did you buy?
Soy sauce.
[Nanying District Sub-Bureau
Xinggang City Public Security Bureau]
In Xie Wuqiang's chat history,
we found
a middleman for human organ trafficking.
According to his confession,
Xie Wuqiang signed an agreement with him
for paid provision of corneas.
As soon as his son, Xie Xiaohua dies,
Xie Wuqiang will immediately trade
Xie Xiaohua's corneas for money.
So you're saying
Xie Wuqiang is the one who most wanted
Xie Xiaohua to die?
Scum.
If that's the case,
we need to search Xie Wuqiang's
house again
to see if we can find
that cornea transfer agreement.
[Head: severe trauma to the left rear side
caused by a heavy object
The blow to the back of Xie Wuqiang's head
was delivered with the left hand?
That's right.
The killer of Yang Youmo
is a very meticulous person.
Would such a person
use a blunt object to strike
the back of Xie Wuqiang's head?
Would they commit the crime
in such a manner?
We need to visit Wu Ping's house again.
Have you ever seen an
organ agreement signed by Xie Wuqiang?
No, I haven't.
Think carefully again.
I haven't.
Wu Ping.
That organ agreement
very likely concerns
Xie Xiaohua's safety.
Why?
Officer.
That kind of agreement is illegal,
you know?
You must investigate this thoroughly.
Our Xiaohua's transplant
already succeeded.
He's recovered.
There's no need to donate his
corneas anymore.
This can't happen.
-You must find out the truth.
-Did I mention
it's about cornea donation?
You've seen it, haven't you?
Just now in the kitchen,
I smelled a lingering scent of
burnt paper.
You burned that agreement, didn't you?
Because that was the key motive
that made you want to kill Xie Wuqiang.
[Forensics Division]
[Signed by Party B: Xie Wuqiang]
[Agreement for Paid Corneal Provision]
[Party A: Zhang Jiajun
Party B: Xie Wuqiang]
[Party A and Party B voluntarily agree to freely trade corneas.
The agreed selling price for Xie Xiaohua's corneas is RMB 100,000.]
[Seller: Xie Wuqiang]
You're the one who hit Xie Wuqiang on the
back of the head with that hammer.
Because your dominant hand is
your left hand.
Wu Ping.
You should trust us
and tell us the truth.
That'll be the best for you, you know?
Yes.
I killed him.
I killed Xie Wuqiang.
I...
I saw that agreement.
It was so infuriating.
If I didn't kill him,
our Xiaohua would have to die.
It was me.
I killed him.
So how did you kill Xie Wuqiang?
I don't remember.
You mean
you were so scared after killing him
that you don't remember anything,
is that right?
Yes.
Then why do you remember
buying a bottle of
soy sauce that you didn't even need?
[Delicious Soy Sauce]
Why?
Go ahead.
Alright, explain the situation to
Advisor Zhong again.
Hello?
Got it. Thank you.
Wu Ping, I'll ask you one more time.
Did you kill Xie Wuqiang?
You didn't kill him.
The forensic team, through
toxicological analysis,
has estimated the time when Xie Wuqiang
was injected with the lethal toxin.
That time almost coincides with
when you were caught on the convenience
store's surveillance camera,
buying soy sauce.
And from the convenience store
to the crime scene,
it takes about 15 minutes.
Tell me,
how could you be in two places at once,
killing Xie Wuqiang while
buying soy sauce?
Why did you lie?
Why were you trying to cover up
for the person who really killed
Xie Wuqiang?
Is it worth lying?
Think about your son.
He said the same thing.
Who is he?
I really don't know.
That night,
I was going to kill that bastard.
Think about your son!
He suddenly showed up and stopped me.
It was that man who killed Xie Wuqiang.
There are both old and new injuries
on your body.
The old ones were inflicted by
Xie Wuqiang.
The new ones probably
happened when you rushed home
from the murder scene
to buy soy sauce, right?
Was it that person who told you
how to create your alibi too?
Yes.
Leave the hammer. Go now.
He was wearing a hat and a mask.
I was very nervous at the time,
and I really didn't see his face clearly.
This place is less than four kilometers
from your home.
You only have 15 minutes.
Remember,
you must
get back to the vicinity of your home
within 15 minutes
to create an alibi. Take a shortcut
and hurry home.
Find a store you frequently visit
and buy something you usually use.
[Jiaqi Grocery Store]
Pretty late, huh?
[Respect Yourself
Theft will Be Punished Tenfold]
Make sure the people in the store remember
that you were there
at that specific time.
I'm sorry.
I'll... I'll compensate for this bottle.
Why did you try to cover up for him?
Because...
Because he saved Xiaohua once.
Officer.
Can I make one more meal for our Xiaohua?
As long as he sees the food I bring,
he'll know
that I come to visit him every day.
Give it to me.
I'll make sure Xiaohua
sees the lunchbox
and knows that you've come to visit him.
Thank you.
You need to have hope in your heart.
I know the best criminal defense
lawyers in all of Xinggang.
I'll ask them to defend you.
You don't need to pay.
When the judge is sentencing,
they'll also consider the fact that
you and your child
have been long-term victims of
domestic violence and abuse.
Why? Why do you want to help me?
Because you're a good mother.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I'll try to call you
"Greedy Lawyer" less from now on.
Can't you just not call me that at all?
I can't.
Xi, I'm coming in, okay?
Doing your homework?
What's wrong?
Dad.
How is Uncle Liao doing recently?
You haven't forgotten about him, have you?
How could I?
Why do you suddenly mention him?
The teacher assigned an essay.
The topic is "My Superhero."
[My Superhero]
I want to write about Uncle Liao,
but I don't know how he's been
doing lately.
He must still be working as a
doctor, right?
He must've saved many patients, right?
He has severe psychological issues.
You didn't pay.
Now he's also suffering from
Alzheimer's disease.
Not everyone is willing to
face their past.
I almost wish my condition
would worsen now.
Captain Zheng.
The technical department has
made a new discovery.
[October 17, 2017]
The surveillance footage in Yang Youmo's
studio has been overwritten.
It was difficult to recover,
but we still managed to find a way
to export some content.
[October 17, 2017]
Is it him?
Sit down.
Dr. Liao,
do you know Yang Youmo?
Yang Youmo? Yes, I know him.
Keran.
Can you explain to us
how the two of you got into a conflict?
He was a bastard.
I asked him to sell my painting.
Not only was he uncapable of selling them,
but he also burned a hole in my painting.
That was my most valuable possession.
Where's the painting now?
Dr. Liao.
Tell us where it is, we'll get it.
It's in that cabinet.
I'll get it.
Dr. Liao.
Where were you on the evening of
November 3,
and what were you doing?
I can't recall.
Think carefully.
I think I had some drinks and
went to sleep.
Look.
[Indication: Patients with mild to
moderate symptoms of Alzheimer's disease]
Okay.
It's been verified. The medical
records are genuine.
The hospital has Liao Boyan's
medical records.
He indeed has Alzheimer's disease,
which is senile dementia.
He was diagnosed with senile dementia?
But he's not even old.
Exactly.
Nowadays, this disease no longer
has a direct correlation with age.
Genetics, mutations,
and unhealthy lifestyle habits,
they can all lead to early-onset dementia.
How could an international
top neurosurgeon,
Renxi's lifesaver,
have brain issues himself?
Boss, he didn't pay again.
Chen. Chen.
This...
Never mind, forget it.
[November 20
Take out the trash, eat]
How could an international
top neurosurgeon,
Renxi's lifesaver,
have brain issues himself?
Nowadays, this disease no longer
has a direct correlation with age.
[Yang Youmo]
The victim's name is Yang Youmo.
He was injected with an
overdose of adrenaline.
Yang Youmo.
[Xie Wuqiang: adrenaline trafficking]
Revenge?
Xie Wuqiang.
Those who want to buy
anesthetics and adrenaline
mostly go to him.
I think his death
is related to his drug trafficking.
[Xie Wuqiang: adrenaline trafficking,
silenced]
The killer timed the death perfectly.
This killer must
have some medical experience.
[Underground casino]
The person who killed Yang Youmo and
kidnapped Zhao Qian
has a very meticulous mind.
It can't be someone
who has Alzheimer's disease.
[Xie Wuqiang, adrenaline trafficking,
silenced][Underground casino]
Liu Renkai has no benefit in
killing Zhao Qian.
You're a murderer!
[Underground casino]
Zhang Qiaoyun couldn't possibly have
killed her own son.
I didn't expect a person like this
to get involved.
[Zhao Qian]
Zhao Qian from Lyuyun Group?
Zhao Qian's foe.
A year ago, Zhao Qian ran a red light
and hit someone with her car.
It wasn't Zhao Qian's first time
running a red light.
She was fined by traffic police
five years ago.
Five years ago.
Liao Yifan. Car accident.
It was also five years ago.
His daughter, Liao Yifan,
was hit and killed by a car right
in front of him and his wife.
The hit-and-run driver escaped.
They haven't been caught for five years.
Liao Yifan.
[Liao Yifan]
Zhao Qian.
[Liao Boyan]
Why is the killer so twisted,
forcing Yang Youmo to play a deadly game,
[Yang Youmo, had a conflict] [Liao Boyan]
[Zhao Qian]
and throwing Zhao Qian, who has OCD
about cleanliness, into a garbage pit?
[Liao Boyan]
There must be some deep-seated grudge.
[Zhao Qian] [Liao Boyan]
That's why
such complex criminal methods were used
to carry out the crime.
The purpose was
to mentally torture the victims.
Torture. Mental torture.
[Liao Yifan]
[Father and daughter]
I think it's all about revenge.
[Yang Youmo] [Zhao Qian] [Liao Yifan] [Liao Boyan]
If Zhao Qian was the one who hit
and killed Liao Yifan...
[Zhao Qian]
Liao Boyan.
Dr. Liao.
Can you stop bothering me?
What exactly do you want?
What do you want to see?
Look, look.
[People's Pharmacy of Nanying District,
Xinggang City]
There're pharmacies nearby.
Why did you go so far to buy it?
There are better discounts over there.
Since you've become rich,
you've forgotten how ordinary people live?
I haven't.
And I don't dare to forget.
Dr. Liao.
There's a question weighing heavily
on my mind.
Did you find
the driver at fault who hit and killed
your daughter five years ago?
Driver at fault? More like murderer!
Officer Zhong.
Do you have any leads?
Tell me.
I thank you on behalf of my daughter.
I'm not a police officer.
And I don't have any leads.
Dr. Liao, I understand how you feel.
But I hope you know
what you should do
and what you shouldn't.
Last time you asked me out for a drink,
you also said you could understand me.
Think about it, if tomorrow night,
your daughter
goes to buy ice cream after school,
and suddenly
gets hit and killed by a car!
Don't use Zhong Renxi as an example.
I remember now.
Her name is Zhong Renxi.
It's been five years.
Zhong Renxi has long been cremated.
Your life has been completely ruined.
Someone suddenly comes to you and says,
"The one who killed Zhong Renxi was
a driver at fault!"
I said,
don't use Zhong Renxi as an example!
You're angry. Take this.
Your daughter's birthday,
parent-teacher conferences,
Children's Day,
every day she could have lived well,
you have to go through them alone.
You can only fantasize about a sudden
thunderbolt from the sky
striking the killer dead!
No one will ever call you "Dad" again.
You're just a
damn medical doctor
who couldn't even protect
his own daughter!
Do you understand me now?
Tell me what I should do
and what I shouldn't!
You can't understand me!
Let go!
Don't say you can understand me.
Zhong Ning.
My daughter is dead.
Yifan is dead.
I really envy you.
You have a daughter waiting for you
at home.
My daughter is dead.
I really envy you.
[Yang Youmo, had a conflict] [Xie Wuqiang] [Liao Boyan]
You have a daughter waiting
for you at home.
Tell me what I should do
and what I shouldn't!
You can't understand me!
I'll definitely
give her this lifetime.
[Zheng Gang Calling]
[15 missing calls from Zheng Gang]
What are you doing?
How many times have I called you?
Renxi is about to cry at school.
Why?
You forgot?
Hurry up!
What are you doing?
What do you think? We're already here.
I'm her uncle. Can't I attend the
parent-teacher conference once?
Hurry up.
Next, let's welcome Zhong Renxi
to share with us
[Xinggang Yucai Experimental School]
her essay that received an A+,
[Welcome to the Parent-Teacher Conference
of Class 2, Grade 4]
"My Superhero."
[Welcome to the Parent-Teacher Conference
of Class 2, Grade 4]
My Superhero.
Superheroes don't just exist in movies.
They also exist in real life.
When I was four years old,
something bad grew in my brain.
My parents took me to many hospitals,
and we visited many doctors,
but no one dared to operate on me.
They all said the chances were slim.
Then I met my superhero,
Liao Boyan,
Uncle Liao.
He's the world's best super doctor.
He personally performed
a miraculous surgery on me.
He removed
the bad thing in my brain that
had caused me so much pain.
Okay.
Once, death had...
Got it.
Closed the door of life and the window
of health for my young self,
after which
I had been in a constant state
of fear and anxiety.
What's wrong?
Xiao Dade
is dead.
[The Perfect Suspect]