Time: 8:30 to 11:00.
Gosh.
Sun Storm!
Electromagnetic storm.
Parallel time call.
No way.
Sun Storm!
Electromagnetic storm.
Ahn Jin-jin is really weird these days.
She ignores me as soon as she appears in Jiangling.
Do you think it's weird
Is it strange?
You're the same.
Do you want a beating?
There must be something between her and Jiangling.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
I have a very important question
to ask you.
Which question?
Can you tell me
the parallel time call
and butterfly effect?
What is this?
I searched online.
The butterfly effect means
In the power system,
the slight changes in the initial conditions
will lead the whole system
which will lead to
for a long time.
This is a chaos.
In real time and space,
the butterfly effect
because of the parallel time call?
For example,
I've only seen
in math.
the remaining sequence.
But if we use it
to physics,
how can you show the butterfly effect?
How do you present the butterfly effect?
Most importantly,
if we accidentally
change its original track,
will it affect the real time and space?
Ahn Jin-jin.
As a teacher,
I'm glad you're so interested in physics.
But
I'm a high school physics teacher.
If I could understand,
I'll hang it here.
(1879 - 1955)
It seems to rain.
I want to live next door to you.
Standing at your house like a fool.
Hello?
This is Jiangling.
Jiangling, 2024.
You mean
I'm
calling Jiangling in 2024.
Times?
If you really
in 2012,
In 2012,
Didn't humanity perish?
I've figured it out.
The one that appeared at your place
was Jiangling in 2012.
He and I
the same person.
I'm Jiangling, 2024.
Am I dreaming?
It's not a dream.
I can tell you everything that will happen in the future.
In 2012,
September 30,
China's Good Voice will live in the Final.
The champion is Liang Bo.
November.
What is not a good voice in China?
Or...
What are you?
A reality show.
A human show, right?
I forgot.
You...
It's the end of February.
Wait a minute.
Let me see.
The All-star Game
It's about to start, right?
Kobe!
In one attack,
Waid broke his nose.
I don't care
what you said.
I don't care either.
If this is not a dream,
you're a liar.
I suddenly remembered
You...
That thing
will happen soon.
What is it?
That's impossible.
Okay, everyone.
The poem evaluation question yesterday
is about expressing skills.
We just said
how to express it.
You...
That thing
will happen soon.
Things
to express our feelings.
It's called
a will.
And
Let's talk about our current situation.
We use some ancient things
to refer to the slope of the closer line.
The slope
Its slope is 1.
The diagonal rate here is two.
Louder.
The first half of this double curve
is intersected.
Let's see.
That thing
will happen soon.
Everyone,
In this class,
we have a reaction
High school oxygen oxidation.
Combination price.
After class,
according to the teacher's knowledge frame,
Copper oxide.
In this reaction,
It's happening.
Hyoxide reaction.
Third,
Rehabilitation reaction.
Based on
and integration prices.
That's all for today.
Okay, class is over.
Thank you. Stand up.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, students.
It's Beijing time now.
2012.
February 26th.
[12:30 p.m.]
Welcome to the weather forecast.
Jin-jin.
Aren't you hungry?
You ran to the canteen first.
Why aren't you eating?
Stop looking.
He rarely comes to the canteen.
Jiangling.
The guy with glasses.
No food is allowed at school.
Why is he here again?
If something goes wrong, you'll be responsible.
Just come and eat.
Time to eat.
I'm talking about you.
What are you doing?
It hurts, you know?
What?
Chicken
Do you want some?
No.
I heard that the chicken he bought
was thrown away by a lady in the canteen.
He directly quarreled with the lady in the canteen.
The one you cook every day.
Fried eggs with tomatoes.
I'm sick of it.
We eat this every day.
It'll be weird if we don't eat it.
Guys,
Am I right?
Yes.
There are eggs all day long.
No wonder I didn't do well in the exam.
And hair.
So much hair
I've had a lot of hair
I'm full.
Yes.
Qianqian.
That's not hair.
It's hair
I told you not to eat.
Why did you snatch my chicken?
Give it back!
You snatched me!
Come here.
He paid for it.
What's wrong with him?
Why can't you buy it yourself?
What a waste.
I get scolded every time I take it out.
This is too much.
Get down!
Which class are you in?
Who is the head teacher?
Call him here.
and your parents.
I don't want to eat in the canteen.
I'll make you
you can't stay in school.
Don't eat in the canteen for the rest of your life.
What are you looking at?
Get down.
Get down!
Stop!
Smash it!
Seok.
Is he crazy?
Back off!
Step back.
Be quiet.
Come down.
Hurry up.
Come down
Come down.
The whole war has been upgraded.
Until...
Come down.
What are you doing?
Are you rebelling?
Do you all want to be punished?
Then...
Mr. Glasses
Next, the punishment
of Class 8, Grade 12.
Considering yesterday,
Shi Xiaoxin from Class 8, Grade 3
in the canteen
in the canteen.
Therefore,
a serious warning.
I hope you can learn from it.
For 12th grade students
the college entrance exam is coming.
The school has decided the lunch time.
All 12th grade students
can choose to eat at school.
Let's go eat.
Finally.
Without me,
Impossible.
Great!
Sit down and be quiet.
We want fried chicken.
What are you doing over there?
Class begins.
Mom, I'm home.
You're back.
So many delicious food.
One, two, three, four.
Where's my dad?
Your dad is working overtime.
Where is he working overtime?
He's a grown man.
I don't know where he works overtime.
He can't get lost.
But I want to have dinner together.
Let's not talk about this.
Well...
Look.
I think I'll cook some vegetables for you.
And
I'll cook shrimp for you.
Okay?
Is this enough?
Please.
Wash your hands and get ready for dinner.
Can I watch TV first?
You can't watch TV.
I'll just watch for a while.
Let me relax.
This kid.
On a rainy night,
the mysterious woman died under the withered tree.
But there was no smoke within ten miles.
What are they hiding
behind the murder?
hidden?
It's complicated
It's hard to tell if it's true or not
Ambush chasing the murderer
or time travel?
Who is it?
Who?
Surprise!
You're back.
I came back as soon as the meeting was over.
I want to spend more time with you.
Great.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Dad, sit down.
We haven't eaten together for a long time.
Thank you, mom.
Thank you, Mom.
Eat this.
Good boy.
Thank you.
Eat up.
Let me ask you.
how did you do this time?
If I do well,
is there any reward?
A reward for the mock exam?
What about the college entrance exam?
Can you do something practical?
Tell me
4S.
My phone is too low.
And it's stuck.
As long as you pass the exam,
I promise you.
All right.
Try it.
Is the shrimp cooked?
Thank you, mom.
Try this.
And this dish.
are all your favorite.
I must have made them for you.
You can't even shut up with so many dishes.
Eat up.
I think this is delicious too.
This soup looks really good.
Why isn't he online yet?
I'll ask you again.
Please interact.
Is there a big shot who knows about time communication?
I read a post about time call this morning.
I caught a cold.
But it was deleted.
So I reopened a post.
Do you have a friend who has the same cold?
You should
to Zhen Zhen's school.
At least meet her class teacher.
Why should I meet the class teacher?
Aren't you going to see your homeroom teacher?
and care about her study?
You can go.
Do I have to go?
An Jianhua.
Really study
You don't worry at all
Can you keep it down?
I dreamed of a ghost.
Nice.
Good morning, dad.
You didn't sleep late today.
Seize it.
Dad.
What are you looking at?
All-star in the American professional basketball tournament.
Let me tell you.
Kobe's nose is broken.
Okay.
He is handsome.
But I think
he'll get hurt soon.
What are you talking about?
You don't know.
Your dad is a fan of Kobe.
In this attack,
Kobe's nose was broken by Wild.
Stop looking.
Hurry up and pack up and go to school.
It's raining today.
Give her a ride when it rains.
Mom.
Don't go.
Let's do it together.
I want you two to do it together, Mom.
Let's go, Dad.
Let's go.
Stop looking.
Together.
Breakfast.
Eat it while it's hot.
Freshly cooked.
Fill it up.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Take the umbrella.
The weather forecast says it'll rain today.
I'm leaving, Aunt.
Don't tire yourself out.
Take care.
Dad.
Stop at the intersection ahead.
I can walk by myself.
Walk by yourself.
Don't buy snacks.
I'm not buying.
I won't buy it.
I'm full for breakfast.
Jiang.
Is that you?
Are you still there?
It's me.
I'm still here.
Did what I told you last time
come true?
Yes.
All come true.
So,
these things
in your time and space.
How do you remember so clearly?
The principal was hit.
for the rest of your life.
Ahn Jin-jin.
Listen to me.
I can't talk to myself.
There's something
I need your help.
I'm publishing a book.
I was scammed.
He's always hiding.
I had no choice.
But we
are not in the same timeline.
I can't help you.
I have an idea.
What about you?
let me in 2012
buy a lottery ticket
and let him go to the bank to keep his name.
With it,
it can solve my urgent problem.
Don't worry.
I'll pay you back
I just need to pay my debt.
I'll give you the rest of the money.
I only need a chance to change myself.
Okay.
But...
I have something
to ask you for help.
Go ahead.
as long as I can do it,
I will do it.
Can you
help me
what the future me is doing.
Are you happy?
Whether you have money or not,
Most importantly,
how my parents are doing.
I promise you.
Remember this number.
Wait.
Go ahead.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Tomorrow,
we must let Jiangling buy this lottery ticket.
Besides,
I found that
I can only call you
when it rains.
I...
It's thundering here too.
So,
we need to thunder at the same time
at the same time.
Not necessarily.
I'm still
I'm still trying.
Currently,
I only know that
it's related to the thunderstorm.
By the way,
about what you told me,
there's another big problem.
Gangneung is too cold now.
I don't think it's possible
to buy a lottery ticket.
Listen.
Back then,
had a huge weakness.
Guys.
That's all for today.
Class dismissed.
Stand up.
Goodbye, teacher.
Goodbye.
Actually,
I have a special hobby.
I like noodles.
There's a small noodle shop
there's a small noodle shop.
Go buy a bowl of noodles after class.
There are so many people.
How long do I have to wait?
In our city,
in this city.
But only the red specialty place put the most chili
The noodles are flexible. Line up.
Back then,
I often went there.
Great!
It's my turn.
Auntie.
Give me a bowl of noodles.
Excuse me.
Our noodles are sold out.
Come at night if you want to eat.
Sorry.
That's all.
It tastes terrible.
There's no oil or water. Why didn't you buy it?
No.
How could I not?
Why can't I?
I'm already in line.
Why is it gone when it's my turn, Zhen Zhen?
Where have you been?
You didn't even eat.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Great.
Why is he so quiet?
Yeah.
He's so cold.
Jiang.
Good evening.
I'll buy you noodles.
Here's the thing.
I observed the sky at night.
I think
like the noodles here.
You're not hungry, right?
It's okay.
The noodles are here anyway.
Are you hungry?
What are you doing?
I'll eat.
I'll eat it.
You...
Why?
Did I buy the wrong one?
Lower your voice.
It doesn't make sense.
I know.
Why are there so many people here?
Line up.
Jiang,
I bought
must be your favorite brand.
How did you get it?
I've been queuing for a long time.
And I've never seen you before.
Are you...
Zhen Zhen.
Why are you eating noodles again?
Don't you feel upset eating so much?
Jiangling.
You also eat noodles here?
You two bought them together?
Monitor.
You've worked hard.
I bought you some noodles.
Come on!
The monitor is studying.
Look.
It's affecting.
I should study too.
Study
Abandon
abandon
I've never seen
such a difficult man.
Have you heard of
Maya's doomsday prophecy?
I know.
It would be great if it was before the college entrance exam.
I don't want to take the college entrance exam.
Me too.
Let me tell you something.
About this Mayan prophecy,
I have a new understanding.
Something happened to me recently.
It's very scary.
Let me tell you.
Look.
That guy...
is going public.
Who's the woman next to you?
No way.
Accept the reality.
This should be photoshopped.
The photos are out.
It's photoshopped.
This face is different.
Is this the end of the world?
Jiang,
I'm not blaming you.
Do you really know yourself?
These days,
I did everything you said.
You didn't give me any hint.
No wonder he likes noodles so much.
He's completely crippled.
Like this.
If it doesn't work,
there's another way.
What is it?
There is a bookstore on Wanhong Road.
Go find a book there.
Speaking of
Zhuge Liang caught the Mengmeng.
Why do you look so familiar?
Have you been captured by me?
I have a public face.
A public face?
Where are you going so late?
To admire the moon.
BA091.
You even look up at the moon.
Lower your head and think about your hometown.
Nice receive!
BA091.
Stay inside.
I'll go to your dorm keeper.
to work together.
Are you playing 36 strategies with me?
Are you trying to divert us?
Ask your dorm keeper.
She can't run away.
Boss,
Do you have
Kim something?
What version?
Juicis.
There seems to be something behind.
Look for it yourself.
Okay.
Thank you, boss.
I'll go find it.
Hurry up.
We're closing.
Foreign literature.
Where are you?
None.
It's not here either.
It's not.
Dust.
Resurrection.
Foreign literature.
Paris Holy Mother Hospital.
Wuthering Villa.
Where is the boss?
I've searched everywhere.
Go to the back and look for it.
Inside.
The innermost.
How much inside?
Let me see.
Why are there so many books?
Juicis.
You're not only difficult to understand,
but also hard to find you.
Juicis.
Do you like it?
Jiang.
These two books are
are my treasures.
I dare say
I'm the only one
in the city.
Here you go.
How much?
I don't want money.
I take money as a piece of shit.
Actually,
I just want to make friends with you.
Look.
I've been
these days.
I gave you your favorite noodles.
I gave you books you like.
Can't you see
the sincerity I want to make friends with you?
I took a look.
The money is just right.
I just want to be friends with you.
I don't mean anything else.
Take it.
We are friends.
Let me treat you to noodles.
No need.
Let's go, good friend.
I'll buy you noodles.
Let’s go.
Jiang.
I brought my new friend here for noodles.
Mister.
You know each other?
We’ve known each other for years.
Jiang
is warm
and kind.
You should make more good friends.
Get back to work.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll get back to work.
He's warm and kind.
He's so funny.
I helped him
I helped him.
You're different
from what I imagined.
You like reading novels like that?
Don't you boys
watch Doolo Continent?
That's literature.
Since you like literature so much,
why don't you apply for liberal arts?
Let me in 2012
to buy a lottery ticket.
I only need one chance to change myself.
Actually...
Actually,
I need your help.
Do you remember
the phone call I received yesterday?
What I'm going to say next
may change your views.
Be prepared.
The call
that called me yesterday
was from the future you.
You like noodles.
and read that kind of novel.
He told me everything.
See for yourself.
The day before you transferred,
the day before you transferred.
At that time,
I didn't even have your number.
So...
What do you want?
The future you
was cheated.
He's a terrible liar.
He asked me to take you to buy lottery tickets.
Otherwise, the future you
even dare not go out.
That's your only purpose.
My goal is to help you.
So...
Let's go to the lottery store.
Let's go.
I'll go after eating.
Fine.