It's time to take the medicine
Oh
Okay
Yitan, wake up.
You're not strong at all.
You're really good at controlling.
Very good.
Drink it all.
I'm not sure if I said it right.
It's not your fault.
Didn't you say a small wound?
Why is it bleeding?
It's still bleeding.
Because I was born with a blood clot.
I hope for more.
I only think about you in this life.
I hope we can be together from now on.
Yitan, are you cold?
You know if you don't want to die
Let people know that there are two people
You know that the flower is in full bloom
It's the most romantic thing
You know that for a moment
I drew the most beautiful heart
You know your name
But I have never been the shortest love
Yitan, you never touched your hand.
The whole world is actually like me.
The left sword is a step back.
Don't use it.
Brother, do you really only move your mouth?
Can you do it?
So this is the reason why you never came out.
The last day is the most warm start of my love.
Brother, sister has so many clothes on her.
It's okay to take off one.
How can we lose to a little sister like this?
What's the point of playing like this?
Why don't you just kill us?
Is it a trick?
If I show my real strength, do you dare to be hard?
I dare not
This time it's your brother's turn
Let's bet who will be faster
You are using a sword
It shouldn't be
Okay
You lose
I said you could live
You guys are cheating
You can cheat
Why can't we?
Jialai has never lost
I don't know
You guys are cheating
You can cheat
Why can't we?
Jialai has never lost
I will kill you two
It's you
Very good
I am satisfied
Come with me
Jialai
You recognize her
Is it beautiful here?
Beautiful
So perfunctory
You can't wait to leave
How can we leave?
You only beat me once
So only one person can leave
I will use all my power
To send you to a place
You two can kill each other there
Either you all die
Or one of you kill the other
And leave here alive
Who will leave here alive?
What is this place?
July 7
Huaishuizhu Pavilion
This is very important to us
So this should be
The depth of our consciousness
Dongfanghuizhu
Is it the person Mr. Jiuhuo chose?
To be precise
Jialai
Why do you create this illusion?
Do you know
You will disappear
When the demon is near
Mantua flower represents hatred
Although you have cleared her memory
But Dongfanghuizhu still has love in her heart
You want them
To kill the one they love
Where they have the best memory
Only in this way
Mantua flower
Can take her soul completely
Only then
Can she become a real
Perfect
You are talking about a story again
If it is a story
How can you control fire?
That fire mark
Do you really have no impression?
Between you and me, there is no need
Between you and me, there is only one life
Mr. Jiuhuo
If you want to kill me
You would have done it before
But if you use fire
I will not be able to defeat you
Okay.
Take the sword.
Let's fight again.
The soul of the heart.
If you die here,
your consciousness will also sink forever.
There is no difference between living and dead.
Then why don't you fight?
If there is a person among us who must die,
that person won't be you.
So,
you are willing to die for me?
I won't die for you.
I want us to live together.
Come with me to a place.
Where is this?
We were here before.
We saw the sunset together.
The sunset today
is falling so fast.
It will be better if it lasts a little longer.
If you think the sunset is short,
next time,
let's watch the stars together.
Okay.
The Sunset
You...
What do you remember?
I...
I remember.
Remember?
What?
This is...
I remember.
This is your place.
This is your place to die.
Remember,
you are the bad guy from the East.
I must not believe Jiuhuo.
Wang Quanhongye,
Lord Jiuhuo,
I don't believe anyone.
I only believe myself.
How is he?
He...
was killed by you in the illusion.
He will be in a dream forever.
He won't wake up again.
What?
You don't want to?
How come?
He has already died.
In the end, his own life is more important.
Sister,
you have to look forward.
I have already won.
Can I go out now?
Sister,
look at the scenery here with me.
I am not a corpse.
I am just a shadow left by the demon
when Jialan left the Sky Mountain.
I am about to disappear.
When I disappear,
the barrier of the Sky Mountain
will be broken.
It's interesting to see the scenery.
I want to hear
the story of you and Lord Jiuhuo.
Why?
You are not like the kind of person who likes to ask questions.
Because
we are alike.
And I want to know
if Lord Jiuhuo is worth following me.
Of course.
Lord Jiuhuo is the only one
who loves us in this world.
The only one?
Your appearance
is very pleasing to the eye.
That's because
I was born evil.
According to the legend,
you were born
a bad fox.
You probably know that
there is a huge bitter love tree in our Mountain.
The most powerful fox demons in our Mountain
have no parents
and are born from bitter love trees.
It is said that I was born
different from other fox demons.
My body is black.
My power is very strong.
I turned into a human when I was ten years old.
I was born different from those fox demons
who like flowers and grass.
The elders of Mount Tushan
soon found out my difference.
They pushed the image
and calculated my fate.
They said that I was born evil
who was born out of the grudge of the heaven and earth.
I will destroy the heaven and earth in the future.
So they sent me
to a love-trap beyond Mount Tushan
and set up a trap
and gave me a seed of bitter love tree.
They lied to me that
as long as I could plant a bitter love tree,
I could be free.
In the end,
I planted a black bitter love tree
with my hatred.
My power also grew
with this black tree.
I am waiting for them in the love trap.
I want to tell them something.
I will revenge
those who hurt me.
Who are you?
You killed
all these demons?
Interesting.
But
many fox demons will come to kill you soon.
I am the heaven demon Jiuhuo of the imperial family.
Come with me.
Do you think they deserve to die?
No.
That's good.
In addition to Lord Jiuhuo,
there is another person waiting for me.
They want to imprison me for life.
Why can't I kill them all?
What happened after that?
Why are you left with only the shadow?
I am the god of death.
Did Lord Jiuhuo repair the Golden Pond
for you?
There are many problems.
But I have no time.
You are going to disappear.
Lord Jiuhuo just looks at you like this.
He promised me.
He doesn't want to see me disappear.
We will meet again.
That's good.
Instead of letting you disappear,
why don't you give me your power?
What a pity.
I like to listen to stories.
But I am never moved by other people's stories.
The red night of death.
The moment I died,
it was quite beautiful.
The Golden Pond
Lord Jiuhuo.
What happened?
The broken pieces of the Golden Pond
still lack one piece.
I deserve to die.
A water drug has been with me for a long time.
I don't know why it still remains.
It has been thrown away from the Golden Pond.
Such a big thing happened.
You tell me now.
Seven Star Pearl will end in a few days.
Don't worry, sir.
I have sent people to search the city.
I will find it soon.
If you can't find it,
I will use you to make up for it.
Yes.
Is the Left Guardian back?
Yes, he is in the room.
The Red Night of Death
Who is it?
Miss, what do you want?
Miss. Miss.
Miss, I didn't mean to do that.
I just disturbed you.
I am really sorry.
I just want to ask you for directions.
Miss.
Water Spirit Eye?
Miss, you are a medical doctor from the Demon Realm.
You are from the Water Tribe.
Tian Eye?
Where are you going?
Miss, please tell me how to get to the Golden Pond.
Miss, what's wrong?
Why are you going to the Golden Pond?
Do you have to go there?
Because there are some things
I have to go there to figure it out.
So, please don't bother me.
Go five miles north from here.
Ten miles west.
Then go north to a village.
Then ten miles east. Then you will...
Miss, can you slow down a little bit?
Go three miles east.
Thank you.
Why did she leave?
Thank you, Miss.
You have to remember that you are the owner of the Eastern Region.
You must not believe in the Nine Deadly Sins.
Why am I exactly the same as that Jialan's demon?
Very good. I am very satisfied.
Who is Jialan exactly?
What is she satisfied with?
Since you are back, why didn't you come to see me?
Are you angry that I didn't save you from the barrier of the Sky Mountain?
How could that be?
You only trusted me.
And I saw the old brother of your master there.
I saw your former disciple, Jialan.
That's just a shadow.
But the demon's body is clearly the same as Jialan's shadow.
Shouldn't you give me an explanation?
In the chaos of the Demon-Killing Method,
when I picked you up, you were in a state of panic.
I used Jialan's demon power to enter your body.
But his demon power is too strong.
After you regained your demon power, you forgot the past.
Then what was my identity before I lost my memory?
Is it possible that I really know Wang Quanhong?
I don't know that.
But the human race has always been greedy for demon power.
To get and control the demon, to play with the emperor.
You should know that.
I won't believe it.
It's just...
Just what?
Your power is boundless.
You must be happy to be with Jialan.
I'm curious about your story.
Since I took Jialan as my disciple,
the dragon tribe and the Tushan tribe have been fighting against me.
In this battle, my demon core has been destroyed.
But he actually fought alone for me.
I'm a demon of all kinds.
What's my grudge against you?
Let's go.
He took the dragon elixir back and used it to repair my demon power.
We all realized that we are each other's only.
But it's been a long time since we found out that 500 years ago,
Jialan was able to drive away the dark forces of the demons
and was taken by the Yuyang State's Chief.
They set up a trap to destroy me.
In order to save me, Jialan came to the Yuyang State's underground palace.
500 years ago, in the underground palace of the Yuyang State,
what happened between you and Jialan?
Jialan!
This memory is something I never want to forget.
In short, everything I do now is to save Jialan.
You mean Jialan is still alive?
Of course.
But she's blocked outside the circle and can't come in.
It's a pity that I'm not Jialan. I can't help you.
It's okay. Jialan is Jialan and you are you.
You just have to be yourself.
There's nothing else to think about.
As for that Wang Quan Hong Yi...
He's already dead.
A man who's been digging and practicing swords and holding on to the blood of the Yi Qimeng clan.
He just wants to get my power.
He's not going to die.
All of this is in the past.
You don't have to think about it.
Yes, my Lord Jiuhuo.
I can't be left out in your eyes.
I'm falling again.