Go to Nanjing healing stage
I'm sorry.
Huai Che.
You're back.
Dongfang Huai Zhu.
Jiuhuo.
I, Dongfang Huai Zhu,
was not born for the Black Tiger.
You will regret
for luring me to Bilo City.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
I swear
to become Dongfang Huai Zhu.
Jiuhuo.
You must bow to your master.
Brother, you're awake.
Where's Huaizhu?
Really?
I sent for a mission
I need to take medicine
Is Lord Wenxin here?
В tutor
Who'sInaudible
At this time,
なら
Пушли
Пупы
when I saw you all alone,
I almost nearly fell dead.
ceremonies of
It's me.
Dongfang Huaizhu.
Brother.
We won this battle.
Where's Mu Mian?
He's injured.
His spirit energy has been exhausted.
But he should be fine.
Miss Cuiyu is taking care of him.
After Brother Ling has repaired the Golden Lotus,
we can go back.
But how are you going to deal with the wine and goods?
The wine and goods are immortal.
It was sealed before.
We brought it back to 20 years ago.
We sealed it again.
fourth brother
Huaizhu
What are you doing insectism?
I'm sincere.
I'll appear before Brother Ling in 10 years.
Yuxuan,
it has to start now.
Be fast.
Okay, I'm laughing very hard.
Do you think you can get away with this?
Let's go.
Give me your hand.
Your hand is a little cold.
Warm it up for me.
It's warm.
Is it warmer?
You've been in many battles.
Your internal organs are seriously damaged.
You need to take care of it after you go back.
Huai Zhu,
I want to understand two things about this battle.
The first thing is that I want to apologize to you.
I didn't tell you the truth.
I didn't mean to hide my dual identity from you.
I just want to tell you when the time is right.
And the second thing is that
I don't want to make the appointment for the seventh month of the first month.
In the Yang family,
we've said that we'll never meet again.
Young Master Wang Quan,
please stay.
The seventh month of the first month,
the water will be the roof,
let's be friends.
So,
you want to see me
only at the seventh month of the first month of each year?
Of course not.
Don't tell me
you're SUBSCRIBE toJessica's big video.
Are you tricking me?
Have this medicine.
I'm sorry.
But
there's still some inner energy
and soul fragments in my body.
The Black Fox is so cruel.
If we really break it,
the consequences will be unimaginable.
We can't sleep anyway.
Let's go out and take a walk.
Let's go and see
the world twenty years later.
I never thought this street was so far away
because of people and demons
praying together.
Whether it's people or demons,
everyone wants the same thing.
Bless my father.
May he be healthy.
Brother Neg meus altando estava dulcemente.
Mother too.
They are all in despair
trying to find hope
to choose this life
as a いordinary thing.
People
and the demons
are all living against their own will,
whether they receive anything in return.
The Make a Wish
There's no sleeping pill.
He talks so loudly about快乐的事.
Finally you slept soundly.
After you conjunto to fix the magic device,
we can go back.
I...
I'm afraid.
Hongye.
I have a question for you.
In order to save me,
why did you do this?
I've never thought about it.
What if the result is not as you wish?
Then what have you thought about?
I can't lose you.
You're not the only one.
I'm not afraid of the cold.
How sad
I'm not willing to be with you for the rest of my life
I don't care if you're in the
is should dress商 size
知我者 依潭哥 也
do you think we are currentkas
John
Dare to go
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Isn't this how we usually drink?
Really?
Then why do I feel that today is very different?
Let me count.
The first time was when we were in the mud.
The second time was when we were in the sky.
There were so many times when we were in the sky.
And then we had a mission.
Xiao Mei.
Another mission?
Yitan, do you remember when we were young,
my father would hold you like that.
He would walk up to me and say,
you are my future husband.
Of course I remember.
But that day, you stole the rice wine from home.
You immediately started drinking.
You chased me and scolded me and bit me.
You still wouldn't marry me.
It was all when we were young.
Yitan, you were so young.
You were so young.
Yitan was always very nice to me.
He always made me feel at ease.
He even made me feel a sense of foreboding.
What sense of foreboding?
Do you like me?
Of course I like you.
Because you are my sister.
Xiao Mei.
Fourth Brother.
What is it?
Nothing.
It's just that I haven't seen you in a long time.
I want to see you more.
You can't hide your feelings.
Just tell me what you want to say.
I think...
There are some things...
You have the right to know.
These are all after my brother died.
These are all letters from Miss Huizhuai to you after my brother died.
Huizhuai?
It's Dongfeng Huizhuo that you kept in the spring after you were out of power.
Every year on your death day,
he would bring the letter to your coffin.
I decided to keep these letters.
There are not many letters.
Because...
Ten years after you were out of power,
he died.
Brother.
Don't you want to see it?
Brother,
don't you want to see it?
I don't want to see it.
I believe that
fate can be changed,
and the future can be seen.
This is definitely not the end of Dongfeng and I.
You are here to laugh at me.
You lost.
You clearly know that
as long as there is evil in the world,
the black-bone love tree will be destroyed.
You are not a man.
You are a man.
The black-bone love tree will always be there.
My Jialan will definitely come back.
Of course I know that
the evil thoughts in the world will never be eliminated.
No matter how hard we try.
You are afraid.
Likewise,
you can't stop the light.
The light of the black-bone love tree
is like this moment.
The arrows in our hands
will pierce your chest deeply
and make you afraid.
Even if we fall,
the future people will know
that you are not weak.
I believe that
as long as there are people holding swords,
there will be a day when the world will be clear.
No.
I will kill all the people holding swords first.
I
will definitely kill you.
Come on, Brother 4th.
It's really been a long time
since we had such a fast drinking.
Are you happy?
I should say this.
The wine I drink alone
in the Poting Temple
is bitter.
To the meeting.
To the farewell.
To reunion, to farewell.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Actually, thinking about it,
this wine store is a bit sentimental.
It's not worth sympathizing
for the personal feelings of the two of you.
Please.
You humans are really funny.
I think he is not wrong at all.
As long as the people I like can be free and comfortable,
I don't care about the others.
Love is hard to mention.
Let's just pass this topic.
Yes.
No matter what,
he lost.
My brother is right.
Let's drink to the end.
Cheers.
Your mother loves this fish the most.
Try it.
My mother often mentioned you to me.
She was obsessed with it.
You look like your mother.
Really?
Come on.
Mu Min.
You haven't recovered yet.
I'll drink this for her.
I'll drink it for her.
I'll drink the next cup for Mu Min.
Actually,
the small chain will be repaired soon.
Once the small chain is opened,
you can all go back.
I'll be here alone.
Brother.
Didn't we agree that
we would change everything?
We would all be alive.
The Pottian Temple
won't be so cold and quiet.
It won't be so dark and gloomy.
The mountains will be covered with water and the land will be barren.
The whole foot step will be covered with water and the land will be barren.
Great.
Our Brother Tao Jisi is back.
Come on.
The mask troupe that was established 20 years ago,
and us after 20 years,
all the unhappiness and pain
will all pass.
Cheers.
Mu Min.
Miss Huai Zhu, how is my brother?
His body is broken in five ways.
His meridians are broken.
He was injured in a battle of wine and fire.
Impossible.
He was fine just now.
It's just that his stomach hurts a little.
He's not sick at all.
Right.
This child is just like Mu Xiaowu.
He's not saying anything.
Is there any way to cure him?
Yes.
What medicine do you need?
I'll think of a way to get it.
Cuiyu,
your water quality is good.
You can use medical skills to build a factory.
I have no other way to do it now.
Please save him.
Okay?
I'll go.
Prepare another room for me.
No one can come and disturb me.
I couldn't protect Mu Xiaowu before.
Can't I protect Yan's son?
Huai Zhu.
Yitan.
Don't blame yourself.
No matter what,
we've seen his medical skills.
We'll talk about it after Mu Mei is cured.
Cuiyu.
You know I can't cure him.
I can't do anything
about your medical skills.
Lan Yan.
Come out.
Come out!
Lan Yan.
I know you're here.
Come out!
If you don't come out,
Xiaomian will die.
He will die.
Do you know that?
What are you doing?
It's your turn to repay me.
I want you to sleep forever.
Don't wake up again.
All along,
we shared a body.
I was the only one
who could live.
I sealed Lan Yan
and took over the body.
I can't replace him.
If I want to replace Lan Yan again,
I have to disappear
and return the body to him.
Only in this way
can I save Xiaomian.
From the beginning to the end,
you love Lan Yan.
You love Lan Yan.
So I'm the one who's in need of you, right?
Xiaomian,
since when
did I start to like you?
Maybe
since you asked me
to be your girlfriend.
I was fooled.
What's so good about Xiaomian?
She's stupid and dumb.
But I still can't help
falling in love with you.
When I see you
talking to another woman,
I'll be angry.
Every time I see you,
I just want to scold you.
But why don't you understand
that I scold you
because I want to hear your reply?
Xiaomian,
I know
I'm arrogant and domineering.
I can't control myself.
I'm sorry.
If I force you,
you'll be unhappy, right?
So
I'm leaving.
From now on,
I'll let your favorite Lan Yan
stay with you.
Okay?
You sleep for a while.
Your Lan Yan
will be here soon.
The bright and bright sea of stars
is not the place to come back.
How can you see it clearly
that the flowers and flowers are blooming?
Like the wind and the flow of the wind.
It turns out that time has changed.
You and I have agreed to wait.
The wind and the flow of the wind
is not the place to come back.
I'll return your favorite person now.
But
you can't forget me.
Don't turn back and go.
The light is like a flash of light.
I like you.
It's you, Miss Houyuan.
What...
What did you say?
I like your domineering.
I like your straightforwardness.
I like you to tell me
everything you think.
You're not afraid of anything.
You don't care about anything.
You're the most
free person I've ever seen.
Although
sometimes
you're unreasonable,
I've never hated you.
I like you to scold me.
I don't mean I don't want to get back at you.
It's just...
It's just that
when I looked into your eyes,
my heart
was beating so fast.
All the words in my heart
I don't know how to tell you.
You asked me
who I liked.
You asked me to think about it.
I don't need to think about it.
I like you.
It's always you.
Why?
Why is it so late
in this world?
No.
No, Miss.
No matter how late it is,
it's always you.
Little Cucumber.
Thank you for cheering me up.
I've been here
and never loved you.
No.
Jin Chen Xi is complete.
As I expected,
Hong Yan gave up on himself.
I
didn't fail.
Save me.
Think about everything that happened in the underworld.
Think about the Jialan who killed you.
It's just to get out of Long Wen Xi's heart.
Don't let me down.
Jin Chen Xi is waiting for you.
Kim Rocky, Jin Chen Xi is waiting for you.
Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi
Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi
Jin Chen Xi, Jin Chen Xi,
then being left behind.