IIIIII IIIIII IIIIII IIII II IIIIII II I don't play
That moon sponsored a drop of white
Hurry up and turn me into asa
The pain of the human brain
I'm sorry.
Episode 15
Ladies, the yard is ready.
Take a seat.
I'll take you there.
I didn't expect that Miss Dongfang
would come to the Demon Kingdom.
Did you tell her
that you were here to investigate the Black Lake?
She should have guessed it.
But the key to the question is
the first clue I found
is about Miss Dongfang's mother,
Jiang Juanxue.
She is the Saintess of the Northern Mountain Sect.
And the origin of the Northern Mountain Sect and the Black Lake
is closely related.
This is the yard
that you wanted.
It's a little rough.
But it's in a good location.
It's a good view.
Thank you.
The person you're looking for
is a little special.
Please be careful.
Goodbye.
Sister.
I like it here.
It's not bad.
But I didn't expect
that the Crown Prince
would come to the Demon Kingdom.
He just saved us.
I know.
So I'm grateful to them.
And I didn't laugh at them.
Qinglan.
Why don't you ask
why I brought you to the Demon Kingdom?
Why should I ask?
You did the right thing.
Do you believe me?
Of course.
You're the only one
in my heart.
I'll go out for a walk.
I want to get familiar with the environment.
The previous owner of the Dream Tower, Er Zhuyu,
died of assassination a year ago.
He was killed.
The current owner's identity is unknown.
General Xue trained a woman
named Er Zhuyu.
She was the owner of the Dream Tower.
She was?
Yes.
She died a year ago.
After Er Zhuyu died,
something should have stayed in the Dream Tower.
Who is the current owner?
The current owner of the Dream Tower
is very mysterious.
No one knows about it.
I've sent someone to investigate.
We'll get news in a few days.
But now the clues are broken.
Yuyao Valley has closed the city gate.
The current situation
is really unfavorable for us.
Who leaked the news to Yuyao Valley?
Useless!
It's been three days since we closed the gate.
We can't even find a shadow.
Can the red leaves of the dead spring
grow wings and fly?
Maybe the news of the dead spring
is fake.
The red leaves of the dead spring
didn't come at all.
Useless!
You're lying.
What good can it do?
Tell Ananyan to come to the palace.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
You don't need to summon me.
I'm here.
Okay.
I've put a lot of effort into it
to make you the State Preceptor.
Why?
Because you told me in person
that you wanted to take the head of the red leaves
to repay me.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
The people who assassinated the red leaves
have already left.
I'll wait and see.
Step aside!
I'll go down and see.
Wait for me here.
Someone has reported to Ruyi Pavilion
that the people who hid the Yiqi Alliance...
Search!
Search every room!
Yes!
Young Master Wang Xuan.
Boss Qingmu told me
to take you out of the back door.
I'll go to the back door.
Yes.
The Sword is a fake?
If he was used to assassinate the people
in the previous episode,
no one in the Yiqi Alliance
would be able to resist.
Didn't Fifth Sister
receive any news
about the master
who came to the Demon Kingdom?
Fifth Sister.
I'm here.
I'm sorry.
I was careless.
I don't blame you.
Since my whereabouts have been exposed,
I can't stay in Ruyi Pavilion anymore.
Is it dangerous
for you, Fifth Sister?
Don't worry.
I'll just say that you're my big brother.
Qingmu's family has been doing business
in the Demon Kingdom for so many years.
They still have a way out.
Lingyi should be back soon.
Make another identity card
for us.
The identity card of the Demon Kingdom
is made of stone.
The mine is controlled by the master.
I finally got two pieces
and was used to save people.
Fifth Sister, you
must have a way.
I do have a way.
The demon in Demon Kingdom
is the property of the Demon Master.
No need for an identity card.
You want us to be demons?
If we want to stay in the Demon Kingdom
and investigate,
there's only one way left.
It's not a problem
to make a demon pill
for Lingyi.
But who should we be demons for?
What do you think?
The Demon Lord
Dongfang Huizhuo.
Do you think you can get away?
I've been integrated with you for a long time.
And now
I'm just being suppressed for the time being.
If he was used in an assassination just now,
no one should be able to hear the whole thing.
Was it you?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're hurt.
It's seriously hurt.
It's okay.
Why would you live in such a shabby place?
I'm used to it.
You're the master of the Zhang family.
Why are you so selfish?
Where are you going?
I'm looking for food.
Ran.
Wang Xuanhong is still alive.
I'll find another chance.
Don't call me by that name again.
Dongburn.
D'oussaint-Nua has died.
Please come in.
Hey.
Why can they go in?
Why can't we go in?
You don't even know the rules of the Dream House.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
What rules are there in the Dream House?
If you don't have a substitute,
you're not qualified to participate in the Tear-Demon Competition.
What is the Tear-Demon Competition?
This is the place where the Demon-Python Master
plays the Tear-Demon Competition.
It's good that you know.
If you want to enter the Dream House,
you must participate in the Tear-Demon Competition.
Otherwise, you won't get in.
Let's go.
I'll go.
You two.
Please come in.
It's okay, big sister.
I'll go catch two little demons tomorrow.
Then we can go in.
What?
Where did you get the snacks?
Miss Huizhu, you're back.
I'm not a human.
Why don't you say hello to me?
Nice to meet you, Master Qin Lan.
Who is your master?
You're back.
The meal will be ready soon.
So,
you two are here to help us?
Cooperation?
That's called cooperation.
Mind your words.
I don't want to cooperate with you.
Wait, how did you...
Qin Lan.
So you came here
to investigate the Black Tiger, right?
Yes.
But I don't know why
your identity was exposed
and your whereabouts were leaked.
Your brother was assassinated in Ruyi Pavilion.
Did he get hurt?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Then stay.
There's a care center in Yiqi.
Sister, it's not a care center.
It's a care center.
You've said it.
We're here to take care of you.
Qi Chu.
Well,
Mr. Han.
What's the matter?
we will become the real medicine.
You'd better be a human first.
I'll stop pretending then.
The second son of the Tao Yuan family, Li Qu Zhuo.
Sit down and focus.
Okay, Brother Lei.
I can be a demon.
A demon?
Qu Zhuo can be a demon?
That's amazing.
Of course.
When Qingmu Yuan sends the Demon King blood,
I can get it out.
We can eat it and become demons.
Then, Sister-in-law, you...
You're so good at this.
I'm not a demon.
I'm a human.
You...
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, you can wait and see.
Okay.
But there's no bedroom.
Where do you live?
We can clean up the woodshed.
We'll live in the woodshed.
You clean it up?
I...
I clean it up.
The recent research of the Demon Kingdom
only found that two bottles of demon blood were used.
One bottle is snake demon,
and the other is dog demon.
Brother, do you know
what will happen if you take the blood of the Demon King?
Don't worry. I have you.
I'll use my brain to separate the demon from the demon.
It won't be a problem.
It's not as simple as you think.
Once you take the blood of the demon,
you can't use your power.
You can only use your power.
And the blood of the demon will also be affected.
Maybe it will become a fatal weakness of you.
Especially the snake demon.
Its biggest weakness is that it is extremely cold.
Once it enters the desert,
it will become extremely fragile.
The demon will be released in ten days.
Don't worry.
Give me the snake demon.
Dog demon, mine.
It smells good.
Enough.
I can't control you two.
I'll go back first.
Qu Zhu, this will definitely...
Don't worry.
I won't let sister-in-law know about this.
Let's go.
I've already put the blood of the Demon King
that Miss Qingmu sent in.
You're making a fuss.
Isn't it just swallowing the blood of the demon?
What do you know?
I used the gourd to peel off the demon's blood
and then I purified the demon's blood
until it was clear and like a glass.
You won't lose your nature, will you?
Don't worry, Miss Qingmu.
The demon will be released in ten days.
Although we can't use our power,
we can still use the power of the demon.
Right.
And ten days
is enough for us to complete the task of the Demon Valley.
What is this medicine?
The purple one is snake demon's.
The silver one is dog demon's.
The Demon Lord will be excited after the midnight.
By then,
as long as we relax,
there will be no problem.
Okay.
Let's wait and see.
In the autumn in the Demon Kingdom,
it's really scary to live in Wen Cha.
Why haven't those two come out yet?
After all, it's the Demon King's season.
It always takes some time.
I'm worried about them.
It's obvious that they are low in materiality.
We can't use them.
Young Master Li
has finally become a great man.
Li Gou.
It's really you.
Sister.
It seems that the demon can't make people smarter.
I think Young Master Wang Quan
may not be as good as this little dog.
I'll go and check.
Okay.
Li Gou.
afford me.
I'm puzzle- Ass Doncs.
Wu!
Didn't you say it was a monster?
We don't know how to get to it.
He has the spirit of a snake
but he's not fully enjoying it yet.
Qinglan, help me carry him shoe.
I don't need to.
Gitong, carry him.
Should I say someone who puts outwerws
Yes
Here
Junior Lee
Come out
I- I...
ihten-
Z ble
I...
Li Gou, Li Gou.
How old is this dog that you're still peeing on the bed?
That...
Are you hungry?
Hungry.
Come.
I think the kitchen is just for these things.
I can only make a sour and spicy soup.
Tomorrow, I'll go out and buy some meat.
We'll make pork, meat, and green onion cabbage.
My sister doesn't like pork and meat.
Then let's make green onion and pork.
You...
You dog.
Three pieces. Three pieces will do.
I didn't think you could cook.
Of course not. Our noodles...
I...
I cook with my friends.
Even my brother can only help me.
What is this?
It's so cool.
Okay.
Then forgive me for peeing on the bed last night.
I'm a talented person.
I can make a medicine quickly.
Where's my brother? How is he?
What?
Is there something wrong with me?
No.
How did I fall asleep last night?
I don't remember.
You didn't sleep at all last night.
But your inner heart is still very confused.
I'm sorry.
You need to take care of yourself.
You...
I'm going to the pharmacy for a checkup.
I need to get in touch with more people and monsters.
I also need to learn how to find out more information.
I'll go out with you.
I have an appointment with someone today.
You?
Don't worry. Once it's over, I'll go to the place for a checkup and find you.
Let's go home together.
Sister, let's eat!
Let's go.
Sister, I'll go with you to the doctor's office later.
I'll go with your sister.
You don't even know how to walk. How are you going to go?
I can control myself.
Also, Miss Qin Lan,
I have a favor to ask of you.
The demon elixir in Qu Zhuo's body hasn't fully melted yet.
You need to take care of and train people.
And Miss Qin Lan, you are talented and smart.
You have high magical power.
The most important thing is that you are kind and patient.
I wonder if you can help Qu Zhuo.
Help Qu Zhuo?
Yes.
Help Qu Zhuo.
But your demon elixir hasn't fully melted yet.
If you go, it's a gamble.
This...
You can control water?
I just adjusted my waist a little bit.
I did it.
It seems that the way the demon elixir is made is different.
Then, Qin Lan,
what is the effect of Li Shao Zhu's elixir?
It's a very strong elixir.
Then, Qin Lan,
can you take care of Li Shao Zhu?
Master,
I really need your help.
Thank you, Miss Qin Lan.
Uncle Huai, let's go.
My brother just...
Water...
That's it?
Brother is really a brother.
A good person always shows his talent.
Then, Mr. Li of the Tao Yuan family,
what is your demon elixir?
I...
My demon elixir...
You are a dog, right?
Damn it.
I have good news for everyone.
Miss Er Zhu said
that people and demons can be treated for free.
You don't have to be afraid.
You can come in and see the doctor.
There really is a free doctor for demons.
Thank you, Miss Er Zhu.
Hurry and go in.
Is it true?
It's true.
Don't lie to us.
Come in.
Hurry and go in.
Go.
Prince of Bumu,
long time no see.
How are you?
Young Master Wang Quan,
you...
Thanks to you, everything is fine.
That's good.
This outfit you are wearing,
you must have some kind of mission, right?
To be honest,
I came here to ask you for a favor.
You once gave me a gift in the snow.
I will never forget it.
It's okay to say it.
I want to know
what happened to Jiuhuo and Black Tiger
in the Demon Kingdom back then.
There is also the Saint of Beishan Sect, Jiang Juan Xue,
the master of the Drunken Dream House he trained.
How did Zhu Yu die?
This underground palace was once the altar of the Beishan Sect.
Five hundred years ago,
the Heaven Demon Jiuhuo was sealed here.
Jiuhuo was sealed by the Beishan Sect.
Why was she sealed?
I don't know the details.
Young Master, please come with me to a place.
We have arrived.
This is the secret room of the State of the Demon Kingdom.
This is not an ordinary barrier.
It's not a barrier that can be broken.
But this barrier
was also set by the Beishan Sect during the Ding Sheng period.
It's the Beishan Sect again.
I got news that
the Beishan Sect is related to the origin of Black Tiger.
So,
there might be something that the Young Master needs here.
How can I get in?
Only the Chief of the State can enter with the seal.
What if I find the Beishan Sect?
The Beishan Sect has been destroyed
after the death of Er Zhu Yu.
Destroyed?
Er Zhu Yu was assassinated?
Yes.
Did he leave anything behind?
After you said that,
it's really strange that he died.
Er Zhu Yu was the most fierce Tower Master in his life.
After he died,
the most fierce Tear Demon Festival
became more and more frequent.
Tear Demon Festival?
It's over.
What is it?
A cake.
Did you get anything today?
Not much.
They say that the Drunken Dream Tower is a small and quiet place.
It's heavily guarded.
Except for the Tear Demon Festival,
people and people are not allowed to enter.
Let's go eat something.
Maybe love
is blooming in the heart
So love
is in the heart
Did you take the medicine?
What do you think?
The love is coming, don't be hasty
Just change your heart
Don't be afraid to change your mind
Just face the love that hides you
I don't want to be loved
When the eyes meet
We will be sure that we will not
cherish each other
Maybe love
is blooming in the heart
So love
is in the heart
Maybe love
Your heart is broken.
If we separate,
we can still love each other
Then each piece is yours.
Shake hands.
You're so good.
Come, congratulations on your promotion.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Qizhu, what are you doing?
Sister.
Brother.
I just want to stimulate his power.
I just tried the fire.
I just want to use some primitive methods.
Okay, I don't practice.
Go to cook.
You've been practicing for a day.
He asked me to cook now.
Who told you to meddle in the affairs of the world?
Don't talk nonsense.
Okay, no cooking today.
Huizhu and I
bought your favorite roasted chicken.
Roasted chicken?
Give it to me.
Li Gong.
I found that the fourth brother met his younger sister.
It's really a star.
They two
had a good time.
Do you want to consider
telling him that you are the mask?
What I'm worried about is that
the mask group is so powerful
that it's the only thing that can't be tolerated.
So I still think that
it's better not to know.
Look at him now.
How nice.
Then wait a little longer.
When you think it's right,
you can tell me.
I found something
after coming to the Demon Kingdom.
What is it?
Black Tiger Demon Cove.
Did the
Internet of Life and Death not evolve?
It seems that
it was just temporarily suppressed.
The demon core of Black Tiger is still in my body.
It may be re-invented at any time.
I came here for this.
Actually, my mother left me a clue in the letter.
She asked me to go to the Drunken Dream House
to find someone named Er Zhu Yu.
I must get the West Martial Arts.
Er Zhu Yu was assassinated.
You know that?
When I got the news,
Er Zhu Yu and your mother
are from the Northern Mountain Sect.
The Northern Mountain Sect
is related to the origin of Black Tiger.
But now the Northern Mountain Sect
has been destroyed.
Black Tiger and Northern Mountain Sect?
I also met Prince of Bumu today.
He also mentioned
the most ridiculous thing you said just now.
He said that after Er Zhu Yu died,
the Thunder Demon Competition in the building
was held more and more frequently.
It's unusual.
It seems that the Drunken Dream House
is the key.
The wind blows like a wind,
the clouds stop like a cloud,
the
sky is clear,
the clouds stop like a cloud,
The sky is full of stars.
I look up and see
the years and years.
I look at the stars and see the bright stars.
I fall in love with you as if we first met.
I have so many times to rub my shoulders.