't worry there's nothing that will not let you off
Love and hate are both
Flowing
With tears as the wind
The sky is as deep as the boat
Don't turn back and keep walking
Life and death are in front of you
From the fire to the fire
Whose love
Is more vast than the universe
Don't turn back and keep walking
Life and death are in front of you
From the fire to the fire
Whose love
Is more vast than the universe
It's me
The Long Ballad
The Noblest Man In The Water
Episode 1
Go!
A'Cui, look at this.
Brother Yi, thank you for coming to see me.
Here.
The dance is ahead.
Let's go and have a look.
Good.
There's more.
Boy, this is difficult.
No.
Good!
Brother Yitang, I like you!
You're pretty good! Look!
Good!
You're talking to me?
Brother Yitang, I like you!
I'm not asking for money because of your kindness and tolerance.
Trust and respect.
You also protect me.
You stand for me.
You also silently stand behind me.
I feel that every day,
I feel very excited when I'm with you.
I won't give such a good you
to someone else.
I know what you're thinking.
No matter what happens in the future,
I will be confident to face it with you.
Even if we're together for a year,
a month, a day,
I just want to be with you.
Brother Yitang,
are you willing to give me this chance?
I'm willing to give you this chance.
What is the reason for my desire?
What should I do?
I feel like I'm having a daughter.
If Yang Yi is not good to her,
I'll break her legs.
He's our second brother.
You can beat him.
The fireworks are so good.
Yes.
The fireworks will make the atmosphere better.
If only my brother were here.
Why didn't you say anything?
You have a daughter.
What do you think?
Who put the fireworks?
I don't think it was arranged by Qingmu.
Yes.
Who is so talented?
Oh, you're the only one I'm in love with
It looks smooth.
Your fireworks are also friendships.
I really appreciate it.
Then in return,
you can money it with me.
Oh, you're the only one I'm in love with
I'm still lonely next to you
Oh, you know I won't be weak
I fell in love with you, the warmest start
The day I knew the end
The night is cold as water
I see the star of the female bird
I remember the first one who told me the story
It must be a gentle person
It's my mother
Her name is also nice
Jiang Juanxue
A very poetic name
Yes
Although she has died for many years
I can't remember some things clearly
But every time I see the star
I will remember her
Remember what she told me
I remember those words
A'Zhu
Look at the stars in the sky
How beautiful
Although the weather is bad tonight
But wait for the wind to pass
The stars will still come out
The stars are coming out
Maybe one day
Darkness will take over your life
But you must believe
There will be a star
Light up your way
My mother left me a puzzle
I have to find the answer
Do you need me to help you?
This is what I have to face
What are you laughing at?
You seem to be suspicious of me today
Are you leaving too?
I will leave for a long time
But you don't have to worry
I will come back before the end of the summer
I won't worry
Because in this world
There is someone who can kill you
I want you
I'm going to the Demon Realm
What's up?
Miss, you told me
If there is any information about Zhang Zheng's family
I must report it to you as soon as possible
What information?
Zhang's family dressed up and entered the Demon Kingdom
Demon Kingdom?
How many demons do you have?
You?
See
This is already the third time during this month
This month, the demon kingdom
what's the case?
and mountains, like that
ladies
Is Zhang Zhang's family's importance to you?
Do you want to say something?
He never showed up
when we came to the brothel.
He wasn't like this before.
When we were in the same window,
he was nice to me.
He saved my life once.
Why isn't he here yet?
He's just ahead.
This place doesn't look like
a place where the flowers bloom.
Did you make a mistake?
No.
What are you doing?
We're in the same window. Stop it.
Miss Qingmu,
aren't you amazing?
No one can see you.
Without light,
I'll see how you get out of this dreamy formation.
Let's go.
Stop!
Don't go!
Father!
Mother!
Miss Qingmu, are you okay?
I'm here to save you.
The wound is broken.
Don't be afraid.
I'll take you out.
Let's go.
These are all the flowers of your inner fear.
Don't be afraid.
I'll protect you.
I'm here.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Thank you, Zhang Tongchuan.
Our Tongchuan has been here for many years.
Although he doesn't talk much,
he's very nice to me.
He's a very nice person.
What happened later?
Later,
he became the master of Zhang Zheng's family.
Since then,
he's changed a lot.
You've seen it.
I've become the master of Ruyi Pavilion.
He invited me as the owner of the building.
He rejected all of them.
Why?
I don't know.
He's ruthless and I'm a coward.
Miss, you don't have to mind him.
There are many people who admire our Miss.
But I just can't let him go.
When you're young,
sometimes it's your whole life.
Zhang Zheng,
what are you going to do
in the Demon Kingdom?
It's your turn, Brother San.
Brother San, look at this.
It's not easy.
Brother San,
this time you went to the Demon Kingdom
to investigate the Black Lake.
I'm afraid you can't.
Do you want to tell Sister Huai Zhu?
She has something important to do.
I don't want to bother her.
How is it?
I'm good, right?
You two just got together.
You have to separate.
Can you do it?
How about
you go back and accompany your sister-in-law?
I'll go with Brother Yi Tan.
What Xiaomei said makes sense.
Have you arranged
the people who will take over the Demon Kingdom?
Don't worry, Brother.
I've arranged the best one.
Who?
Me.
You?
The head of the Demon Kingdom
has always been angry with Brother.
If this mission is not done well,
it will reveal Brother's whereabouts.
So I decided
to take the role of the head of the Demon Kingdom
to separate the Demon Kingdom.
The sun is coming out from the south today.
Miss Qingmu is going to take the role.
Can't you?
Well...
But I heard that
the Demon Kingdom is very far away.
And the weather is very dry.
It's not good for your skin care.
Don't worry.
I've thought about it.
And my rouge and water powder
are on the way.
You have to get up early for the mission.
If I get up early,
is there anyone more suitable than you?
It's decided.
I'll go to the Demon Kingdom to explore the way.
When you arrive,
someone will pick up.
I'm leaving.
You're leaving?
Yes.
Yitan,
you just saw something with your eyes.
It's not normal for Sister Qingmu.
Qingmu can do things without worry.
Before I go to the Demon Kingdom,
I have one last big thing to do.
Yang Yitan.
I'm sorry.
Yitan,
what are you doing?
It's Bien,
he's lying outside.
Yitan,
Alright,
I don't put up with it.
in my catch up with Jingxing,
have you ever looked down on me?
Don't bully him!
Please rest assured, sir.
I'll get prepared.
I won't miss out on anything.
Have your grandpa and uncle carefully go.
Got it.
Arrogant!
You married a lady with a foot.
What's the hurry?
Yang Yang. Yang Yang.
Father.
What's the big news?
You're so loud in the morning.
It's a big news.
Go to the butler's place
and prepare the wedding gift.
Go to Wang Quan's place with me.
It's a good thing.
My grandson.
Please look forward to it.
Early December.
How many months to prepare?
Miss Wang Quan will get married.
She must dress up.
But Yang's family is not like Wang Quan.
I wonder if you like the wedding gift.
Our A Zui doesn't lack gold, silver and jewelry.
Of course.
I just don't know
why A Zui
will marry Yang's family.
Is she the young mistress of Yang's family?
She must be the mistress of the family.
When Miss Wang Quan marries into the family,
I'll pass on the position of the mistress to her.
I have a suggestion.
I don't dare.
After all, she's the mistress of Wang Quan's family.
She's a senior.
She's not as good as Wang Quan.
I heard that you owe a lot of debts outside.
No.
Absolutely not.
You can't hear rumors.
But there are your handwriting and handwriting on it.
Young mistress.
Of course.
Since we're a family,
I'll take care of the matter of Uncle.
Thank you, Young Mistress Wang Quan.
Wang Quan's Mansion is indeed the best place in the Yi Qi Alliance.
How can our family marry Wang Quan's family?
It's really a blessing in disguise.
No hurry.
I have another gift for Uncle.
I bought two mines.
The jade mine.
Young Mistress, you're so generous.
So, we can't wait for the good business.
I'll go to Nanchui to make money.
Nanchui?
No.
Nanchui people are mixed.
Have you prepared the carriage?
Yes.
I have a family.
Young Mistress Yang's wife and the concubine's house,
and the three houses and the family,
and the seven children,
are all gathered.
The carriage outside the mansion
seems to have started fighting.
Why don't you send me to Nanchui to make money?
Well...
Please.
Father, you're so mean.
I'm very satisfied with the gift.
It's settled on the fifth of December.
She has been sent away.
Before she got on the carriage,
I've asked her wife and concubine
to catch her face.
Tell Duhuang
that I don't want her to leave Nanchui.
Yes.
Come out.
Did you hear that?
I heard that you cheated people
and drove them to Nanchui without a trace.
You also told them never to come back.
Cui.
Take it.
We ate a few apples
that were given to the immortals.
We're safe and sound.
If you object,
I'll take it.
I can call her back.
I object.
Because you're so nice to her.
You bought a mine for her.
You bought two.
I bought
the reputation of your after-you-go-to-Yang family.
That's not true.
I'm angry when I think of Aunt Yang Yan.
Then think about it.
Why did she buy
such a profitable mine?
Is there any possibility
that she has any bad debts or enemies?
That's right.
That's my brother.
He's so cruel.
Cui.
I...
I want to ask you a question
and I'll send it to you.
Before Partizan
ran here and out of Meltdown,
how are you and Pelletie doing?
He said
you're a vigor.
After Bray.
I know.
Yes.
For you,
under the makeshift
I am even ready to meet up with you.
That is all,
I used the Demon-Witching Cultivation for a long time.
I hope that this time,
I can break through the limits of my bloodline
and manipulate the real life.
Qin Ren Feng.
Tell me.
What can I get from your arm?
It's naturally opportunity and power.
Opportunity?
I'm not sure.
Opportunity and power.
Opportunity and power?
With your ability,
the position you can climb is limited.
Human life is short.
You may work hard for a lifetime
and only get into a small head of a blind man.
Okay.
Tell me.
What can I do for you?
Do you know where the Eastern Huai Zhu is now?
They went to the Dream Tower of the Demon-Witching Cultivation
to get the West Martial Arts.
West Martial Arts?
Qin Ren Feng.
Your priority now
is to find the Tower Master
before the Eastern Huai Zhu
and get the West Martial Arts.
Why should they listen to me?
Go and send a letter to the Demon-Witching Cultivation Master.
Tell him
that Wang Quanhong is entering the Demon-Witching Cultivation.
The Demon-Witching Cultivation Master hates him just as much as you.
He will help you.
Now is the best time to kill Wang Quanhong.
Wang Quanhong and the Eastern Huai Zhu went to the Demon-Witching Cultivation.
They are changing the fate.
Lord Jiuhuo.
You must stop them.
When I have some rest,
I will go back and handle this matter myself.
But it's too slow.
Your demon core is badly injured.
The magic treasure has been destroyed.
It's easy to go back and impeach it.
But the desire of human will never stop.
I don't want to be a pawn anymore.
That Jin Ren Feng from the Sacred Fire Manor
hopes that he won't let me down.
It's too cold.
It's a little cold.
It's cold.
It's okay.
Pick some more.
Here you are.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Sister.
Is this the Demon-Witching Cultivation?
So many demons.
It's interesting.
The master has ordered
to close the gate.
Everyone,
check your identity.
don't move.
Anyone who moves,
will be handled by the spy of the First Qingmeng.
Search.
Lord.
What's going on?
Recently, the first Qingmeng
has some disciples from the Shi family
who have come to my Demon-Witching Cultivation.
All the guests in this restaurant
have no identity cards.
But they don't have demons
with their identity cards.
Take them away to investigate.
Wait.
Who are you?
Let them go.
Take away their identity cards.
We are from the Pulan clan.
Pulan clan?
Where are your demons?
I didn't bring them out.
You are dressed like a nobleman,
but you don't have demons.
Suspicious.
So what if I didn't bring them?
I didn't bring my brain.
Don't talk nonsense.
Take them away.
Come on.
Move.
Let's go.
Chief Zhou.
Where is the card?
Over there.
Go.
Yours.
Where is the card?
Madam.
Go and tell Ruilou
that they look like
from the Sacred Fire Manor.
Okay.
Let's go.
Go.
Sir.
It's almost dinner time.
Even if you don't let them go,
at least give them some food.
Stop it.
I'm busy now.
They only have a small bite.
I'll deal with you later.
Who is so bold?
How dare you arrest the lady of the Erzhu family?
Go.
Sister.
My lady.
I finally found them.
Why are you here so late?
I...
What did you say?
Are they from the Erzhu family?
Or are they my lady?
The lady of the Erzhu family
doesn't bring her ID card
or waist.
They're all over the street.
The ID card is here.
Come on.
Open the door.
Hurry up.
You...
Why are you attacking me?
Don't be so aggressive.
We don't have to block the door.
You...
My lady.
I'm sorry for being late.
I've made you suffer.
Sister.
Let's go.
Yes.
Stop.
The ID card is not fake.
But the state preceptor gave a death order.
We don't dare to be careless.
So, my ladies,
can you explain it to us?
Explain what?
My ladies.
You just don't have ID card or waist.
Why didn't you get hurt
when you were caught?
Squat.
We haven't
settled the score with you.
You caught the lady
of the Erzhu family for no reason.
Now you're questioning our lady.
You deserve to be punished.
If you don't give a reasonable explanation,
I'll make this old man
a scapegoat today.
We're not leaving.
Look at this old house.
It's full of cockroaches and rats.
Look at this dirty place.
Get your waist out.
I can walk on my own.
Let's go.
Sister.
Wait for me.
Let's go.
What's the hurry?
Slow down.
Brother, slow down.
Give it to me.
I'll take it.
Goodbye, my ladies.
It's so dangerous.
If we delay for a while,
we'll be caught.
I'll go with you.
It's you two.
I didn't see it.
How are you?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine.
So the ghost that was screaming
was you.
You talked to your savior like that?
That's great.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
I thought...
You can talk.
Why did you touch me?
Sorry, Miss Qinglan.
But, sister,
how did you know
that it was them?
Li Juzhuo wrote it on his hand.
What did he write?
What's the word?
It's gone.
How did you know
that we were here?
I heard that you were caught
in Ruyi Pavilion.
That's a great news.
You're going to
sweep the reputation of the Ghost Valley
if you mention it.
What did I say?
You're going to sweep the reputation
of the Ghost Valley
if you mention it.
What did I say?
Brother, don't be anxious.
Let me think of
a perfect plan.
So...
In a word,
Qingmu Yuan gave us the Demon-Poisoning Talisman.
Thank you.
I don't know what you're doing,
but in this situation,
we'd better...
No better.
We'll go our separate ways.
Now the people who are
following you
are more dangerous.
You're right.
Remember.
Take these two identity cards.
If you have any problem,
come to Ruyi Pavilion.
What about you?
We still have them.
Let's go, sister.
She'll fall on you.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.