Why did you have to say that
and ruin everything?
Wait.
Does this mean I have to stay in
a coma for three years before waking up?
All right, if that's how it is.
Then…
-Choi Jun-woong will go back into--
-I'll take him.
I'll take him.
EPISODE 3: FOREST OF TIME 1
Ma'am.
Working at Jumadeung is the epitome
of success in the afterworld.
You need to beat
thousands of other candidates to get in.
So why…
would you let a nobody like that in?
Excuse me?
What? A nobody?
I was pretty impressive
when I was alive too.
I'm someone with countless certifications!
I'm telling you!
He won't be just observing.
What were you thinking?
Do you really not know?
Why I accepted someone
with no basic skills or abilities
and who only gets into trouble?
No, I don't know.
So I can use him how I want.
Aren't you getting in?
Get in, Mr. Choi.
Isn't there a single thing here
that's normal?
REPORT CRIMINAL SOULS
CALL NUMBER 2482
REAPER ACT OF CONDUCT
This is the Risk Management Team's office.
It's a bit messy, right?
It used to belong to
the Special Crimes Unit,
which was a part of the Escort Team.
Special Crimes Unit?
They escorted the souls who go to Hell
for the crimes they'd committed in life.
It used to be led by our Team Manager.
Move!
What about now?
The team was dissolved,
and now we use this office.
Why? Don't you like it?
No, not at all.
It's very sophisticated and retro…
It's so cozy I think it's a great space
to get some work done.
POTENTIAL SUICIDE CASE
Let me formally introduce myself.
I'm Lim Ryung-gu.
Ryung as in "high"
and gu as in "to rescue."
I'm sorry, I don't normally laugh
at other people's names.
I apologize, Mr. Lim.
Well. It's fine.
I'm used to people making fun of
my name since I was little.
Right.
Was your name Mr. Temp?
No.
Was it Mr. Contract?
I guess you can read a person
by the impression they give off.
-You're not the chill type, are you?
-Physiognomy?
-Yes.
-Let's say I'm very competitive.
I'm not the type
to back down from a challenge.
You aren't?
Neither am I.
-Mr. Lim.
-Yes.
Begin.
Hands out. Stand at attention.
I will begin explaining
the Code of Conduct for Jumadeung Reapers.
A Reaper may not dress or behave
in a way that compromises dignity.
It's my first time doing this.
This looks expensive.
There's not much
to spend on once you're dead.
I think
this is going to look really nice
once it's done.
You look like a rag doll.
You're right.
Keep looking forward.
You will receive a new
Resident Registration Number,
NAME: CHOI JUN-WOONG
DATE 10/12/2021
along with a new name.
NAME: KIM WOONG-JUN
But…
what if I run into someone who knows me?
Don't worry.
They'll see the new face we've inputted.
-What?
-It means they won't recognize you.
Not even my family?
Of course.
No Reaper may use their abilities
in front of humans
or intervene in human affairs
or leave any ties to
the Land of the Living.
TEAM MANAGER KOO
ASSISTANT MANAGER LIM
STANDARD AFTERLIFE
EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT
COMPANY NAME: JUMADEUNG INC.
EMPLOYER: JADE EMPEROR
And the most important part is,
from today,
the Choi Jun-woong
from the Land of the Living
is no longer.
I wanted to fill your shoes better
but this is how I managed to get a job.
Still, this is…
a pretty big company.
I don't think
there is another one as big in Korea.
So don't worry, Dad.
I'll do a good job
and go back to
Mother and Min-young in no time.
Stop drinking, Mom.
It's the anniversary of your dad's death.
I'm just feeling a little down.
Try to understand.
You know how our family is
unnecessarily frank and objective, right?
You want to drink because of Jun-woong.
You'll make Dad sad.
I told you it's not like that.
Please.
Mom, we need to prepare for
the long run with Jun-woong.
We can't lose our energy this early on.
Okay?
Goodness.
People say your own children
are the scariest.
They're not wrong.
Mom.
How come we don't have
any pictures with Dad?
Given the journalist he was,
your father was always the one
taking pictures of us.
If I had known he wouldn't return
from that business trip,
I would have taken a photo of him
that day he left.
You're right. What a pity.
Let's clean up.
I'm sure he's finished.
Bring it here. I'll wash it.
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
Name, Namgung Jae-soo. Age 29.
He's been studying for the Police
Academy Exam for the last three years.
His Negative Energy Levels
have surged recently.
But there's a problem.
What is it?
He's Jun-woong's closest friend.
What is the world coming to?
I feel like my job is just studying for
the Police Academy Exam.
ACQUAINTANCE OF CHOI JUN-WOONG
CURRENT NEGATIVE ENERGY LEVEL: 85%
Should we exclude Mr. Choi from this case?
Why? Do you think his personal feelings
will get in the way?
Yes.
Personal feelings
can help sometimes, right?
Anyway, why isn't he here?
Where did he go?
You don't think…
What?
A blind date?
Stop filming.
Give me back my shoes.
You think you can talk back to me
because I've been nice?
Piss off unless you want to die.
I worked part-time to buy them.
Jae-soo.
Namgung Jae-soo.
-Why are you being like this?
-Put the shoes on.
-Your face.
-Your face, smile.
DREAMS OVER GRADES
FRIENDSHIP OVER COMPETITION
Let's just go get a snack.
Give me back my shoes.
This dumbass is at it again.
Give them back.
Jae-soo in his designated spot.
Give them back already.
That's cute.
Hey, give me back my shoes!
You little.
No, getting involved
will only cause more problems.
Hey, give it.
Give it!
Give me my shoes.
Persistent bastard.
Let's end this today.
Give them back!
Hey.
My shoes.
Shoes?
Who are you?
What?
You surprised me.
What do you want?
Haven't you had enough?
Give him the shoes.
Are you friends with this guy?
Hey.
No, we're not friends.
Hey, you went to Seonam Kindergarten.
Seonam Kindergarten?
If we're from the same neighborhood
and in the same class, we're friends.
Three to two sounds doable.
Thanks, friend.
Please, three to two?
Wait.
Let me talk to him for a second.
Nice to meet you, friend.
Get ready, go.
Did you mess with my friend?
Really? Damn.
Hey, on three.
One.
-Two.
-Three!
Oh, man.
This is salty.
This is exactly when
you should eat fried chicken.
When you need cheering up.
What are you on about?
Did you get hit a lot?
So my father's factory
went under during the IMF,
and my family had nothing.
How are you so nonchalant about that?
It's not like your family
became penniless.
My family went under too.
For some reason, ever since then,
I get this craving for fried chicken
when I need a boost.
How are they related?
It's like how people eat samgye-tang
during the dog days of summer.
It's just chicken.
That's a long story just to say
you want fried chicken.
I failed today, but I'll go again tomorrow
to get them back.
-Get what back?
-I need to get my shoes back!
Are you insane? Have you gone crazy?
Failure means you should try again,
Jun-woong.
Who came up with that nonsense, Jae-soo?
My father.
Such wise words from your father!
Tell him I'd like to meet him someday.
I want to hear his wise words in person.
He passed away.
A long time ago.
Sorry, I can't say anything
without putting my foot in my mouth.
Anyway, failing isn't bad.
Let's just accept this one as a failure.
Stop shaking your head
and let's just fail.
-I don't want to get beat up again.
-No.
I'm going again tomorrow.
I'll get my shoes back.
Look at you.
You persistent bastard.
Hey.
Hey, Jae-soo.
Jae-soo!
Seriously.
You, hey, you!
You're home, open your door!
Come on and open it already, you idiot!
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Who…
are you?
It's me.
It's me, you idiot.
What if I run into someone who knows me?
Don't worry.
They'll see the new face we've inputted.
It's perfect.
NATIONAL ID CARD
KIM WOONG-JUN
What?
Hey, Jae-soo.
Open the…
Jae-soo, come on out.
I just need a minute.
Is this the police?
Please, you need to save my friend.
My friend's trying to
kill himself right now…
Please, come quickly. Please.
Here, quickly.
Jae-soo.
Someone called in a breaking and entering.
-What? Why?
-Come with us.
What? No.
Hey, sir. Wait.
RESIDENT DATABASE
CHOI JUN-WOONG
Choi Jun-woong.
9410124-1…
How many times do I have to tell you?
We need to go right now.
It's an emergency.
Give us your real name
and resident registration number.
What do you mean?
Will you take responsibility
if something bad happens?
Don't you know it's a crime to
use someone else's identity?
Tell us your real one, not someone else's!
I'm telling you that one is mine!
I'm telling you it's mine.
Why do you keep asking…
What are you doing here?
Hello. He's a close friend of mine.
He's been in an accident,
and he's not in his right mind,
as you can see.
-What are you talking about?
-Wait.
Did you forget?
They can't recognize you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Get it together.
How can I get it together
when my friend is supposed to die?
You should be more logical and reasonable
because he's your friend.
Please, I can't do that.
What are you going to do if you can't?
Even if he wasn't your friend,
we need to save Namgung Jae-soo.
Can you really save Jae-soo?
Give me the report.
This is his third year
taking the Police Academy Exam.
This year, he failed the first exam.
The first one?
No, that can't be.
He always passed the first one.
Come on, just a little more.
What's the situation now?
Don't you have any more?
-Bye.
He's not doing anything.
-I'm back.
It's as if
time has stopped for him.
He won't leave his house.
What should we do?
Fried chicken, fried chicken.
Fried chicken should do the trick.
-What are you talking about?
-Is that all you need?
From where? You can get it delivered--
No, not like that…
The chicken Jae-soo
used to eat with his dad
when he was around six years old.
He always talked about it
whenever he had a hard time.
Even if you're a Reaper,
there's no way to go into the past.
How can you be sure
that fried chicken will make him better?
Memories are easily distorted.
-I don't agree.
-Mr. Lim's right.
Let's go see Namgung Jae-soo first.
We need to get him out of the house first.
I have a way.
We're here to spread the good word.
Can we have a moment of your…
He's sharper than we thought.
It seems so.
Seriously?
Excuse me.
I mean, really.
Who on earth opens their door
to cult members these days?
Then what? Do you have a better idea?
FAILURE MEANS YOU SHOULD TRY AGAIN
WHO ARE YOU
COME OUT IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
What did I tell you?
This isn't going to work.
That idiot.
Never mind, just tear the door off
and drag him out.
What?
He's fast for a guy
who never leaves his house.
He's preparing for the police academy!
Stop chatting and run!
We're going to lose him!
Wait.
Let's teleport.
Teleport.
No, there are security cameras!
What kind of Grim Reaper
is scared of security cameras!
Not even ghosts can get around
security cameras.
Really?
Hey, Jae-soo!
Hey!
Where's Jae-soo?
I lost him.
Let's split up.
You go there and you go that way.
Okay.
The signal.
Where on earth are you?
What?
SEOUL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
That's the hospital I'm at.
Heo Na-young, born September 27th, 1993.
Death by car accident.
Escort her.
No, I can't go like this.
Wait, please. Just for a minute.
Let me say goodbye.
Your time in the Land of the Living
has come to an end.
Please.
Of course.
I knew you couldn't have sent it.
Jun-woong! What's wrong?
Hey, Jun-woong.
Excuse me, sir.
Crap, he's tachycardic.
-Get me the defibrillator, quickly.
-Okay.
-Charge to 100.
-Yes.
Are you crazy?
Choi Jun-woong.
Stop making trouble and stay still.
Who are you to tell me to stay still?
You nearly died.
Explain so I can understand.
A newbie who doesn't know the basics.
-What?
-A subordinate with no sense of duty.
And a team manager from Hell.
Looks like this team won't last
for much longer.
Maybe I was worried for no reason.
No. You were right to be worried.
And you should stay that way.
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
I'll send my people in advance…
Team Manager Koo.
Seriously.
I mean…
what did I do wrong?
Do you really not know?
You didn't read the contract, did you?
The contract?
The clause stating
a temporal error will occur
if your temporary body
gets close to your real body.
So?
Your memory will be erased randomly…
You didn't read it.
So what if I lose a little of my memory?
You could forget your own face.
Then you can't return to your own body.
Simply put, you'll die.
Die?
Why are you telling me
something so crucial now?
You should have read the contract!
Come on.
Yes, I didn't read it.
Then I suppose you read
all your contracts thoroughly?
Down to the last clause?
Mr. Lim Ryung-gu?
I do.
I read every single word.
Thoroughly.
You have to be born like that
to be that annoying.
Who are you?
Why do you keep following me?
You're drunk.
Stay seated. Please.
Look at you, spending money
when you don't even have a job.
As if you're not broke too,
studying for the civil service exam.
That's why
I only spend money
-when it's a bang for your buck!
You know what you're talking about.
Jun-woong…
Jun-woong.
It feels like hell.
I soldiered on with the hope
that one day my day will come, but…
The final thing we're going over
is liability.
Legal liability means
civil and criminal liability.
For criminal liability…
2022 POLICE ACADEMY RECRUITMENT EXAM
ADMISSION TICKET
RECRUITMENT NOTICE
What did I do that was so wrong?
How come I'm the only one
who can't make it?
I worked my ass off studying every day.
What for?
Why!
I know.
It feels like everyone's moving ahead…
and I'm the only one who's lost my way.
Like I'm the only loser.
Like I'm the only one standing still.
But you were always someone
who tried until you succeeded.
Right?
You…
You're not like this.
I was barely holding on.
But you're not here,
and I've reached my limit.
Don't cry!
Never mind, cry it out.
I want fried chicken.
What?
Hey.
Hey, Jae-soo.
Come on.
Jae-soo.
Wake up.
You heard it, ma'am, Mr. Lim.
We really need…
We really need that fried chicken.
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
When did you say
he had that fried chicken?
When he was six.
What are you going to do?
There's no way to go into the past.
Then we make a way.
You keep an eye on Jae-soo.
I'll be back
before your end-of-work alarm rings.
I'll come with you.
No. Do you have any idea
how dangerous this is?
He's my friend.
He's my friend, so I really want to help.
I said no!
I'll do everything you say.
I won't even talk back.
And I know the neighborhood
since I used to live there.
So…
please, ma'am.
Aren't you supposed to be working?
I came to borrow the car.
You know that going to the past
was banned a long time ago,
since it never ends well.
Not to mention it often has
a negative impact on the present.
I don't want to go either.
-But I have to.
-No.
Let me go.
Why on earth are you going anyway?
To get fried chicken.
Fried chicken?
Fried chicken…
Yes…
Okay.
Right, fried chicken, right.
Yes, fried chicken.
Right, you should be the one to go.
Mr. Baek has the key,
so go ask him for it.
Okay.
Fried chicken.
I know, the 12-hour limit.
I won't be able to return if I'm late.
-Twelve hours…
-Okay.
Thank you.
Look at all this!
Ma'am!
This is my dream car, can we take this?
This one.
Can't we take this one? This one, come on.
Let's take this one!
No? All right. I'll yield.
I'm yielding voluntarily.
You have to remember that.
How far are you going? How far…
This one here at the end?
This one is good. I like this one too.
Where are you going?
Where are you going…
You're not…
No, come on.
Come on. Why?
Why would you leave this great car
and take that one?
Get in.
This…
It looks like it won't even start.
Okay, fine, getting in.
It looks dangerous.
Why can't we take that car?
Why this one out of all the cars?
Jeez.
It's bumpy.
No!
YEAR 1999
Look at that.
TICKET OFFICE
We really went back in time, right?
Stop looking around and start navigating.
Oh, right. Go straight.
Hello sir, this is Hoban Insurance.
We left a message
asking you to call us back
because we're missing
your insurance payment.
I haven't been able to pay my phone bill,
so I can only receive calls,
not make them.
When do you think
you can make the payment?
I don't think I'll be able to for a while.
Wait.
HOBAN INSURANCE
CERTIFICATE OF INSURANCE
How much can I get back if I cancel this?
Well, this one
doesn't preserve your premium
so you don't really get anything back
if you cancel.
It's only if you pass away…
Okay.
Yes, I understand.
Jae-soo.
Since it's your birthday today,
do you want me to bring your favorite,
fried chicken for dinner later?
Yes!
Okay.
Then be a good kid
and listen to the teacher
until I pick you up later, okay?
Okay, let's go.
SEONAM KINDERGARTEN
Let's go.
Excuse me…
I'll see you later, Jae-soo.
-Excuse me, Mr. Namgung.
-Yes.
It's just the principal said
you're really behind on Jae-soo's tuition…
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay soon.
I mean, the principal says she can't…
No! I want to go!
I want to go to kindergarten!
It's my birthday party today!
Don't cry, Jae-soo. Don't cry.
I told you
we'll have your favorite fried chicken
tonight. Right?
Right. Fried chicken.
That's right.
Let's go now, okay?
Let's go!
I heard they went under during the IMF.
It really does seem like
they're struggling.
Let's follow him.
Welcome to Two O'Clock Date.
No way. They still have this show now.
Cool.
Do you need new socks?
I'll give you a good price.
Please come take a look.
They're at a great price.
Jae-soo, I'm just going to
quickly send this resume,
so if the police come,
tell them Daddy is coming back soon.
Okay.
It's 500 won per pair,
and 1,200 won for three pairs.
Men's socks here, women's socks there.
It's free to look around.
Jae-soo, what are you going to do
with the money you earn?
I need to pay Mom's hospital bills,
and I need to go to kindergarten
and if I have any left,
I'll eat something delicious with Dad.
How are you so nonchalant about that?
Wait, but mister.
How did you know my name's Jae-soo?
What?
I said that?
Yes. You said, "Jae-soo, what are you
going to do with the money you earn?"
What are you talking about? Me?
I didn't, I really didn't.
Right?
He said he didn't.
See, she says I didn't. I didn't.
-But you did…
-I didn't! I really didn't.
Please, believe me.
POWER OF COMPANIES
My dad studies really hard.
He never sleeps and studies all the time.
HOBAN INSURANCE
GENERAL LIFE INSURANCE NON-DIVIDEND
I don't like studying.
-What do you like?
-Fried chicken!
Today, Dad said he's buying me
fried chicken because it's my birthday.
Yes, that. From where?
Which store sells your favorite flavor?
The one Dad buys.
The one Dad buys?
Right. It's 1999, so Texas?
Or Jonggatjib?
Jonggatjib?
No? Then…
Of course! The Mexican Sauce?
Right! The Mexican Sauce is the best.
Come on, how do you not know
the name of the fried chicken you like?
Is it the Mexican Sauce Chicken?
Jonggatjib? Where?
Come on, tell me.
You're on the same level as the kid.
He said his dad is buying it.
We'll know if we wait.
Yes, I sent my resume
and the analysis data.
Oh, you received it.
Really? Okay.
Please give me a call
if you have a spot open.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm in a tight spot this month.
Could you cut me some slack?
We already did.
If you don't pay the bill
in full this month,
-there's nothing we can do.
-I mean…
How can you say there's nothing you can do
when she's that sick?
You know there's nothing we can do
even if you do this to us.
I couldn't even make you
seaweed soup today
when it's your birthday.
Dad said he's buying me
fried chicken later.
Really?
Lucky you.
Mom, are you okay?
Honey, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's go home, Jae-soo.
Honey.
The hospital bill is big, right?
I'm all better.
I can go home now.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry about it.
I took care of everything.
So don't worry about that.
You just focus on getting better
for Jae-soo here, all right?
WOORI SARANG HOSPITAL
Oh, man. These can't get wet!
Jae-soo, you go in.
Don't come out, okay?
They're all wet. Gosh.
Jae-soo.
Jae-soo!
Jae…
I told you to stay in the car!
Who told you to do that?
I'm sorry, Jae-soo.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
Jae-soo, I'm sorry.
Daddy's sorry. It's okay.
It's okay.
What happened?
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
Hurry up.
Let's wrap it up in ten minutes.
Hey, you can't…
You can't do this out of the blue!
What do you mean I can't?
You haven't paid the rent in months.
I don't want to talk to you.
Still, you can't do this,
not when it's raining!
What are you getting angry at me for?
Do it by the law!
Like I'm not annoyed enough already.
Just how much more stuff is there?
-Dad.
-Jae-soo.
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
Mr. Namgung!
Crap. Mr. Namgung!
He said he had been happy…
Human memory is selective.
It keeps what was good
and discards the bad.
It wraps up the past in nostalgia.
Because that's the only way
you can keep on living.
I guess it was like that for Jae-soo.
Some people are the opposite.
Their past becomes more painful
as time goes by and becomes wounds,
and when they can't bear it anymore
they make that drastic decision.
-Let's go back.
-What about Jae-soo?
What about the fried chicken?
We'll have to find another way.
Since we've come all the way here,
I'll just go and say goodbye.
-Jae-soo.
-Yes?
Daddy will…
drop you off at Mommy's hospital.
Go be with Mommy.
Okay. You're coming there too?
Yes.
You know…
I love you so much, right?
Yes.
Dad, why are you crying?
I just have something in my eyes.
Okay.
All right.
I'll bring fried chicken, okay?
He's dropping Jae-soo off at the hospital
and going to buy the chicken.
You can go on your own, right?
Go on.
WOORI SARANG HOSPITAL
NAMGUNG JAE-SOO, AGE 29
STUDYING FOR POLICE EXAM
Mr. Namgung!
Are you out of your mind, Namgung Jae-soo?
Let's just talk for a bit.
Right, the fried chicken.
That fried chicken you had
in the happiest moment of your life.
It's coming.
So please!
Don't do anything stupid.
That day, on my birthday.
I finally understand
that look in my father's eyes.
Why is he going so fast?
That road leads to the outskirts…
What's wrong?
Do you really not know?
You don't mean…
HOBAN INSURANCE
GENERAL LIFE INSURANCE NON-DIVIDEND
The life insurance?
Yes.
Sir!
Stop the car, sir!
Sir, can't you hear me?
Sir!
Hold on tight.
EPILOGUE
Hello.
You have a wonderful aura.
Did you just get a new job?
Yes.
I see.
I can feel it.
The life you've lived.
It's like a flashback.
A flashback? Jumadeung?
What department are you in?
If you're asking where I belong,
I guess I have to say with "that one."
Oh, the Director?
Well, I suppose since they are at the top.
They're the ones who called me.
So that's the Director?
Yes. He says if you don't give offerings,
your fortune will dry up
and things won't go your way.
The Director says,
if you keep on doing this,
you'll get punished.
I got conned by a cult member.
The word Jumadeung hooked me in.
Where are you going, sir?
You're saying the Director is here?
Yes, this way.
Goodness.
Your ancestors must have given
many offerings.
You're making me blush,
staring at me like that.
Why are you staring at me?
SELECTED AS BEST SHAMAN
BY KOREAN BUDDHISM ASSOCIATIONS
Ma'am, Mr. Namgung is in danger.
Choi Jun-woong, where are you going?
You got punished because of me.
I don't want the RM team to be dissolved.
Heo Na-young, born September 27th, 1993.
Death by car accident.
I can't go to the afterlife like this.
Get more people here
and comb through the area.
You're the one who saves people
who are going to commit suicide,
right?
Do you not know getting entangled
with a runaway soul can cause trouble?
Go and find Heo Na-young.
She's related to our case.
We can't just hand her over.
If you keep getting in the way,
I won't hold back next time.
Subtitle translation by: Jung-in Park