Why are you still alive?
You should go to hell.
Give me back my life.
Go to hell.
So tragic.
Give me back my life.
Go to hell.
Song Ping.
Why can you still be alive?
Give me back my life.
Song Ping.
I died such a tragic death.
No one can help you now.
Didn't you perish
with those Japanese underground?
With him?
He wanted to trade his life for mine.
So are they really all dead?
You have already seen them,
and even wrote a report about it.
That means
they are really dead.
And now,
I will avenge those wronged souls.
Come to claim your life.
My lord.
I beg you.
Please save me.
Save me.
I will manage Taohua Town well for you.
I will.
You saw them die with your own eyes
and reported it in an official document.
Naturally, they are dead.
I understand.
So you wanted to use me as a mouthpiece.
Tell outsiders
that there are no living people left in Taohua Town.
Chief Song, you are indeed smart.
This way,
anyone who wants to enter Taohua Town
and take this away
will have to think twice.
So you guys are in this together.
More than just knowing each other,
our relationship is not ordinary.
Right, Dad?
Good thing I arrived in time.
Wang Shiqi.
Otherwise,
if something happens to
this pretty daughter-in-law,
that brat
would never let me hear the end of it.
I don't want to be a wandering ghost.
Song Ping.
You've done so much evil.
Today,
I will use your blood
to pay tribute to the innocent souls you killed.
Good, good, good.
Good riddance.
I forgot to sharpen the knife.
And you won't even become a ghost.
Good.
Brother Shiqi.
Good thing I gave you this back then.
Thank you for bringing your troops, Madam,
wiping out those devils,
and saving the whole town.
Protecting the borders and the people
is a soldier's duty.
It's also thanks to Miss Su risking her life
to send the message in time,
that a disaster was avoided.
The person you really should thank...
It's her.
It's a pity.
To the rest of the world,
you are all dead now.
It's better to be dead.
We've all discussed it.
From now on,
we will all become ghosts
to protect the precious cultural relics
buried underground.
Okay.
The mayor didn't report the news
that everyone was alive.
Taohua Town was forgotten during the war.
And only by turning this place into a ghost town
can we deter tomb raiders
and temporarily protect the national treasures.
You brat.
You did a good job this time.
I will continue to wander around
the world
and uphold justice.
What do you say?
Want to come with me?
I certainly want to.
But
I haven't got a wife yet.
Think about it.
If I follow you,
I'm afraid I'll really become a eunuch.
You blockhead.
I was anxious to have a grandson.
How could you believe my bluff?
I knew it all along.
I was just
trying to make you happy.
After all, I'm your son.
But, Dad,
this time,
I've made up my mind.
I want to stay here
to continue protecting underground cultural relics.
I can't let those relics
fall into the hands of foreigners.
I believe that one day,
we can completely drive them
all out.
Good.
Ambitious.
Wang Shiqi!
Brother Wang!
You executioner!
Does your promise to marry me still count?
You said you'd compensate me with your body.
I still haven't got it.
Me...
Give it to me!
Brother Wang!
You!
You deal with it.
You can't either!
Dad!
You!
You can't leave!
I...
I've made up my mind.
I'll follow you.
I want to wander around the world with you.
I can't
handle this situation!
I can't be careless
about choosing my daughter-in-law.
Do you see this copper coin?
Whoever gets this coin
will be the daughter-in-law of the Wang family.
Give it to me!
I want it.
This is mine.
I'm really going to become a eunuch.
Dad!
Okay.
Tell Dad today,
what you four little rascals
have been up to again.
Today, two more tomb raiders
were scared away by us.
Awesome.
Then
tell us the story of
how you slayed ghosts back then.
Tell us.
Tell us, Dad.
Alright.
Stop.
Stand still.
Then Dad
will tell you again
the stories of those ghosts.
Are these stories true?
Whether they are true
or false,
remember,
it's all to protect our national treasures
from being coveted by bad guys.
Why does good always
triumph over evil?
To deter those bad guys,
just like
the stories Dad told.
Come on.
Children,
come to Mom.
Come to Mommy.
Come here.
Auntie.
Mom.
Auntie bought you some delicious food.
Come.
Come here.
I want a hug too.
Mom.
Mommy will take you to eat something good, okay?
Good.
Maybe,
it's all an illusion.
Who knows?
Wanrong and I have four children.
Yinlian and Jiaojiao became my siblings.
The happiness makes me a bit dazed.