♪I love the clarity in your eyes♪
♪Like a shooting star across my world♪
♪Repeating the goodbye we never said♪
♪Through sleepless nights♪
♪I miss the way you looked at me♪
♪Like photos freezing that summer bit by bit♪
♪By the shore with warm winds, maybe we'll meet again♪
[Fall in Love Again]
[Episode 1]
I don't believe I can't get him this time.
Mr. Fu,
I've done everything you asked.
When will you keep your promise?
You don't trust me?
Yet you still deal with me?
Of course I do.
My body and my heart are yours.
Okay.
Moving on.
Get ready for the next scene.
Okay.
Give it to me.
All departments, prep the next scene!
- Thanks. - Props, pack up.
- Prep the next scene. - Good work, everyone.
Wait outside for me.
Okay, Yu.
I'll wait outside.
You scared me.
I just saw you kissing He Zheng.
You were really into it.
What?
You like him?
Jealous?
He's just an unknown actor.
With you here,
why would I look at him?
That's more like it.
Hello, Xi.
- Everyone, gather up. - Hello.
- Three people over here. - Hello, Xi.
Okay.
Makeup, quick touch-up for the actor.
On it!
Xi.
Um, let's double-check.
There are four.
Xi, what brings you here?
Aren't you wrapping today?
I came to check in.
I brought milk tea and desserts,
get someone to pick them up.
- Thanks. - Okay.
Here's water.
Gaffer, I need you here now!
Hello, Xi.
Where's Director Qi?
- What are you here for? - Get in touch now.
He's giving notes to the cast.
I'll go get him for you.
No need. He's in the lounge, right?
I'll go myself.
- You do your thing. - Two people over here.
- You'll handle this later. - Move over a bit.
Okay.
Qi, do you love me?
Yes, yes, of course I do.
If you love me, don't marry her.
Alright?
Marrying her
is just to satisfy the public.
Otherwise the image I built
would fall apart.
You only think about yourself,
never about me.
How could I not think about you?
The female lead in my next drama
is still you.
Really?
Of course.
How will you repay me?
Chu Jingxi.
You are?
I'm He Zheng.
The male lead of this show.
Thanks for your hard work. Milk tea and desserts outside.
Ms. Chu.
Go over there.
Set it a bit farther.
Anything else?
I like you.
I'm your fan.
I've liked you for years.
May I get your autograph?
You startled me.
Where should I sign?
Coming.
Here.
On your clothes?
[To: He]
[To: He Zheng — May all your wishes come true]
Good luck.
You just...
I didn't interrupt, did I?
Honey, what brings you here?
I heard you're wrapping today.
So as the boss's wife,
I came to show some support.
Xi is so kind.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What scene were you discussing?
It seemed intense.
Yu was doing an argument scene.
I gave her some pointers.
The emotions went a bit too far,
so things got a little messy.
By the way, honey.
How's the wedding prep going?
I'm on set every day.
I haven't been much help.
Just focus on filming.
I've got things covered at home.
Be mindful of your image out there.
You're a leader, after all.
Director Qi, I'll head out first.
I won't interrupt your sweet moment.
Yu,
I brought your favorite tiramisu.
I'll have the assistant bring it over.
I'm cutting sugar lately.
I don't want to age faster.
I'll pass.
A little won't hurt.
Xi,
you haven't acted in a long time.
You wouldn't get our struggles.
I'll go get ready.
What's with Yu?
- She's acting weird. - Just leave it.
Honey, I haven't seen you in days.
I've missed you.
Focus on work.
Okay.
Honey.
By the way,
the son-conceiving remedy my mom gave you,
have you been taking it?
I don't want it—it's too bitter.
Honey,
please bear with it,
since we're trying for a baby, right?
I've got it all planned.
For our honeymoon,
I'll take you where you want to go.
The Maldives.
Really?
Really.
Director, the actor has changed outfits.
Okay, got it.
Then you get back to work.
I won't interrupt.
I've got a lot to handle at home.
Work hard.
I'm heading out.
Go ahead.
Yang,
come help me.
Okay.
Let go.
Does this look straight?
A little more to the left.
Like this?
Okay.
All set?
All set.
You're like a perfect rose.
How did you end up in the wrong vase?
That's a terrible analogy.
Hey, be careful.
You're a grown-up,
but you still act like a child.
Mom.
What does your mother-in-law mean by that?
Pregnant?
What are you talking about?
It's too soon.
Too soon?
No, it's not.
Anyway, you don't have a job.
So after the wedding,
you might as well stay home and have a baby.
Who says
that once she's married, she must stay home and have kids?
And who says Chu has no job?
Everything your son has today
comes from Chu's resources and connections.
Even if she's not working right now,
it's because your son is insecure
and won't let her be seen.
Yang,
Mom and Qi mean well.
I mean well, don't I?
Chu.
Let me be clear.
Our family has its rules.
After you're married,
see less of those questionable friends,
so they don't affect my son.
Who are you calling questionable?
Mom.
Did you bring that remedy for a son?
You're willing to drink it?
Okay.
I'll go get it now.
I'll grab it right away.
I'll go get it for you now.
Seriously?
- A mother like that? - It's fine, it's fine.
- A person like that? - Don't be mad.
- And she's your future mother-in-law. - Okay, don't be mad.
Oh my god, she called me questionable?
She was the one inappropriate!
Alright, don't get so angry.
Listen to me.
A troublemaking mom-in-law,
and a macho guy.
Plus all his scandals.
I'm telling you,
this marriage,
you should think it through.
Yang.
You're a top agent in our circle
and you believe gossip like that?
When you were my agent,
how many made-up scandals did you fix for me?
Have you forgotten?
Fine, let's say 80 percent.
80 percent of it is fake,
but that leaves 20 percent that doesn't add up.
Right?
Yang, since I chose to love him,
I have to trust him.
For the first thirty years,
I had no family.
I didn't even know who my parents were.
Now,
I've finally found my happiness.
You should be happy for me.
Silly girl, I just want you happy.
I want what's best for you.
But you!
You, I...!
Forget it.
I hope I'm wrong.
Yang,
you're my only family.
I want your blessing.
Alright.
Then today,
we'll toast with water instead.
Wishing you both happiness.
Thank you.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
To a lifetime together.
Okay.
Please welcome our beautiful bride.
Over here, over here.
Miss, look at the camera.
Ms. Chu, over here.
- Over here. - Ms. Chu.
- One more. - Look at the camera.
He surprised me,
I'll surprise him too.
Chu, whatever you do,
I support you.
The bride looks stunning.
Someone's dream girl is marrying another man,
too bad the groom isn't him.
How does that make you feel?
Get lost!
I wish the earth were flat,
so I could keep looking
and still see you.
Only see you.
Fits the classic line from "Fleet of Time", right?
As long as she's happy.
Chu,
I started from the bottom
and climbed my way up, step by step, to where I am today.
Everything I have now
thanks to your support and for being by my side.
And above all, I'm grateful
to have someone as amazing as you in my life.
So please believe in me,
I'll love you properly
and cherish you.
Well said!
- Yes! - Well said!
You should've cherished me.
But you didn't.
Have you lost your mind?
This is my wedding.
Isn't this the madness you like?
Alright, Yu.
Let's stop this.
I want to be your bride
before Chu Jingxi does.
You little tease.
This wedding's off, let's go!
I can't leave.
♪When clouds sink into the deep sea♪
♪Ripples spread♪
♪Traces of a racing heart♪
♪Is it the sky or its reflection♪
♪I can't tell anymore♪
♪Lost in your eyes♪
♪As we draw closer♪
♪The space of an embrace♪
♪Scatters the dark♪
♪When the wind comes, raise the sails♪
♪And sail on♪
♪Miles ahead are no longer a dream♪
♪Where even migratory birds can't reach, you're by my side♪
♪Then I can spread my wings and fly with courage♪
♪If storms rise, I'll follow your light♪
♪Trusting we'll reach a warm shore♪
♪Where even migratory birds can't reach, you're by my side♪
♪I'll break through the haze and run toward what I once longed for♪
♪Even if I'm hurt, I won't wander alone♪
♪You're where my heart belongs♪
♪As we draw closer♪
♪The space of an embrace♪
♪Scatters the dark♪
♪When the wind comes, raise the sails♪
♪And sail on♪
♪Miles ahead are no longer a dream♪
♪Where even migratory birds can't reach, you're by my side♪
♪Then I can spread my wings and fly with courage♪
♪If storms rise, I'll follow your light♪
♪Trusting we'll reach a warm shore♪
♪Where even migratory birds can't reach, you're by my side♪
♪I'll break through the haze and run toward what I once longed for♪
♪Even if I'm hurt, I won't wander alone♪
♪You're where my heart belongs♪