When I was young and read the story of marking the boat to find a dropped sword,
I always thought that man was so stupid.
Didn't he know that if you drop something in the middle of the river,
there's no way you can find it by going to the riverbank?
But after we grow up,
we always return to the riverbank over and over again.
We want to use that original mark
to find the things we've lost.
Revisiting old places.
Reuniting with old friends.
I hope I can see you again someday.
And tell you,
I am Song Yao,
and this is my best friend, Zhang Yiyi.
I didn't expect that we would start here,
and part ways here too.
Old Antique,
I'm sorry we couldn't send you back.
Maybe in the near future,
there will be a time machine.
You might just wake up from a nap
and be able to go back to where you want to be.
Even if you don't go back,
don't be sad.
At least in this city,
you still have Yaoyao and me as your friends.
This is for you.
After all, I'm your Chinese teacher.
Old Antique.
Take care of yourself.
Do you know?
Actually,
at first I thought
I had already sacrificed my life.
Everything I've experienced recently
feels like a dream to me.
But,
I might wake up one day.
I hope that when I wake up,
all my good brothers will be by my side.
I will tell them,
we won.
I don't know
what else I will experience in this life.
But I will always remember
the days I spent with you.
Is it not a pleasure to learn and practice what you have learned?
Is it not a delight to have friends come from afar?
Is he not a gentleman who remains unbothered when others do not understand him?
A gentleman does not seek a full belly nor a comfortable home.
He is diligent in his actions and careful in his speech.
Hi, Yaoyao.
Yiyi!
Guess where I am right now.
Where is that?
I'm at school now.
I'm a teacher now.
Ah? When did you become a teacher?
How come I didn't know?
It's not a big deal.
At first, I was quite torn.
I was afraid I wouldn't do a good job.
But unexpectedly,
after I came, I realized it's no big deal.
Yiyi, you are so brave.
I really admire you.
What's there to admire?
You persisted in doing what you wanted to do.
What about you?
What are you doing now?
I'm writing that paper on the Southbound Overseas Chinese Mechanics.
By the way,
um,
is Old Antique with you?
He went to his driving lesson.
Then tell him.
I'm not just a troublemaker.
Also,
young people today all have their own ideas.
Even though many people don't understand why I do this,
but Yaoyao,
I believe
you will understand me.
I didn't choose to lie flat.
My choice is right.
I believe in you, Yiyi.
Keep it up.
Hey,
do you want to see our school?
Take a look.
So beautiful.
I'll wait for you to come back, Yiyi.
Okay.
I'll hang up now.
Yeah, bye.
Keep it up.
Bye.
Hear me?
Drive like this.
Drive properly.
Did you hear me?
With the way you drive,
you have to come practice even on your day off tomorrow.
Every day, you never give me peace of mind.
Aren't you hot wearing so much today?
I'm used to it.
Tell me.
How did your license get revoked?
Speeding.
I hate people like you who speed.
You think your skills are amazing.
Let me tell you,
speeding is not allowed here.
You must obey the law,
use your turn signals according to traffic rules.
If you see an old lady walking her dog across the crosswalk,
you wait right there until she passes before stepping on the gas.
Hear me?
Just drive like this.
However you say.
Let's go for a spin.
Oh! Oh!
The way you drive...
Slow down.
Goodbye.
Lin Yaozu.
We will definitely meet again.
Right?
Publisher.