♪In youth there is confusion♪
♪And collision♪
♪But so what♪
♪Invisible darkness♪
♪Gives me♪
♪More invisible power♪
♪The unyielding heart♪
♪Gives a signal♪
♪And has a pair of wings♪
♪Darkness won't be a problem♪
♪The day gets dark♪
♪So the light is on♪
♪Get ready to pull out♪
♪The gun is fired♪
♪Time goes by without stop♪
♪Days and nights♪
♪It keeps shining♪
♪Self-discipline is♪
♪The edge of the blade♪
♪Focus on enjoying♪
♪Every moment♪
♪Life will be worth♪
♪The power given by youth♪
♪Blood is burning♪
♪Scores determine the outcome♪
♪In the dark I am♪
♪The only light♪
♪Taking back hard work in old days♪
♪Applause replaces cold treatment♪
♪I'll always run to you♪
♪And be your eternal sun♪
♪The only light♪
=Hello, The Sharpshooter=
=Episode 11=
Well done.
The center density is quite right.
Xiaoci.
Look at my sweat.
It's all because of the training.
You haven't eaten, right?
I brought you some food
from the canteen.
Have some..
Xiaoci.
You prepared
the food specially for me?
Hard work
indeed pays off.
You have to keep up the hard work.
Or there will be no payback.
The food from the canteen
is so good today.
Even the rice is so delicious.
If I practice like this every day,
can you bring me food tomorrow?
Let's go over there first.
(Locker Room)
Hold them.
Do you know what they are?
Leather coats for air rifle shooting.
Don't you only practice air pistol?
Let's go.
Captain,
you look so cool in that outfit.
But our captain
looks perfect in everything.
Captain!
Captain,
I've finally managed
to borrow a rifle for you.
Tell me,
how are you gonna thank me?
It's quite heavy.
Just do two shots.
After all, air pistol
is different from air rifle.
Easy does it.
Our captain is an all-rounder.
Yes.
Special target sheets.
Thanks.
Captain Shen,
let me change the target sheets for you.
Thank you.
Miss Tang,
how did Captain come to think of
giving you a demo of air rifle shooting?
It was a spur-of-the-moment idea.
It's ready, Captain Shen.
He's loading the rifle.
10.9.
Awesome!
Awesome, Captain!
That's great!
Fantastic!
Yes, he's awesome.
10.9.
Your target is
several times larger
than ours.
Ours is a coin target
and you could even…
Captain Shen,
your shooting posture
is also up to standard.
Your shooting talent
is beyond question.
Our captain is an all-rounder.
- Yes, an all-rounder!
- An all-rounder!
Our captain is capable enough to do it.
Don't be so shocked.
Thanks.
Captain, you rock!
Awesome, Captain!
Captain is my idol.
I was wrong.
I know you are not only good at
air pistol,
but we'd better
keep practicing air pistol.
Wait a minute.
Air rifle shooters
call this outfit skin.
Externally,
it can insulate against
the recoil force of the rifle.
Internally,
it can insulate against
subtle changes
including heartbeat.
I suppose you know this.
Give it to me.
Leave it here for now.
Stretch out your hands.
Your shooting posture is unstable.
It can help you improve
the stability of your shooting.
And give you a feel of practice.
Shen Qingyuan.
Did you call me?
You don't remember me?
Hi, Captain Shen.
I am Tang Xin from Rui Live.
Starting from today,
I'll be in complete charge of
recording the shooting team's
daily routine
and I'll also try hard to be
a good roommate who brings no trouble.
Hope I can get your approval.
What are you doing?
Back then,
we didn't have a good start
and brought many confusions and hassles
to each other.
Now, Shen Qingyuan,
let's start all over again.
The best scenario is…I can accept you
and you can accept me.
Shen Qingyuan,
go sleep in your bedroom.
Or you'll easily catch a cold here...
Shen Qingyuan,
why are you being so nice to me?
Didn't you say
you couldn't remember me?
Or is it that
whether you remember me or not,
you will always find me again?
It's quite heavy,
but it can relieve pressure.
Can you feel your heartbeat?
What about cellphone vibrations?
(Shen Qingyuan)
(Accept)
It seems
this is a substandard leather coat.
No.
It's quite good.
If only I could wear this leather coat
for the 2v2 game
and the following commentary
tomorrow.
Air pistol is different from air rifle.
Air pistol is all about
challenging yourself.
You too.
Tang Xin. Keep it up!
♪Having the world between my arms♪
Tang Xin.
Is he gonna give me a high-five?
♪You make me♪
This is clay.
Imagine.
Imagine you are holding
the wooden cover of an air pistol.
Control the intensity of your force.
♪Let time tell♪
♪My true heart to you baby♪
He still remembers
what I said yesterday.
Keep it up.
♪I just want to be with you♪
♪No vows and confessions are needed♪
Raise your arm.
Keep your feet further apart.
Shoulder width apart.
Keep this hand relaxed.
♪Your love♪
♪Is simple yet special♪
♪Because of you♪
Come here.
♪I've found my purpose in life♪
♪You make me realize♪
♪The simpler the love the better baby♪
Give it a try.
♪We need no drama♪
♪I only want to hold you in my arms♪
Keep your hand relaxed.
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The chocolate foundation…
The taste of the barbecue…
The taste…
The taste of the barbecue
is in…invincibly super-duper spicy.
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The taste of the barbecue
The chocolate foundation
and marshmallows…
Let's go.
OK.
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
Chocolate…
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The chocolate foundation
and marshmallows
are so sweet that you worry about
losing your teeth, teeth, teeth.
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The chocolate foundation
and marshmallows
are so sweet that you worry about
losing your teeth, teeth, teeth.
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The chocolate foundation
and marshmallows
are so sweet that you worry about
losing your teeth, teeth, teeth.
The taste of the barbecue
is invincibly super-duper spicy.
The chocolate foundation
and marshmallows
are so sweet that you worry about
losing your teeth, teeth, teeth.
Why?
Please enjoy.
Thanks.
You are here, Mr. Du.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
This way, please.
Go.
Please.
Thanks.
Another drink.
Wait a minute.
You guys go with me to drink a toast.
Hold on a second.
Mr. Du.
We haven't met for a long time.
Well, here's to you.
- Mr. Du.
- Hello.
Mr. Du.
No, thanks.
I need to talk to your boss
about something.
OK. Go back to drink first.
We'll come over later.
All right. Come over later.
OK. Go.
You've become a rare visitor.
How have you been?
Haven't you devoted yourself to sports?
Why do you have time
to patronize this place today?
I'm just here to look around
and incidentally test myself.
Test?
Do you know how I feel
when I see these things now?
Just one word.
Boring.
Bro, have you become dumb
since you started practicing shooting?
Have I?
Do you have to be so deep into the game?
It's all because of
the one who guides me.
Shen Qingyuan?
Well, bro,
now you are also
thinking about a partner on your mind.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about a chick.
No.
I shouldn't call her
with such a tacky word.
Is there a story?
Come on.
Come on, tell me more.
What's going on?
I'm off.
You've just come and you are leaving?
Curfew time.
She's only given me
an hour for some fresh air.
I'm off.
(Du Lingfeng)
Xiaoci.
How can you have
Du Lingfeng as your WeChat contact?
Didn't you agree not to befriend him?
As you know,
we've been playing 2v2 these days.
I have to keep an eye on him.
Be mindful.
Don't lose control of yourself.
I'm going for a shower.
Dr. Ding,
here's my update for you.
I've been practicing rap these days
and getting on pretty well.
Besides, I found
Shen Qingyuan has become
increasingly softer to me,
and occasionally even very gentle.
Could it be he's remembered something?
Whether or not
he's remembered something,
it's a good sign, isn't it?
Tang Xin, keep it up.
Thank you, Dr. Ding.
I wanted to thank you in person,
but you've been on leave these days.
Also,
is there any disagreement
between you and Mr. Zhou these days?
(Dr. Ding typing…)
I'm sorry, Dr. Ding.
Am I talking too much?
I shouldn't have
asked about your privacy.
It's OK.
Nine times out of ten,
disappointing things
happen to us in our lives.
There may be few people
we can confide in.
You'll probably understand this
when you grow up more.
Is maturity
such a cruel thing?
But Dr. Ding,
I believe
everything will be fine.
You are right.
But I hope you'll never
get to experience these things.
And your Shen Qingyuan.
(Mental Health Assessment Report)
You've recovered pretty well
after this period of therapy.
I don't think
anything will go wrong with you again.
Dr. Ding,
thank you for what you did
during this period of time.
I might not
be able to hold on till now without you.
I don't know
if I'll have the chance
to see you again in the coming days.
Of course you will.
No.
I mean
not in a doctor-patient relationship.
Could we
develop it further?
I'm sorry.
I have a husband already.
Sorry.
It's OK.
I'm off for now.
OK.
Here you are.
Excuse me
for not seeing you to the door.
(Hubby)
I'd rather not have one.
Don't think nonsense.
Concentrate on your work, Tang Xin.
Are you all right?
Why are you not having that thing on?
What?
The head?
Because I'm going to drink some water.
Are you gonna do livestreaming?
Would you like me
to tap the beat for you?
Won't that take up your time for rest?
Come to work in the living room.
I'll tap the beat for you.
I'll begin.
Hey, boy,
never mind
how small the target paper looks,
how far it is from you,
blocking out everything
and leveling the sight bead
is the choice for calming your mind.
I heard that shooters
find faith in guns
and their bullets
are always straight linear.
Looking for the destined magnetic field
is something to long for.
(Your Bear: Good rhythm.)
Hello, Tang Xin.
Nothing particular.
I'm just a bit uptight.
I'm going to do livestreaming tomorrow.
OK, OK.
I see.
Go on with your work.
I'll be waiting for your plan.
OK.
♪Holi holi holiday♪
♪No need for an alarm
Get out of bed quickly♪
♪Today's first ray of morning light
With a new dress♪
♪With a new dress on me♪
I knew it was you.
♪Don't stare at me
as if you had delusions♪
♪Spend the holiday together♪
♪Join the fun party together♪
(Summer Wind: Yesterday's lyricism
didn't work, so it's shooting+rap today.)
(The livestreamer is so talented.
I think she's going to hit the big time!)
♪Don't be afraid of being unmasked
You must know you can do it♪
♪Just trust the feeling♪
♪Who cares what will happen tomorrow♪
♪I can't expect anything better
without you♪
♪Will appear♪
Thank you, Brother Big Spender.
Brother Big Spender,
do you ask for any extra services?
Like extra VOD
and commentary and things like that.
♪Do whatever you want
Just like you are…♪
♪Holi holi holiday♪
Do your livestream well.
Don't take others as your brother
willy-nilly.
All right. Thank you, guys.
Bye. Bye.
♪Promise me you'll come again♪
♪Holi holi holiday♪
Great!
Hasn't she signed off?
Why is she filming the wall?
Is it getting stuck?
(You two are inseparable.
Your fate is intertwined.)
Do you…
want to open this?
You open it.
Can I ask you a question?
Why are you wearing
so many layers these days?
You begin to stammer
as soon as you see me.
I wonder if
it is because I'm inadequately clothed,
so I just put on extra layers of clothes
in case your thoughts begin to wander.
I don't daydream.
I mean wild imaginations.
Wild.
So you are
wearing extra layers for me?
Thank you.
But
you don't have to wear so many layers.
I think
it's necessary for us to have a test.
Hasn't she signed off yet?
What are they doing?
I'll begin.
Are you OK?
What about now?
I got it.
This is
the ultimate dressing code
for getting on with you.
I'll bear this in mind.
Tang Xin,
you brought this on yourself.
Don't blame me.
Hello, sir.
Do you know
someone who can do simple processing
on videos and photos?
I need them tonight.
OK. Thank you, sir.
I'll send them to you now.
Is this Room 401?
Xin.
What…what brings you here?
I'm here…
to bring you the quilt Mom made for you.
Didn't you say you'd send a package?
What's the point of sending a package?
If I didn't say that,
how could you
tell me your address honestly?
Tang Liqi, you've picked up vices.
You've become cunning.
I can't help it.
Mom taught me well.
No, no, no.
It's not what you think.
Well,
were you guys undressing
while livestreaming?
You've got something.
There are just the three of us.
Is it going to be OK?
It'll be OK.
Look at you,
I know you usually
react more slowly than others,
but you were
just too daring.
Xin, where is your room?
I'll put the stuff in there for you.
Let me do it.
Thanks.
Xin,
the high-octane scenes have been sent.
There's no use in worrying.
Well, why are your…
your glasses
hanging so low?
I forgot to introduce myself.
Hello, brother-in-law.
I'm Tang Liqi.
Tang Xin's younger brother.
Hello.
Well…
Actually, I am your idol.
No, no.
You are my idol.
A slip of the tongue.
It's OK.
It's a bit embarrassing.
Can't help it.
Brother-in-law,
this is a mobile game I'm playing.
Let me give you a demo.
Brother-in-law,
you are so good at shooting.
You must be an expert
in such shooting games.
Tang Liqi!
He's not your brother-in-law.
Shooting game?
Nowadays we are in the e-game area.
It's called first-person shooting game.
It's super-duper.
Tang Liqi.
Stop your demo.
He…he doesn't know how to play.
Brother-in-law, are you not interested?
I don't usually play these games.
Prince Charming of Marksmanship.
Got it.
It shouldn't be the case though.
Do you play no games at all?
It's OK.
Let me tell you,
- this AK is super powerful.
- Tang Liqi.
It's more powerful than M4.
- I picked up an AK…
- Tang Liqi!
How long are you staying?
I…
Right.
I've got to go.
The anime I'm following
is about to be updated
in 30 or 40 minutes.
I really can't spend time with you guys.
I'll take a tangerine.
Bye, brother-in-law.
Xin.
I can solve
livestreaming problems for you,
but only limited to the computer
and internet area.
I really have no idea of other areas.
I see. Get out of here quickly.
OK, OK, OK.
Be safe on the way.
I will, I will, I will.
Brother-in-law.
Bye.
Good…
Good night.
Morning.
Xin.
Lizi,
why does everybody look weird
as if they don't want to talk to me?
Tang Xin,
why are you so careless?
Don't you know our company outright bans
livestreaming on an alternative account?
Now you are in trouble.
Ai has reported you.
I didn't use public resources.
And I was only entertaining myself.
Why did Ai report me?
How did she know
I was doing livestreaming
on an alternative account?
Don't worry so much.
Your top priority of the moment is
is to explain to Mr. Zhou.
To beg for mercy.
Well, it needs to be revised here.
Mr. Zhou.
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhou.
I was indeed doing livestreaming
on my alternative account,
but I didn't do any publicity
in the company's name,
still less seek personal gain.
Tell me your story.
Why did you open an alternative account?
I was doing it…
under the force of circumstances.
What was the force of circumstances?
Tang Xin,
I actually found out about it
in the shooting hall the other day,
but I was afraid that…
so I dared not speak out.
Do you find yourself
unable to speak properly
facing Shen Qingyuan?
Mr. Zhou,
I do find myself stammer
when talking to Shen Qingyuan,
but I've found a way of
doing livestream and giving commentaries
through rapping.
I don't stammer at all.
And it goes well with
the rhythm of the game.
Yesterday, I was using
an alternative account
to do an experiment,
and found it worked well.
I was thinking of
talking to you about it today.
It's all my fault.
I was too hasty
and too eager to defend Mr. Zhou
and Rui Live.
I didn't expect Tang Xin
was working out a way
to solve her stammer problem.
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhou.
I was too impulsive.
I caused a misunderstanding.
You did the right thing.
It's you to blame.
Why didn't you
tell me earlier that you stammer?
How can stammer be overcome so quickly
by practicing?
Even rap livestreaming.
No.
It's neither serious nor fitting.
No, no.
Tang Xin,
this issue can be either big
or small.
Either
you cure your stammer quickly
or give me a new plan,
otherwise there's nothing I can do.
Mr. Zhou,
please don't be angry.
I think Tang Xin
must have her own inconveniences.
But in order to avoid suspicion,
I think
it's better
to have the alternative account deleted.
Let's go on.
Xin,
were you doing the livestream
on an alternative account?
When
did you start stammering?
A few days ago.
You really make me worry.
Don't be disrespectful to your senior.
I'm not stammering on purpose.
What's going on, Tang Xin?
Ai didn't get to see you
when she came just now.
She asked me to pass the word to you
that Mr. Zhou reminds you
to delete the live room
on your alternative account.
Mr. Zhou said no to rap livestreaming.
♪I'm not used to being a yes-man♪
♪But unless I'm sure♪
♪Some things are better left unsaid♪
♪You watch how I fail again♪
♪Thoughts pour over me♪
♪I can't get away♪
♪When looking up I'm all wet♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I'm familiar with waiting♪
♪How can I avoid it♪
♪Why does it keep bothering me♪
♪It's simply a kind of self-defense♪
♪Cover my eyes♪
♪Hiding quietly in the corner
with lights off♪
♪Even steep roads will be much gentler♪
♪I've enjoyed the scenery♪
♪But I still don't want to leave♪
♪In front of you
I try to behave more naturally♪
♪But I'm still clumsy♪
♪I haven't said anything♪
♪In case I say too much or too little♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I miss you regularly♪
♪Finally I get free♪
♪Torture me as you wish♪
♪Love is just over♪
♪I pretend
I don't understand the failure♪
♪I still don't admit it♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪Welcome and take care♪
♪When I leave♪
♪I nod whether I smile or feel sad♪
♪I've bidden farewell
to everything about you♪
♪From this day on♪
♪I'll get ready and leave♪
♪My future can be bright♪