♪In youth there is confusion♪
♪And collision♪
♪But so what♪
♪Invisible darkness♪
♪Gives me♪
♪More invisible power♪
♪The unyielding heart♪
♪Gives a signal♪
♪And has a pair of wings♪
♪Darkness won't be a problem♪
♪The day gets dark♪
♪So the light is on♪
♪Get ready to pull out♪
♪The gun is fired♪
♪Time goes by without stop♪
♪Days and nights♪
♪It keeps shining♪
♪Self-discipline is♪
♪The edge of the blade♪
♪Focus on enjoying♪
♪Every moment♪
♪Life will be worth♪
♪The power given by youth♪
♪Blood is burning♪
♪Scores determine the outcome♪
♪In the dark I am♪
♪The only light♪
♪Taking back hard work in old days♪
♪Applause replaces cold treatment♪
♪I'll always run to you♪
♪And be your eternal sun♪
♪The only light♪
=Hello, The Sharpshooter=
=Episode 35=
Did I provoke him?
Dr. Ding,
what should I do?
Am I supposed to leave
or should I call 120?
I noticed yesterday
that he'd turn away from me
once he saw me.
But once
something bad happened to me,
he'd control his emotions
and force himself to look after me.
If I keep being around him,
I'm concerned
that he may
be more and more depersonalized.
And his career may be…
Tang Xin,
please calm down.
The most important thing right now is
the helper needs
to share the patient's pain.
So for Shen Qingyuan's sake,
you have to stay strong.
Only with the help of your guidance
will Shen Qingyuan be willing
to come back
and take the psychotherapies
so that he can continue to shoot.
Dr. Ding,
I really don't know
what I'm supposed to do now.
Tang Xin,
you must affect Shen Qingyuan
with positive emotions.
Don't be scared.
Because you're the crux of his disease.
Every time he sees you,
it's like he's facing the trauma itself.
His agony
is his emotion
that has gone out of control.
So the constant positive emotions
from you
will help rectify his reaction.
Understand?
Okay, I understand.
Don't worry.
You can do this.
I have faith in you.
But if his condition worsens,
you let me know at once.
Yes, something is destined,
but I believe men can conquer destiny.
Men can conquer destiny.
Shen Qingyuan.
Did you feed me
with medicine last night?
I was in deep sleep.
Was I difficult to look after?
Put my coat on.
I'm not cold.
Shen Qingyuan.
(Low battery)
Your cellphone is out of power.
I'll help you charge it.
(Unanswered Calls: Dad Mom)
I know I shouldn't do this.
When I was young,
I hated to be forced to get up
by my parents.
But there's a saying.
No going hard,
no getting up.
Here I come.
You're so heavy.
I can't get you out.
I'll move the bed away, okay?
The bed is heavier than you.
Shen Qingyuan,
even though you don't speak to me,
I have ways to make you happy.
Shen Qingyuan,
welcome to Tang Xin's mini play.
This is the exclusive drama for you.
What play will it be?
I'll improvise, then.
Once upon a time,
there was a little hedgehog.
He was super aloof.
Just like you, Shen Qingyuan.
The hedgehog
was like a boss in the forest.
Because he was covered with spikes.
No one would dare to get close to him.
But over time,
the hedgehog felt
a touch of loneliness.
One day,
the hedgehog smelled
something weird.
That should be
the smell of destiny.
The hedgehog felt like
the duck had feelings for him.
So after long deliberation,
the hedgehog decided
not to be aloof anymore,
and chase the duck.
But the duck was startled.
When the duck
saw the hedgehog for the first time,
he was still a small hedgehog
who had short and soft
spikes.
But now, the hedgehog had grown up.
He was covered
with pointy large spikes.
How would the duck
dare to get near him?
And
the duck had her own problem.
In her youth,
when the duck played with the hedgehog,
she accidentally lost
most of her feathers,
so later the duck
became featherless.
So all of her shortcomings
were fully exposed.
If the hedgehog didn't protect her…
My comedy turned out a failure.
It looks like
I lack talent in comedy.
I'm supposed to guide
and cure you.
Now nothing works.
♪As a blank canvas♪
Shen Qingyuan,
I'll go make breakfast for you.
♪I can feel the ways of the world♪
♪Tears shed for you♪
If someone harms you,
I can protect you.
But if the one who harms you is me,
Tang Xin…
♪Your heart rippled a little♪
♪If I can stay by your side♪
♪My life will bloom for you♪
♪Maybe the last second♪
♪You won't remember me♪
♪At least I'm brave enough♪
♪Love is like wind♪
♪You're unreal♪
♪Ride the wildest wave♪
♪Have fun like a kid♪
♪As a blank canvas♪
♪Hopefully with the one I love♪
♪I can feel the ways of the world♪
♪Tears shed for you♪
♪I believe in that moment♪
You came downstairs at last.
Breakfast will soon be ready.
Let's have breakfast together.
You can't leave
without having your breakfast.
♪If I can keep you company♪
Shen Qingyuan.
Since I failed to comfort you
or cheer you up,
it's time to show you
how dark the world is.
♪Maybe the last second♪
It's different
from the tutorial.
Shen Qingyuan.
♪At least I'm brave enough♪
So this is how it feels
when you look down at me.
The tutorial said,
if your boyfriend is mad,
you can fix it in three steps.
Make a turn,
take a leap and kiss him.
But it didn't say
what to do if you fail to kiss him.
♪You won't remember me♪
♪Maybe that's what happiness is♪
(Dad)
Shen Qingyuan,
the call from your dad.
Won't you pick it up?
I'll speak to your dad
on your behalf, then.
Mr. Shen.
Qingyuan isn't
doing very well.
I'd like to tell you something.
And I owe you and Mrs. Shen
an apology.
Shen Qingyuan's stress response
was caused by me.
I didn't expect the winter training
would become like this.
You didn't expect many other things.
Captain and Miss Tang's
romantic relationship
hasn't been smooth.
Don't feel so down, boys.
We can't just wait.
Listen, Tang Xin.
Now the top priority
is that Qingyuan gets
the best medical treatment.
His mother and I
will rush back to the country
as soon as possible.
Before that,
you'll have to
take care of him for us.
No problem, Mr. Shen.
Oh, Mr. Shen.
Do you still remember
what exactly happened
when Shen Qingyuan had the car accident?
Sorry, I don't really remember
what exactly happened.
But what I do have
are some police documents
about the car accident.
How about
I send them to you?
Okay.
Mr. Shen, bye.
Thank you.
Dr. Ding.
How long will it approximately take
for Shen to get well once he takes
the clinical psychotherapy
by your estimation?
I can't really say.
You know
that Shen Qingyuan has a record
of running away from
clinical psychotherapy before.
To be honest, Dr. Ding.
The team is facing pressure
from every direction.
The Chinese New Year is near.
The trial for national team
will be in April,
by then…
Let's put how I explain
to the university or the bureau aside,
I'm afraid it can cause
more damage to Shen.
He
had too smooth
of a career before.
A fallen prodigy
only has two options.
He either falls to the bottom
and becomes an ordinary guy
or
struggles out of it
and flies to higher places.
Which one
do you think Shen Qingyuan is?
Let's wait for the message
from Tang Xin for now.
(Coach Zhang)
Hello, Tang Xin.
Hello, Coach.
I spoke
to Shen Qingyuan's dad.
Glad to know.
But I
have to tell you that
the shooting team doesn't give shooters
very long Spring Festival holidays.
If Shen doesn't return to the team
after the holidays…
I see, sir.
I'll try to find the solution
as soon as possible.
Okay.
I'll help you
handle the pressure from the bureau.
I've seen
too many talented shooters
fall halfway through.
This time,
I'm willing to sacrifice my job
to keep Shen Qingyuan around.
Tang Xin, good luck.
I wish to hear the best from you.
Miss Live Streamer,
get Shen Qingyuan back.
Tang Xin,
I believe
you and Shen Qingyuan
can get through the toughest.
Miss Tang, good luck,
help Captain through it.
Miss Tang, don't worry.
God will get Captain
back on his feet.
Tang Xin,
please.
Girl,
you're the hope for Captain Shen.
Shen Qingyuan,
it is your tug-of-war with fate.
Everybody
is on your side.
So please, get well.
Okay?
(Road Traffic Accident)
(Responsibility Confirmation)
From south to north.
Shen Qingyuan was going
in the wrong direction.
Collision.
Shen Qingyuan.
Let's go back to Yongcheng.
Shen Qingyuan, look.
This is
the Road Traffic Accident
Responsibility Confirmation.
According to this,
you weren't running away.
You were on the way to save me.
Look.
You didn't run away.
You wanted to save me.
If you still don't believe me,
let's go
to the site of accident and verify it.
Okay?
Shen Qingyuan,
let's drop our luggage
at the hotel.
Then we buy some snacks
for Jujube.
We went out in a rush.
I'm worried that we didn't
bring enough food for him.
Jujube.
I thought he'd miss us.
So before I left,
I shipped him here.
We'll soon arrive.
It should be around here.
But we need to
spend more time finding the turn.
You know?
It's become so different
from what it was like in 2015.
Look over there.
The subway.
And the road is wider.
Are you sure it's this road?
I am.
A small path can grow.
Let's go.
This is the crossing
we'd always pass.
This should be it.
It's okay, Shen Qingyuan.
Look.
(Road Traffic Accident
Responsibility Confirmation)
All that you did at the time
was recorded
by this surveillance camera.
The car came from uphill,
and was driving south.
But you were going in
the wrong direction.
So the car hit right into you.
Shen Qingyuan,
I'm dead certain
that you were trying to save me.
You were running towards me.
Let's go up there.
Maybe it'll ring a bell.
Let me go!
Don't move!
On that day,
this is where I was…
Stop.
It's okay.
Shen Qingyuan.
After we took our selfie,
it didn't take us long
to walk to this place.
And then we ran into the robbers.
I think these two
had a criminal record,
so they hid here.
They heard us, and they…
Would you like to go and have a look?
No.
Tang Xin,
let's head back.
Shen Qingyuan,
it's good enough
that you walked me here.
Does it mean
you're starting to believe me?
Even if the evidence
that Zhou Yue provided is real.
A responsibility confirmation form
and a screenshot
of the footage of the car accident.
The two pieces
of real evidence
are enigmatically contradictory.
Does it mean
there's another explanation
about the whole thing?
Tang Xin,
why do you have so much faith in me?
You're such an idiot.
You still don't get
how I really feel.
It's because I love you.
When you're in love with someone,
how do you not
know who he is like?
He's nice to me,
and I've felt it
in my daily life.
And that
is something
that cannot be easily erased.
I love you,
so I trust you.
I'm sorry.
The moment you say sorry
makes me want to cry.
I won't say it again.
That's more like it.
You can't let me experience
such a hard time again.
Nor can you leave me behind again.
Thank you.
There you go. You're welcome.
Coming.
How do you know
I like Yoji nectar?
I didn't know.
My gut feeling told me to order it.
So
you haven't completely
lost your memory,
am I right?
Before,
you often took the bus
back and forth with me
to have the desserts here.
Yoji nectar was my favorite.
You teased me,
saying only kids love desserts.
Why don't you say something?
Being quiet is so not you.
It's good
to be quiet from time to time.
You have nothing to say to me already?
What do we do
once we live together, then?
Live together?
Sure.
That's very likely.
Even if it is,
it's still early to talk about it.
Get prepared.
You never know.
♪Like I have a predisposition♪
What's my favorite?
I surely remember.
Yoji nectar.
Two Yoji nectar, please.
Thank you.
♪Blush, stammer, out of breath♪
♪All of my symptoms♪
♪Are caused by you♪
Still tastes the same.
No wonder
this shop is still here
while other ones aren't.
It has been waiting for us to return.
♪Control my emotions♪
Shen Qingyuan,
do you still remember
saying this a lot back then?
"A professional athlete
isn't supposed to have desserts."
♪No one can defend♪
♪The disease is you Oh♪
It's okay that you don't remember.
I don't mean to blame you.
I don't know why,
but as soon as I entered the shop,
I had
a strange feeling.
Is it because it hasn't really changed
just like you said?
It looks like a revisit
has really worked.
In this case,
how about
we go to our high school tomorrow
to recall the good old days?
Which way?
Where should we go?
You can't find the way back
to the school?
I was here before.
I just don't remember the way.
I suck at directions.
I'll check the GPS.
No.
There's a bus station.
- Quickly.
- Quickly, quickly.
Shen Qingyuan,
you're now
using your cellphone quite smoothly.
It's always good to be prepared.
(Bus Stops)
(Destination: Yuying High School)
(Yuying High School)
Shen Qingyuan, look.
The destination of the bus
is our high school.
You remember that?
Yuying High School of Yongcheng.
I do.
I also remember you said
that you went to No. One High School
in the south of the city.
Oops.
You know
I was messing with you, right?
Forget it. Forget it.
We're on this trip
of finding our real memory anyway.
Excuse me. Make way, please.
(Yuying High School of Yongcheng)
I remember here.
Especially that corridor.
When I trained in high school,
I'd only travel between
the classroom and the training gym.
About the rest,
my memory is kind of vague.
That's because all your important
memories about this place
were those you had with me.
So you don't really remember the rest.
Shen Qingyuan, you know?
Every girl has this dream
in a romantic relationship.
They all want to take their boyfriends
to the schools they went to.
The more unfamiliar
the boyfriend
is with the place,
the more fulfillment the girl gains
as his guide.
Let's go inside.
Stop. Stop there.
Who are you?
It's now the winter holiday.
You two don't seem like
the students here.
- We…
- Get out. Get out.
- W-We are…
- We are…
Out. Out.
Who are you two?
You know what?
Sneaking into the school
over the wall
is exactly what we'd do
when we were students.
Shen Qingyuan,
let me show you
what Yuying High School of Yongcheng
is really like.
Follow me.
Those two young people
look familiar.
(A Shooter of Our School Successfully Made It
into the National Junior Shooting Championship!)
Yes.
This is him.
Shen Qingyuan.
(Yuying High School of Yongcheng)
The basketball court.
This is
where I hit the ball
with my head countless times
before
a boy named Shen Qingyuan
caught the ball for me
for no reason.
Shen Qingyuan,
give it back to me.
Shen Qingyuan.
This is the teaching building.
This is
where I'd often
secretly watch you.
(CVS)
And here.
This is the CVS.
(Push)
What's special about it
is that this is
you bought me ice-cream
for the first time.
Too bad, it's the winter holiday.
Do you remember
you bought me ice-cream
at the Candy Carnival?
I do.
That was ice-cream for couples.
Look over there.
(Shooting Center)
Shen Qingyuan.
Shooting Center.
This is where I saw you
for the first time several years ago.
I doubt the authenticity
of the story.
Though I can't really remember it,
I always have a feeling
that the story has another version.
I think I paid attention to you
earlier than you thought.
My state
after our re-encounter
was the best proof.
So
there's no way I abandoned you,
right?
You two.
- Run.
Stop running. Stop running.
Stop. Stop.
Where are you going?
I've locked the gates.
Sir,
we're sorry.
We shouldn't have sneaked in.
It's just
we used to study here.
It's a rare opportunity for us
to revisit our high school.
Sorry
that we caused you trouble.
Sorry.
I just remembered
you're Shen Qingyuan
from the shooting team,
aren't you?
And you're the little girl
who always
followed him anywhere he went,
aren't you?
Tang Xin.
You don't doubt my story now, right?
You came to see the shooting center?
Yes.
I'll open the door, then.
I'll show you around.
It's been so long.
Now that you're here
in your old high school,
we'll enjoy a proper tour.
- Come on.
- Thank you, sir.
Thanks.
(Shooting Center)
Never mind, sir.
No need to open it.
What?
What's wrong?
Sorry.
(Shooting Center)
I mean, you're already here.
Just take a quick look.
Sir,
we came here in a rush.
We'll come back again
when the school is open.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
Fine, fine.
You're welcome
to tour around the school.
Sure, sure.
Okay, okay.
See you next time.
What's the matter with you?
Shen Qingyuan,
do you remember
our promise
about the Olympics?
Xiaoci.
Coach.
Everybody else went home
to celebrate the New Year.
Why are you still here?
No worries. I'll train more.
This is the last year
of the Olympic cycle.
Our responsibility is heavy.
I'm kind of stressed.
But it's fine.
My home isn't far.
I can go home some days later.
Pack your stuff.
I have something to say to you.
Okay.
Xiaoci,
I'd like to hear
your plan for the future.
My plan for the future
is the same as before.
So is my desire to win.
There's something
that you can hold on to,
but if something
happens inevitably,
getting prepared in advance
for yourself is the best option.
You're a sensible girl.
Go home and think about
if you need
to make a change.
Will you put more effort
in the individual race
or will you find a new partner
to continue staying in the mixed team?
But no matter what decision you make,
you have my support.
Thank you, Coach.
I got it.
Coach Zhang,
have you lost
faith in Shen Qingyuan?
I do expect him to return,
but Haiya doesn't
need a shooter
who'd lose control of himself.
Even if he returns,
he'll have to show
that he's good enough
to stay on Haiya Shooting Team.
I see.
Coach said so?
Xiaoci,
I have been
reconsidering
when to quit.
What?
Want to be my new partner?
Are you teasing me?
I'm thinking
if I should delay my quit.
Though you have
a better rapport with Shen Qingyuan
than with me,
I am still
a fine shooter.
I can temporarily
serve as your training partner
until Shen Qingyuan
comes back in a good state.
I'm impressed
that you think this way.
I'm just worried about you.
I'm worried that you may lose hope.
I'm supposed to fulfill
my duty as your boyfriend,
aren't I?
So I'll begrudgingly
stick around a bit longer.
Don't feel stressed, okay?
Got it.
Let me go.
No.
No peeking.
Why so mysterious?
Just let me have a look.
No.
- One look. Just one look.
- No. No.
One look. One look.
Just one look.
- Just one look, please.
- No.
Shen Qingyuan, go get the door.
♪I'm not used to being a yes-man♪
♪But unless I'm sure♪
♪Some things are better left unsaid♪
♪You watch how I fail again♪
♪Thoughts pour over me♪
♪I can't get away♪
♪When looking up I'm all wet♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I'm familiar with waiting♪
♪How can I avoid it♪
♪Why does it keep bothering me♪
♪It's simply a kind of self-defense♪
♪Cover my eyes♪
♪Hiding quietly in the corner
with lights off♪
♪Even steep roads will be much gentler♪
♪I've enjoyed the scenery♪
♪But I still don't want to leave♪
♪In front of you
I try to behave more naturally♪
♪But I'm still clumsy♪
♪I haven't said anything♪
♪In case I say too much or too little♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪I miss you regularly♪
♪Finally I get free♪
♪Torture me as you wish♪
♪Love is just over♪
♪I pretend
I don't understand the failure♪
♪I still don't admit it♪
♪Memories flood back♪
♪Welcome and take care♪
♪When I leave♪
♪I nod whether I smile or feel sad♪
♪I've bidden farewell
to everything about you♪
♪From this day on♪
♪I'll get ready and leave♪
♪My future can be bright♪