(2nd day morning at Yeon House)
"Hold the hand of the woman you're most attracted to..."
"and return here for the first-come, first-served date."
(You have one chance, and the older women can't refuse.)
(At the news of it being first-come, first-served,)
(the younger men start running.)
(Ji Seung.)
(Will you go on a date with me?)
(Ju Hee, go on a date with me.)
(Sure.)
(Ji Hye, if you need some time, I'll wait outside.)
(Let's date with me.)
(You were asking me?)
(I liked it because we held hands.)
(The first date starts with butterflies in their stomachs.)
(When you're on a date,)
(the princess doesn't need to do anything.)
(Is there anyone you're attracted to?)
(You, Jun Han.)
(Thank you.)
(Jun Han and Yu Jin's first date was sweet.)
(If I ask you out...)
(on a date again,)
(will you like it?)
(It'll be weirder if you don't.)
(He's cute.)
(He's funny...)
(and cool too.)
(I don't know anyone else beside you.)
(Do you know anyone in Yeon House?)
(Other women?)
(I don't know either.)
(Is there anyone you're interested in?)
(Jun Han?)
(They either took a step closer or away on the first date.)
(At that time, a message arrived.)
(Older women and younger men, please gather separately.)
(Are they telling us to end this date?)
(I don't want to.)
(What a shame.)
(The younger men arrived at an unknown place.)
(The older women have gathered too.)
(A new younger man has arrived.)
(A new older woman has arrived too.)
(Will their affections and interests change?)
I mean,
what kind of a dating show...
adds the catfish on Episode Two?
I thought they could settle with the current relationships,
but things will change now.
- Things are shaking up. - Exactly.
Yes.
(The first-come, first-served dates chosen by the younger men are over.)
(The older women gather at the designated location.)
(Yu Jin is the first to arrive after her date with Jun Han.)
(Ji Hye arrives after her date with Jin Wu.)
Hello.
You give off a different vibe today.
- Don't I look refreshing? - Yes, very.
Hello.
You both look so pretty.
Come on.
- Hello. - You're here.
- A gorgeous woman walked in. - I'm not.
- Everyone's vibe is so different. - Exactly.
Hello.
- You look so pretty. - Hello.
(Ju Hee arrives after her date with Yun So.)
You look so bright.
How was your date?
(Nodding)
- Was it fun? - Was it fun?
- Was it fun? - Yes.
Really?
- They asked right away. - Right away.
I thought it'd be uncomfortable, but he made me feel very relaxed.
I think we got quite close.
- What about you, Ji Seung? - Me?
Well, he was similar...
to what I thought.
- Who was your date? - Si Won.
Her reply is a bit iffy.
We took a picture together.
Really?
Yes.
Shall I show you the picture?
- Sure. - Yes.
It came out great.
It came out nice.
- We took this too. - It came out really nicely.
- Really. - It was really pretty there.
This is so pretty.
- Is it? - Yes.
Is she showing them the photos because she liked the date?
- Or is it... - Of course she liked it.
- Really? - Yes.
Not something like, "Don't touch him"?
There's a bit of that too.
She's setting the mood.
Going on a 1-on-1 date...
definitely changed things for me.
He was very different from his first impression.
We hit it off a lot better than I thought.
Really?
- I'm curious. - He was very talkative.
Things might be different when you meet them 1-on-1.
They were very satisfied with the dates.
Do you think you'll change your mind...
if they're way too young for you?
I don't know.
- If they're way too young? - Way too young.
Ten years younger.
- Ten? - In that case,
I'd obviously feel very unsettled.
- Yes. - Don't you agree?
- It... - Yes.
I've never dated anyone who's that much younger than me.
- Everyone thinks alike. - Right.
When I first came here,
I told myself I'd just go for it regardless of their age.
That I'd do however I feel like.
But I suddenly got so scared.
Because it feels real.
What if he actually turns out to be ten years younger than me?
I'll be like, "What should I do?"
- Exactly. - It'll be a lot to think about.
(Sighing)
He asked how I'd feel in that situation.
I said, "I'd feel sorry for you."
I hope they're older than they look.
- Me too. - But...
- I hope they just look very young. - Yes.
- Oh, you mean the men? - Yes.
- The men. - The men.
- I agree. - I'm scared.
That's their biggest worry. The younger men's ages.
- Of course. - That's their biggest concern.
But you can't help it if your feelings grow, can you?
- Yes. - Yes.
They can't guess what they'll do themselves...
because they've never met someone so young.
(At that time)
(A black sedan enters the cafe where the older women are.)
None of the men has that kind of car.
None of them rode a sedan.
Hello, I'm Kim Jeong Won.
He's handsome.
Many older women tell me that I don't act like...
a younger man.
He has a good physique.
The older women relied on me more.
If there's something I can help,
I'm sure she won't just think of me as a younger guy.
I'm a fiery man,
so I want to give love.
I want to show them that I'm not immature.
I look forward to it.
(A younger man with a new type of charm makes his appearance.)
I can't wait to see what kind of faces...
they'll make when he goes in.
I'm looking forward to their faces when they see the new man.
So it...
Since there's that...
(Surprised)
Hello.
It's...
(Surprised)
(Whip around)
- They're surprised. - Hello.
He startled me.
- Gosh. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
What's happening?
Hello.
(Confused)
What's happening?
- Hello. - Hello.
Where should he sit?
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- Please sit down. - Okay.
"Please sit down."
- You're sitting in the middle? - Since there are four of you,
I thought I should keep it balanced.
He sure is a different type of guy.
I'm Kim Jeong Won.
- Kim Jeong Won. - Kim Jeong Won.
What are your names?
I'm Gu Ji Seung.
Ji Seung. What's your name?
I'm Park Ji Hye.
Ji Hye.
I'm Choi Yu Jin.
I'm Yu Ju Hee.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so shocked.
I see you already got your drinks.
- Yes. - Would you like some coffee?
- Why don't we talk a bit? - Okay.
(Laughing)
(Glancing)
How was today?
We just came back from our first date.
Could you share how you felt?
- How I felt? - How I felt?
- How I felt? - How did it go?
He leads the conversation.
- He has good leadership. - Well,
yesterday, we spent a long time in a group setting.
We didn't have time to talk individually.
We got to talk a lot and get to know each other a lot.
- It was a 1-on-1 date, right? - Yes.
It sounds fun.
"It sounds fun?"
(Brushing her hair)
(Glancing)
The atmosphere doesn't seem bad so far.
- You'll be doing it soon. - Sorry?
You'll be doing it soon.
Yes, I should soon.
He doesn't look nervous, right?
- Yes. - That's true.
(Glancing)
I'm so upset by their reactions.
- Why? - They came back from the date...
and were sharing how good it was, but now...
- Don't be. - Especially Ji Hye.
- Yes, she's so... - Ji Hye.
I'll just say it frankly.
She fell in love.
Yu Jin also looks like...
She kept doing this.
Do you know how she rolls her shoulder?
Yes, that.
- She rolls her shoulder. - What's that?
She does this.
Ju Hee is no joke too.
Ju Hee is blushing a bit.
They're all so cute.
- Don't you feel awkward? - Sorry?
Don't you feel awkward?
It's a bit awkward.
But we'll be getting closer.
You'd feel less awkward if you drink something.
Then I will...
Would you like a dessert?
Cheese cake?
- If there is. - Cheese cake?
I got it.
I'll go and buy it.
I think I know what you like.
- Really? - Yes.
- Please wait a while. - Okay.
They're so excited.
- See you. - Okay.
- I'll go and buy some. - Okay.
(Jeong Won goes to buy desserts for the older women.)
Isn't he quite similar to Si Won?
- Yes, he is. - Is he?
- He has sharp features. - He looks like an actor.
- Very strong features. - Yes.
They're saying he's handsome if they say...
- he's similar to Si Won. - This is crazy.
- I can't with them. - This is crazy.
Is that what normally happens?
They start talking as soon as the man leaves.
- Of course. - Really?
Of course.
But what about courtesy?
The moment he takes two steps away...
They start talking right away.
Shall we?
He bought so many.
(Surprised)
I bought all the pretty desserts.
Amazing.
What's this?
My gosh.
(He bought every single dessert for the older women.)
There are so many.
He basically bought everything that's on the menu.
- I haven't had lunch yet. - You should eat.
So I'll have a sandwich.
- How pretty. - Thank you.
They're so pretty.
It's the afternoon tea vibe.
- It looks like it. - Aren't they very pretty?
- They are. - Yes, they're so pretty.
- Please go ahead. - Please go ahead.
(Eating)
It's been one day for you.
Did you become close?
Yes.
- You already became close? - Quite.
I think we got closer with the men we dated today.
That's right.
- With your respective date? - Yes.
I still feel awkward with the rest.
We didn't get to talk with everyone...
since it's only been a day.
Then I won't feel too left out, right?
- No. - No.
We all feel left out.
- Really? - Yes.
You all feel left out?
You came at the right timing.
I agree.
What's your ideal type?
(What is Jeong Won's ideal type?)
I'm curious.
There's a specific internal trait...
I personally go after.
What is it?
I'm a bit...
I like someone who can coexist with me.
Someone whom I can imagine planning our future together with.
That's my ideal type.
Someone I can live with.
I think I know what you mean.
Someone whom I can build my future with.
You normally don't use the term "coexist" in a relationship.
Symbiosis, coexistence.
Have you ever dated an older woman?
- An older woman? - I've mostly dated...
older women.
Really?
There were a few younger women,
but the latest relationship was with an older woman.
What was the age gap?
The biggest gap or the most recent one?
- The biggest one? - Both.
The latest one was four years.
And the biggest gap was eight years.
- Those are the numbers. - Eight years.
Yes.
But it didn't really become...
much of an issue.
- Right, age really doesn't matter. - It was the same.
- That wasn't what you said before. - No.
Well... What's that...
You know what I mean, right?
What was that?
- I don't. - This...
(Flustered)
Gosh, hold on. Yu Jin is scary.
She's keeping her in check.
Ji Hye said something else before,
and she thought, "Did I just go back on my word?"
And Yu Jin exposed her immediately.
I must still be half-asleep.
My mind keeps changing.
It isn't easy.
Right.
Does it feel fascinating since you're here for the first time?
It's my first time here,
and my first time meeting you ladies.
Do you use honorifics to your girlfriend...
if she's older than you?
No, I call her "honey."
You use honorifics when you're in a situationship?
It's a bit iffy.
I use honorifics right until I get in a situationship with her.
I just call her by her name when we're in a situationship.
And...
the moment I get in a situationship,
the boundary of age...
disappears a lot.
That's nice.
Yes, that's what situationship is for.
That's right.
How do you feel coming here?
Me?
I'm just getting started.
And I think it'll be fun.
- You think it'll be fun? - Yes.
(The appearance of a new younger man)
(What changes will he bring upon Yeon House?)
His sentences are neat.
"I'm just getting started. And I think it'll be fun."
(Impressed)
- I'm a bit upset. - Why?
It's barely been a few hours since the date,
but they're so happy to see him.
But DinDin, this is the second day.
The older women need to keep changing their minds...
for us to enjoy watching.
- I'm loving this. - Isn't it so fun?
Seeing the older women all flushed makes me so excited.
I hope at least one of them would be indifferent.
But all four of them are so welcoming, which makes me sad.
(The spokesperson of the younger men)
Here it is.
- What is it? - A text?
So everyone gets it?
I didn't get it.
- Neither did I. - Me neither.
(Hold the hand of the older woman you're attracted to...)
(and leave the building to go on a 1-on-1 date.)
This is a big one.
The sound wasn't as loud as yesterday.
(The older women don't know what message Jeong Won received.)
When everyone receives the message, the sound gets so loud.
That's right.
(Getting nervous)
(The benefit given to the catfish, 1-on-1 date)
I think it's either Ju Hee or Yu Jin.
- I think it's Yu Jin. - Yu Jin.
(An awkward tension between the older women)
Then...
Shall we go?
Where are we going?
- Where? Do we leave now? - For me...
For me...
I would like to talk more...
with Ji Hye first.
(I would like to talk more with Ji Hye first.)
You feel bitter when you don't get chosen.
Shall we go?
(Jeong Won chose Ji Hye.)
I'll go have a chat.
- Where are we going? - Shall we?
- We need to hold hands? - Yes.
Holding hands?
Why do they ask us to hold hands?
(Giggling)
Really?
Here you go.
(They head out to a date while holding hands.)
Where are we going?
- Just talk here? - Well...
We just need to go that way.
She's popular.
Ji Hye.
She got to hold many younger men's hands today.
- Exactly. - Honestly, just from watching this,
doesn't it look like Ji Hye likes Jeong Won over Jin Wu?
Frankly, she's forgotten about Jin Wu.
She could forget about him in this moment.
If you ask her,
- she'll go, "Who... Oh, Jin Wu?" - That won't be the case.
(Meanwhile, the older women who weren't chosen)
I feel bitter. What are we going to do about this atmosphere?
(All they can do is laugh.)
- Him joining us... - Yes.
I thought he'd come...
- either today or tomorrow. - Right.
I never imagined he would come at this moment.
- I wonder if there's a new girl. - Me too.
I can't wait to find out who she is.
And I wonder which room she's going to.
- Right. - Which room will she get?
- They're concerned. - Yes.
- Right. - They're like,
"We should also be worried."
- The male catfish is good-looking. - Yes.
So, they're thinking, "The new girl must also be..."
- "attractive." - Obviously.
- Yes. - Obviously.
(After the 1st-come, 1st-served date...)
(with the woman of their choice,)
(the younger men move to the next location.)
(Yun So got here first after the date with Ju Hee.)
- Hey. - Hey.
Good to see you.
How was it?
(The date)
It was fun.
- Who did you go with? - I...
went with Ju Hee.
- You went with Yu Jin, right? - Yes.
Is she your first choice right now?
- No. - Number one?
Not exactly.
- What? - I'm interested in two women.
I can't believe how honest he is.
(When he asked Ju Hee whom she was curious about,)
(she answered, "Jun Han.")
- Jun Han? - Yes.
Ju Hee was interested in him,
so I was concerned.
I want to have a chat with them.
(With the ones I'm interested in)
He must be worried.
(Jin Wu returns after his date with Ji Hye.)
- The forgotten man. - Welcome back.
(Si Won arrives last after his date with Ji Seung.)
Long time no see.
Hey. How was the date?
How was the date?
My first choice has been...
- Ju Hee? - Ju Hee from the beginning.
I was really happy. We had a lot of good food.
And we had a good chat.
It was nice overall.
(It was nice overall.)
We had so much in common.
(With Yu Jin)
So I liked it too.
I certainly prefer a 1-on-1 date.
- Right? - Yes.
She was...
far better than I had expected.
- Really? - Yes.
They're also showing off.
How about we tell each other this?
If you get another chance to pick your date,
would you choose the same person or not?
It won't be such a bad idea...
to go on a date with someone else.
I'd go with the same person.
I want to focus solely on Ju Hee.
I also want to go with the same one.
(With Ji Hye)
Oh, no. Ji Hye went with someone else!
I want someone else.
- Someone else? - Yes.
As I said, I'm interested in two.
(Interested in two women)
You don't want to tell us who you're interested in...
other than Yu Jin, right?
Oh, the other one?
It's one of the three.
I'll be your competitor next time.
He's really straightforward.
(After their first dates,)
(there's tension in the air among the younger men.)
The younger men in Season Two are brutally honest.
He said, "I'll be your competitor next time,"
with a smile on his face,
- It hits hard. - so it hit harder.
- The older woman. - Here she comes.
Here comes the star.
(A car arrives at the coffee shop where the younger men are waiting.)
I think...
I'm the total package.
(I think I'm the total package.)
In terms of intelligence, personality,
and looks, I lack nothing.
She has it all?
I've already bought a house...
at the best location in all of South Korea.
That's amazing.
He can just stay at home and be a homemaker.
I'll be the breadwinner.
I could pay off his student loan.
But I won't be able to tolerate...
any credit loans.
I'm confident...
that they'll fall for me eventually.
(Lee Jin Young)
Oh, she's pretty.
(The fifth older woman walks toward the younger men.)
Hello.
Hi, everyone.
Wake up, Jin Wu.
Wake up, dude!
Oh, my gosh.
Hi, everyone.
(They don't know where to look as soon as she enters.)
Jun Han seems to be in love.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They weren't expecting to see her.)
We should get her a chair.
Jin Wu is the first one to move.
You can sit in the top seat.
(Jin Wu moves faster than any other men.)
(Restless)
They're all stunned.
- Hello. - It's nice to meet you all.
- Nice to meet you. - Hi.
Hello.
Have you been waiting long?
- No, not really. - No?
- That's good. - If we had known you were coming,
we would have dressed up more.
- Didn't you know I was coming? - Not at all.
Really? I see.
(Looking)
She looked fancy.
Appearance-wise, I like women...
who have large eyes...
like a fennec fox.
She was beautiful.
(She was beautiful.)
All the younger men are frozen...
- because she looked so tough. - Yes.
- They don't know what to do. - Exactly.
It's cute.
Tell me your names, please.
I'm Yu Jin Wu.
- Yu Jin Wu. - Jin Wu.
I'm Lee Si Won.
Lee Si Won.
I'm Lee Yun So.
- Lee Yun... - So.
- Yun So. - Yes.
- I'm Lee Jun Han. - Jun Han.
- Yes, Jun Han. - Jun Han.
My name is Lee Jin Young.
- Please remember. - We will.
Jin Young?
- Lee Jin Young. - Jin Young.
Jin Young.
Have you gotten to know each other by now?
- The men did. - Considering it's our first...
Just the men?
What about the women?
- We're getting to know them. - We're pretty close.
I see. I was worried, in fact.
I was worried that you would all be close by now.
Of course, she was.
We only met last night, so...
- Last night? - Yes.
(Relieved)
I see.
- What would you like? - What would you like?
I...
I'll take the orange drink.
- Orange? - Yes, please.
(Jin Wu naturally looks after her.)
Jin Wu is so sweet.
- You all had lunch, right? - Yes.
- Didn't you? - Me?
- No. - Should we give you bread?
I feel like we should give her bread.
Do you want me to cut it?
- The cake? - Yes.
- This is... - Would you like a fork?
Thank you.
(The younger men got busy looking after her.)
Do you like it?
Eat up.
You can eat.
(Staring)
Would you like a blanket if it's uncomfortable?
Yes, please.
- That was so sweet. - I was about to ask you.
You're so considerate.
I was about to ask you.
You're amazing.
(They were one step behind.)
Jin Wu is so sweet.
Thank you.
(Smiling)
I'm so thankful.
I don't know if he's always that considerate,
but he is.
- He's so polite. - It's natural for him.
Does that give him extra points?
I'd be so grateful. He does get extra points.
A sweet guy is the best.
- Yes, a sweet guy. - Yes.
Did you do anything before this?
- We... - Were you on a date?
- Yes, we all were. - Yes.
I have a question, then.
Do you have anyone you're interested in?
All of you.
How would they answer that?
(She asked them out of the blue.)
(Flustered)
We had a vote on the first night, so...
I'm sure everyone has one.
That was a good save, Yun So.
You must be worried.
- Me? - Right?
No, I'm not worried.
(No, I'm not worried)
I'm not.
I doubt anything major happened in only one day.
That's true.
- Am I right? - Yes.
Right.
Do you have a type, Jin Young?
I actually...
(What's her ideal type?)
I like someone who's like a puppy.
A puppy?
Like a large dog?
Like...
- Maltese? - A large...
Not a Maltese.
(Joking)
I like someone who's like a large dog,
but when I think about everyone I've dated so far,
they were all different.
I don't think...
it's about the looks. Once I'm hooked on something,
I fall for him.
- Is there a specific quality? - Specific?
When he's...
being considerate?
- Considerate. - Considerate.
Jin Wu must have earned a few points.
I know, right?
The blanket.
Jin Wu!
(Shy)
You can't beat sweetness.
And I'd like to have good banter.
- Like... - Do you like to make jokes?
- You're trying to make jokes. - No.
I like it, though.
I like a guy who's funny...
and is on the same wavelength.
Being able to have a proper conversation.
It's all good as long as we have fun together.
Have you dated a younger guy before?
No. Never.
I've never even dated anyone my age.
- How young can you tolerate? - How young?
- Five or six years? - Five or six?
Five or six years?
Say you had feelings for someone without knowing his age.
Then, you found out he was more than five years younger.
- Would you have a change of heart? - No, I don't think so.
She's honest.
Age doesn't really matter to you.
- No. - The person matters more.
You're really sociable.
- Me? - Yes.
- I'm trying. - You're trying.
- I'm trying. - You're so unfazed...
in front of four men.
Well, I'm older than all of you.
I have to do something, right?
(He finds her cute.)
(Smiling brightly)
I'm older, after all.
I have a feeling you have a lot of cute charms.
- Cute charms? - Yes.
- Does it look like I do? - Yes.
You're not going to answer that?
You can try and be closer if you're curious.
(You can try and be closer if you're curious.)
Jin Young knows how to ease things off.
(Glancing)
The younger men met a new older woman.
Is that a positive reaction? Do you think they're excited?
I'd say it's super positive.
- Super positive? - Super positive?
But they've said things before she got there,
so they're trying to keep their dignity.
- Oh, my gosh. - I see.
But the women were the same.
They told each other...
- about how nice the dates were. - No, that's different.
The women forgot about everything the moment Jeong Won walked in.
But the guys remember what they said,
so they're trying to keep their pride.
I noticed that they were pretending.
Was that too obvious?
I think you got a text.
She got a message.
(Take the hand of the younger man you're attracted to, go outside,)
(and enjoy your 1-on-1 date.)
- Are you flustered? - I am.
It's too sudden.
(They don't know what the message is about,)
(but they're nervous for some reason.)
I personally like Jin Wu and Jin Young together.
I'm rooting for those two.
But Si Won makes a lasting first impression.
He does. He's good-looking.
To be honest, I was torn between Jun Han and Jin Wu.
Okay.
Jin Wu was so handsome when I saw him.
He stood out.
He was too handsome to look at.
I actually had a hard time looking him in the eye.
Jun Han was quick to react,
and he was funny.
He felt like a good friend I felt comfortable to be with.
I couldn't decide...
between someone who I was more interested in...
and someone who could have a good time with me.
(Who will she ask out?)
She's thinking.
The weather's nice.
Do you want to go on a date with me, Jun Han?
(The younger man she wants to go on a date with...)
(is Jun Han.)
Sure.
- See you. - Come on.
We'll be back.
Come on.
Over there. We have to hold hands.
We do?
Let's go on a date.
(Jin Young and Jun Han go on a date while holding hands.)
Jin Young and Jun Han look compatible, personality-wise.
- Yes. - I agree.
(Excited about their date)
(And the younger men who weren't chosen)
I wonder who the male catfish is.
Right. So do I.
He must have gone on a date with one of the women, then.
We'll be able to find out who he took when we get there.
We probably will, right?
Yes.
(Jun Han and Jin Young's 1-on-1 date)
Put on your seatbelt.
He's going in her convertible.
- The benefit of an older woman. - She's opening the top?
Let's hit the road.
- Sure. - He'll...
(Look at Jun Han's face.)
He'll never be able to forget that moment.
He'll remember her the rest of his life!
(Coming from experience)
I get to ride such a cool car, thanks to you.
(Off to the dating spot while leaving an impression)
It's pretty romantic.
It's so therapeutic.
- Is it? - Yes.
Right?
He says it's therapeutic. He loves it.
- This is my goal for next year. - Okay.
Next year, I want to buy a convertible.
- Really? - Yes.
If things work out for us...
and we get to leave together,
you'll be the first one to go on a drive.
Then,
I'll drive you around until then.
I'd like that.
Things are looking good.
They're already picturing the future.
She's a woman who owns a home at the best spot in Seoul.
(The story of an older woman who owns a home and a convertible)
What are you like in a relationship?
- In a relationship? - Yes.
When I'm in a relationship, it's like we're friends.
A boyfriend who makes me feel comfortable and makes me laugh.
I'd go to PC cafes together or...
- You like going to PC cafes? - Yes.
(Glad)
He must like it too.
My friends know this.
The word "PC cafe" is something that can easily win me over.
Really?
When I go to a PC cafe,
- Yes. - I like eating delicious food.
- You know what I mean, right? - Hold up.
Are you flirting with me, or are you being serious?
- I'm being serious. - Really?
I'm so vulnerable to this.
I'm not even lying. I met you for the first time,
but my interest in you grew so much.
Jin Young naturally has high energy.
- Yes. - Is your hair okay?
Hold my hair. I want to look pretty.
Hold it down so that I look pretty.
- Thanks. - Like this?
Why don't we drop the honorifics until we go back?
- Sure. - Good.
Sure.
(He can't hide his smile.)
Jun Han is speeding up.
"Speeding up?"
(They quickly get intimate...)
(and arrive at their dating spot.)
Let's go.
(They naturally hold hands again.)
(Locking our pinky fingers)
Oh, my.
Oh, my gosh!
Let's get coffee.
Coffee's on me, kid.
That was so awkward.
(Jun Han went to order.)
What did you bring this time?
He learned from Jin Wu.
- The owner gave me one. - Thank you.
It was getting chilly.
- Right? - Yes.
You're dressed too lightly for this weather.
I bought it.
- Seriously? - Yes.
(And some snacks to give her energy)
- Oh, my. - It'd be nice...
Yes.
- to eat it with this view. - I love it.
- Thank you. - I hope it's good.
Thank you so much.
I'll open it for you.
- Do you like brownies? - Yes.
You're so sweet.
- Sweet food... - I have a sweet tooth.
- Really? - Yes.
So, I did well?
(Feeling proud)
Yes, you're awesome.
You said your ideal type, appearance-wise,
- was a guy who looked like a puppy. - Yes.
- I'm a Doberman. - Yes, you look like it.
You really resemble a Doberman.
Then,
do you also like Dobermans?
Or do you like Reti...
My tongue is tripping. Or do you like Retrievers more?
I'm just curious.
He's being awkward. She broke him.
(She thinks he's cute.)
(Nervous)
He must be nervous.
- Dobermans? - I prefer Dobermans.
I won't be able to sleep now.
You're feeling anxious, aren't you?
- Are you nervous? - Yes.
You don't know what to do with your hands.
Yes.
(Fretting)
This feels like a blind date.
They make a cute couple.
Actually, when I first came here,
I was only interested in two of the four older women.
One of them has a pretty smile,
and the other had the looks of my ideal type.
I told people that they were my type.
I'm telling you this because...
it's like you're the combination of those two.
Oh, my gosh!
He was interested in 2 of the 4 women,
- "You're those two combined!" - but she's the combination.
What a great line.
(Jun Han is smooth.)
And you have the eyes of a fennec fox.
- Me? - Yes.
Really?
Your eyes are quite flirty.
You have those eyes.
- Those eyes? - Yes.
What do you mean by that?
I just mean that you're naturally attractive.
No way.
(Feeling happy)
- Right. - Check out the sunset.
It's beautiful.
(Hesitating)
You're pretty too, Jin Young.
(You're pretty too, Jin Young.)
I think she's a bit flustered.
What?
We've only seen each other for hours, sir.
I don't hide my feelings, though.
If you're pretty, I say so.
After this date,
let's go for a walk.
Will you?
Do you want to think about it?
(Nervous)
He wasn't like that when he was with Yu Jin.
He looks like a different person.
(Looking unfamiliar without his usual playfulness)
Sure.
I'll give you a coupon for a night stroll.
Sweet.
That means I get two dates with you...
unlike others.
I love it.
As for Jun Han,
when he was at the cafe,
he didn't look nervous, and seemed like a mischievous boy.
But since they're alone together...
When we talked to each other face to face,
I could tell he was super nervous.
He couldn't relax his hands on the table...
and kept fidgeting with them.
I thought it was cute.
I found it cute that he didn't know what to do with himself.
(How will this date affect their future relationship?)
(Meanwhile, 1-on-1 Date between Jeong Won and Ji Hye)
The male catfish chose Ji Hye,
and now they're on a date.
I like the vibe here.
- It's pretty. - These flowers.
(Laughing)
- It's awkward, isn't it? - Yes, it is.
It feels awkward.
Gosh. What's that?
Gosh. It's so pretty.
The cherry blossoms are so pretty.
- Gosh. What? - It has an amazing vibe.
I can't believe I get to eat under the cherry blossoms.
I've never been to a place like this.
(Shy)
Let's talk...
- Casually? - casually. Yes.
- That's better. - Yes, I like that better too.
If we keep speaking formally,
it'll continue to get awkward.
Why did you choose me?
She's straightforward.
I met with four women, but...
you seemed like the most difficult tone to me.
So, you wanted...
a challenge?
- Yes. - I see.
I have to go for the most difficult one first.
When I think of you,
I think of someone who is cold, aloof, and...
strong.
Is that how I come across...
- when others see me? - A little.
That's why...
I wanted to talk to you first.
I'm curious about you.
(I'm curious about you.)
You went on a date...
- today. - Yes.
How was it?
It was comfortable. I found him comfortable too.
Was it fun?
I mean, it was the first date.
- I see. - It was only for a couple of hours.
(Ji Hye hedged when asked about her first date with Jin Wu.)
Yesterday, I had no time to do it at all.
Really? Thanks.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What's your type?
Am I having a dejavu?
- Right. We talked about it. - Yes. I don't know my type.
I guess I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
I guess a little?
- The look on her face has changed. - Yes.
- Don't be nervous. - Okay.
- What? - She likes it.
- Why is this so funny? - What?
- She's happy just to see him. - Yes.
Ji Hye, you said...
you had a consistent type when it comes to one's looks.
What's that?
I like someone who looks sharp.
- I see. - Someone without double eyelids.
Someone who looks cold and has a distant vibe?
- And a player? - "A player."
I like someone who has a bit of a player vibe.
With a right amount of dark, sensual vibe?
Yes, you're right.
But as for the personalities,
he has to be fun to be with.
- I see. - He's funny and easy to be around.
Good banter matters the most.
You don't like being uneasy.
No. I hate it.
Your personal color is cool-toned.
- You're right. - Am I right?
- I'm also cool-toned. - Yes? That's why black suits you.
- Yes. You must look good in black. - Yes.
Most of the clothes I brought are black.
(They have the same personal color.)
You also like leather, don't you?
- I brought many leather clothes. - You did, didn't you?
I knew it.
I packed three leather clothes.
Likewise.
Gosh. What's with those two?
They seem like a couple who's been dating for five years.
(Savoring)
It doesn't taste like anything.
Do you like something less sweet like this?
Yes, I like this.
Things like puffed rice crackers.
- Me too. I don't like sweet ones. - Things without flavors.
- Yes. - That's right.
How can they click so well?
Can you have such a conversation on your first date?
I've never seen anyone...
who clicked faster than these two on a dating show.
Overall, Jeong Won is good...
at keeping the conversation going.
- You're right. - Yes.
Ji Hye, then,
what's your soul food?
- Spicy stir-fried pork. - What?
- Really? - Of course.
I love spicy stir-fried pork.
His reaction is amazing.
We have similar taste buds too.
When you like someone,
- you like everything about them. - You like everything.
They like each other.
- It's really pretty here. - Yes, it is.
Yes.
I've had this romantic dream...
to take a photo...
with my girlfriend in front of the cherry blossoms.
I've never done it.
I've never taken a photo with my girlfriend...
with cherry blossoms in full bloom.
Do you want to do it now?
Did I sound like a thug?
(Flustered)
- I liked it. - Should we get a photo?
Let's do it.
I like it.
- I like it. - Yes.
Sure.
It's pretty. You look so pretty here.
I'll come to your side.
- I'll sit next to you. - Okay.
Okay. Here we go.
- Let's take it here. - What a sweet sight it is.
(Taking a photo as a couple in front of cherry blossoms...)
(on their first date)
It's possible to do this during our first date, right?
- Right? - Yes. We have to record it.
They'll be gone tomorrow.
Right.
This is fun.
Do you want to go and have spicy stir-fried pork?
- When? - When should we?
- Tomorrow? - During our stay here?
- Yes. - Sure.
Do you want it outside?
- Are you going to cook it? - Spicy stir-fried pork?
Why don't we make one each?
Is it a competition?
- Yes. - Like "Culinary Class Wars?"
- Yes. "Culinary Class Wars." - Sure.
Didn't she make a promise to have it with Jin Wu too?
(Ji Hye said the same thing to Jin Wu during the lunch date.)
(And Jin Wu promised to cook her spicy stir-fried pork.)
- Then... - Please make it tasty.
- Well... - I already told you I love it.
My goodness.
It's plain to see...
that she treated Jin Wu like a younger brother...
when she went on a date with him.
The date with Jeong Won feels like a grown-up date.
- She likes dopamine highs. - Yes.
- Jeong Won gives her the thrills. - Yes.
I think she found that attractive.
They look good with each other.
(In the meantime)
(Yeon House)
(Those who didn't get selected by catfish Jin Young...)
Is this meat for jjigae?
- What? - Is this for jjigae?
I have another meat for jjigae. Will you dap that one...
with a paper towel?
He's making one.
What are you making? Boiled pork?
- What? - Are you making boiled pork?
- No. Spicy stir-fried pork. - Spicy stir-fried pork.
- What? - I told you!
Gosh. Oh dear.
Goodness.
(Cooking spicy stir-fried pork while thinking only about Ji Hye)
I hope it will taste super good.
(He preps the ingredients...)
(and makes the seasoning himself.)
Please be delicious.
I can't say it for sure,
but if his mother is watching this, she'd go,
- "My goodness." - "My boy."
"Look at my boy."
(Will Jin Wu's feelings reach Ji Hye?)
They are here.
(Ji Seung and Yu Jin approach the common area.)
- I think Jun Han... - Yes.
went on a date with the catfish.
Am I right?
Jun Han, who went on a date with Yu Jin, is absent right now.
(Jun Han, her former date, is the only one missing.)
- Really? - It's crazy.
- Hello. - Hi.
- It feels like it's been a while. - Seriously. It's been a while.
It smells good in here.
(Si Won notices Ji Seung coming in, instead of going on a date.)
So? How is the new guy?
What do you think of the new guy?
Is he all right?
(He's curious about what the women thinks of the new younger man.)
I don't know.
I'm not good at reading people at first sight.
What was he like?
- He has strong features. - He looked strong.
- I see. - Yes.
- I thought he'd be very outgoing. - Agreed.
He seems like an extreme Type E.
They're excited and wary at the same time.
How's the female catfish?
- What? - What about the female catfish?
She is...
(Glancing)
She seems like a confident person.
Is she? That's great.
- She didn't mean it at all. - Did you see her?
She was totally unenthusiastic, right?
- "Is she? That's great." - "That's great."
(Laughing)
Is she? That's great.
She spoke really well...
- in front of the four guys. - Really?
- The male catfish was the same. - That's right.
- Really? - Yes.
- Hi. - Hello.
Hello.
(She didn't go on a date.)
(Looking relieved to see Ju Hee)
He's looking around.
Ji Hye isn't here.
(Ji Hye, who Jin Wu has been waiting for, is the only one missing.)
(Sighing)
He even made the spicy stir-fried pork.
Gosh. What now?
It didn't occur to me at all...
that Ji Hye would go on a date with the male catfish.
She wouldn't be able to eat what I cooked today.
So, that didn't feel good.
I wouldn't be able to give her everything...
that I wanted to give today.
(I wouldn't be able to give her what I've prepared today.)
Did you get some rest?
I slept.
There's a paper towel now.
(Ju Hee checks in with Yun So first.)
- What was the catfish like? - What?
How was the catfish?
"How was the catfish?"
Were they at a seafood restaurant? "How was the catfish?"
"How was the catch today?"
"How fresh was the raw fish?" He sounded like that.
(He's very competitive.)
- What was the catfish like? - What?
How was the catfish?
He was new.
Was he all right?
Well, he was...
I don't know.
(Laughing)
Were you with the male catfish before you came here?
Yes. And one of you guys...
- One of you went on a date, right? - Yes.
Jun Han went on a date.
- Yes. - You were right.
- She said that. - He wasn't here.
- But... - I saw it.
- What is it? - Really?
Jun Han was enthusiastic...
- About what? - when he talked.
He has a way with words, doesn't he?
- Yes. - Come on.
He was acting awkwardly too.
- Was he? - Was he nervous?
Really? He must have liked her.
"He must have liked her."
My goodness.
It hurts to see.
(Jun Han and Jin Young arrive at the Yeon House...)
(after finishing their date.)
Do you want me to carry it?
(Do you want me to carry your bag?)
You have to carry it...
so that I can be confident.
Is that so?
Gosh. He's even carrying her bag.
- It's my first time... - Yes.
carrying a woman's bag.
It's the first time in my life.
He even confessed...
it was his first time carrying a woman's bag.
It was fun.
(Jun Han expresses his feelings until they reach the Yeon House.)
I'm a bit nervous.
I might get all the attention,
and I feel uneasy about it.
Exactly. We're here.
(It's a nervous first encounter for Jin Young.)
- Hello. - Hey.
- Or we can use the paper towel. - Yes.
(Noonas saw Jun Han and Jin Young.)
- Hello. - Hey.
She saw them.
What?
I feel uneasy about it.
(It's a nervous first encounter for Jin Young.)
- Or we can use the paper towel. - Yes.
(Noonas saw Jun Han and Jin Young.)
She saw them.
What?
- Welcome. - Hello.
(Jun Han comes in carrying Jin Young's bag.)
Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(He's self-conscious for some reason.)
Hello.
You need to take off your shoes.
- Gosh. I'm sorry. - Right. Shoes go here.
She looked like a fashionable one.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
She looked very young.
(Jin Young says hello to them confidently again.)
- Hello. - Hi.
She came in a very cheerful way.
And I found it interesting.
So far, when we came,
we were very awkward.
But she was very cheerful.
Her characteristics completely different from others.
- She has a distinctive voice too. - Yes.
- It's high. - It's unique.
Hello.
(A new dynamic occurs with the presence of Jin Young.)
Did you eat?
Have you finished eating already?
Gosh. The bag.
He's following her around.
(Glancing)
She's looking at the bag.
Her eyes are on the bag.
Her gaze went down and up.
Gosh. If I were Yu Jin,
I'd be so hurt.
He went too far.
He did go too far.
Why is he holding her bag when they've just met?
But guys,
- that's how he feels right now. - Exactly.
He can't deceive his feelings.
I thought...
I had something going on with Jun Han.
So, I was a bit surprised.
- It's awkward, isn't it? - What?
No, it's fine. It's not awkward.
I'll help you by your side.
Do you need help?
You're all busy.
No, it's okay. You're a guest today.
- You should sit. - Am I a guest?
Is everyone here?
- What? - Has everyone arrived?
- No. - Ji Hye isn't here yet.
- Ji Hye isn't here. - And the male catfish.
Is there a male catfish?
- Yes. - A male catfish.
(Jun Han and Jin Young found out about the male catfish too.)
That's crazy.
We should take out more spicy stir-fried pork.
We need more spicy stir-fried pork.
Where is it?
- It's... - Where's the spicy stir-fried pork?
I hid it.
- Why? - Should I take it out?
He hid the spicy stir-fried pork.
When is Ji Hye coming?
(Jin Wu has been waiting only for Ji Hye.)
I made the spicy stir-fried pork for Ji Hye.
Really? Goodness.
She'll be here.
(Time has passed, but Ji Hye didn't come.)
(He put some in the container.)
Freeze it and have it tomorrow.
(Jin Wu hid it secretly when everyone was busy.)
My goodness.
- Did you really hide it? - Yes.
He's unbelievable.
- Did you hide it? - Really?
I didn't necessarily hide it.
- I saved some for her. - Come on.
You can't be more obvious.
- You don't see us. - Come on.
There are some here.
Wait. I've never been to a place like this.
- It's really pretty, isn't it? - Yes.
I feel like watching a movie, knowing how it's going to end.
Gosh. You must be nervous.
Why am I nervous?
(Relax.)
Gosh. They've grown so close to each other.
Is it here? Well...
The other girl is here too.
The male and female catfish are meeting...
each other for the first time, right?
They're here.
- Hello. - Hi.
Hi.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
Gosh.
He said, "Gosh." He's so honest.
Hello.
(Glancing)
- Hello. - Hi. Nice to meet you.
(Jeong Won says hello to everyone as soon as he arrives.)
Nice to meet you.
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - Hi.
He is visually stunning.
(The younger men observe quickly as the male catfish arrives.)
I was very surprised.
He has a great physique.
I got a bit nervous.
He's very good-looking.
I understood why he was the male catfish.
The male participants think he's handsome too.
Nice to meet you.
(Jin Wu greets him quickly.)
- Have you eaten? Were you eating? - What?
For you,
- I made the spicy stir-fried pork. - Really?
Good job. I'm glad he told her.
At that moment, I didn't care about Jeong Won.
I was waiting for Ji Hye.
So, I told her right away,
"I made the spicy stir-fried pork for you."
"I want you to have some..."
"if you haven't eaten already."
That was what I told her.
She looked really happy at that moment.
I've never experienced such a moment...
with a man in real life.
- I see. - I mean...
He went, "Move away."
"Noona, I made this for you."
"Have you eaten?" That's so...
- That's a bit... - That's some experience.
- Yes. I would melt. - Right.
Jin Wu has that vibe of a devoted younger guy.
- Jin Wu does? - Yes.
Hello.
(Ji Hye and Jin Young meet at last.)
I was really surprised.
She looked really young.
I thought she might be younger than me...
when I first saw her.
I'm worried about Ji Hye.
When she entered the house,
I saw that she was a woman of glamorous beauty.
That made me nervous a bit.
(What kind of changes will occur in the Yeon House...)
(with the presence of new participants?)
(They sit around all together for the first time.)
Gosh. It's a full house now.
- Should I go first? - Yes.
I'm Kim Jeong Won.
Jeong Won, like garden in Korean.
I'm Lee Jin Young.
Jin Young. Okay.
Let's have some fun in the coming week.
Yes.
- Should we get a drink? - Yes.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Nice to meet you, everyone. - Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
By the way, Jin Wu got to sit...
- next to Ji Hye. - Yes.
Everyone is wearing similar outfits.
You're right. Those three...
- are wearing similar outfits. - We're like the catfish look.
- He's right. - You're totally right.
- We're like the catfish look. - Wait, true.
- In all black. - Right.
Catfish look?
- You stand out all alone. - The color.
You stand out all alone.
She and I were a couple today.
- Right now? - Jin Wu!
- Jin Wu! - What a blow.
He said, "A couple."
She and I were a couple today.
- Did you see Ji Hye's face? - She looked unhappy, right?
She looked shocked.
- Like, "What's wrong with him?" - Yes.
"Just hush!"
Ji Hye looks taken aback.
Really? Why aren't you wearing matching outfits?
- I got changed to cook. - I see.
Were you wearing an emerald outfit?
- Emerald? - Mine was light blue.
- Light blue? - Yes, light blue.
- Not bad. - We chose blue tones.
I'm surprised Jin Wu spoke out.
Oh, no.
What did everyone talk about yesterday?
When we normally gather together...
Yesterday, we talked about ideal types.
- Ideal types. - From Jeong Won.
From Jeong Won. What's your ideal type?
I don't really have one when it comes to looks.
But it'd be someone I click really well with.
Also, someone I can picture...
the future with would be my ideal type.
Earlier, Ji Hye said...
her ideal type was someone she can click well with.
- Jeong Won said something similar. - You're right.
But he said someone he can coexist with earlier.
- You're totally right. - Earlier...
Only Ji Hye would notice that.
- Yes. - True.
(It'd be someone I click really well with.)
(Also, someone I can picture the future with.)
As for me, someone who is puppy-like.
- You like a guy who is puppy-like. - Yes.
- I do. - Our ideal types are different.
What's your ideal type?
I'm not a big fan of puppy-like guys.
An immediate answer?
- Wolf-like? - Wolf?
Or fox-like?
A guy who looks fierce.
Really?
I don't like someone with kind looks.
Is that so?
But Jin Wu looks incredibly kind.
Yesterday, you mentioned dinosaur-like.
- Didn't you? - Yes, like Woo Do Hwan.
I did.
I don't like guys who look as if I need to protect them.
Guys who look as if they'll protect me.
(Looking around)
Jin Wu.
Oh, no.
(What are you like?)
I get told that I look sickly the most.
(Laughing)
(This is bad.)
Oh, dear.
No, you're really handsome.
- He is. - Like really.
(Don't be upset!)
You may be right.
(The sickly guy is anxious.)
What kind of puppy-like face do you like?
A big puppy. Someone with a big puppy-like face.
- Like a retriever? - Well...
A Dobermann.
(A Dobermann?)
So the puppy isn't gentle-looking.
You must also like Woo Do Hwan.
Woo Do Hwan? Of course.
In that sense, your ideal types overlap.
They do.
(Ji Hye and Jin Young's ideal types overlap.)
What's with the two?
(Scared and flustered)
That must be why you chose Jun Han. He looks Dobermann-like.
To point it out like that?
- She's no joke. - Ji Hye is sharp.
Doesn't he look more like...
- a Dobermann? - He's like a retriever.
- A Dobermann? - Or not. But it's a compliment.
- Do I look like one? - He does, right?
- Kind of. - Right?
If he were one of the guys, would you have chosen him?
(If Jeong Won were one of the guys, would you have chosen him?)
(Would Jin Young have chosen Jeong Won, not Jun Han,)
(if he had been at the first meeting place?)
Aren't you putting her...
- on the spot? - Am I?
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure.
- I'm sorry. - Would you like to sit here?
This is so interesting.
Look. The girls are...
- It's gone wild. - They are...
throwing out questions...
- to guard their guys. - Exactly.
The girls have a lot to nitpick about.
They're like...
"Hey, don't come here. Go away."
"You two suit each other." It's to protect their guys.
- Right now... - It's no joke.
Ji Hye, Yu Jin, and Jin Young...
- are against each other. - Yes.
Ji Seung is the one adding fuel to it.
Exactly.
Burn!
The three are at war, but out of the blue,
she's like, "Doesn't he also look like a Dobermann?"
Adding fuel to the fire.
(Ji Seung adds fuel to the fire.)
Nice timing.
- We've got a text. - Nice timing.
(Just as Yeon House heats up,)
(a message comes in.)
What could it be?
(Shocked)
- What is it? - What does it say?
(Surprised)
A box has arrived.
The Job Box.
(The Job Box has been delivered to the door. Reveal your job.)
- Job Box? - The Job Box.
The Job Box?
We're already revealing our jobs?
(Delivered at the door...)
(are 10 boxes.)
(The Job Box has items that help them guess each other's jobs.)
Job Box? I've always wanted to see it.
- I'm dying to know. - This is fun.
I've been wanting to know...
- what they do. - For real.
The catfish joined in just two days. But now, the jobs?
- It's hitting the fan. - Honestly,
how the show unfolds is like going through YouTube Shorts.
I'm really curious.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Right away like this?
- But really, how fast. - Right away like this?
What a shocker.
I'm suddenly all nervous.
This is making me the most nervous.
It's nerve-racking.
(A strange tension fills Yeon House.)
- Who will we begin with? - Me.
(Opening Yu Jin's Job Box first)
I'm excited.
(Surprised)
Wait. Isn't this science-related?
(A mysterious item was in the first box.)
What is that?
Isn't it related to biology?
Biotechnology? Doesn't this have to do with that?
- Genes? - Genes.
(There are many job guesses.)
- Maybe chemistry-related? - A lab?
- Yes, maybe chemistry. - Somehow...
A graduate student?
(Laughing)
- A lab! - Research!
- A researcher. - A chemistry researcher.
- Things like atoms and molecules. - Yes.
No doubt.
Maybe chemistry.
I have a feeling this belongs to Ji Seung.
(Nodding)
- She's nodding. - Me too.
- Really? - Right? Ji Seung.
My guess is her too.
- Me? - Yes.
Why? Please tell me a reason.
- It just suits you. - Exactly.
Molecular biology isn't bad at all.
(As all guessed)
- It suits you. - For sure.
Without a doubt.
Who does this belong to?
- It's mine. - Really?
- Really? - Yes.
It didn't even cross my mind.
- What? - What?
(It's Jeong Won's?)
What?
- Catch it first. - Okay.
(What could Jeong Won's job be, based on this item?)
- This right here is... - Yes?
- a molecular structure. - Right.
I'm running a cosmetics brand at the moment.
- Cosmetics. - This is...
the molecular structure...
of our best-selling product's main component.
So it's the actual molecular structure.
I'm currently running a men's cosmetics company.
He's the CEO of a cosmetics brand.
(CEO Kim Jeong Won)
My job isn't limited to branding and distribution.
I regularly stop by the packaging company...
and the manufacturing company...
to maintain the quality.
(Developing and maintaining the quality himself)
The brand is expanding...
outside of Korea to Asia.
Our yearly sales are about three million dollars.
The long-term goal is to make it a total men's lifestyle brand.
(Kim Jeong Won)
He's got a clear goal.
(CEO of a men's cosmetics brand)
I'm in the cosmetics industry.
Interesting.
It was a surprise.
"Does he work in the skincare industry?"
It did cross my mind.
But little did I think he'd be running a business.
"Cool. That's cool."
Men's cosmetics are popular now.
He's operating in a blue-ocean market.
(To whom does the second Job Box belong?)
- What? - What is that?
- A norigae? - What?
- What is that? - Are they in the crafts industry?
(Crafts?)
- Isn't this a gua sha tool? - Gua sha tool?
It's not hers for sure.
I have no idea.
This one's tough.
- Maybe it has to do with crafting. - What is this?
Dancing.
(Dancing?)
What is that for real?
- It's Ju Hee's. - What?
- It's Ju Hee's. - Correct.
(The Job Box belongs to Ju Hee.)
Are you a dancer? Like in modern dance.
I play the gayageum.
(Shocked)
Cool!
(Surprised)
Ju Hee,
- What is this? - what's with the sewing kit?
That is...
the ornament hanging from the end of the gayageum.
That over there is called anjok.
Move it around, and it changes the pitch.
- Do you play the strings with it? - Yes.
Cool.
(The second Job Box belongs to Ju Hee.)
Interesting.
I'm Yu Ju Hee, a gayageum player...
- and instructor. - How cool.
It suits her perfectly.
I attended grad school at Chung-Ang University...
and was a member of the Chung-Ang Gayageum Ensemble.
I've been teaching gayageum for eight years now.
(A gayageum instructor for 8 years)
I'm teaching those majoring in gayageum.
Some of my students are regular office workers.
Goodness.
(Yu Ju Hee, Gayageum instructor)
- The gayageum suits her. - Totally.
- Totally. - It's totally her thing.
How beautiful.
She's got that classical beauty look.
It's just made her more charming.
She's become more charming.
(Woo Young, pull it together.)
(Feeling shy)
For real.
Amazing.
Now that she mentioned the gayageum,
- I can see it in her. - Totally.
- She suddenly looks elegant. - Yes.
Right?
- You give off that Korean vibe. - Yes.
I've always thought anyone who plays an instrument was cool.
Someone I'm interested in plays the gayageum.
It made her more charming and cool.
Look at his face.
(What's the item in the next Job Box?)
- What? - What?
Isn't this bok choy?
- Bok choy? - A cook.
A farmer.
- A farmer? - A farmer.
- A farmer. - That's a possibility.
- A farmer. - A young farmer.
A young farmer.
There are many young farmers.
- Maybe a malatang place owner. - Malatang.
Malatang?
It's yours, right?
- Bok choy. - Do I look like I'd cook malatang?
A farmer.
No, it's not Jin Wu.
(Or not?)
Wait.
Don't you think we might have a cook here?
- He kept cooking for us. - Right?
- We cooked together. - Now that you say it...
- Didn't we cook altogether? - But...
Didn't Jin Wu say he does...
- a bit of cooking? - No.
I think it's Lee Si Won.
(Who is it?)
- Yes, it's me. - Bok choy...
- Really? - Oh, my gosh.
- What's the bok choy? - What do you do?
(Curious)
(Is he really a cook?)
(Or a young farmer?)
I'm not a cook.
- But I do run a restaurant. - A restaurant.
Is that why?
What kind of restaurant?
I run a shabu-shabu place.
- A shabu-shabu place? - Shabu-shabu.
Hence the bok choy.
- This is so cute. - Bok choy.
There's even a plate for it.
It looks very fresh.
I'm currently running a restaurant.
What a twist.
While running the restaurant,
I'm managing the employees, daily inventory,
(Overseeing everything from employees to inventory)
the overall restaurant operation,
and the counter.
(The central role in the restaurant operation)
(Yu Jin Wu, Restaurant CEO)
Seriously, I didn't get even one right.
- I can't imagine it. - Right?
- Like, I have zero clue. - But this is fun.
It was a big surprise.
Jin Wu has a distinct image.
So here's what I thought.
"Does he work in the entertainment industry?"
"Or was he a celebrity?"
Right.
The restaurant business was a shocker.
(What's the next job?)
I'm nervous it might be mine.
(I'm curious.)
What is it?
What is that? An MP3 player?
An earphone?
Is that an earphone?
The earphone looks quite different.
- It has to do with music. - Or an engineer.
- A singer. - A singer?
- Maybe. - They must be a singer.
They're probably in the music industry.
If it's someone who does music,
the equipment is quite...
The equipment is quite unique.
Do you wear it around your ears?
Isn't it a job where they have to listen...
to the tune really well?
Are they a sound engineer?
A songwriter.
- Right? - Maybe.
Who does it belong to?
It's mine.
Really?
(Who does the earphone belong to?)
(Ji Seung)
What is it for?
I'm an interpreter.
- Oh, gosh. - Really?
Hold on a minute.
(Ji Seung is a simultaneous interpreter.)
She's a simultaneous interpreter.
No wonder she was hosting everyone in the center.
(You're right.)
She was interpreting...
people's feelings in the center.
You're right.
(What is Ji Seung like as a simultaneous interpreter?)
I'm currently a simultaneous interpreter...
and an English MC for many international events.
An MC?
At international conferences or events,
there are small booths.
(A small booth at conferences or events)
The whole event, meeting, opening ceremony, and more.
My core job is to interpret...
everything.
I also interpret at events held...
at government agencies and companies.
Amazing.
I can have various personas.
That's the charm.
It suits her.
(Gu Ji Seung, Conference Interpreter)
- No wonder you have a nice voice. - Hold on a minute.
Amazing.
How you talk...
- and your tone of voice. - Right.
- You have clear diction. - They were different.
It was my first time meeting someone...
working as an interpreter.
Ji Seung, the interpreter, was cool.
It boosted his feelings for her.
That means Si Won...
has a completely different job,
- not related to interpreting. - Right.
(Whose job will be revealed next?)
(A walkie-talkie?)
- A bodyguard. - It's for a bodyguard.
- A police officer? - Police officer?
- A bodyguard. - A bodyguard.
(Everyone starts looking at one person in particular.)
What could it be?
Isn't it Jun Han's?
- It's not mine. - He doesn't know where to look.
It seems like Jun Han's.
- It's Jun Han. - Jun Han.
Jun Han!
But Yun So also has a good build.
(Between Yun So and Jun Han, who does it belong to?)
Yes, it's actually mine. Let me explain.
- Cool. - A bodyguard?
(What's the meaning behind the walkie-talkie?)
I'm not a bodyguard or anything.
- "Not?" - Not.
- Not. - My job isn't sports-related.
I work at an advertising agency.
- An advertising agency? - Really?
That was unexpected.
(Impressed)
This is another twist.
(What is Jun Han like as the team leader of an advertising company?)
I'm a field team leader...
at an advertising company.
That's so cool.
I operate and set up pop-up stores,
assign workers, and train them.
(At pop-up stores)
(Lee Jun Han, Advertising Company Team Leader)
This is a real twist.
(The older women are surprised by his job.)
That would change up the mood.
(Glancing)
It made me more interested in him.
I really wanted to know what Jun Han did for a living.
I thought he might be in sports or something.
Him being in marketing and the pop-up industry...
really suits him.
- He simply works out as a hobby. - Isn't it better, actually?
His job isn't related to sports,
but he still maintains that body.
- It means... - Yes.
he works from 9 to 6, works out,
- and is hardworking. - Good self-discipline.
- It means he's very diligent. - Exactly.
(Half of their jobs are revealed. Who is the owner of the next box?)
This is fun.
I know, right?
I should've revealed mine later.
What is this?
What's this?
Seriously, what's this?
Isn't that...
It's a bar code...
(A bar code scanner?)
Do they produce this?
That could be it.
(What?)
- A bar code... - Is it...
- He's blinking. - His face turned strange.
I think it's Si Won's.
It is.
It's not me.
- Really? - Yes.
Ji Hye.
Who's the owner?
It's me.
What?
(Surprised)
I had no idea.
I really thought it wasn't you.
(The owner of the sixth object, Ji Hye)
This is fun.
This is a bar code scanner.
I'm in the clothing business.
I had a guess.
- Yes, it suits you. - It really suits you.
It suits her.
I do clothing business.
I'm the CEO of a company...
with the annual sales of two million dollars.
(Annual sales of 2 million dollars, a self-made CEO)
The business is flourishing.
I've worked for a long time as a fit model,
and I naturally got interested in clothing business.
"Let's start my own business."
(She started the business thinking she wants to make her own brand.)
I mostly do modeling,
styling,
web work,
and various and overall tasks.
(She overseas various tasks.)
It suits her so well.
(Park Ji Hye, a clothing businesswoman)
- That's my job. - You're so cool.
It suits you.
She's running her own business,
which is incredible.
My...
impression of her did get better.
(What's in the next Job Box?)
It's soccer.
(A soccer tactics board?)
They must be a soccer player.
- They must be a soccer coach. - A coach?
It's definitely Si Won. The end.
- It's Si Won. - Me again?
You look like...
- you'll be good at sports. - Exactly.
You have the face of a soccer player.
Yes, he has the face of a soccer player.
It is you, right?
- You're very sure. - Yes.
I'm very sure this time.
- Yes, it is me. - Right?
You must be really good at soccer.
A soccer player?
Not anymore.
I was a soccer player...
from elementary school until high school,
but I quit because I broke my clavicle.
Now,
I work as a soccer coach for kids.
I currently work as a youth soccer coach.
Yes, he's a coach.
I teach them strategies, positions, and so on...
in my training sessions.
I do my best to create an environment...
where the kids can enjoy soccer and grow up.
(Lee Si Won, a soccer coach)
That soccer center...
You could really enjoy playing football there.
His face doesn't matter to the kids who go there.
You're really an elite player if you played until high school.
I see.
I thought he'd do arts and sports.
He was a youth soccer player.
It was cool...
and unexpected.
I'll go.
(There are 3 remaining Job Boxes.)
Is this the instruction?
(What?)
My gosh.
I'll reveal the mission.
- A mission? - That's a mission?
Isn't this...
a certificate?
One... Goodness.
(Surprised)
Look at him.
(What is written?)
Is it a land deed?
I think it's a certificate.
What is it?
It's a patent certificate.
A patent?
They must have their own brand.
Looking at the registered patent,
it seems like the name of a brand.
Is it related to exercise or sports?
(A patent related to exercise or sports?)
- Right? - It is.
- Me? - Yes. I think it's you.
It isn't.
What?
Who is the owner?
(Is it Yu Jin? Or Jin Young?)
It must be Jin Young, judging from her face.
It's mine.
I...
I run pilates centers.
They're located in Gangnam...
and Seoul Station.
(She runs 2 pilates centers in Gangnam and Seoul Station.)
I integrated power plate and pilates...
and came up with my own way of exercise.
I even got it patented.
(Choi Yu Jin, a CEO of pilates centers)
- Really? - Yes.
So cool.
(The remaining jobs are Jin Young and Yun So's.)
What's this?
(An unknown pair of gloves in the box)
- What's that? - Gloves?
Aren't these medical gloves?
A doctor?
A hairdresser.
Maybe they deal with medicine.
(A hairdresser or a job related to medicine?)
I have no clue.
- He acts so well. - Is it Yun So?
- Yun So. - These are mine.
Really?
(Surprised)
I'm Lee Yun So, a hairdresser.
That's cool.
I had no idea.
My job...
is to style the customers to fulfill their needs.
I'm a hairdresser.
I found dressing up someone very charming.
(I found dressing up someone very charming.)
(Lee Yun So, a hairdresser)
It's so fascinating.
It suits you.
(Gosh, it's so fascinating!)
It's so fascinating.
I had no idea.
(Glancing)
Yes.
I did not expect that at all.
But when I heard it,
I remembered the conversations we had.
We talked about hair perm.
Everything was fascinating.
(Everything was fascinating.)
We're left with Jin Young.
I'll open it.
I can't wait to find out.
(What?)
An eyeliner?
(An eyeliner?)
It's makeup-related.
She's a makeup artist.
(Is she a makeup artist?)
What do you do?
I...
Yes.
I'm a skin care doctor.
- A doctor? - A doctor?
Yes, I'm a doctor.
(She's a doctor.)
Amazing.
(Amazing!)
That's amazing.
(A job they never imagined)
I'm a skin care doctor.
This is so unexpected.
As soon as I graduated from med school,
I started working in the field of skin care.
I worked as a salaried doctor for one and a half years...
after graduating,
and then I quickly opened my own clinic.
Our goal at the beginning of the year was 10 million dollars,
and we overachieved it.
Now, I'm the CEO of a company which does...
consultations and branding of skin care franchises.
I have three branches,
And in August, three more will open,
including one in Gangnam.
- She must be very busy. - Exactly.
Last year's annual sales was about 10 million dollars.
(Total annual sales of all branches was 10 million dollars.)
I work as a skin care doctor and a CEO.
(Lee Jin Young, a doctor)
She looks so different in the white gown.
- It's cool. - So different.
- That's cool. - That's cool.
I'll go and get my skin care done one day.
I open a branch in Gangnam in August.
- You can come to Gangnam. - In Gangnam?
- You can come to Gangnam. - Do we get a friend discount?
Of course.
I'll give you a discount if you come.
(I'll give you a discount if you come.)
A dermatologist? That's unexpected.
She looks so young.
I was very surprised.
- So cool. - Everyone's job is so unexpected.
(Feeling shy)
I was so shocked.
I thought she did investments...
or business.
She does business,
but I had no idea she was a doctor.
(Nobody expected Jin Young to be a doctor.)
I think Jun Han...
completely fell for her.
(Cracking up)
I'm sure he went like this.
"Then in the future..."
But imagine.
My older woman...
does beauty business,
and she's a doctor too.
She rides a very expensive foreign car,
and it's convertible.
She even has a house in a prime location.
- This is... - What's this?
- She has everything. - What's this, seriously?
Jun Han, don't let go of her.
Everyone's job is so unexpected.
- It was fun. - Let's go when there's a pop up.
- Why? - It'd be fun.
It's fun.
What is it?
Pop ups in Seongsu-dong...
- Is it 11pm? - It's 11pm.
What kind of pop ups do you do? There's beauty, for one.
Yes, a lot of beauty-related ones.
It's 11pm.
I work a lot with marketing agencies.
- Really? - Yes.
But not so much with pop ups.
But...
I work often with agencies when I do MC gigs.
I thought I saw you.
- When I first saw you... - Actually, I also thought...
- you looked familiar. - Right?
You might've worked together.
I work on site often too.
Exactly. As a promoter?
A promoter...
Not as a promoter, but as a site manager.
Exactly. I thought you looked very familiar.
Since Jun Han talked about fitness,
I naturally assumed his job was sports-related.
But he said he worked at a marketing agency,
and I work with them often.
I could talk about this freely with him.
I look forward to it.
Do you not make products for women?
Women's color cosmetics...
are very difficult to make.
My company does men's products.
I plan to keep it that way.
I plan to do cosmetics too.
- Because... - You can ask me anything.
The end goal of my business...
- is cosmetics. - Cosmetics?
(Turning her head)
- This is four-way. - This is how it gets?
I'll do cosmetics no matter what.
You must.
It'll be fun to make it together.
I'll help you a lot.
- Thank you so much. - I really like working together.
- Thank you. - I'm a workaholic.
Me too. I've only been working all this while.
They hit it off well.
I talked about business with Jin Young.
Her goal was similar to mine.
That's when I started to get attracted to her.
"This is fun."
The talk was very interesting to me.
- Coexistence. - Coexistence.
They're coexisting.
- They can plan the future together. - Yes.
And I think Jin Young is the type of person Jeong Won pursues.
Someone whom he can learn from.
Yes. The word "coexistence" is perfect for them.
You can come in and...
"Send a Love QR anonymously."
(They receive a Love QR message yet again today.)
"You can express your feelings."
(But a lot has changed since yesterday.)
This is so hard.
Goodness.
(A lot has happened today.)
(Did they have a change of heart?)
Do you think they'll waver now that the jobs have been revealed?
I think there will be...
a huge shift.
The war will start now.
I thought I was very firm with my feelings.
(Ju Hee seems to be deep in thoughts after the jobs have been revealed.)
(But I want to go on a date with you.)
(When you're on a date with me,)
(I'll make you laugh at least once.)
We all...
(At that moment, Yun So comes to meet Ju Hee.)
I won't say it.
(This is bad.)
(I was very flustered.)
(Sighing)
(Meanwhile, Jin Wu tells Ji Hye how he feels truthfully.)
(After talking with Jeong Won today,)
(I honestly don't know how my feelings will change.)
(I didn't exactly feel elated.)
(I'm so curious about you.)
(If there is a date tomorrow, do you want to go with me?)
(We should go on a date.)
(Let's do it.)
(The way she walked...)
(made my heart race.)
She looked pretty.
(The younger men's hearts flutter at the sight of the older women...)
(they've never seen before.)
(The time has come.)
(It's time to show them.)
(They're men.)
(Which older woman does he like so much?)