(Their ages were finally revealed.)
I was...
born in 2002.
(Si Won, 25)
(Si Won is 12 years younger than Yu Jin.)
I was born in 1992.
(Ju Hee, 35 years old)
(She's 11 years older than Yun So.)
So she's 35.
You don't have to answer
if you feel pressured.
Do I still have a chance?
For you?
(Nodding)
After yesterday's date,
I've been thinking a lot about you.
Have I always been your favorite?
Is that why you were so shocked?
Since yesterday, yes.
Actually, I wrote down your name yesterday
as my first choice.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I've been wanting
to have a conversation with you.
I think I've become
more interested in you.
(Yu Jin and Si Won learn
how they feel about each other.)
I don't know what you think.
I felt like my conversation
with Si Won went better than I expected.
- After only a few hours?
- Yes.
So you've set your heart on Si Won now?
Yes. I think I have.
Actually, I was...
a little surprised last night
when you told me that.
You felt a little...
I'm not saying you were aggressive, but...
it felt like a declaration of war.
That was the impression I got.
(Ji Seung felt
like it was a declaration of war.)
I was just trying to explain my situation.
It wasn't a declaration of anything.
(Where will Si Won's heart go?)
Last week, the ages we had
all been the most curious about...
were finally revealed at Yeon House.
For me, this season is my first
as a panelist.
I didn't know how big...
of an aftermath
that information could bring.
What do you think?
It's huge.
- It is.
- I mean...
I realized...
that age can change how people feel...
about each other.
And there are some people
who don't care about it at all.
So it made it even harder...
for me to predict what will happen next.
- Right.
- It's impossible to predict.
What?
(A message for another new day arrives.)
What could it be?
- Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
- This is insane.
- What? A group date?
- "A 2-on-2 group date."
"A group date?"
How are they going to pair up?
My goodness. We have a group date today.
(A mysterious box...)
(appears in the Secret Room.)
(The group date will be
decided by random draw,)
(splitting them into either a group
of 6 or a group of 4.)
"A retro date versus a Gen-Z date."
So it has a theme.
I was hoping to go out...
with Yun So.
Ju Hee has changed.
I wanted to get to know the people...
I was attracted to.
I want to go out with Jung Won
as much as possible.
I was hoping to be grouped with Jung Won.
Things are starting to take shape.
(With emotions growing complicated,
the random group date begins.)
"Old and New."
The two dates have different themes.
(Who will end up with whom?)
(Yeon House)
(Time to reveal the results of the draw)
This is going to be fun.
(The first one to reveal is Jung Won.)
(Jin Young gets nervous
before Jung Won's reveal.)
(And Ji Hye too.)
Mine says "Old."
Old.
(Jung Won is in Old Group.)
Old?
I'm in New Group.
- New.
I see. New.
The two of them are in different groups.
I'm in Old Group.
(Jung Won and Ji Hye are placed
in the same group.)
I see. New.
Jung Won and I ended up
in different groups.
But Ji Hye drew the same team as Jung Won!
It made me feel really anxious.
Is that why you disappeared?
Sorry.
(Ji Hye gets a chance to go out
with Jung Won as she had hoped.)
Since we ended up on the same team,
I hoped today would be...
the day I could express my feelings...
for him.
(Next up is Si Won.)
Please, deities of entertainment.
(Yu Jin and Ji Seung are curious.)
Please make it spicier.
I drew New too.
New.
(Si Won got New.)
(Grinning)
Did Yu Jin draw the same one?
She's smiling.
- Wait. What about Ji Seung?
- This is so interesting!
I drew Old too.
(Ji Seung is in Old Group.)
(Si Won and Ji Seung are separated.)
- New?
- Yu Jin got New!
She looked like a hamster just now.
(Yu Jin ends up going out with Si Won.)
- Of course, it bothered me.
- It really did.
I was hoping
things wouldn't change between us...
or that nothing would change.
That's...
what I believed before.
(Ji Seung was sure about Si Won.)
But I'm not sure anymore.
What does Gen Z do on dates?
All I can think of is taking
instant photos.
- What do I do on a date?
- You're the youngest.
- Right.
I was very satisfied.
I felt relieved because I'd been...
into Si Won.
I'm in Old Group.
Hold on.
(Now it's time
to reveal Ju Hee's results.)
- Please let her be in Old Group.
- Old!
(He hopes they'll be together.)
- Mine is Old.
- Old!
(Ju Hee is in Old Group.)
I'm so glad.
(Ju Hee and Yun So are placed
in the same group.)
I'm Old too.
See? All of them.
I'm New.
- Jin Woo?
- Jin Woo and Jin Young!
(Jin Woo is in New Group.)
This is insane.
What will happen today?
This is a huge variable.
How could this happen?
"Arcade."
(New Group's date will be at an arcade.)
- We're going to an arcade?
- We're going to an amusement park.
Yes!
(Old Group's date will be
at an amusement park.)
(What will happen on their group dates?)
Will we wear those headbands
at the theme park?
- I think so.
- Yes.
Today is going to be fun.
I agree.
Can we have some churros too?
With vanilla ice cream? Yes.
Sir Jung Won said
he'd buy them for everyone.
So Ji Seung calls anyone
who buys her things "sir."
Don't call each other that. That's weird.
Let's all just be friends.
Yes.
We're practically the same age.
Thirty-three isn't that old.
Yun So, you're really young,
so use honorifics with everyone.
(Reading the room)
(Sulking)
I'm not going to talk to her.
Ju Hee is starting to smile
at Yun So's jokes now.
(Finding him cute)
Have you all made your final picks?
Sorry?
What about it?
There's no such thing
as a definite decision.
- Really?
- Yes.
But I've already made my final decision.
Already?
- Yes.
- That's fast.
I'm curious.
You are, aren't you?
Yesterday's date...
with Ji Hye was great.
I wanted to show her my charms
without Jung Won around.
So being grouped with Jung Won...
made me feel a little uneasy.
Oh, no.
(He is bothered by Jung Won.)
So all the men are bothered by Jung Won.
There it is!
- Really?
- No way!
(They arrive at the theme park.)
Hey, look. There's a dragon.
It's pretty nice.
(An amusement park perfect
for a retro date)
- It's so retro!
- This is going to be so fun!
It's been a long time
since I last visited a theme park.
Wait. That's a merry-go-round.
- Are you okay with riding rides?
- Yes.
Take it together!
Yun So is cute! "Take it together!"
So cute.
(Satisfied)
Wait. That's...
"Fairy Tale Castle."
- What's that?
- I don't know.
(Touching him)
(They burst into laughter
at small things.)
- What's that?
- It's a Fairy Tale Castle.
No way. Really?
(Turning around)
Let's take pictures over there later.
At the Fairy Tale Castle?
Hold on.
Things aren't looking good for Jun Han.
Jun Han seems to have lost confidence.
Let's ride the bumper cars.
- Bumper cars sound nice.
- Bumper cars?
Let's start with the wildest one.
- Is it a two-person ride?
- It's a two-person ride!
(If that's the case...)
Ju Hee, come on. You can drive.
(He calls Ju Hee right away.)
- Me?
- Yes.
You drive.
- Really? Can I?
- You drive.
- That feels a little off.
- You can drive this one, can't you?
That would make me look really bad.
He's been giving
off younger-boyfriend vibes for a while.
He seems comfortable around her
since their ages were revealed.
"Ju Hee! You drive."
"Ju Hee!"
"Ju Hee, over here!"
(Copying Yun So)
(Reading the room)
So it's a two-person ride?
Seems so.
(Spotting Ji Hye)
I'm a good driver!
Who wants to ride with me?
Oh, no.
- Isn't everyone getting one?
- Sorry?
(Ji Hye didn't hear him.)
The two of you will ride one, right?
The two...
(He calls her over again.)
Oh, no.
(His signal doesn't reach her.)
(Jun Han ends up with Ji Seung.)
- I mean, you...
- Yes?
You're so big.
Isn't it one car per person?
It's a two-person ride.
- Do you want to drive? Or should I?
- I see.
You drive.
No, you do it.
No, you can do it.
No.
You want me to?
(She goes to Jung Won with a big smile.)
- You trust me, right?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Taking one by yourself?
No, let's take it together.
Are you looking in the mirror?
I don't know.
Oh, no.
I hope it won't be all white and blurry.
- No way.
- Right?
- They look good together.
- They really do.
(Ju Hee and Yun So look
so close in the picture.)
That scared me.
(An alarm goes off
to signal the start of the ride.)
There we go.
How do I drive this thing?
Why isn't it moving?
This is pretty rough.
It's rough.
It's rougher than I expected.
(Excited)
Let's run away!
- Get away from them!
- I'm sorry.
Run away!
I'll hold your bag in place.
(Using her bag as an excuse)
Just leave it.
(Her firm answer makes
his hand hover in the air.)
You get the biggest hit
when you go head-on.
Let me go all the way there.
(The two can't stop laughing.)
Wait. Where are you going?
We get back in.
Wait!
- Are you okay?
- Are you all right?
(The fun bumper car time ends.)
- That was fun.
- That was really fun.
(His hand is still hovering.)
That was fun.
- I had fun.
- It was fun.
Shall we get coffee?
Yes. Let's get coffee.
- That was fun.
- Coffee?
She just looks at him, and he comes.
(Feeling her gaze,
Jung Won walks over to her side.)
I want to wear a headband too.
- We could buy one there.
- Are there some over there?
- I see some there.
- You do? Do they sell them?
(He doesn't seem to blend in.)
He must be so annoyed.
He can only watch her from behind...
unless he walks in front of her.
He tries to join them,
- but he can't.
- How can he?
It's impossible.
(The second ride is the Viking.)
Let me check your tickets.
(Ji Hye sits next to Jung Won again.)
Oh, dear.
(Jun Han is late again.)
Let's sit here.
(Jun Han sits with Ji Seung
in front of Ji Hye.)
Why is there a safety belt here?
- Are you scared?
- I am.
(He tries to hide it, but he feels sad.)
I feel bad.
- Ji Hye is acting like he's not there.
- Right, on purpose.
- On purpose.
- It's like she's ignoring him.
She's making it clear...
that she's not into him anymore.
Poor Jun Han.
(Yun So and Ju Hee are sitting
across from them.)
- It's so hot.
- I know!
- It's really hot.
- I feel like we're going to get tanned.
Is it too hot?
(Yun So shades her face with his hand.)
(Smiling)
It's moving.
It goes high.
Wait.
It's so intense.
(That's cute.)
(The pirate ship goes up
to almost a 90-degree angle.)
Please!
Wait.
Ji Hye, seriously.
Relax.
(They get close while scared.)
She held his hand briefly.
It's making my hands sweatier.
(Pale)
It's refreshing.
(He's also anxious.)
It goes higher than I thought.
(Heart, calm down.)
(Embarrassed)
(Yun So is terrified,
and Ju Hee finds it funny.)
(His face freezes up from nervousness.)
This is so funny.
Look at his face.
(Look at Yun So's face.)
His face looks pale.
(Pale)
(The terrifying pirate ship ride ends.)
- This is it.
- We're here.
It's nice.
This place? It's cool.
I haven't been to this kind of arcade
in a while.
- It's so pretty.
- That looks fun.
Shall we play the claw machine?
They seem to be in a good mood.
Let's win some plushies.
Let's see what they have.
Do you have a favorite character?
Loopy.
Do you like Loopy?
Can you get that? It's too big.
Loopy?
Should I get it for you?
- Really?
- Do you want one?
Try it.
Hold on.
Is that good?
- No?
- A little higher.
- Is it good now?
- Okay.
(That was close.)
You were so close.
Do you really want one?
- Loopy?
- Yes.
Well, it does look cute.
If it looks cute, I should get it.
Should we try it one last time?
When we leave Yeon House, you can eat
at my restaurant for free forever.
- Forever.
- As long as you're happy, I'm happy.
If this can make you happy,
that's enough for me.
She's an angel.
- I know.
- Let's go.
(Jin Woo was having a hard time
after being rejected by Ji Hye.)
Try to have a good time on the date...
for your date's sake too.
It'd be better to have
this kind of mindset.
I might ask you out.
(And Jin Woo showed some interest
in Jin Young.)
- Me?
- Yes.
Okay.
Just like I practiced.
I should drag it from the end.
You've practiced enough.
Win one for him.
No way!
- What?
What?
(Surprised)
Did you see that?
- What? I'm stunned.
- Did you see that?
Did you see that?
She pulled that off?
Jin Young is great.
That's impressive.
Since they moved into Yeon House,
- Jin Young is the first person...
- She's the first.
- who has done something so kind for him.
- You're right.
Jin Woo won't be able
to get her out of his mind.
(Will this make Jin Woo fall for her?)
- What?
- This is me.
I did this.
It's me.
I told you I'd win this for you.
He's so excited.
- Are you happy?
- This is awesome.
Go to sleep holding this.
- Carry this around with you today.
- Okay.
I think we look alike.
She looks just like you.
Give me a wink.
(Winking)
That was cute.
I really appreciated it.
I even have a Loopy phone case.
I really love Loopy.
I was really grateful,
and I thought she was a good person.
Hey, let me take a look.
Should I carry you?
- You shouldn't touch the ground.
- Carry me around on your back.
Okay. I'll show you.
Yu Jin seems jealous,
so Si Won wants to try too.
It bruised his ego a little.
Let's lift that one.
This one? Can it be lifted?
Let's drag it and put it
in the corner like this.
It's not as easy as it seems.
It's not that easy.
Let me try this.
Please, Si Won.
(Lifting)
My goodness!
- He did it.
- My gosh.
(Jackpot!)
It slid.
- Where is that arcade?
- It slid in.
Amazing!
I've never won anything
from a claw machine before.
Let's win them all.
- That's awesome.
- Can I try?
- Hey, Loopy.
- Loopy.
- Win something for me.
- My gosh.
This is fun.
- That was fun.
- How did we improve so quickly?
I know! We got better.
- I'm sweating so much.
- Me too.
- Were you nervous?
- I got too excited.
This is the most fun I've had
since I came to Yeon House.
Let's go.
(Team Old moves on to the next spot.)
Is this a photo studio?
We're going to take a family photo.
Since they're the old team,
they'll take an old family photo.
Oh, dear.
Seriously.
Amazing vibes here.
(Full of retro items)
That's fun.
(A 40-year-old photo studio)
Get a little closer.
Like a family photo from back then.
Okay, that's good.
I like that.
Why is Yun So so stiff?
In 1, 2.
That's cute.
(A vintage-style family photo,
perfect for Team Old)
Do you want to take more pictures?
As you've been getting to know each other,
has there been anyone
you've called dibs on?
- Call dibs on?
- "You're mine?"
Pictures in pairs?
- Do you want one?
- Let's do it.
Let's take pictures in pairs.
(Jun Han misses Ji Hye again.)
Let's take one.
(Yun So will take one with Ju Hee.)
- Let's take one.
- Okay.
Who wants to go first?
- Let's take one quickly.
- Okay.
Can we switch seats?
The right is my good side.
So you're a couple?
He's doing a good job.
Well...
- We don't know.
- No.
We're not sure.
(Sad)
How do people usually pose?
Your expression looks so awkward now.
It's like you're saying,
"We're strangers."
Not her shoulder.
- Not the shoulder?
- Put it down.
Her waist.
Why are you so shy?
- Can we do whatever we want?
- Yes.
- I like that.
- Relax your hands.
- Let's cross our legs.
- Okay.
I feel bad.
Aren't we almost like a married couple?
I'm the most myself...
when I'm with Jung Won.
He just makes me laugh nonstop
without even realizing it.
I had a wonderful time.
I just liked everything.
Actually, that's the best it can get.
He brings out the real you?
Nothing beats that.
They really looked great together.
It felt like Ji Hye's feelings were
shifting more toward Jung Won,
and that really made me unsettled.
Jun Han's a completely different person
from Day Two.
Oh my, look at the two of you!
(The two are becoming
more natural together.)
Sorry?
I really enjoyed taking pictures with her.
When we saw the photos afterward,
they were actually hilarious.
We both looked so funny,
- but even then,
- They look great together.
they really felt like couple photos.
We looked so good together.
(Next up are Yun So and Ju Hee.)
Can I do a peace sign?
Our hands feel a little awkward,
don't they?
You're keeping your hands
a little too neatly.
Rest your arm on his knee.
(Me?)
Are you two not close?
Us?
Put your hand on his knee.
(The photographer's suggestion brings
the two even closer.)
When she rested her arm on my knee,
my heart skipped a beat.
We already had a little physical contact
on the bumper cars,
so I was excited then too.
Getting close again at the studio
made me feel really happy.
(Even the smallest touch
makes Yun So's heart race.)
Smile.
We were much closer than usual,
and I really enjoyed the time with Yun So.
"Really."
(How did Yun So and Ju Hee's
heart-fluttering photos turn out?)
- Oh, that photo looks really good.
- It's nice.
How lovely!
(And Jun Han and Ji Seung's photos
with a newlywed vibe)
- Let's go.
- That's so hilarious.
I'm having so much fun today.
The second floor here.
(Meanwhile, where is
Team New's second stop?)
This kind of looks
like a self-photo studio.
(A self-photo studio
where you take your own pictures)
Let's go in and figure out
what poses to do. We have 15 minutes.
Sure. Should we just start
taking pictures?
Let's just take them naturally.
I'll sit over here.
(Yu Jin and Si Won start
their photo shoot.)
How should we pose
to make the pictures look good?
How should we pose?
(Gently laying her hand)
(Stiff)
This feels a little awkward.
- It does.
- What should we do?
Tell me.
(Their first couple photo shoot starts
off a little awkwardly.)
Then I'll just lean on you instead.
Hold the clicker lower
so the cord doesn't show.
Like this?
Or you could hold it with your other hand.
- So the cord doesn't show?
- Yes, try to hide it.
In 1, 2, 3.
Those two look so good together.
- How is it?
- Should I lean a little closer to you?
Like how?
Your pose looks good.
I should move a little closer to you.
Sure.
Good.
That's nice.
Good. Just keep it natural.
- This looks nice.
- Oh, I like this.
How about we look at each other?
I like that.
You know...
Let's just keep pressing the button
and take pictures.
- I think that'll look much better.
- It does feel natural.
Right? Just like this.
You're good at this.
- Isn't it nice?
- You're good.
Like this?
I think we should keep doing it this way.
Right.
(They can't contain their smiles.)
- Oh, gosh!
- Even I feel awkward!
- You know how it feels.
- Yes.
(Shaking)
I might break this chair today.
(Sliding on)
Yu Jin is having a blast.
I've never seen her this happy.
Let's just keep taking pictures.
Let's just take a whole bunch.
These two have such great chemistry.
(Glancing)
(Shy)
Like this.
At this rate, they might end up kissing.
I really enjoyed it.
Nothing felt awkward with Si Won.
The poses came naturally,
every little interaction felt effortless,
and I found him really cute.
I think I liked him even more after that.
At this point, they're basically dating.
Let's take an extreme close-up.
- This is making me a bit nervous though.
- Why?
An extreme close-up with Si Won?
Come on. It'll be fine.
Should we make flower poses
with our hands around our faces?
- Okay.
- Are you okay with that pose?
I'm really trying
a lot of new things today.
You do the flower pose,
and I'll just look at you.
Okay.
But then won't you be out of the frame?
I'll stay close enough.
He must really want
to keep looking at Yu Jin.
How does it look?
This one is cute too.
You think so?
I think you came out really well.
Were you only looking at me?
No. I looked at myself too.
I think taking pictures with Yu Jin made
my heart flutter even more.
It was exciting,
It definitely was.
and I really enjoyed doing
something together with her.
After that photo shoot,
I think my feelings for her grew
even stronger.
Once they finally had
some real physical contact,
- they...
- They definitely seemed a lot closer.
- Right.
- Hold on.
Now, I'm curious
how Jin Young and Jin Woo did.
Jin Woo, let's see what you've got!
Go for it.
Let's do the pose we talked about first.
The pose we talked about?
- Then I should just stay still, right?
- Yes.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The two are
effortlessly adorable together.)
That turned out well.
(Poking)
In 1, 2, 3.
Oh, my goodness.
Come forward.
Should we just take one without any pose?
(Glaring)
(Surprised)
(The closer Jin Woo gets,
the more flustered Jin Young becomes.)
Honestly, I thought
he was incredibly handsome...
from the very beginning.
I even thought he looked like an idol.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't feel butterflies.
Jin Woo's face is his greatest weapon.
What pose should we do?
Think of one.
Think.
(Staring)
What should we do?
(Getting close)
Gosh.
(Frozen)
You're the one who picked this pose.
- We had to take something somehow,
- You chose it.
so I just went with it.
Okay.
(There's an awkward tension
between the two.)
Jin Woo suddenly got
really forward with me.
It made me wonder,
"What's going through his head?"
I did feel butterflies a bit,
to be honest,
but everything happened so suddenly...
that I kept thinking,
"Why is he acting
like this all of a sudden?"
I was actually trying
to focus my feelings on Jung Won,
so part of me felt...
that...
Jin Woo shouldn't
suddenly come on so strong.
But he's seriously so handsome.
He really is.
It's almost unfair.
I think she was probably wondering...
whether the poses
and things I did during the photo shoot...
felt like a romantic move,
or whether I was just doing them for fun.
Well, it's not like Jin Young...
suddenly became the person I was
most interested in overnight.
I think that would've been
too sudden a change in my feelings.
I approached Jin Young
with about 30 percent romantic interest,
and through that process, I realized
I was starting to see her romantically.
At the same time,
I found her really fun to be around...
and a genuinely nice person.
(What change will
Jin Woo's straightforward approach bring?)
- Let's go in.
- Bye. Great job today.
- Good night.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow.
- Good job. Good night.
- Good night.
(Si Won looks through the photos
he took with Yu Jin.)
Oh, he's looking at the photos again.
(Giggling)
Si Won must've been really happy.
(Just looking at them brings
a smile to his face.)
(Si Won reminisces about his time
with Yu Jin.)
(The plushie Si Won won for Yu Jin)
Look at how tightly she's hugging
that plushie.
The typical behavior of those who have
just come back from a date!
(Yu Jin thinks about her time
with Si Won.)
- See you at ten.
- See you.
Bye!
Good night.
Si Won.
I'm back.
Brother.
- Did you have fun?
- I'm back.
Did you have fun?
- Those two are both on cloud nine.
- It's game over.
This room is the winners' room.
It's a full-on celebration in here.
I wish the people in these rooms would
go on a double date together.
How was it? Your
date with Jin Young and Yu Jin.
Did you have fun?
- It was way more fun than I expected.
- Really?
I had such a great time today.
I can tell by the look on your face.
Really?
I've never seen
Si Won react like this before.
(As soon as she gets back to the house,
Jin Young heads somewhere.)
Jin Young, go shake things up.
Si Won,
ask Jung Won to come out for me.
She must've really wanted to see him.
Jung Won,
someone's asking for you outside.
Okay.
Is it Jin Young out there?
Yes.
(Learning that Jin Young is outside,
Jin Woo immediately heads out.)
Jin Woo is going out?
She asked for Jung Won.
Jin Young.
During the interview...
(Jin Woo hands her the photos
they took together.)
You wouldn't want these photos
sitting around in our room, right?
(Jung Won comes out immediately.)
(Peeking)
(Jung Won notices Jin Woo is
with Jin Young.)
I don't want Jung Won
to see this right now.
- Really?
- Do you want to keep it, then?
No, you can keep it.
But I don't want you to show it to him.
Jin Young is really clear
about everything, isn't she?
- I'll hide it, then.
- Okay.
You can tell me anything.
- Can I just tell you random things?
- Yes.
He's hurt.
(Jin Young didn't want
Jung Won to see the photo.)
She doesn't want Jung Won
to see the picture.
And she wants him
to hide it from Jung Won.
But what if Jin Woo...
He understood, right?
After she said that,
what if Jin Woo put it
on Jung Won's pillow?
(Evil smile)
(Jin Young and Jung Won come
to the common area for a conversation.)
(This is the first conversation
between these two today.)
(Staring)
Who did your hair today?
My hair?
Guess who.
What?
I think you did.
I did.
Who else would do my hair except me?
- Don't you think?
- You're right.
I need to trim my fingernails.
Your nails are already very short.
It'd be painful
if you trimmed them too short, right?
Goodness.
They're already short.
What more is there to trim?
I can just trim them a little more.
- So you never leave any white part?
- I guess not.
(Everyone gathers
in the common area one by one.)
(Peeking)
The big sister is coming.
Ji Hye really does look
like a fitting model.
Watching her take pictures today,
I understood why she could be a model.
She's good.
Oh...
Hello.
(Finding her cute)
Oh, no.
- She's different.
- She's a pro.
- Of course.
- You're a model, right?
How long do you think I've been modeling?
What an expert.
(Laughing)
(Ji Hye and Jung Won seem
very close after the date.)
(Jun Han and Yu Jin also come
into the common area.)
(Peeking)
(Si Won moves his seat
after spotting Yu Jin.)
I want to sit next to you.
- I want to sit here.
- Okay.
(He pushes Yun So away...)
(to make space for Yu Jin to sit.)
(During the job reveal...)
(and last night,)
Wait!
(Yu Jin has always been sitting
in the corner.)
(Si Won saves Yu Jin's spot.)
Because Yu Jin loves that corner,
he moves there to sit with her.
(As Yu Jin comes in...)
(Peeking)
It's been a while
since I last saw you, Yu Jin.
(Yu Jin comes over next to Si Won,
just as he expected.)
- That's so sweet.
- He's cute.
The picture of us.
- I brought it to show it off to everyone.
- We took a picture together.
- Let me see!
- Let me see it.
Our picture is really cute.
It's a really good picture.
- It really is a good one.
- So cute.
- You're even in similar outfits.
- Right.
It's so good.
The picture is so good.
(Ji Seung arrives.)
- We're so cute.
- We really are.
(Ji Seung comes closer
to see the picture.)
I told you we'd take the instant photo.
(Flustered)
So cute.
Yu Jin, you look so cute in this one.
Si Won is really handsome, isn't he?
You're really pretty.
(Ji Seung quietly leaves the spot.)
Yun So, can you make a finger heart
when you take a photo?
- Can I make this sign?
- Of course he can.
I can.
You should
at least make a cheek heart too.
(It bothers Si Won that he couldn't
make a cute pose while taking photos.)
That's the minimum, right?
You should at least make a cheek heart.
- A cheek heart?
- Can you do it now?
Of course I can do it now.
That's crazy.
(Cute)
Joy and disappointment collide.
After the date,
the two seemed really close.
It bothers me a little.
Si Won might have had a change of heart.
- Do you want to go out?
- Let's go out.
Let's eat this outside.
This is so romantic!
The place is amazing.
(Jung Won and Jin Young sit
next to each other.)
You're wearing the thickest clothes,
a padded coat.
Jin Young, can I have a moment with you?
(Turning his head around)
Are you drunk?
No, I'm not.
You turned as red as a carrot.
No, I'm not drunk.
Not at all?
Maybe about ten percent?
- How much did you drink?
- A couple of shots of soju?
- I'm not drunk.
- You drank two shots?
Two or three?
(Jin Young enters Jin Woo's room.)
You're sitting in the spot
where you sat yesterday.
(They face each other in the same spot
where they talked last night.)
What are they going to talk about?
Yesterday, I talked things
over with you, right?
And today, it was a date.
As your date today, I did my best.
But I couldn't act like your boyfriend
after just one night, right?
So I fooled around a lot on purpose.
- Oh, did you?
- If I crossed...
any line, I'm sorry.
No, you didn't do anything wrong.
Anyway, although it wasn't
a 1-on-1 date with you today,
I tried my best to be romantic with you.
And I feel...
the most comfortable around you.
I'm attracted to you.
That's why I called you here,
to hear what you think.
He's so straightforward.
(She hesitates to answer.)
(Nervous)
Actually, in the first interview
when I had just arrived here,
I said Jun Han was first,
and you were second.
I told them that Jin Woo was so handsome.
- On the day you arrived?
- Yes.
You were so handsome
that I couldn't look into your eyes.
But time passed so quickly.
And now, I'm the most attracted
to Jung Won right now.
He makes me feel romantic.
So...
Oh, no.
I want to focus on the person
I care about the most.
- Because we're almost out of time.
- Right.
It doesn't matter to me who you like
the most or the second most.
I know you've been building
relationships with others.
But rather than that,
I just want to keep asking you out...
if you see me as a man.
That's what I want to do.
What should I do? Seriously.
Is it because you feel sorry for me?
No. Geez. What should I do?
It's not that I don't see you as a man.
But the timing isn't good right now.
And I've made up my mind...
that I'll focus only on the person
I care about the most.
- That's what I'll do.
- I understand.
So I don't want to lead you on.
You're not.
But about that timing,
from my point of view...
- Is that misleading too?
- No, it's not.
But I think it's something I can change.
It's not you misleading me.
It's me wanting to do something about it.
It's not like my heart
didn't flutter today.
Of course, I found it somewhat romantic.
Especially, I've been thinking
that you're really handsome,
- and you made...
- I made my moves?
Yes, you did.
I was thrown off.
- "Is he crazy?"
- Like, "What's going on?"
"Is he crazy?"
- But...
- Where? When did you feel that?
Did I go that far?
When we took the pictures?
- Or before?
- No. Your problem is your face.
That's your biggest problem.
Anyway, you have that handsome face
as your weapon.
However...
No.
Do I have to keep listening?
Your heart pounded today
because of me anyway.
- Yes, it did.
- That means you see me as a man.
- That's true, but...
- But?
But if I keep leading you on,
I don't think I'll be able to focus
because it'll be too confusing for me.
So you want me to stop?
But what if I don't want to?
What if I don't want that?
No, I mean... Anyway.
(Broken)
I mean...
Hey!
She can't hide it.
I can still ask you out, right?
- That's up to you.
- Right.
(Jin Woo makes a move toward Jin Young.)
(Where will their relationship go
from here?)
Today's date wasn't bad at all.
- No, it wasn't.
- So...
How about we all root for Jin Woo?
I just want the two of them to work out.
For now, I think we should keep
our eyes on them from here.
I should've grabbed my coat.
It's so cold out here.
Is it? Did you have a good conversation?
Yes.
What is it?
What is it about?
Pandora's QR?
(Pandora's QR is now open.)
"Scan the QR code
of the person you're curious about..."
"and you can check their top picks
so far?"
(If you scan the QR code
of the person you're curious about,)
(you'll be able to check
their top picks so far.)
It disappears in an hour.
- All their top picks?
- From Day One?
- Every night.
- All their top picks from Day One.
Their top picks?
You should start running now.
I'd never check that.
- No?
- I wouldn't either.
I would never.
Who do you think would check whose QR?
Jin Young and Ji Hye would
check Jung Won's.
Yun So...
would check Ju Hee's...
and start getting rid of them.
- With force?
- Yes.
He might push one into a pool.
He'd give them
the same hairstyle overnight.
(The QR Room is open again.)
(You can see who your crush picked
every night.)
(Who will open Pandora's box?)
- My gosh.
- It will disappear in an hour?
It disappears in an hour.
(Checking is optional.)
They gave them enough time
so they can check in secret too.
This is epic.
"Checking is optional."
I never check something like this.
I don't open Pandora's box.
- Right.
- That's cool.
Seeing that would make me feel uneasy.
- I...
- I won't check either.
Do you want to see it?
I'll open it.
I knew it.
I knew you'd open that.
(Glancing)
I'll open it.
If you want to check, you should go now.
That wouldn't be bad.
If you don't want to, don't go.
(Looking around)
I'll go open it.
(Ji Hye gets up right away.)
There she goes.
- She's going to open Pandora's box.
- There goes Ji Hye!
Ji Hye is going.
- Go!
I'll be back.
(Going to the QR Room without hesitation)
I wanted to open it immediately.
I was curious.
I wondered the person I was into...
had been choosing.
I thought it could help me...
make up my mind.
- Does it matter that much?
- It's important to her.
- Is it that important?
- Yes.
She can just go for the person she likes,
can't she?
Some people go
for the person they're into,
while others prefer someone
who's into them too.
(Which younger man's feelings
does Ji Hye want to be sure of?)
(The first person to face Pandora QRs)
(Swiping)
(The person Ji Hye is curious about)
(The Pandora QR that Ji Hye opened is...)
It must be Jung Won, right?
(Jung Won's.)
I knew Ji Hye would choose that.
(Who has Jin Won been into every night?)
(Frowning)
(Day 2: Ji Hye)
(Day 3: Jin Young, Day 4: Jin Young)
(Except for the first day,
Jung Young has been choosing Jin Young.)
That might be a bit of a blow.
He's been choosing Jin Young
except for his first day.
Actually, I thought about it a lot
after the amusement park.
I was worried...
that Jung Won might just think
that I'm a fun older woman.
Did I make myself come across that way?
Have I been doing it wrong?
I kept wondering.
But after checking his QR,
I realized I was right.
Jung Won only sees me...
as someone who is fun
and easy to be around.
If Jin Young likes him,
I should let him go.
(Will Ji Hye give up Jung Won like this?)
I'll go after Ji Hye.
Really? Do you want to check?
I never open Pandora's box.
- Me neither.
- I wouldn't bother.
What matters is the end.
I just want to satisfy my curiosity.
I get it.
I'll be back.
She looks happy.
Do you feel better?
Yes!
I wonder whose QR she opened.
I won't tell you.
(Sassy)
(Jin Young arrived to check Pandora QRs.)
(Looking around)
(Smiling)
(The person Jin Young is curious about...)
(is Jin Young as expected.)
She only has eyes for him.
(Smiling)
She saw Jung Won's QR.
To be honest, I was a little surprised.
When I saw it, I was like, "What?"
(Day 2: Ji Hye,
Day 3: Jin Young, Day 4: Jin Young)
He's been choosing me
since we played Truth Game.
During that game,
he kept choosing Ji Hye as his number one.
(Say something heart-fluttering
to your number one.)
I had a lot of fun today.
(Jung Won chose Ji Hye as his top pick
during Truth Game.)
That's true.
So I don't know why he sent me his QR.
Why did he choose me?
I wanted to ask him why.
I was so curious.
And I'm kind of touched.
(Jin Young is touched and also curious
at the same time.)
(Smiling)
It made me like Jung Won more.
She's happy.
Now that I think about it,
we don't really know how Jung Won feels.
Right.
Their love triangle is still unclear.
(After checking Jung Won's Pandora QR,)
(Ji Hye seems to be lost in thought.)
I'm going to go over there.
- The QR Room?
- Yes.
- Are you going to open Pandora's box?
That's good.
(Nodding)
Jin Young's steps...
- Her steps look light.
- Is it light?
She looks cool.
(Relaxed?)
(Jin Young seems excited.)
- Show us again.
- That was cute.
- Why is she so cute?
- I know.
She's cute.
- Ji Hye must be annoyed.
- Look at her face.
- They saw the same thing.
- Yes.
She's coming back like, "I won."
Jung Won must be anxious.
He must be sweating everywhere.
His back and his armpits.
(Glancing over)
You can go now.
I'll be back.
He's fast.
(Whose Pandora QR will Jung Won open?)
Did you get your answers?
- What?
- Did you get your questions answered?
- Yes, I did!
- Because she opened it.
I feel good.
(Jung Won came running.)
Let me see.
Will Jung Won open Ji Hye's
or Jin Young's?
(Whose Pandora QR will Jung Won open?)
Is it Ji Hye's?
Whose QR will he open?
(Male Bombshell Jung Won's choice?)
(The Pandora QR that Jung Won opened...)
(belongs to Ji Hye.)
I'm into Jin Young,
but I wanted to see Ji Hye's.
I wanted to know something
that would give me clarity.
If Ji Hye was never into me,
I would keep going for Jin Young.
But when I saw her Pandora QR...
Ji Hye's Pandora QR.
(Tilting his head)
(Day 1: Yun So, Day 2: Jung Won)
(Day 3: Jun Han, Day 4: Jung Won)
(Ji Hye chose Jung Won at the end.)
And she chose me.
I felt like...
my assumptions had been completely off.
I'm really confused.
(Learning about Ji Hye's choice
gives Jung Won a lot to think about.)
After seeing that,
Jung Won thinks Ji Hye is into him,
and he changes his mind and pursues her.
But after seeing his QR,
Ji Hye changes her mind.
Then they misunderstand each other again.
He shouldn't hesitate.
He should resolve this situation quickly.
Why does everyone look so serious
when they come back?
What's with everyone?
(Glancing over)
(Glancing)
How was it? Do you feel any different now?
I just had a question.
- Do you have more questions now?
- Did you get an answer?
Did you?
(Smiling)
No comment.
This isn't something to bring up here.
Did you get to talk
to everyone you wanted to?
I think Jung Won did.
Well...
Almost?
Almost.
But even though I've talked to them,
I haven't actually been
on a proper date with them yet.
Talking to someone and going on a date
can be completely different.
That's true, though.
Jin Young is probably wondering
if Jung Won is talking about her.
She's also trying to figure out
what he really means.
Then if you get a Date Choice Pass,
are you going to ask that person out?
I don't know.
You're so evasive.
- He's such a sly fox.
- He really is.
- He's a total bombshell.
- He is, for sure.
The bombshells really are different.
Right.
Ji Hye's mind must be all over the place,
The bombshells are different.
Did you get the answers
you were looking for?
It was pretty much what I expected.
Really?
It was exactly what you expected?
- Pretty much...
- It was pretty much what I expected.
Is that so?
Just as I expected.
(Jung Won can't stop thinking
about Ji Hye's answer.)
No?
(Jung Won has no response.)
They can't go to sleep tonight.
If they do, it's game over.
Why are you so serious?
- I'm not.
- Really?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
So the Pandora QR was meant
for these three all along.
So, how was everyone's group date today?
And after the group date?
- I had so much fun.
- Did it change how you feel?
Well,
it kind of...
Mine definitely changed today.
- Really?
- Seriously?
I'm sure of it.
Did your feelings become more certain,
or did they change?
They've become completely certain.
- After today's date.
- Really?
- After the group date?
- Sorry?
After the group date?
Yes.
I think she's saying it to Jung Won.
Right?
(Smiling)
Jung Won is happy.
(Reading the room)
Looking through it is actually pretty fun.
- Really?
- It's so much fun.
Jin Young is...
saying that on purpose
to get under Ji Hye's skin.
So the choices we've made are in it?
Exactly.
I can't believe it's already day five.
It's only day four for the bombshells.
Have you checked the bombshells' QR too?
I got you!
What's gotten into Jin Young?
It's cute that she thinks
he checked out her QR.
(Jin Young is completely mistaken.)
(The two become lost in thought.)
(The older women and younger guys
move to the common area.)
Maybe I should go check the Pandora QR.
But I'm not so sure.
It's really just
about satisfying your curiosity.
I'm not that curious.
So, you're not curious about anyone?
That's not it.
Then what is it? What's going on?
Me?
Shall we step outside for a minute?
(Ji Seung steps outside
with Jin Young for the moment.)
Wait, Ji Seung and Jin Young
are going outside together?
It's great that Jung Won is left!
You're going out?
Yes.
Are you actually escorting her out?
I'm just going out...
to get some fresh air too.
I might check the Pandora QR,
or I might not.
- Let's go out.
- And think about it.
I'm the type of person
who puts things off as long as I can.
Isn't this a huge opportunity
for Jung Won?
(An exchange of glances)
(Bursting into laughter)
I knew it.
Do you want to talk?
(Nodding)
Now?
(Ji Hye and Jung Won immediately get up.)
I was thinking that
I should have a conversation with you.
(The two opened each other's Pandora,
and now they start talking.)
Whose QR did you check today?
I checked yours.
- I checked yours too.
- Really?
(They both laugh at the same time,
feeling awkward.)
I checked yours because I was curious.
How do you feel now?
I don't know.
At first,
I was obviously interested in you.
But I thought you weren't
showing any interest in me at all.
Ji Hye is surprised since she thought
she had shown her feelings.
So I thought you weren't
showing your feelings toward me.
But you kept saying that you were
getting more certain about this person.
So I thought that person wasn't me.
And I chose Jin Young...
because she was much more direct with me.
You chose Jin Young for two days in a row.
I chose you on the first day,
and I chose Jin Young the other two days.
So I thought, "What I thought was right."
I thought you only saw me
as a funny and comfortable older woman.
If I had been certain
about my feelings for Jin Young,
would I have checked your QR?
Think about it.
If I'd been so certain about her.
I thought you would check Jin Young's QR.
From what I've seen, you seemed
to take care of Jin Young a lot.
If I'd felt like
you were only taking care of me,
I think I would've
shown my feelings to you too.
I thought I approached you a lot
at the swimming pool.
I was the one who made
a lot of effort to get closer first.
I think I chose you
on the Love QR that day.
No, you chose Jun Han then.
- No.
- Yes.
That was the day
we played the Truth Card session...
after we came back from the pool.
And I kept choosing you
during the session.
That's true,
but you eventually sent the QR to Jun Han.
I just looked at your history.
I had to get to know other people too.
I said I'd let you know after that.
This is what makes me confused.
What will happen between these two?
But what I really don't understand is...
that Jun Han, Jin Woo, and even Yun So
all asked me the same thing.
They all asked, "Don't you like Jung Won?"
Was I the only one who couldn't tell?
Why was it so hard for me to notice?
They all came to me and asked that.
Everyone seemed to know,
to the point where I wondered
if I was making it too obvious.
I really didn't notice at all.
Maybe you just wanted
to pretend not to know?
No, absolutely not.
I really didn't notice.
I thought...
I was honest with you and showed
my feelings a lot at the amusement park.
- Was that not enough?
- No, today at the amusement park,
I saw how you expressed your feelings,
- I thought I expressed myself a lot.
- and I acknowledged it.
I admit that you expressed
your feelings a lot today.
- I really did express myself a lot today.
- Right.
And I'm also grateful
that you asked me to talk.
If you hadn't asked me to talk,
I might've just given up and thought,
"He must end up with Jin Young."
Exactly.
Right. If those two hadn't talked today,
who knows what would have happened?
So how do you feel now?
I'm sure now.
What are you sure about?
I'm diving in with you.
(Ji Hye is going to dive
right into Jung Won.)
- Is Ji Hye the only one who's sure?
- Unbelievable.
No more wandering.
I finally understand your feelings now.
I don't think I'll worry about it anymore.
Right. We only have two days left.
I think a lot of things will be sorted out
and changed in the next two days.
"Changed?"
Anything can change, of course.
Nothing is impossible.
But you shouldn't change.
I don't think I will.
You shouldn't.
(Jung Won doesn't leave a clear answer
to Ji Hye's confession.)
Even after Ji Hye lowered herself
this much...
and tried to explain her feelings,
he still isn't giving her a clear answer.
(Exactly.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Seung is still not sure
about opening the Pandora QR.)
I started wondering
if there is anyone here that you like.
Well...
Let me guess.
Go ahead.
Si Won.
- Actually...
- No?
Actually,
it's true that I chose Si Won a few times,
but I don't really know how he feels.
- You don't?
- No.
That's what I'm struggling with.
I just don't know
if he's worth checking his QR for.
- Let's go to the door and think about it.
- Hey!
Let's think about
whether you should open the door.
But I don't know if he is worthy enough
for me to check that QR.
But do you know what's funny?
I've kept choosing Si Won.
I think Si Won kept choosing me
in the beginning too.
But now I don't know anymore.
It started because he asked me out first,
and I think he is a really good person.
He is handsome too.
But the age...
- The gap is big, though.
- Right.
Still, he is really mature.
But there isn't much time left.
(The Pandora QR will close
in three minutes.)
Then should I just do it?
- Let's just do it.
- If I were you, I would do it.
Then half the responsibility is on you.
(She decides to open the Pandora QR.)
She must want to see it so badly.
She really wants to know,
but I think she is afraid.
Let's go.
(Si Won's No.1 choice every night)
(Day 1, Ji Seung)
(Day 2, Ji Seung)
(Day 3, Yu Jin)
(Day 4, Ji Seung)
Si Won chose Ji Seung again yesterday.
But the choice he made on Day 4
doesn't really mean much.
The same thing happened
to all the couples.
Today's dates were so intense
for everyone.
(Right after the ages were revealed,
Si Won sent his Love QR to Ji Seung.)
(But after that, Yu Jin and Si Won
had some time alone together.)
(Will Si Won's feelings
still be the same?)
Thank you for waiting.
- So, what do you say?
- What do I say?
(The QR Room closes after Ji Seung.)
Honestly, I'm not so sure about this.
Why aren't you going?
- Me?
- Yes.
I tend to live in the moment,
so I don't really care much
about the past.
- Exactly.
- That's a great mindset.
I was curious.
When things first started sparking
between you and Yu Jin?
I had absolutely no idea.
Well, when we went to the pool,
there were five of us in each car.
- Right, we were in different cars.
- Yes, and then after that,
we ended up sitting
right next to each other.
And our conversation
just flowed so smoothly.
True.
It was really fun talking to her.
Ever since then,
I wanted to sit down and have
a proper conversation with her.
And I feel like we've been
progressing step by step.
But then,
right before we finally got to talk,
we found out we have a 12-year age gap.
So things hadn't even started
at that point yesterday?
Right. Until our ages were revealed,
I hadn't really gotten a chance
to talk to her.
But after we found out,
we talked until very late at night.
And I really loved our conversation.
- Oh, they're coming.
- So...
So you wanted to talk to her
and see where things stand?
Going on a date is completely different
from just chatting.
Where did they go?
Why is everyone in such a rush
now that Pandora's QR is closed?
And our date today was really nice too.
So as of today, I'm locked in on her.
They are on completely different
wavelengths right now!
You know what's crazy?
As soon as I looked, it said,
"The QR Room is closed."
- Was it closed when you checked?
- Yes.
- It doesn't really matter to you, right?
- Actually, I'm glad.
Oh, you're happy about it?
Jin Young.
(Pointing)
What?
- Huh?
- Want to head outside?
Outside? Sure, let's go.
Did Jung Won and Ji Hye go somewhere?
- Huh?
- Did they go somewhere?
It's exactly what you think.
This is my only chance.
I don't want to take away
from your time with Jung Won.
You know, I'm a little tipsy.
More than I was earlier.
I like that.
- I'm way more drunk than before.
- He likes it.
Si Won looks uncomfortable.
This is funny.
Why?
- Nothing.
- Why is it funny?
It's just funny how we're all
splitting off in pairs.
I see.
(Ji Seung looks relieved
after checking the Pandora's QR.)
(Si Won looking at the photo
he took with Yu Jin)
He's looking at his photo with Yu Jin?
This is getting really interesting.
Is it?
(Awkward silence
after a brief conversation)
(Si Won looking at his photo
with Yu Jin again)
What on earth is going on here?
They're just staring straight ahead.
It's like they're in completely
different worlds.
(They sit in complete silence.)
I don't know, though.
What?
I think I'll head back to my room.
I don't really like it out here.
Let's head to our room.
"Let's head to our room?"
Or we can head back later.
(Si Won doesn't answer.)
Everyone else is chatting.
We can always meet back up later.
She practically invited him to her room,
but he's totally ignoring her.
(Si Won's silence continues.)
I think I'll head inside.
Okay.
(Ji Seung heads back alone.)
(Si Won is left alone
after rejecting Ji Seung's invitation.)
Si Won is so ruthless.
He's looking at the photo again.
He completely shut her down.
(Are his feelings for Ji Seung
completely gone?)
So, they're pairing up?
(Jin Young and Jin Woo head
to the Talk Room.)
We might have to pull an all-nighter.
(Ji Hye and Jung Won
step outside as well.)
Let's grab a drink!
What do you want to do? It's up to you.
- Me?
- Go talk to him if you want.
I think I'll talk to Jung Won a bit more.
- We're going to keep drinking.
- I see.
- Do whatever you want.
- Let's keep drinking.
Okay.
This is a great chance for Jin Young.
She hasn't really had a chance
to talk to him yet.
(Locking arms)
Are they locking arms?
Do whatever you want.
If you're not coming with me,
I'm going to sleep.
Really?
- Hey, Jung Won.
- Yes?
- Are you leaving?
- No.
Let's have a drink here.
Oh, really?
She wants some alone time with him.
Really?
Jin Woo!
Talk Room is right over there.
Okay. Is someone in there?
I don't think so.
- Jung Won, can I borrow a sheet mask?
- Yes, sure.
(Jin Woo gives Jin Young some space.)
(Ji Hye leaves as well.)
- Why do you look so upset?
- What? No, I'm not.
Why is your hair such a mess?
- Is it?
- What were you two doing in there?
Nothing. We didn't do anything.
- Nothing.
- You seem highly suspicious.
There's nothing to worry about.
The two of them...
need to clear up
all their misunderstandings right here.
(What will they talk about?)
Did you ever tell me?
Why you chose me on the third day?
No, I didn't tell you yet.
Tell me.
So, before that, I had chosen Ji Hye.
So why did I switch to you after that?
Nothing really happened between you
choosing Ji Hye and then me.
So why the sudden change of heart?
For me,
when you locked arms with me,
it made a huge impact.
Because I had been feeling really bad.
He felt so guilty.
I felt like I wasn't stepping up as a man.
I had asked to meet up and talk,
and I definitely could have made the time.
But I didn't,
and I felt terrible about it.
Right.
But despite all that,
in front of everyone,
you still came up and locked arms with me.
I had so much respect for you
for doing that.
And that was the moment
I found myself most attracted to you.
I see.
Now I have my answer.
Did you check my Pandora's QR?
Or someone else's?
Oh my gosh!
- The QR?
- Yes.
Whose do you think?
Mine, right?
(Awkward silence)
- Oh, no!
- It's a secret.
Why can't you just tell me?
Stay curious about me.
I'll tell you some other time.
- No, tell me now.
- No way.
- Why not?
- I want to keep you guessing.
Oh, come on.
I want to keep you curious.
Come on, you've already been caught.
You chose me.
- Oh, no.
- I don't know.
But...
why are you so sure about me?
What do you mean "sure?"
Are you not sure about me?
- Why do I like you?
- Yes.
Out of all these people here.
(Jin Young thinks deeply
about Jung Won's question.)
I think...
Well...
When I picture being with someone
in the real world...
and who fits into my life,
it was you.
I really like you right now.
But...
I don't know...
if it's just the excitement
of this environment,
or if we are actually compatible people...
who would work well in the long run.
I wanted to be sure about that.
Come on, I'm not just
some fleeting excitement.
I don't know.
I'm actually great in the long run.
Sell yourself to me then.
How should I win you over?
You'll find out soon enough
once we're out of here.
(Laughs)
Come here.
What did you and Ji Hye talk about?
What did you talk about with Ji Hye?
(Naturally holding hands)
They're holding hands.
What did you guys talk about?
How much do you want to know?
I'm dying to know. Tell me.
- Really?
- Tell me.
What is happening right now?
(What on earth is this timing?)
(Ji Hye suddenly enters the Talk Room.)
(Flustered)
Where did Jun Han go?
He was cooking in the common area earlier.
(Leaves)
She was so upset
she didn't even close the door.
What worries me about this is...
how deeply Jung Won was talking
to Ji Hye just a moment ago.
They had such a serious conversation.
But the second he walks out,
he starts acting like this with Jin Young.
- And Ji Hye saw the whole thing.
- Yes.
It's hard to look at Jung Won
in a good light right now.
This is going to be so tough on Ji Hye.
I think...
Jung Won needs to make up his mind
and stick with it.
He's playing the ultimate
wild card right now.
(What a massive curveball.)
With Ji Hye?
I just...
told her that I felt bad.
Okay, I won't pry any further.
Why? You can ask. It's fine.
So, how was your date with Jin Woo today?
Jin Woo?
He was flirting with me big time.
Really? And how did you react?
(Jung Won holds Jin Young's hand.)
See that?
For me,
I've already made up my mind
to go all-in on you.
Well, that's...
Why don't you waver just a little bit?
Even if you choose me in the end.
- Just to keep it fun.
- Should I?
(Look at this guy.)
Calm down. It's okay.
Control yourself.
We're the hosts.
Oh my gosh.
Why don't you waver just a little bit?
Even if you choose me in the end.
- Just to keep it fun.
- Should I?
And make you a little more nervous?
Yes, keep me on my toes.
You want me to make you nervous?
Is that what you want?
I can definitely do that.
What are your plans for tomorrow? Tell me.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
- Just sleep well.
- No way, don't give me that.
Act tough.
- Okay?
- How do I do that?
Act like a tough woman.
(Staring)
They look like they're about
to hug any second.
Okay?
You're so corny.
- Just act tough.
- You're suddenly being so corny.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
Aren't you? Be honest.
Jung Won is the ultimate king
of this jungle.
(Meanwhile,
Jun Han is in the common area.)
(Ji Hye comes to see Jun Han.)
- I'm here.
- Hey.
Here, eat this.
What did you make?
What's this?
What did you make this time?
Bean sprout soup.
You get pretty bad hangovers.
(During Jung Won and Ji Hye's
conversation a moment ago)
Wasn't it that day?
Can we talk for a bit after you're done?
Sure.
- I'll head over as soon as we're done.
- We'll keep it short.
Take your time.
I'll be waiting in the common area.
(Then he made
bean sprout soup for Ji Hye.)
Maybe this will be
the turning point for them.
Eat up.
Are you serious?
Is this actually happening?
Let's eat together. Come over here.
You seriously made this for me?
Ji Hye walks out completely upset
after checking the chat,
and Jun Han is waiting for her
with bean sprout soup?
This might actually make her think,
"Maybe he's the one."
- Life is all about timing.
- Time to change your pick.
It's my first time making this.
- My absolute first time.
- Really?
Yes.
I'm touched.
This is so cheesy that I'm actually
cringing and a bit embarrassed.
(Nervous)
Wait, is his hand shaking?
But I really wanted to tell you this.
I'm going to start wearing my heart
on my sleeve tomorrow.
I'm going all-in.
(That's cute.)
What?
I'll just cut to the chase.
I know you like getting straight
to the point.
I don't care about the process.
I'm all about results.
Right?
So I'm asking you for a chance.
A chance to show you how I feel.
Let's go!
Okay.
I get what you mean.
Speak of the devil.
- Who?
- Jung Won.
Drinking a lot, are we?
Why are you still up?
I was just about to go to bed.
Why the romantic look?
I've decided to go all-in.
(Bursts out laughing at Jun Han's comment)
You've said that so many times already.
How many all-ins do you have left?
Seriously, you keep saying that.
No one is going to take him
seriously anymore.
I'm really going to prove it
starting tomorrow.
- It's not like the other...
- Did he say this multiple times?
Has he done this before?
Oh, no. That totally ruined the mood.
No, that's not...
Are you really that shallow?
No, I told you...
You're so funny.
I'm just...
Whatever. I'll just say it.
Everyone thinks I flirt with everyone,
so I'm just going to lay it all out here.
Whenever I open up, I always get rejected.
I see.
I actually chose Jun Han that time.
And...
I thought you were already taken.
You thought I was already taken?
That's what I thought.
- So I was just happy we got to talk.
- But he didn't know that.
Didn't know what?
That it was him and me.
Me?
Why are you pointing at me?
There is no way Jung Won
didn't know how you felt.
- If he's claiming...
- He said he didn't.
Then he's a total player.
(It's finally happening.)
Jun Han!
Then he's a total player.
What do you mean, a player?
If you're saying you didn't know
even after the Truth or Dare...
So I told him,
"How could you not know
when literally everyone else did?"
Didn't know what?
- I have no idea.
- What is it?
I don't know.
- They just went straight at him.
- Exactly!
I never got a real chance to approach you,
so I wanted to try at least once.
Jun Han really opened the floodgates.
I'll say it right in front of Jung Won.
Why do you keep dragging me into this?
I have no idea what's going on
between you two.
You guys were talking, so...
Why are you doing this to me?
You're free to go on dates with Jung Won,
but I'm just asking you
to give me a chance too.
Just a little bit of your time.
Okay.
I said this right in front of him
so you know I'm sincere.
I was being honest.
You really laid your cards on the table.
He really shook things up.
A battle between an open book
and a mystery man.
(What will happen to these four?)
What now?
"Check your date partner for today."
I think...
I wanted to be sure.
(Day-drinking date decided
by the older women)
You don't have any other guys
you want to talk to, right?
What about you? What do you want to do?
I think I'm going to focus entirely
on the girl I'm interested in.
Where are you coming from?
(Happy to see him)
I was so happy to see you.
I should just sleep out here tonight.
I'll stay with you.
(Blushing)
Have you made your choice?
I'm still figuring it out.
You need to reassure me.
I will.
I wanted you to be here...
and you actually were.
Was there something you wanted to ask me?
(Hesitating)
- It's hard to say.
- Is it?
It feels like you're in a rush...
to get married right now.
Really?
I'm not in a rush.
I just want to date someone...
with marriage in mind.
(Sighing)
It felt like he was
under a lot of pressure.
After talking with Ji Hye today,
I'm having second thoughts.
(Sigh)
I don't think there was anything
I could have done.
(Sigh)
Jin Young.
Do you want to talk?
You have terrible taste in men.
(Sighing)
Why do you even care about someone
who only makes you cry?
Why are you being so nice to me?
Just use me.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
Use me to take out your anger.
(How will the tangled love lines
at Yeon House play out?)