♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 11=
Here's today's paper.
It has a really important story.
The ban on Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui years ago
has been lifted.
- Great.
- Yes, exactly.
- Exactly.
- Wonderful.
- Huge news.
- This is good news.
What is it?
These model operas can't go on now.
I worried daily about our troupe.
I wondered what we could do.
I needed a nap, and a pillow showed up.
Now, I know exactly where to go.
Well said.
The movie Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui
was an amazing revolutionary film
with song and dance.
Back in those years,
every time I watched it,
I was moved.
Me too.
Too bad it got shut down.
Good thing it's back now.
Deputy Director Zhu and I decided
to rehearse Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui.
Great. Let's do it.
- I believe
- Great.
other County Troupes want it too.
So, we have to beat them to it
and stage this show first.
Our first show has to make a splash.
Are we confident?
Yes!
♪Gunfire rings out all around♪
♪The sky goes dark; the sun goes dim♪
Aren't you the lead? You do it.
- You do it.
- It's a rare chance.
Do you know that?
♪They harm, seize grain,
and burn villages♪
♪Trying to turn Honghu
into a slaughter ground♪
Too windy to watch. Let's leave.
Stop your nonsense.
This is a rare chance to learn.
Can't you handle this difficulty?
I can.
Come on, come on.
- Hang in there.
- Come here.
- Go.
Overcome this difficulty.
Hold that rope up.
Yes, pull it tight.
Pull it dead tight.
The moment that tests us has arrived.
- Get ready to move.
- Hang in there.
We must overcome this difficulty.
Don't leave. Sit down.
- Pull it tight.
- Peng Batian is leading
- Pull it flat.
- the Baiji Society,
killing along the way.
They've reached the cross ferry.
Great.
♪The foes swim right into the net♪
♪Wild winds can't bring down the sun♪
- What are you doing?
- Why come back?
- Go pull it.
- Hold it on.
- Go.
- Go pull it, Hu Sanyuan.
- Come here.
- What are you doing?
- Go, go!
- Go pull it.
♪Everyone joins the fight♪
♪We'll drive all the foes away♪
♪Drive them away♪
Why did you sneak back like this?
You didn't even tell me.
You came back alone?
Oh, you're carrying one.
It's pitch-black in here.
Why not turn on the light?
Don't move.
I was already on the table.
But I got down.
Either way, it's a life.
I'm keeping it.
Right.
That's right.
I'll be the kid's uncle.
There's something else
I need to get straight.
Before you left,
you had Laidi bring me a letter.
The child got soaked in the rain.
The letter got drenched;
the words blurred.
I've been thinking about it.
What exactly did that letter say?
Were there any instructions?
It doesn't matter anymore.
We're putting on this opera.
Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui.
The film is for us to study.
We're about to start rehearsals.
Mi Lan is playing Han Ying.
A great film.
Good lines and songs.
Such a pity. If only it were you.
At the meeting early this morning,
we were instructed repeatedly
to act with caution.
Do not make any rash moves.
Captain, Captain.
Secretary Han went to an early meeting.
Captain, Peng Batian is leading
the Baiji Society,
killing along the way.
They've reached the cross ferry.
♪Honghu waters, wave upon wave♪
♪The shores of Honghu are my home♪
♪Boats set out at dawn
to cast their nets♪
♪Returning in the evening
with holds full of fish♪
(Music score of Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui)
Let's do this line again.
♪Everyone says heaven is beautiful♪
♪But how can it compare
to Honghu's rich land?♪
Why did you stop? Keep going.
♪Thirty years on the east bank♪
♪Forty years on the west♪
♪Honghu is ours once again♪
What's wrong, Qiu?
Things change.
Peng Batian is back!
What's gotten into you?
He's lost it.
Look.
(Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui)
What's this?
A script.
Huang Zhengjing and Zhu just asked me
to play the lead villain.
I'm Peng Batian now.
The troupe doesn't have villains now?
I'm a villain.
- You don't look the part.
- Hu Sanyuan!
Come on, you answer to me now.
What are you doing?
Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui
is a major production.
I'm short on people.
I needed more people,
so Director Huang assigned you to me.
Why am I assigned to you?
Do you need drum cues for carrying
some ragged prop onstage?
What drum cues?
Come help me with props.
Say that first. Creative work, huh?
Let's go.
There are two more here. Take them too.
Dozens to feed, with barely three hands.
One's off to play the villain.
Why don't you take all of us,
so everyone can eat the air?
Master Song, yelling at me won't help.
Take it to Director Huang.
I'm a brick of the revolution.
I'm moved wherever I'm needed.
On the Great Wall, I won't brag;
in a latrine, I won't feel down.
Master Song,
there are scallions left.
Chop, chop, chop.
Hu Sanyuan,
you're a traitor too.
If you leave, who does the work?
All right, that's enough.
Opera comes first in the troupe.
Come on, cook.
Zip it and get back to work.
You chop the scallions.
For years, eight shows for everyone.
Forget whether the audience
is sick of it.
We're tired of acting it, right?
So, this time,
everyone in the troupe
is like monkeys let loose
for Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui.
No one can stop us.
Cut the warm-up.
Just tell him what you want to make.
Fine.
Nail.
Your chance to shine is here. Look.
What is it?
(Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui Prop List)
30 rifles.
5 Mauser pistols.
20 broadswords.
A provincial Qinqiang Opera show
wouldn't be any bigger than this.
It's a rare chance.
This time, we need to do it right
and stage a major opera.
Big ambitions.
Well.
With this much work, we can't keep up.
You have help.
Right.
Hu Sanyuan.
Here.
You're prepping this, okay?
I am?
Props are all on you now.
If so,
what are you doing?
I have sets and slides to draw
and prisons and a home
for Peng Batian to build.
I've got plenty on my plate.
It's a ton of work.
I can't handle it alone.
I can't do it.
If you can't, tell Director Huang.
You little brat,
using Huang Zhengjing to pressure me?
Director, look. Look!
Hu Sanyuan,
it was I who told Huang Zhengjing
to put you on props.
You're too outstanding
to work in the kitchen.
That's a great injustice.
I don't think so.
It's not an injustice.
The kitchen food is pretty good anyway.
Why should I come here to be treated
like donkeys?
Listen to me.
Besides you,
no one in the troupe can handle this.
Don't flatter me. It's no use.
Anyway, this is settled.
I'm just here to inform you.
Look how great you think you are.
Just putting on a play.
Why don't you get a cannon
and blow up Peng Batian's house?
Mi Lan,
you sang the "Honghu waters" section
so beautifully.
This part
was transplanted from the opera,
and the adaptation is very successful.
The melody is lovely;
it rolls off the tongue.
Anyone would sing it well.
That's not true.
Once you perform this play,
it's sure to be a success.
Exactly, exactly.
Once you perform it,
this play is sure to be a hit.
It's everyone pulling together.
If the play succeeds,
the credit will be everyone's.
We're all supporting roles.
You, however, are the lead.
Ms. Hua, you're washing up too.
The audience mainly comes
to see the star.
You're washing up too.
You go ahead.
I'm done. I'm heading back first.
All right.
Too cold.
I'm heading back too. Too cold.
I watched you rehearse today.
It was quite good.
Thank you.
The "Honghu waters" section
is very soft and graceful.
You could sing it with more boldness.
I think
that Han Ying is a hero,
but she's also a woman.
The whole play is full of boldness,
but
this is the tender, emotional section.
Shouldn't it show her feminine side?
That's different.
She is no ordinary woman.
She is the soul of the team.
The moment she opens her voice,
you have to feel
she's the pillar of the troupe.
Ms. Hua,
we are not the same person.
Shouldn't we sing different Han Yings?
Yes.
I spoke out of turn.
Caixiang,
thank you.
It's nothing.
Hu Sanyuan,
where on earth are you taking me?
Just take your ride.
Today, the seven-character quatrain
we are learning
is Cun Ju.
The first two lines describe the scene;
the last two describe the people.
Among them, what technique is used
with "brush" and "drunk"?
Personification.
This is Nail; you've met him.
This is the Qiaolian I told you about.
Hello, Qiaolian.
Hello.
Qiaolian, two things today.
First,
to introduce you two.
Second,
I need to ask you a favor.
Start with the second.
The troupe is staging a play.
We need some red-tasseled spears.
Could we borrow your students'
red-tasseled spears?
If you do the troupe a favor,
let's call it mutual help.
Right?
How many do you need?
Forty.
That many?
Well, I'll go report it
to the school leadership.
For our County Troupe,
it should be no problem.
All right, make it quick.
Your leg has healed, hasn't it?
Nail cares about you a lot.
It's healed, no problem.
Don't you limp?
Who said I limp?
How could I possibly limp?
What nonsense are you talking about?
See? Now you're relieved.
What's there for me
to be relieved about?
You two have now officially met.
Chat a while on your own.
I'm off to browse the street.
Hello.
Sit, sit.
Come on, don't stand on ceremony.
Then I'll sit.
Sit here.
Okay.
No pushing!
Forget it, let's go.
Sit down.
- Sure.
- How old are you?
Well... 28.
Push. Don't slack off.
On the way here,
you let me ride the cart.
On the way back,
you won't even let me sit.
On the way here, it was downhill,
so I let you be comfortable.
On the way back, it's uphill,
and you still want to laze around?
Why don't you say
that there were two bachelors
on the way here,
and there's only one bachelor
on the way back?
You've got what you want.
You've successfully dumped
the burden on me.
I'd like to take on a burden
like that too.
Who'll dump one on me?
I'm coming in.
I went to the countryside
and got you some eggs.
You jerk.
Barred Rock eggs.
Take them away.
I don't want them.
Don't fight against yourself.
If fate has decided it,
just accept it openly.
I shouldn't have come back.
Completely superfluous here.
Stop right there.
Take them away.
What are you doing?
Comrades should care for each other.
I've decided.
Decided what?
To transfer out.
I'll go to Zhang Guangrong's place.
No more opera singing?
No more.
I don't agree.
My drumsticks don't agree either.
What difference does it make
if you agree or not?
This is your old nest,
your headquarters,
and your base.
It was before.
Not anymore.
I'm just an outsider now.
That's only true
if you stop singing opera.
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
What's my situation to you?
Why are they arguing? What happened?
No idea.
Hu Sanyuan.
Come here.
Easy, easy.
What is this thing?
A homemade cannon.
I've thought it over.
Your idea was good.
You've got guts and bold ideas.
I've decided to take your suggestion.
At the very end of the play,
we'll use a homemade cannon
to bring down
Peng Batian's courtyard wall
and kill Peng Batian.
Are you serious?
Of course.
I was just talking nonsense.
Your nonsense was brilliant.
Listen, I've never found
a breakthrough for this play.
Now, I have.
Blowing up Peng Batian
is the perfect breakthrough.
The audience will find it satisfying.
Our play
will surely be a huge success.
So, it's settled.
Settled for what?
I don't know how to make this cannon.
Hu Sanyuan,
I've been a director for half my life.
I'm about to retire.
This might well be
the last play I direct.
I also want to put a perfect full stop
on my directing career.
Just do me this favor, all right?
I'll give you a bow.
I'm begging you.
Our goal is
to make achievements
in agriculture, industry,
national defense,
and science and technology
within this century.
Qin Feng.
What are you doing?
Why are you making a homemade gun?
Si was stabbed to death
by people from Xiguan.
When did this happen?
A couple of days ago.
What do you need?
I want to ask you
to help me make something.
Who are you planning to blast?
Let me see.
This is powerful.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
You're too old for this!
Impulsive when young is one thing.
Now, you have a family.
Aren't you stupid to do this?
Who do you think you are, lecturing me?
You were tough before;
now, you're just a fool.
Making homemade guns is illegal.
You'll go to prison.
You have a family.
If something happens to you,
what will they do?
Si is dead!
Even so, you can't commit a crime.
Try it again, and I'll report you.
♪Only hatred fills my chest♪
♪Let the enemy rage as they may♪
♪The setting sun won't last long♪
♪Through a mountain of swords
and a sea of fire♪
Stop, stop.
Hold it.
What's going on, Mi Lan?
Why couldn't you hit the note again?
We've been rehearsing all day.
Why do you fail to do it every time?
At this point in the play,
your emotion
should be getting more intense.
Why is there no passion at all?
Director,
this part should come in
on the beat now.
The rhythm should kick in.
If the drums lack power,
how can I have passion?
Even if I shred my voice, it's useless.
How is this our fault suddenly?
How are we not giving it power?
The drum is nearly smashed.
What more can we do?
Mr. He,
one beat, one clap.
You're not giving it power.
At this point,
if the rhythm can't keep up,
my singing won't change a thing.
What's wrong with you?
The tempo wasn't slow at all.
Unbelievable.
You were just off-tune and off-beat,
you know?
What do you mean?
When Hu Sanyuan plays,
he watches the actress's rhythm.
You just bury your head in it.
Your drumsticks even fell to the floor.
How can you blame me?
Why don't you let him play it?
Let's see who has the problem.
Your eyes are so sharp
that you can see my drumsticks fall.
Hu Sanyuan?
Why don't you ask Hua Caixiang to sing?
Stop arguing.
Hu Sanyuan, Hu Sanyuan.
Come here.
Here, over here.
What?
Play this section.
I can't do it.
Why not?
I only have two hands.
I'm not saying
I don't watch the actress.
What's so great
about watching actresses?
We're the drummers.
Why should we watch the actresses?
- Mr. He.
- What?
Shouldn't the drumming follow
the actress's rhythm?
And there you are,
blindly drumming away.
- What can I do?
- We keep the rhythm.
We're not here to watch the show.
Can this play still go on?
If not, let's just break up.
Don't ruin such a good play.
The orchestra and the vocals
have always been intertwined,
helping each other.
Yet you two keep blaming each other.
It'd be a miracle
if the play didn't fall apart.
Come on, let's play.
Put some power into it.
You drew this?
I drew all of these. Look.
This.
This one, and this one.
I drew all of them.
How is it?
- Good.
- Have some.
Have some peanuts. And this too.
I designed all these blueprints.
How about that?
Listen, not just these blueprints.
Look over there, the backdrops.
Look.
These.
These scenery flats at the back.
I painted all of them.
And I used this.
Can I touch it?
Sure, go right ahead.
This is where I usually live.
Usually, no one helps tidy up here.
It's a bit messy.
Let me show you this. Come.
This is the prison wall.
You know?
I painted all of it back there.
Qiaolian.
How was it today?
Was the troupe interesting?
I'd only watched performances before
and never seen rehearsals.
It was interesting.
Listen to you.
How could we
casually let outsiders
watch the rehearsals?
Today, you enjoyed family treatment.
You know?
I told you about letting you
watch performances for free for life.
How about that?
I kept my word, didn't I?
Is your cannon ready yet?
Almost.
Will it go off?
If not, can it be called a cannon?
I'm telling you.
Safety first.
Don't you dare act crazy with me.
Then what do you want me to do?
How's that?
Great.
You're fine, huh?
Hu Sanyuan,
your cannon is short and thick.
Can this stubby little thing work?
Lie yourself down.
See if you're as long as the barrel.
What's with this idle chatter?
Set one off for us to see.
People up front, move aside.
Nail.
Get up on the platform.
You're testing it on me?
- Hurry up.
- You...
Is it safe?
Hu Sanyuan,
don't mess around.
Can you do it or not?
There must not be any problems.
Rest assured, everyone.
This chicken has taken three blasts.
It didn't lose a single feather.
Come on.
Everyone, stand back.
Move aside.
Come on, stand behind me.
Nail.
Light it.
- Are you sure?
- Light it.
(Best wishes)
Slow down.
(to the premiere)
To the right.
Yes, yes.
(Revolutionary drama)
Take a look.
(Hong Hu Chi Wei Dui)
Good.
What are you pouting for?
Hurry up and peel.
Tonight is the official performance.
We have to rehearse soon.
You two
are just playing two lotus leaves,
standing there motionless. Why rehearse?
No need to go.
We have to sway,
like being blown by the wind.
Even if you two sway into lotus fairies
and lotus leaf sprites,
you have to finish this first.
You have to rehearse.
Why did you run off here?
They're peeling firecrackers.
Get back.
Mi Lan,
your "Honghu waters" section
is very soft and graceful,
but if you added more heroic spirit,
it'd be even more perfect.
She asked you to tell me that?
Who?
Hua Caixiang.
What's it got to do with her?
I think so myself.
What else do you think I need
to pay attention to?
Be more confident.
Tonight,
it will surely be a huge success.
Thank you.
I haven't been paid yet.
Next time, next time.
They're here, Director.
- They're here.
- Greet them.
Let's go.
- Make way.
- Clear the way.
- Get in line.
(Best wishes)
Line up.
Welcome, welcome.
- Good.
- Come.
Maintain order.
Hi, sir.
Come, come.
(Best wishes to the premiere)
Good, everyone, be alert.
Good.
- You're here.
- Are you ready?
Yes.
The leaders have all arrived.
There must not be any trouble.
Don't worry, no problem.
Secretary,
from your busy schedule,
thank you for coming to inspect.
It's only right.
It's time.
Begin.
(Best wishes to the premiere)
Hu Sanyuan,
how's it going?
Everything is ready,
waiting for the cue.
Let me tell you.
The CRC leaders are all here.
We must not drop the ball.
Especially that final cannon blast.
That's the most crucial part.
This is no simple cannon blast;
it's a continuation
of the October Revolution cannon fire.
We must make it earth-shaking.
Earth-shaking, understand?
Relax, relax.
I'm counting on you.
I'll head over first.
♪Honghu waters, long and long♪
♪The people's hearts turn
toward the Party♪
♪He Long led the revolution♪
♪Red flags flutter, winning the battles♪
♪Men held red-tasseled spears♪
♪Women took up blades
to defend their homes♪
♪Red Guard members
stepped forward bravely♪
♪With shared hatred,
they headed to the battlefield♪
Move out.
Sure.
Comrades, wait a moment.
Deputy Director Zhu.
Deputy Director Zhu,
chaos outside the door.
Our star performer.
Not bad.
(Qi Xi Bai Hu Tuan)
(Sha Jia Bang)
(Hong Deng Ji)
If the Baiji Society
dares to set foot in Honghu...
Leaders, leaders.
- Director.
- They'll be smashed
- to pieces.
- Director.
- Move out.
The singing is not bad.
Don't come any closer.
Whoever breaks my gate down today
will pay for it.
No one can get in.
You two, block them.
What's all the shouting about?
The leaders are watching the play.
Director.
What's going on?
Too many people without tickets,
clamoring to push their way in.
Even the police
probably couldn't stop them.
I'm telling you.
The ones who came tonight
are all top county leaders.
We can't lose control.
Even the police can't do anything.
What can I possibly do?
Idiot.
Let us in.
Here's the thing.
Go hook up the loudspeaker outside.
They can listen outside.
Won't that cause even more chaos?
Just go do it.
All right.
It's full.
Come back tomorrow.
Come on.
Line up on both sides.
♪Honghu waters, long and long♪
♪The people's hearts turn
toward the Party♪
♪He Long led the revolution♪
♪Red flags flutter, winning the battles♪
(Best wishes to the premiere)
♪Women took up blades
to defend their homes♪
♪Red Guard members
stepped forward bravely♪
♪With shared hatred,
they headed to the battlefield♪
They've calmed down.
When you do things,
you've got to pay attention to methods.
There are always more solutions
than difficulties.
We've got to use our brains.
Right.
As expected,
you do have work experience.
We haven't seen a scene like this
in many years.
Zhu,
I have a hunch.
Tonight, our cannon blast
is probably going to make a big noise.
Right.
An instant hit.
Look at Chu Jiahe's hand.
It's shaking.
Could she be scared?
Your local tunes sound lovely.
- With so many people here,
- Call them up.
I'm even scared for her.
To add a bit of elegance for our leader.
Sure.
Sir, what would you like to hear?
Just sing anything.
- Don't be nervous.
- Just sing anything.
- Singers.
Come in.
Go.
Singers, sing well.
If you sing well,
our leader will give you a reward.
(Build socialism with greater, faster,
better, and more economical results)
Little girl,
a little tune is easy to sing,
but hard to start.
A little country girl,
who hasn't seen the world,
seeing such a high-ranking official
as you,
is too scared to sing.
Very good, very good.
Little girl,
sing boldly.
Pick up the saucer in your hands
and start playing.
I'm all sweaty from anxiety.
Experience solves it.
(Best wishes to the premiere)
♪Gentlemen and officers,
listen with pleasure♪
♪The shores of Honghu are my home♪
♪Boats set out at dawn
to cast their nets♪
♪Returning in the evening
with holds full of fish♪
That's more than during the rehearsal.
This cannon blast
is a continuation
of the October Revolution's cannon fire.
The director said
it must be earth-shaking.
Keep it under control.
Not only is it under control,
but there's a ball of fire in my heart.
It's about to suffocate me.
Try to open up a bit.
In the world of opera,
singers always take turns,
taking a foreign land for one's home.
No one can stand on stage
for a lifetime.
I'm going to a foreign land tomorrow.
You'll go have the baby?
I'll go take
a foreign land for my home.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
Aim at the enemy! Fire!
Go to the hospital now! An emergency!
Hu Sanyuan's current condition
is very bad.
He needs emergency treatment.
Is Ding Zhisheng's family here?
He's gone.
Hu Sanyuan did it on purpose.
He's making it worse.
He wants Hu Sanyuan dead.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪