♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 35=
I'd like to toast Comrade Yi Qin'e.
To be honest,
my life before meeting Yi Qin'e
was completely aimless.
I didn't know
what the meaning of life was.
In the blink of an eye,
all these years just slipped away.
But
things are different now.
Ever since I met Comrade Yi Qin'e,
my life has become so fulfilling.
Now, even eating a bowl of liangpi
makes me feel happy.
It tastes amazing.
I wake up full of energy in the morning.
Qin'e,
you have
completely changed me.
You made me realize
what true happiness is.
I'm so moved.
That was well said.
Great!
Well said, bro!
Getting sentimental here.
I don't really know what to say.
But
I hope to do better in the future.
I raise this glass
to toast Comrade Qin'e.
Hongbing!
Bro, are you proposing?
If you're proposing,
it's only romantic on one knee!
Get down on one knee!
Don't talk nonsense.
On one knee! On one knee!
Come on, get down!
On one knee!
On one knee! On one knee!
Fine, I'll kneel.
Qin'e! Qin'e!
Qin'e!
(Restroom)
Qin'e! Qin'e!
Do you need to throw up?
What's going on?
It's empty in here.
(Diaojia Village)
Wang's roast chicken, spiced beef.
Let's eat and drink our fill today.
Sanyuan, what's this?
Are you trying to bribe me with food?
Why would I need to trick you?
Haven't you always wanted to hear
my thoughts on the new play?
None of that matters.
Aren't you heading back?
I just wanted to treat you today
to a nice meal and some drinks.
Say whatever you want.
Alright, sure.
Excuse me, sir.
How do I get to Tian'anmen?
Miss.
You're from Chang'an Opera Troupe,
right?
You sound like you're
from Northwest China.
Tian'anmen? That's quite far.
Is it on the golden mountain?
What?
They say
it's on Beijing's golden mountain.
There's no golden mountain in Beijing.
We only have Fragrant Hills.
If you're heading to Tian'anmen,
go this way.
Turn right outside the hostel
for the bus.
Take Bus Line 1 for seven stops.
Get off at Tian'anmen East.
Thank you, sir.
Wei Changsheng
brought Qinqiang opera to Beijing.
The best part is
that he competed
with Kunqu opera in Beijing.
It's known as the Huabu
and Yabu rivalry.
Finally, Wei Changsheng staged Gun Lou.
Crowds flocked to Qinqiang troupes.
The Six Great Troupes
of the capital faded.
So, people started asking
how he did it.
Because Qinqiang opera is down-to-earth.
It has no deep historical allusions
or overly poetic lyrics.
It's all about everyday life
and local slang.
It comes from the people
and goes to the people.
That's true vitality.
Well said.
Come on.
(Before going on stage tonight,)
(Yi Qin'e's hands are shaking.)
(But once the drums start,)
(she is no longer afraid.)
(The applause below no longer matters.)
(What matters is she's singing.)
(Chang'an Avenue is so wide;)
(the streetlights are so bright.)
(Finally, she brought opera to Beijing.)
(Long Live
the People's Republic of China)
Changing it isn't wrong.
It's true that Qinqiang opera
has always been sung
for the common people,
but
times have changed.
Qinqiang opera must change too.
But how do you change it?
You can't
just change the superficial aspects.
You're right.
It has to change.
Also, I need
a favor from you.
Go ahead.
Can you write a new play for Qin'e?
They just brought back the old plays.
Who'd watch a new one?
Well, the old plays we have now
were once new plays too, right?
If you don't write new plays now,
what will they sing as old plays later?
Sanyuan,
you're absolutely right.
Old plays were once new.
Alright.
Then I'll write it.
I'll write an exclusive play
for Qin'e,
so whenever its name is mentioned,
they'll know it's her play.
Oh, Sanyuan.
Sooner or later, this world will become
something neither of us
can keep up with.
But I'll say it again:
No matter
how you change,
as long as people of Qin live,
Qinqiang opera won't die.
With the Qinling Mountains here,
Qinqiang opera will survive.
(Many big things happened that year.)
(The wanted Wei Zhenhai)
(was finally caught in Chang'an.)
(The citywide uproar finally ended.)
(Good News)
(The people of Qin shined in Beijing.)
(Listen to Qinqiang Opera)
(The Qinqiang opera was popular.)
(Qinchuan Qinqiang Opera Theater)
(Congrats to Yi Qin'e on Her Transfer
into the Province)
(And Winning National First Prize)
(The train rumbled south.)
(Time is money)
(Shenzhen built fast.)
(Early 90s)
(Everyone went into business.)
(It seemed like everywhere)
(was full of money and chances.)
(Congrats on the Art Theater's Division)
(The provincial troupe had a reform.)
(The province wanted stars to lead.)
(Yi Qin'e couldn't decline it)
(and became the Youth Troupe Leader.)
(The troupe's new housing was built.)
(Everyone's living environment)
(Housing Handover)
(changed from the tube-shaped)
(apartment buildings to flats.)
(Xishi Tofu Shop)
(Those who got houses were overjoyed.)
(Qin Bawa focused
on writing a new play,)
(wondering if it could beat
the rock noise.)
(Times have changed;)
(people have changed too.)
(But as long as the curtain rises,)
(with the lights up,)
(the show must go on.)
(The End)
♪In the crowd, there are you and me♪
♪Meeting, knowing,
figuring each other out♪
♪In the crowd, it is you and me♪
♪Pretending to be decent with a smile♪
♪No need to say too much♪
How is it?
What?
Awesome, right?
Boom-cha-cha is out of style now.
This is the hottest trend.
Do you know what this is?
Rock and roll.
If you ask me,
this was just copied
from the Qinqiang opera's
painted-face role.
♪Just as charming, just as beautiful♪
Are you deaf from all this noise?
If you can't stand it, let's go.
Let's listen; it's good.
Really?
Listen, then.
♪You know♪
♪What we really want to do♪
♪Don't care too much♪
♪And don't be sad♪
♪One day you'll leave me♪
Why are you looking at this?
Look at this.
505.
Give me one.
Exact same recipe as 505.
What is this?
It's only a fifth of the price.
Come on, give me one.
A great deal for yourself or as a gift.
Here, take a look.
This looks pretty legit.
I'll take one.
I was wondering what to get my nephew.
He's starting middle school.
This will be perfect.
Just get a few more.
Your future kids can use them too.
Will it still be useful
when they grow up?
Seriously.
What? Come on.
- 30% off for you.
- Enough!
30% off, 30% off!
Take it, take it.
Come on, have one more.
Wang Qinsheng, what are you doing?
Is this rehearsal room a flea market?
Director Feng.
Director Feng,
my buddy has this Kombucha.
It's perfect for people like you.
What kind of person am I?
You know.
You've been stressed for years,
always wearing a frown.
Let me help you relax.
You're exactly right.
- Director Feng.
- You make me frown.
Director Feng.
This is...
- Mr. Qin.
- Hello.
I'm Feng Zi, Director of the troupe.
Come on, everyone, stand up.
No need, Director Feng.
Please, don't stand.
Just make yourselves comfortable.
No need to stand up.
Let me introduce him to you all.
Today, we're very honored to have
the famous Qinqiang opera playwright,
- Mr. Qin Bawa.
- Great!
Let's welcome Mr. Qin Bawa
to share a few words with us.
He spent a whole year pouring his heart
into writing this new piece,
Hu Xian Jie,
which is also our upcoming play.
Is that okay?
Yes!
Hello, everyone.
Regarding Hu Xian Jie,
some might feel it's distant from us.
It tells the story of a fox,
but it's actually not distant at all.
- Let's sit and talk.
- Okay.
Because in Hu Xian Jie,
the main character,
a fox spirit from the deep mountains,
has been cultivating in the wilderness.
Her talent led her to enlightenment,
but knowing nothing of the human world,
she feels confused.
She's lost between friendship and love,
just like
Prometheus or Sisyphus
in Greek mythology.
She is
a tragic figure full of idealism.
Her entire life
is about exploring, seeking,
and choosing.
I see the script has been given to you.
Next,
it's your creation.
Yes, exactly.
Everyone, let's explore together
the long journey of the fox.
Great, great.
Mr. Qin,
I've read the script.
May I share some thoughts?
In this script,
it says people are greedy and blind.
But I think
that it's the reform and opening-up era.
It advocates for some to get rich first.
So, I was wondering this:
Does the script try
to lamb paste the world too much?
Lambaste.
Baste what?
The word is lambaste.
It means to severely criticize.
Everyone, don't laugh at him.
Stop laughing, guys.
Don't mind them, sir.
What kind of question is that?
Your question...
No, no. Director Feng.
It's a great point.
Come up to the front. Come on.
Come here.
I like it.
I'd love to discuss things
with you all.
Sit.
Don't be shy.
You were right to ask.
You asked this question
from a different angle.
You're different, but that's normal.
I don't think it's a condemnation.
Let me ask you about Jia Baoyu.
Would you say he's affectionate
or heartless?
It depends on perspectives.
Exactly.
Most readers think Jia Baoyu
is affectionate.
He's romantic, right?
Right, right.
But from Xue Baochai's perspective,
he showed her no affection
at all, right?
Right, exactly.
So, your angle on this question
is great.
If you want to better understand
my script,
you need to read more.
Not just myths and legends,
but also ancient poetry.
Because when I wrote this play's lyrics,
I referenced the poems
of great Tang Dynasty poets,
such as Li Bai, Cui Hu, and Li Shangyin.
Stop.
Stop dancing.
Rehearsing this is worse
than trading stocks.
At least stocks have ups and downs.
Look at you guys.
One note from start to finish.
We're done for today.
You can't blame us.
There's not even a single drumbeat.
Just a tape recorder.
Is it my fault?
Guo Chuizi took time off.
The Youth Troupe took our lead drummer.
Troupe Leader Yi gave the word,
and they swept away all our best stuff.
They're working hard,
rehearsing, and making money.
And look at us,
just hanging around here half-dead.
Jiahe,
isn't Troupe Leader Yi your classmate?
She didn't even look out for us.
That's uncool. Go talk to her.
Enough, you guys.
Don't blame your tools for a bad job.
You lack skill, so you blame the drum?
Director Dang, not trading stocks today?
What's wrong? Did you lose money?
What do you know about stocks?
Let me tell you.
It's incredibly thrilling.
You know what?
I stayed at that market
all day yesterday.
It was so incredibly crowded.
You'd think there was a festival.
How about I take you there
in a few days?
Acting is just like that.
With the exact same role,
your act and his would just...
Director Feng, are we about done?
Can we call it a day?
Sure, sure. You can go.
We're done for today.
Feel free to leave if you need to.
Alright, I'm taking off.
Thank you. Thanks.
Mr. Qin, I'm a huge fan.
Mr. Qin, this is Xue Guisheng,
a Xiaosheng transferred
from Tianshui, Gansu.
A student of Su Yumin.
Yes, exactly.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, Mr. Qin.
Mr. Qin,
could I get your autograph?
Why?
I'm not a big star.
Come on, you're a great artist.
Yeah, write a message for the youth.
It'd be very meaningful.
Is that okay?
Alright then.
You're a Xiaosheng?
Xiaosheng, yes.
I'm so lucky today.
Indeed.
(Hu Xian Jie)
Nice handwriting.
(Waste no time)
You distract me.
- That's true.
- Done.
Very good, very good.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Elegant scholar,
do not decay.
Waste no time.
Where did all your studying go?
It's an uncommon word.
Read more, read more ancient poems.
Okay, okay.
Mr. Qin.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Thanks, thank you.
Troupe Leader.
Thank you for your support.
I've been meaning
to treat you to a meal.
The last time you came,
we went to Beijing for a show.
- Yes.
- Right.
Sir, I wasn't asking you to host me.
I really did it for the play.
Now, you've paid me the writing fee.
I've said my piece on the play.
My job is done.
- Thanks.
- Okay, bye.
No, no.
You should stay for a few more days.
Aren't we partnered
with Tangcheng Hotel?
- Yes.
- Let Mr. Qin stay there.
- Okay.
- No, no, no need.
I'm used to being free.
I've already picked a place.
Goodbye.
- Let it go.
- Please, let it be.
I'll walk him out.
- Okay.
- Goodbye, Mr. Qin.
Thank you, Mr. Qin.
Yeah.
We've paid him?
Yes.
He's explained the play?
He explained it perfectly.
That's good.
Troupe Leader, look what Mr. Qin wrote.
Elegant scholar,
waste no time.
Right.
Why didn't Mr. Qin give me an autograph?
I'll sign one for you.
Why would I want yours?
Mr. Qin! Mr. Qin!
Always peeing!
The whole yard reeks of pee!
Do you know where we are?
This is the provincial capital.
Day in and day out!
Have you got a prostate problem?
Always peeing!
You want to pee?
Do you know how hard I work all day?
Pee, pee, pee!
Why not pee on your mom's Kang?
Let me tell you!
Mr. Qin, why do you live here?
It's great here.
It's full of life.
To truly understand Chang'an locals...
This way.
You have to come here
to look
and listen.
You must live here.
Did you see that woman?
She isn't
from Chang'an.
She must've married in from out of town
just a few years ago.
How do you know?
A true Chang'an native
wouldn't emphasize it.
"I'm from the city."
"I'm from Chang'an."
"I'm from Qinchuan."
That just loses confidence.
Did you hear what she said
in a panic?
Those words like Kang?
That's not local in Chang'an.
Language...
A person's experiences
are all hidden in their words.
That right there is folk language.
Grounded and solid.
Full of charm and so powerful.
I've never been
up to the City Wall.
Let's go.
Let's go take a look.
It's so wide up here.
You could even drive a car on it.
You've never been here before?
No.
Ever since I came,
I've just been focused on performing.
Mr. Qin,
your new script is truly amazing.
I feel like it was written for me.
It has so many things I want to say.
It's just...
How should I put it?
I...
I don't know how to explain it.
I'll definitely perform this play well.
Take it easy.
By the way,
I haven't congratulated you yet.
In the years since you came to Chang'an,
you've achieved so much.
You've become a star
and the deputy troupe leader.
You've really made it.
I don't really care about all that.
Besides, I don't know anything else.
I just focus on performing well.
Fame and fortune are funny like that.
When you ignore them,
they come looking for you instead.
But you need to be careful.
Don't let fame drag you down.
Your hardships and obstacles won't be
singing, reciting, acting,
or acrobatic fighting.
You need to be mentally prepared.
Prepared for what?
Well...
That varies from person to person.
I really can't tell you.
You have to figure it out
and experience it
on your own.
If you figure it out,
you'll make it.
Here are the receipts
from the past few days.
Take a look at this.
Here's the plan.
After finishing eating,
have your guys buy the paint.
Okay, sure, no problem.
Look over here.
Welcome home.
Come in and take a look.
See how I set up the new place.
I cleaned up everything
that I possibly could.
Here, let me take your bag.
Feel free to look around.
The lighting in here is great.
I went to Zhuque Gate this morning
and happened to pass the flower market,
so I brought this pot of flowers back.
Don't they look fresh?
They smell amazing.
Come on.
Here, put your slippers on.
I'll put your shoes right here.
You must be exhausted from work.
How was work today? Did it go well?
Have some warm water.
A banana full of love.
Qin Town's Mipi and Laozao.
Come on, take a bite.
Your favorite soup dumplings.
I got them at Huimin Street
this morning.
Come on, have a taste.
Li Huiniang's eyes are so expressive.
I'll hang it up.
Liang,
you're amazing.
This is
Toshiba.
How much was it, bro?
It's nothing.
Over two thousand.
It's this unit, 201.
- Got it!
- Handle it with care!
Especially the speakers,
over 7,000 yuan.
What speakers cost over 7,000 yuan?
They're imported.
Lili.
This sofa feels amazing.
How much is it? Let me get one too.
You can't afford it; it's custom.
- Give me a hand!
- Sir!
Can this sofa fit through the hall?
I have a piano too.
A custom-made Yamaha.
Slow down, slow down!
So, this piano is
just like our Biangbiang noodles.
It has to be freshly made.
Shut up.
You know nothing about art. So tacky.
Take it easy.
Fine, I'm a bumpkin.
How about this?
Bring me along with you.
The clothing business
seems very lucrative.
Why do I even bother doing flips, right?
You're destined to do flips.
- Slow down.
- Let's go, sir.
I'll get the door for you.
- Liang.
- What?
The clothing business is so lucrative?
Lili is just that capable.
Sometimes, I even feel
like I'm a kept man.
Bro,
are you sure she's selling clothes?
At Luoma Market, running a stall.
You little brat,
I'll tear your mouth off!
Don't you know what she sells?
Alright, bro.
This jerk.
You think you're amazing?
You just sell clothes.
A self-employed entrepreneur.
Why act all high and mighty?
So full of yourself.
Right, Qin'e?
(Over the past year,)
(nothing has changed
between Yi Qin'e and Liu Hongbing.)
(No progress.)
- (Liu Hongbing hasn't backed off.)
- What's wrong?
- (He's still devoted,)
- You were fine.
(running errands,)
- (and buying things.)
- Qin'e.
- (Yi Qin'e has)
- What's wrong?
- Do you have other business?
- (mixed feelings.)
My business
is looking after you.
Then just leave.
What's the fuss about?
Aren't I helping you right now?
I told you we're not right
for each other.
I didn't say we were a match either.
Stop pestering me here, alright?
Don't you still need my help?
You just moved here.
If I weren't here helping you decorate,
you'd work yourself to the bone.
Don't worry.
I'll leave once I'm done here.
Here, wipe this.
You're helping me?
You...
What are you doing?
- Qin'e.
- Give it here.
What?
The keys.
The custom rug and sofa
will be delivered
to the door in a few days.
Once I set them all up for you,
I'll leave.
Change the locks
if you don't believe me.
I need to go to Beishan in a few days.
It won't be long.
Don't miss me too much.
♪I am Bai Yunxian♪
♪Miss Bai♪
(Youth Troupe)
♪Mr. Xu, where do you live♪
♪My family has lived in Qiantang County
for generations♪
♪My name is Xu Xian♪
♪What do you do for a living♪
It tastes strong.
Comrade Yi Qin'e from your troupe
has all the acting talent in the world.
Thank you for caring about Qin'e.
The development of Qinqiang opera
really needs your strong support.
Yes, absolutely.
Why isn't Yi Qin'e here yet?
Yeah.
She'll be right here.
Let's drink with Chief Hu first.
Pour the drinks.
Come on, come on.
Okay, okay.
Xue Guisheng,
how long has it been since you showered?
Do you know you smell awful?
That's nonsense. It's not me.
What nonsense?
The wind is blowing from the east.
It blew all your stench over here.
Don't think I don't know.
They all said they've never seen you
shower in the troupe's bathhouse.
And you still deny it?
Impossible. Smell it.
What are you doing? It stinks!
It can't possibly be me.
I just showered last week.
Qin'e.
Why laugh? Seriously.
Look.
Jiahe is the lead now.
You're a big star too.
Let me play Qing next.
We're both from Ningzhou.
I'm no worse than Zhu Hanmei.
You've taken too much time off lately.
They already cast Zhu Hanmei.
There's nothing I can do.
Don't ask. I got scammed.
What happened?
Weren't you dating someone?
I saw your boyfriend.
When are you getting married?
He was a total scammer.
He said his dad could get me a job
in the Provincial Bureau of Culture,
but his dad is just
a Provincial Party Committee guard.
What a waste of my time.
Slow down! Slow down!
Qin'e, why are you still sitting here?
Go get up there.
The leaders are all waiting.
Troupe Leader, ask someone else.
Who else can I ask?
You're the deputy troupe leader now.
Hosting leaders is part of your job.
Then I quit.
You quit? Who will take over then?
I'll do it.
I can do it.
Let me do it.
What could you do?
Tell me what you want.
I need some time off.
You're just causing trouble.
You just think the troupe underpays you.
Right?
You're the troupe leader.
Tell me. Is my pay low or not?
It's not low at all.
The troupe's rule is based
on years of experience and ability.
I meet both, right?
I joined at 14.
First Wusheng role, then Chou role.
After Erhu, I learned Banhu.
From small gong to big gong,
I finally sat at the drum set.
I'm our troupe's drummer.
Fans call me the Northwest Drum King.
Maybe I didn't make great feats,
but I put in the hard work.
A young girl from another county
even got a raise.
Why is there none for me?
The provincial leaders appointed her
as the deputy troupe leader.
Who do you think you are?
I can't even argue with you on that.
I'll tell Troupe Leader Yi, then.
Troupe Leader Yi,
after tonight's performance,
I won't perform. I'm taking a leave.
What a troublemaker.
I'll deal with you later.
Qin'e, you should go up.
Zhou.
Come on, let's switch seats.
You must be tired.
You just started out.
You'll face many awful people
and things.
Take your time.
Dealing with plays is relatively easy.
You'll succeed if you work hard.
Dealing with people is too hard.
Look, look.
You figured it out in just two days.
Troupe Leader,
I really think
I'm not cut out for this deputy role.
Who said that?
Look at you now.
You're managing both troupes so well.
Yang Pai Feng
is already showing results.
The person you recommended is great too.
Chu Jiahe really has some solid skills.
Keep it down.
I don't want anyone
to know I referred her.
I haven't told a soul.
But Director Ding recommended her too.
Troupe Leaders, I need a word with you.
Wang Qinsheng
hasn't shown up for over a week.
Hu Xian Jie
can't depend on him.
See who can fill in for him
and run a scene with you.
The one reading the book, right?
We're on the same page.
I didn't say a word.
I didn't say a word either.
From now on, we'll give up
on the picky ones.
The show is everything, right?
Qin'e,
if there's any mess from now on,
I'll take the heat for you.
You just need to focus
and do your job well.
In the future,
we'll work together.
With me here,
just rest easy and sing.
What are you doing?
This is a clinic.
Don't make it look like a shady salon.
This is embarrassing.
No rush, I'm not done yet.
See how this feels.
Does it look good?
You really are a genius.
We need to change our mindset.
Do you know what's trendy now?
Wellness and health care.
We can't just rely
on people with leg issues coming to you.
We need to get healthy people
to walk in here too.
Illness is a very abstract concept.
Back in the tough times,
bleeding didn't mean illness.
Now that life is better,
even feeling a bit down
is considered an illness.
I get it now.
From now on, we treat the sick
and create an illness
to treat, right?
Then you should change the sign outside.
Add the words: Wellness Center.
That changes everything.
Then, you can treat anything, right?
You're quite a genius.
Why do all these geniuses
end up in our small clinic?
And you're so excited?
How dare you earn dirty money?
No.
Don't mess around.
That's not my idea.
We'd get bad karma.
Just do our job.
Dirty money?
Nonsense.
I was talking about wellness
and health care. What are you saying?
You must be tired.
You've lost weight again.
It's peak season for bookings right now.
The Hu Xian Jie rehearsals can't stop.
I perform out of town every few days
for three to five days at a time.
I have no time to rest.
How do you handle it?
I completely understand.
Promoting a star is like Xuan paper.
A drop of ink spreads everywhere.
Once the paper is laid out,
the ink can't stop flowing.
You can't eat or drink when performing.
You really need someone by your side.
Luckily, Hongbing is always around.
He has nothing to do with me.
How can you say that?
Not just the provincial troupe.
Even in Diaojia Village,
everyone knows you two are together.
What are you thinking?
I'm asking you.
Can my hair be washed now?
Just a minute.
I'll do yours after this one.
Okay.
Here, let me see.
Come here.
You look great. So beautiful.
So do you.
You haven't changed a bit.
I'm old. Look at these wrinkles.
If I didn't dye my hair,
who knows how much gray hair I'd have?
You still haven't answered me.
What's really on your mind?
What about you and my uncle?
Me and your uncle?
You think we can explain ourselves?
Exactly.
There's a lot we can't figure out.
Let's just let it be.
You didn't become a leader for nothing.
You're mature and steady.
And you make perfect sense now.
Aunt Hua,
my current troupe needs a lead drummer.
I want my uncle to join us.
Do you think that's a good idea?
Absolutely.
If you asked him to do something else,
he might hesitate.
But if you ask him to play drums,
he'll jump at the chance.
Just tell him later.
I can't go.
Why?
You just became
the branch troupe leader,
and you're already
bringing your uncle in?
It just gives the gossip ammunition.
You played for You Xi Hu last time.
No one said a word.
That was different.
The troupe asked me to help out.
It wasn't for you personally.
Why is your eye makeup so red?
It looks like someone punched you.
And your hair...
Why is it like a hard shell?
What's this look?
You silly old man.
This is called fashion. Got it?
Stop saying what!
You lack drive; don't hold the kid back.
Leave. You're not welcome here.
I haven't had liangpi.
I didn't make any for you.
Leave.
Get out of here.
Go.
Think about what I said.
What's there to think about?
I understand him.
Just give him some time.
Like uncle, like nephew.
You always keep things to yourselves.
You've got a mind of your own.
Hello.
What book do you want?
Any poems by Li Bai, Cui Hu,
and Li Shangyin?
Someone just asked the exact same thing.
Let me check.
Okay.
We're sold out.
The last book on Tang Poetry
was bought by that person.
When will it be back in stock?
Not until next month.
Check back later.
Okay.
Check out something else.
(Xinhua Bookstore)
Xue Guisheng.
Troupe Leader Yi.
Are you waiting for the bus too?
I'm reading here.
What book has you so hooked?
(Detailed Analysis of 300 Tang Poems)
Look.
Oh, you bought it.
It's nothing.
Well.
Didn't Mr. Qin say so?
He said Hu Xian Jie has lyrics
that are inspired
by poems by poets like Li Bai,
Li Shangyin, and Cui Hu.
So, I bought a copy to read
to help me understand the lyrics better.
Then why are you reading it here?
This book is 1.5 yuan.
I just asked the cashier.
I can return it while she's on shift.
Her shift ends at 3:00 PM.
So, I decided
to finish reading it quickly
and then return it.
Don't return it.
Sell it to me when you're done.
That doesn't seem right.
Why wouldn't it be?
If you return it,
I'll just have to buy it.
Just sell it to me and save the trouble.
Right?
Take your time reading it.
Excuse me.
Do you have the time?
11:30.
11:30? Thanks.
I can make it.
By 3:00 PM,
I'll give you this book.
Okay.
=The Lead=
(Preview)
After these performances,
I want to take a break.
But we've committed
to the rest of the shows.
How is the troupe
supposed to handle this?
You even yelled at me
over that opera wench.
Don't you dare call her an opera wench!
This is thrilling.
It's the nine-tailed fox
from Zhongnan Mountain.
Nonsense!
Why tear up my book?
Did you cross someone?
Qin'e, don't go there.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪