♪Only after bloom comes fruit♪
♪Who says glory must fade to the past♪
♪Only through thunder
do you reach the clouds♪
♪Who made you the crown of every peak♪
♪I stand at the center of the stage♪
♪My shadow is pinned against the wall♪
♪Facing the light earns every medal♪
♪Little birds,
save your needless pecking♪
♪The open sky rises high♪
♪When night falls,
the moon begins to shine♪
♪I stand in the heart of these lands♪
♪My shadow bears no crown or robe♪
♪Then I know truth needs no disguise♪
♪The green hills see me as I am♪
♪Like dew, lightning,
and moon on the river♪
♪Showing me exactly who I am♪
=The Lead=
=Episode 37=
So, this is where you herded sheep.
Yes.
It's beautiful here.
Just like you.
Your name is beautiful too.
I only found out lately
that your name comes from an old poem
by Li Bai of the Tang Dynasty.
You know,
when I was a kid,
I was awful at memorizing texts,
especially poems and stuff.
But I loved this poem
after one read.
Really.
When I read it,
I felt something I can't explain.
Yi Qin'e.
The flute sobs.
Qin'e wakes up, only to see the moon
over Qin Tower.
The moon over Qin Tower
and the green willows year after year
bear witness to the parting
on Baling Bridge.
On Leyou Plain, crisp autumn falls.
On the ancient road to Xianyang,
there's no more word for her.
No more word for her.
The west wind and fading light
bring out the Han ruins.
Look, there it is.
It came out there.
No more word for her.
The west wind and fading light
bring out the Han ruins.
So beautiful.
You're awake.
Why not sleep a bit longer?
I'm up. We said we'd head back today.
Where's Liu Hongbing?
Your boyfriend
drove Cungen out early this morning.
Laidi,
Mom told me everything last night.
Come on.
After all this fuss,
don't get upset.
And don't think I don't care.
Honestly,
I'd want to trade places with you.
If I were in your shoes now,
they could say anything they want.
If you were here in these hills,
you'd have it even harder
than now after just a few days.
I just want to sing opera.
Don't I want a good life? Can I?
Look around these villages.
Everyone fights to make some money.
Everyone struggles
to raise a child.
Everyone has their struggles.
At least you're doing what you love.
Be grateful.
Go back and do what you need to do.
Uncle, Aunt.
We're back.
We bought you a few things.
Why buy anything?
You shouldn't have.
We came
in such a hurry.
It wasn't proper. Look.
Share these things
with the relatives.
What kind of liquor do you like?
We don't know about types.
We're not picky about that.
Look at you, being so fancy.
You knew we had a trip ahead,
yet you're still wasting time.
I just filled the tank in town.
Once we head for Chang'an,
we won't need to stop.
Good prep saves time later.
- Right.
- Wufu, hurry up.
I'm not done yet.
Hongbing, we got Laidi
some herbal medicine.
We don't have much else here.
Take it back and brew it for her
to soothe her throat.
All right. Thanks, sis.
- Thanks, bro.
- Don't mention it.
Qin'e.
Pack up. We're leaving. Hurry.
Once you get back,
hurry up and get married.
You're not getting any younger.
Your dad and I want grandkids.
Hongbing's parents
must be eager too.
Aunt, don't worry.
I'll handle this.
Right, right.
Let's go, hurry up.
We need to be back before dark.
Look out for each other.
Goodbye.
Take it easy.
Bye-bye.
Hey, kid.
Listen to me.
Study hard, okay?
After graduation, find me in Chang'an.
Okay, okay.
That's good.
Good kid.
Hongbing,
where have you been?
A tiger's den?
So what?
My lifetime happiness is at stake.
I'd go anywhere if I had to.
Are you done with that woman
from the provincial troupe for good?
What's it to you?
Rumors are everywhere.
What rumors?
No surprise.
Those trashy magazines are everywhere.
What star hasn't had rumors?
It's just sour grapes.
Do you know who started the rumor?
How would I know?
If I knew, I'd make him pay.
Hongbing,
I have a buddy.
He's well-connected on Wenyi Road.
How about I introduce you?
Sure.
(Yi Qin'e's Romantic Past)
What are you doing?
I'm washing the car.
What? Can't you see?
Why spray here?
Move. What are you staring at?
Go on.
Move, move. Hurry up.
You're rotten to the core.
I'm telling you.
Don't you dare stare.
Caixiang, this garlic won't do.
I'll get you some good ones later.
I know a guy who deals in garlic.
I'll get you big solo garlic.
(Hua Ting Xiang Hui)
With that in liangpi,
it tastes amazing.
You're stuck here all day now?
I'm peeling garlic.
You like liangpi more than I do?
- ♪I truly fear♪
- Caixiang makes it so tasty.
- ♪What if the Wen family knows♪
- So dramatic.
- ♪I can't rest easy♪
- How's Laidi been?
- ♪I look around♪
- Fine. She's practicing.
She seems the same as before.
- ♪No one's around♪
- Maybe it's over.
- ♪I step up and kneel♪
- Some wounds hide.
♪I keep calling for you♪
(Qinchuan Province
Qinqiang Opera Theater)
Come on. Let's start.
Morning, Master Chen.
♪To the residence in Chang'an♪
♪I, the fox maid, must leave alone♪
♪I can hardly leave my loved ones♪
♪I can hardly leave
this fleeting warmth♪
♪I can't bear my family's harsh torment♪
♪I can't bear the immortals closing in♪
♪I can't bear the rules
that are as sharp as needles♪
♪Enough, I'll harden my heart♪
♪Leap off the cliff,
and sever love's root♪
Sorry.
I spaced out.
Let's do it again.
Wash or cut?
I'm looking for someone.
Laohei.
Just a small token.
Please accept it.
I'm Qin'e's boyfriend.
You?
You're Yi Qin'e's boyfriend?
Do you know she has an uncle?
Of course.
Hu Sanyuan, right?
And an aunt.
Hua Caixiang.
So, it's true.
It seems
you know her uncle well.
I'm not close to her uncle.
I know Caixiang well.
What is it? Tell me.
Help me find someone.
Who?
Wang Qinsheng, who used to be
in the provincial troupe.
The Xiaosheng?
The one who partnered with Yi Qin'e?
That's him.
Why look for him?
Hey.
What took you so long?
I've been swamped lately.
The troupe's staging a big show.
I'm the lead.
The troupe can't be
without me.
How many are in your family?
Four...
Who is it?
Who?
What are you doing?
Liu Hongbing.
(Xiaoli Massage)
What are you doing?
Why take photos?
Come here, give me the film.
I'll give it to you.
Come on.
Give it a try.
Hey, what do you want?
What do I want?
I want to send a copy
of this photo to your workplace
and Tangcheng Tales,
so you can experience
what it feels like to be famous.
Hongbing,
tell me.
How did I ever offend you?
You spread rumors about Qin'e.
What a wimp.
You messed with the wrong person.
I'm not that kind of person.
I wouldn't do that.
That'd be way too humiliating.
Keep pretending.
Go on, keep acting.
Come on.
- Act.
- I swear.
If I started that rumor,
I'd be an extra forever
and lose all my family.
Was it this guy?
Was it him?
- It must be him!
- Master Hu.
Uncle! Uncle!
It wasn't him.
It really wasn't. Probably not.
- I didn't do it.
- Uncle!
Don't be mad.
I have to sing opera, Uncle.
Uncle, really...
Really...
I'm sorry.
Maybe it wasn't that guy after all.
There were a lot of things
about Qin'e at County Troupe.
Wang Qinsheng couldn't know that.
Uncle, do you think
Chu Jiahe could've done this?
The more I think about it...
Stop thinking about it.
Don't stir things up
before you find proof.
If you keep digging,
you'll never get past it.
Let it go, starting now.
Don't bring it up again.
I saw you with Laohei earlier.
How much did you give him?
He wouldn't take it.
He did it for my sake.
At least he's got a conscience.
He said
that it was for Aunt Hua.
That clueless fool.
Uncle, don't be mad.
He can't compare to you.
Not even close.
Right. Enough about me.
How are things with Qin'e now?
Nothing new.
Same as before.
You're not getting any younger.
Qin'e's career is stable now.
Some things should be planned.
Uncle, do you approve?
What good is my approval?
All across Chang'an,
everyone knows you're Yi Qin'e's family.
But Qin'e hasn't said yes yet.
Then I can't help you.
What do women even think?
Didn't you say
there's no trick in love
but a true heart
that you have to show?
Exactly.
Uncle, if you ask me,
you and Aunt Hua
are messier than Qin'e and me.
Between you two,
there's a third person.
Get lost. You never say anything nice.
Qin'e, open up! Qin'e!
It's me.
Qin'e.
What?
Look here.
What are you holding?
A camcorder.
Come on, hurry.
I barely got this from a friend.
You've been down lately, right?
Let's put on a tape.
It might help you unwind.
Look.
This one is huge right now.
The Price of Madness.
I want to see
how wild it gets.
You sit over there.
I'll set it up for us.
Don't worry about it.
Sit, sit.
Why keep reading that script?
It's a crime drama.
Just relax a little.
Come on, watch.
I'll get it going.
Let's see how wild it really is.
Here we go.
It's started.
Look.
See? Trouble right off the bat.
A chase scene.
That's not right.
This isn't the beginning.
Let me fix it for us.
Hold on. I need to rewind.
I'll rewind it.
Starting off this wild?
Okay, play.
Wait. What is this?
What is this?
Why are you showing me this?
No, I didn't mean to show you this.
My guy gave it to me.
No, Qin'e.
I asked my guy to get it.
My guy picked it up.
It won't turn off.
Get your stuff out.
I'm going, I'm going.
No, this...
I borrowed this lousy thing from him.
What's he doing?
Trying to get me in trouble?
Your coat.
There's too much stuff.
There, there.
So much stuff.
See? No problem.
Look, look.
You're so cute when you smile.
You should smile more often.
Got it?
Don't keep life so tense.
If you ask me,
you play a female general onstage.
But offstage,
smile more.
You're really cute.
I think you're beautiful.
To me, you're the prettiest.
♪Pick up the saucer in your hands
and start playing♪
♪The tune is easy,
but the words are hard to say♪
♪Each line can't sing all life's pain♪
♪Gentlemen and officers,
listen with pleasure♪
What are you doing here?
- Sanyuan.
Something's wrong.
What?
Shunzi got hurt.
He's getting bandaged.
What happened?
Take a look.
Who did this? How did it get so bad?
What?
My mom did it.
Your mom did this?
This...
This is Shunzi's kid.
Shunzi's daughter.
What's your name? How old are you?
I'm Juhua. I'm six.
What happened?
His wife ran off with someone.
Leaving is one thing.
But look what they did to Shunzi.
He's badly hurt.
Call the police.
Shunzi won't let us.
He says she's still Juhua's mom.
Come on, come on.
Easy, easy.
- Bro.
- Here, hold him up.
Careful. Easy, easy.
Come on, quick.
Easy, easy.
- Hold him.
- Watch out.
Come on, sit.
Dr. Du.
You're getting good at bandaging.
Can he even eat now?
Why can't he?
I left his mouth clear.
Dad, how did you end up like this?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I'm just not capable enough.
I made my kid suffer.
What suffering? It's nothing.
We can't let a minor setback
make us deny our whole life, right?
Of course, this isn't exactly minor.
I'm just not good enough.
She wants a better life.
How can I stop her?
We stagehands
are lowlife.
Don't say that in front of the kid.
No one's better or worse.
It's up to you.
Dad.
Then,
I'm singing
at the Children's Palace tomorrow.
Can you still take me?
I can't go.
Tomorrow,
have Uncle Sparrow take you.
Shunzi,
tomorrow,
I've got a stage setup job.
I can't get away.
Right.
Well.
Don't worry.
Listen. I'll take the kid.
Just tell me where to go.
(Singing Match)
Here.
(Qinchuan Qualifier)
(Registration Desk)
Diao Juhua, right?
Yes. How much?
Eighty.
Why is this contest so pricey?
Children are tomorrow's sun.
They're the next generation.
It's not pricey to invest in the future.
Come on.
Fine, I'll invest.
Here, Juhua. Hold this.
- This is five.
- Forty-five.
And this is ten.
Put it on.
(Little Bud Cup Singing Match)
You look great.
Remember what I taught you?
Don't get nervous in there.
Sing it just like I taught you, okay?
What's your name? How old are you?
What song will you sing?
So, what's your name?
Juhua.
I mean your full name.
Diao Juhua.
What song will you sing today?
Do you have backing music?
Hey, kiddo.
I'm Juhua.
Juhua, let me explain.
For kids singing here,
there's a time limit.
If you don't speak or sing,
once time is up,
you'll lose your chance.
Not this one.
Miss, please take her off.
Let's have the next one.
Okay.
♪Once outside♪
(Little Bud Cup Singing Match)
♪My back feels behind♪
(Qinchuan Qualifier)
♪So I can keep my belly♪
♪Out front♪
♪All uncles are uncles♪
♪Tables and stools are all wood♪
♪One step forward and one step back
means nothing♪
♪Donkeys and oxen are beasts♪
Is Diao Juhua's guardian here?
Yes.
Sanyuan,
I knew it was you.
Long time no see.
Mi Lan.
You haven't changed a bit.
Neither have you.
You don't mean that.
I do.
Is Juhua your kid?
No, she isn't.
She's my buddy's kid.
My buddy is sick.
I brought the kid to the contest.
She's got an off-key voice.
That doesn't mean
she won't have a chance.
Look at Laidi.
This time, let's be honest.
Don't give her any special treatment.
Just say it like it is.
If she's not cut out, tell her straight.
Better make it sound firm,
so she'll drop the idea for good.
If she doesn't fit, don't let her do it.
Got it?
Don't worry so much about the result.
Let her hang with us for a while.
That'd be good too.
Think of it
as helping your buddy babysit.
Can you babysit her?
Okay, then that's fine, right?
Bro, why are you in Chang'an?
Are Caixiang and Laidi here too?
Yes, they're here.
Can you take me to meet them?
Of course.
Of course, I can.
(Mi Lan, Chairman)
No.
Why?
Why do you think?
How is she now?
Same as ever.
I don't see much change.
Her clothes look pricier now.
Just like that title on her card.
She is always smart.
One right move led to another.
I somehow think you should go.
Maybe she can help you find a job.
She knows the Children's Palace well.
She's the boss there.
No.
All these years, I'm used to this.
I think this is pretty good.
No need to overthink it.
I don't want to change anymore.
Nor can I change much anyway.
It's just dinner.
Why pick somewhere so fancy?
Is this the place?
Right here.
Come on, hurry.
Hey.
Little Laidi.
Mi Lan.
Look how grown up you are.
- Long time no see.
- She's grown up.
Yeah.
Come on, have a seat.
Caixiang didn't come?
She's got something going on.
She couldn't get away.
Come sit down first.
What's keeping Caixiang so busy?
She's running a small business now.
She can't leave her stall.
- Thanks.
- What kind of business?
She sells liangpi
at the Diaojia Village entrance.
Laidi,
you've really made something
of yourself.
You're a big star now.
You know,
you're in the news nationwide.
I'm truly happy for you.
Mi Lan,
back when I was inside,
you took such good care of her.
You should thank Mi Lan properly.
Thank you, Mi Lan.
I'll never forget what you said to me
before you left the troupe.
Honestly, I forgot what I said.
I really didn't do much for the kid.
But even back then, I knew
that Yi Qing'e was bound to be a star.
Hey, is everyone in the troupe okay?
They're doing great.
Come back to the county when you can.
If they saw you now,
they'd all be blown away.
No one would've imagined
you'd become who you are today.
Ma'am,
you must've mixed it up.
Why is there so much chili?
I'm sorry.
I'll make you a new one right away.
Ma'am, one bowl of liangpi.
Extra chili, no garlic.
It looks like you're doing well.
That sounded a little sour.
My jealousy comes by the basin.
I really did miss you,
so I came to check on you.
Then sit over there.
Watch closely in a bit.
Sure, ma'am.
Peel a couple of cucumbers.
Or peel some garlic.
How do you still have this stuff?
This is how ordinary folks live.
A simple life is better.
Not like me, alone in Beijing.
When I get home late to a cold kitchen.
I don't even want to eat.
Let me.
What about your spouse?
We've been apart for four years.
If it weren't for this company,
it'd be better to live apart at our age.
I've actually figured it out.
Marriage is just sharing a life.
As long as no lines are crossed,
the marriage can still hold together.
Can't you look on the bright side?
Do you have kids?
No.
Luckily, I don't.
Once you have a kid,
your mind is all on the child,
and your career takes a back seat.
Listen to that.
I'm not sure who you're taking a jab at.
I don't get it.
You two are together now?
He told you that?
Does he need to?
When Sanyuan mentions you,
his eyes just light up,
just like back in Ningzhou.
I really envy you two.
You can connect on a deeper level.
Comforting me?
Afraid I'd feel bad?
No need.
Now, anyone who's not blind
can tell at a glance
which one of us
is doing better.
Sis,
you're better than me at everything.
You sing better than I.
You've got a better character.
Back then, if it had been you,
you wouldn't have married someone
nearly 20 years older
without love.
And now, if it were you,
you'd divorce him in a heartbeat.
You wouldn't still endure it like me.
Only I know what I've been through
all these years.
It'll all pass.
We're not in the County Troupe now,
fighting over the lead,
as if it were life or death.
What's the point?
Do you want liangpi?
I'll mix you a bowl.
I'm really good at it now.
That's all I can do now.
All you can do?
You don't sing anymore?
♪Grandma tells of the brave old days♪
♪When sacrifices were made♪
Wow, you really sound worse now.
I like it that way.
Regardless, I still like singing.
It makes me happy.
If you're so good, you sing.
Sing.
♪Oh, Grandma♪
♪17 years of care, deep as the ocean♪
Qin'e,
you're back.
No, I...
That's not what I meant.
Last time,
you got it wrong.
Just let me explain.
I really didn't...
Qin'e.
I'm sorry.
No.
Qin'e, you...
This is my pledge letter.
Never go against Yi Qin'e's wishes
in anything I do.
If Yi Qin'e says east,
I will never go west.
Devote my life to Yi Qin'e.
Be her support off the field.
Have warm salt water, throat lozenges,
and a dry towel
ready in advance.
Make sure that after the show,
her coat is brought right away,
so she doesn't catch a cold.
Respect Yi Qin'e's artistic exchanges.
No suspicion. No interference.
If any rumors about Yi Qin'e
come up out there,
I must step up at once.
That is my pledge to Yi Qin'e.
The final say
belongs solely to Yi Qin'e.
Qin'e,
I lost my head last time.
I apologize.
I won't do that again.
Okay?
You did nothing wrong.
It's on me.
You should go.
Don't come back
anymore.
There's no chance for us.
Is it because of that rumor?
Don't worry.
I'll get you an answer.
(Zhijiu Bookstore)
Pick any book you want.
Scholar of Tangcheng.
Who are you?
How do you know my pen name?
Did you write
The Pan Jinlian in Chang'an?
Yeah, I wrote it. So what?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Who told you to write it?
I didn't write it.
Her coworker put me up to it.
That's why I wrote it.
Who is it?
Her coworker.
She stayed anonymous.
Zhou Yuzhi.
Jiahe, what brings you here?
I came to see how you're doing.
You've been off so long. Are you okay?
I'm fine, just taking it slow.
The doctor says coughs linger.
I made some porridge.
Have some with me later.
Sure.
Why bring so much stuff?
My mom gave it to me. It's too much.
So, I brought some for you.
Okay.
When are you doing Yang Pai Feng?
They haven't set a date yet.
Why?
What's the point?
If my transfer had gone through,
I wouldn't be here singing.
I'm so mad.
It wasted my best years.
All year long,
I dated three or four men,
but none of them worked out.
I swapped your pillow for down.
(The Choice)
Better than buckwheat.
Sure.
(Scholar of Tangcheng, Lead Writer)
Jiahe, don't move.
What magazine is this?
Is this Tangcheng Tales?
Where are the cover
and missing pages of this book?
Did you pin them on the notice board?
Answer me.
Yes.
Why would you do that?
I've always looked out for her.
But I only asked her once
to let me play the second female lead.
She gave me the official runaround.
In that moment,
I felt she deserved no pity.
You're not as good onstage,
so you pull these shady moves.
I really misjudged you.
No, Jiahe, you...
Let go.
Chu Jiahe,
this isn't Ningzhou anymore.
You're not the lead anymore.
Do you know how you got
your Yang Pai Feng?
She had no time to perform it,
so it was handed to you.
I heard it myself.
She told Troupe Leader Shan.
Or could you ever play the lead?
=The Lead=
(Preview)
For the lead in the troupe,
strange things often happen.
Do you have any ideas?
There's nothing going on
between Yi Qin'e and me.
We're innocent.
You know the answer.
You started that rumor.
I don't need your pity.
I'd rather quit Yang Pai Feng
than accept your charity.
If you hadn't come to me,
I would've come for you.
Yi Qin'e, hurry and answer it!
What happened to Liu Hongbing?
He jumped off a building for you.
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪We met and brushed past♪
♪Your shadow drifted out of sight♪
♪The stove fire blazed in my dream♪
♪Lit up the tracks of pearly tears♪
♪In my dream, water sleeves flew♪
♪Hiding a lifetime of love♪
♪The Qinling Mountains
crossed the stage♪
♪Spring water brewed strong wine♪
♪Sheep moved through the valley♪
♪It felt like a promise
from another life♪
♪When I woke up and turned back♪
♪I wasn't sure where to go♪
♪If I chose again, I'd still roam♪
♪All over this sunlit plateau♪
♪The dream ends; the curtain falls♪
♪Moonlight washes off this stage makeup♪
♪The one in the mirror wears gray hair♪
♪Already sang all my joy and sorrow♪
♪Already shouted across Qinchuan Plain♪