[1999]
[Jewelry Art]
[Zhuo'er Jewelry Explores
Diverse Aesthetic Fields]
[Pioneers Fashion Trends]
[Integrates Wholesale and Retail,
and Develops Chain Operations]
[The Young Entrepreneur Couple
from Yunzhou]
[Innovates and Founds Zhuo'er Jewelry]
[Beloved]
[Episode 3
All Her Life, She Has Always Been Useless]
[Wanxi Road Police Station]
Go to hell!
[1986]
Qu Tong,
tell me,
did you write
these two names?
I didn't. It wasn't me.
She did it. She's lying.
[Teacher's Office]
Move aside.
She's coming. Step aside.
Step aside.
Don't block her way.
Make way.
Step aside. Step aside.
Step aside.
Ms. Shen,
you're finally here.
This is Hao Meili's mother,
and this is Hao Meili.
You're Qu Tong's mother, right?
How do you even raise your daughter?
Today we need
to clear this up right here.
Or I won't let this go.
Did you do it?
Mom, I didn't do it.
Ms. Zhang.
You're saying Qu Tong did it,
but do you have any evidence?
This is the evidence.
[Qu Tong, the prettiest in the class]
[Hao Meili, the ugliest in the class]
This is the evidence?
Everything is blurry.
What do you mean by that?
Your daughter did it!
No one else but her.
It was her.
What are you looking at?
Ms. Zhang.
What we've been taught tells us
that for anything we do,
we must base it on reason and evidence,
and seek truth from facts.
This principle
holds wherever we go, doesn't it?
Ms. Zhang.
I wonder
what you think about this.
Yes.
Coming here to show off to me
that you're educated, right?
So you're educated,
what's so great about that?
You still raised a daughter like this.
She's just embarrassing herself here.
I may not be well-educated,
but my daughter is a good student.
Unbelievable.
Mrs. Shi, please don't be angry.
Ms. Shen
certainly didn't mean it that way.
Right now,
we truly don't have
sufficient evidence to prove
that the writing
was done by Qu Tong.
Of course, this incident has gone too far.
Our school will never tolerate phenomena
like students judging others
by their appearance
or bullying.
Wait, what are you saying?
So Meili suffered for nothing?
My daughter transferred here,
and she can't score better
than my daughter.
It's obvious!
So,
she just
used something like this
to bully my daughter?
You're way too mean!
Ms. Zhang.
Now I get it.
There's no evidence at all,
right?
It's all just speculation.
Are you trying to weasel out of this?
You think we're soft targets,
easy to bully, right?
Ms. Zhang,
you can't resolve this, can you?
Please
get the principal here right now.
I demand an explanation today.
Or this isn't over.
Ms. Zhang.
I'm quite busy with work.
Let's do this.
Qu Tong will come back with me first.
Once I find out more
about what's going on,
we can talk further.
Okay.
You can go back first then.
Wait, Ms. Zhang.
What do you mean?
We're not done here.
How dare you leave?
Hold on.
What do you mean?
You haven't even sorted this out yet.
What are you doing?
Come here, sit down,
Explain everything to me.
Sit here. Don't be afraid.
I'm here with you.
[Yunzhou No.1 High School]
Mom.
I really...
That Qu Tong,
[Mediation Room]
she's the one
who hurt my daughter, you know?
Then he dragged me here.
You...
Come in.
Qu Tong!
Listen to me.
You pay attention.
As long as I'm alive,
as long as I'm breathing,
I won't let you off.
You hear me?
Mrs. Shi.
Today I'm going
to tell you very clearly.
Whatever happened to Shi Yue
had nothing to do with me before,
and has nothing to do with me now.
Nothing to do with you?
Then who is responsible?
Shi Muxian!
You think I don't know anything,
right?
Your relationship with Su Muxin
has been bad for a long time.
He doesn't even go home.
He abandoned you.
He didn't want you.
So you hated Meili, right?
So you hurt her.
So you killed her,
didn't you?
Say something!
Yes, you're right.
My relationship with him
has indeed been bad.
But do you know why?
Because I lost interest
in him long ago.
I actually hoped Hao Meili
would take him away completely.
All her life,
she has been so useless.
Is that Zhou Mi?
Is that Officer Zhou?
Yes.
Take it easy.
That's her, right?
Captain Zhou.
Two elderly people are here to see you.
They've been waiting for you
for a long time.
Are you Officer Zhou Mi?
We have something
to discuss with you.
Could you...
No.
-Officer Zhou.
-Zhou Mi.
Alright.
Zhou Mi, please hear us out.
Officer Zhou.
-Zhou Mi.
-Officer Zhou.
That's enough.
Officer Zhou!
We've been waiting for you all day!
[Police]
Officer Zhou!
Enough!
Mentor.
Didn't you agree to take me
under your wing?
Then you should at least
teach me something.
I'm just a rookie.
You don't answer my questions.
You don't tell me anything
about case developments.
I can't make sense of anything.
I'm completely lost.
How am I supposed to learn?
If you have any other complaints about me,
just say them all at once.
The elderly couple
at the entrance just now,
why wouldn't you even
let them speak?
They might have legitimate concerns.
They could be relatives of someone
involved in the case.
Or they might want to provide some leads.
If you're unhappy with my way
of handling cases,
go find Captain Gao first thing
tomorrow morning
and get a new mentor.
Also,
don't follow me around anymore today.
Go home and rest!
[Couple, married in 1995]
[Su Muxin's office in Zhuo'er]
[Colleagues say Su Muxin
cherishes Qu Tong]
[Home visit in Yunzhou]
Captain Gao.
Still studying the crime scene photos?
Found anything suspicious?
Many things.
The night of the incident,
power went out on Hesheng Street.
[General Manager Su Muxin, missing]
Su Muxin stayed at Shi Yue's place
for the entire night.
He was very familiar with that room,
so logically he should have been able
to easily restore these things.
But,
he only took
Shi Yue's phone,
leaving all this evidence
untouched.
There are contradictions
and illogical aspects everywhere.
We previously deduced
that Su Muxin and Qu Tong
were conspiring together,
that Qu Tong was helping Su Muxin,
and that Su Muxin was hiding in Yunzhou.
But now I think
our deduction was wrong.
Maybe all of Qu Tong's suspicious behavior
had nothing to do with Su Muxin.
Why do you say
your previous deduction was wrong?
Qu Tong is someone
who's extremely cautious
and doesn't trust anyone.
I've dealt with her a few times
and she has never told the truth.
But today
when she was facing Shi Yue's mother...
Say something!
Yes, you're right.
There was the mix of old and new grudges.
Her reaction was emotional.
Because I lost interest
in him long ago.
I think that was the real her.
Her relationship with Su Muxin
is probably
different from what she's showing.
Without some
special reason,
she wouldn't help Su Muxin.
It's getting late.
You should get some rest.
You
stop cooping yourself up here all day!
Go home if you need to.
One more thing, Captain Gao.
Not up for discussion.
About Wu Dong,
you have to mentor him,
whether you like it or not.
Are you
there?
[Wait for my contact]
[Yunzhou No.1 High School]
[July 19th,
the 4th day after the incident]
Officer Zhou.
I'm Ms. Zhang.
[Teaching Building]
When school starts again,
we'll all be moving
to the new district.
This place will be demolished.
To be honest,
I'm quite reluctant to leave.
This school was built
back in the 1970s.
You called
to ask about Qu Tong,
Su Muxin,
and Hao Meili from the 1986 cohort.
I've done my best
to collect all the things
they left behind
back then.
But it has been a long time.
There's not much left.
Okay.
Here's everything I have on them.
[Hao Meili, Class 1, Senior 3]
[Li Li, Class 2, Senior 3]
[Su Muxin, Class 1, Senior 3]
Do you have a strong impression
of Su Muxin?
Su Muxin was the class monitor then,
with excellent grades.
[Qu Tong, Class 1, Senior 3]
He was from Chen Village,
far from the county town.
I remember he only had his mother,
no father.
Thank you.
There were no highways back then.
Going home
would take him an entire night.
So at that time,
he lived in the dormitory.
In the 1980s,
getting into college was very difficult.
So the whole village was proud of him.
Ms. Zhang, I'm innocent.
In today's class meeting,
although I apologized,
it wasn't sincere.
I really didn't do that.
It has been
over ten years.
But I still can't get over it.
I didn't handle it well back then.
I want Qu Tong to apologize!
[1986]
Hao Meili.
I want her to apologize.
I'm sorry.
What kind of person
is Qu Tong?
In my impression, she was
very introverted,
quiet,
and strictly supervised by her family.
So she never attended
any gatherings with classmates.
She didn't talk much,
and basically had no friends.
Vixen.
The vixen of No. 1 High School.
But she was very smart,
with excellent grades.
Before Hao Meili transferred
to our school,
she always ranked first in exams.
After that incident happened,
it had a huge emotional impact on her,
even affecting her academic performance.
But she recovered quickly,
and eventually
got into college successfully.
So I think
she might appear fragile on the outside,
but actually
she was a very resilient girl.
Well,
was Qu Tong responsible for
the bullying of Hao Meili?
There's no way
to verify this matter anymore.
But I don't think it was her.
Was Su Muxin involved?
I'm not sure about that.
Qu Tong seems
a bit pitiful.
Indeed.
You feel sorry for her?
Do you know what she is?
What?
The vixen of No. 1 High School.
Vixen.
You feel sorry for her?
That vixen.
Feel sorry?
Why feel sorry for her?
She's just a vixen.
[Sanjie Restaurant]
Maybe we missed something.
Otherwise we shouldn't
have failed to catch Su Muxin.
So you called me here
to see if there are any other leads?
[Sanjie Restaurant]
[Open]
Mr. Zhang, look here.
From here you can see
our car across the street.
Qu Tong must have spotted
that we were following her
and passed the message to Su Muxin.
It must be like that.
Our car was parked right over there.
[Sanjie Restaurant]
Besides Qu Tong,
was Su Muxin close
with any other classmates?
I heard from students
in his year
that after Su Muxin got into college,
he cut off contact
with his former classmates.
Later, someone
ran into him in Yunzhou.
It was said he worked
at the Industry and Commerce Bureau
and had become a senior official.
At that time, Qu Tong's car
was parked right here.
After she went out,
she got something from her car.
We didn't notice
anything suspicious.
After getting off the car,
she walked along this road
straight ahead,
never leaving our sight.
Where exactly did things go wrong?
Details.
There must be some details
that we've missed.
Hello.
[Yunzhou Trading Company]
I'm here to see Mr. Li.
Mr. Li, Officer Zhou is here to see you.
Please come in.
Officer Zhou from Dongjiang, right?
Hello, Mr. Li.
Hello, please have a seat.
I'm here today to ask you
about someone.
About whom?
Su Muxin.
Mr. Su from Zhuo'er Jewelry?
In 1994,
Su Muxin was transferred back
to serve as deputy section chief
at Yunzhou Industry and Commerce Bureau.
At that time,
you hadn't resigned
to go into business yet.
You were his superior,
weren't you?
Yes.
But after he married Qu Tong,
he resigned
not long after.
Later I also went into business.
We didn't interact much.
You know Qu Tong too?
Just a coincidence.
They reunited
at the Industry and Commerce Bureau.
I was there at the time.
Director Li.
[1994]
Come in.
Could you please check
if their paperwork
is missing anything?
This is similar to the case
you handled last time.
Sure.
Su Muxin.
I wrote you many letters,
but you never replied.
I even called the school
to confirm
that the address was correct.
Is that so?
It doesn't matter.
The good thing is we've met again.
Tong.
We should go now.
Section Chief Su.
About the paperwork,
I'll leave it in your hands.
You're welcome.
[General Office]
Tong, let's go.
Since you're so busy,
I won't bother you anymore.
This is my pager number.
I'll be going now.
[Announcement Board
of Yunzhou Industry and Commerce Bureau]
This high school classmate of yours
is Qu Lijun's daughter?
Their family
is quite well-off.
He made his fortune in Guangdong.
A couple of years ago, he took over
a factory in the county,
specializing in jewelry processing.
It's going quite well.
And
they've even landed a contract
with that high-end brand Jinfeng
from Guangdong.
They're really expanding.
That's why
they're applying for land to scale up.
Take a good look at this.
Section Chief Su.
[Yunzhou Trading Company]
I'm sorry, Officer Zhou.
I couldn't be of much help.
About his case,
my knowledge is quite limited.
What do you
think of Su Muxin?
Speaking of Su Muxin,
I think he's destined for great things.
He's decisive in his actions
and at the same time,
he's hardly influenced by emotions.
He's very rational.
Of course,
from another perspective,
some might find him a bit cold-hearted.
I see.
Thanks for your cooperation.
My pleasure.
Please don't see me out.
Take care.
Where did we go wrong?
Otherwise we shouldn't
have failed to catch Su Muxin.
It's fine. Let's head back first.
Hello.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Mentor,
I think there's one possibility.
Qu Tong and Su Muxin
did actually arrange
to meet at Sanjie Restaurant.
But she discovered early on
that we were following her.
You were inside the restaurant then,
while I was watching at the entrance.
When Qu Tong left,
her movements were a bit strange.
But only now do I realize what was wrong.
After she went out,
she went to her car to get something.
There was a clear unlocking sound.
But when
we came back with her,
she made
a fake unlocking gesture,
with no unlocking sound.
Goodbye.
She wasn't getting something earlier.
She was just unlocking the car.
If we follow this reasoning,
when we were following her,
her nervous expression
and looking back at us
wasn't because she feared
us following her,
but she feared we wouldn't follow her.
Right.
I suspect
that during this time,
Su Muxin had already hidden
in the trunk of Qu Tong's car.
[Restroom]
Hello.
Are you here for a meal?
[Restroom,
Caution, Wet Floor]
[Friendly Reminder,
Officer Zhou.
I need to use the restroom.
Me too.
[Restroom,
Caution, Wet Floor]
[Emergency Exit]
Are you there?
I'm here.
Come down.
The trunk is directly facing
the main door.
Turn left and you'll find the stairwell.
You know which floor it is.
You're on your own now.
[Captain of the First Detachment]
Qu Tong.
You won't come to a good end.
Help me!
Help!
Qu Tong.
Save me!
Help!
On the morning
of July 20th, 2002,
an unidentified body was discovered
in the Wangjiatuo River
[Yimin Grain Store]
in Ansiguan Township, Yunzhou County.
According to the investigation,
the deceased was an adult male,
180 cm tall,
wearing a white cotton short-sleeve shirt
and blue boxer shorts.
Currently,
the police are conducting
crime scene investigations,
interviews and other related work.
The general public is requested
to actively provide
any leads to the police.
We will continue to follow
the developments of this case
and bring you the latest reports.
Now for another news story.
Hello.
Criminal Investigation Unit.