WHAT TYPE OF GUY
ARE WOMEN MOST DRAWN TO?
I'm such a sucker for well-dressed guys.
They don't even have to be glam,
just well put together.
That alone makes them attractive.
For real, girls.
Scent matters too.
Like they're always fresh
out of the shower.
That's definitely a win.
As for looks,
no need to be super handsome.
Just decent-looking is enough.
At least if you get your heart broken,
you know you cried over
someone good-looking.
Have a good day, Sun.
Should we look for green flags too?
Like, is there even a guy
who ticks all the boxes?
But at the very least,
I want someone polite
who cares about people around them.
Today's sure gonna be a good day
because it started with your smile, Mook.
Or the guys who help others out in public.
That's pretty impressive too.
- Watch out, miss! Miss!
- Oh!
Hey!
How about an apology?
Or should I just send your license plate
photo to the police?
Sorry.
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
- Thank you so much.
- Not at all.
Oh, I just noticed
there's a guy in the audience.
Would you like to come up
and share your thoughts?
Hi… I guess I've been caught.
I just wanted to listen in
and see what women think.
It might help me improve myself.
But sometimes,
we'd like to hear from the guys too.
Do you mind if I ask you
something in return?
Do men believe in love at first sight,
like women do?
Love at first sight?
I think…
it's possible.
Hey, boy!
She already paid. Give that to me.
What's this got to do with you?
Is she your girlfriend?
- No.
- Do you know her?
No.
Secret admirer?
Just give it to me, come on.
Now go! Watch out for cars too.
Where are you now?
Mr. Sun, are you still there?
Yeah, I am.
I just want to say
that for love at first sight to happen,
you have to be completely unattached.
But right now,
that's not the case for me because
there's already someone I'm focused on.
Here we are.
Where are you taking me?
Don't open your eyes just yet.
All right. You can get out now.
Keep your eyes closed.
Take a few steps forward.
Here we are.
One, two, three!
Huh? What is this?
You're taking me to a haunted house?
No, it's this.
What's with the teasing?
Isn't it more fun to be surprised twice?
Did you have to go all out like this?
What's the occasion?
It's our 15-day anniversary.
This way, ma'am.
Thank you.
Feels like a dinner by the Han River,
like in a K-drama.
Do I give off K-drama lead vibes?
Well, if we're talking Lee Min-ho,
Bo-gum, Cha Eun-woo, and Jaehyun,
there's no way
I'd ever get to date any of them.
But the luckiest thing is…
I have you, Sun.
You can make me smile wider
than those four.
I never thought I could feel this great,
not just today,
but ever since the first day we met.
I know it hasn't been that long…
but every day we've talked…
I've kept thinking over and over
about what this feeling really is.
And today, I'm sure…
that this feeling I have
just keeps growing.
Are you going to take this seriously?
Then I will too.
Let's end it right here.
What?
Then why'd you even do all this?
It's a send-off.
It's exhausting having to do all this
just to please you.
You know, the standards you've set,
they're too high for real life.
Try living in reality for once.
Enjoy your meal.
Consider it my farewell treat.
Sun, go rot in hell!
Job No. 7/2005 is complete. Gudji.
She raises the bar so high
for men to reach
and romanticizes love
like it's some K-drama fantasy
when in reality, it's just not possible.
She deserves to stay single.
There's no such thing as true love.
Love is just a tool for my work,
nothing more.
Please get out of your car, sir.
Make sure you clean
every corner thoroughly.
I want to take this
as washing away the bad luck.
That's Earnearn 6/2025.
Want me to take a photo for you?
EARNEARN 6/2025
A woman who cheats
deserves to be cheated on too.
Sure.
Shit!
I'll come back to pick up my car later.
Hey!
Go, go, go!
That was almost karma coming for you.
I told you,
angry women are the scariest.
When it was her doing it to someone else,
she didn't seem to feel sorry at all.
I did everything exactly the same
as Earnearn did.
I copied every single detail
down to the last step.
I just did what she did to our client.
And that was something that
happened long ago.
Imagine if it were a fresh wound.
Whoa. She would've gone full meltdown.
Like Gudji…
You asshole!
Absolute piece of shit!
Sun, you jerk! I hope you die tomorrow!
So brutal.
The angrier they are,
the more it means
we struck the right spot.
Exactly.
But you've gotta give me some credit.
I dug up all the info you needed
so you could finish each job perfectly.
Maybe a bit overboard, actually.
But seriously,
taking breakup gigs just to get revenge?
Does that really make sense?
7 YEARS AGO
Gale,
for you.
Hey, hey.
Can't you two wait until you're alone?
This is kinda awkward for me, you know.
That's exactly what I feel.
That's why I brought you along.
I wouldn't have the guts
to give it to her.
So what now?
Every time you two go on a date,
I have to come too?
Honestly, it'd be great
to have you with us.
Otherwise, Chin gets so shy
he won't do anything.
GALE: I'M NOT JUST SAYING THIS,
I WANT TO HAVE YOU AROUND.
Why'd you want to see me?
You got something to tell me?
Let's start with you.
You look like shit.
What's going on?
Man…
I found out
that Gale's seeing a bunch of guys.
She tried the same thing with me.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
What?
I'm seriously pissed, man.
What can I do to make her hurt like I do?
Just leave it to karma.
I'm supposed to wait
until the day she dies?
We're friends, aren't we?
Help me get back at Gale.
GALE 1/2018
FIRST JOB
Sleep soon or you'll get sick.
Are you sure about this?
Out of all the guys I'm seeing,
I like you the most.
Ow!
But I feel nothing.
I just wanted to have some fun
just like what you did to my friend.
You asshole, Sun!
GALE 1/2018
JOB DONE
Damn.
This is your freakin' gift.
You could make a living off this.
You'd be rich.
Come on.
Don't go that far.
It's not exactly decent.
Then just do it
to the ones who deserve it,
like those cheating, two-timing girls.
When they get hurt, they'll think twice
before doing it to someone else.
Because they've got you,
love karma in the flesh,
coming for them in this lifetime!
Serves them right.
You do bad, you get what you deserve.
Karma just showed up
a little faster than usual, that's all.
Being the asshole in someone's life
is something not everyone can pull off.
But you can.
Is that a compliment?
I guess, yes.
Anyway,
where's my pay?
Now stop overthinking it.
It's this pay
that answers everything.
Think about it, man.
The more cases we get,
the more money we make.
If this is a sin,
then I'll call it
a sin that puts food on the table.
Just thinking out loud here,
but if all those people knew each other
and teamed up to get revenge on you,
I'm telling you,
the day that happens,
it'll be hell on earth for you.
The deepest level of hell.
So deep no one's digging you out.
Damn you. Watch your mouth.
Or I'll smack it right off your face.
Are you even on my side or what?
I'm always on your side.
I love you the most, you know.
Even if you're a total asshole,
I still love you.
Let's just say,
once I land a big, juicy sin
that brings in serious money,
I'll quit this job for you, ladies.
I need to go now.
Where are you going?
We just got a new job in.
Nah, I need a break.
- Let me be myself for now.
- All right, see you.
LIGHT AND SHADOW GALLERY
You know what else
candid street photos are called?
Sneak shots.
If you'd just asked nicely,
the photos would've turned out better.
"Sauvage."
Do you have to call me
something that harsh?
It's your perfume.
So you're not mad
about the other day anymore?
The other day?
If I had a deep night with someone,
I'd remember them all,
but I don't remember you.
Not that.
There's not only one kind
of "deep night," right?
Talk for ten minutes
and it's already deep.
But we met during the day.
And the stuff you bought
is still with me.
Okay, there's a storyline.
That's kinda cute.
But honestly, that whole
"have we met before" pickup line?
I don't think it really works anymore.
Or maybe…
maybe it still does.
Because I want to get to know you now.
Everyone!
Stop the corrupt monopolies.
Stand against the power
that exploits the powerless.
Stop the corrupt monopolies.
Stand against the power
that exploits the powerless.
Stop the corrupt monopolies.
Stand against the power
that exploits the powerless.
Stop the corrupt monopolies.
Stand against the power
that exploits the powerless.
You really think this is gonna work?
STOP CORRUPT MONOPOLIES
If I don't shout,
no one's gonna hear me, right?
Are you the owner of this painting
or something?
No, but it bothers me.
Honestly, I get you.
I get your method too.
But the people you should be targeting
are the ones who actually wronged you,
not the owner of this painting.
You think?
Well, now my target…
is you.
You okay?
Hey… what's your name?
Sun.
I'm Sairung.
Help record all of this for me.
If this is how you want to do it,
then why don't we create
something together?
You can do whatever you want with it
because it won't involve
anyone else anymore.
Now,
you get to say what you want to say
with your whole self.
And I think
this way, it'll be even louder.
STOP CORRUPT MONOPOLIES
She's so cool.
How did she do that?
Miss. Miss?
Miss!
ART BOMBER GETS BOMBED BACK,
HAHAHAHA.
Do I still look good?
Thanks for helping out earlier.
Can I treat you as a thank-you?
That line is just as old as
the "have we met before" line.
Then forget the thank-you treat.
Would you like to come?
I want someone with me tonight.
I thought it'd be nice if it were you.
Wrong guess.
So… what's the punishment?
Take a shot of Devil Kiss.
It'll be fun.
Hello, hello. It's time.
Are you guys wasted yet?
It's Saturday night.
Our regulars know it's Open Mic time.
OPEN MIC = TAKE THE MIC AND SING
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
No.
Come on.
There are so many other people.
No, no way.
Give it to other people.
Whoa.
She's so cool.
If I'd never seen your smile
If you and I'd never locked eyes
When you're unaware, when you're shy
Had I not been right there
If we'd been just passersby
If, to me, you hadn't been so kind
My thoughts wouldn't wander
So far and high
Had I not been right here
People who don't know us
might think you'd just confessed
your love to me.
Confessed my love?
That's a bit much, don't you think?
But maybe… someday.
Who knows?
Too close not to have my thoughts wander
Too close for me to handle
Someone next to you trembles
Have you realized this at all?
The more I get closer
You seem to float away further
If one day I can't hold it in
Don't be mad if I catch feelings for you
"Si."
SI: PERFUME NAME
You've got a sharp nose.
Were you a K9 agent before or something?
So I got it right?
Si, you're very right.
SI: YES
This is probably one of
the first times in years
that my heart's actually
raced for someone.
Watch out. You may slip.
I'm not gonna slip.
Look, it's not slippery at all.
Watch out, the ground's wet.
Hey.
You really don't remember
that face-changing doll?
No, I don't.
Just get rid of it.
That face-changing doll.
Time to say goodbye.
I need to go home.
I hope we meet again.
What…
What's gotten into you?
You were acting all tough before you left.
I got revived.
You're all over the place, man.
Well, snap out of it.
Help answer this client. They are waiting.
De, I really need a break.
I want to live a little.
What, bro?
Hey.
Don't tell me
you're falling for a girl
and thinking of changing yourself?
Oh, come on. No.
I'm not quitting this.
I just want a break, that's all.
- INTERESTED. PLEASE GET BACK TO ME ASAP.
- I CAN'T TAKE ON THIS JOB RIGHT NOW
Hey!
Are you out of your mind?
You don't care about work and money now?
THEPPACHAI
Hello.
I'm not really available
for jobs right now.
I'm taking some time off.
How about watching the clip I sent first?
Then let me know if you decide
to stop taking some time off.
He knows exactly what I like.
The type I'm weak for.
Feels like he was made to be
my perfect match.
Makes me fall in just a few days.
And in the end,
I fell right into his trap.
It's a send-off.
It's exhausting having to do all this
just to please you.
You know, the standards you've set,
they're too high for real life.
I'm hurt.
I'm so pissed. I'm mad.
I want revenge.
"THE HEARTBREAKER FOR HIRE"
Wasn't it fun?
Enjoyed it, didn't you?
That was just a teaser, Mr. Sun
The full clip has plenty more victims,
all ready to expose you.
If you don't want me to release
the full scoop,
come talk to me.
I'm sure you know where to find me.
This is the place?
Don't die just yet.
Because I'm just getting started.
From now on,
you're my dream,
Mr. Sun.
You do know, right?
I never left you.
I walked you all the way
to hell's door myself.
But I'm not in the clip
so you're on your own now, bro.
You'll be my dream too.
You ungrateful bastard!
What are you waiting for?!
Hey, here you are.
Come on. It was just a greeting.
I'm not gonna hurt you, come on.
Hello.
I'm Theppachai.
Nice to finally meet you.
I think we should talk
in the meeting room.
There's a lot of details to go over.
Come on.
You can chug it down. It's not poisoned.
SCAMMER!!
WITH A BRAND-NEW TRICK!!
Well, you did mess her up pretty bad.
You should understand.
When girls get hurt, they act like this.
But I didn't think
she'd be this mad either.
Hey!
There, there. Okay, okay.
So this was your plan all along?
Using Gudji to trap me?
Yes!
I kinda had to.
It was the only way to meet you.
What do you want from me then?
You want this scoop
to go viral or something?
It's not what you think.
The truth is,
I want your help.
And it's something you're really good at.
So… who do you want me to break up with?
No, no breakups this time.
I actually want you to do the opposite.
Because the truth is,
your real talent is
how easily you make women fall for you.
Here's the proof.
Hey, would you stop it already?
I want you to flirt with my daughter.
None of that now.
If you don't do what I say,
I'll expose everything!
How did I get to this point?
So this really is your place.
I thought I had the wrong one.
Have you been following me since that day?
What kind of game are you playing today?
I can't keep up anymore.
You always keep me on my toes.
You dropped this,
so I wanted to return it.
Didn't you want to see me again?
What's with the familiarity?
Since when have we been close?
Are you crazy?
The person you met wasn't me.
Stop making things up.
I'm so confused here.
Why are you pretending
you don't remember me?
If you're here to return something,
then give me back my doll.
I paid for it. It's mine.
Now… you remember that doll?
How could I not remember what's mine?
Now give it to me
and get out of my place.
It all feels bizarre.
There's got to be something I'm missing.
I don't get scammers these days either.
Too many tricks up their sleeves.
What are you and your daughter
trying to pull?
You want to blackmail me, I get that.
But messing with my head like this?
I don't get it.
You're not tricking me
for some dating reality show, right?
What the hell did you run into?
Actually, I've met your daughter before.
I don't get scammers these days either.
Too many tricks up their sleeves.
And now, suddenly,
I'm a scammer?
Seriously, what is all this?
Good.
Since you saw it for yourself,
this'll be easier for me to explain.
My daughter is not weird or anything.
When she says she doesn't remember,
she really doesn't.
Because
she's a completely different person.
I have just one daughter,
but she has…
five personalities.
And all five personalities
lead their own lives.
Your real job is,
you must flirt with my daughter,
and you must make all five of them
fall
in love
with
you
successfully!
Love karma
is really making a U-turn straight
back to me.
MULTIPLE PERSONALITY DISORDER
DISSOCIATIVE IDENTITY DISORDER:
A PSYCHOLOGICAL DEFENSE MECHANISM
WHERE A PERSON HAS TWO OR MORE
DISTINCT IDENTITIES OR PERSONALITY STATES
Multi personalities
like one person during the day,
another at night?
Something like that,
but it's more than that.
Like I said,
my daughter has five personalities.
Are you joking with me?
I wouldn't joke about
my daughter's condition.
She used to be
just like any other ordinary kid.
Sairung was a sweet kid.
The three of us were
really happy together…
until
my wife passed away.
Sairung became a completely different kid.
You've worn down the blue one.
Sharpen it.
You use it too, don't you?
Why don't you sharpen it yourself?
But I don't use it as much as you do.
Sairung was still so young.
I had no idea what to do back then.
Sairung, come out and play with us.
I have a doll here.
Losing her mother
affected Sairung's development.
The doctor said
she showed unusual symptoms,
similar to Dissociative Identity Disorder.
But not exactly that.
So I had to take care of her closely.
That's why I quit my job
and started this online news site.
Sairung started to smile again,
and that gave me hope that she might
return to who she was before.
I already named this doll Muffin!
I picked the name before you did.
Just call it Woowoo instead.
- But the color is way more like a muffin.
- I have to admit…
- Sairung is no longer the same person.
- I want to be called Muffin.
I tried every kind of treatment.
From conventional medicine
to all kinds of therapy,
I tried everything to help my daughter.
But none of it worked.
Then I heard about you.
Me?
I'm not a doctor.
Have you heard this quote?
Mahatma Gandhi.
Or this one.
"The power of love and desire…"
"It has the power to make you do anything"
- "The power of…"
- Seriously?!
Those are lyrics from "Pong, Hin Lek Fai"!
Oh, you know this song?
- My mom used to play it.
- Great taste there.
There's also this line.
Stop it.
What exactly are you trying to say?
It's just like what Mahatma Gandhi
and Pong said.
Love has the greatest power.
It has the power to make you do anything.
- The power of--
- Hey!
Okay.
I believe that
if all five of Sairung's personalities
can experience the same kind of love,
her unusual condition
might actually go away.
Look…
I feel really sorry for you
for everything that happened.
But I stand by what I said.
I'm not capable of helping anyone.
What I do
only ends up hurting people.
You've seen that.
Anyway,
if I come across a doctor or someone
who can actually help you,
I'll let you know.
But for now, I have to go.
He knows exactly what I like.
The type I'm weak for.
Feels like he was made to be
my perfect match.
Makes me fall in just a few days.
This is not a request,
but an order.
That's the love karma!
These are the five girls that we must do
whatever it takes to make fall for me.
What's the name of the last one?
My name is Marnmok.
Marnmok seems like
the hardest one to approach.
My name is Sun.
Just focus on your work.
You don't have to try to get to know me.
It's the final boss.
Let's see who's got the most power.
Prai-Fon, Storm…
Sairung and Marnmok had a huge fight.
They decided to live separately.
Where are the other girls now?
We each have our own personal space.