♪Why am I so vulnerable,
life is full of twists and turns♪
♪Worrying about gains and losses,
your smile makes me change♪
♪My eyes are avoiding♪
♪I know I've been captured by you♪
♪How could I break free♪
♪You come and go repeatedly,
like the wind, like fire♪
♪I toss and turn,
I can't help but fall again♪
♪Think about,
how to make it profound♪
♪The evening breeze tells me,
this winter is very suitable♪
♪I want♪
♪I want to watch the fireworks with you,
on a winter night♪
♪Want♪
♪To whisper to you on a crowded street♪
♪Your heart belongs to me♪
♪My heart belongs to you♪
♪I want to stay with your forever♪
♪I want♪
♪I want to watch the fireworks with you,
on a winter night♪
♪I want to spend♪
♪Every season with you♪
♪Miss you every day♪
♪Miss you every second♪
♪With me around, love will bloom♪
♪Under the starry sky♪
=Chasing the Wind=
Wei, you have resumed training.
Mom loves you.
Meniscus...
How did you injure your meniscus?
Nie Chi has already returned to Beijing.
Lysholm Knee Scoring Scale
shows that your score is not ideal.
Did my surgery really succeed?
Do you mean
that I can't conduct overload training
like an athlete?
Anyway,
(TPO iBT, Reading)
we have to get him abroad.
Are you dating Nie Chi?
=Episode 19=
=Please Let Me Be Stubborn Once=
(National Ice Sports Base)
What's up?
Your relationship isn't that great.
And then what happened?
Then his mom just left.
I haven't even had the chance
to finish what I want to say.
What's there to negotiate?
Whose parents would call talking
with their children a negotiation?
I think they
don't care at all about Nie Chi's thoughts.
Whatever.
As long as Nie Chi cares, that's good.
That's right.
Nie Chi doesn't want to go.
Can they force him to go?
Yeah.
(Force him...)
Mom, can you give me the phone?
No.
We agreed on this before
that you absolutely can't get hurt.
Otherwise, you must stop training.
Now we want you to go abroad,
but you said you still want to practice.
Is everything you said before is in vain?
Injuries among athletes are common.
You can't move in bed.
Is that common?
Don't fool me.
I don't know about short track speed skating.
But how could I not notice your injuries?
If you keep practicing, you're doomed.
It's the same to recover abroad.
You behave well.
I will return your phone when we get there.
Excuse me.
Where did the patient in No. 23 go?
He was just taken away by his family.
Excuse me.
Which ward is Nie Chi in?
Sorry, who are you?
We're the unannounced inspection personnel.
WADA
will give you three chances.
But in here, if one inspection is missed,
you will go back to where you came from.
The positive inspection result
affects not just your performance,
but the whole team's,
thereby blackening the national team.
Hello? Master.
Do you know Nie Chi's mom's phone number?
All right.
I'm hanging up. I have something urgent.
Hello?
Hello? Mrs. Nie, I'm Lin Ge.
A cold call.
Mom, I promise you.
Can you let me
do exercise?
Use this.
The traffic is terrible.
(The inspectors have arrived at the hospital.)
(Come back within an hour.)
(If not, your career will be affected.)
Chao, I'm here.
I called his mom.
It was hung up as soon as it was connected.
It's ok.
I just asked them, and they just left.
It hasn't been long.
Let's go chase after them now.
We still have time. Go.
Wait. Where?
To...
Nie Chi sent me the address.
(Leda Shopping Plaza)
It's so congested.
Traffic jam? That's good.
Traffic jam is so great.
- Chase?
- Let's go.
If you really love sports,
let's choose a sport over there. Ok?
Foreign universities
prioritize sports the most.
Let's choose a safer one.
No sport is completely safe.
Is there a specific location? Where is he?
The location is right around here.
It's so congested. They won't go far.
♪Have you ever given and received♪
Chess, Go, and bridge game,
aren't they all quite safe?
Aren't those also considered sports?
If a person is unlucky,
he may choke on cold water.
You...
Here. It's here, right?
♪I silently pass by alone♪
See!
♪Who will accompany me♪
Nie Chi! Nie Chi!
Chao, carry me. Hurry up.
Come on.
Hurry up.
♪The dreams in my heart are calling me♪
Lin Ge.
Nie Chi!
♪Keep it up, young man♪
♪A youth like the wind♪
♪Make your own future shine brighter♪
Where are we going?
Return to the hospital.
The inspectors are there.
There is still half an hour.
Hurry up. Quick.
♪Cross the finish line facing the wind♪
You acted recklessly.
Why didn't you ask us for help?
Didn't you say the inspection can't be missed?
We're afraid Nie Chi may miss it, so...
Still making excuses, huh?
It's such a dangerous thing.
Have you even thought this through?
I'll deal with you when I get back.
Mr. Nie, Mrs. Nie,
why don't we go out and chat?
Let's just talk here.
I'm afraid they might
take my son away again.
They won't.
Nie Chi must be tired.
Let him rest well.
Let's go out and talk for a while.
Let's go.
You two stay here.
It's doomed.
When we get back,
Mr. Li will definitely scold us badly.
Why do I think that he isn't angry?
Not angry?
Like that...
Wasn't he angry?
But Mr. Li is talking with his parents.
I won't beat around the bush.
I suggest
that you respect
Nie Chi's opinion.
I don't understand, Mr. Li.
Nie Chi is already injured like this.
Why do you, Lin Ge,
and all the people in your team
still let him continue practicing?
He can't even walk now.
How could he practice?
Let me put it this way.
In short track speed skating,
the waist, knees, and ankles
are the most easily injured areas.
I have been a coach for so many years.
Eight out of ten athletes
have knee injuries.
Nie Chi's situation is not the most severe.
He is very likely to recover.
You just say words that sound good.
It's not like that.
This is the conclusion of medical experts.
As the head coach of the national team,
I take responsibility for every player.
If Nie Chi just gives up like this,
it's really a pity.
Nie Chi is lying in the bed, unable to move.
We care about him the most.
I am also a parent.
I can feel your pain.
Let's think from a different perspective.
If you force someone
to give up his dreams
and do things that he doesn't like,
isn't this person even more pitiful?
All right, all right.
Don't talk to me about dreams.
Children's dreams are all fanciful.
Only by sending him abroad now
to receive a better education
can he have a better future.
For parents, children are always children.
But Nie Chi has already grown up.
He has the right to choose his own life.
I still have that suggestion.
Listen to his thoughts more.
You tell me
what we should do now.
Where are you going to go?
Mr. Li, we are going to check on you.
We're afraid you can't persuade them.
What will you I do if I can't?
Are you planning to run away again?
It's not impossible.
You...
Let's go back to the team.
What about Nie Chi?
He will be in the hospital.
Where else can he go?
Won't he go abroad?
Nie Chi, we gotta go.
You rest well.
- Ok.
- As for your parents,
talk to them properly.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
Thank me when you can stay.
I will do my best.
We're off.
Come on.
What specific exercises need to be done?
At this stage,
the key is to rehabilitate his knee
back to a level
for daily activities.
What should we pay attention to?
At the early stage of rehabilitation,
he will definitely feel pain.
Especially the injured area.
He should avoid large bending movements.
Is there any way
to recover a bit faster?
Rehabilitation training can't be rushed.
It needs to be done step by step.
If you want to help him recover faster,
you can conduct rehabilitation training
for uninjured areas
to prevent muscle wasting.
Secondly,
conduct appropriate cardio training
to maintain good physical function.
Chi, time to eat.
I brought you some bone broth
to nourish your body.
I can't drink this soup.
This was not bought outside.
I brewed it at home.
I also selected the bones personally.
I knew you need to eat light food
after the surgery,
so I only added a bit of salt
and didn't put anything else in it.
Not because of this.
Your mom simmered soup all afternoon
to nourish you.
Can't you even take a sip?
Dad, Mom,
you may not know
that one positive drug test
may affect the entire career of an athlete.
So athletes must be very cautious
about the food they eat.
Because of this,
I haven't eaten the meat
outside for many years.
I haven't taken good care
of you all these years.
I didn't even know these things.
It's not that.
I should apologize to you.
I've made you anxious these days.
Actually, I deceived you when I promised
that I wouldn't get hurt.
As an athlete,
it's inevitable to have injuries.
But the reason I insist on this
is that I learned it from you.
I remember when I was very young,
Dad was unemployed
and he took the only savings
to go into business.
That's why we have our good days now.
Dad, you know what?
Actually, you are my idol.
Back then,
I was taking a gamble.
It's different from your situation.
We have good living conditions now.
Mom and Dad will fully support you
to study at a well-known school abroad.
In this way
you will have a better future, right?
I know all this.
And I also know many people
advised you not to act impulsively.
But you still made your own choice.
I also don't want to disappoint my dreams
and the people who love me.
So...
So please let me be stubborn once.
(Honorary Champion Wall)
(Apartment)
- Lin Ge.
- Gao Kai.
How is Nie Chi recovering?
A bit better.
But not so quickly.
Don't worry.
As the saying goes,
it needs a long time to recover.
All right, thank you.
I gotta go.
Gao Kai,
I have a question to ask you.
Many business people add me on WeChat.
I am not experienced.
I don't know how to refuse them.
Aren't you short on money?
Why refuse?
This season is quite important to me.
I can't be distracted anymore.
Just be courteous.
Give yourself some leeway.
Thank them first.
Say you'll focus more on the competition
and you may cooperate in the future.
All right, thank you.
Keep it up.
Lin Ge. Lin Ge.
What's up? What happened to Nie Chi?
It's not Nie Chi.
Someone claims to be your town fellow
and insists on seeing you.
I don't know what's going on.
My town fellow?
Are you looking for me?
It's Lin Feng's sister, right?
I'm Wu Jie, Lin Feng's friend.
Do you still remember me?
When you just got home in your teens,
I stopped you with Lin Feng
and you scratched my face.
You don't look like a good person.
I don't remember. Get to the point.
Lin Feng is hospitalized.
He needs to undergo surgery now.
But no one signs it right now.
I really have no way.
I remember he has a sister in Beijing.
You are his sister.
The hospital will allow you to sign.
I'm not going.
I have no relationship with that family.
Ask his grandma to sign it.
What are you doing?
He is currently in the hospital.
He needs to undergo surgery now.
His family must sign it.
How can I have time to find his grandma?
Who knows if what you said is true?
If you are really Lin Feng's friend,
you should know
how his family treated Lin Ge.
How could you come here?
- It's a matter of life and death.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Who are you?
What's going on, Lin Ge?
Her brother is now in the hospital.
He needs to undergo surgery and has no money.
I really have no way.
Her brother? What surgery?
Lin Feng and I work at a construction site.
Lin Feng fell from the scaffold
and was pierced by a rebar.
Just come with me to take a look.
Just take a look.
Is Lin Feng's family here?
Lin Feng's family.
- Doctor, this is his sister.
- Lin Feng's family?
All right.
Doctors from related departments
conducted a consultation for him.
Lin Feng's current situation
definitely requires surgery
to remove the steel bar.
Do you agree with this plan?
- Agree.
- All right.
Once the test results come out,
the surgery can be performed.
The doctor performing the surgery
will talk to you again shortly.
Do as you say, doctor.
All right, then come with me.
Let her stay here, ok?
- Ok.
- Let's go.
Call his grandma first
and explain the situation to her.
If she needs me to sign,
then I will sign.
In case something happens in the end,
she will blame it on me.
I've already made the calls,
but his grandma didn't pick up.
Call her as she said.
Don't dilly-dally.
Manager.
Lin Ge.
I talked to the doctor about his situation.
The surgery cost,
including the follow-up treatment costs,
is not low.
I've paid the money in advance.
No.
You said that the cost is not low.
I have to find a way myself.
Will you tell Nie Chi about this?
Don't tell him for now.
Don't tell the others when you get back.
You can not tell others.
Why don't you tell Nie Chi either?
He's working hard on rehabilitation.
He is already under a lot of pressure.
I can't help anything with him,
I shouldn't add to his troubles.
Fine.
I've been busy with training these days
and haven't had time to see you.
(Lin Ge)
It's ok.
I have been recovering well these days.
Focus on your training.
I miss you very much.
Me too.
Don't be too anxious.
Listen to the doctor.
(Lin Ge)
Don't be anxious in your training.
If there's anything, remember to tell me.
Ok. Good night and sweet dreams.
Good night and sweet dreams.
(National Ice Sports Base)
Lin Ge.
Well, I need to tell you something.
Your grandma
has passed away.
The neighborhood handled the funeral.
I originally wanted my dad
to go to her place to get the money
for Lin Feng's surgery back.
But in the end,
my dad didn't receive a penny,
but spent over 1,000 funeral expenses.
That's Master's style.
What do you plan to do next?
With Lin Feng's situation,
even after the surgery is done,
he won't recover in a short time.
We can't earn much anyway.
You have spent all of your money, huh?
No worries. I still have some money...
Don't worry about money.
Don't tell your dad and mom either.
I will think of a solution myself.
Sorry, I'm late.
It's ok. I just arrived too.
Their food don't contain
illegal additives.
You should be able to eat it, right?
I can try a little bit.
Mainly because the calories are too high.
About the live broadcast,
how have you considered it?
I'm really sorry.
Our team is collaborating with a brand.
It should be your competitor.
I'm afraid I can't do it.
Don't reject me so quickly.
We can't make it clear over WeChat,
so I want to meet and talk.
First of all,
the part you are involved in
doesn't involve brand promotion or sales.
This is a co-branded
charity activity that we are doing
together with the chamber of commerce.
We come to you
because we hope you can
support our products as a star.
You just need to say a few words.
Secondly,
in terms of price, we are very sincere.
You can take a look.
(100,000 yuan)
We know about the competitor.
But after the World Championship,
your contract with them should be expired.
The live broadcast
is before the World Championship, right?
We say it is a live broadcast,
but in fact, it is pre-recorded.
We invite you to our company
to shoot a video,
and we broadcast it when the time comes.
See, there is a time on it.
(Broadcast time)
It's stated clearly.
It is after the World Championship, right?
Moreover,
we have four or five candidates.
But I come to you first.
We have been in contact before.
And I especially like you.
I really want to give you this opportunity.
Thank you.
Can I take this contract
back to have a look at it?
I'm willing to let you take it back.
But my colleague
is also in contact with others.
If they sign it first,
I might not be able to wait for you.
Well...
I heard your brother is having surgery.
It must have cost a lot of money.
How do you know?
I am the PR for the brand.
I did some research.
But you can rest assured.
I would never tell others
about this matter.
Don't worry.
It must be after the World Championship.
(Live broadcast cooperation contract)
keep it up!
Mr. Li, I'm sorry.
What's the use of an apology?
What is the qualifying round?
It is to qualify for the next round.
What did you do?
To compete for first place in the group,
you can't make it to the 1,000m semifinal.
What I'm thinking is to achieve first place,
I can stand on the innermost lane next round.
What about now?
Where can you stand? In your dream?
How is your injury?
I can hold on.
Tomorrow, the 500m semifinal and final
will still be led by Xie Lingwei.
- Mr. Li...
- You're not convinced, huh?
You tell me who should be the main force.
Zhu Zhu.
Let me help you to the team doctor.
Doctor, I'm leaving.
Ok, have a good rest.
Prepare well for tomorrow's match.
Doctor,
is my leg injury getting worse again?
Just tell me directly.
I can handle it.
Wait until the coach and manager get here.
Is there really no way?
Yes, surgery is the only option.
Give me an injection.
I've made my decision.
Nonsense!
Li, say something.
Mr. Li,
only I made it to the next round of 1,000m.
We can't give up the gold medal, huh?
Moreover, if I don't compete this time,
I don't even know if I have a chance
in the next match.
Mr. Li.
Go ahead.
Zhu Zhu stays in the lead.
Cross the line. Zhu Zhu is the champion.
An unexpected incident happened.
Zhu Zhu fell down.
The fall after the match
may be due to her exerting
too much effort during the match.
Hope she is fine.
(Beijing Station)
But for veteran Zhu Zhu,
this is another highlight moment
in her career.
Congratulations to her!
♪I've moved on♪
♪I'm sad and restless♪
♪But I forgive you♪
♪I shouldn't have been obsessed with you♪
Are you ok?
Don't you need to compete?
Go get ready. Get out.
- How is it going?
- The same issue.
The effect has gone.
- Lin Ge.
- The pain affected her activities.
♪The past and former days♪
I won.
♪Let it go with the flow♪
You are the world champion now.
♪Behind those smiles with tears♪
♪Is silence♪
♪Wave my hand♪
Next up is
the women's 500m final.
Please start warming up
immediately.
The final is about to start.
(Beijing Yuefei officially announced
(that Lin Ge has become)
(the new brand spokesperson.)
Lin Ge, you took on the endorsement?
(Lin Ge has become the new spokesperson.)
Why did they announce it?
When did you take on the endorsement?
Shouldn't it be announced after the match?
At such a critical moment,
how can you do that?
Don't worry.
It must be after the World Championship.
The match has not yet started.
The camera is on the head coach
Li Haifeng and two athletes.
How are you preparing?
- Mr. Li.
- Li Haifeng should
- be giving them some reminders.
- What happened to you two?
- Yes.
So serious.
Put aside all distractions,
don't think about anything and stay calm.
Have you memorized the tactics?
Xie Lingwei tries to get first place.
Lin Ge, be ready to provide cover.
Get ready.
Please prepare for your entrance.
Go, Team China!
Wei,
let's rely on our own abilities this time, ok?
Ready.
Very good.
Lin Ge is still firmly holding the position
for Xie Lingwei.
Is there a change in tactics?
Lin Ge overtook Xie Lingwei.
Xie Lingwei fell off the track.
The European player overtook Xie Lingwei
and collided with her.
Hold on, Lin Ge.
Xie Lingwei, speed up.
There is one last lap left.
Hang in there, Lin Ge.
(It's my first time to see the rink this way.)
(Perhaps it will be the last time.)
(National Ice Sports Base)
Mr. Li asked me to give this to you.
(Songbei)
Take care.
(Some people compare life to a bowl.)
(As long as you hit the bottom,)
(any direction you go is uphill.)
(If that's really the case,)
(then my life)
(is probably a bottomless broken bowl.)
(I keep falling deeper.)
(New troubles are always waiting for me.)
(I can't hate anyone.)
(And I have to keep dodging.)
(The person whom I should say goodbye)
(is the one I can't face.)
(Room 306)
Nie Chi, bad news.
Lin Ge...
Lin Ge was returned to the provincial team
by the coach.
What are you doing?
I will go find Lin Ge.
Are you crazy?
How are you going like this?
I don't care.
I can't let her go back alone.
Ok, I'll go with you.
What are you doing?
Nurse, I want to leave the hospital now.
How is that possible?
You're not fully recovered yet.
I have an urgent matter. I want to leave now.
Then I'll ask the director first.
Slow down, slow down.
- It's from Lin Ge.
- Read it.
I have returned to the provincial team.
Sorry. I didn't say goodbye to you in person.
I'm feeling very confused right now.
I want to be alone for a while.
Don't worry about me.
I will take good care of myself.
Do the rehabilitation well.
Hope you get better soon.
Sorry, the number you dialed is...
What's going on?
It's powered off.
♪Tears in my heart♪
♪I've moved on♪
♪I'm sad and restless♪
♪But I forgive you♪
♪I shouldn't have been obsessed with you♪
♪Should I leave or stay♪
♪I can give up my dignity♪
♪That I care about♪
♪The past and former days♪
♪All have gone♪
♪Let it go with the flow♪
♪Memories are close at hand♪
♪Behind those smiles with tears♪
♪Is silence♪
♪Wave my hand♪
♪Perhaps after I grow up♪
♪I keep tears in the heart♪
♪Unknowingly, I already regret it♪
♪I'm sad and restless♪
♪But I forgive you♪
♪I shouldn't have been obsessed with you♪
♪Should I leave or stay♪
♪I can give up my dignity♪
♪That I care about♪
♪The past and former days♪
♪All have gone♪
♪Let it go with the flow♪
♪Memories are close at hand♪
♪Behind those smiles with tears♪
♪Is silence♪
♪Wave my hand♪
♪Perhaps after I grow up♪