Seriously, what is this?
What do you even mean
when you say you're probably in love with me?
Since the day you came,
everything's been messed up!
About the eggs...
Mom's were creamier.
They were so delicious.
But... it's not like Madoka-san's
weren't tasty.
It's fine. I understand.
Morning.
Good morning.
Are you alright?
You should rest today.
No, I have a test soon.
You do? Don't ovedo it.
Okay.
Ah, I made dashi.
Could I leave the rest to you?
You won't be eating breakfast?
As expected, I have no appetite.
I'm heading out.
Take care.
I will.
Morning.
Sorry.
Did something happen with Sayuri-chan?
Why?
It's just that...
You took care of her when she was sick, so
I thought you started acting sisterly, and yet...
But I guess things can't work out overnight.
It's hot.
Hey, you'll catch a cold!
Then don't pass it on to me.
Anyway, put this on.
Thanks.
Did something happen at home?
Why?
It's just that you haven't stayed over lately.
Yeah...
It's comfortable here.
What?! Move, move!
What is it?
Found it!
I've been looking for it for ages!
I'm so glad!
Don't forget your stuff here, like a lover.
What if my girlfriend had said
"Hey, Nao-kun, what is this?!"
What would you have done?
Girlfriend? Where? Where?
Shut up!
Well, there may be plans to
get you one soon. A girlfriend.
What kind of plans?
What kind of face is that?
Handsome?
Apologize to all the handsome men in the world!
Should you be saying stuff like that?
Face your manju punishment!
No! Ow ow ow!
Seriously.
Ow! No way!
What is it with you?
That's dangerous.
Go to sleep.
You damaged your manga, didn't you?
You... seriously.
Incoming call: Shida Yui
You should sleep because you had a cold.
How's it been since your dad remarried?
What do you mean?
They're good people at heart, right?
Both your new mother
and sister.
Speaking of which,
your dad got himself quite a catch.
Your new mother is very beautiful.
I guess.
But...
How should I say it...
I can't figure out that person.
Yui-san.
What is she like, honestly?
What is she...
She has a kind side.
Yeah.
She understands things about me...
Such as?
About mom and such.
I see.
But I'm not entirely sure...
Huh?
Is it fine the way things are?
Somehow...
She doesn't feel like an older sister at all.
This is a free fansub by Sanashi @ D-addicts
Not for sale or rent! Don't upload to streaming sites!
I wonder who it is at this hour.
What happened?
Sayuri-chan is at your place, isn't she?
She is.
Thank goodness!
Have you been looking for her this whole time?
Ah, no, it's fine.
I'm sorry for coming so late at night.
Well then, good night!
She was seriously worried!
Why didn't you tell her you'd be staying over?
Hey, are you listening?
Huh? Ah, yeah.
Is something wrong?
Say, Nao...
Yeah?
Have you ever kissed someone?
What?
So you haven't.
Of course I have!
Ooh? Who, who?
Well, you haven't either, have you!
What?
What?!
I haven't.
Yeah.
What I mean to ask is,
when do you normally do that?
When do you normally...
Would you like to try and see?
Don't be stupid!
Ok, I'll be sleeping downstairs.
Thanks.
I missed this smell.
In the past, we used to sleep side by side, right?
I'm turning off the lights.
Night.
Here.
Thanks.
I've been thinking...
Yes?
Maybe we were being unreasonable.
What?
This house has become uncomfortable
for Sayuri-chan to live in.
Isn't that why she's staying over
at the house next door?
What's wrong with doing that
from time to time?
Keigo-san.
Look...
We don't have to be fixated on marriage, right?
I wouldn't mind us living apart.
Ah! Hey, do you mind if we go in?
Alright, let's go, let's go.
Ah, how cute!
Ah!
Wow, it's so cute!
What is this?
For the door?
How cute!
I've been thinking about
replacing my slippers.
Those are cute.
Right?
What's this?
What's that?
Ah, it's a magnet.
The pink one is cute. Is this genuine?
Let me see.
Come in.
Welcome home.
What is it?
What?
Take this.
For me?
Can I open it?
Different color?
Because it's weird for you to
still be using guest slippers.
How cute.
Thank you, Sayuri-chan.
I'm off.
What should we do today?
It's been cold lately, so I don't
feel like going to the park.
But I don't feel like going straight home either.
Sorry, I have plans today.
I'll head home first.
Hey, didn't Sayuri have a skip in her step just now?
She did.
This is good.
Thank you.
I can't take photos like this,
but they're good.
Saeki-san's photos
have incredible energy.
That is why I love them.
Just the photos?
Even now,
my feelings for you...
This is a free fansub by Sanashi @ D-addicts
Not for sale or rent! Don't upload to streaming sites!
I'm home.
What?
How should I say it...
Yes?
Is Saeki-san just your boss?
Aren't you actually dating?
I am not dating him now.
My mind is all muddled already!
What do you even want?
You're the only one acting indifferent.
First and foremost,
suddenly showing up at my house,
saying don't mind living with me,
suddenly kissing me...
saying you want to know me,
saying you want to touch me,
saying you love me.
Always looking like you know everything.
Then actually really understanding
everything about me.
Going out to find me,
even though no one asked you to.
Steadily finding your way
inside my heart.
By doing that, you...
Maybe you were teasing me,
or having fun by doing that.
I've been feeling confused,
since the day you came.
It's driving me crazy!
Ever since that day,
I can't stop thinking about the kiss.
I saw you with Saeki-san just now,
and I felt so annoyed.
What is this? Could this be jealousy?
I thought to myself.
I actually realized that I didn't mind kissing you.
Not at all.
I thought how I'd like to kiss you again.
See, I've already gone crazy, right?
I don't even recognize myself anymore.
Doesn't this mean...
that you love me too?