It's alright for us to love each other, right?
Yes.
Are you serious?
I'm sorry.
What did Yui-chan say?
She said she was serious.
Welcome back.
Do you both have a minute?
Sayuri...
I still don't really understand.
What is the meaning of this?
Are you seriously...?
Sayuri, I won't understand if you keep quiet.
Are we doing something wrong?
Is it because we're both girls?
Or because we're sisters?
We aren't doing anything wrong.
I am serious about this.
Sayuri is so cute
and important to me.
I don't want to lose her.
I want to be proud
of my love for Sayuri.
Yui.
Stop.
Just stop.
Prayer; Name: Hayama Sayuri
May I find: my fated person, dreams, Tiffany's double heart
This is a free fansub by Sanashi @ D-addicts
Not for sale or rent! Don't upload to streaming sites!
Thank you.
The person you have dialed can't take your call now...
Why weren't you at school today?
My sister...
Did something happen to your sister?
Yui...
left.
Are you okay?
Here.
Thanks.
What do you mean she left?
Don't be shocked, ok?
Don't be weirded out.
What is it?
You see, I...
It's okay.
Even if you say "I'm not actually a manju,
I'm a melon bread," I won't be surprised.
I...
love my sister.
Yeah.
I noticed, somehow.
What?
I've been watching you since we were kids.
So it's not really surprising.
Right.
That's right.
But it's over already.
I see.
I hurt Yui a lot yesterday.
When I woke up this morning, she was already gone.
I can't reach her phone, either.
I went looking for her
but I couldn't find her.
Yui was always finding me...
and I couldn't find her.
I keep losing everyone I care about.
Sayuri.
I may not be the person you care about...
but I'm not going anywhere.
If you need someone by your side,
if it can be anyone,
I'll be there for you.
I'll always be there for you.
After all, I'm Superman, right?
Another.
You know, yesterday...
You were snoring.
I didn't!
You didn't.
Ow!
You know, my body is stiff from sleeping
on the floor to begin with!
Thank you.
And also...
I was unexpectedly dumped yesterday.
Sorry.
You're very cheeky for a manju.
You're using that line way too often.
My face has changed recently.
Morning.
Mirai, I need to talk to you when we get to school.
It won't take long.
Please.
What did you want to talk about?
It's about our conversation from before,
about the person I like.
Huh? Why are you bringing that up now?
"In the end, Nao was always by side."
"I realized I love him," is that it?
It's not.
You may think it's weird, but...
It's my sister.
The one I love is my sister.
I'm sorry, I don't understand you at all.
That's right. How could you.
But, she left the house
and I lost sight of a lot of things.
Nao happened to know about it,
so he kept me company, that's all.
I couldn't think of anyone other than myself.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand at all, but...
Not being able to think of anyone other than yourself when you fall in love...
That I understand.
And I don't think it's weird.
Huh?
Your sister is extremely beautiful.
I can somewhat understand why you like her.
And such things aren't unusual these days.
But...
I'm annoyed about the situation with Nao-kun.
I'm sorry.
Can I do it once?
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Your voice cracked.
Good afternoon.
Yui-chan!
What's wrong?
This is a free fansub by Sanashi @ D-addicts
Not for sale or rent! Don't upload to streaming sites!
Thanks for waiting.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry about the other day.
It was my fault in the first place.
It's not something that's any one person's fault.
If this is about Sayuri,
she's going to school every day.
Is that so.
I don't know how to say this,
but thank you for caring about Sayuri.
Okay.
About Sayuri...
Please don't worry.
I'm not keeping in touch with her.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Even I still don't know
what is the right thing to do.
Don't be.
Say...
What Christmas present would make Sayuri happy?
I have no idea what a 3rd year high school girl wants.
Tiffany's double heart.
Double heart?
I think it's a necklace.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
Well then, excuse me.
I'm sorry for bothering you at work.
Say...
What do you want, Yui-chan?
What?
Present from uncle-Santa.
It was a short time,
but thank you for taking care of us.
Miso soup was delicious.
Madoka