"Jin Isoo
by Ahn Bohyun"
"Lee Ganghyun
by Park Jihyun"
"Park Junyoung by Kang Sangjun
Choi Kyungjin by Kim Shinbi"
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
IN SAFE SITUATIONS.
Everyone
has their own task
in their life.
But I've never believed that.
Living with no purpose
was not that bad.
But now...
a question was thrown into my life.
Now, I start my journey
to find an answer.
"Two months ago"
Mr. Choi.
Oh, you watched this?
"Jin Isoo vlog/free diving/dun-dun/Jaws!"
It's cool, isn't it?
Yes.
It's cool.
You didn't sleep well again?
No, I didn't. As always.
Management strategy meeting
begins in two hours.
What?
You should be there as the head
of the Management Strategy Team.
Jeez, I need more sleep.
Tell them I'm not available.
I'm so tired.
Where the hell are you now?
"A kidnapping case occurred"
A case occurred.
Get the support team ready.
- The status?
- 30 kidnappers.
VIP is on the top floor.
Are you okay?
It was fun.
Rescue completed.
It's all skinned!
Jeez... I got too much blood on my suit.
What if I can't get this stain out?
Hey?
Wow, you're a great actor.
I know I am.
You should pay for my laundry, though.
I'll pay double.
See you next time.
Okay, then.
Hey, wait.
You seem familiar.
No way.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's check
the damage.
It'll be cleared in three hours.
Jin Isoo, Jin Isoo!
Do wealthy people play like that?
He is different.
He even risks his life to play.
Stop there, Oh!
"Choi Kyungjin, Park Junyoung
Violent Crime Investigation Team 1"
"Oh Byeongsu
suspected murderer"
Stop? My ass.
Stop, you punk!
"Lee Ganghyun, leader
of Violent Crime Investigation Team 1"
"Danger"
You're arrested for a robbery and murder.
Drop the knife.
Shit! What you're gonna do?
You hit him with a car?
I used a taser.
How dare you! Jeez...
Damn it.
Where's your friend?
I don't know.
You see that?
Confess before it's recharged.
Or I'll shoot again.
-Please, don't.
-She will.
She put her life on arresting criminals.
Right.
I swear I don't know.
Three people died.
Stop lying.
I don't know who he is.
My cellmate introduced this job to me.
I thought the place was empty,
but he killed everyone there.
I was scared, so I just ran.
Call and summon him.
How can I do that?
-Kyungjin.
-Yes.
Okay, okay.
I'll do it.
Please don't use a taser.
Shit.
Goddamn it.
I'm calling now.
It hurts, I mean it.
Kyungjin, I'll write a report.
-You prepare a montage.
-Okay.
"Father, two children"
"Victim Park Eunah"
"stabbed in the stomach"
"Victims: Park Kiyul,
Park Eunah, Park Chaehyun"
"Oh Byeongsu, hammer
Accomplice, knife"
"Appointed place: Gangha-2 dong,
Food Alley next to Hansu Dpt."
Let's split into three groups.
Junyoung and Kyungjin take Oh Byeongsu
-to the appointed place.
-Okay.
-Don't get caught.
And team 2,
please stand by at the alley nearby.
Let's go.
He has slanted eyes
like an evil. More.
Okay, that's it.
And he had inner double eyelids.
He just looked like a chicken.
Is that a chicken?
I mean it. He has a chicken-like face.
Hey, Isoo!
We rented the whole club thanks to you!
Have a drink.
Where's Younghwan?
Huh?
My friend, Jin Isoo...
Younghwan, you, again!
Isoo, you want to try, too?
No, no...
No! Please... Don't!
Hey, hey!
I told you I'd never see you
if you did it again.
I can make your company closed.
Leaving?
Please pay for parking.
Get me my bike
and call a driver service.
Okay.
Stay put.
Hey.
Isoo, where are you?
Well...
Wasting my time somewhere.
I made it clear
you had to be at today's meeting.
I couldn't go due to the Code Zero case.
You played cops again?
Yeah, I rescued a super beauty today.
The press conference is due in nine hours.
Father would be humiliated if I go there.
Isoo...
Please listen to me.
Okay.
I'll be there in time.
Stop playing and go home.
Ganghyun barked up the wrong tree again.
How long should we stand by?
It's been two hours. He's not coming.
They say
it's time to close the bar.
Okay, let's wrap it up.
Thanks for your hard work.
Junyoung, take Oh to the station.
Mister...
Please give me a light.
Hey, hey...
Light...
- Light...
- Younghwan!
Please? Lend me a lighter.
What was that?
Damn it. Are you okay?
- It hurts.
- That punk.
Gosh...
Damn, it hurts.
What the hell?
You want to stab me, too?
I learned MMA professionally.
Goddamn.
Hey, stand up.
Hey
Get up!
Let go.
Hold on.
You're using a knife? How mean!
Go to hell.
Damn it.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey.
Damn it.
Are you his friend?
Which team are you with? SWAT?
Whatever! Get off of me.
What?
Are you pretending to be a cop?
Gosh...what?
You're arrested for a special assault.
You'll regret it.
You're here.
He's the youngest son of Hansu Group.
Jin Isoo.
Jin Isoo?
We arrested Jin Isoo?
-You know him?
-Of course, I do. He's a celebrity.
"Jin Isoo"
"Strategy Management Team, Hansu Group"
He's awesome, isn't he?
He's an attention seeker.
What a freak.
He rented a mall
for a survival game today.
Woah, he's awesome.
That freak is awesome?
He's the son of a rich family anyway.
How fun would his life be?
What's he saying?
Says his nose broke.
Let's go out for a soju.
- Yes.
- Lee Ganghyun!
What the hell did you do?
You did a great job.
The son of Hansu Group
instead of a murderer?
You even broke his nose!
He assaulted a passerby
in a drunken state.
Just release him.
Don't complicate the situation.
No, I can't. He was caught in the act.
What did you say?
Once we arrest someone,
we must investigate them.
It'll look weird
if we just release him now.
Don't interrupt.
Your team is such a mess.
We'll make it quick. Don't worry.
Stop making trouble.
Don't make a fuss, you punk.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Get it right.
Yes!
So...
What do we do now?
I don't know.
Why didn't you tell me
you're the son of Hansu Group?
You didn't give me a chance.
Look forward to the letter of complaint.
It must've been tough.
You can go home now, sir.
Okay. Remove it.
You expected this?
Sit down.
No special treatment.
Name, Jin Isoo.
Social security number is 92119...
What are you doing?
I'm investigating.
You assaulted a passerby
at 2:00 a.m. on September 4th.
Right?
No.
How about you?
Corrupt assault against the Act
on the Aggravated Punishment.
Right?
-How smart!
-Article 125 of the Crime Act.
If a judge, prosecutor, cop,
or any other individual
involved in the restraint
of the human body
commits violence or cruelty
against a criminal suspect
or another person
while performing their duties, they
shall be imprisoned for up to 5 years,
and their qualifications
shall be suspended for up to 10 years.
I have a lawyer's license.
In this case, you can be dismissed.
For what
did a rich son need that license?
Well...
Maybe I was too bored.
Corrupt assault?
But what if that was necessary
to arrest a flagrant offender?
So, what you did today...
playing a survival game at the mall,
drinking at a club,
and doing some drugs?
I'm not a junkie.
We'll see the test result.
A rich son who has nothing to do
and nothing to be scared of.
You've never taken
any responsibility, right?
You know me so well.
Are you my follower?
I just know it.
I know a lot of rich bastards like you
who are never indicted after arrest.
That's because of your incapability.
But I think I can do it.
He had a knife.
I protected myself.
There was no knife at the scene.
And I'm not the cop
who goes easy on someone
with money and power.
I do have money and power,
but it was clearly a self-defense.
My friend got hurt by his knife.
Call him and check.
Hello?
This is Lee Ganghyun
in Gangha Police Station.
Jin Isoo was arrested
as a special assault flagrant offender.
He says the victim had a knife
and you were stabbed.
-Is it true?
-No way.
Nothing like that happened.
Okay, thanks.
He says
it never happened.
Maybe your friend
doesn't want to lie.
Make a call.
You'll need
expensive lawyers.
I don't need a lawyer.
I did nothing wrong.
Take off your shoes.
Jeez...
An innocent civilian is caught.
And your socks, too.
My socks?
It's part of the process.
Okay, then.
Jeez...
Why didn't you hold me?
Hey, hold on.
I'm so thirsty.
Can I have an iced Americano?
How many are here?
It's on me.
Okay?
Woah!
You're Jin Isoo, right?
I'm your big fan.
Oh, are you? Okay...
You should do it like this.
Oh, yes.
Don't get too close to me.
-Okay.
-Please sit down...
Sit down.
Goddamn it!
Somebody puked here.
What did he eat?
Hey, someone puked here!
Gosh...
Get some sleep.
Damn it.
Hey, Chohui.
Guess who we arrested today.
It's someone huge.
I shouldn't say his name,
but he is
Jin Isoo.
Not Chang Isoo, but Jin Isoo.
Isn't it awesome?
So, I...
"Lee Giseok
reporter in SBC"
Mr. Park!
Wedding plan's going well?
Oh, hello, Mr. Lee.
Let's eat together
before your hell gate opens.
Yes, why not?
Get me a drink!
Get some drink!
Hey, shut up, there.
What are you?
Here's your statement.
Where's Isoo?
He's coming in time.
Assign Isoo
to the overseas branch.
He's a failure.
I put everything on the line.
I'll definitely win.
A failure shouldn't walk around
at this crucial moment.
You look great, honey.
Hello.
I'm the chairman of Hansu,
Jin Myeongchul.
I'm here today
to give you an announcement
which is very important.
My father, the former chairman
always said to me,
"You're the one who decides
and takes responsibility."
"No matter how hard it is,"
"always take the right way,
not an easy way."
"Candidacy declaration
For better Seoul"
I, Jin Myeongchul,
will run for the mayor of Seoul,
which I believe is the right thing to do.
All those charity
and scholarship work
which you've done so far,
were for the election?
I firstly
made a support foundation
25 years ago.
If I had known this at that time
I'd not be here today.
I'd be a fortune-teller.
Your rival is a leading member
of the ruling party.
Do you think you can win?
You would know better than me
what I've gone through to be here.
I never play
a game I'll lose.
Do you know
your youngest son is detained
in Gangha Police Station now?
I heard the victim is unconscious now.
"Assault case at dawn
by an immature rich son."
Hey, Jin Isoo.
Jin Isoo!
Gosh... It's cold.
Bro!
-Just keep sleeping.
-Oh, okay.
Come out.
You should've got it right.
You detained a suspect without checking.
Just say it.
I'm waiting.
-Waiting for what?
-Apologize when you made a mistake.
A mistake?
You know I was right.
I misunderstood I could arrest anyone
in the criminal act even if he's rich.
Next time you get caught,
you'll never escape again.
Why don't you reflect
on what you did first?
Hey.
Mr. Choi.
Gosh, my nose hurts.
Please get in.
Okay.
Father.
The press conference
went well?
Please leave them alone.
I told you to behave
until the election ends.
Is it that hard?
You know what you've done?
Something that you hate, maybe.
What's your limit?
I don't know.
I didn't hit the rock-bottom yet.
I shouldn't have let you in
in the first place.
It was my mistake
to try to bear you as a son.
You tried to bear me?
I didn't know that.
Seungju,
you're my only son from now on.
Fire Jin Isoo.
Our legal team will leave this case.
Whether you go to jail or pay a fine,
handle all of these...
on your own.
You...
are nothing without me.
Jeez...
Why didn't you call me?
I didn't want to bother to.
It's not a big deal.
You didn't want to humiliate him, right?
Why didn't you just tell him?
It's not that.
You know I'm a mess.
I've been Father's...
no...
the chairman's failure.
I'll talk to Father for you.
And...
I'll settle all things down. Don't worry.
Seungju.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It was not my fault.
You should've got it right.
He had a knife.
I protected myself.
"Fingerprint chekced"
"Background check result"
Are you sure?
Yes, I checked with Oh Byeongsu.
Goddamn it.
Who is he?
Lee Changhyun, a 43-year-old man
with two convictions for robbery.
I have only six months to retire, damn it.
What's your plan?
How will you make up for it?
I'll release Jin Isoo first
and announce the result.
Announce?
What will you say?
Get out.
I told you. Get out.
Isn't Jin here for assault?
That's what we thought
but the victim was a murderer.
A murderer?
Of the Gangha 2-dong case.
The family murder?
Keep it down.
It's confidential.
-Check it out.
-Yes, sir.
It's going to be
a bombshell when revealed.
Tell them it was Ganghyun's own decision
and cancel her position.
That's not bad,
but I'm not sure if that'd be enough.
Because of her father's case
the press will like it.
Excuse me, sir.
You have a guest.
I told you not to interrupt.
You have the same issue as mine.
So, let me interrupt.
I don't need any drink.
Have a seat.
Well...
What do you mean by the same issue?
My brother caught an offender
of a robbery and murder case of a family.
That's our issue, right?
It's not your fault.
It's you who found out he was the culprit.
They've got a good reason to kick me out.
I'll go talk to them.
Don't take my side.
I should take
the responsibility anyway.
So, we're planning
to release your brother immediately
and close the case as self-defense.
You think...
that's enough?
Our chairman's declaration for candidacy
was insulted.
We'll take the responsibility
for all of those--
Responsibility...
That's the word
for those who are capable of it.
Your plan is just...
to cover everything,
isn't it?
To keep the dignity of the police
and restore
the chairman's image
I suggest this.
You should take action right now.
Oh...
Coffee? Nice!
Yeah, yeah, enjoy it.
Oh, I'm finally breathing.
And get changed.
Gosh, it stinks.
You can drink it at a time like this?
How's your nose?
Don't ask. I can't even breathe well.
That fuzz...
I don't even know her name.
I'll sue her.
A criminal complaint for corrupt assault
and you...
By the way,
what about me?
Self-defense, right?
You are so lucky.
Lucky? I broke my nose
and slept next to an old man in a jail.
The guy you caught
was a murderer...
What?
of a family murder case in Gangha 2-dong.
No way.
So, I'll get an award
for good citizenship or something?
It's more than that.
You'll get to work...
as a police officer.
What?
We'll tell them he's been working
as a cop for two months.
He can be specially employed
with the lawyer's license.
He's been working together with cops
to catch the murderer.
It's our story.
Wait...
You think that makes any sense?
Make it make sense.
You'll do the press conference.
Sir...
you can't cover it like that.
Let's just...
process it by the book.
What?
By the book?
"The son of a chairman caught a murderer"
"that police has failed to catch
for two months."
Sounds good?
What if we tell them
the police arrested that brave civilian
and broke his nose?
Your team would be broken up
to be sent to local offices
with 3-month wage cut.
If they want,
you could be dismissed.
You want to be like your dad?
You really want that?
It's not only for you.
It could humiliate the whole organization.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Me working as a cop all of a sudden?
Upper line also agreed with it.
It's the only way.
We'll let Jin work at our station
and announce that
he's been investigating with us.
We've already talked about it
with Hansu Group.
He won't hold it out
for a long time, anyway.
This is good for everyone.
Father runs for the mayor for our country,
and you become a cop
to serve for the society.
This will also restore your image.
What's there to restore?
I already have a good image.
Good image on SNS?
That's not real.
That's why I like SNS.
They like me for no purpose.
What if you are indicted
for assault and go on trial?
Do you think
they'd still like you?
Do you think so?
We agreed to cooperate,
so it won't be that hard.
Just behave yourself
until the election ends.
Okay.
Let's just think
that you're playing cops, as always.
No way.
I won't do that.
This mayor election
had been
Father's long-cherished ambition.
People are now laughing at it.
That's none of my business.
You heard it earlier.
We're not a family now.
We'll announce
the investigation result
for the family murder case
and Jin Isoo's assault case.
On July 3rd, Jin Isoo became a cop
through special hiring for lawyers
to work in the Violent Crime
Investigation Team 1
for the family murder case for two months.
He arrested the accomplice Oh Byeongsu
let him lure out the suspect
and started staking out at 12:00 a.m.
with the whole team.
And at around 2:00 a.m.
Jin spotted a suspicious man
and arrested the suspect.
Then, what about the exclusive report
by SBC?
That was...
a false report.
What was the process of his hiring?
It's you who copied it.
Stop copying other reporters' articles
and just check it by yourself!
Hang up!
You should've checked it as the chief!
Exclusive?
I swear I saw him.
Jin Isoo was detained in the station.
Hansu Group and Hwang Sunggu made it up.
It's Hansu Group.
So, don't complicate it anymore.
Let's say you made a mistake.
Get out.
It must have been tough, Manager.
I'm not a manager anymore.
I'm fired.
You can go now.
Hey, my friend Jin Isoo!
Who are you?
Hey, Isoo, I'm sorry.
Okay?
I shouldn't have done this
to you as a friend, but...
You know, I did a drug last night.
I'll get caught if they run a test now.
And I thought you'd be released soon.
Of course, you would.
You're the son of Hansu Group.
You'd get released
even if you killed a person.
Oh, I mean...
I know you're not that kind of guy.
Isoo...
I'm so sorry.
You want me to kneel down?
Hands off.
Annoying punk.
You got a treatment?
Uh? Yes...
Go, then.
One special set,
two beers, and one soju, please.
Okay.
Hello.
Thanks.
That silver spoon
took away the culprit from us,
and I lied to the whole citizens.
Jeez... What the hell is going on?
You had no other way.
By the way, I'm so excited. You aren't?
Okay. I won't ask you why.
We're working with a rich man.
No way.
What?
He wouldn't come to work
but just slack off.
Seriously?
Gosh, I was so excited.
Excited about what?
If someone with money and power
is in our team, it'd be so much fun.
He's rich and powerful
but thoughtless.
The youngest of a rich family
would just power-trip.
No way!
My bro Isoo isn't that kind of rich.
Bro?
His followers call him bro.
Don't even dream
of calling me like that.
Why would I?
Are you on a mission to provoke me?
Workplace harassment!
Correct.
No way.
He'll never come to work.
Mom!
Hello.
I'm the vice chairman of Hansu
Jin Seungju.
I'm here today
to notify
the truth
about my brother's case.
The truth is...
I need to get approval
for closing the case of Lee Changhyun.
Jeez...
Ganghyun, I'm so sorry.
You'll face a lot of trouble.
I'll be fine.
We prepared something
to cheer your team up.
Show them.
Team 2, Gangha! Get ready!
Hey! Gangha!
You got this!
Good luck!
Byungsik.
Yes?
It's not funny.
Really?
-It's not funny?
-It is.
This is why I told you
to pass this case on me.
You lost the culprit
and got a silver spoon.
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but that silver spoon
wouldn't come to work.
It's already half past 11.
That punk wouldn't even think
about coming here.
A red carpet.
Lay them all over.
Do we have an event today?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Ms. Lee.
Chief wants us to come down.
"Welcome, Senior Inspector Jin Isoo"
Detective Jin!
Senior Inspector Jin Isoo
has been working confidentially
after being specially hired.
He didn't want a special treatment.
He just wanted to work and investigate
like other cops.
But as people with talent
always stand out,
he ended up revealing his excellence
-in this murder case.
-Gosh... He's awesome.
A precious talent like him
joined the police,
so, we'd like to give a hearty welcome!
What are you doing?
Podori, applause!
You prepared flowers...
-Camera.
-Yes.
It's cute.
Thank you.
Huh?
Wow, you didn't have to prepare
this much.
Thank you so much.
Oh.
Let's work hard.
"Hansu Group's son Jin Isoo
to investigate criminals?"
Special thanks to Kim Kim Eui-sung,
Ahn Seho, Oh Heejun,
Baek Jongwon, Park Seri, Yoo Heekwan,
Jung Chansung, and Cho Guesung
Where's my desk?
Stay put doing nothing.
You'd better
not bother my work.
Had you investigated properly,
I'd never been bothered like this.
A dead body at a quay.
Her face looks familiar.
She's a model.
Only real cops
can get into the site.
Is she always oppressive
and overbearing like that?
He'll get him alone
and move out if he fails.
- Stick behind me.
- I'm a good fighter.
Ms. Lee.
Let's go. We're late.
Stay tuned for bonus clip
Wait.
You're under arrest
for Jung Ina's murder. Got it?
You have the right to remain silent
and challenge the properness of arrest.
Hey, Mr. Park!
Mr. Park! Mr. Park!
Damn it.
Translated by Hyeryung Kim