"Jin Isoo
by Ahn Bohyun"
"Lee Ganghyun
by Park Jihyun"
"Park Junyoung by Kang Sangjun
Choi Kyungjin by Kim Shinbi"
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
IN SAFE SITUATIONS.
I'm Lee Seongwook,
the manager of the Oryun Community.
I'd like to meet you.
I...
will reveal everything.
Wait.
Please...
Hey, wait. I'll...
I'll call Bori now. Wait.
Hold on.
"Park Junyoung"
Yes.
A dead body
was found in the Han River.
I'll be there. I'm around.
Police.
"ID card
Moon Dongsu"
Okay, confirmed.
Wait.
"A year ago"
Come in.
Chief.
Don't you feel hungry?
Come on in.
Why are you still working?
I just have something to think about.
What's that?
Hey.
Jeez.
Hey, Ms. Lee.
"Mass suicide in a motel"
Mind your own business.
- Okay.
-  Sit down.
"Suicides"
It's getting soggy.
He's here.
Do you plead guilty?
Dad.
You found his ID card?
Oh.
Yes.
It's a drowning case, right?
Junyoung.
On the body, I saw...
a tattoo of the Oryun Community.
My son, Dongsu,
was originally a good boy.
He changed last year.
He had a hard time
seeking a job
and suddenly said
he'd join a meditation center.
That's not a meditation center.
It was kind of a false religion.
They lure students,
saying it's a meditation center,
and make them their members.
- It's called the Oryun Community.
- Shut up!
Dongsu isn't that silly.
Mom, I've been there
to see what it is.
To settle there, he even used our names
to borrow money from a loan shark.
"The deceased, Kim Seonyoung"
I'm sorry, Mom.
Now I know...
how tough your life had been.
I really want to figure out
why you had to leave me like that,
but I'll stop that now.
As my name that you gave me,
I'll be someone helpful in this world.
So, please keep watching me.
"The deceased, Kim Seonyoung"
My brother...
was drowned to death?
Why are you so surprised?
Because it's impossible.
He was a survival swimming instructor.
Unless he was drugged or something,
- he couldn't die like that.
-  Right.
He swam across the Han River four times.
Then,
would you agree with his autopsy?
No.
- Your brother told us not to do that.
- Mom.
We want the autopsy.
It's a suicide letter.
Mr. An.
Send it to be analyzed.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
"Missed calls, 010-0287-5974"
Okay.
Let's go.
"Lee Ganghyun"
"Chief Park Changun"
Hello, sir.
Yes, sir.
You know Lee Seongwook, right?
Did you meet him recently?
- What's up?
- He killed himself.
What?
And the last person
he talked to was you.
Come on.
He committed suicide?
When?
Where and how did he die?
I'm asking you.
Why is your number on his phone?
What the hell did you do?
What's going on?
What's up?
A dead body was found
at the construction site this morning,
and we found Lee's name on his call list.
Did you talk to Lee Seongwook?
For what?
What was your plan this time?
You already know
that it's Lee Seongwook.
How did you know that?
- I was reported--
- The Chief is here.
Who were you reported from?
That's none of your business.
What happened?
It seems to be a suicide case.
We found a suicide letter.
- Okay, then. Wrap it up--
- This is not suicide.
He wanted to reveal everything
about the Oryun Community.
That's why he called me.
We were going to meet up.
Who on earth were you reported from?
Shut up.
- Are you interrogating me?
- Just answer me.
- Who was that?
- Shut your mouth.
I'm your boss.
I'm the captain, you punk.
You always overreact
every time
the Oryun Community is mentioned.
You...
are under probation from today.
Stay out of my sight for a week.
Get lost, punk!
Sir.
I'm just...
You saw she's out of her mind.
She could cause big trouble.
Don't share anything with her.
Yes, sir.
Ganghyun.
Yes.
Hey.
What's that face?
What's up?
No, it's nothing.
Hey, what's up?
Tell me.
Let's talk later.
I'm busy now.
Mr. An.
This is not suicide.
Let me see the suicide letter.
No, I can't.
Captain told me not to.
You owe me something.
Damn it.
I'm begging you.
You...
are not allowed to see this. Okay?
You got it? Jeez.
"30-year-old man who fell to death
Investigation report"
Hey.
You guys, come here.
You have coins?
You have some.
-  They're for later. Come on.
-  You have coins.
I should use them later.
Just come here.
What's up?
Why are they always talking alone?
They're supposed to share
everything about the case with us.
I don't think so.
That seems too complicated.
I don't want to get involved.
You're so cool in some ways.
I prefer simple life.
Hey, Park.
You looked so serious.
What's up?
Ganghyun is under probation.
What?
- Why?
- You don't need to know--
Why don't we? We're a team.
It's about a private matter.
Never mind.
Yes, sir.
We need to talk.
"Copy of the suicide letter"
It's been a humble life.
I lived frugally.
I'm sorry to my wife
who always cared about me.
I wanted to be a giver,
but no matter how frugally I lived...
"543 Seongan-ro"
Come in.
Salute!
Oh, Mr. Jin.
Have a seat, please.
Okay.
How's your work?
I'm just killing my time.
Just wait a little.
You'll be in a better position
after the election.
Right.
I'm here to ask you something.
Sure. Ask me anything.
Well,
I heard Ms. Lee is under probation.
Oh, that.
I'm so curious about everything.
But no one tells me anything.
Oh, really?
- Maybe everyone hates me.
- No way.
That can't be.
Well,
as you may have seen so far,
Ms. Lee is a bit thoughtless.
Oh, yes. Right. She's thoughtless.
Her father, Lee Hyungjun,
accepted a bribe before.
The father and daughter
are humiliating the whole organization.
She loses her temper
whenever that case is mentioned,
so I told her to take a rest.
Oh, I see. She lost her temper.
You don't need to care about that.
And, by the way...
when the chairman becomes the mayor,
please put in a good word
with your father for us.
Yes.
Of course, I will.
I'll talk to him for you.
- Thank you so much.
-  Okay.
Bambara bam bam!
Bambara bambam bbam bbam!
Dun dun dun!
"Samseonjang Motel"
I heard the news.
I don't know why he did it--
It's not suicide.
This morning,
he was going to meet me up.
He said he would reveal everything.
Didn't he leave anything to you
just in case?
No, nothing.
I'm sorry to ask you this all of a sudden,
- but you need to agree--
- No, I don't want the autopsy.
It could be a murder case.
You're Lee Hyungjun's daughter, right?
You kept calling my husband to bother him.
Why should I trust you?
I'm home.
-  Oh.
-  Hey.
You're early today.
Yes.
There's not much work.
-  Really?
-  Have you eaten?
Sure.
You told me to eat on time.
Have some.
It's good.
From tomorrow,
I'm off.
You're off?
You are? I see.
You have any plan?
How about a movie with me?
Oh, I'm going on a trip.
To where?
I reserved a temple stay.
Let me join you.
It's a meditation program
staying in a temple,
which is no fun at all.
Why don't you spend some time with me?
You can play with me.
Sorry. Maybe we can go together next time.
Okay.
"Lee Hyungjun"
"Mass suicide in a motel
Investigation report"
"Case report"
This case occurred
on October 26th, 2022
at 2:22 p.m.
In a motel in Gangha 2-dong,
three young people took poison
and were found dead.
Tablets including potassium cyanide
were found at the site,
and a suicide letter was found.
The letter said,
"It was so painful that
I had no other choice"
and "No autopsy, please."
Wheel tattoos found on the victims' bodies
turned out to be the same
as the emblem of the GY Meditation Center.
Therefore, this case can not be concluded
as a suicide case,
and it is clear that their suicide
was induced by the Oryun Community.
"Mass suicide related
to the Oryun Community"
As I mentioned earlier,
this is a case
where three young people died
even before they were 30,
which is a tragedy.
Apparently,
it seems like a mass suicide,
but we suspect
there was a community or a force
that induced their suicide.
We applied for a search warrant
for the GY Meditation Center
and the Oryun Community.
We'll continue
an additional investigation.
What's up?
Lee Hyungjun,
you're arrested for bribe acceptance.
"Urgent Arrest of Superintendent Lee
for Bribery Charges"
Mr. Choi.
Do you happen to know
about the Oryun Community?
I've heard of it from young entrepreneurs
that it's a kind of meditation center.
Please look into it.
Okay.
"Urgent Arrest of Superintendent Lee
for Bribery Charges"
How...
is Isoo doing these days?
He went back to the house.
It'll take some time,
but he'll understand.
I thought it would be easy
to be a good father.
My father had always been strict
and scary to me.
I thought at least I could do
better than he did.
Now I'm such a mess.
You're handling all stuff instead of me.
You'll have a chance to talk to him.
Don't worry.
He's getting used to the police work,
and he got some good friends there.
Seeing you're here again,
you must have a lot on your mind.
Here.
Why are you not asking?
I realized that someone
just standing next to you
could be so comforting.
And I can tell what it is.
I heard from the captain
about why the thoughtless Lee
lost her temper last time.
So, what are you going to do?
I don't know.
If you're to fight,
I'll be on your side.
You don't even know what happened.
You trust your father,
and I
trust you.
Right.
I trust my dad.
Dad was digging into the Oryun Community,
and I bet they set the trap.
For the past year, I tried to persuade
the manager of the community.
And today,
he told me he would reveal everything.
But he died
all of a sudden.
Now, I don't know what to do.
I'll just leave and take a break.
I have a villa on the beach.
You want to stay there?
I have a place to go.
If you change your mind
to stay at a luxurious villa,
call me anytime.
Jin Isoo, you're so cool.
What? Why?
About Lee Seongwook's case,
let me look into it for a few more days.
You know, I was accused
for urgent closing last time.
Okay. Get it right this time.
Yes, sir. Salute!
You're taking it again.
You take one.
Take care of your health.
Is it that good? Should I try one?
How about an article?
Did you finish it?
What article?
About Jin Isoo's mother.
Next week,
there will be a debate
for mayor candidates.
We'll blow it by then.
I didn't write anything.
What?
I wasn't sure
if it's within
the citizen's right to know.
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
I'm not a man without fault.
I know I'm a trashy reporter,
but I don't want to be a real trash.
I can't cross that line.
You punk!
You'd better be careful, too.
I heard some rumors about Wang Jongtae.
If you stand on his side,
you'll get embarrassed someday.
Rumors?
What is it?
Hey.
"Kim Jeongyeon"
Jeongyeon hasn't been here recently.
You didn't know?
She hasn't been here for weeks
working on an exclusive case.
Without my permission?
The phone is off,
and we'll connect you to voice mail
after the tone with extra cost.
You made gimbap?
Yes,
I prepared it for you
going on a trip in a long time.
Here.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
It's good.
Have it on your way.
Thank you, Mom.
Dad.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Have a great time.
-  Okay.
-  Good.
Call me.
I will.
She'll do well.
- I'm off.
-  Okay.
Good trip.
Why?
It's just...
She's weird, isn't she?
What's weird?
Something's up with her?
She's been busy,
so she just needs some alone time.
Just turn a blind eye to it.
Let's have gimbap.
I'll serve you some.
"A 30-year-old man's drowning case
in the Han River"
"Moon Dongsu"
"GY Meditation Center manager"
"drowned to death in the Han River"
"No wound, evidence,
Oryun Community tattoo?"
- Hello, Dr.
- Yoon.
Yes.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Where are you going?
To hear the autopsy result
for yesterday's case.
Let me join you, then.
You don't need to come.
Jeez.
You're so dull for a detective.
You still don't get it?
I'm a master key in investigations.
Let's go.
-  You're here.
- Yes.
What was that?
Is he an unexpectedly popular man?
The autopsy is finished?
Yes, just now.
He was drowned to death, right?
Right.
But
he didn't die in the river.
If he died in the river,
there should be plankton in his stomach,
but we found nothing.
Then?
He was drowned somewhere else,
and his body was thrown to the river.
So, it's a homicide, right?
If he was forced to be drowned,
bruises on the body
or anesthetic ingredients in blood
must be found.
But there was nothing.
The victim was an instructor
of survival swimming.
I really don't know how he died.
That's an emblem
of the Oryun Community.
Where was that found?
Here.
How do you know that?
I found it out by myself.
Because you guys don't share
any information with me.
Let's share
what is going on from now on.
This is not the kind of case
that you could poke around.
The honor of Ganghyun's father
depends on this case.
And it's also for capturing a cult leader
who killed innocent young people.
I'll take advantage of everything I have
to solve this case,
whether you help me or not.
"Samseonjang Motel"
Police.
Where
are the security cams here?
In the parking lot
and at the entrance.
Can I check them?
No one died here.
Why do you guys bother me?
Guys?
A female detective came here
and took the footage.
Please let me check it, too.
Two people related to the Oryun Community
died on the same day.
Lee Seongwook is a manager
and a key member of the community.
Moon Dongsu is the manager
of the GY Meditation Center,
which recruits Oryun's new believers.
Something must be going on
in this community.
You're investigating Moon's case, right?
What's up?
There are texts
between Lee and Moon.
They're on Telgram,
so we're analyzing it now.
What's the cause of death
of Moon Dongsu?
It's drowning.
His body was found in the river,
but it seems
that he was killed somewhere else.
How did Lee Seongwook die?
You can tell him. He's also in Team 1.
He fell to death.
A suicide letter was in his pocket.
We also got the security cam footage
from the motel he stayed.
I'll open it.
Okay.
This car is owned
by the GY Meditation Center.
If these guys killed Lee Seongwook--
No security cam is in this site,
so we can't prove the murder.
And it's hard to identify them with it.
But this footage
seems to have been checked
by Ganghyun yesterday.
What?
Do you know
where Ganghyun is now?
It might be hard to reach her.
She's in a temple stay.
This is tricky.
You're forwarded
to voice mail...
What's up?
This letter looks weird.
What's weird about it?
We confirmed his handwriting.
This story doesn't make sense.
He's always a bit off the wall.
It's been a humble life.
I lived frugally.
I'm sorry to my wife
who always cared about me.
I wanted to be a giver,
but no matter how frugally I lived
and worked hard,
I couldn't be rich enough.
Now is the time to unload everything.
- Goddamn!
- Jeez.
My gosh.
I made it again!
I'm so...
Am I... really...
Am I a born genius?
What the hell is it this time?
Come take a look. Come on.
Look.
What?
"Autopsy, please."
Autopsy, please.
Great job.
Do you know
who these people are?
They could have killed your husband.
This is his suicide letter.
Please agree
with the autopsy.
You don't know well
about the Oryun Community.
The primary doctrine
of the Oryun Community
is never letting a knife
cut a human body.
I'm a member of this community.
I met him there.
You don't want to catch the culprit?
My husband
just got an answer.
"Oryun, the five most important virtues
in Confucianism"
"GY Meditation Center"
Are you enduring
a tough time every day?
Do you have a grief you can't tell anyone?
We're here for you.
We'll bring peace to your mind.
I don't understand
what this community is for.
Mr. Choi.
Found out anything?
Yes.
A man called Bori in the Oryun Community
is popular among entrepreneurs these days.
Bo... what?
Bori?
It means, "I realized."
It sounds very superstitious.
To have a meal with Bori,
they should pay 100 million won.
100 million won?
Is he Warren Buffett or someone?
So, who on earth is Bori?
Little has been known about him.
He's covering himself thoroughly,
so no one knows his real name.
The Oryun community was founded
about 5 years ago.
But...
many members of the community
committed suicide.
Then, I need to find out why.
This case looks very dangerous.
I don't want you to get involved.
Then...
let me ask you a favor.
"Na Han Won"
So, is this the scene of exploitation?
Anyone needs a cop?
Police is here.
If you need a cop,
raise your hand.
"GY Meditation Center"
Get off, everyone.
Should we go?
Who is Bori?
Mr. Bori?
I'm the founder of this place.
You're so young and handsome
for a cult leader.
Are these people paid properly
for their labor?
All of us
are working to leave this mortal coil.
It's worth more than--
Nothing is worth more than money
in capitalism.
This is what we grew here.
Try it.
No, thanks.
What if you poisoned it?
"GY Meditation Center"
"Room 201
Lee Soeun"
Please go to your rooms
and come back after unpacking.
Please come in.
Okay.
Wait here, please.
I'll go get changed.
Sure. Take your time.
I have plenty of time.
You got a call, sir.
Jin Isoo is here.
Welcome to Na Han Won, everyone.
First of all,
we'll collect your cell phones
in this box.
During your stay here,
you'll learn
how to leave mortal coils
in this world.
Now, pour out all your thoughts
that harass you
onto this paper.
If you write them down sincerely,
Bori will give an answer to you.
Pass it, please.
I can't hold out anymore.
Please give me an answer.
Bori, please select me.
"Lee Soeun"
Smells good, right?
I only drink coffee.
Lee Seongwook was found dead.
I heard that.
That's...
too bad.
Why do so many people here
commit suicide?
Because they misunderstand me.
In this world, special people exist.
Some people read the flow
of the world economy.
Some create genius ideas,
and some people like me
realize the truth about life and death.
I was raised in an orphanage.
I always envied other people.
-  Mom.
-  Children with parents,
those raised at home,
-  I'm leaving.
-  Okay.
and lucky children
who don't need
other people's sympathy.
Everyone has to leave the orphanage at 18.
I headed to a construction site.
I worked sincerely at first,
but a resentment
started to build up in my mind.
"Why should I live like this?"
"I want to be rich."
"I'd be happy
only if I had a lot of money."
So I decided to work at a company
where anyone could be employed.
It was a pyramid selling job.
Yes.
It caused a foregone conclusion.
I fell into huge debt.
After being kicked out
from the rented room,
I thought about it for the first time.
"Should I just die?"
"How should I kill myself?"
I was thinking about it...
when I came to the huge realization.
Then, I finally realized
that I had already lived
five other lives before.
"Hanyang, A.D 1443 "
"Seongju, A.D 1866 "
"Gyeongseong, A.D 1932"
"Seoul, A.D 1967"
Everyone said I would die, but I survived.
I decided to live
to spread my huge realization.
I help hopeless people by telling them
there's next-born life.
But some people misunderstood that...
and committed suicide.
Gosh, I almost fell asleep.
At least, it's not like "I'm the God."
I'm glad about that.
But anyway,
it's just a well-made bullshit.
Mr. Jin Isoo.
You're living the second one now.
In the previous life--
Enough.
Stop talking about that.
You lost your mother when you were young.
She was a warm and kind woman,
but she committed suicide.
Don't you miss your mother?
She is living her next-born life now.
You might need some time to think.
How about staying here for a few days?
Wow.
Yeji, you eat so well.
It's good?
Yes.
In here,
I eat and sleep
better than usual.
You feel comfortable here.
Right.
Well...
I...
was guided here
by a manager called Moon Dongsu,
but I can't find him.
Oh, Mr. Moon.
Right. These days,
he's not been around.
He was called by Bori
and went to his private residence.
I haven't seen him since then.
His luggage is still in his room.
He might have some urgent business.
Well...
How can I
meet
Bori?
Oh.
It's your first time here, right?
Yeji is here for the third time,
but she still hasn't met him.
I see.
Write down
your long-cherished wish.
Your earnest wish
will reach the Heaven.
"Justice"
"Next-born life"
To wrap it up,
we give you a tea of peace.
You'll sleep tight tonight
with no agony.
How did you...
come here?
My father is missing
after borrowing money from loan sharks.
Mom
and I...
tried everything to pay it back,
but it only kept growing day by day.
I'd only been thinking
about dying while sleeping,
and I happened to know Bori.
If I could be born
in a rich family in my next life,
I'm willing to die anytime.
It's not scary to die,
it's scary to live,
isn't it?
They said I need to make an offering,
so I borrowed more money
but
I haven't got any answer
from Bori yet.
Maybe I need to pay
more money to get it.
Jin?
Why are you here?
And why are you here?
Get out.
Do you call this a temple stay?
What's that hair? Damn.
Stop joking.
Tell me why you're here.
To be saved and...
I wondered who Bori is.
You met him?
Sure.
I heard you need to level up to meet him.
I was born on a high level, you know?
Where are my slippers?
What did you talk about?
That was just...
a well-made bullshit.
That's not important now.
It's not the river
where Moon was not killed.
He was drowned first
and thrown to the river.
That's right.
I think this place
is the murder site.
What about Lee Seongwook?
It'll be closed as a suicide case.
May I ask why he was...
He was too greedy.
I warned him he could get hurt
by his greediness.
What did you do with Jin Isoo?
I threw him a stone.
You lost your mother
when you were young.
She committed suicide.
Don't you miss your mother?
You might need some time to think.
How about staying here for a few days?
Oh, should I?
An immature rich son
is not a big deal to you.
There's this one
who really bothers me.
Moon Dongsu
disappeared after coming here to see Bori.
He must've killed
somewhere inside here.
"Background check"
Lee Ganghyun.
She's Lee Hyungjun's daughter.
I ruled her out from this case,
but I don't know where she is.
Leave here right away.
You leave here first.
This place is very dangerous.
They don't go easy
on rich and powerful people.
You came to such a dangerous place alone?
You didn't even tell Junyoung, did you?
This is my job.
They could be in danger.
You...
You don't trust anyone.
Everyone's worried about you.
And I'm also your friend,
aren't I?
That's enough.
Take a picture of it
and send it to Junyoung.
They took my cell phone.
What?
They said
I should renounce the world first.
Why did you let them--
"The result of Isoo and Ganghyun's investigation
into the Oryun Community is?"
Something's up in there, right?
Where's Ganghyun?
Mr. Jin
sneaked into the community.
Jin!
Bori
will give poison at 9:00 a.m.
- We'll raid the scene.
- Okay.
Woohyuk will run away
after the plastic surgery.
You remember the one
with penetrating injury?
He was dead.
Get up!
How many people have you killed?
Those are all fake.
Who will get hurt
if you keep digging it?
Ms. Lee and Isoo are in danger.
- Changun!
-  We
will save Ganghyun.
-  I'll bring the support team. Go!
- Yes, sir.
You'll die here.
We're here. Hold out!
Wake up!
Wake up, Ganghyun!
Stay tuned for bonus clip
You're not allowed to be here.
Do you know where Ganghyun is?
I can't reach her.
Answer me.
I heard the news that Lee Seongwook died.
Something's going on
in the Oryun Community, right?
Right?
We don't share anything with--
Changun!
Ganghyun seems to be investigating alone now.
You get it?
Get out, please.
Please protect her.
I'm asking you.
Translated by Hyeryung Kim