"Jin Isoo
by Ahn Bohyun"
"Lee Ganghyun
by Park Jihyun"
"Park Junyoung by Kang Sangjun
Choi Kyungjin by Kim Shinbi"
THE CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS.
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
IN SAFE SITUATIONS.
"3 hours before the appointment ceremony"
Mr. Choi...
I need more sleep. Please...
Yes, sir.
Where's Isoo?
He's in bed.
-He's still in bed?
-Yes.
Wake up.
Gosh...
What's up at this early?
I'm tired.
And my nose hurts.
Get up, you crazy brat.
Didn't I tell you to go to work today?
No, I won't.
I told you I wouldn't.
What's wrong with you?
This is a different scale
from what you've done so far.
The honor of Father and our company
depends on you.
Why, in the first place,
have you involved me
in such a big matter?
That's...
Don't say like that.
I trust you.
You're making a mistake.
You'll regret
if you mess this up.
You want to disown your father like this?
Seungju.
Since I became Father's...
no...
the chairman's son,
my life has been a mess.
It's time to stop this mess.
He's gone?
For press conference.
He has one every day.
Does he enjoy it?
He'll announce
that everything was made up by himself.
He'll make up for it
by resigning from his position.
The chairman would cancel his candidacy.
Vice chairman will be kicked out
to the overseas branch.
What a good chance for his cousins
who had eyes on his position.
Hello.
I'm the vice chairman of Hansu
Jin Seungju.
I'm here today
to notify
the truth...
about my brother's case.
- The truth is...
- The truth!
I'll tell you myself.
Jin Isoo!
This is for you.
You knew he would come?
You didn't?
Isoo is a good boy.
How did you become a cop?
I was so into detective stories...
Detective stories?
How did you get the culprit?
I heard the accomplice didn't appear
at the appointed place.
Oh...
Well, during the stakeout
I just got an intuitive sense
like a kind of hunch.
"Incapable police needed my help"
Incapable police?
Do we have an event today?
Musicians!
Play it well today. Okay?
- Yes.
- Okay?
Pull it from the back. Pull!
More, more.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Chief wants us to come down.
Thank you.
Huh?
Wow, you didn't have to prepare
this much.
Thank you so much.
Oh.
Let's work hard.
Ms. Lee?
Damn it.
It's nice.
Neat and clean.
Where's my desk?
You don't need to come.
Why don't you go home?
Why are you being polite?
Just go home.
You don't need to do this.
Yes, I do.
When I commit, I give my all.
Commit what?
Playing cops?
Here's not your playground.
Why do you treat me like this?
You shouldn't do that.
Oh, these incapable police officers
are supposed
to give you a standing ovation?
Jeez... I've never said that in this way.
This is what reporters do, right?
But this is true.
So?
So what?
You'll come everyday
with a sense of duty?
Yes.
-Very sincerely.
-Then, I'll give you a piece of advice.
Stay put doing nothing.
Anything you hear or see in this place
is never allowed
to be uploaded to your SNS.
If you bother my work,
you're dead.
That's not one piece.
Let's go to the meeting.
I welcome you. Let's take a photo later.
That's your desk.
Let's go!
Okay.
Is that a hazing or something?
They're so childish.
Aren't they?
Oh, I'm fine.
It's so embarrassing.
Even a chair is a mess here!
I'll get you a new one.
Mr. Choi.
Get me new clothes
and do me a favor.
Please transfer Jin Isoo
to desk duty.
Desk duty?
He caught the culprit you failed to catch.
He's in your team now.
A police investigation
isn't a child's play.
He's an untrained citizen
and an immature rich son.
I'm sure he'll make trouble.
You should handle that
all by yourself.
It's you guys who caused all of these.
Please get the fact right.
It was decided by the upper line.
Then...
you just tell them the truth
and make up for it by resigning.
You want that?
That sounds good.
Forget it.
I'll handle him.
Watch him closely.
- Okay.
- Watch your mouth.
Yes, sir.
Start the reporting.
Yes.
Oh, you're up.
Yes, mom.
- Good morning.
- Yes.
I'm worried about Isoo.
He's not pulling himself together,
and now he became a cop.
I know Seungju had no other way, but...
I'm afraid he'd make any trouble.
I couldn't even sleep last night.
Isoo is not that immature.
Trust him.
My Seungju is so reliable,
but what's wrong with Isoo?
Mom.
Your mom isn't wrong.
Prepare to send him overseas
after the election.
He'll be a burden if I win the election.
Mom.
Please stop nagging on Isoo.
I've never nagged on him.
- That's all.
- Okay.
So, team 2 will focus
on the serial robbery cases
and team 1 will take
further cases coming up.
"Protect warmly,"
"execute fairly."
Don't worry.
He knows his father's election
depends on him.
He'll behave himself.
You think so?
Wow, it's awesome!
What's all this?
Ossobuco
and Parmigiana di melanzane.
Sounds so delicious!
- I'll have those.
- Okay.
Michael Ballack!
His team is winning 2 to 1.
He's easy in dribbling. Great.
Here comes Drogba from the right.
He's coming.
Drogba! Didier Drogba!
Lampard on the right under, shoot!
Computer!
Com...
Don't you know
you shouldn't turn it off like that?
you shouldn't play games here?
Here's not your playground.
You still don't get it?
I understand this situation exactly.
This is a kind of business
between the police and Hansu Group.
We are in a contractual relationship.
You don't have any power to break it,
but you're not cooperating
due to your self-esteem,
inferiority, or something.
I don't bear any of those.
You don't?
But everyone bears that.
If you decided
to carry out the contract,
you shouldn't behave like this.
Had you done it properly
in the first place
I wouldn't have had to do this.
Get out in three minutes
or I will arrest you
for obstruction of official duties.
Hey!
What kind of official duties
did they obstruct?
It's delicious.
Thank you.
You have two minutes and 40 seconds left.
That punk...
We couldn't find a good place,
so we prepared it here
to enjoy with all of you.
By the way, who are you, sir?
I'm a secretary of detective Jin Isoo.
No detective
needs a secretary.
You're not allowed to be here.
You have two minutes.
Let's wrap it up.
Goddamn it.
You're done?
You saw his desk?
Calm down.
He's just trying to get on our nerves.
Gosh, what do we do?
No idea.
We can't kick him out
or send him away to other team.
Let's make him quit by himself.
How?
Hey, is that yummy?
Ye... No, it's not!
Come here.
That Jin Isoo...
What's his weak point?
-Weak point?
-Yes.
You must know.
You follow him
and even call him bro.
No weak point but only strong points.
Damn...
Isn't there anything he hates?
Anything he hates...
Oh, he hates something boring.
Something boring?
"Investigation report"
What's that?
Work for you.
Files on Lee Changhyun's case.
Summarize them by today.
You know,
90% of police jobs are writing reports.
Work hard
and get it right.
That's already done.
Keep quiet.
For your reference.
It'd be hard for him.
Absolutely.
It's hard even for you.
Hey, I'm...
Huh?
But isn't this
workplace harassment?
Okay.
Go report us.
Call the police.
Forget it.
He's gone.
Files are also gone.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
What's up?
I don't know. He wants me to come.
"Ji..."
Oh, Ms. Lee.
I didn't expect
I would write a report
at this age.
I'm sorry.
Jin asked me how to write a report.
It's you
who should guide and teach him
every single work, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'll handle it.
-Mr. Jin?
-Yes?
Come with me.
Okay.
Your typing improved.
They're getting me more wrinkles.
Jeez...
Wow, this is...
It really soothes my wrist.
Lady first.
Remove it.
Don't ask anything.
Is something up?
A 70-year-old with dementia
is missing in Gangha 3-dong.
Jeez... Gangha 3-dong is huge.
How do they...
Let's help them.
What?
Missing Investigation Team
needs more hands.
Let's go.
Wait...
Hey, Jin, let's go.
Okay, let's get to work.
Jeez, it's so annoying.
76-year-old male, Park Chunsik.
At the time of missing, he was wearing
daily hanbok with a gray vest.
Let's search for him.
Yes, sir.
We'll search
from here to Gangha station.
Thanks.
I'll pay you back.
From here to Gangha station.
We're walking? From here to there?
We should find him before sunset.
He could collapse
due to diabetes.
Let's go!
We don't have much time.
Right. Move quickly!
Okay, I got it.
Jin Isoo.
I got it. Gosh...
How grumpy...
Hello, sir.
Have you seen this man?
What's all this?
What?
Excuse me, sir.
Have you seen this man?
Hey!
They found him.
He's awesome.
Take care, sir.
Okay.
He won this watch!
What the hell is going on?
He's a man of capacity.
Searching for an old man
with dementia.
The one who finds him first
will win this watch.
Tell him to delete it now.
Okay.
It's cool.
- Good morning.
You were awesome, bro.
Oh, stop.
Hey, take a look.
-Which one looks better?
-The upper one.
I'll pick this one, then.
Good morning.
He's annoying me in every way.
Violent Crime Investigation Team 1.
Okay.
A body was found at Gangha quay.
Let's go.
Detective Jin Isoo.
We should go.
Okay.
Hey, you come in your luxurious car.
Let's ride this.
- I'll drive.
- No.
I'll drive.
Get on.
Jeez, my new outfit...
To the Gangha quay
in 30 minutes.
Be there on time.
You're challenging me?
Okay.
That punk.
That road is under construction.
That prince isn't good at directions.
"Gangha Quay"
You can't get in now.
- Police.
- Ah...
Hold on.
- What's up?
- Police are here.
We're from Gangha station.
You found a dead body?
Yes, I reported it.
Leave your car here
and let's go to the scene.
Wasn't it found in the yacht?
Let us park inside.
That area is only for boat owners.
I can't let just anyone in.
Just anyone?
We're here for an investigation.
Sorry, but some clients
are very sensitive about outsiders.
I can't help it. Sorry.
That's my bro.
"Yoon Jiwon
forensic doctor in NFS"
Nice weather.
Is he the silver spoon?
Yes.
He looks sly.
He looks rude.
We're putting them on?
It's like a movie.
Only real cops get into the site.
You told me to come to the site.
Watch your tone.
I'm talking casually to Ganghyun.
Don't do that to me.
You wait in the car.
Go wait in your car.
Is it why you told me to come?
I brought you to keep you
from making any trouble.
No SNS allowed.
Hey...
By the way, why am I obeying her?
Is it an aftereffect?
Post-traumatic stress disorder?
Goddamn it.
Okay.
The dead body was left to be easily seen.
The manager here said he thought
she was sleeping.
The dead body was not hidden.
Here's a bag.
Found out something?
Yeah.
A ligature mark here
and a wound on the occipital.
Her dress is wet, but not by dewdrops.
So, she could've been drowned?
We'll see by an autopsy.
She's wearing a luxurious dress
but she seems malnourished.
By the way...
her face looks familiar, right?
You okay?
Yes.
I envy him.
Come check this powder.
Yes, sir.
This is her. Jung Ina.
She's a model.
Right.
Let's find out her agency.
Okay.
Detective Jin.
See me later?
Woah.
Can I take a picture?
Of course!
Let me join you on it someday.
I'll let you drive it
if you promise to be on my side.
I'm always on your side.
I'm the Star-Lord X.
I'm your follower.
My girlfriend, too.
Hmm...
So, she's Gamora?
-No, she's Groot.
-Groot?
Yes.
That's a new combination.
Come on.
Jin, let's go.
To where?
Just come.
Is she always like that?
She's so oppressive and overbearing.
No. She just hates you.
You're way too honest.
Hey!
Hey, there!
You're ignoring me?
Hey, Ms. Lee!
Get on.
Do you think I come and go
whenever I'm told to?
-You're doing that now.
-No way.
I'm going home.
You can come when you want
but need my permission to go.
When seniors order, juniors must obey.
You can quit
if you don't like it.
Why is this car like this?
Is it a bumper car or something?
Gosh, it's dirty.
Shut up and fasten your belt.
Jeez...
Where are we headed to?
In a movie, a cop's life
looks so interesting.
They chase criminals
with fascinating actions
and handcuff the criminal.
You know what they don't show?
A labor of detectives in reality.
When a case occurs,
we investigate the victim's family,
friends, and colleagues one by one.
To get security camera footage,
we call everywhere to ask
or visit every store.
Why whine next to me?
A sheltered-grown rich son
doesn't need to do all of these.
That's what I mean.
Jeez...
After threatening failed,
you're convincing me.
I'm saying it for your sake.
So, where on earth are we going?
The victim is a model.
Police.
Where's the CEO?
Wait, please.
They're tall.
Come this way.
Meet all the staff
and ask about Jung Ina.
Meet all of them?
Find out something useful.
Yes...
No, that's not enough.
Hm?
Yeah.
I see...
What humble clothes!
How old?
Police.
Right, I know...
I know it's a good opportunity,
but it's us who decide our own value.
Tell them to revise the contract.
Yes, that's what I mean.
Why don't you hang up for now?
What's up?
Jung Ina
belongs here, right?
What about Ina?
She was found dead.
She was here last night.
She left
for an important appointment.
What time did she leave?
It was around 8:00 p.m.
You know whom she was meeting?
No.
Did you notice any change in her
or anything strange
she was going through recently?
No. Nothing special.
How's her family relationship?
Well...
She had a widowed mother
who passed away ten days ago.
Maybe she has no other family.
Okay. Thank you for cooperation.
Please call me
if you recall anything about her.
Jung Ina's dead.
Check out
all the contracts on her.
Let's follow each other.
I heard he's a Casanova.
Not a Casanova
but a romanticist.
What about Hong Euna of MK Group?
Oh, I know that.
The Gangnamdaero case?
That was not a romance but a thriller.
Wait for a second.
Stay here.
Go eat sushi in Japan?
Hey, Ganghyun!
I found out something.
Submit it as a report.
Jeez... Where's her manner?
Stop joking and open the door.
Hey!
I don't have my wallet.
How rude! Gosh...
Jung Ina's autopsy begins.
A ligature mark.
I'm home.
You're late.
Are you still up?
Do you eat on time?
It's kimchijjigae.
Want a drink?
Okay.
Hold on.
Cheers.
A case occurred?
Yes, she's a model, only 22 years old.
She was about to blossom.
I came out after the autopsy started.
You'll be busy from tomorrow.
How's the newbie?
Jeez... I've never seen
that kind of jerk.
He called a catering service
to the police station.
And he got a large computer
to play a game at work.
Even worse, the chief...
Anyway, he's a real freak.
I see.
Jeez, it must be tough for you.
Okay.
One more drink.
Jeez.
Another drinking party?
It's not a heavy drinking.
Just one drink while she's having dinner.
What a father and a daughter.
Ganghyun.
Yes?
You know,
-the son of that pharmacy--
-That again?
Enough.
Just listen to me.
He looked like actor Song Joongki.
Mom.
He has such blessed looks,
yet he has no girlfriend?
Then, something's wrong with him.
No, I won't see him.
I wish you
spend a night at your boyfriend's place
instead of a night-duty room.
Don't you think it's a waste
of your beautiful youth?
Not at all.
Dating is a waste of time.
I'd rather catch one more criminal.
Okay, both of you are such know-it-alls.
Why me, too?
Wash up and go to bed.
You know what time it is?
Okay, you go get some sleep.
- Go.
- Good night.
Cheers.
Wrap it up!
Okay, okay. Go.
Go to bed. We're done.
- Just one more bite.
- Go inside.
Why are you so depressed?
The whole team is ignoring me.
After ordering me around all day
just as she wanted,
she threw me on the street and left.
I don't understand.
You remember your high school days?
You know,
some guys were jealous of you
and held you in check.
That's what they're doing.
Those guys are scared
if you catch a culprit again.
Just smash them.
Sounds good.
What's up this time?
I'm feeling sensitive
after missing my morning coffee.
Why didn't you get up earlier?
What do you want?
The autopsy result is out.
Why do you care?
Do you have to ask?
Detective Lee, let's go. We're late.
Jin Isoo.
I'm warning you.
An autopsy room isn't for anyone.
It's too much for normal people.
Do I look like a normal person?
- Hello.
Where's Dr. Yoon?
She's in the room.
-Should I call her?
-No, I'll go see her.
You want to check?
Oh...
Okay. Let me see.
You brought the silver spoon?
Yeah, he's so annoying.
Jin Isoo.
Jin.
Stop playing a trick.
Jin Isoo, wake up.
Jin Isoo, Jin Isoo?
You okay?
I was joking.
You're fooled, right?
What the hell?
The estimated time of death is?
It's from 1:00 to 1:30 a.m.
And the cause of death is?
Well...
It's complicated.
You saw this last time.
She was strangled with hands
but no congestion or fracture.
A fracture could occur
by strangling?
If I strangle you with a hand
your hyoid bone here often breaks.
I see.
Okay.
She's not strangled to death.
Right.
She's not drowned, either.
River water was in her stomach,
but it was not that much.
That means she was in the water, though.
What was fatal is
an occipital fissure in the left.
She was hit so hard
that her skull was sunken.
A murder weapon
would be like this
or this.
From the angle,
the murderer is left-handed.
They will be strong.
But...
she might've been hit from the side
with a right hand like this.
Wow.
You're so keen.
I am.
But...
Hitting from the side...
Gosh...
and hitting from the back
make different shapes of wounds.
We also consider that.
I see.
So, you mean the victim
was strangled, hit on the head,
and drown into the river?
Right.
And...
she has bruises on her arms.
What could this be?
I don't know.
She was hit on the head, strangled,
and thrown into the river.
And she was picked up onto the yacht.
No, no. Or...
Throw her into the river and pick her up,
and then hit her head?
Why?
For what?
Sherlock Holmes on the case, huh?
What's your purpose?
What?
What's your plan this time?
Why?
Are you scared?
You're scared
if I catch the culprit again.
Hey, mister.
A motiveless assailant became a cop
and finally got insane.
You think you'll catch the culprit
by accident again?
What if I catch the bastard?
Never.
That'd never happen.
If I fail to catch him,
I'll get out of your sight.
I'll move to desk duty or stay home.
-Sounds great.
-But if I catch him,
you should admit
that I'm a real cop.
Deal.
The forensic result is out.
This zipper bag found on the site
was empty.
It's a new one.
Why does she carry an empty zipper bag?
Anything else?
This powder
is a new type of LSD drugs.
Any footprints?
It's 11-inch hiking boots.
We confirmed its brand
but over 120,000 pairs
were sold last year,
so it's meaningless.
I see.
How about bloodstains?
There were only diluted ones
around the body.
And fingerprints on the champagne glass.
Okay, thanks.
- Yes.
- Good job.
Jeez...
Anything from the security camera?
We found a suspect.
They went in together,
and after an hour,
he came out alone.
Huh?
He's the youngest son of DN Media.
We know that.
His fingerprints
were found on the glass.
DN Media...
Jung Ina shot the CF of that company.
Right. A week ago.
You must not know this.
Another model was going to shoot it
but was replaced by Jung Ina.
Police officers are not capable enough
to find that out, right?
I found it out from other models.
I'm interested in this field.
Who owns this yacht?
- Cheon Taesung?
- No, Cheon Taeyoung.
His elder brother.
I heard a rumor about them--
Let's see Taesung first.
Where is he now?
That's...
unknown.
He didn't go to work,
and his secretary can't reach him.
This picture was uploaded
on his SNS an hour ago,
but I don't know where it is.
Where's this?
Uh?
Oh, my gosh.
I know where it is. Gosh...
What's wrong with that punk?
He'll catch the culprit by himself.
And if he fails,
he'll move to desk duty.
- Kyungjin.
- Yes.
Find out where it is quickly.
- Okay.
- Hurry up.
You're here, sir.
Mr. Jin, it's been a long time.
Yeah, I've been busy.
Where to, sir?
I'm here to see Cheon Taesung of DN.
This way to the tanning room.
Oh, I'll go see him by myself.
-What's up?
-It's me.
Damn it.
"Cheon Taeseong
DN Group's third son"
You know who I am, right?
Of course. You're a troublemaker of Hansu.
It's you who is a troublemaker.
I am...
the detective.
You're a detective?
Wow.
Shit.
Look how nonchalant you are.
You felt like tanning after murdering?
Yes.
Argh... Wait.
Police.
We're here to find someone.
Let me get in.
This place is only for members.
Stop talking about that freaking members!
I'll just go in and get him.
I hope you cooperate.
Come back with a warrant.
You think I can't?
Do it if you can.
Cheon Taesung is here, right?
Hey, wait.
You're arrested for Jung Ina's murder.
Well...
You can remain silent,
and challenge the properness of arrest...
Hey, Mr. Park!
Mr. Park! Mr. Park!
- Mr. Park for what?
- Mr. Park, hurry up!
Goddamn it.
What about Jin Isoo?
Jin Isoo from Hansu Group. You let him in?
Gosh...
It's so embarrassing.
Oh, you're here.
What the hell did you do?
I got Cheon Taesung.
There he comes.
Damn.
Get away, punk.
Hey.
Go kill him.
Police. Back off.
Hey, what are you doing?
Just go smash that punk!
Stay behind me.
I'm a good fighter.
Then, you handle it.
Go ahead.
Hey, give me something.
You said you're good.
Only for a 1 to 1 fight.
What?
I'm only used to a 1 to 1 match.
Stick behind me.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Hey, no one can beat
against a group attack like that.
Call me when you need help.
How confident.
"A rich cop who catches a rich son?"
Special Thanks to Park Bokyung
Stop behaving mean
and keep your dignity.
It looks weird.
This is not the way
a conglomerate family works.
One of your sons
seems to have killed Jung Ina.
It's Taeyoung.
He does drugs in the yacht.
So scared that I pushed her.
What did you talk about?
Not much. I don't remember.
Young girls
who have eyes on a rich man
still exist.
There's something more.
I found out something huge.
They're running.
They applied to leave.
He's the culprit.
Stay tuned for bonus clip
-Hello.
-Mr. Choi.
Where are you?
I'm reading nearby.
I'm moving out.
To where?
You know the place
which has no relation to Hansu.
My own house.
Okay.
I'll prepare for it.
Translated by Hyeryung Kim