[Studio Banshan]
[Regeneration]
[Episode 7]
Don't be nervous.
This is just a little scammer.
This scumbag should be grateful to you
for being able to live some extra hours.
So he can know why he has to die.
You hear me?
It's all your fault.
It's your sin.
He tried to run out of the country,
but my people stopped him.
Before killing him,
I just want to know one thing.
Exactly how many people has he scammed?
What kind of a man is he?
As smart as I am,
I just can't believe
that I got tricked by this scumbag.
Luckily, I'm a curious person,
which spared you
a few more hours to live.
Today,
I invited all you victims here,
to settle all the debts.
To clear out
everything
he owed you.
Mr. Chen, calm down.
He... He doesn't deserve to die.
Drop the knife.
You're not dragging us all
into murder, are you?
Are you crazy?
Relax.
Fei Ke doesn't exist anymore.
If we keep our mouths shut,
no one will know.
That driver's one of my own.
He'll get rid of the boat.
If you don't do it,
you're not getting out of here.
Do what?
You each stab him once,
and make him feel our pain.
And then,
we drop him into the sea.
You can call the police, or sue him,
but you can't kill him!
Sue him?
How many years would he serve?
You people!
You hated his guts
when you talked about him.
Now that I have him here
so you'll take vengeance.
And you're now
playing noble?
You think
you'll get your money back?
No!
Those transfer records,
bank account and keys,
were all faked by me!
I did all that to make you
speak out about
all the dirty things he did!
You.
Can you get your face back?
Can you get your innocence back?
Can I get my daughter back?
This is for Jiajia.
Kill him if you want,
but leave us out of it!
This is for me.
Stop it!
Why are you smiling?
Liu Mo,
pick up the knife and kill him!
Do it!
You hear me?
Give him a chance to explain.
Have you lost your mind?
He's a fraud!
You can't let him talk!
Give me the key.
I'm the only one that can drive a boat.
If you want to go home,
you'll have to listen to him.
You!
If you won't let him talk,
then I'll talk.
You asked me to look into Fei Ke,
but during the investigation,
I found some suspicious clues.
Fei Ke did scam you,
and he did deserve to be punished,
but the details I found
are quite different
from what you told me.
Which side are you on?
Mr. Chen,
between you and Jiajia,
who met Fei Ke first?
In 2015,
at the Bailu Golf Club,
Fei Ke paid
for a hundred hours of training.
He signed in for the first 32 hours,
but the rest
were all signed by you.
Gao.
Hi.
Dad, why are you taking me here?
I can't play golf.
I can't, either,
but that's how you do business.
Watch and learn.
What brings you here today?
Long time no see.
Yeah.
My daughter.
Lovely.
Uncle Gao,
how many goals have you hit?
About 90.
Qi,
how's your son?
His son was just born.
I'm a grandpa now.
Look at you!
Why didn't you tell me
about the wedding?
Congratulations!
What about your daughter?
Is she married?
Not even close.
Come on.
Who's that young fellow?
I hear he's a shareholder of this place.
The son of some chief.
Okay.
Go on and have fun.
Young man, nice hit.
Thanks, Mr. Chen.
I'm an amateur.
You know me?
We haven't met,
but I've heard about you a lot.
You flatter me.
Please teach me.
I can't seem
to get the right swing.
It never hits hard enough.
I'm also kind of new in this,
but I have a good coach.
I can introduce him to you.
That'll be great.
I bought a hundred hours of his.
Next time you're here,
just use my account
and put it on my tab.
That's not necessary.
Don't be polite to me.
I won't need so many.
You can just use my hours.
Well, thank you then.
Come on! Yeah!
Let's
befriend each other.
Okay.
Take a note.
My name's Fei Ke.
If you need to book time or service,
just give me a heads-up.
Okay.
Are you here alone?
With my daughter.
Jiajia!
Was Fei Ke and Jiajia's marriage
solely arranged by you?
Why, all of a sudden?
Well, I was just curious.
Are you married?
No.
Girlfriend?
And your parents weren't anxious?
Actually, they want me
to be cautious instead.
Why?
Wait,
what do your parents do?
My father's in Beijing.
He's just an ordinary public servant.
My mother is a college teacher.
Which department is your father in?
Just tell me.
I won't tell anyone. Come on.
Management Department,
the Ministry of Lands and Mines.
Okay.
Then we must have met each other before.
Is his first name Fei too?
I took after my mom.
Oh, I see.
I get it.
Why won't you get a girlfriend?
I just got back from abroad.
I don't know a lot of people yet.
And I haven't met the right girl.
What do you know?
You see, my daughter studied abroad too.
In Britain, the uh...
Mar... Something.
Saint Martin's School of Art?
Right! Master degree.
See, I may not look good,
but my daughter's pretty.
She took after her mom.
She's almost as tall as me
wearing high heels.
Son,
do you have time?
I wanna set you up on a date.
You both studied abroad,
I bet you'll have some common language.
You should get to know each other,
you know?
[Ministry of Lands and Mines]
Mr. Chen,
I did some background check.
There is indeed a Deputy Director General
surnamed Li.
Born in 1960.
I found some photos for you.
Okay.
There's one more thing.
The legal staff told me
that we still have problems
with the procedures
of the mines we purchased in Luanchong.
I suggest we wait.
Why wait?
Just get them first.
Okay.
[Fei Ke]
Hello?
Mr. Chen,
this Saturday at the Huxin Club,
there's a charity auction
for autistic kids.
A lot of artists
and entrepreneurs will be there.
I'll go too.
I'd like to invite Jiajia
if she has time.
Okay.
She does!
Then I'll send you the invitation.
[Elsa, Chen Jiajia]
Why didn't you tell me you're back?
Look.
Isn't that incredible?
You do the chase and I'll do the talk.
She'll change her mind eventually.
Jiajia,
Fei Ke
has been waiting for you downstairs
for over an hour.
He's such a nice young man,
and he's crazy about you.
Why don't you... Why don't you
just make friends first?
I have enough friends!
I just want to you settle down,
you know?
Why can't you just give me that?
This is my life!
Why do I have to do what you want?
Why?
Because I'm your father!
You can have what you want
when you can support yourself!
Here.
Why won't you go home?
I have to pretend to be with you
so my dad would shut up.
Why pretend?
I have someone I love,
but my dad doesn't like him.
Where is he?
My dad drove him away.
I can't find him.
Can't you guys sit down and talk?
No use.
All my dad knows is verbal abuse
and guilt-tripping.
I'm so sick of him now!
If he forces me any further,
I'll kill myself!
Don't say that.
Then,
why not stay at a hotel?
He froze my credit card.
Then you'll take the bed
and I'll take the couch.
Mr. Chen.
How are things with Jiajia lately?
Pretty good.
When are you planning
on getting married?
Isn't that too hasty?
Come on.
You're not getting any younger.
I want to save up first.
Right now,
I can't even afford a decent wedding.
Money cannot buy time, can it?
How much longer do you want Jiajia
to wait?
I'm eager to have a grandson, okay?
That's not what I meant.
I was just hoping
that I'd give Jiajia a better life.
Jiajia's life is good enough already.
Don't worry about money.
Just treat her well
and be faithful.
That's all I'm asking.
Can you do it?
Yes.
I can.
Set up a time to meet your parents.
But my father's in Beijing. He can't come.
My mother's fine, though.
Then,
shall we meet here, or at my club?
Your club then.
Okay.
Let me sum up.
This marriage between our kids
is now decided.
Okay.
Your call.
Here.
Hello?
Yes. The quota is limited.
It's a star project.
A lot of ETFs are after it.
I'm eating outside.
I'll talk to you later.
What star project?
Count me in.
A project about a cancer probe
is currently contacting us.
It's patented by Wylon Medical.
What's the estimated return?
I'm just a tiny project manager.
I've got no authority for that.
Show me the profiles first.
Nanlin's successful already
and it's still not good enough?
No one ever has enough money.
Jiajia,
Jiajia, what's wrong?
Dad,
I don't wanna get married.
Why?
I don't love him.
Forget love.
Fei Ke will be a good husband.
He's perfect for you.
I'm happy with him.
Why does it matter
if you're happy with him?
I'm the one who's marrying him.
Well, love can be cultivated.
He's a great guy.
You'll regret it
if you miss him.
You just want his family background!
Well, marriage
is between two families, you know.
Dad,
I still can't get over him.
You will.
Time will wash out everything.
Dad!
Enough.
You see.
Now that the parents have met,
the wedding has been set,
if you back out,
you'd really embarrass me, okay?
Dad, please!
It's settled.
Listen, you'll thank me later.
I'm only doing this for your own good!
Don't force me to do this, dad!
Let's eat.
Go pick your wedding dress later.
Dad,
Organization Code.
[Business License]
Look.
This is the official website
of the Ministry of Lands and Mines.
All the mining certificates are required
to be filed and publicized.
Your Luanchong projects are here.
Good.
Very good.
Although,
I can only give you the backup copy.
The official paper certificate
has to be kept in the ministry.
It's mainly for your protection.
Oh, I see.
Do protect your father too, okay?
I heard that there are several mines
with rented accounts in Zhifeng Group
looking for buyers.
If I buy them,
can you help me
get them approved?
Will that work?
You'll need to hurry.
Things are getting stricter now.
I see.
Let's cooperate.
Whatever you need, just tell me.
Writing a web page like that
is a piece of cake for Fei Ke.
I've visited all of Nanlin's providers
and clients
between 2014 and 2016,
there was no problem with your business,
while you insisted on expanding.
That's why you became reckless
and purchased many illegal mines.
Dad!
You knew Zhifeng's mines are illegal!
How could you buy them!
Did you ask Fei Ke
to get you the permission?
Stop asking.
Stay out of this.
Just live your simple life.
Don't you care what I want?
Am I just a tool to you?
I'm only doing this for your own good!
Getting married and having kids
is every woman's duty.
Having kids early
helps you recover fast, okay?
And it's good for the kid too.
You're just trying to gain favor
from Fei Ke's family!
Shush!
Is that right, dad?
Is he upstairs?
Yes.
Come here!
Do you honestly think
that I need to gain favor from anyone?
I'm old. I'll die before you.
I have to find someone suitable
to take care of you.
I want to find him myself.
I don't love him
and he doesn't love me either.
There's no way we'll be happy together.
You!
You haven't been married.
You don't get it.
The truth is,
love is overrated.
l know better.
Fei Ke
has got high IQ and EQ.
And he's got the best outside
and inside.
He'll treat your kids well.
I don't care!
I'm an adult.
I have my own judgment.
Yes, you're an adult,
but I'm your father.
I will do everything in my power
for your happiness.
I'd rather
every disaster
and pain
fall on me,
so that you'll never have to suffer.
Understand?
But I'm suffering right now!
How come you're suffering?
You're living in a big house.
You have more money you can spend.
And you have a great fiance!
You're just being picky!
Dad,
Fei Ke is not as powerful as you think.
Be careful.
I don't know what water of oblivion
you gave to my father,
but I'll just never gonna marry you,
and don't you ever touch me!
I won't touch you.
Good.
I heard what you just said.
I said it out loud on purpose.
Actually, I was forced
into this by my parents too.
People like us
can never have the freedom to choose.
Even if they don't control us,
we're not capable enough
to control our own lives.
Say that for yourself.
I am.
Then why don't you go look for him?
I can't find him.
You will if you try.
You're just afraid.
You don't want to piss out your dad.
You complain about him,
but you also love him.
Because he brought you up all by himself.
Indeed, he did a lot.
That's why I don't want to disappoint him.
Actually, we don't have
to really get married.
What do you mean?
We could have the wedding,
but we could skip the legal procedures.
We could act before our parents
and get what we want.
Chen Jiajia,
we might not love each other,
but you're a good girl.
What do you mean?
Dad,
[Prenuptial Agreement]
I know that Jiajia's also
a shareholder of Nanlin.
A lot of your cars, estates,
and other assets are under her name.
That's why I hired a lawyer
and got a prenup
to protect Jiajia's property.
That's nonsense!
That's absolutely unnecessary.
This way, you'll have
nothing to worry about,
and I get to show you my sincerity.
I know that this marriage
has brought you rumors.
I want
to show my earnestness to Jiajia,
which has nothing to do
with money or background.
Enough.
I won't let her sign it.
If this gets out, I'd be embarrassed.
Everyone will think that I'm stingy!
Then we'll get married after the purchase
of Luanchong and Zhifeng.
In that case,
the profit of the purchases
will become Jiajia's premarital property.
Are you kidding?
It'll take years
before the deals are sealed.
I'm eager to have a grandson, okay?
How about this, dad?
I've got a compromise solution.
We do the wedding,
but not the legal procedures.
We're not getting the marriage certificate
until the two deals
are settled.
That way,
your face is saved
and my dad's protected.
Well,
okay. Go ahead.
Okay.
Thanks, Dad.
Mr. Chen, hello!
Congratulations!
[Groom: Fei Ke, bride: Chen Jiajia]
You have my daughter now.
Don't worry, dad.
As a father,
you've been controlling Jiajia's life,
forcing her,
using her as a bargaining chip.
That's why she's so depressed.
And also,
you lied about the crucial fact too.
Did Jiajia really kill herself?
The son of some chief.
Ten million.
As estimated, within three years...
I'm a shareholder!
Fei Ke!
Dad,
why do you hate him so much?
I kind of like him, you know.
He knows me better than you do.
Look how professional
the actors he hired are.
Shut up!
We don't love each other,
however,
he cared about me.
Nonsense!
He's just a big fat liar!
I thought you had a good eye for people.
I guess you can be wrong.
The one I love,
you despise.
And now look,
you brought home a scammer,
forced me to marry him,
and claimed to be doing it for me.
Let me tell you something else.
The truth is,
Fei Ke and I
have been putting on an act.
The marriage
is fake.
Being in love
I never allowed him to touch me at all.
Happy?
You forced me to do this, you know?
It's your own arrogance
that got you to fall into Fei Ke's trap.
I wanna thank him.
He showed you
how ridiculous,
how arrogant and stupid you are.
You don't deserve to be a father.
Get back!
Jiajia!
Jiajia, stop the car!
Are you trying to kill yourself?
The surveillance camera got everything.
You tried repeatedly to stop her car,
which led to her car crash.
Cheng Hao,
you've only been on one business trip
in the September of 2014.
It was Flight AR1519.
Seat 5L.
First-class seats are mostly empty.
I checked the seating record.
Your next seat 5J was not taken.
So I wonder,
how did Fei Ke sit next to you
and chat with you?
Excuse me.
I noticed that you were reading CFA.
Are you a finance student?
Sort of.
Freshly graduated?
Just graduated from grad school.
I majored in technology
at Chengjiang University.
And I recently switched
to the financial industry.
Everyone in the company is some hotshot.
I have to try catching up
in my spare time.
You're being modest.
You're reading a level three,
which means you've passed level two.
That's something.
Beats most finance students already.
May I know your name?
My name's Fei Ke.
But I thought your first name is Li.
How do you know?
I was right behind you
at the security check.
I saw your ID card.
My parents got divorced
when I was little.
I used my mum's first name.
I'm Cheng Hao.
A pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
Cheers.
Come on, again!
Here!
Cheers!
My good buddy, Fei Ke.
He's also in the financial industry.
Song is also from your university.
I'm from the Materials School,
Class of 2002.
A true senior of mine!
Which class are you from?
I took a year off due to illness
in my freshman year.
I'm actually from Class 2005,
but I learned with Class 2006.
You should've graduated by then.
Who supervised you?
Professor Lu.
Do you know Kong Xiangzhe then?
He's also from Class 2006.
Who?
Kong Xiangzhe.
No.
I probably remembered it wrong.
Nice.
Fast reaction.
Is he really from Chengjiang University?
We didn't have anyone
by the name of Kong Xiangzhe.
He lied.
To test me?
A lot of people are imposing
as Chengjiang graduates now.
There are too many scammers out there.
Our circle doesn't just accept anyone.
Everyone lies.
Fei Ke memorized
thousands of names within those classes.
He's difficult to be exposed.
Shall I drive you home?
No need.
I live in a hotel room nearby.
Why live in a hotel?
See you!
Bye!
The apartment I rented
has been leaking.
Then...
I haven't cleaned the guest room
for a while.
I'll have the cleaning lady
clean it tomorrow.
No need, brother.
I'll just sleep on the couch.
We have similar sizes.
I'll get you some of my clothes.
They're brand new.
You and Fei Ke
share similar backgrounds,
and you're even similarly risk-driven,
that's why you appreciated each other.
He knew your sense of insecurity
coming from a small town
and he knew what you crave underneath.
He also knew what he needed to do
to make you find him
useful.
A hundred and seventy-seven square meters.
Twenty-year loan.
Monthly payment of 24 thousand.
In our town, you're the first one
to buy a place in Chengjiang.
Good for you!
Son, you're so great!
You live alone in such a huge apartment?
That's wasteful.
You need to get a wife.
Have a few kids.
Yeah, okay.
I've checked.
On the day Fei Ke opened his account,
he put in three million yuan all at once.
More came afterwards.
Where did he get the money?
Rat trading with my account?
We're not family.
The supervision won't find out.
Maybe not, Hao.
If we get caught,
we're both going to jail.
If we don't tell anyone,
no one will find out.
Besides,
we use our money to invest
and the earnings go to your account.
What do you have to be worried about?
Alright.
Fei Ke.
Be bold.
Remember.
If we can succeed,
the means won't matter.
The wind's getting heavy! Turn around!
If we go any deeper, the boat will flip!
No one can get home alive!
Su Qian,
the money you lent to Fei Ke,
was it your own?
Let me be more straight.
When you first met Fei Ke,
were you single?
Apart from being professional,
I believe I'm also a detail-oriented,
meticulous person.
Actually, I think to be an accountant,
you don't need smartness or strategy.
All you need is earnestness.
treating every number with sincerity.
Mr. Zhao.
Please sit.
Dan.
Come see me after the interview.
Okay.
Actually, this is my first
job application
after I came back home.
This girl's kind of nice.
That's right.
Get Susan a table by the window.
Susan, we got you a new table.
Here.
Okay. Thanks.
[New job, new beginning]
[Posting]
[Susan]
What brings you here today?
Long time no see.
Yeah. This is my daughter.
Lovely.
I'm on my way home.
No need.
My phone's dying. Talk to you later.
Boyfriend?
No.
A company leader.
Chasing you?
No.
In 1490,
Dürer traveled through Europe.
Don't you invite me up?
Next time.
You're home. Why so late?
I met a high school classmate.
We haven't seen each other for long,
so we chat for a while.
Really?
Right. I cooked you soup.
Try it.
Thank you.
A friend of mine saw you today.
You went to Dürer's art show?
What art show?
Your friend must have got it wrong.
Let me be straight.
You went out on a date?
No.
What are you trying to say?
That classmate of yours
seems much younger than you.
Can you stop sounding so jealous?
I told you I didn't.
If you won't believe me, fine.
That's not what I meant.
Why don't you ever take me home?
My home is too small, too messy.
Building Ten in Yuling.
Each apartment is
about 220 to 370 square meters.
There's no month rent below 20 thousand.
Small?
You looked into me?
Why so nervous?
Are you married?
Yes.
Why are you looking like that?
I don't love him.
He's 17 years older than me.
He brought me a job and residence
so I could settle down in the city.
Do you know how important that is
for a thirty-something woman?
But I'm not young anymore.
Those are not what I want right now.
I wanna respect my body and my heart.
I don't want to keep lying
to myself anymore.
Why did you lie to me then?
He doesn't mind.
What are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid,
but there's not gonna be any result.
What result?
Why can't we just enjoy the process?
If your husband wasn't Wylon's CEO,
would you dare do that?
I'm getting married.
Married?
With who?
I'm just here to say goodbye.
I don't get it.
I thought we were in love.
Fine. If it's me
and him that's bothering you,
I can get a divorce.
- Forget it.
- If that's the problem,
I'd really...
Just give me time, okay?
Stop lying to me!
I'm not lying to you.
What's the point?
I don't love him at all
and he doesn't love me either.
He doesn't care about me.
Apart from money,
he can't give me anything.
With him,
I feel like a dead person.
But with you,
I feel alive.
But you need money.
You need the social status he gives you.
You enjoy it.
I don't need it!
You can't leave him.
I'll tell you again.
I don't need it!
What I need now is you.
I understand you
and I want you to understand me.
You can't help me.
She can.
I can too.
Do you have money?
I do.
Never mind.
Please! Don't leave me!
Please!
Please.
[Su Qian]
[Your account has received
a deposit of 3,000,000 yuan.]
Who on earth are they?
What did they do to you?
Where did you get so much money?
Don't worry about it.
I can borrow more.
Give it to me. Are you out of your mind?
How much do you still owe those people?
The principal is five million.
[Zhao Xiaoyang]
With interest,
eight million.
I'll give you ten million.
Pay them back.
You can use the rest
to get back on your feet, okay?
[Transfer Amount: 10.000.000.00 yuan]
I don't want to owe you any more money.
I've owed you too much already.
[Dear customer,
your transfer transaction was successful!]
Are you Zhao Xiaoyang?
Yes.
We're the police,
from the Economic Department.
Please cooperate.
After Zhao Xiaoyang went to jail,
did you go see him?
I couldn't.
I was too ashamed.
You wanna know what he said?
You again?
Chief Zhao.
Please don't call me that.
I'm no longer Chief Zhao.
Mr. Zhao.
I'm a journalist,
not a lawyer or a judge.
You've never answered my questions.
I'm not here for my media.
I'm here for myself. I want to ask you,
did you actually sign those?
What was your motivation?
I'll give you the same answer.
I made a mistake.
I confess.
I will pay the loss with my own savings.
I deserve to be punished.
Let's wait for the final verdict.
Also,
please leave others
out of this.
Okay?
I admit.
I lied too.
No one drugged me.
And I wasn't drunk that night.
On the contrary,
I can drink a lot.
I've been dreaming
of dancing the lead in Swan Lake
since childhood.
Why Swan Lake?
Because one person
can dance two roles then.
Especially the part of the Black Swan,
which is much more difficult.
Not only her movement and expression
but also her psychological activities
can better reflect my level.
When you're in your fourth year,
you'll be able to dance the lead
at your graduation performance.
But I can't wait.
I dance much better than anyone else.
Haste makes waste.
Fei Ke,
can you help me get the lead?
How will I help you?
You know the agent
of the performance company.
Get them to sponsor our show!
I'll try.
Fei Ke.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
The show was great!
This is Jin Hai,
Chief Agent of Bolshoi Ballet in China.
This is...
I'm Zhang Xuan.
I'm Fei Ke's friend.
So you're a dance student too?
Yes.
Ballet, traditional, classic.
I can do them all.
Give me a call
if you have any dancing gigs.
Sure. Nice meeting you.
You're back.
- Congratulations.
- Here.
Come on. Hold it for me.
You're going out?
Jin threw a congratulations party for me.
I have to go thank him in person.
Isn't it too late now?
It's a special case today.
Plus, I'll need more favor from him.
He's got connections in the business.
I might need him one day to land a job.
You're only a freshman.
Go with me, okay?
No.
Why not?
I thought he was your friend.
You're okay if I go alone?
Fei Ke.
Mr. Jin.
How are you? Come. Sit.
- Please sit.
- Mr. Jin.
Here!
Do you drink?
Yes, I do.
Western wine, or?
Anything.
What a drinker!
Guys, hear me out.
I'm late,
so I'll drink one first.
Bottoms up for me, casual for you.
Nice. Mr. Jin's friend is the best!
Sit.
Thank you for taking care of me,
and for your referral.
You're welcome.
I'll drink this one up. Mr. Jin, please.
Cheers.
Let's sing songs. Play a game.
Easy.
It's okay.
Let me pour you another glass.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
Let's play a game, Mr. Jin.
Okay.
Come on.
Play Lie to Me.
I'll guess two twos.
Are we done?
Let's go home.
We barely got here.
Not so soon.
It's late.
No, it's not.
Then I'll go first.
Okay. Go on.
♪Walking alone
through time's dreary paths♪
Wait for me at home.
Come on. Let's do it.
♪I got used...♪
Who is it?
Why are you here?
Alone?
What do you think?
I feel terrible.
My head hurts.
That's normal for first-time drinkers.
I'll never drink like this again.
Ever.
What happened yesterday?
I don't remember.
I left first.
I called you at twelve.
You told me you were drunk.
After that,
you never answered my calls again.
They got me a hotel room nearby.
A few girls took care of me.
They left afterwards.
Jin said he told you.
I thought you were drunk
and you didn't remember.
Why are you dwelling on the details?
I don't do this every day.
It's the first time.
Put it down.
Whose watch is this?
Whose is this?
Jin's.
Why is his watch in your room?
He was drunk too.
He insisted on giving it to me.
It's worth hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
How could I take it?
Come on.
Don't be mad.
I won't do it again.
I'm sorry, okay?
Can anyone explain
Aristotle's Wax Theory?
Miss? Wake up.
Please answer this.
The cognitive capacity of humans
is like a piece of blank paper.
There are no marks born with it.
Cognition is created
under direct influence
from the outside.
Like a wax creating a stamp.
Boring.
So boring.
I'm a technology student,
taking your class.
What do you have to complain about?
Come on. I'm an art student.
I hate literature classes!
Any plans for tonight?
Studying.
Let's go out for fun.
The finals are coming.
I'll fail even if I study.
I take a re-test before graduation.
They invited me to sing.
Go with me.
Who?
Jin's friends from last time.
Fei Ke.
Come on!
Since we're here,
sing a song.
Drink then.
You turned Fei Ke's friend into yours
and made more friends via them.
Soon, you lost interest in Fei Ke.
Well, you know about love.
We were young.
We change a lot.
What's the real reason
for you to go get plastic surgery?
None of them look good.
Can't you
sit down and read a little?
I'm too fat.
So ugly.
No, you're not fat
and you're not ugly.
You're just anxious.
Look.
Does it look taller this way?
I want to get my eyes widened.
No, you don't.
Why not?
They all did.
I want to get a new chin too.
Who are they?
The chicks in the clubs?
A lot of college students
do micro-plastic surgeries!
What's the big deal?
Whatever.
You're saying yes?
Then
lend me some money.
I don't have any.
The surgery costs a lot.
If it doesn't go well,
your parents will hate me even more.
My parents don't care about that.
I honestly have no money.
Fine. I'll ask someone else.
Zhang Xuan,
if you change your face,
we'll break up.
Fine. Break up then.
You're stingy
and you're outdated.
This has nothing to do with money.
This has everything to do with money!
You don't want me to become pretty.
You don't want me to make friends.
You don't want anyone
better than you in my life!
Fei Ke.
You're so pathetic.
Get out!
Fine. I'll get out.
Once I get out, I will never come back.
Also, you didn't just
take a break from college.
You dropped out.
That's right.
After I hung out with those people,
I realized that I've got nothing
in common with my classmates.
They kept talking about
internships and degrees,
so boring, so childish!
What's so good about college anyway?
So what, if you graduate?
It's knowing the right people
that's more important.
You took pictures and posted them
on WeChat Moment,
blocking out your family and classmates.
Every time,
you spent a lot of time grouping.
Your lifestyle was envied by some,
but shameful
to the others.
Who are you?
How do you know so much about us?
Why did you try to defend Fei Ke?
I wasn't trying to defend Fei Ke.
I'm just trying to find the truth.
He is indeed guilty,
but you need to resolve it with law
rather than violence.
He Shan.
I'm finally seeing you again.
In fact,
she's the person I've known
for the longest on this boat.
♪The lights are on my wounds again♪
♪Not saying anything,
but feeling uneasy inside♪
♪Still pretending to be happy♪
♪I can't even blame you
for being so cruel♪
♪When you're lost and sad♪
♪I even don't have the right
to comfort you♪
♪I took a script
that has too many twists and turns♪
♪I can't either love or quit,
just pretending to smile♪
♪Who cares?♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a role
that doesn't have a story to tell♪
♪Wait till the song is over
and everyone's gone♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a puppet led by invisible strings♪
♪Yet watched by your coldness♪
♪As my weary smile fades♪
♪I can only be picked♪
♪With no right to know the outcome♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a role
that doesn't have a story to tell♪
♪Wait till the song is over
and everyone's gone♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a puppet led by invisible strings♪
♪Yet performing for your coldness♪
♪Let the most fragile heart ache♪
♪Feeling wronged in silence♪