[Studio Banshan]
[Regeneration]
[Episode 8]
Li Zerui,
come here.
Stop playing.
We have something for you.
The Internet suddenly went down.
We can't receive the answers.
You go find Mr. Bao
and go over the exam questions.
Check your answers with each other.
Otherwise, the teachers won't be able
to grade the exam.
What about the other teachers?
They're all invigilating.
If we can't get the grades tomorrow,
it'll affect the ranking
of the second municipal mock exam.
[Network Diagnostics]
[Connecting]
[Connecting to adsl...]
How's it going?
Can you fix it?
As soon as I can.
Question 22 is misprinted.
X should be cube,
not square.
It can't be solved if it's square.
Hello?
Okay.
Class, let's pay attention.
In question 22, the second
and third sub-questions are misprinted.
X has been changed from square to cube.
[Class 5, Year 12]
How did you do on the exam?
Use calculus to solve geometry?
This is high school math.
It's beyond the syllabus.
It's faster this way.
It's not for you to show off.
It's to create a standardized answer key
for the students.
Quick. Chang to a regular solution.
Li Zerui,
quick.
Put on your new uniform and follow me.
So handsome.
This is our school's top student.
He's been accepted
to Chengjiang University.
Wait a minute.
Don't crowd around here.
Let's watch it on TV later.
You're also admitted?
Go back and study.
Hello, Li Zerui.
First, congratulations on
I'm not afraid.
your early admission
to Chengjiang University.
Margin call is fine.
Buy more.
I'm not afraid of a full position.
See what I told you?
It's not that serious
I think interest is the best teacher.
He sure is a proud kid.
[Hangfan TV]
Do you feel any pressure?
The pressure hasn't changed.
So I'm going to prep for college courses
during the summer vacation.
So imposing.
This is the kid from your school
who got early admission, right?
He's not a kid.
He's already a college student
at Chengjiang University.
He hasn't even enrolled yet.
Just a kid.
Let's also apply
to Chengjiang University later.
Your mom's right.
Let's apply to Chengjiang University, too.
We can absolutely get admitted.
If Shan also gets
into Chengjiang University,
they'll be classmates
and hometown friends.
They can take care of each other.
I'm not familiar with him.
No problem.
You'll get familiar in two days.
- Come and eat.
- Exactly.
Look, you like fish.
Your mom cooks it for you every day.
Hurry up.
You won't be able to eat it soon.
You're going to college.
And this is your favorite.
[57 Days before the Examination]
Have more fish.
[Li Zerui will get
into Chengjiang University.]
[He Shan will get
Half achieved.
It'll all be achieved.
It's for you.
What is it?
A World Cup commemorative T-shirt.
My dad bought it
on a business trip to Munich.
Don't you like soccer?
One for each of us.
Thank you.
You look like a fool, unlike a student
admitted to Chengjiang University.
Why don't you try it?
If people see us
wearing the same clothes,
they'll talk to your parents.
They said last night
that if I also get
into Chengjiang University,
we'll take care of each other.
What did you say?
I said I'm not familiar with you.
Why did you lie?
I told a good lie
for the right purpose.
A lie is a lie,
not good or bad.
What do you think will happen
if we both get
into Chengjiang University?
Don't envision the future.
When the day comes,
time will give us the answer.
I hate waiting.
I've always turned
in my exam papers early.
But you turn in everything early,
except this.
I've been looking forward
to leaving Huishan
and that home for a long time.
You thought we bought too little food.
We haven't finished the food
we bought yesterday.
Forget yesterday's leftovers.
Cook them something fresh and delicious.
Zerui,
come upstairs.
We'll celebrate for you.
Zerui, congratulations.
Hurry up and come upstairs.
Zetian.
Dad.
You're back.
Let's make room.
It's so grand.
My son got early admission
to Chengjiang University.
Such good news.
We have to celebrate it.
Right,
here.
Take it.
For good fortune.
Thanks, Dad.
It's fine.
Zerui.
Hello, Auntie.
If your brother did half as well
as you in school,
we wouldn't have to worry so much.
It's all set. Come on.
Zerui,
go wash your hands.
Well...
What a kid.
Where's my red envelope, Dad?
Your brother got admitted.
What about you?
Don't mess it up.
My son is doing well.
Come on.
Congratulations to Li Zerui
for being admitted
to Chengjiang University.
Come.
Congratulations. Cheers.
Thank you, Auntie.
It's all your favorites.
Come... Let's eat.
Auntie.
Zerui,
congratulations.
I have a gift for you.
You've always liked it, right?
Thank you, Auntie.
Zerui,
I have something to discuss with you.
What is it?
I've kept some things in my heart
for years.
I did wrong you
and your mom back then.
Since your mom passed away,
I've been feeling guilty for years.
Whenever I burned incense sticks
and bowed to Buddha,
I chanted sutras for her.
It's been so many years.
Forget it.
Zerui,
since you came into our family,
I never mistreated you, right?
We're still family.
Auntie,
if you want to say something,
just say it.
Zetian's second mock exam result
came out.
It just passed 410,
not even enough
for a second-tier college.
Tell me.
Why is he so far behind you?
You have to ask yourselves.
We have the same father.
Yes,
he's just like me,
a stupid head.
You...
Don't you think
he looks like you?
Like my father.
You're brothers.
Brothers should help each other.
The entrance exam is in a few days.
How can I help him improve his grades?
I'm not counting on you
to help him improve his grades.
I'm counting on you
to take his exam.
Only the three of us
know about this.
I won't even tell your dad.
Please. Help us.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I really don't want him
to study for another year.
Even if he does,
he might still fail the exam.
Life is so short.
Isn't it a waste of time?
Don't people who didn't go to college
have a successful life?
People who go to college
are more likely to succeed.
Zetian is the only thing
I have to hold on to,
just like you do for your mom.
If you don't want to say yes,
forget what I said.
Don't tell your dad.
Auntie.
Thank you.
Rest early.
As long as Zetian can go to college,
I'll do anything.
The admission ticket is printed
in black and white.
The invigilator won't look at it
that closely.
You're so good at it.
Just lend him a hand.
It'll be no problem.
Dad,
Mom will be buried tomorrow at 8:00 AM.
The ashes will be buried at Ziyun Hill.
[Yongfu Hall]
Wait for me.
I'm heading out right now.
Who's calling?
Zerui.
Okay.
Don't take our car to send her off.
Are you insane?
Zerui's waiting.
Doesn't she have any other
relatives or friends?
Who would let their ex-husband do this?
She's gone. You're still hung up on her?
Don't go.
It brings bad luck.
You...
You're hysterical.
I'm telling you.
If you go today, then never come back.
Come in. Come.
Zetian,
this is your big brother.
Zerui, this is your little brother.
Come. Come in.
Look.
During the day, this is just a sofa.
You can open it up
to make it a bed at night.
It's not a big house,
so we must make do.
Dad, I think
the room downstairs is nice.
I'll live there.
It's a utility room.
It's not a place for people to sleep.
It's okay. There's a sofa.
Just listen to me. Come on. Come in...
Come in.
Auntie.
Zerui, what's wrong?
About last night,
I will do it.
Really?
Zerui,
you mean it seriously?
We're family.
Zetian is my brother.
I should help him.
Thank you, kid.
You're really a good brother.
Great.
Dear audience, today is 7 June.
The 2005 college entrance examination
kicks off.
Today, the temperature has dropped
to over 20 degrees,
which is quite comfortable.
- This year in Huishan, 11,700 students
- Check and do the easy questions first.
- are taking the entrance exam. I'm now
- Tackle the hard ones later.
- at Huishan No.1 High School.
- Make sure you get the name and ID right.
- The school and the traffic police are
- Do a thorough check if possible. Ace it!
- all in place, standing by,
- Go.
making every effort
to create an orderly
and warm examination site.
[Sealed]
Dad, I'm all set.
Put your best foot forward.
I
believe in you.
No problem.
Come on, get in the car.
Zerui, why are you going?
To cheer for Zetian.
Good. The two of you coming together
can achieve anything.
Good luck. I'll be waiting
for good news from you.
Come on, boy.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Don't drive too fast.
Sure.
Zerui,
thank you.
[Li Zetian's Admission Ticket]
[Huishan National
College Entrance Examination]
Zerui,
be careful.
Li Zerui,
why are you here?
To cheer for my brother.
Your brother?
You cheer for your brother?
Right.
Where is he?
He went to the restroom.
I'll wait for him to finish
and check his answers.
Go!
Aren't you going to cheer me on?
Good luck.
And you're wearing this T-shirt.
Yeah, you gave it to me.
Do you know what this means in German?
What does it mean?
''Viel Erfolg''
means ''Wish you success''.
Viel Erfolg, I can do it.
You surely can.
Good luck.
Let's meet at Chengjiang University.
He Shan,
good luck.
[Exam Paper Bag]
[Exam Paper of the Ministry of Education]
Now for the first exam, Chinese.
The exam lasts two and a half hours.
The paper consists of six pages
and is worth 150 points.
You can hand in the paper 30 minutes
after the exam starts.
Use a 2B pencil on your answer sheet
for the multiple-choice questions.
Exam starts.
[Name: Li Zetian]
[Name: Li Zetian
Admission Ticket No.: 0502832]
Zetian,
how's your exam?
Not bad.
Stop asking, Dad.
Don't pressure him.
I just checked his answers.
He did really well.
Right...
It's the last day tomorrow. Do well.
Okay.
[Exam Paper of the Ministry of Education]
Arts Comprehensive.
The exam lasts two and a half hours.
The paper consists of eight pages
and is worth 300 points.
Exam starts.
[Li Zetian]
I've booked a private room
at the Shangri-La.
Let's invite your uncle, auntie,
grandma and grandpa
to celebrate your success,
okay?
Let's wait until I finish my exam, Dad.
What a kid.
Let's eat.
30 minutes left before the exam ends.
Don't go.
It's bad luck.
Let's eat...
[Name: Li Zetian]
[Answer Sheet for Arts Comprehensive]
The exam is finally over.
Shan, good job.
Here.
Drink some juice and get some nutrients.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Zerui, how's it going?
Don't worry.
[He Shan's Admission Ticket]
0502511.
Chinese,
128 points.
[Li Zetian's Admission Ticket]
Li Zetian.
Chinese,
117 points.
Mathematics,
131 points.
139 points.
English,
142 points.
112 points.
Arts Comprehensive,
275 points.
zero points.
368 points in total.
676 points.
676 points, a big surprise.
Yeah, 676 points.
Zetian,
think about it.
What...
Did you forget to write your name?
How can you get a zero?
What's going on?
Shan,
if you did so well,
do you think we can get
into Chengjiang University?
It's called
a sure thing.
It's so important.
Don't you have any brains?
Don't panic.
I'll figure it out.
I'll find someone.
As long as you didn't turn in
a blank paper, I'll see if I can fix it,
if I can appeal.
I can study for another year.
Why another year? Study for another year?
You did so well
in the first few subjects.
If you study for another year,
are you sure you'll do better than this?
What if it's not as good as this year?
No way.
We can't just
let this go.
Zetian,
think about it and try to remember.
What if we can fix it?
Right...
Try to remember.
Did you fill in the answer sheet or not?
Say something.
Shan, you're a student
of Chengjiang University now.
Let's think about how to celebrate.
Invite all your brothers
and sisters over.
I'll go out and book this place later.
You go first.
Zetian.
Zetian, let your brother go. Let go.
Let Zerui go.
You're going to strangle him.
You let Zerui go.
Are you nuts?
Zerui,
let him go.
Zerui.
Zetian, have you lost your mind?
Have you lost your mind?
What are you doing?
You scoundrel.
You're crazy.
Coming.
Who is it?
Hello.
Hello, He Shan's home, right?
You are...
We're
from the Huishan Education Commission.
We'd like to check on one case.
Can we talk to He Shan?
Shan,
it's for you.
Okay.
Hello,
you're He Shan
from Class 5, Year 12,
of Huishan No.1 High School, right?
Do you know
Li Zerui from Class 1, Year 12?
I know him.
Here's the thing.
On the 6th and 7th of this month,
the two days
of the college entrance exam,
did you see Li Zerui at the exam site
of Huishan No.10 High School?
Yes.
What happened to him?
We suspect he's a surrogate exam-taker.
Recall your memories
and cooperate with the investigation.
Zetian.
Zetian, you can't go with them.
Sir,
I'm begging you.
Zetian.
- Please.
- Zetian. Don't get in the car.
I'm begging you.
Sir, you must be mistaken.
He's still young.
Listen to me.
We're just investigating,
not accusing him of breaking the law.
Zetian.
You must be mistaken.
Sir.
Alright, get in...
Zetian.
It was a strange summer,
very cool.
I heard it was because
the earth had turned to the aphelion.
In July,
I was admitted into the Journalism School
of Chengjiang University.
but I wasn't the least bit excited.
After that,
they confirmed the evidence
that he's a surrogate exam-taker.
so his admission
to Chengjiang University was canceled.
We moved.
Your auntie lost her job.
Your brother got punished, too.
He's going out to work.
Great.
From now on,
what are your plans?
Going to college.
College?
Where?
Chengjiang University.
How can you go if you're like this?
I'm sure I can go.
Take this 20,000 yuan.
Find a job.
Dad,
I won't ask you for a penny from now on.
I'm going to be very, very rich.
Zerui,
I've always wanted to ask you.
Ask me what?
Why did you say yes
to your auntie in the first place?
Why on earth did you say yes to her?
Didn't you care
about your own life anymore?
Have you ever thought
that the day you cheated on my mom,
you've already ruined my life?
[Chengjiang University
of Science & Technology]
[Chengjiang University of Technology]
[Chengjiang University]
Is that the bus
to Chengjiang University?
Are you a freshman
at Chengjiang University?
Mathematics School.
Then get on the bus.
How much?
For what?
It's a free university shuttle bus.
Come...
I... I'll do it myself.
[Chengjiang University]
Hey,
you're going the wrong way. That way.
That way.
Thank you.
It's alright. Go.
[Welcome to the new class of 2006!]
[Recruitment for the Animation Club]
[Student Council Recruitment]
[Finance Club Recruitment Launched]
Hey, take a look at the Finance Club.
Would you like to take a look
at the Photography Club?
Go to your right.
Sign in for your dorm.
Freshmen, this way.
Five hundred yuan a bed.
Pay monthly.
[Choreographer's License]
Cold water is free,
[Construction Special Operation License]
but hot water costs 30 yuan more.
[Chengjiang University]
What do you think?
If you take it, pay one month's deposit
and three months' rent in advance.
Okay, I'll take it.
Hello?
6400 Graphics card
to Qiu's.
Chengjiang University?
Okay...
Sure.
Sir,
let me deliver it
to Chengjiang University.
[Chengjiang University Campus Network]
[Please set your username.]
[Username: fake]
[Register]
[Registration Successful]
[Chengjiang University Postings]
Rui.
What?
Take you to the movies.
I don't have money.
It's free.
No need for money.
Will it work?
I've seen all the movies in years.
I didn't pay a dime.
It's an employee benefit.
A lot of people here today.
What's playing in the main theater?
Shooter.
You go ahead.
Mind your step.
Bye...
Watch out for the steps.
Bye.
Bye!
Watch out for the steps.
Let's start work.
What do you mean?
Screw you.
Awesome.
[Name: Xu Ou]
Chengjiang University's student.
You can take the money.
I need to return the ID.
What do you know?
It's the most valuable.
[Name: Xu Ou]
It's encrypted and can't be copied.
It's 3-D printed and 0.8mm thick.
What are you doing?
Chengjiang University just changed
its student ID card this semester.
I'm worried about no template.
It came by itself.
Hey, Feng.
[Name: Xu Ou]
We're taking orders
for the smart ID card
for Chengjiang University.
You can't use it to pay,
but we guarantee it will
be exactly the same as the original.
When are you coming?
Hello,
do you know this Xu Ou?
I'm sorry. I don't know him.
Thank you.
Hello,
do you know this Xu Ou?
I'm sorry. I don't know him.
Hey,
do you know this Xu Ou?
Xu Ou?
A senior, International Trade major,
the President of the Finance Club.
Just find him
in the Finance Club's activity room.
Thank you. This way?
Right.
Okay.
Mr. Xu Ou.
Hello,
can I help you?
Is this your wallet?
Thank you so much. I thought I lost it.
It's not lost. Someone found it.
Someone found it and gave it to me
in front of the campus.
Ask me to give it back to you.
Thank you...
Here.
Take the money.
No...
Check if the money's still there.
Money doesn't matter.
I'll just need my card and ID.
Well, I'm going first.
Hey, which school are you from?
The Mathematics School, class of 2006.
A freshman.
Won't you consider joining
our Finance Club?
What's the Finance Club for?
It's in line
with your Mathematics School.
Undergraduate in Mathematics,
graduate in Finance.
It's perfect.
Since fate brought you here,
why don't you fill out a form?
[Finance Club, Chengjiang University]
Next time.
I have a class and am late. Next time.
Finding Xu Ou's student ID
provided an opportunity.
I finally entered Chengjiang University.
I can finally get back
the chance I once lost.
Hey,
the computer is full of client secrets.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I only solve questions
and write comments in the forum,
nothing else.
If you like solving questions so much,
you should study for college.
I didn't get in.
Thanks to Xu Ou,
I've been getting a lot of orders.
Why do they need this card?
Take classes. Study for graduate school.
Aren't they afraid they'll get caught?
Do you know how many people
are at Chengjiang University?
Undergraduates, graduate students,
faculty, staff, and their families,
adult education students,
all kinds of people,
tens of thousands in total.
Hundreds or thousands of students
in one school.
Many of them never spoke to each other
until they graduated,
without knowing each other.
♪The lights are on my wounds again♪
♪Not saying anything,
but feeling uneasy inside♪
♪Still pretending to be happy♪
♪I can't even blame you
for being so cruel♪
♪When you're lost and sad♪
♪I even don't have the right
to comfort you♪
♪I took a script
that has too many twists and turns♪
♪I can't either love or quit,
just pretending to smile♪
♪Who cares?♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a role
that doesn't have a story to tell♪
♪Wait till the song is over
and everyone's gone♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a puppet led by invisible strings♪
♪Yet watched by your coldness♪
♪As my weary smile fades♪
♪I can only be picked♪
♪With no right to know the outcome♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a role
that doesn't have a story to tell♪
♪Wait till the song is over
and everyone's gone♪
♪I'm just an unneeded character♪
♪Like a puppet led by invisible strings♪
♪Yet performing for your coldness♪
♪Let the most fragile heart ache♪
♪Feeling wronged in silence♪