She’s been coming here for two days now.
You used to be just like her.
I’m Kara.
Allie.
Did you fight?
Worse.
I realized I feel so suffocated in our relationship.
Is that why you came to Siargao?
Just for the short time that I’ve been here,
I realized that
I don't need permission to be myself.
To do what I want.
[JAO] I’m doing all of this
because I love Allie.
I’ll help you,
but please, spare me the details.
What do you mean, as in everything?
He controls everything.
Plans, schedules, what I eat, what I do-
[JAO] Actually, I made a list
of all the possible places Allie might go to.
[KARA] I'm the tour guide, right?
I don’t think she’ll come here.
[KARA] Jao is stubborn.
He thinks Allie’s just playing hard to get.
He won’t stop until he finds her.
I had a hard time throwing him off.
Just make sure, okay?
That you have sound judgment.
Kara!
[JAO] Allie?
Allie?
I’m not Allie. Who are you?
Sorry, Jess. He thinks you’re his ex.
Sorry. I thought you were someone else.
Are you following me?
I was calling you back there by the main road,
you must not have heard me.
Stop pestering me.
We’ve been searching for Allie all day.
Okay, sorry.
I'll go ahead.
Close call.
I know.
Don’t come. Jao’s here!
[AHON BY JL]
[MAN SINGING]
Excuse me, sir.
Can I ask you something?
Have you seen this girl?
I don’t know her, sir.
Look closely.
I don’t know her.
Okay. Thanks.
Excuse me, ma’am.
Have you seen this girl?
No, I haven't.
Okay, thanks.
Jao! Go get some food there.
I’m fine.
Is there really no other boat available?
No. It’s peak season.
What about that?
That one’s broken.
Is there really no other way we can go someplace else?
Maybe we can rent a private boat.
Well, I can’t leave.
I have a commitment here.
You just won’t quit, huh?
I don’t give up easily.
It's one of the qualities Allie liked about me.
That's why she said yes to me.
Before...
I was so focused on schooling. Plus, I was an introvert.
Allie was the total opposite.
Rich kid, life of the party.
An extrovert, basically.
But when we got together, I really stepped up.
I picked her up and dropped her off every day.
I always check on her.
I would ask her if she has already eaten.
- You know, every-- Maybe that’s why she left.
You babied her too much.
Wait, enough about me.
Why are you here?
What? Leave me out of it.
Why? You're the only one who can ask questions?
I’m just curious because, you know…
How could someone who has a perfect life in the city
decide to move to the island?
You don’t need to know that.
Come on.
Okay. Well…
Here in Siargao, I’m not bound by
other people’s expectations.
I can be myself. I’m not pressured.
Life is slower here, which is really, really nice.
And moving here
made me learn how to stand on my own.
That’s how it is.
You need to leave the place you came from
to learn how to stand on your own.
Who knows? Maybe that's what Allie needs.
I’m not leaving here without her.
A fruit, of course.
Vegan...
Are you good with this?
Thanks.
Anything you want?
Every time I wanted to do something,
he’d just brush it off.
Or he’d make up an excuse…
just to stay in control.
He always had to be in control.
What about what I want?
You can try...
mussels…
and vegetables.
Here.
Is that okay?
Where are you going?
I'm going to ask around over there.
[KARA] Allie, can you…
[ALLIE] I’m leaving tomorrow.
I need to lie low a bit. Let’s meet.
You better sing later.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
- Come on, hurry. - Brother, need help?
- Let’s get this started. - Almost ready.
It just needs stronger fire.
By the way, are you settling in just fine?
If you need anything, just let me know.
No worries. I’m good, brother.
Your hotel is amazing.
Okay, so what do we have here?
Cooking barbecue…
Oh! Perfect.
[BACKGROUND CHATTER]
Pineapple juice for pork?
Yup!
It makes it more tender and it makes the sauce
more savory and sweet.
That’s what we do in our restaurant.
Let me try it, okay?
Okay, I’ll tell you what…
I’ll do one classic and one with pineapple juice.
Okay. We will taste it later.
If it’s bad,
you will eat everything and pay for it all.
Deal?
Game. But if it’s good, you owe me soju, okay?
- Deal - Good evening.
Jao!
This is Quinito,
the best chef in Manila.
And this is Jao.
- Hi. Jao. - ‘Sup, brother?
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Come on, join us.
- Join us. - Come on, join.
Karaoke night.
No, I’ll pass.
I need to rest. I had a long day.
You guys enjoy.
Oh.
- Too bad. - [ARIEL] That's mama's favorite song!
Okay!
[SIARGAONON] Good evening to you all,
my Katig people!
[CROWD CHEERING]
This song is for you.
Let’s go!
[PEARL CLEARS THROAT]
Go, Miss Pearl!
[PEARL LAUGHING]
[PANGARAP NA BITUIN BY SHARON CUNETA]
[PEARL CLEARS THROAT]
[ARIEL CHUCKLING]
In which corner of the sky will I find
The luck I have never felt.
I have only seen in my dreams.
A glance at the heavens and a genuine smile
Stars will shine
Guiding me to the right path...
Everybody!
Little by little, I will reach
The heavens and the stars
Little by little, my future will shine
I’m holding on
to courage
Tomorrow, when I wake
My dream star will be with me.
There you go!
[CROWD CHEERING]
- Next! - Amazing!
Who’s next?
Han Bin oppa.
- Han Bin oppa! - Han Bin oppa!
- Me? - Yes.
Yes, please sing for us.
[HAN BIN] Okay. Let’s go.
- Han Bin oppa! - Han Bin oppa!
Wow!
[HAN BIN CLEARS THROAT]
[AKIN KA NA LANG BY THE ITCHYWORMS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[QUINITO] Go, brother!
Don’t believe him
He doesn’t really love you
Your life would be a waste
- If you go with him... - Pearl.
You sing really well.
Do you sing?
Not well.
Do you dance?
Are you sure?
Look at you!
Get up on your feet!
You’re doing great!
More! There you go!
[PEARL LAUGHING]
- Just be mine - [PEARL LAUGHING]
There’s no one better than you.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Thank you, guys.
Han Bin oppa!
I didn’t know you had such a good singing voice.
- Thank you. - I’ll upload the video
of your performance on my vlog, okay?
No, no, no, no!
Why?
You’ll have so many fans.
[HAN BIN SIGHS]
Just please don’t.
I’m a private person. Please don’t do that.
Delete the video.
Okay, chill.
But I’ll send it to you first so that you can see it.
And then I’ll delete the video. Here.
Okay.
I’ll just upload Pearl’s singing video.
Thank you.
[KOREAN] Geon-bae? Cheers?
[KOREAN] Geon-bae. Cheers.
[CAROL] What?
Feeling guilty already?
[KARA GROANS]
I shouldn’t have gotten myself involved.
It feels wrong getting Jao’s hopes up again tomorrow.
So what's your plan?
I’m just thinking of Allie.
She really doesn't want to face Jao.
- Sounds complicated! - I know.
Should I talk to her?
We’re meeting tomorrow.
Do what you think is right.
I’ll make some tea.
- Yes? Okay. - Yes, please.
[CAROL SIGHS]
[KARA SIGHS]
[HORN BLARING]
Sir, is it still there?
Yes, ma'am.
It’s Captain Abong, Pilot.
Pilot.
Very good nice!
Here.
Is that okay?
Allie!
Kara!
Oh, my gosh!
Thank you so much for helping me.
Where are you going?
Anywhere.
Far away from Jao.
Are you really set on that already?
I feel like Jao really cares for you a lot.
He seems to really love you, Allie.
What if you just stay?
[HORN BLARING]
[MIKA] Sir, I found this photo on one of Allie's friend’s profiles.
Taken just last month.
[JAO] You were fooling me all along.
All this time, you made me believe you didn't know Allie.
I thought by keeping you away, I was doing the right thing.
I want to talk to her.
Take me to her, Kara, please.
Hello, Kara?
[KARA] Hello, Allie?
[JAO] Allie?
Hello, Allie?
All he was really thinking about was Allie.
I enabled Allie.
You should have stayed out of it.
[KARA] No need to rub it in.
[BOSS] Everything all right on your end?
I’m flying out Thursday, sir.
[BOSS] Keep me posted.
This project is going to be huge!
[PEARL] Oh!
What happened, Pearl?
Nothing, sir.
- Something is in my eye. - Wait, let me see.
Jao!
We’re going to Pacifico. You want to surf?
No, maybe next time. I need to go somewhere.
Too bad.
You’re going on another tour?
Actually, I found her, Mr. Han.
I found Allie.