We are all destined to be together
From the start of our life, we have decided to part
It's a trace of love
I'm like you, how can I get rid of you?
I hear a sound of a log, I miss you so much
I miss you so much, I miss your voice
I don't want to be separated from you
I hear a sound of a log, I miss you so much
I'm like you, how can I get rid of you?
Episode 1
Jiang Yao, you go first, you are our teacher, they won't make you feel bad
Let's go together
Jiang Yao, the mission is done, leave the rest to us
You go first
Mission, sorry
Jiang Yao, get up, the breakfast is ready
I know
Mom
I bought it for you
What's wrong with your mouth?
I'm on fire
Then let the kitchen cook some tender soup, eat slowly
President Jiang, why don't you eat?
The newspaper said that a big person came to the city recently
The young general of Jiangbei
It's said that Jiangbei will be called to his hands
Jiangbei Young Marshal Chi Yanzhou
Isn't he the son of Chi Dujun?
I heard that he was defeated by a girl
He lost his important secret in the army
He even made the army so fierce
Isn't it?
He was taken as a son by the leader of the army
But recently there is a military law
This is good for the people
But this morning it's not about the military
Yao Yao, every few days you and Wenlan's engagement
That Mr. Fang is always in the city
I think you have to go out of the city these days
Ok
Eat while it's hot, quickly, I'll make you a hot soup
Du Jun, the medicine was stolen
What did you say? The medicine was stolen?
I told you such a big thing
I told you earlier, isn't it you?
No, no, no
You bastard, you can't even hold a bottle of medicine
I'll bite you, bite you, bite you
Help, help, help, help, I'll go, I'll go
You're wasting my theme
Sell flowers, sell flowers
Come and take a look, sell flowers
Give me some flowers
Are you ok last night?
Did Chen Yanzhou trouble you?
He must be looking for a revenge for that time
What do you want?
He's going to be taken away
The brothers of the group are killed by Chen Yanzhou
Who took him away?
Chen Yanzhou
I'll go find him
No, he came here because of you
If you go again, he'll be bitten by the tiger
Do we have any other way?
Miao Zhao
Not only did he take revenge on your old lover
but also took away Du Jinshan's medicine
and made him a suspect between the two
Now he's just waiting to be taken away by the fish king
Miao Zhao, he's really a master
This medicine is not just for me
Your father was also very angry with Du Jinshan
But who would have thought that even a dog could find the tiger teeth
He was also the biggest man in the world
But in the end, Jiang Yao is still the best
Yesterday you took her back
I thought you could kill her
How could you be so tender?
Don't underestimate beauty Yun
Although she looks tender and kind
she's very gentle
She's free and kind
She's even more beautiful
You know her so well
You seem to really like her
Don't touch her
You're still raising this flower
Why not?
She's just reminding me
Some things are beautiful
but they're poisonous
Flowers are
and people are
Well
I didn't get the chance to feel it yesterday
I personally sent it to you today
It's not impossible
My life is yours
So you want to die
Okay
I'll help you
Jiang Yao
You're just a cheap person
Your life is as simple as a dead horse
If I kill you like this
I'll be too cheap to be yours
What do you want to do?
Of course I want to play with you
I don't want to eat anything else
I want to eat
I told you to go east
You can't go west
I told you to kneel
You can't stand up for me
How's it, Miss Jiang?
Cheap?
Why? Are you afraid I'll fall asleep?
Maybe one day I'll be in this situation
So if you think it's hard
you can't kiss me
Although I like to force people to kiss me
I'll kiss you
Commerce
Yummy
This is a heh
Throw out the wine
Pose
Clean it up
If you insist,
I won't mind sharing the truth with you.
Goodbye.
Did I ask you to leave?
What else do you want?
Come here.
Love is a dream
I'm so sorry. I'm so late.
Maybe I'm not worth it.
I'd rather be the one to blame.
I'll never be free.
Love is in the cold.
The world is full of waves.
The love is in the rain.
The past is in the past.
The most familiar place is you.
Love is in the heart.
The past is in the heart.
I can walk with you.
I can't read your story.
I've seen your dream.
But it's also a lie.
I never forget.