I won't let you down
Episode 1
What's wrong?
Why are you sitting here?
Did you sit here for a whole night?
You didn't change your clothes?
Mom, I'm fine.
You can go out first.
Mom, what's wrong?
Tell me.
You can go out first.
Then wait for me to come down and eat.
Episode 1
It's already night.
Miss hasn't come back yet.
What's wrong?
Miss, you're finally back.
Come. Thank you, Miss.
Where have you been?
Why haven't you come back at night?
You're making me angry.
I'm fine.
I just met a friend.
So I've been chatting for a while.
What friend?
You've been chatting for a whole night?
You don't know that.
I didn't sleep last night.
I've been waiting for you.
Is this the Chi Palace?
Yes.
There's a letter from Miss Jiang.
Please pass it to Mr. Chi Yan Zhou.
Okay.
It must be the love letter he wrote to Young Marshal.
That woman left
and didn't let Young Marshal take her.
You're talking nonsense.
What?
What did he say?
He asked me out.
He's here?
I can't wait.
Tell me.
If he's really so cruel,
we can only do it according to the plan.
That's right.
I know.
You're right.
Tell me.
Ma'am.
Young Marshal.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Miss.
Sir, how much is this?
I'll go instead.
As always.
tablespoons.
Your son.
Xin Weiyin is good with Mekong.
He is beautiful.
But it's not me.
Only my son.
Thank you.
No problem.
He and my father are playing japan.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
It's okay.
Miss Jiang, you know this place very well.
Yes.
I often come here.
This is for you.
Tong Xinjie used to pray for peace.
I hope you can also be safe.
It's so expensive.
I didn't come here last time.
Is it okay for you to take it?
Why are you so expensive?
Since you've been here,
you should know
that Tong Xinjie
is going to tie the vegetables
on the tree.
It's so poor to have
a lover on the tree.
Xin Yue is a homeless man.
I bought it.
Thank you.
You're here.
Why did you buy it?
Boss, it's too hot.
I came here
because it's too hot.
There are few people here.
But it's not hot.
Let's go ahead.
Where?
Although it's too hot,
the money is still a waste.
I can't waste it.
I still have to hang it
on the tree.
You're willing
to let Tong Xinjie
marry me
and marry me?
Look, look.
Tong Xinjie is here.
Why are you still in there?
Wait for me.
No matter what,
I will always be here.
The future is still far away.
I'd rather be in the dark.
I'm coming.
There are many lovers here.
But they may not
be able to be together in the end.
The new world is a thousand times.
No one can find it.
That's why
someone will be disappointed
with these desires.
I didn't expect
to be like this.
I know that
people's hearts are a thousand times.
But I didn't expect
that someone's heart
would be fake from the beginning.
Xiaoyao,
five years ago,
you were in the fire for the mission.
Did you have
a moment
because I wanted to leave?
Even a moment,
if I give you another chance,
you will still think so?
I'll take you somewhere.
I didn't expect that
you would leave
before you came.
Yes, I did.
I was a little reluctant
to leave.
Miss,
you are
a person who is reluctant.
I'm not.
What's going on?
What happened?
Miss,
wait a minute.
I'll go down and ask.
Brother,
what's going on?
Mr. Du is here.
What's going on?
It's so good.
Thank you.
Miss,
Mr. Du
is the one
who is in the bomb
outside our company.
It's said that
the old lady in the night
is in a mess.
No one cares.
She often hurt
those innocent girls and children.
It seems that
Mr. Du's friend
is also guilty.
He is in there
and is being justice for the people.
I've heard that
you are
tricking people here.
If you let me see you again,
I'll go.
Take her away.
Yes.
Leave it to the police.
It seems that
we have a close relationship
with Mr. Du.
Mr. Du.
Miss Zhou,
what a coincidence.
Yes.
What?
Miss Zhou
also likes to watch TV?
I've been there.
Miss Zhou, you're hurt.
When I was
tricking people,
I was careful.
It's not serious.
What about you?
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
Get lost!
What are you doing?
Miss Zhou, be careful.
It's so embarrassing.
Miss Zhou.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Du.