Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only. They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series. Viewer discretion is advised.
No animals were harmed or mistreated at any time during filming.
Hey!
I know you’re in there.
Are you going to open the door or not?
If not…
Ti… Tiger, please don’t hurt me.
My kid just started school.
I can’t come up with the money in time.
You can’t come up with the money,
or you can’t stop spinning the slots? Huh?
I’m really sorry.
Please don’t hurt me.
I’ll do anything you want.
I’m sorry. I really am.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, bro.
I’m really sorry. Please don’t hurt me.
I’m sorry. I beg you.
I’m sorry.
Argh!
If you don’t pay me by tomorrow,
you’ll end up like this phone.
Understood.
This is the last stop.
Boss said this one’s the toughest.
I don’t know why.
Anyone who walks in here goes soft
and never comes back with the payoff.
Well, well, well.
They’ve got money to open a cat café,
but they can’t pay off their debt.
What’s wrong with them?
Hey, Dong.
You can go back first.
What?
I’ll take care of this case.
You can hold him.
Go ahead.
You can hold any of my cats here.
Just don’t take them home.
Well, I…
I’m allergic to cat fur.
Oh, really?
But you’re okay just looking at them, right?
Jiro,
keep your distance.
Social dis-cat-ing, dear.
There he goes.
Well…
actually, I’m here for—
Are you here for a cat fix?
You must take off your shoes first.
Welcome.
Every cat here is a stray
that was abandoned.
Cats are like people, you know?
Even if they’re the same breed,
they all have different personalities.
(Most of them like being alone, though.)
(Cats like things neat and orderly.)
(Looking good is their top priority.)
(People usually think
cats don’t understand us,)
(but they actually understand
everything we say.)
(It’s totally up to them
whether they feel like responding.)
I feel truly honored to visit Thailand.
I love the racetracks here,
Thai food, and Thai massages.
But what I love most is…
the Thai smile.
My work here is done.
You can freely enjoy the party, Mr. Enrique.
Have fun.
Aren’t you coming with me?
I still want to talk to you.
(When you talk to cats,
you need to listen with your eyes.)
(They respond to us
through their body language.)
(If cats get angry, they flick their tails.)
(You’d better run,
or they might scratch you.)
Do you want to add a cat to your friend list?
Huh?
Make eye contact and blink slowly.
If they blink back, it means
they’ve accepted your friend request.
Or if you want to go somewhere else with me,
I’m fine with that too.
How about coming to my room?
My partner, who’s an F1 fan, is waiting for me.
I’m sure you’ll spend
the whole night talking together.
Looks like his friend list is full.
It’s alright.
I’ll go find you a new boss.
HOPE YOU FIND YOUR FAVORITE CAT.
I’ve got plenty of cat bosses for you
to choose from.
Come here.
Go ahead, make your pick.
Which boss do you like?
JUMBO, JIRO,
JENNIE
LYNX
That one is named Lynx. He’s my son.
He ran off and became a stray.
He’s a tough nut to crack.
If anyone can make him blink back,
I’m ready to give him up,
along with this café.
LYNX.
Je Meow, your ice is here.
Close the door for me, Krapor.
The cats might sneak out.
Oops, I forgot.
I knew it.
This cold guy is yours.
My whole arm’s already numb.
Then hurry up and fill it.
So cold.
Always with an intro.
You’re such a punctual guy.
No wonder Jennie loves you so much.
Sadhu.
I’ve spent a fortune on her cat treats.
Still, she won’t even let me hold her paws.
That’s why this song was written,
♪ I shed my tears at a cat café ♪
Don’t give up just yet.
Why, Sis?
Just wait and see this man.
Who?
Here he is.
Welcome to Cat-Cheer Café.
Jiro.
Jiro, my boy.
I’ve got to respect Tiger’s dedication.
He’s been here, same time, same place,
every day for three months.
Jiro still hasn’t blinked back at him.
At first, he was like a sugar cat daddy.
When treats didn’t work,
he spoiled him with gadgets instead.
But lately, he’s been coming in empty-handed.
He’s probably given up.
Said who?
He’s been wearing the same old shirt
for like a month.
Huh?
He must’ve heard
cats recognize people by scent.
Let’s see if he finally gets recognized.
Jiro.
Jiro,
let’s be friends.
Yes!
Jiro finally accepted his friend request.
Let’s go over there.
Yes!
That was amazing, Tiger.
Jiro finally accepted your friend request.
Hey, Je Meow.
This isn’t Jiro.
Huh?
They look really similar,
but Jiro has bigger eyes
and chubbier cheeks.
Come on, no drama.
I’m just messing with you.
You’re good, though.
You remembered Jiro.
This is another orange cat
someone’s letting me look after for now.
So I rotated him in with Jiro.
Here you go.
There he is.
Your Jiro.
Jiro.
Tiger’s here.
Tiger could remember you.
Give him a reward.
This is the real Jiro,
with the verified blue checkmark.
Congrats.
Je Meow.
Can I take a picture of Jiro
for my phone wallpaper?
Sure. Go ahead.
How about I take it for you?
Make sure Jiro looks handsome.
Nice.
(Our condo doesn’t allow cats,
in case someone here didn’t know.)
What’s up?
(Hey, Lynx. We’re all here.
Where the hell are you?)
On my way.
(Be real. Aren’t you still at home
and standing us up?)
Good. If you already know, I’m hanging up.
(Hold on. Remember telling me
you were looking for a full-time job?)
(One of my clients is looking for
a full-time interpreter in Melbourne.)
(It’s tough work, but the pay’s huge.)
When does it start?
(Next month.)
(It’s a long-term contract, though.)
(If I could stand being away from my bae,
I’d go myself.)
Tiger!
Hi, Je Meow.
Those are for Jiro?
Yes.
I’m not sure which one he’ll like.
Pick the blue one.
Jiro told me he likes blue.
You can talk to cats?
Shhh.
Yes, I can talk to cats.
Kidding.
Cats see blue better than red.
Oh.
It’s in their nature.
I see.
He’s gonna like it.
After you.
Thanks for helping me carry these bags.
Why did you buy so much stuff?
I bought ingredients
to make fried noodles for Lynx.
It’s his favorite.
He’s dropping by.
I bought enough to make extra for you too.
I saw you always checking out
Lynx’s pictures.
No, I didn’t.
Come on, I’m kidding.
I actually wanted to cook for you
to thank you for going easy on me
about the debt.
So…
you already knew who I was?
I did.
I’m sorry for paying back late.
I haven’t been well,
so I had to close the café a lot.
But I promise
I’ll pay off the debt as soon as I can.
Okay.
Why didn’t you ask Lynx to help you out?
Oi, I was already glad
he even picked up my calls.
We haven’t talked in three years.
I don’t know if something’s going on.
My son’s a tough case, right?
Want to give it a shot?
If you win him over,
the cat café’s included.
I’ll give it to you.
You’re interested, right?
Let’s go.
Oi.
Are you alright?
You okay?
I’m okay.
I’ll be fine.
Just something that comes with age.
Let’s go.
I’m okay now.
Let’s go eat fried noodles.
Oh!
What time is it already?
Gosh, Lynx still isn’t here?
Should you call him?
He probably had something urgent.
It’s fine.
No matter how urgent, he could’ve called.
It’s alright.
Just knowing he’d come
already makes me happy.
I even thought he’d never
step foot in here again.
Cat owners get used to being ignored by cats.
But when it’s your own kid,
no matter how long it’s been,
you never get used to it.
It’s pretty late now, Tiger.
You should head home.
I’ll pack you my Korat fried noodles.
You’ll love it.
You don’t have to.
Come on, my cooking’s really good.
I don’t want to trouble you.
Try them.
Je!
Je Meow!
Je, Je Meow.
Je!
Meow~
(Hey! Call an ambulance now!)
- (What do we do?)
- (What happened?)
- (What's wrong?)
- (What's wrong with Je Meow?)
- (Je Meow, wake up.)
- (Why is Je Meow on the floor?)
(Have you called an ambulance?)
(Call an ambulance. Call it now.)
Hello, someone passed out.
Please send an ambulance right away.
PUNARI VILAWONG
8 AUGUST 1980 – 23 MARCH 2025
Where the hell were you that night?
Do you know your mother…
waited for you until her last breath?
Hey!
(Hey, lil' bro. Your fly's open.)
What happened to me? I really can hear them talking.
Who are you talking to?