[English subtitles are available]
As long as I can take over Ning'an Palace,
I'm willing to pay any price.
Cleanse the court of traitors and sycophants.
The cinnabar imperial brush determines one's life and death.
Everything
is like a dream.
I once was indebted to a lot of people.
Zhang Zhe, help me.
I'll be a good person after this.
I'll marry the one I spoiled.
There are things
you can't give me.
But he can.
To keep my life,
only you, Sir, can help me.
Everyone in the world is entitled to escape.
But I'm the only one who can't.
I want to do my best to make up for
my past regrets and wrongdoings.
Mr. Zhang, do you believe in predestination from the previous life?
I'd rather believe in what's in front of me.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Congratulations on returning to the capital of our homeland.
Ning'er, what are you afraid of?
But in the unfathomable,
there's always an invisible hand
that puts everything back to its original place.
You've taken revenge and paid your debts.
At the end of the day, who are you?
A bustling place, or a battleground.
A life of absurdity, a story of mistakes and regrets.
[Story of Kunning Palace]
[Episode 28]
Who're you? Why are you trying to enter the capital in the middle of the night?
Emergency news from the border.
Request to see His Majesty.
As expected from the vicious State of Yue.
Not long ago, they sent an envoy to submit a credential,
in which they proposed a marriage of state.
Later on, they assembled troops to the border and provoked us repeatedly.
Your Majesty.
This move of the State of Yue
is clearly a threat.
They're trying to tell us, the State of Qian,
that if we don't promise them profits,
they'd resort to arms.
They've shown their greedy and cruel nature.
Your Majesty.
Since the era of Taizu, the State of Yue
has been expelled 300 miles away from the State of Qian.
Over the years, half of Yan's troops have been garrisoning at the border
to intimidate the State of Yue.
Now, why does
the State of Yue have the courage
to invade our border for no reason?
You're underinformed, Mr. Yao.
The troops at the border
were supposed to be replaced every three years.
Now, since the Yan family was exiled, the troops lost their commander-in-chief.
The garrison suffered heavy casualties.
If they switch shifts with the troops in Tongzhou according to the old practice,
it'll require a large amount of military pay.
It must be because the State of Yue witnessed this that they rebelled.
Minister Jiang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
If we go to war with the State of Yue now,
how much military pay can the Ministry of Revenue raise?
Your Majesty.
Over the past three years,
there've been floods in Huaizhou
and locust plagues in Qianzhou.
The government has repeatedly reduced or exempted taxes.
So now, the state's coffers are rather empty.
If we want to start a war,
I'm afraid it won't be in our favor.
So we can neither switch troops
nor declare war.
Are we just going to wait around for the State of Yue to send troops south
and invade our State of Qian?
Your Majesty.
I'm willing to lead troops to the border
and go onto the battlefield myself.
Please allow me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I think
it's inappropriate.
Why?
Wars mainly depend on soldiers,
while soldiers mainly depend on the commander.
Duke Xue hasn't led the army for a long time.
He's not familiar with military affairs and the tactical situation at the border.
Besides, the case of embezzlement on disaster relief funds in Jiangnan hasn't been cleared yet.
Duke Xue is still a suspect.
If he led the army to go to war at this time,
I'm afraid the public wouldn't be convinced.
Zhang Zhe.
Are you suggesting that we State of Qian just endure the humiliation
and send Her Highness there for peace-making marriage?
The matter of leading the army
is vital.
It needs to be treated with great care.
From what you said,
do you have a better recommendation?
Your Majesty.
If the State of Qian is really going to fight with the State of Yue,
for the country and the people,
Old General Yan Mu
is the most suitable person.
Ridiculous.
Your Majesty.
Colluding with the rebels
equals treason.
Yan Mu has been exiled thousands of miles away.
How can he be qualified to lead the army?
Although I have my wrongdoings,
I'm more than loyal to our state
and Your Majesty.
I'm willing to lead the army to the border,
to redeem myself
and serve Your Majesty.
Even if I may die on the battlefield,
I have no regrets.
Enough.
I need time to think about it.
Let's discuss it later.
Xue Yuan?
He's that old,
and his body was drained by his lust for alcohol and women.
He wants to lead the army to war?
What a joke.
Xue Yuan is a man who only does things for profit.
I'm afraid
his proposal of leading the army isn't that simple.
He has many private soldiers.
If he took this opportunity to lead the army north,
then after several battles,
he'd be able to secretly recruit his private soldiers into the army.
That would be his leverage to control the State of Qian.
That old bastard.
He's really full of dirty tricks.
What should we do?
Today in the court,
I wanted to take the chance
of the State of Yue invading the border
to suggest recalling Marquis Yan and Yan Lin to the capital.
I didn't expect Zhang Zhe would have thought the same thing.
He proposed it to His Majesty faster than me.
His Majesty agreed?
If His Majesty agreed,
would he look
so worried now?
So he didn't agree.
His Majesty won't send Her Highness there to get married for peace, will he?
Or, will he let that glutton
Xue Yuan lead the army?
The Xue family is a danger to His Majesty.
But in his heart, the Yan family is also a threat.
He worked so hard
to regain the Yan family's military power.
He wouldn't let the Yan family get back on their feet so easily.
His Majesty's mind is unpredictable.
Whether there'll be a war or a peace-making marriage
is all up to him.
My Lady.
Are you really not going to see First Young Lady?
If she likes kneeling so much, just let her be.
My Lady.
Things may not be as serious as you think.
Didn't other families' age-appropriate daughters
also participate in the election?
The Xue family couldn't just frame whoever participated, right?
But other daughters didn't offend the Xue family
or have an affair with Lord Linzi.
Now,
even His Majesty and the Empress Dowager know about this.
I didn't raise and teach her for over 10 years
to let her
jump into the fire pit and suffer.
My Lady.
Someone who claims to be Her Highness is waiting outside.
She's in the front hall now.
Why did Her Highness
come to our home for no reason?
Don't worry, My Lady.
It doesn't look like something bad happened.
Her Highness didn't bring any attendant.
Besides, her outfit is...
Let's go.
Madam Jiang.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I didn't know you'd come to my humble residence, Your Highness.
I'm on a private visit.
No need to stand on ceremony, Madam.
I'm here for Ning.
Why did you suddenly come out of the palace, Your Highness?
Because I missed you, of course.
Jie's marriage
caused so many troubles.
Now, Mother doesn't allow you to come into the palace to accompany me anymore.
I was so bored by myself,
so I asked Mother for a day off
to have fun out of the palace.
You rarely come out of the palace, Your Highness.
I'll be your guide today
and take you to have some fun.
Keep your word.
I didn't bring any money.
I'm going to use up your money today.
There's indeed the most beautiful scenery in the capital here.
No wonder Yan Lin used to boast about it to me a lot.
It turns out that the world outside the palace is so wonderful.
No one would choose to be born to be trapped in a cage.
Those outside the palace try their best to get in.
But after entering the palace,
they'd find there's no turning back.
Yes.
Who wouldn't want to leave that place?
Unfortunately, Yan Lin had a choice,
but I...
Your Highness.
I always look happy to you, right?
Actually,
I've always been pretending.
Ning.
At first, like them, you also thought
I was a fussy and domineering princess
who enjoys the bustle of life, right?
Actually, I know
that I
have a bad temper,
and I'm not well-educated.
Others respect me and awe me,
but they wouldn't connect with me.
Only you and Yan Lin
would talk to me sincerely.
Now, Yan Lin is gone,
Jie
is getting married soon,
things ended up like that
for Shu,
and conflicts are surging
between Lang and Mother.
I thought
as long as I keep living carefreely,
these things would have nothing to do with me.
Unfortunately...
In life,
we all have our own responsibilities to bear.
Your Highness, you were born noble,
so you don't have to suffer from hunger and coldness.
You have your family to keep you company,
and you made many friends.
Although you have things to worry about,
you're still quite lucky.
Is that so?
If things could start over,
I'd rather not have this luck.
If possible,
I don't want to be born in the royal family.
I also want to leave the palace
and explore the vast world.
Your Highness.
What's the matter with you today?
Did something happen in the palace?
No.
I'm just chatting with you.
When I get the chance,
I'll ask Lang to issue an edict
and allow us to travel around the world.
Shuzhong,
Jinling,
and that sea in the south.
We'll go to all those places together.
We must ask Yan Lin to join us.
Yes.
By then,
Yan Lin must have become a general.
He'll have a sword and golden armor.
He'll escort us
to leave the capital
and never come back.
Okay.
Your Highness.
It's time to return to the palace.
I was permitted one day's leave.
Why?
It's not time yet.
It's already dark.
His Majesty and the Empress Dowager
are both worried about Your Highness's safety.
If you want to stay a little longer, Your Highness,
we'll stay here to keep you safe.
No need.
I'll go back with you now.
Yes.
Ning.
I'm leaving.
There're lots of things going on in the palace lately.
Don't come into the palace.
Your Highness.
What happened exactly?
Everything is fine.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Something wasn't right with Her Highness today.
Did something happen?
Miss!
-I...
-What's wrong?
Chang Zhuo told us
that...
What did he say?
He said
he heard that
the State of Yue submitted a credential and proposed a marriage of state.
His Majesty is considering it.
[Coffin of Princess Leyang]
No wonder she acted like that today.
But why did it happen even earlier?
What happened earlier?
No.
I have to go into the palace.
Miss.
What nonsense are you talking about?
The palace's gate has long been closed at this hour.
You may leave now.
I want to be alone for a while.
The State of Yue?
Peace-making marriage?
She will die.
No way.
Absolutely not.
Sir.
Have a seat.
Sir, so you know that Her Highness
is going to be married there for peace?
His Majesty hasn't issued the edict yet.
Since you knew it,
why didn't you tell me earlier, Sir?
Are you here to question me today?
Sir.
Her Highness can't agree to that peace-making marriage.
It's exactly because the imperial edict hasn't been issued that there's still a chance to change it.
You want to get involved in this?
You know
how well she treats me.
On my way here,
I heard some rumors
and came up with a plan.
But
I have some doubts and I'm a bit hesitated.
So I wanted to ask you, Sir.
Why don't you play a game with me first?
I'm not good at the game of Go.
I can't think many moves ahead of my next move.
I'm no match for you, Sir.
Playing Go does require calculation.
It's indeed a method.
But when we talk about the game of Go,
it's more about momentum.
Calculation is only a method,
but if you can seize the momentum,
that's the essence.
Momentum?
The Go board is like the territory,
and the stones are like the soldiers.
Since ancient times, the water that bears the boat
is the same that swallows it up.
Losing one stone may be negligible,
but as time goes on, the losses may accumulate to form a momentum.
By that time, the problem will be hard to solve,
and it will cause trouble.
Therefore,
a Go player should take advantage of the momentum.
Ruling the people and flood control are the same.
How can you compare people to stones?
A stone is controlled by the player,
but everyone has a mind
of their own.
You can control stones when playing Go,
but if you want to talk about controlling people's minds...
Times make heroes,
and heroes shape the times.
Although it's hard to predict people's attitude,
if they don't think clearly,
once others fan the flames,
it's not hard
for a person's mind to follow the momentum.
I understand.
Thanks a lot, Sir.
So you're not going to ask?
I already got the answer.
However,
I want to borrow someone from you, Sir.
Look at the Xue family.
[Candidate, Weng Ang]
What a bunch of losers.
They plotted and schemed for a long time
to take down the Yan family,
causing the shortage of manpower at the border.
Therefore, we failed to keep the State of Yue outside the border.
Now,
they've started to invade the border,
and the safety of the State of Qian
can only be secured
by sending the princess there for peace-making marriage.
How gritty!
Well done!
Qifan.
You can drink as you wish,
but you can't talk nonsense like that.
Are you drunk?
I'm more than sober.
In my opinion,
whoever caused the trouble
should be the one to solve it.
We may as well send
the daughter of the Xue family to the State of Yue for peace-making marriage.
Isn't that good?
She has good looks,
and she's of high status.
The State of Yue must be happy with it.
Qifan.
Let's go somewhere else.
There are too many people here watching.
I'm not drunk yet.
It's okay. Let's go.
I'm not drunk.
Let's go somewhere else.
I know that man.
He comes to Cengxiao Restaurant for drinks a lot.
I heard that he's a candidate.
His name is Weng Ang.
People call him Weng Qifan.
He's very talented.
That's why
he's arrogant
and dares to say anything.
What?
Miss Jiang, do you have a crush on him?
Are you serious?
What do you see in him?
The will of the people.
In the streets,
one or two people's words
may be negligible
and will disappear in an instant.
But the voices of thousands of people
are different.
I wanted to see you here
for this.
You're thinking about controlling the will of the people?
Not controlling,
but guiding according to the momentum.
The will of the people already exists.
Everyone
has their own judgment.
Weng Ang is like that.
It's also true for others.
As for the State of Yue's disruption of the alliance and troublemaking,
Her Highness's peace-making marriage,
and the doings of the Xue family,
there're already lots of voices against those
among the public.
But those voices are too scattered and too weak.
What I want
is to amplify the people's voices
to form a torrent,
which will become the power to stop Her Highness from getting married.
You've been in the streets for a long time.
You must have your connections.
You can count on me
for this.
But...
But what?
If you want more people,
this is a must.
30,000 taels.
Ask me for more if it's not enough.
This...
Really?
I didn't know
you are so rich.
This was meant for someone else.
I didn't expect after what happened,
this money would be used here.
But you...
You can ask someone else to do this.
Why
does it have to be me?
Because your surname is Xue.
If you get caught,
the Xue family will be the one to blame.
It'll have nothing to do with the Jiang family.
I...
How is the investigation going?
The case Minister Jiang brought up is well hidden.
Since the government's money for disaster relief
is specially marked,
I used my connections in business to investigate,
found the private bank that specializes in erasing the marks
in the dark market,
and finally found a clue.
It's said that
after the Xue family embezzled the money,
they bought a lot of military supplies with that money.
The arms of Tongzhou Army
and the military supplies here.
How many soldiers is Xue Yuan maintaining exactly?
But
why does he need so many soldiers?
Is he planning to rebel?
That's too bold.
He's eager for quick success.
It's not surprising that he has such thoughts.
Besides, Xue Yuan is very scheming.
I'm afraid he also hid it from the Empress Dowager.
If so,
our plan to deal with the Xue family needs to be adjusted,
in case they get irritated and act on impulse.
How's it going with Ning'er?
She's generous.
She offered me tens of thousands of taels
without even blinking.
In order to save Her Highness,
she's willing to sacrifice anything.
Sir.
Zhou Yinzhi is waiting outside. He wants to see you.
Zhou Yinzhi?
Why haven't I heard of him?
Who's that?
He's one of the Xingwu Guards.
Xingwu Guards?
Wait.
Why does he want to see you?
He must have his own reasons.
Greetings, Mr. Xie. I'm Zhou Yinzhi.
What brings you here
in the middle of the night, Mr. Zhou?
To be honest,
I've been suspected
by Duke Xue since I helped Miss Jiang several times.
Now in the Xingwu Guards,
my hands are tied.
So I specially came here tonight to ask you
what I should do in the future, Mr. Xie.
Please enlighten me.
I heard that
Duke Xue maintained some unregistered Xingwu Guards
near the capital.
The Ministry of Justice has also been investigating this case recently.
If you really want to defect to us, Mr. Zhou,
why don't you look carefully for some evidence first?
When I report to His Majesty about this,
I won't forget your contribution, Mr. Zhou.
I understand
what you mean, Mr. Xie.
Have you heard?
His Majesty has been investigating
the embezzlement of disaster relief funds in Jiangnan from 3 years ago.
It's said that Duke Xue was the mastermind behind it.
Yes.
So many people died in Jiangnan back then.
If it really was the Xue family that did it,
we can't let them get away with this.
This is serious.
Let me tell you.
If back then, the Xue family...
The Xue family
not only embezzled money,
but they also tried to attain power.
The Yan family was persecuted because of this.
If the Yan family was still there,
why would Her Highness have to get married for peace?
I heard that
not long ago,
Miss Xue abused her power in Xingwu Guards
and framed others with rumors.
But she didn't get punished at all after things got exposed.
Is that the privilege of the Xue family?
Why is it not the Xue family
that marries their daughter to the State of Yue?
What kind of world is this?
Exactly. What kind of logic is this?
If there will be a peace-making marriage,
the daughter of the Xue family should be the bride.
The Xue family should be the one to do it, right?
Why should they just enjoy the privileges and not take the responsibility?
Why should the Xue family just enjoy the privileges and not take the responsibility?
Exactly.
Mr. Xie.
Have you heard about
the public opinion on the Xue family in the capital?
What public opinion?
I've been busy recently,
so I didn't notice.
I don't know what happened exactly,
but in the streets, there've been voices that demand
the Xue family to confess their crimes.
They also said Miss Xue should be sent there for peace-making marriage instead of Her Highness.
In short, the public is very dissatisfied with the Xue family.
There are always criticisms in the streets.
Soon, they'll disappear.
Besides,
Duke Xue will handle these things himself.
-We don't have to worry about it.
-Yes.
Yes.
We should just keep investigating.
Who do you think
leaked the crimes
of the Xue family?
There are many people involved in the case investigation.
And countless Xingwu Guards were investigated.
Anyone is possible.
I'm afraid the source
cannot be traced.
[Cengxiao Restaurant]
The poem you wrote
is really wonderful, Su.
Wonderful.
If it were a little subtler...
Are you Weng Ang?
Yes, I am.
Who are you, may I ask?
Why did you hit me?
So you were the one
who spread the rumor and criticized the Xue family.
So you're Mr. Xue.
Come on, everyone.
Come and take a look.
See if I'm right.
The Xue family is tyrannical
and bullies others.
What Mr. Xue is doing right now
is the best evidence.
I'm more or less a man of honor,
yet you dare to hit me in public.
If I were a commoner,
he might do something even wilder.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll teach you how to behave.
We studied hard for more than 10 years
and passed the imperial examination
with the aim of seeking justice
and voicing injustice,
not begging for mercy from you powerful people.
I won't change my word
even if you beat me to death today.
Fine.
You're a tough one.
I'll take you back and loosen your bones.
Arrest them!
What are you doing?
Let go! Let go!
Let go of me!
The Xue family are all degenerates.
I would say the same thing even if you arrest me.
Does the imperial court
belong to the Xue family?
Someone is going to be killed.
Look, everyone.
Xue felt guilty.
He wants to kill me in public.
Is there any law?
Is there any justice?
Exactly. So outrageous.
Am I right?
Is there any justice?
-Go.
-Let go of me!
Don't let him get away.
-Don't run if you dare.
-Move!
Stop him, everyone.
Scum of the Xue family!
Don't run if you dare!
Stop!
You heard it all?
You asked me to leak the information of Weng Ang to Xue Ye.
Is that what you want? Public anger?
The Xue family's foundation is martial arts after all.
They don't know the pride
or the anger of scholars.
Weng Ang is not someone Xue Ye can beat.
The Xue family
will be vilified by the scholars all over the country.
Aren't you afraid that
Weng Ang would be beaten to death by them?
Didn't Teacher send Dao Qin to protect him?
He wouldn't die.
But it hurt.
No wonder even someone like him is under your control.
So cruel.
Bastard!
I told you to stay at home,
yet you went out to cause trouble.
Do you think the trouble is not enough?
Father.
It's because that Weng Ang went too far.
He criticized our Xue family everywhere he went
in the name of a candidate.
He even said that our Xue family is viciously ambitious,
and we should send Shu to the State of Yue for peace-making marriage.
The peace-making marriage is nothing
compared to the collapse of the Xue family.
Can't you even tell what's more important?
Look at you.
How can you be the viscount of the Xue family?
Father.
Father, I know I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Please give me another chance, Father.
Go away!
You are a man.
How inappropriate!
Get up!
Father.
What should we do now?
If we want to win the people back,
we can only follow the will of the people,
not against it.
You mean
we should follow the will of the people
and send Shu there for peace-making marriage?
Please save me, Aunt.
I really don't want to be sent there for peace-making marriage.
Please, Aunt.
If you didn't
use that stupid trick to frame Jiang back then
and didn't get the Xue family involved,
I might be able to defend you today.
After all, the Xue family is powerful.
If you're sent there for peace-making marriage,
it'll be like a thorn in His Majesty's heart.
He also doesn't want the Xue family to collude with the State of Yue.
But look at you.
You handed the knife to His Majesty yourself,
so that he could use that excuse to weaken the Xue family.
But your stupid move
somehow probed His Majesty's mind
by chance.
I have to clean up
the mess you made.
As for the peace-making marriage,
there's nothing I can do even if I want to.
I only agreed to see you today
because you
kneeled outside the palace for hours.
You may leave now.
From now on,
you don't have to enter the palace anymore.
Are you really going to watch
me go to that dangerous State of Yue for peace-making marriage, Aunt?
Zhiyi is my own child.
She can go, so why can't you?
There're no family ties in the royal family.
You are too stupid.
It's not that I'm too cruel.
Aunt.
Aunt!
Please, Aunt!
-I beg you, Aunt!
-Huang Renli.
-Guards!
-Aunt.
Aunt!
Aunt, please!
[Tai'an Hall]
The eunuchs in the palace must have been careless.
How could this thing be here?
[No animal was harmed during filming]
Give it to me.
I know the routes in the palace.
I want to be alone for a while.
I can get out of the palace by myself.
Yes.
If we want to win the people back,
we can only follow the will of the people,
not against it.
You may leave now.
From now on,
you don't have to enter the palace anymore.
Are you really going to watch me
go to that dangerous State of Yue for peace-making marriage, Aunt?
You dragged Xingwu Guards,
your father,
and I into this.
How can I show you mercy?
Bastard!
You're a disgrace to the Xue family.
Your Majesty.
Where are you resting tonight?
Nobel Consort Qin has been pregnant for a long time.
If I don't go see her tonight,
I'm afraid she'll come and make trouble again.
Your Majesty.
Miss Xue from Mansion of Duke Xue
has something important to tell you.
Let her in.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
So about Nobel Consort Qin...
It's fine.
I can go later.
You've never been
close to me, Cousin.
Now the palace gate is going to be closed.
Why are you here?
I'm here
to surrender to you, Your Majesty.
We are family.
What are you talking about?
Your Majesty, you work hard to govern our state,
and you're in your prime.
Now that Nobel Consort Qin is carrying a royal heir,
you should have attained great power.
However, the Empress Dowager is interfering with the court affairs,
and the Xue family is deeply rooted so you can't get rid of it.
Your Majesty,
your hands are always tied.
Although someone in the court
dug up an old case which might shake the Xue family,
Rome wasn't built
in a day.
Likewise, the roots of a giant tree can't be pulled out
within a day.
If you want to get rid of the Xue family, Your Majesty,
I'm willing to offer my help.
You're willing to be my knife?
Yes.
Don't forget
your surname is Xue.
Why should I believe you?
My surname is Xue, so what?
In Father and Aunt's eyes,
I'm just a pawn.
When I'm no longer useful,
they can throw me away anytime.
Since I'm destined to be a pawn,
of course
I'd rather be a pawn
for the most noble person in this world.
Shu didn't come back all night.
Could something have happened to her?
Didn't the maid say she went into the palace yesterday?
Maybe she stayed in the palace to serve the Empress Dowager.
It's nothing unusual.
I don't think we need to worry about her.
But this time, she went out
without my order.
When she comes back,
I must punish her by the family rule.
Eunuch Wang.
Congratulations, Duke Xue.
What for?
Your daughter slept in the Imperial Study last night.
She got conferred the title of Consort Xian this morning.
His Majesty ordered me to deliver the edict.
Of course I should congratulation you, Duke.
[Tai'an Hall]
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Who asked her to come?
Get out.
Mother, calm down.
Yes.
Don't get mad and ruin your health
for some
disgraceful hussy.
It's the palace rule
that consorts should greet Your Majesty every day.
Since you are not in a good mood today,
I'll come again tomorrow.
I'll take my leave.
Shu.
You have something to say to me, Your Highness?
Why did you do that?
What did I do?
Shameless?
Getting into His Majesty's bed?
Why don't you ask yourself, Your Highness?
Wasn't it because of you all
that I became who I am today?
When did I ever do anything to you?
You didn't.
We've known each other for years.
But in your heart,
I'm not even as important as Jiang Xuening.
I was born to be a perfect match for Lord Linzi.
But he fell in love with Jiang Xuehui
who's inferior to me in every aspect.
Where were you
when he refused to marry me?
And where were you
when I was abandoned by the Xue family, Your Highness?
Now,
the State of Yue is invading.
You should be the one who marries there.
Why should I go instead of you?
So you think
everything you did
is right?
Are you talking about right and wrong with me?
Your Highness, you've never experienced the taste of losing everything.
When that day comes,
you will know that
everyone
will make the same choice as me.
There is only victory or defeat in this world.
There's no right or wrong.
She actually did that?
I thought
she was supposed to be arrogant and conceited.
I didn't expect her
to disgrace herself like this now that the situation changed.
But walls have ears.
The rumor has started outside.
Even if she was conferred the title of consort,
her reputation would still be ruined.
She seems to have ruined her reputation,
but she saved herself.
Now Her Highness
is faced with the dead end again.
Your Majesty, you still haven't made up your mind to issue an edict?
She is my own sister.
But she's also the Princess of the State of Qian.
She's supposed to share your burden, Your Majesty.
Now you're in a dilemma.
On the one hand, you don't trust the Yan family.
On the other hand, you can't hand the military power over to the Xue family.
There's no capable general in the court that can be of use,
so there's no chance of winning if you declare war.
I also think
it's better not to go to war now.
Why do you say so?
The State of Yue is experiencing the change of royal power.
The new emperor has just ascended the throne.
They also don't necessarily
want to go to war.
In my opinion,
it's just a means for the new emperor of the State of Yue
to win over the people.
But maybe
a peace-making marriage is what they actually want.
The State of Yue is viciously ambitious.
The peace-making marriage can only suppress them for now.
If I really let Zhiyi get married to stop the war,
the people will
spit on me.
I know it's hard for you, Your Majesty.
But it's only called peace-making marriage if we were defeated.
We only want to make that marriage happen
to build a good relationship between the two states.
If a marriage can stop a war,
the people will only be grateful to you, Your Majesty.
Actually, speaking of which,
Zhiyi is not young anymore.
She's already age-appropriate for marriage.
Getting married far away
is just a temporary measure.
When the tactical situation becomes stable at the border,
and when you gain steady control over the court, Your Majesty,
we can get her back.
The biggest taboo
is someone else sleeping on the emperor's bed.
His Majesty wouldn't have conferred her the title of concubine for no reason.
Especially
at this critical moment.
After thinking about it,
there's only one possibility.
Xue Shu cut off her family ties herself
and drew a line.
From now on, she'll change her target
and fight against the Xue family for His Majesty.
It's a good thing
that she'll fight against the Xue family.
But it's not a good thing for Her Highness.
If Her Highness really leaves for the peace-making marriage,
she will be the first one to die
when we go to war with the State of Yue in the future.
How do you know there will be a war?