The End
As long as I can enter the Ning'an Palace
and pay all the price
I will be willing to do so.
The End
Everything seems to be a dream.
I have owed a lot of people.
Chaozhe, help me.
I will be a good person after this.
The End
I will be the one to take the favor.
There are some things you can't give me.
But what about them?
The life you chose is for Mr. You.
In this world, everyone has the right to escape.
But I can't.
I want to regret it.
I will do my best to return.
Does Mr. Zhang believe that everything is decided?
I would rather believe in the future.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
We are all in the same boat.
Ning'an, what are you doing?
In the end,
there is a pair of invisible hands
that will break everything.
The revenge is long.
Who are you?
The Emperor of the mortal world is so long-winded.
The world is so desolate.
The End
Episode 19
You are so smart.
It's a pity that you miss it.
You are so clever.
What do you want to do?
I should ask you this question.
Miss You, how could you hit someone?
The fifth generation of the folding door.
Who doesn't love?
Samsung Galaxy Z series.
Folding mobile phone, Ning'an is like a dream.
If you are hungry, eat good-hearted bread.
Good-hearted bread, Ning'an is like a dream.
No experience, only a cup.
Use the treasure.
The good-hearted treasure, Ning'an is like a dream.
Miss Jiang,
it's not easy to repair the jade vase.
If you want to play,
please go to other places.
But I'm sorry to bother you.
I'll just stand by and watch.
Let's have a look.
See if there's anything you want to buy.
This is good.
Boss,
you are too sweet.
Do you have any sweet?
Try this one.
Does Mr. Zhang come here often?
I'm not interested in the ancient Anjia.
I'm just free and peaceful.
I rely on my mother to make a living for me.
I'm learning the words of the book.
If I repair it here,
I can get rid of the silk.
I have many tools in my house.
I can ask my father to come.
I didn't mean to offend you.
I'm just free and peaceful.
I want to learn the craftsmanship.
I can't ask others.
If you come,
I can ask you to come.
Miss Jiang likes this too?
Yes, I do.
I used to like it.
I didn't like it.
I can like it in the future.
I'm not a liar.
Jiang Xie Ning.
What are you doing?
Stop.
Zhang Zhen.
I've been looking for you these days.
I've also given you several cards.
I don't mind if you don't reply me.
What do you mean?
Is this your man?
Miss Yao, you misunderstood.
I just met Mr. Zhang here.
It's not him.
Shut up.
If I didn't see it today,
I would have wronged you.
How did you tell me in the palace?
What did you do?
You're so calm.
You're so shameless.
What's the matter
with you?
I just want to explain it to you.
Those messages are from someone else.
They want to make a fuss between you and me.
No one wants to make a fuss.
You're lying.
If Jiang Xie Ning told you something,
why did you come to the palace
after you said it in the palace?
If you don't like it
because of me,
I want to apologize to you.
I just never wanted to marry you.
All these things are because of you.
You're so heartless.
You want to marry me.
That's all.
Please don't misunderstand me.
Don't make a fuss
and make me feel innocent.
Chengzhe,
why did you treat me like this?
I'm leaving.
Miss Jiang,
you haven't recovered your health.
All right.
I've seen you before.
You should be dead.
Don't cry here.
You're making me laugh.
Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Zhang and Yao Jia are getting married.
I really understand.
Are you trying to persuade me?
I have something to interfere with.
As long as you don't regret it.
This portrait
is the book of the Fan's Family.
When I first came to the capital,
I only had a house
with my mother's apartment.
Until I broke
the 42 cases in the Ministry of Justice,
I had to live in this house.
Mr. Zhang has no family.
He has a few talents.
If he's not married because of his birth,
he's not.
The family of the Jin's family
is full of joy,
joy,
and love.
I don't like it at all.
I don't like the marriage between
the two of you.
If you marry Miss Yao,
you'll have a good relationship.
Why do you want to hurt her?
Well,
if there's a woman
who doesn't like these things,
it's just that you're in the same situation.
Can't you do that?
Maybe.
I can.
I'm just going to marry Miss Yao.
It has nothing to do with Miss Jiang.
Don't worry.
It's late.
Please go back.
Be safe on the way.
Zheng Zhe,
I'm not the empress this time.
I'm a good person.
Can we be together?
Boss Lv,
did Ying Zimei come back?
She's been in the same position
since yesterday.
She went back to the residence.
She said she was in a bad mood.
Who knows what she's doing?
Boss Lv,
I think
there's still a chance
between people.
There's a chance.
People are always saying that
they've been in the same position for a hundred years.
Besides, we still have a contract.
Right?
Once she wants to break up with someone,
what's the use of the contract?
I've sent someone
to look after the place.
If she dares to act like a flower,
I'll kill her.
But,
tell me honestly.
Why did Jiang Xuening
invest money in the eyes of business?
Could it be
some kind of internal news?
I don't know.
You're confused, right?
Fine.
I understand.
How about this?
You can open a box for me.
You can tell me
what she's going to say to you.
You can tell me.
We're all from the market.
I understand.
How can you do that?
You trust me so much.
I can't betray her.
That's not enough.
Don't talk too much.
I can give you
a hundred taels.
Why are you turning your face when you're talking?
You have something to say.
Say it.
Hong Pei.
You didn't think about it.
I don't have
any customers in this shop.
I just got back from the spring.
His Highness was so angry.
I was so scared that I had to run home.
You're finally back.
I'm afraid you forgot me
a few days ago.
Why are you so cold-hearted?
I brought you
some delicious and fun food.
And you forgot
that you can't forget me?
If you're so cruel,
I'll bring you delicious and fun food.
Don't forget to forget me.
Piyang,
I like it the most.
Please take care of me.
Let's go.
You all can leave.
Yes.
Your Highness,
I'm not here for nothing.
I have something to ask you.
What do you mean?
Did I make you feel bad for not taking care of me?
I was scared to death.
I made you feel bad.
No.
But I still have a plan
for the last time.
My family said
I was not a high-ranking emperor since I was a child.
I didn't deserve to stay in the palace.
I just hope you can order me to leave.
You want to leave?
Ningning,
I'm so kind to you.
Why do you want to leave?
What should I do if you leave?
Your Highness, you're so noble.
You don't need me.
No.
Don't think about it.
Change one.
All right.
Well...
Your Highness knows
I really don't like to play the piano.
Can you do something
that can help me
to get rid of the thing about playing the piano?
I'm talking about Zhao Ge Lian Qin.
But Mr. Xie
made a mistake in person.
Are you afraid of him?
How could I?
I'm a princess.
I'm afraid of Mr. Xie.
I was talking to Yan family
the other day.
I was upset because I was upset.
If I'm even a liar,
I can't do this.
Change one.
No.
Think about it.
Change one.
I'll definitely agree to it.
Then please
let me see your daughter-in-law.
She's the one who's taking care of you.
I'm sure the family can be at ease.
No problem. I'll agree.
It's just a half-do.
It's not a big deal.
Thank you, Your Highness.
These are all given by you.
It's so beautiful.
Sister Jiang.
Your Highness is so nice to you.
I'm so envious.
Your Highness is the same
to all of us.
I've won some awards today.
It's your turn.
Don't forget me.
It's too expensive.
Take it.
This is also so beautiful.
It's not a treasure.
It's just a common reward.
It's worth your pride.
I used to think that
the more stupid I am,
I can't get past Jiang Xue Ning.
Now I see her as a liar.
I can't figure out
why everyone is like her.
We're different from her.
We can't learn
her mischievous attitude.
This is for your dad.
It's just that
she's a person of color.
We'll understand
sooner or later.
I can't get married now.
Uncle,
you've been looking for me for months.
You don't have any words at home?
I...
I'm just a senior.
I'm not good at tea.
Why do you suddenly want to steal my wife?
Are you playing with me?
Why do you want to steal my wife?
Brother Wang, you don't know that, do you?
I was called here
because of you.
Alright.
Don't just chat with me here.
Just go play.
I'm not good at playing with you.
It's okay if you're not good at playing with me.
We have a good friend here.
Jian Er,
take your uncle and sister to play with you.
Don't bully her.
You stay here.
Back to your position.
Maybe I can play with him again.
I clearly don't want to go anywhere.
I'll let you two go so you can rest and rest.
I love you!
I know you're well.
In this situation.
Ourmbforth,
soon we'll fight.
I'll play around.
Go ahead and play.
Oscar is no match for you.
I'm not that kind of person.
You really think so?
Your Highness also thinks that the blood family has a grudge against the Yan family.
The two families are not even happy.
I didn't mean that.
The family affairs can't be changed.
But at least I can control my heart.
I don't have any enemies against the Yan family.
I'm even more envious that he has his own heart.
It's hard for you to think so.
Aunt, there's a mistake.
I don't like you.
But I'm also helpless.
I don't want you to be my brother.
But at least I don't want to be your burden.
Actually, it's not like that.
We know each other since we were little.
It's not like we're burdened by anything.
It's just that there are some things that are too strong.
It's really hard for people to be like that.
I've been wronged before.
Don't let it go.
Aunt Su.
It's you.
Aunt Su, this...
How did this lady enter the palace?
To answer your question,
the girl from the Qingyuan Manor suddenly got hungry and couldn't come to the capital.
She controlled the area with the help of the princess.
This lady is also the daughter of the general in the family.
She came to the palace to the capital.
That's great.
I mean,
as long as she likes to be warm, she will be very happy.
You met her so soon?
I'm afraid that Miss Xue Da is in a bad mood now.
Sister Ning, why did you let me come to the palace?
I'm the princess of the Lingzi King's position.
I'm sure you have heard of it.
Because of this handkerchief,
I think Xue Shu Bao is your own handkerchief.
I used the handkerchief that should have been on you
and used it on me.
I don't want to carry this black pot for you.
So I brought it here for you.
Are you not angry?
It's because I've taken you in.
To put it in words, I'm sorry to you.
And after you found out the truth,
you can not tell me about your feelings.
You can also tell Miss Xue directly.
But you didn't.
You overestimated my feelings and arranged me to meet you.
Why would I be angry?
You're so self-conscious.
I'm afraid that if you enter the palace,
you'll hate me again.
I don't want to be a heartless person.
Maybe I'll have to cut my back.
Anyway, you chose the path yourself.
If you want to be the princess,
you have to be yourself.
Okay, I'm tired.
I'm done talking about what I should say.
Please go back.
The last time I stole your voice,
I won't owe you this time.
The doctor said that after drinking these two,
although it's a good medicine,
you still need to rest well and don't worry.
I saw you were in the room and you were in the bathroom.
How could that be?
Now it's your turn to get me involved.
These days, I'm not in the mood to do anything.
I've been in the mood for two times.
Later, Zhou Ying didn't know what to do.
Now, I'm feeling much better.
It's Mr. Xie's side.
I've asked you several times at night.
I'll report Mr. Xie's answer to you.
Report!
My Lord, the Crown Prince.
Li Yun Xuan has sent the invitation to the Crown Prince's court.
The official is checking the new weapons in front of the house.
I'm here to ask.
I don't know if these weapons are still working.
Why not?
The Marquis's Mansion is in this state of light.
Even if we send the weapons,
how many people will come?
Why bother?
Mr. Xie has taught me that
if you don't fight, you won't be able to see the people.
Now that the Heavens has given us a chance to see the people,
why bother to let my father and I go?
Go back to the house.
If the new guards don't allow the people to go out,
tell them that the emperor just wants Yan family to cooperate with the investigation.
He'll be in charge of the affairs and the principles.
Ask them who dares to stop you.
Yes.
Mr. Zhang has passed away.
He must be talking to His Majesty.
I wonder what he's up to.
Do you still have the script to write?
Your Majesty, I have the script.
It's not appropriate.
Your Majesty,
there are already several days of the new guards in Yong Yi's Mansion.
Now, the Yan family is in charge of the affairs.
The case is closed.
The Ministry of Justice will be the one to decide.
I ask His Majesty to order the new guards to approach the mansion.
It's better for me to hold the crown prince's official ceremony.
Your Majesty,
the new guards are not going to be in charge of the affairs.
Then the mansion of Yong Yi won't be able to be removed.
Now, at this time,
what are you planning to do?
What's the reason?
Your Majesty,
the Minister of State has made a point.
The case of the new guards is now closed.
But the Marquis's Mansion
is always closed.
It's hard for us to find out.
So you mean
I stopped your case?
I'm so impressed.
I just think that
the crown prince's official is a big deal.
He can't wait.
If we delay the time,
we can't delay the time.
Fine, fine.
Isn't it just a ceremony?
Just do it.
The new guards are guarding the entrance.
They can't find out the truth.
As for the case,
I think you can find out
the truth by looking at the details.
Zhang Zhe.
I'm here.
Before Gu Chunfang returns to the capital,
you still have the order.
I'll give you the order.
You'll investigate the six steps in the capital.
You must give me an answer as soon as possible.
Yes, Your Majesty.
類雙激
Ms Xue, you're young
but you're very avowal.
Obviously there's a world
whereçandrible time waiting to come.
Thank you for your compliment.
Miss Jiang just came. She is not familiar with Ke Cheng.
I don't know her very well.
It's hard to say that she is not familiar with the deal.
Why don't you invite Miss Jiang to the scene?
Then please invite Miss Jiang to the scene.
Let's start.
Although Xue Hui is not good at music, she is more willing to take the chance.
I hope you and everyone can have a good time.
This is not good at music.
What should we do?
Ning Ning, it's really your sister.
Why don't you two be a little bit different?
Sister is always smart and kind.
I am not bad at it.
But we can only play with each other.
That's why we are so close.
No, no, no.
Miss Jiang is good at music.
She is so kind.
I can't say that she is not good at music.
It's a very good song.
You all should learn it.
Especially you, Miss Ning.
You know that you are more affectionate.
You should go back to prepare the basic music.
I want to draw tea.
Yes.
Miss Jiang.
Try it.
The peach cake my chef made is so delicious.
Thank you.
I said, Bao Ying.
How can you take out your treasure today?
Didn't you just give it to Xue Ning?
Then I like this, too.
Mr. Jiang.
No need to be so formal.
I just brought Qin Pu back to get it.
What are you waiting for?
Go ask Zhao Ge for love.
Then I will leave today.
I will give you a few pieces of paper.
I heard that Miss Jiang is talented.
I didn't expect that she is so good at this.
Compared to that Miss Jiang.
She is so good.
Miss Yao is over the moon.
I am a little worried for you.
You are the eldest daughter of the family.
I heard that you still have to bear the anger in the house.
You are bullied by her.
If I were you,
and I didn't learn to be so uneducated,
I would be so embarrassed to be a teacher.
Otherwise, the reputation of this dress
would be ruined.
Although my second sister is short of school,
she is far from being a teacher in the house.
Although my family is not as good as those high schools,
but the house management is strict.
If you have any mistakes,
please take care of your parents.
Why do you need to talk so much?
If Miss Yao has nothing to do,
I will leave first.
What a pity.
What are you saying?
I am a good-for-nothing.
I am just a piece of paper.
I am so sorry.
I don't care how you talk about your feelings.
I am just a piece of paper.
Come over and have a tea.
Use some snacks.
A peach cake?
The one from the Yushan House.
I don't like it.
I don't like sweet food.
The chef of the Bao Ying family is from the Yushan House.
He is also famous in the capital.
The peach cake from their family is too sweet.
The cooking skill of the Yushan House is almost the same.
It's better than your cooking skill.
You still remember it?
The Hero
The rabbit Vietnamese did not LIVE
I told everyone to leave.
And I ran into this wilderness.
Now I'm lost.
I can't go out.
I didn't eat or drink.
Eat.
Eat this.
Eat that.
Who made such tasty connecting hearts?
You won't face은 death any more.
I've forgotten I can never forget you.
Actually in the end, I still ate the rabbit.
In front of one could only choose what he hadn't loved,
but overnight, he would have been ousted.
The most real and maybe the ugliest side of the road.
I'm really afraid of death and I'm still very heartbroken.
By the way, sir, where did you buy that peach slice cake?
It tastes so good. I can't help but to say no more.
Sir, don't worry. I've already remembered the past.
Especially about you. I only remember the peach slice cake.
I forgot about it.
I won't make things difficult for you because of this.
By the way, the court today allowed the Yan family to hold a ceremony.
And let Zhang Zhe take over the case of the Yan family and you.
Mr. Zhang?
That's great.
If Mr. Zhang is here, he will definitely return the Yan family to his family.
Do you believe him that much?
I believe you.
The Xue family has just taken a step forward.
You can make them take the next step.
The court today is your first competition.
I admire you.
I hope there won't be any more waves in this ceremony.
There won't be.
Miss Ning'er, you're back.
How are you? Are you tired?
Do you want to have some tea?
Why did you suddenly call me Miss Ning'er?
We've discussed it.
Now we have two Miss Jiang.
We haven't made up our minds.
I'll call you Miss Ning'er.
Call me Miss Xie?
Don't you usually call me Miss Ning'er?
I know she calls me Ning'er.
But I don't know if she's your girlfriend.
What's wrong with that?
But she's the only one who calls you Ning'er.
Only her?
Other people call her...
Right?
Look, we have called you Miss Jiang.
We have called you Xue Ning.
But only Mr. Xie calls you Miss Ning'er.
What's your name?
It's just a matter of time.
Just call me if you feel comfortable.
By the way, how's Lv Xian and Daoqing?
Everything is under your supervision.
That's good.
Be careful when you walk.
Sir, you're back.
I bought a new fish today.
And some glutinous rice and a set of walnuts.
You can try to make a peach cake.
Sir, what's the matter this morning?
Did you hear the teacher's lesson this morning?
My good sister got the questions right.
But he didn't say anything.
You didn't see Xue Shu's face.
You took so long.
You had to make a few jokes to make it work.
That's so funny.
Ning'er.
Have I been too harsh on you lately?
You should have said that to me.
I'm afraid that you can't do it.
I'm afraid that you can't do it either.
It's so hard for me to be a student.
Have you used the lunch box?
What time is it?
Of course I have.
Where's the light?
I've used it, too.
You don't like the light in the palace, do you?
I just got the feeling that I'm going to be idle.
I'm just going to be idle.
I just ate a few bites.
Why?
You can't use the light in learning.
It's another lie.
It's made of honey.
It's not too sweet.
I don't like it.
It's delicious.
It's sweet and not too sweet.
It has the taste of the past.
Sir, where did you buy it?
It's just in the palace.
I made it myself.
If you like it, you can take it all.
Thank you, sir.
Actually, there's one more thing.
I want to thank you, sir.
What is it?
When I was in the capital,
you were like the others.
I was like Jiang Er.
But after you disappeared for a long time,
you didn't call me Jiang Er.
You're called Ning Er.
I didn't notice that,
but now I've come back and I understand your meaning.
It's just a simple name.
What is it?
Jiang Xue Ning, Jiang Xue Hui,
Jiang is the family's surname.
Blood is the self-sacrifice of the rehearse.
Only this name
belongs to myself.
to my Про OC Notice visit
We meet there
company
So she indeed
comforts me
Really
YourDon's kindness
doesn't allow you
He was so upset
to take me as
others
I am not
Which Of your
do you like?
You used to be the only girl in my life.
You are the only girl in my life.
And now,
it's good to face the past.
But if we have to make it clear,
I think that the girl now
knows what she wants,
and it will be better.
It will be better in the future.
Can you understand
that you have no malicious intent
and no place for me?
Are you willing to be honest with me?
What else?
You and I have been like this all along.
Thank you, sir.
Don't worry, sir.
As long as you don't want to kill me,
I will listen to you.
Miss Xie Erwei,
you were even Be 어디 עלilong conversions you.
My dinner thinking this ends like this.
Are you putting the person
who asked you to hand in thisバイ記 something?
Place it here.
I will.
I'll make sure
to study on my master's physicaldegree.
You...
I won't return it to you.
I'll let you find the ring.
I'm afraid that no one can figure it out.
So I'm taking it out on you.
I've never been so stubborn to defeat Jiang Xue Ning
and even entered a Jiang Xue meeting.
So Ji Er is the one who's in charge of the new family.
What do you think I'm saying?
I'm sorry for my aunt's teaching.
A few days ago,
His Majesty was busy with the Yan family's affairs.
Your father...
Now, we need to quickly
set Ji Er's status as the emperor.
So that we won't have many dreams.
Who's there?
I'll go and have a look.
The Ferryman
Hi, Sister Xue.
Sister Bao Ye.
Isn't this Sister Yao's pick?
Why does it come in your hands again?
This fragrant nang is not for Jiang Xue Ning.
Use all the horse's dung.
Are you kidding me?
Move!
Mister,
Mighty美女长,
your husband always
likes to take care of bowl owner.
Right?
Mom,
did you programming
do not support the drama firm?
company?
Senior,
It is my fault.
It was my fault as well,
First,
my daughter Head of Employee
expressed herself
Yao Xi deliberately left this in the garden
and wanted me to misunderstand you with Empress Dowager.
Didn't Miss Xue and Yao Xi grow up together?
You and Miss Jiang are also in the same team.
But I went to the court and found out that
you two are not close to each other.
You are more like enemies.
Even the first half of the poison was used to poison the palace.
You came here on your own.
Miss Jiang is a smart person.
There is no point in talking in front of a smart person.
I did the one in the paper jacket of Cha Chaoyang.
But it's not true to you.
I misunderstood you because of this year's investigation.
I feel a little guilty and uneasy.
Miss Xue is joking.
I may have misunderstood you,
but I lost my life.
I can't accept a hat like yours.
I know you don't want to forgive me easily.
But Miss Jiang is going to leave the palace soon.
Although I have to kill you,
I can't hurt you.
Besides, I have to deal with your sister.
If I want to take out the sincerity,
can this grudge be a little bit more?
Qi is not very good at it.
If you are against him,
you will have a good bone.
I don't like to have some small grudges around me.
It makes me feel sick.
Why don't I help you
to beat him up?
It's better to let you be close to him.
Thank you for your kindness, Miss Xue.
But I am not used to
being a good person.
I don't have the habit of being innocent.
I hope Miss Jiang can keep thinking like this.
But my sincerity will always be there.
Yes.
Fresht.
Xie Qing.
I told you not to come.
I have good news for you.
What we have in the capital
has some secrets schools.
I will never forget you