THE AGE OF HATRED
The age of hatred.
GET LOST, ENEMIES OF DOCTORS
You didn't know?
He got branded as a whistleblower.
They draw a line just because I have
different thoughts from them.
I heard you worked as an escort
until recently.
They belittle me
and humiliate me.
There's no need to beat around the bush.
Find another hospital.
You have no dignity as a doctor.
A cheapie like you who's only after money
can't work with me.
They diminish me as they like.
You can look after the emergency patient
who's in the OR now.
Collective egoism and dichotomous thinking
turns anyone who isn't on your side
into an enemy.
A black-and-white world.
Cha Eun-jae.
Do you want to lose your license?
Our respect for one another disappeared.
This is why I don't like to hire girls.
The world is now full
of disrespect and hatred.
And that's when…
Gosh! What should we do?
Doctor Kim!
-Tell us!
-Doctor Kim!
-Please tell us!
-How's Minister Ryu now?
-How is he doing?
-Doctor Kim!
-Is he here?
-Tell us something!
-Please come out!
-Where is he?
-Say something!
-How is he?
-Excuse me!
-Doctor Kim!
There was a man who suddenly appeared.
Why don't you send her to me?
A CS who can't even go into the OR?
Why would you take her?
You should find a different doctor.
Darn you.
Dr. Seo has the worst reputation here.
But…
I need money.
I've never
put a price on a person in my life.
You said you needed a hand.
A doctor is who I'm looking for!
What do you mean by that?
It is your job
to find the answer.
UNDEFINED SETTING VALUE
Defense Minister Ryu Woong-il was involved
in a car accident on his way
to oversee a joint training
of the three military forces held
in Gangwon Province this morning.
His driver, Park, suddenly suffered
from a myocardial infarction,
then the car deviated from the road
-and fell off.
-The driver died at the scene,
and Minister Ryu and his secretary
were seriously injured.
He received his first operation
and was sent to the ICU of this hospital.
The hospital staff mentioned
that they are doing their best
to treat Minister Ryu's serious injury.
Minister Ryu's family
haven't arrived at the hospital yet.
The Ministry of National Defense said
as soon as Minister Ryu gets better,
they plan on moving him
to the Armed Forces Hospital in Seoul.
You don't have to worry.
Professor Park Min-gook is a surgeon
who's known in this industry
for having the best surgical skills.
Now that we're treating Minister Ryu,
I believe it's our duty to provide
the best surgeon that we have.
Thank you. Please do look after him.
-There wasn't a huge change.
-No.
We can continue to keep our eyes on him.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
His blood pressure is at 90 over 60,
but his temperature went up to 38.9.
What about his urine?
Around 10 to 15 ml per hour.
Get him on propacetamol
and please get the chest portable.
And keep checking his IO and temperature.
-I'll get Doctor Kim.
-Yes, sir.
Seo Woo-jin?
You were here?
What brings you here?
I'll take over the treatment
for Minister Ryu as of now.
I'm sorry,
but I haven't heard anything.
It was just decided,
so you'll hear about it down there.
Let Dr. Yang take over,
and please move aside.
I cannot leave the patient's side
until the doctor in charge tells me to.
Hey.
Seo Woo-jin.
Dr. Seo. His blood pressure is dropping.
Didn't you hear Professor Park?
He's in charge of Minister Ryu now.
So move aside, okay?
I can't leave the patient's side
until the doctor in charge tells me to.
You're unbelievable.
Dr. Seo, the patient went into arrest!
Goodness.
This is obviously a declaration of war.
We need to come up with countermeasures.
Why don't we give a briefing
to the reporters regarding Minister Ryu?
That's how we can have them under control.
Okay, striking them first.
I'm all for that.
Before President Do…
I mean, before Chairman Do does something,
we can give an official statement
regarding Minister Ryu's operation
and his current status.
Yes, this is Doctor Kim.
I'll check his pulse.
He's in PEA.
PEA: PULSELESS ELECTRICAL ACTIVITY
I have the ABGA.
ABGA: ARTERIAL BLOOD GAS ANALYSIS
Metabolic acidosis?
METABOLIC ACIDOSIS: ACID IMBALANCE
Give me three bicarbonates.
BICARBONATE: AGENT THAT REGULATES PH
Not with the epinephrine. Another one.
I'm Park Min-gook, GS of Geosan.
I'm Minister Ryu's doctor as of now.
Carry out the order right now!
-Yes, sir.
-I'll put him on another IV line.
How long has it been?
Two minutes.
Ho-jun. Switch with him.
Okay, I'll switch.
I'll do it.
He said, it has been two minutes.
I'll do this!
Stop that and switch.
Stop it and switch hands with him.
What happened?
He went into PEA arrest.
Urine didn't come out due to hypovolemia,
and he had metabolic acidosis as well.
He's getting bicarbonate injections.
I gave the order just now.
I'll keep the place under control.
Please leave.
-Ms. Oh.
-Yes?
Get the stapler remover
and blade number ten.
Yes, sir.
Don't make this too complicated.
Move aside.
Can you take responsibility
if the worst happens to him?
Can you save him?
That should've been your first question.
Don't you think so, Dr. Park?
All ready, Doctor Kim.
Switch hands with him.
Oh, okay.
Iodine.
Remover.
Keep going!
Yes, sir.
Scalpel.
What is he trying to do?
Stop.
What is he doing right now?
Tell him to stop now. Right now!
Doctor Kim is doing his best
to save him right now.
Trust him.
He'll make sure he saves Minister Ryu.
He doesn't have enough volume.
Squeeze the RBC pack.
I'll do that.
Professor Park.
Hey, his pulse is back.
He got his pulse back, Doctor Kim.
Gosh, my legs.
Great work.
Professor Sim?
Who are you?
I'm Cha Eun-jae,
a second-year fellow of CS.
I was dispatched here as of yesterday.
Is this the staff room?
Yes.
What brings you here?
Whose pillow is that?
That's mine.
Can I use your bed?
Yes, of course.
Gosh, my back.
Things will be awfully tough
for a few days.
Aren't you going to sleep?
It's all right.
You can go ahead and sleep.
You should sleep while you can.
That's how you can survive.
Can you give that to me?
What? Sure.
Oh, hey. That's perfect.
Professor Park?
I'm all finished.
Keep your eye on him.
If his vitals look even a bit odd,
give me a call right away.
Yes, sir.
Great work, Dr. Seo.
You did well.
I was just surprised and flustered.
You kept the patient with you
until Doctor Kim got here.
You did well.
I'll send Nurse Park over.
You shouldn't strain yourself.
Get some sleep if you can.
HOPE, LOVE, SERVICE
You really are amazing.
I was honestly touched.
That was probably the third time
I've seen an open heart massage.
Today was the first one that succeeded.
I got lucky.
And he isn't completely stable yet.
Why do you stay at a nameless hospital
with your skills and competence?
It's not nameless.
Didn't you see the sign out there
that says Doldam Hospital?
Is this like Schweitzer syndrome?
I can't explain this situation
if it isn't the case.
Why does the only doctor in Korea
who's triple-board certified
stay in a desolate hospital
like this one?
It's not like you get
any money or fame from doing this.
Because these patients need me.
Is that really the only reason?
Does a doctor need another reason
than his patients?
I've been curious about you…
for a long time.
I offered to come down here
because I wanted to meet you.
And now that I've met you,
I think you're one of the two.
You're either insane…
or an awful liar.
I don't believe anyone does a goodwill
without expecting a return.
I've never seen anything like that.
It's getting pretty late.
You should get to sleep.
SURGERY, FAMILY MEDICINE
I heard he was like a monster.
I guess the rumors weren't that off.
We'll see after we take his mask off…
if he really is a monster
or if he's a snob pretending to be one.
HOPE, LOVE, SERVICE
Gosh, he's so annoying.
I can't believe now snooty he is.
Guys who are a big success at his age
tend to have that symptom.
An inflated ego.
So annoying.
I want to smack his head
and tell him to behave.
Why did you get so tough?
No idea. Maybe it's menopause.
It's hot.
HOPE, LOVE, SERVICE
SEARCH FOR MEDICAL STAFF:
GENERAL SURGERY, PARK MIN-GOOK
MEDICAL STAFF: PARK MIN-GOOK
CREDENTIALS
JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY
Johns Hopkins?
RESEARCHES
MEETING PARK MIN-GOOK, KOREA'S BEST
HEPATOPANCREATICOBILIARY SURGEON
HE DEEMS HIS LIFE AS A BONUS
TO SERVE HIS PATIENTS…
TO SERVE HIS PATIENTS
AFTER A BUS ACCIDENT 11 YEARS AGO
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Someone is coming out.
-Someone's coming.
-Get ready.
Someone's coming out!
-Someone came out.
Hurry up.
Hey, run.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL CODE OF ETHICS
Why is he sleeping here?
Hey.
What are you doing?
What?
It's nothing.
Nothing, really.
What's this?
This?
A pen. It's a pen.
Hey, that hurts.
Will you let me go?
Hey.
What are you doing?
What? Why?
STAFF LOUNGE
Gosh, stop it!
Darn it.
You jerk.
Goodness.
-Do you have the ABGA?
-I'll have to check the chart.
-One second.
-Show me the chest X-ray.
Okay. When did you take this?
As soon as the minister arrived.
What is it?
Hey. Dr. Seo.
Oh, no.
Darn it! This is driving me insane.
What do I do?
Darn it, that jerk.
Oh, no. What do I do?
Darn it!
EMERGENCY ROOM
RESTRICTED AREA: OPERATING ROOM
DENTAL MASK
What are you doing?
Ms. Oh. Hello. You're here early.
Are you ill?
A little. I must have caught a cold.
I have a sore throat,
and I'm coughing a little.
Am I feverish?
You aren't feverish at all.
Gosh, I'm glad I'm not.
Ms. Oh.
Can you come for a second?
She's looking for you.
What is it, Nurse Um?
You need to see this yourself.
DOLDAM HOSPITAL
Hello.
I'm GS Park Min-gook of Geosan Hospital.
As you are all aware,
Minister Ryu Woong-il of National Defense
got into a car accident
and was hospitalized here
at Doldam Hospital, a branch of Geosan.
His condition was so critical
that he couldn't be transferred to Seoul.
We conducted the first operation
here in this hospital,
but there was no improvement
to his condition
so we will conduct his second operation
this afternoon.
Will Dr. Bu Yong-ju operate on
the minister again this time?
MINISTER RYU TO RECEIVE SECOND OPERATION
I'm going to operate on him myself.
Wait, what is he saying, Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh!
There are reporters
and Professor Park out there--
She's already watching.
Right. I see.
But you're all just standing around.
Don't blame me for anything.
I'm just doing my job as I was told.
What's this all about?
Is it because he's a minister?
Of course.
If it weren't for the minister,
why would he make such a scene?
People from all walks of life
have their attention on this case.
There's no better chance than this
for someone who craves attention.
But don't you think it's wrong to steal
someone else's patient?
It's not like doctors are some thugs.
What's going on, Dr. Seo?
You've changed a little.
-What?
-You were never that type.
Keep your character, will you?
If you suddenly change too much
you'll only end up being confused.
Those up above will make the decisions,
and, Dr. Seo, you can just do your job.
All right?
Just let them go on.
What? You…
You want us to leave them alone?
We have to leave them alone.
They want to do all the hard work.
Why should we stop them?
I'm just glad I can get more rest
thanks to them.
By any chance,
are you avoiding this?
Let's say I'm observing the situation.
You can't just sit around observing!
Why do you keep overreacting?
Weren't you going to stick around
for just one week?
You said you'll reconsider in a week.
That's only if you change my mind.
But you are…
nowhere near the answer.
Are you going to let them handle
the minister?
Hey, don't worry about him.
They all studied a lot too.
There's someone over there
who trained at Hopkins too.
Hey, guys like them
won't put in the needles the wrong way.
-Doctor Kim.
-Yes?
I'm all done organizing.
Oh, okay.
Nurse Park, go get some sleep.
You probably didn't get to sleep
after staying up all night.
Goodness.
My goodness. I'll stretch out
and get a good sleep for once.
Hey.
If it's not an emergency,
don't wake me.
My gosh.
TREATMENT ROOM
What was that?
Why did he suddenly change?
Am I the only one who's flustered?
I completely understand how you feel.
If you do, then why did you stand around
doing nothing?
Because Dr. Kim made that decision.
If he makes a decision,
are we supposed to blindly follow
as if we have no opinions
or thoughts of our own?
It's not because we have
no other opinions or thoughts.
We follow because we respect his decision.
-Please explain.
-A comment, please.
Say a few words!
-Can we get a comment?
-Why the sudden change?
Why the sudden change in lead surgeons?
From what I know,
Dr. Bu Yong-ju put many lives at risk
by performing risky, reckless procedures.
Is that the reason?
At the moment, all I can say is that
we will do our very best to make sure
the second surgery is a success.
As for the surgical outcome,
we will hold a detailed briefing
after the surgery is over.
That'll be all.
-Wait.
-A few more comments, please!
DOCTOR PARK MIN-GOOK WILL PERFORM
MINISTER RYU'S SECOND SURGERY
Hi, Reporter Choi.
It's me.
Weren't the questions too direct?
No, of course not. Well done.
That's the media's role, you know.
You can't dig out the truth
with a dull knife.
Make some time to meet with me.
I'll take you to a nice place.
Sure. Of course.
Call me then. All right.
Professor Park?
What is this game you're playing?
You don't even work at this hospital.
Who said you could hold
a press conference here?
And who gave you the authority
to decide to lead the second surgery?
Who are you?
I'm Oh Myeong-sim, the head nurse.
This isn't something
a head nurse should meddle in.
Yes, I'm aware.
Usually, I'd stay out of things like this.
However,
what is happening right now
is just shitty, Professor Park.
-Look.
-Ms. Oh!
Calm down, please.
We're calling it a second surgery,
but you just need to sew him up
once the hemorrhaging stops, right?
Doctor Kim saved his life.
You're barely doing anything,
yet you'll take all the credit.
You'll tell everyone that you saved him.
-Am I wrong?
-Ms. Oh, please.
Tell me if I'm wrong!
You're right.
That's why I held the press conference.
Will you please excuse me now?
This way, sir.
-What a jerk!
-Calm down.
Please calm down, Ms. Oh.
-How dare he!
-Gosh, please. Enough.
Goodness, unbelievable.
-I'm speechless. My gosh.
-All right.
CHIEF OF GENERAL SURGERY, DOCTOR KIM
People of Doldam.
Those jerks
want an all-out war with us.
We will no longer tolerate this.
I get that they're from the main hospital,
but they belittle and mistreat us
just because they feel like it
without any valid reason or cause.
They do this to us all the time!
And now, those savages are even
intercepting one of our patients.
We absolutely won't let this slide.
You all know what Doldam stands for.
A hospital where anyone can visit
when in need of medical assistance.
We're open 24/7, 365 days a year.
I think Nurse Joo likes Nurse Park.
What?
-But he is…
-They say a rolling stone…
obviously married to his job.
It'll be hard to win his heart.
What are you talking about?
-Hush.
-I can no longer…
-Keep it down.
-tolerate their impudence.
As of this moment, they're not allowed
to view or access any of our patient files
including Minister Ryu's.
From the surgical reports
to basic patient charts,
we won't share any information with them.
No exceptions.
Do you all understand?
Yes, ma'am!
And I guess Nurse Um's love life
-isn't going so well.
-We won't surrender.
A fight, perhaps?
We'll stay strong and…
Her boyfriend must be ignoring her texts.
-Dr. Yoon.
-I trust that…
-Gosh, keep it down.
-you're all with me.
Dr. Jeong, Dr. Yoon.
-Yes, Ms. Oh.
-Yes.
You will join us, right?
Yes, of course. Sure thing.
Yes, me too.
This is not the time to laugh.
My apologies.
And Ms. Oh probably has low estrogen.
What?
So?
You still don't have the surgical reports?
I've put in several requests,
but they just keep saying no.
-No, you can't view them.
-No can do.
Sorry, but I can't help you with that.
Well…
They'll disobey the minister's doctor?
Oh, Minister Ryu's doctor?
You mean, Doctor Kim?
We only take orders from Doctor Kim.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
Don't they know that Professor Park
is Minister Ryu's doctor now?
They know that, of course.
They're just in denial. That's all.
Do they all want to get fired or what?
The staff here are as rough
as the hospital itself.
Yes, Professor.
Oh, right.
Yes, I'll be there in five minutes. Okay.
Was that Professor Park?
He's headed to see Minister Ryu now.
Gosh, this is crazy.
Do you know anyone at this hospital?
Using your connections
would be the only solution.
How would I know anyone
at this darned hospital?
Bae Moon-jung?
Dr. Yang Ho-jun?
Dr. Cha Eun-jae?
How's the patient doing?
His BP, heart rate,
and oxygen levels are all stable.
His temperature is a little high
but it's nothing to be alarmed by.
The brain CT scan looks fine too.
I have to check his follow-up lab results,
but I think he's stable enough
to go through the second surgery.
Let me know when the results are out.
By the way,
you've never taken over
another doctor's patient in the past.
We'll go ahead with the surgery
if all the results come back clean.
Book an OR and call me.
Professor.
Here, I have it.
SURGICAL REPORT
LEAD SURGEON, DOCTOR KIM
Do you know anyone in CS
at the main hospital?
CS?
Yes, I do. One person.
Then find out more about
Cha Eun-jae, a second-year fellow.
Cha Eun-jae?
About her personality
and why she was transferred here.
Okay, will do.
Hey, what? What's going on?
Sit down.
Hey, be my ally.
What?
Are you talking to yourself or what?
I said, be my ally. "Ally."
I can't hear you with that mask on.
Gosh.
Your face looks like an abstract painting.
This wasn't what I was going for.
Don't get cheeky with me.
Listen up, okay?
This is very important to us.
What's so important?
We might be able
to go back to the main hospital.
What do you mean?
Did you participate
in Minister Ryu's surgery?
Oh, yes, I did.
I've been tending to him
since he arrived at the ER.
I see. That's good.
The second surgery is booked
for this afternoon,
and I need someone
who participated in the first one.
Oh…
I see.
My answer is no.
Can you hear me out first?
This surgery is so important
to Prof. Park.
And we'll assist him
in that important surgery
on the condition that he has to take us
back to the main hospital.
-What do you think?
-Do it if you want to.
I'm not interested.
I'd obviously go in alone if I could.
As you know, I left halfway
through the surgery.
Fine.
I will forgive you for this ridiculousness
you did to my face, so--
Eun-jae, I said no.
I won't do it.
You're frustrating me so much.
This is a good opportunity for you.
Nothing bad will come out
of winning points with Professor Park.
I don't need to win points with him.
You said you need money.
Isn't the pay higher at the main hospital?
Let's go back together.
Come on. We have a shot at it.
Life must be so easy for you.
What are you talking about?
You think you can outsmart everyone
not knowing you're the biggest idiot.
Hey. What kind of idiot is this smart?
You didn't know?
There are so many idiots like you.
Nerdy idiots who like being in first place
but know nothing about life.
Those delusional idiots think
they're the smartest.
Enough, okay?
If you go on, I'll be really insulted.
Just think of it as advice
from a friend.
"Friend"?
Since when were we friends?
Since when did you care about me enough
to offer me such words of advice?
Go wash your face.
Your face looks hilarious.
Hello, Dr. Seo.
STAFF LOUNGE
My, he's so cool.
Woo-jin, stop right there!
Oh, Dr. Cha.
What happened to your face?
-Is that mold?
-No, it's not.
It's just atopic dermatitis.
Atopic dermatitis?
That sounds so cool.
Nurse Park.
I should get back to work.
Yes, I'll keep you updated.
Sir, we'll do an ultrasound.
Gosh, it looks like the capsule burst.
The entire abdominal cavity is…
Put him on a drip of 100 ml
of saline and 50 ml of pethidine.
Got it.
Hello, this is Jeong In-su.
About the spleen injury patient
who was admitted to the ICU yesterday.
Minister Ryu's secretary.
His vitals are suddenly fluctuating.
Dr. Seo just did an ultrasound and spotted
severe intra-abdominal hemorrhaging.
Yes, we'll get ready.
We're moving him to the OR now.
-Let's move him.
-Okay.
Sir, we have to transport you.
Hang in there, please.
Excuse me, what's wrong?
His condition suddenly worsened.
It looks like he needs surgery.
Sir.
Minister Ryu will be taken to the OR
in five minutes.
Two of you stay here.
The rest, go to the OR.
I'll go with the minister.
Understood, sir.
That jerk.
STAFF ROOM
Why do you keep following me?
I have nothing to say to you.
I was just on my way to get changed.
I have to put on my scrubs.
MALE CHANGING ROOM
Hey.
Must you really join the surgery?
Yes. I'm going in.
You asked me what Doctor Kim is like.
So? What do you think he's like?
I think…
he's a little scary.
Is that why you shrank away?
Because you're scared?
He's not "scary" in that sense.
Then how?
I feel like he may be the real deal.
That's what scares me.
Do you know what kind of people
scare me the most?
Those who don't need me.
As of this moment,
you're banned from my OR.
Those who jump to conclusions about me
when they don't even know me well.
Leaving your patient like that
is enough to disqualify you as a doctor.
Do you understand?
Get over it or just quit being a doctor!
So?
Are you saying Park Min-gook needs you?
He at least remembered my name.
Are you really not coming with me?
I'm asking because I need your help.
Will you help me?
PATIENT: RYU WOONG-IL
By the way,
will his family not be present?
His wife passed away,
and his children live in Jeju Island.
But the planes are grounded
because of the weather.
I see.
His secretary's family isn't here either.
His parents passed away when he was young.
He has one brother.
Could you not reach his brother?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
PATIENT: LEE JOO-YOUNG
GUARDIAN: LEE DAE-YOUNG, BROTHER
MILITARY POLICE
Sir.
The minister's son and his wife
just arrived at Yangyang Airport.
They'll head over here right away.
Okay.
What do you mean?
They got their hands on the records?
I just got a text from the ICU nurse.
They have the chart and surgical records
as well as the anesthesia records.
Gosh, who gave them everything?
-Who on earth--
-I…
gave them the records.
What?
You did? Why?
Because I was told to.
By whom?
Doctor Kim.
Doctor Kim?
Yes.
Why on earth did you do that?
Do what?
The minister's chart and surgical reports.
You told Dr. Bae to hand it over to them.
Right, I did.
But why?
That man, Park Min-gook.
I've done some research,
and he's pretty good.
I figured
he'd do a fine job with the surgery, so--
So you are
surrendering like this?
What?
Right.
Do Yun-wan obviously has more power
now that he's the chair of the foundation.
I know that, but…
I didn't think
you'd throw in the towel this easily.
You saved that patient.
How could you give up so easily?
I didn't save him by myself.
We saved him together, Ms. Oh.
Also,
I haven't given up.
Then what is this?
Why let them operate on him?
What's another word for "crisis"?
"Anger."
Gosh, you have such a fiery temper.
To turn this crisis into an opportunity,
we need to use what Do Yun-wan
never considered.
But he already knows everything
about you and our hospital.
He might even know things
that we don't know--
Hush.
No.
I don't think that's the case.
There are things that he doesn't know yet.
RESTRICTED AREA: OPERATING ROOM
I'm here, Professor.
Hey.
Did you already administer the anesthesia?
What would you like me to do?
Nothing.
There won't be much for you to do.
-Pardon?
-Dr. Cha.
Anxiety attacks in the OR?
I was told that you ran out of the OR
less than ten minutes
into the surgery last time.
I'm sorry,
but we can't let something like that
happen during Professor Park's surgery.
It's simply unacceptable.
But…
I've been following up on his condition
since he arrived at the ER.
I'm sure I can be of help.
It's okay.
Someone else is joining us to help us out.
There he is.
Seo Woo-jin?
What is going on?
What do you think?
He betrayed you and joined us
so that he could snatch the opportunity.
This punk is a pro at stabbing others
in the back, you know.
The minister is under anesthesia now.
All right.
Okay, let's get ready.
Yes, sir.
But why me?
I know all they have to do is sew him up,
but they still need someone
who knows about the first surgery.
You're the only one who can do it,
so go help them.
I don't want to.
I wasn't asking your opinion.
Just do as I say.
Eun-jae will have to go in if you don't.
Do you want to see her throwing up
and running out of the OR again?
RESTRICTED AREA
RESTRICTED AREA: OPERATING ROOM
Do you think it'll be okay?
I have no idea either.
Doctor Kim always thinks
outside the box, you know.
But we'd at least be able to tell
which one of the two
will stay and which one will leave.
What if they both leave?
Or both of them might stay.
OPERATING ROOM 1
OPERATING ROOM 2
That scumbag.
All right. Let's begin.
Okay, let's begin the surgery.
Scalpel.
"Friend"?
Since when were we friends?
Since when did you care about me enough
to offer me such words of advice?
To tell you the truth, back then…
TAXI
Darn it! I'm so late. Gosh!
Gosh, what do I do?
Why Prof. Jung's lecture of all classes?
Gosh, this is so crazy!
Diagnosing a malignant bone marrow…
What is this?
You're late for your first class?
I'm sorry.
You all know that I don't forgive
tardiness or absences, right?
What's your name?
I'm Seo Woo-jin, sir.
Let's see. Seo Woo-jin.
-You can sit here.
-You're getting three penalty points.
Don't be late.
-Okay?
-Yes, sir.
Isn't Eun-jae really something?
She got all A pluses, again.
I heard she never eats dinner
because she doesn't want to waste time.
-Apparently, she never even poops.
-Stop.
-She was famous in high school too.
-She's obsessed with being the top.
Gosh, how obnoxious.
Why wouldn't she eat?
If I get put on probation, I'll be doomed.
PATHOLOGY
CHOLECYSTITIS, TUBERCULOSIS
RENAL CELL CARCINOMA
Darn it.
Gosh.
All right. Someone…
got a perfect score on the test.
-What?
-Seriously?
Seo Woo-jin.
My gosh!
Give him a big hand!
Here's your fritter.
Thank you.
Here are your tteokbokki and fritters.
I heard you excel on practical tests,
but you barely make the cut
when it comes to written exams.
Let me know if you need anything else.
How about we become allies?
Help me do better on practical tests.
What will you do for me in return?
I'll share all my study materials
with you.
I have one for every course.
If you memorize everything in here,
you won't fail a single class.
Back then…
FORENSIC PATHOLOGY, NEUROLOGY
HEALTHCARE, PATHOLOGY
PROS OF DROPPING OUT OF MED SCHOOL
The pros of dropping out of med school.
I can sleep, play, and eat
as much as I want.
And no more exams.
I won't have to study anatomy anymore.
I can get a dog.
I can learn to surf and travel.
Play StarCraft all day long.
I could hang out with my friends
and maybe date someone too.
The cons of dropping out of med school.
My mom will be sad.
When I found out
that you were simply enduring it
instead of thriving,
I changed.
GEOSAN UNIVERSITY
REQUEST FOR WITHDRAWAL, SEO WOO-JIN
REASON: CAN'T AFFORD THE TUITION
I REQUEST TO WITHDRAW FROM ALL COURSES
No, don't hold it vertically like that.
-Keep it down and do it in one go.
-In one go?
Just do it.
-Gosh, I don't think I can do this!
-Geez.
It hurts more if you hesitate like that.
Okay.
-Just stick it in, okay?
-Okay.
Muster the courage and stick it in.
Yes, just do it.
Muster the courage.
-There!
-Gosh!
My gosh!
Does it hurt?
I'll sue all the doctors and the hospital
for medical malpractice.
Is that worthy of a lawsuit?
Did they try to coax you or something?
I know you want to go back.
I'll persuade Professor Park,
so promise that you'll keep quiet.
If you decided to side with Doctor Kim,
just stay on his side.
You obnoxious opportunist.
What about the CT scan?
You didn't check before coming in?
Did you deliberately send me there
to test me and see
what I'd do to Professor Park?
You told me to find an answer!
Damn it.