[Film planning | Studio Dragon]
[Production | CJs Entertainment]
[Seo Ye Ji]
[Park Byung Eun]
[Yu Seon]
[Lee Sang Yeob]
[Eve]
[This program contains product placement and virtual advertising.]
[This drama is fiction and the characters, names, institutions, events, organizations, and circumstances are not real.]
Secretary Kim!
Did you get in contact with him?
Still nothing?
It's 5:00 a.m. in the morning! 5:00 a.m.!
Is he staying out? He's not coming at all?
Does that make sense?
Say something, I'm going insane!
I'm sure an unavoidable situation occurred. When he returns, he will have an explanation, Madam.
He's not spending the night elsewhere?
Then, why would he turn off his phone?
Why did he leave his car behind?
Tell Secretary Cha to come.
You can't hide love.
It's insanely spontaneous.
It blurs your consciousness.
And with formidable destructive power, it paralyzes your rationality.
The ecstasy of love even numbs the pain of death.
It's dangerous since it even paralyzes your senses.
It's a dangerous thing.
[Episode 6]
Chairman.
I don't want to wake you, but you should go.
I've been asleep until now?
I haven't been able to sleep for a long time.
I don't know how long it's been.
Did I tell you to save the country?
I'm not asking for anything difficult, you can't even locate the chairman?
I apologize.
Is being sorry everything?
Hold on to this so we can communicate with each other.
Can I contact you as well?
I'll always be waiting.
It's too extravagant for me to wear around.
No matter how elegant a jewel is,
it's nothing compared to you.
The chairman is here.
Hide.
What are you doing? Were you like this all night?
What did you think I would do when you didn't come home?
Everyone, go home.
- Honey.
- Go home!
How many times do I have to tell you? Our employees are not slaves.
Digging around, throwing fits, cursing. What do I need to do for you to stop?
Does it matter how I act towards people like them?
What were you doing with your phone off?
Where did you go?
And on my birthday, of all days? Tell me everything.
Before I go crazy.
It's true, I was thinking about what to say on my way here,
but now that I'm here, I don't want to explain.
I'm sick and tired of you.
Why are you being like this?
Are you on drugs? Are you in your right state of mind?
It's fascinating that I've been able to hold it in for this long...
when I hate you this much.
How can you say something like that to get out of this?
I won't let this go.
Staying out on my birthday and saying harsh things,
I won't stand for it.
Have you ever let anything go?
Secretary Cha.
I saw the parked car, come out!
I called him because I was worried about you.
A wife hasn't seen her husband come home, can't I ask your secretary for that much?
Did you put the GPS in the car because you were worried as well?
What GPS? I don't know what you're talking about.
Secretary Cha, who told you to put the GPS on my car?
There's only one person in this house that can give an order like that.
Please forgive me, Chairman.
Get out.
How is that important?
If you love your husband, you can do something like that.
Then what is important? Your birthday?
Of course, it's important. It's my birthday.
My feelings.
What I want.
Whatever happens, I should always be your priority.
You want me to act like one of your employees.
Are you trying to change the subject because you didn't come home?
Tell me where you were yesterday before you complain about anything else.
I just...
needed a place to rest.
Then you can rest.
At home!
This is your house.
I'm not finished talking. Where are you going?
Why are you in the guest room? For what?
I don't want to sleep in the same bed as you. Let's sleep separately.
Not separate rooms. I'll never allow it.
I'm really sick and tired of this. Just stop.
I'm the one who should be angry, why are you like this? Honey.
Teacher, now is the time.
I applied the hacking device in Chairman Kang's phone.
Mom.
How was the wedding?
The bride was so pretty.
You must be tired from the long drive. What about breakfast?
I ate at a rest stop.
Honey, you're home?
Honey, there was a package in front of the house.
Lee Tae Joon. Who is Gediks?
- What is it that you're like that? Let's open it together.
- No!
Dad, what's wrong?
Son-in-law Jang.
Sorry, Honey. I'm sorry, Mother-in-law. I think the package was sent by mistake.
I'm going to make a quick call.
Sir, this is a list of prosecutors who want to join the Zeus Project.
Take a look.
District Attorney Kwon? How can we use someone who almost got arrested because of suspicion of lobbying?
Take a look at this person.
This one is nice. He doesn't talk or create accidents.
Next is Prosector Park.
We worked with Prosecutor Park last time. If we keep giving him money, he'll raise his price.
The documents are all ready.
Thank you.
I even know the passcode.
[Liyan Kindergarten]
Make sure not to hold the grip too hard.
And try the back swing as if you're opening the club face.
- Go ahead. Give it a try.
- What? Chairman Kang spent the night out?
- On Han So Ra's birthday, of all days?
- That's wild!
Is that why she hasn't been showing her face lately?
She must be embarrassed.
She must have lost it after being stood up by us and her husband staying out all night.
I can't live because of it!
Yes, Madam.
Are you not feeling well?
I'll take Da Bi home.
So Ra?
I'm sorry!
So Ra!
- Why are you just getting here?
- Da Bi was getting her golf lessons.
What's going on?
He said he wants to use separate rooms. I can't let that happen.
Mom!
Call Dad and tell him to hurry home.
Hurry!
I'll do it! I'll tell Chairman Kang.
Da Bi, it's okay.
Let's go.
I couldn't turn her down.
You've been so considerate of me,
I am so sorry.
[Letter of Resignation]
I'll head back to my hometown.
If I...
If I give you one last opportunity, will you commit to being on my side?
[Wife]
[Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom]
[Kim Seon Bin]
I missed you.
A day seems like a year.
Chairman, this is Bo Ram's mother.
I think you need to head home.
What's going on?
Are you hurt?
Chairman is home. Da Bi, your dad is home.
Da Bi! Are you okay?
Dad!
Honey.
What the heck is this?
It's insanely spontaneous. It blurs your consciousness.
And with formidable destructive power, it paralyzes your rationality.
You can't hide the love.
Da Bi, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Da Bi, go to your room!
Da Bi, don't move, you'll get hurt. What do you think you're doing!
Did you just yell at me?
And in front of your employee's wife?
Da Bi, don't cry.
Don't cry.
So Ra, you'll get hurt from the broken glass pieces.
Why don't you stay in your room? For your safety?
Did you see the way he yelled at me? The way he looked at me?
I wasn't able to see clearly.
It's Valerian root tea. Please have a sip.
It will help you calm down.
This is a catastrophe. I think everybody got blinded by something.
How else could he have acted out like that?
I won't let this go.
I won't let go of all those people who messed up my birthday party!
Tell the partners of Eun Dam Ri and Yeo Ji Hee to see me separately. Okay?
How could they do this to me?
It's the idea for the new shopping mall. Why don't you show this to your father?
Everything will go back to its place when you keep yourself busy.
Let's show how strong you are and put Eun Dam Ri and Yeo Ji Hee in their place.
Do you have a plan?
We're going to have our performance soon.
She's asleep.
Rest up.
I did mix in some sleeping pills,
but what if she wakes up?
Then, why did you make me like this?
I hope it doesn't leave a scar.
Have you been eating well?
It's delicious.
I'm not the best cook.
I didn't know...
that the best things...
can be found in the most ordinary moments.
[Fate]
I thought you only listened to tango music.
It is tango music.
You can tango to Korean songs, too.
Do you know what we would call it,
if I danced tango here?
It's tango in the room.
This is why I hesitated.
Because I didn't want to fall in love.
In the Han Pan Ro's voice analysis files,
there are at least twenty legally effective files.
It's evidence of illegal mergers and acquisitions, including Gediks Semiconductors, from Chairman Kang's cell phone.
- Thank you for your hard work, Ra El.
- Let's ask the law firm to sue them.
Let's do it that way.
If we ask the law firm to sue, you must be prepared for your true identity to be revealed.
Then it will be harder for us to collect the evidence, and that's why I'm pushing a lawsuit as a last objective.
I want to put Han Pan Ro and Kang Yoon Kyeom in court.
I want to do it as soon as possible.
I feel the same way as you.
But like our original plan,
when we acquire Chairman Kang's safe is the best time to sue them.
Also, that way, we can make this public to society.
Still, I want to speed things up.
I guess you are uncomfortable with Chairman Kang.
It's not easy to get into bed with your archenemy.
I want to end this soon.
Honey, you came home after midnight last night. Did you go somewhere?
Why did you throw this package away?
Gediks Semiconductors was your first workplace.
Why did you lie to me?
And what is this?
What's going on here?
I don't know either! It was delivered incorrectly.
Honey.
You said you weren't hiding anything from me.
I married you because I believed that you were a simple, pure person.
Until you tell me what all these are about, do not even think of touching me.
Honey.
Get out.
I want you to lose someone you love.
Until you want to die because of that pain.
I didn't tell my dad about you acting this way.
I'll be on the Autumn Recital Documentary next week.
My dad is coming to see my performance as well.
You know my dad is fast at reading the room.
He'll suspect things are wrong if you don't come.
Are you threatening me?
I'm saying this on your behalf.
What's the point of pretending to have a good relationship in front of others when we are not?
I'm putting in a lot of effort.
Compared to before, I'm laying low and not really doing anything.
You're laying low? Is that something to be proud of?
How can you live well after committing such a thing back in the day—
That was an accident!
So we make a deal with the Seoul City Government that we'll clean up the brothel area,
and turn that area into LY Group's shopping center?
Yes.
We can't even open anything over there yet.
That's a great idea!
Right, the brothel area is a problem for Seoul City.
Brother, what if we merge this with the Zeus business?
If we have a shopping mall as well, it's easier for money laundering.
Also, the business gets bigger. Isn't that a perfect idea?
You're right!
I want the biggest shopping center in all of Korea.
You brought Assemblyman Seo Eun Pyeong before.
So Ra is on a roll these days!
Who's the person who came up with this plan?
I did it.
Be honest.
Who is it?
She's one of the mothers from the parents' association.
I told her I'd promote her husband, and now she's putting every effort into me.
I'll introduce you to her when you come to the recital.
Now that Han Pan Ro has taken the bait of the shopping mall,
I think we can get the LY Group's money-laundering route soon.
I'll start contacting the law firm.
I don't think it's a bad idea to speed things up, as you said.
You've exceeded my expectations.
I'm sorry about what I said last time,
that you are inexperienced. I want to sincerely apologize.
You took this...
as your life's work.
A lot of our information can only be picked up by the people close to them.
If the LY legal team learns about our lawsuit,
you will be the first one they'll suspect, Ra El.
Since your acquaintance was built overnight.
I'm concerned you may be the recipient of their retribution,
even before the case goes public.
Put some distance between Kang Yoon Kyeom and you.
It's for safety's sake.
All right.
Please double check all related data to the end. Let's call it a day.
Okay.
Um...
What are your thoughts on the offer of becoming the Blue House Secretary?
The speaker is trying to assess what my thoughts are, but I have no inkling.
I will think on it some more. Please give me some time.
Is it the Do-Not-Disturb DD Day?
A time alone before making a big change?
I know it's a useless question, but I'm still curious.
You completely go off the radar on DD Day. Where exactly do you go?
Can't you share a little bit?
DD Day's meaning is literally Do-Not-Disturb. So if I let you in on it, would it really be a DD Day?
It'd be an Open Day instead, no?
That's true.
Please get home.
Good job today!
Ra El.
This is regarding the job request previously made. Contact me when you can.
That's right. That's right.
Wow, it's the madam!
So cool!
You are so pretty.
- What is this about?
- We felt bad for not celebrating you on your birthday.
We are a so-called parents' dance group. We should at least, celebrate each other.
Never mind. It's already passed.
♪ Happy birthday to you, Happy birthday to you ♪
Enough, don't you think?
Secretary Kim.
I will accept your affection.
We also prepared a gift.
It's a premium brand from this industry.
Since a shop opened in Cheongdam-dong, I bought this one.
- Oh my god.
- Was this your idea?
I heard about your birthday.
It made me feel bad that you were alone, so I prepared this gift as a cute joke.
I heard when you get old,
"that" is more superior than the husband.
I hope it makes you feel better.
Why don't we cut the cake?
I will bring a piece if you go to the lounge.
Did you see?
Right where it hurts.
Please lower your anger. I had no idea they were up to this.
The madams have taken their leave.
Please open them.
What is this money for, Madam?
It's an allowance.
Ma'am?
Use it where you need it.
All this?
In this, there are three times the amount of what you have.
Sleep with Eun Dam Ri and Yeo Ji Hee for one night.
You can tempt them or use some other method...
Whoever delivers the result first,
will take it all.
One thing, there's got to be proof.
A definitive one.
Take your leave.
Sis,
should you really go to this length despite how much you dislike them?
It's a crime.
I've always lived doing whatever I pleased.
What if it becomes a problem?
There was never once a problem.
Have you done things like this before?
Do you know why Father doesn't let me work?
Because I'm childish?
I always cause trouble and Dad always handles the aftermath.
I'm sure the old man is probably tired of it. I bet he'd like to live in peace.
Did you do things like this regarding Chairman Kang
or LY Group?
The trouble I caused in order to marry him was probably the biggest.
What was it?
I switched two women's fate... lightly.
In order to marry him, that is.
When he was single, the amount of marriage talk amongst the chaebols was extraordinary.
He was infamous for his good looks, tall stature, and growing up as the ultimate elite without a scandal to his name.
The competition was fierce, but I was older...
and married once before.
And so?
The rumor had it
there was a woman who he was affectionate with.
So, I took care of it.
And then some woman interfered with my plan, claiming we return her husband's company.
Gediks Semiconductor company's wife or something.
Gediks was my dowry.
One young, one old woman.
They switched their fate.
Thanks to me.
Gediks...
I mean...
To those women, what exactly did you do to those women?
You'll get hurt, if you know too much.
There will be many interesting events ahead of us.
You can look forward to it as well.
[Ra El]
Ra El!
What is this about, Ra El? Why do you ask about your mother's last appearance?
Did you hear some news?
Just before she disappeared,
what she spoke about,
how she appeared in that last moment,
do you have anything you can tell me?
It's important.
Shortly after I left for the US,
she disappeared from the nursing home she was staying at.
I don't have any further knowledge of it than what I already shared.
Han So Ra...
Do you suppose there is a possibility that she harmed my mom?
How does a person disappear without a trace?
Don't you find it strange?
When I went to visit your mother...
for the last time at the nursing home...
Ah, are you okay? I brought some porridge for you.
I'd like you to stop coming here.
Your future is bright, Attorney Seo.
Don't get mixed up in a dangerous situation.
What kind of talk is that, Ma'am?
You listen to me.
From now on, never
come to visit me.
Do you understand?
Your mother was always uneasy.
Shortly after your father passed away,
LY took over your father's company.
I thought it was all over then.
What did she say when she was leaving the hospital?
She said she was on her way to meet with her relatives.
She went missing right after that.
Though a person went missing without any cause, there has been no trace of her for over ten years...
The case doesn't make any sense. However, if the most powerful person was involved, then...
we may be able to solve the puzzle.
Of course, it's all a guess at this point, Ra El.
Ra El.
Oh, Ra El!
I only hoped that she lived.
Is it possible to find information about Ms. Kim Jin Sook?
There isn't any known information about Ms. Kim Jin Sook.
Then some day,
I could meet my mom.
That is how I was able to go on.
Ra El!
Mom.
Mom...
[LY Group Kang Yoon Kyeom]
What brings you here, Secretary Jeong?
Your father asks to speak with you.
You say the former Prime Minister Han Pan Ro wishes to meet?
He sent something our way via his secretary.
Mentioning something about how he appreciated your help at the kindergarten.
I'm sure he was trying to grab a chance thrown his way since a premium politician deigned a visit to his event.
You know well how Han Pan Ro conducts illegal deals mixing business and politics.
I cut him directly.
Rotten to the core. How dare he try to deal with you?
Please convey that I'll meet with him.
Sir?
I will meet him.
How do I look?
Madam, you are so beautiful!
Really, it suits you perfectly.
You are too beautiful!
Father.
You bastard.
Kneel!
Did you forget why I raised you as an equal to Chi Kyeom?
I hadn't forgotten.
Is that right?
Han Pan Ro started to approach shopping malls.
He dares to snatch the play mall I gave your older brother?!
I did not realize it.
It's an even bigger problem if you say you didn't know!
How are you managing our household?!
It's a sworn statement forfeiting your rights and legal document about your inheritance.
[Statement of Successor Forfeiture]
I can't rely on you any more.
Sign here!
I gave my life to the company.
You can't do this to me, Sir.
The true successor of this family is Chi Kyeom.
- Father.
- Were we to rely solely on you, we don't know how your father-in-law will behave in the future.
Sign it!
What will my children become then?
Your mother is of low birth, hence you are lowly born,
would your children be any different?
Do you think the seat of a chairman is acceptable to the child born to a good housekeeper?
The only reason you were allowed entrance (to the family) was to support Chi Kyeom, who lacks both in health and ability.
You weren't accepted so you could gobble your elder brother up!
Though I may be the one to have hidden your status of birth,
the time has come for your wife and father-in-law to learn of your birth status.
Sign it!
[Liyan Kindergarten]
Some wounds only heal when they are covered by a bigger wound.
Ra El!
Ra El! Ra El!
If I were afraid, I wouldn't have taken this path.
Ra El...
Why are you so nice to me?
When I came across you then, I still had a belief in innocence.
♫ Though I cannot return to... ♫
Though the time has changed,
I still want to protect you.
♫ I'm looking at you once more ♫
There's no further innocence in me that needs protecting.
I have fallen.
Not at all.
Not a single thing could ruin you.
The situation might have brought you to this point,
but you are still who you are.
Li Ra El. A person of god.
Your revenge has a reason, but I will have to pay for committing the deeds I shouldn't have.
Despite it all,
I plan to help you with your revenge.
Though this may not be the path I'd like to take,
my heart beats with the thought of you.
How will I ever stop?
♫ but because of missing you... ♫
♫ I'll always wait for only you... ♫
Seon Bin, my father's here.
Why haven't you changed into your performance dress?
I will shortly change. And your father?
Please come in!
Congratulation on your recital.
Long time no see!
Hello, Sir.
Your proposal was outstanding.
You are amazing for a person who is a housewife.
I studied business administration.
I see. It makes sense.
I hear Bo Ra's mom is an excellent dancer. Are you going to run a risk of being compared?
Don't be shocked after seeing me perform.
Brother, all that is left is for us to cheer her on.
I bet you're right.
- See you later.
- Yes, Dad.
Fighting!
Get ready, okay?
Hello, everyone.
I am the director of Liyan Kindergarten, Cha Alisa.
Firstly, let me share my gratitude
to the parents and students,
and the relevant persons
who have come to attend our autumn recital.
Without further ado, the first performance will be...
As you know, they are the shining stars of our kindergarten?
We begin the musical recital of the students.
Please show your support with a round of heartfelt applause.
[Liyan Kindergarten]
He disappeared?
He left stating that he had to speak with someone for a moment...
We will bring him back.
Next up is...
in order to elevate our kindergarten's prestige,
the parents have prepared a special performance.
Let us welcome them.
Please applaud.
Pretend you didn't see anything. If you know too much about the 1%, you'll get hurt.
And then some woman interfered with my plan, claiming we return her husband's company.
Gediks Semi-Conductor company's wife or something.
Gediks was my dowry.
One young, one old woman.
They switched their fate.
Thanks to me.
There you go. Shall we take a picture?
Then I'll take a photo now.
One, two, three!
What is that woman about?
She nabs your soul.
What a woman. What a woman.
Encore!
[Hello! Welcome Autumn Recital]
What happened to your face?
You know that clown who mistook himself as the king,
if that clown seizes the throne and becomes the true king,
wouldn't he then no longer be mistaken?
What... do you want to say?
What if I become the real king?
Father-in-law, Father, and Eldest Brother. To step over all who suppress me,
become the king by taking control over LY.
Not as the clown, but as the real king.
Hello, I'm So Ra Han. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
So, So Ra, you were known as the lady of LY, the representative group of Korea.
How come you can dance so well?
Actually, I practiced for a month,
when I got a request for a performance from the kindergarten...
Thank you so much for today.
Thank you.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you so much.
Is it okay?
It was perfect. We got everything that we needed.
I can do anything if you are by my side.
No matter what, promise me that you'll be by my side.
I will.
I will remain by your side, Chairman.
I will walk alongside you.
No matter what happens.
Thank you so much for having us today.
Your performances were great.
I'm happy you enjoyed.
- See you next time.
- Bye.
You saw that my husband came, right?
That man is mine. Forever.
But, Sis...
Yes?
What is it? Tell me.
It suddenly came to mind.
I'm rather intuitive with such things as a married woman.
About the chairman...
What about my husband?
I think he may have another woman.
What?
[Nonexecutive Director and Economic Advisor: Han Pan Ro]
♫ Bailemos Tango (Let's dance tango) ♫
♫ An untruthful story that has yet to end ♫
♫ Unable to escape again ♫
♫ Draped in the memory of this night ♫
[Eve]
What if I become the wife of LY Group in place of Han So Ra?
Do you think he will divorce over an affair? Wake up!
Bring me the physical evidence. If you either say you don't have it or blame it on a mistaken notion, you will die.
With a cruel method, I will make her beg to kill her instead.
Why did you come here? It's dangerous.
Are you saying it was all that Seon Bin's doing?
Tell me. Who are you!
Why can't I contact you, Kim Seon Bin?
Step over her!
I got you.
♫ An untruthful story that has yet to end ♫
♫ Unable to escape again ♫