[Film planning | Studio Dragon]
[Production | CJs Entertainment]
[Seo Ye Ji]
[Park Byung Eun]
[Yu Seon]
[Lee Sang Yeob]
[Eve]
[This program contains product placement and virtual advertising.]
[This drama is fiction and the characters, names, institutions, events, organizations, and circumstances are not real.]
[Episode 8]
We are from the Hit and Run Task Force at the Gongnam Police Department.
Though the car involved in the accident was a corporate vehicle, there's talk that the chairman's family member was using it.
We need to know who was driving. Where do we go to meet with the person in charge?
The Gongnam boulevard mess? What are you talking about?
Madam!
Give me your cell phone.
Is there anything else that can be traced to me?
I'm asking if there are any of my messages or contact information in the computer or the tablet.
There's... none.
You and I... we must never be caught.
If my husband... and especially
my dad finds out, we are dead.
Do you understand?
What trouble did this woman cause?
Why now?
We can't let the TF Team become exposed.
Change our meeting location.
Make sure the media doesn't find out the hit and run was caused by my wife.
Police, media, even headquarters. Block them all.
Yes, Sir.
So Ra, where did this child go? She hasn't returned yet?
She intends on staying at a hotel until the incident settles down.
Why on earth did she crawl out in the early morning and hit another's car?!
What's gotten into her? She's acting insane!
Brother, Yoon Kyeom is here.
Lee Ra El...
I underestimated you.
[LY corporate vehicle hit and run after collision on Gongnam Boulevard.]
We have to appear in front of the Hit and Run Task Force.
Where is my wife?
Why do you look for your wife at my house?
Da Bi was waiting for her mom,
but instead the police showed up.
Is this type of incident insignificant to you, Father-in-law?
So, how are you running your household exactly?
Is this also my fault?
Where is my wife? Please tell her to handle the situation.
- I do not know.
- Father-in-law!
We should cooperate in times like these.
I understand that she is at a hotel,
so I'll bring her here for you two to discuss calmly.
I'm sure it's not a big deal.
A few days ago, in the early morning, at a Gongnam-gu, Seoul City boulevard,
an unidentified vehicle chase was witnessed.
In the early hours of the morning when there was sparse traffic,
two vehicles were engaged in an unknown chase that one could only see in a movie
and stopped only after they ended in a collision.
What? What about Han Pan Ro?
What did he send?
- Welcome.
- Why, thank you.
- Nice to see you.
- I think Han Pan Ro found out
that Yoon Kyeom was trying to buy back shares.
Look at this.
You ought to drive a comfortable car.
Chairman, regarding the hit and run mv file,
we obtained it.
The perpetrator is indeed your daughter-in-law,
and she was with a man.
A man?
Find out who this man is.
Secure the location of Han Pan Ro also.
Quickly!
>Yes, Sir.
- Congratulations.
- Welcome.
Thanks for coming all this way.
- How did you find the time to publish a book with your busy schedule?
- All went smoothly, thanks to you.
- I'll have to work even harder.
- Thank you.
Wow, if it isn't Assemblyman Seo!
I wanted an opportunity to meet you for some time.
Yes, Sir. Nice to meet you, Prime Minister.
It'll be mutually beneficial for us to publicize our acquaintance.
It suits me well, Sir.
In-law!
In-law?
If I had known that you were coming, I would have called you.
Can you survive even with such crude threats, In-law?
My daughter-in-law was with a man.
What are you going to do about this mv file?
Is Yoon Kyeom aware of this?
The fact that my daughter-in-law was with another man?
Wow, those two are putting up quite the intense emotional battle.
[Congratulations on your publishing]
They've been suspecting that Chairman Kang was planning something.
Do you believe Ra El is involved, Assemblyman?
It appears so.
[LY Gallery. Notice of Closure. Due to an unforeseen reason, the gallery will be closed for today.]
An early morning hit and run? Good grief.
What an unfathomably low deed...
It's good to cause trouble once in a while.
Given the fact that you ran over here at once.
I drank a glass of champagne with a friend and hit that car by accident.
I ran because I thought it might cause much talk,
- but it's not a big deal.
- Which friend?
Since when did we discuss minute details?
Is this an occasion for a joke?
Well, it figures. Though we may not know about each other's personal lives,
everyone is well known, so why cover it up?
Answer my question first.
That's the sequence.
I will come right out and ask.
Do you have another woman?
I don't.
What do you believe our marriage is about, Honey?
This gallery... You know we were gifted it during our 5th year wedding anniversary, right?
Gifts for the 20th year and 30th year...
all the gifts we are owed are all determined already.
I believe I deserve to receive a gift each and every year of our marriage.
Our marriage is not happenstance or sentimentalism.
In order to score the man called Kang Yoon Kyeom, I set the stage and achieved the plan.
And in order to maintain it, I put forth an unbelievable effort.
Our marriage is...
the result of my endeavors.
But wait, there might be someone who ruins it.
You don't believe I should forgive that person?
Never.
I ask once again. Do you...
have another woman?
No.
Your words tell me no, but your eyes tell me otherwise.
I really hoped it wasn't true.
It was more like a prayer than a hope.
Then there's only one remaining problem.
Guessing "who" it is.
- I told you I don't have anyone.
- It's decided as to what I should do.
To find who your woman is.
- Vice Chairman!
- Ah, yes!
Your discussion ended rather quickly.
What a relief.
I'll take care of the police.
Who the heck do they think they are to investigate the chairman's wife?
Don't you worry.
I will allow the police investigation.
Pardon?
Just make sure I'm not photographed when I attend.
[Gongnam Police Station]
Ms. Oh Seon Hee, did you really take drugs?
They adjusted the schedule of singer Oh Seon Hee's drug incident.
The chief of police said he'd create a distraction, so attend without worry.
Go.
[Chief of Police's Office]
It's an incident that which both the victim and the perpetrator have disappeared,
hence there are many who are curious.
Unfortunately, we had to investigate. Please, we ask for your understanding, Madam.
I don't mind.
I did not come to be investigated, but to make a report.
Pardon?
The vehicle that fled,
was my car that was stolen.
Uh, wait a minute...
Madam? Are you saying that car is yours?
Are you saying that you hit your own car?
The car that fled the scene was my husband's gift, but it was stolen.
So I was going to catch the thief without my husband finding out, but I failed.
If the police were to catch the driver, everything will be resolved.
What? They've labeled my car as a wanted vehicle?
Make sure Ms. Kim Seon Bin isn't exposed.
Hide the vehicle and send the bodyguard overseas.
What is it?
Ms. Kim Seon Bin is yet to pick up the phone.
Whenever you feel alone and lonely,
open this up.
It contains my plan that can resolve everything.
[Attorney Seo Eun Pyeong]
Mr. Attorney.
You are well, right?
Han Pan Ro and Kang Bon Keun, those two's relationship appears to have gotten worse.
I thought you needed to know.
Are you hoping the situation will get worse?
All right. Whatever you decide,
I trust it.
Didn't you say the box you gave me contains a plan?
There was nothing in it.
I don't have any plans, Ra El.
Not having any plans is my plan.
I will just remain by your side like a shadow.
Only remember... that you have a perfect ally.
If I were to...
commit a deed like a monster...
or...
something even worse than that?
Do it all. It's all right.
Yes, Chief. Did you find the culprit?
Is it possible to get the driver's phone number?
If it is our company's employee, we will handle it within the organization.
She was on her way to running abroad.
Is that face right?
Yep.
Hello, Miss. I'm asking you for the final time.
Whom did Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom ask you to guard?
Shit. You are getting blood on me.
Drag her out.
Where's her cell phone?
[VIP]
A VIP?
[Lee Yeon Ok Bodyguard]
Who are you?
Which bitch is this?
Who the hell are you to be my husband's VIP?
Finding your identity is a piece of cake. Give me a day.
Why don't we meet? Tomorrow at 12:00 p.m.
I will come and find you. However,
under the condition you'd release the bodyguard immediately.
Brother, don't worry about the footage.
According to So Ra, it is a designated driver.
We can reveal the driver's identity.
You said you can find the identity, right?
Yes, Sir.
So, Kang Yoon Kyeom used me to threaten his father?
Haven't you figured out what he's up to?
Not yet. I'm still in the middle of finding out.
On Da Bi's birthday, if So Ra meets with Yoon Kyeom to find out this and that,
I will summarize it and report back to you.
Today's an important day, with Miss Da Bi's birthday and the CMM interview with the parent council.
I will turn you into the most elegant parent in the world.
Have I ever liked playing the role of a parent?
Not at all, Madam. I'm sorry.
Make me appear strong.
Yes, Madam.
Strong I say.
[Liyan Kindergarten]
[Happy birthday, Da Bi!]
Da BI, happy birthday!
Happy birthday
Da BI, happy birthday.
- Thank you!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Hello...
Thank you for coming.
When that bitch shows up at 12:00 p.m, catch her right then and there.
Entrance to the kindergarten, the road, and the parking lot. Guard them all.
Yes, Madam.
I haven't seen Bo Ram's mom at all lately.
I'm sure she'll come today? It's Da Bi's birthday, after all.
There's also the parent interview.
There must be a lot to prepare for the year-end celebration, but she's been absent for so long. Don't you think?
I was going to scold her, now that you mention it.
Let's go.
Good to see you, Sir.
Everyone, attention please.
Thank you for coming to Da Bi's birthday party.
Thank you for being sweet to Da Bi.
Please enjoy yourselves comfortably, and let us know if there's anything else you need.
Let's light the candles.
♪ Happy birthday to you, Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Kang Da Bi, Happy birthday to you ♪
Sis, that bracelet is something I haven't seen before. Did you buy it?
No. I received it as a gift.
Are you dating these days? You are really suspicious.
Did you perhaps receive a diamond?
Not at all.
Secretary Kim, any unknown woman yet?
All are either parents or members of the media team.
Welcome.
Wow!
Bo Ra's mom, welcome.
We were waiting as the interview session starts soon.
We heard that you were ill. Are you all right now?
Yes.
What is she about?
Mommy!
- Bo Ram!
- Ma'am!
Da Bi, happy birthday!
- You are so pretty!
- Thank you.
Let me take a look at you, My Bo Ram.
So pretty. Did you eat?
Are you sure you were sick? You're back more beautiful than ever.
I saw this dress in a magazine and thought it was meant for mannequins only. How do you look so good in it?
It is you two ladies who are really beautiful.
Has anything good occurred lately?
Not particularly.
Can she smile?
Secretary Kim.
Is there still no one who has come?
It is certain that no one came.
What is this?
Bring her to me.
Madam asks to see you.
Da Bi, play with Bo Ram. Okay?
Madam, happy birthday to Da Bi.
You look truly beautiful today.
You are in your element.
You dropped a bomb like that and cut off all contact. What is up with you?
I'm sorry.
I saw the traffic accident news.
Are you hurt?
Why would I be hurt? That bitch who is supposed to come today will be hurt.
Is someone... supposed to come?
They say that the VIP is coming.
Did you find her finally?
I did find her. She was going to run away with her tail between her legs.
Coward bitch.
Who said she ran away with her tail tucked?
If one doesn't show, it is running away. It's past 12:00 p.m. It's a bust.
She's here.
- What are you talking about?
- She showed at 12:00 p.m. on the dot.
I'm asking what you are saying.
I told you to release the bodyguard immediately.
Why do you not listen to me?
Why do you take out your anger on an innocent person? Let's not do that anymore.
You...?
It's you?
I see why...
you seek the chairman's love so much.
Your birthday was our first day.
Today is my birthday!
You can't betray me ever, okay?
Of course not. Until the day I die.
He's not a man I'd want to lose,
that chairman.
Madam.
Would it be all right to begin the parent interview session?
Sure.
Could you stand side by side, please?
Last time, you both put out an amazing performance together.
Are you still as close to each other as you were back then?
Crazy bitch.
Get your act together.
Do you want to be found out being played by me?
If you'll excuse me. I'll only be interviewing So Ra.
Bo Ram, come here. Shall I show you something funny?
Yes, please!
Go play.
I thought I'd lose my mind missing you.
How can you not keep in contact for so long?
I also missed you. A lot.
Let's be together.
I'll go to the Rose house after the party.
It can't be. Not anymore.
This will help your TF Team.
We are over.
What do you mean we're over?
Madam found out.
It doesn't seem possible to see you again.
Not see you again? That won't happen.
There's no way.
You must be out of your mind.
Totally crazy.
Daddy! Can you open this, please?
Okay.
Let's talk later.
I'll take my leave.
Hey!
I'm going to kill you. I'll tear your heart to pieces.
Feel the hellish pain. I'll make you beg for death.
You'd make me beg to die.
Those aren't unfamiliar words to me. But this may not be the best time for you to do so, Madam.
What I might be thinking? Why I did it?
And what will I do in the future? You've not a single inkling of any of it.
What would you do when you haven't even understood the issue?
Why will I need to understand the likes of you? I'm just going to bury you.
I will give you some homework.
How about pondering why something like this happened to me?
It's about time.
You've never really had to think like that before. Because you were always the perpetrator, never the victim.
It's a question familiar to those who suffered a big misfortune.
Why such misfortune as this has come to me?
The question that doesn't leave your brain.
The question that makes you die of not knowing the answers to.
Why? Why do you suppose?
When you find the answer, I can take it a wee bit easy on you.
Honey!
Shush.
Talk with me.
- Get in the car.
- Why would I get in your car?
Are you going to leave separately despite all the eyes watching? Get in quickly.
I said get in quickly. Get in if I tell you to get in.
Let go of me.
Let's talk.
You having an affair makes me seethe,
yet you picked the one that is least suitable. Have you any idea how degrading this is?
I can never forgive her.
- I will not sit back idly and leave her be.
- I was the one who began.
She doesn't deserve the blame. Blame me.
You're still worried about that bitch?
Not me?
I understand how you feel. That's why you should hate me.
Unbelievable.
And?
I'm sorry.
And!
And what else?
Tell me what you want.
What I want?
I want this to have never happened.
I'm saying it will do if you haven't had the affair!
Let's go home and talk.
Why should I? I'm going to my father's house.
First, head home.
I'm going to think about what to do at dad's house.
Driver Park, turn the car around.
Grandma!
Honey.
Honey, thank you for coming back to me.
I realized it desperately that
I can't live without you. Let's start again. I will do better.
Your secret. Can you tell me what that video I saw was about?
Okay, I'll tell you everything.
Vice President Kim Yi Sak. He is the bad guy.
That guy sold Gediks to LY.
It's true that I was an entry-level employee then. But I have no reason to be threatened by anyone.
I never saw the Gediks CEO or his daughter.
Don't let anyone else get involved in this problem.
I won't allow it.
If you were afraid of dad finding out, why did you touch that bitch?
I haven't forgiven you for what you've done.
If you cause any issue, I won't sit idly by.
Who is threatening who just now?
Don't ignore my warning.
Spend one night at your dad's and come home tomorrow.
He confessed that Kim Yi Sak sold off Gediks.
I think it can be admissible in our lawsuit.
You ignored me before, but now you want to help?
It's not that I ignored your words, Ma'am.
My determination to sue together hasn't changed.
Didn't you say you'd make Han So Ra divorce?
Whatever I do against Han So Ra,
it won't disrupt the lawsuit.
You sure are stubborn.
You think that playing with someone's feelings is as easy as cutting radishes with a knife?
As I said before clearly, I do not have feelings for Chairman Kang.
Even if I did, it isn't important.
[LY]
[LY Pay]
- Chairman.
- Yes.
We have a problem.
In order to enter the New York market, Yoon Kyeom
established a TF Team.
There are many experts.
What about the people who were pushing for the IPO?
Why the TF Team?
LY currency circulation was only a decoy.
We were stabbed in the back.
That little...
[LY Pay New York market entry celebration drone show]
What do you mean LY Pay? Not currency circulation?
In the currency, both you and your in-law own shares, but
LY Pay's share 100% belongs to Yoon Kyeom.
So what you're saying, that he's listing it in the NY market?
If he succeeds, taking over the company with the cashflow is only a matter of time.
I'm sorry, Sir.
You may not enter.
How dare you?
Have you any idea who I am?
Without specific permission from Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom, he asked that we do not permit your entry into the company.
How dare...!
- Call Yoon Kyeom.
- Yes, Sir.
You will get what you deserve.
Yoon Kyeom, that bastard, dare fool me?
He's a nasty bastard who'd even play with his own parent.
Repulsive bastard.
What is it?
I apologize. No one can enter without Chairman Kang's permission.
What an unholy bastard!
My son-in-law is such a bastard. You are his father, aren't you?
It appears that he stabbed your back, too.
What a great household.
Wait! There was a video as well, wasn't there?
Shall I say, "Like father, like son?"
Watch what you say! Who do you think started this mess?
What nonsense! Are you trying to say it was because of me?
Since you are nibbling your way into the company in order to take over the shares,
the strife has happened, of course!
LY was originally mine to begin with, you thieving bastards!
How dare you use profanity in my presence, you lowly servant!
- You're a parasite!
- What?
The kind that kisses conglomerate's asses, a political parasite!
You little...
Watch your mouth, please.
What impertinent bastard!
How the hel...
Fuck.
Can't see straight, can you?
You bastard, you still—
What...?
- Let go!
- Come on!
You have to suck it up.
Let go of me now.
- Are you not gonna let go?
- What the heck?
Stop!
Why are you holding me back, you bastard!
I was holding back, trying to let it go.
LY is originally mine, you unholy bastard!
All of these happening are due to you, you bastard!
Hey, are you crazy?
You dare hit me?
You there, you bastard!
Come here, you bastard!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh!
Isn't that the chairman?
[1st Class Global Leader LY]
She doesn't know how scary the world is, is that right?
Okay.
How dare she?
Fine.
Oh, Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom is on TV.
LY Pay utilizes the world's first biometric payment system.
It will become the unconventional biometric payment system.
LY Pay will be historically...
LY's stage isn't only domestic, but global.
Chairman Kang is so cool!
Congratulations, Madam.
You and the chairman will become extremely busy at the end of this year.
I don't want to be burdensome, but I couldn't resolve this issue alone.
Please help me.
All right. Tell me whatever you need.
A female bodyguard that Chairman Kang placed for me is in danger.
She was captured by Han So Ra, but as there are many men, I cannot rescue her by myself.
Of course, you helping me cannot be known.
Hey, what's this?
It's the police. Run!
Are you okay?
- Yes.
Ms. Yeon Ok, are you okay?
Ms. Yeon Ok, please come to your senses.
Ms. Yeon Ok!
Check on where the ambulance is, hurry.
It'll be here shortly.
All right.
Thanks, Myeong Hwan. I owe you one.
Owe what?
If you hadn't saved us,
we would still be in gangs.
Thank you.
Ms. Yeon Ok, open your eyes. Open your eyes!
Ms. Yeon Ok!
They said she should be hospitalized for a few more days.
If it weren't for you, it could have been serious.
Congratulations!
Great job!
You all worked truly hard. Our success is thanks to all of you.
Let's drink a toast.
Cheers!
- Great work.
- Great work!
Thank you.
It's over between us. I don't think I can see you again.
Chairman.
Where are you going?
I need to go somewhere real quick.
So Ra, that bitch.
She can't even keep track of her husband's whereabouts?
What must have she been up to for me to have been humiliated like this?
Hurry and find her.
Yes, Sir.
So Ra, I tried to calm your father but it's not working. He's headed your way.
I'm in front. I'm going crazy...
because I miss you. Just for a moment...
I'll see you... for just a second.
I can't. Think of your wife.
I know.
But on a day like today, the only person I'm thinking about is you. Please let me see you for a second.
Please.
It's over between us.
Chairman Kang.
How could you show your face here? Bo Ram's dad knows about you two.
Don't cause any more trouble. If you don't listen to my warning,
you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
Go home.
I can be by myself.
Lay down. I'm okay.
You seem like a good person.
Can you tell me where the Chairman and the TF Team are celebrating?
Kim Seon Bin sent a present to your office.
[Astor Piazzolla; March 1968; Buenos Aires]
♫ All the days I endured, pinching my hands ♫
♫ All the times you were tired and wanted to collapse ♫
♫ No matter what happened ♫
This is Piazzolla's Bandoneon.
I saw your scar.
Scars may not fade away, but your heart
perhaps can be cured, little by little.
With this Bandoneon,
I hope that it will bring you and
your late mother's soul comfort.
♫ Even on your toughest days ♫
♫ I'll be the one to hold your hand ♫
♫ I won't take a single step away from you ♫
I missed you.
I can't live without seeing you.
Don't say that it's over.
Please.
Chairman!
Who do you think you are?
You think being a chairman makes everything okay?
She has a husband!
Honey!
Were you surprised I called you out randomly?
What are you talking about? I'm happy that you did.
Honey, let's look at the city lights and go out for a drink.
I'm really grateful.
Come here.
Calm down, General Manager Jang.
Who are you to tell me to calm down?
- Please don't be like this.
- Honey.
Why are you holding me back? You should be holding him back!
General Manager!
Are you okay?
Don't touch her.
Who's the one that should be saying that?
She's my wife.
She's my wife!
As long as you're acting like this, I can't let you near her.
You call yourself the chairman, fool around with another man's wife, and now you're threatening me, too?
It's over for you. If word gets out about this, it's over for you!
The only reason you can yell like this is that you're her husband legally.
- Does that mean we should take care of things legally?
- What?
Are you trying to say you'll have us divorced?
I'm Kang Yoon Kyeom. I've always gotten what I wanted.
You're crazy. Definitely crazy.
You are, too.
That's understandable if it's for this woman.
I can't end things with you.
I have a question.
When you had disappeared...
Sure, you probably meant to do so.
What were you waiting for?
A threshold point.
The moment water boils over.
Water doesn't boil all of a sudden.
Ten degrees,
twenty degrees, seventy degrees.
After having gone through all the moments, will it start to boil over.
And from liquid to gas,
it changes into a different state of matter.
♫ It’s just a petty game, but I won’t let you down ♫
People are the same.
When you reach that threshold,
you lose your sanity
and do things you shouldn't do.
♫ Promised not to let you down ♫
Stop!
- No!  - Lee Ra El.
She probably won't stop with getting Han So Ra a divorce.
Tell Chairman Kang that Ra El is the daughter of Lee Tae Joon.
As soon as you can.
You reach the threshold and do things you shouldn't do...
How are you trying to use that to your advantage?
It's an opportunity to
change the destiny that was determined by God.
♫ Just feel me lose my mind ♫
♫ Don’t say a thing, I’m right next to you ♫
♫ Close your eyes, from my shadowed heart ♫
♫ Too far away ♫
♫ Close your eyes ♫
[Eve]
Even if the worst case scenario happens, I have nothing to lose.
What is the reason you called me here?
Honey.
You put in a lot of effort.
What is the reason Han So Ra hates me so much?
Psychopath.
I can't leave you alone, can I?
Sounds like a thrill.
I'll dedicate my entire life to this.
♫ Don’t say a thing ♫