[Film planning | Studio Dragon]
[Production | CJs Entertainment]
[Seo Ye Ji]
[Park Byung Eun]
[Yoo Sun]
[Lee Sang Yeob]
[Eve]
[This program contains product placement and virtual advertising.]
[This drama is fiction and the characters, names, institutions, events, organizations, and circumstances are not real.]
Are you all right?
Your complicated feelings toward Chairman Kang...
I understand it.
First, let's rush and wrap things up.
Then I'm sure there will be a direction, whichever way it may be.
I have a way to get them all, once and for all.
Pardoning only one person... I was using the dilemma that the suspects would face.
Making the suspects... suspicious of each other?
Kang Yoon Kyeom, Han Pan Ro, Han So Ra, Kim Jeong Cheol...
We know full well the dynamics among these four people. We just make them tear into each other.
Since there is a trap called ambition, I'm sure they'll fall for it.
And you. You're very thin, Ra El.
Do you have a future in mind for yourself when everything is over?
I haven't thought about it.
It will be all over soon.
I think you could start thinking about your future.
Future...
What could be there for me?
How about you, Attorney?
As for me...
I want to prepare a warm home-cooked meal for you.
Our ordinary daily lives are the most precious thing for us.
Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom will show up at the trial?
Are you sure?
The head of a conglomerate has never attended a public lawsuit.
I hear LY Group is turned upside down as well.
Kang Yoon Kyeom personally informed the prosecution that he'll attend the trial.
If that's the case, it means he's willing to stand in front of the prosecution and the press.
What could it be? Trying to control the trial by playing it up in the press? Or...
throw his weight around and put the pressure on the prosecution?
I wonder what he's trying to do.
Tell him to come out.
No matter what he does, he can't defeat someone who's willing to put her life on the line.
[Episode 15]
What is your reason for attending the trial, Chairman Kang?
Is Lee Ra El the Strategic Planning Team Manager Kim Seon Bin?
Please say a word!
One word, please!
Please!
It's Lee Ra El!
Please say something!
One word, please!
Lee Ra El! Over here, please!
Lee Ra El, is it true that you were Chairman Kang's lover?
Please say a word, please!
Ms. Lee Ra El, say something!
Is it true that you were once lovers?
Lee Ra El, please tell us!
Tell us, please!
Please look over here!
Look over here, please!
Ms. Lee Ra El, with the head of LY Group in attendance,
are there any changes to the existing charges?
There is.
I'll reveal additional charges.
Kang Yoon Kyeom, Han Pan Ro, Han So Ra, and Kim Jeong Cheol.
Against these four people, according to the criminal code 250,
I will charge them with murder.
- What?
- Murder?
Look. Announcing the suspicion without substantiation is against a presumption of innocence until proven guilty.
[Gediks Semiconductor Documents Relevant to Merger and Misc.]
They tortured my father Lee Tae Joon, CEO of Gediks
and took away his company by force.
Kim Jeong Cheol mainly conducted the torture
and Han Pan Ro and Han So Ra instigated it.
And also Kang Yoon Kyeom.
It was a premeditated murder.
Chairman Kang, do you admit to her statement?
Did you come here aware of the fact that it's a criminal trial?
Chairman Kang, please state your stance.
Lee Ra El!
Just a moment! Just one more word, please!
Please tell us! Wait a moment!
Just one more thing!
One more thing, please!
Please tell us! Do you admit to instigating murder?
Tell us!
Chairman Kang! Tell us!
Chairman Kang!
The compound fracture is severe, damaging his nerves and muscles.
I re-operated on him, but he'll most likely have a permanent disability due to peroneal nerve palsy.
Permanent disability?
Geez, my leg!
What do I do about my leg, Brother!
He says I can't walk straight now!
Why should I have to go through this? Huh?
Let's look for a way. Calm down.
How can I calm down?
She crushed my perfectly fine leg!
I'm so angry! I can't stand this!
Crush that bitch, Lee Ra El's leg, too! Please?
Brother!
Prime Minister, it's trouble!
Lee Ra El pressed murder charges and mentioned actual names.
Chairman, Prime Minister, Madam, and...
Vice-Chairman Kim Jeong Cheol, too.
Wow, damn! Crazy wench! You see that?
On top of that, Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom even attended the trial.
Why would that bastard crawl out there? I'm setting things in motion underground.
Why!
Call everyone on our legal team! Hurry!
Brother, where are you going? How about me? How about my leg? You'll crush that Lee Ra El, won't you?
You bastard. Shut up and get treatment!
That asshole!
Brother! Brother!
In this case that the plaintiff Lee Ra El, who is also the representative of the LY Group Victim's Group,
brought against the defendant Kang Yoon Kyeom
is currently both under civil and criminal jurisdiction.
Depending on the result of the criminal trial, the scope of compensation for the damages will change.
To decide on the compensation amount, we must wait until the result of the criminal trial is finalized.
Lee Ra El, do you agree to this?
I will submit additional evidence that proves the criminal acts by the chairman's family.
Even so, we need to know the result of the criminal trial.
Chairman Kang's attendance here today is proving effective. They're trying to give him more time.
Regardless of the result of the criminal trial, I will settle for the settlement the plaintiff asks for.
What is he talking about?
Chairman, this is disadvantageous for us.
Mr. Kang Yoon Kyeom, it doesn't seem as if you've discussed this with your legal team.
Please repeat once more.
I will settle Lee Ra El's lawsuit.
We can mediate if you're willing to settle.
Ms. Lee Ra El, would you accept his mediation?
By chance, could he have other motives?
I will accept it.
Good. We'll set another date for mediation for you two privately.
Chairman, you don't need to settle this. If you settle this, you won't be able to handle the criminal case later.
I'll take care of it.
Kang Yoon Kyeom, Han Pan Ro, Han So Ra, and Kim Jeong Cheol.
I will press charges against these four people with murder.
What the hell are they doing?
[Han Pan Ro, Han So Ra, Kang Yoon Kyeom, Kim Jeong Cheol, charging them with murder]
Why are they together even there? Are they magnets? Huh?
More than that, the fact that you were named for murder–
That's strong liquor! It'll cause you trouble, Madam!
Even if I pull them apart this way and that way, they get back together.
Are they twins or something?
Will they part only in death?
Is that how those two are?
[Dr. Jeong]
Why is Dad sitting back?
That wench Lee Ra El is causing all kinds of ruckus. Why does he leave her alone? Gosh, I'm so frustrated...
Do Hwan, come to the officetel.
Yes, Madam.
How did you get here...?
How did you know?
How did you get in?
At this rate, you could say I know everything about you.
Wouldn't you think so?
I've been preparing for thirteen years.
Get out of here right now!
Have a seat.
Do you think my family is that easy?
You'll never get away with this.
Kim Jeong Cheol is disabled, and Han Pan Ro is...
starting to look for ways to get out of it alone.
Chairman Kang knows he has to be on my good side to find a way to survive.
You saw it.
Han So Ra is the only one who is isolated without a solution.
It looks like Han So Ra alone will
take all the blame for the murders.
You're running out places to go and no one to take care of you.
You're going to break down helplessly.
What do we do now?
What nonsense.
It's good that we have some things in common. As for fear,
it's much scarier
when it squeezes in rather than when it hits you.
You don't feel true fear when it actually hits you. When you think it's going to hit you soon...
The real fear is when it squeezes you.
Even if you got what you wanted, you shouldn't have made enemies.
When you have enormous rage,
you don't even feel the pain of cutting into your skin.
You shed my parents' and my blood. Now...
pay it back with your blood.
I plan to spray your blood on my father's grave to let him know of your death.
Until the whole world is colored in your blood,
let's go for it.
[Lee Tae Joon]
Dad...
CEO.
I'm sorry we couldn't right the wrong that was done to you for such a long time.
We're not too far from it. So please wait a little longer.
And don't worry too much about Ra El. I'll...
I'll be with her to the end.
You know the trial?
You'll have to face Chairman Kang alone for mediation.
Will you be okay?
It's something I must do.
Okay.
[Plaintiff]
This mediation is separate from the lawsuit for the joint victims' group.
[Defendant]
Regarding the death of your father Lee Tae Joon and mother Kim Jin Sook,
it's mediation for compensation as their inheritor.
Is that correct, Ms. Lee Ra El?
[Mediator]
That's correct.
Mr. Kang Yoon Kyeom, you're willing to settle. Correct?
Yes, that's right.
Aside from Mr. Kang Yoon Kyeom, Ms. Lee Ra El has sued
Han So Ra, Han Pan Ro,
and Kim Jeong Cheol. The problem is that the three people
are not willing to settle.
I will convince them to settle.
Following is the argument from the attorney for those three.
Quite a bit of the evidence that Ms. Lee Ra El submitted
was acquired illegally and could not be considered as evidence.
The illegality of the means of acquiring the evidence is acknowledged. Stealing identity,
invasion of personal information, illegal recording, and etc.
They cannot be presented in the trial. They're all evidence you acquired through deception.
I lost my parents at age fifteen.
I had nothing in my possession.
No one listened to what I had to say. In order to reveal the truth,
that was the only way.
A little girl who had no choice...
getting things legitimately was a luxury.
[Mediator]
Also...
not everything was a lie.
Ms. Lee Ra El, it hasn't been confirmed whether your mother Kim Jin Sook...
went missing or is dead.
We're undergoing a criminal trial to figure out the details of her death.
The problem is that no verdict has been made.
Meaning it will be difficult to come to an agreement for this case.
I would like for this civil suit to end swiftly,
so that I can apologize to the plaintiff.
I will agree to all of Lee Ra El's claims...
and settle this case.
But there's no evidence to prove Kim Jin Sook's death.
I'll bring my mother's belonging in as evidence to prove her death.
Will that be able to prove her death though?
Coming to an agreement is most important in a civil case, so I'll confirm it myself.
All right then. I'll see you next time.
If everything wasn't a lie,
which part is true?
Why is that important? Will it help us come to an agreement?
I'm going to go.
I must hurry to submit my mother's belonging.
I will look into it myself.
That way, you can skip all the documents.
Let's go together.
I'll report on this after reviewing it again.
- Sure.
- Okay.
[Kim Hyeon Cheol]
Yes, Hyun Cheol? I'm listening.
I was notified that they can't hand over Ra El's mother's belongings.
Han Pan Ro is claiming Ra El is guilty of identity fraud, which poses a problem.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry, but we can't hand it over to you.
Han Pan Ro's team suddenly presented a legal problem.
The supervisory office has taken your mother's belongings.
I was given permission from the Public Interest Law Center.
We're still discussing what to do about this.
Give me a moment. I'll let them know your situation.
Why are you still wearing the ring?
I didn't have the chance to take it off.
Your chance was when you found out who I was.
I put it on because I love you.
I'll probably take it off when my love for you dies.
Just because I dislike you,
it doesn't mean my love has died. Don't you agree?
Tell me one thing. I believed we were a twin flame.
Your hurtful past reminded me of myself.
I felt connected to you.
Your feelings towards me,
was it ever once true?
They say a twin flame can communicate without words.
Apparently, in times of life or death,
they transcend time and space and find each other.
We are nothing like that.
I approached you to destroy you. There's no fate in that.
I'm sorry, Chief Secretary Seo.
I wasn't expecting you.
This document here proves that Lee Ra El is the rightful heiress.
This document is perfect, so why won't you allow it?
The truth is, Han Pan Ro is giving us a hard time.
I'm just a powerless employee, too.
Do you operate this place according to power, not principle?
Shall I do that, too?
We were given permission.
The video of your mother's final moment is in the USB.
[Storage box]
[Kim Jin Sook]
I went out on a one-woman protest again today.
I saw Kang Yoon Kyeom coming into work.
[Investigate Gediks Semiconductor's Lee Tae Joon's wrongful death!]
Han Pan Ro and Kim Jeong Cheol going in and out of the company.
It killed me whenever I saw their smiling faces.
Don't just stand there. Get rid of that thing!
The result was always humiliation.
Nobody will listen to me.
But this is the only thing keeping me alive.
Life feels like a living hell.
Anorexia? Harming yourself?
I can't believe this is happening to you.
My heart is breaking. I'm sorry I can't protect you.
Erase the memory of your dad being tortured, Ra El.
You can't live if you hold onto that.
I will take all the pain with me. So please forget it.
It seems like they are the happiest couple in Korea.
We are in front of Han So Ra's home.
The soon-to-be groom is LY Group's heir, Kang Yoon Kyeom.
The man who took over Gediks Semiconductor and jumped into the big pool.
You bastards!
- Bastards! Die!
- Mom...
How could you live like that after taking someone's life?
You evil bastards.
Kang Yoon Kyeom... Han Pan Ro...
Murderers! You all deserve to go to hell!
I can't believe the pain you suffered was all because of me.
You were so young.
I can't even ask for forgiveness.
I'm so sorry.
That's right.
Only your death will suffice!
I'll do whatever it takes.
If I really must die,
I'll do it.
Go wait in the car.
Chief Secretary Seo.
What should I do now?
Please tell me.
I admit to all the claims... that the victims of LY filed.
Gediks Semiconductors was a target of acquisition.
Thirteen years ago, we offered a merger that they declined.
There was a plot to steal the company.
In that process, the CEO, Lee Tae Joon,
sadly lost his life.
It was due to complications from being tortured. It was premediated murder.
There is also a hidden truth to Kim Jin Sook, the CEO's wife, and Jang Moon Hee's death.
I believe that an investigation must be conducted.
Come out, Yoon Kyeom! Come out!
Chairman is not here.
I know he's upstairs!
Come out, you bastard!
I really have no idea.
Take him out.
- Please don't do this.
- Please stop.
I'm going to kill all of you.
Come out, Kang Yoon Kyeom, you punk!
Come out!
In that process, the CEO, Lee Tae Joon, sadly lost his life.
It was due to complications from being tortured. It was premeditated murder.
What?
He's basically proclaiming to come after me!
You think I'm a pushover?
I'm everyone's punching bag!
Have you seen the news?
- How could—
- You punk!
Shut up!
Brother! Hey!
Damn it.
Who's here?
The police are here to investigate you.
They opened up an investigation into Jang Moon Hee and Kim Jin Sook's murders after Chairman's press conference.
Tell them you don't know anything. Why me? I didn't do anything wrong.
A recording that will be crucial evidence... was submitted to the police.
The police chief informed us.
You will betray one another.
Then die a lonely and sad death.
That is your punishment!
You wench. You captured Jang Moon Hee, right?
You starved Kim Jin Sook to death, didn't you?
You killed both of those wenches.
That wench knows I have this woman.
- If he knows—
- Put that down.
Ma'am, the police are still waiting out front.
- What should I do?
- Tell them I'm not here!
Yes, I understand.
Where is he?
Call him.
Ask him what I should do.
Chairman Kang has been missing since the press conference.
Nobody knows his whereabouts.
The secretary's office is in full panic mode.
Who's the one who sent the recording to the police?
Who got it and how!
Wasn't the recording file sent to the police clever?
It was edited to make Han So Ra a suspect.
Do you know who did it?
Han Pan Ro and I made a deal. He said he'll hand you over to save himself.
How dare you screw me over after everything I've done for you?
You don't deserve to live, just like your mother. You're obsessed with your husband.
Han So Ra is the only one deserted without a plan.
You're starting to lose people to turn to.
Nobody to take care of you. You'll be helplessly destroyed.
It looks like fingers will be pointed at you for everything.
I won't believe anything you say.
The truck driver you and Kim Jeong Cheol hired to dispose of the body will be going to the prosecutors', too.
You couldn't receive love even from your husband,
and you're even being abandoned by your own father.
You'll have to die lonely.
Having received no sympathy from anyone.
Do Hwan, that bitch just told me—
- Is it true that my dad betrayed me?
- Ma'am.
Prime Minister, he told the prosecutors' that you ordered it.
That is his testimony.
Somebody has to take the blame,
in order for things to be taken a little lightly.
I didn't think Han So Ra's boyfriend would be anyone significant,
but this is so anticlimactic.
Moon Do Hwan.
Chief Secretary Seo.
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
My mother is ill.
I just needed the money. Please!
Please forgive me. I'm sorry!
How could I forgive an attempted murder?
It's not forgiveness you should be asking for.
Rather, you should be thinking about what you can do right now.
[Woonseo Law Firm]
This isn't enough evidence.
Photos of the prison...
were handed over to the police?
So Ra did this?
Yes.
That good for nothing bitch.
Damn it!
Prime Minister!
You can't do this to her. She's your daughter after all.
Who are you to say anything to me!
Move!
Father!
Did you hand me over?!
Did you sell me for you to save your own ass!
Good that you are here.
Did you hand over the jail photos?
Do you know who made me become like this?
This is all because of you!
You are the one who ruined everything!
Dad.
Dad!
Ma'am!
Ma'am, please stop it, at least now.
If you go this far, I'm dead, too.
How many times do I have to tell you to shut up!
If we let him go, it's not your problem.
I will be the first to die.
Hurry!
Lock it!
Open the door.
Open the door!
Open—
I won't stand back like Mom did.
I'm not the same kid who couldn't say a word!
Hey, open the door...
Stay alert.
I'll leave the house empty since so many people are coming here because of the lawsuit.
All of you are on vacation now. Don't come back until I call you.
Yes, Ma'am.
You get lost, too.
W-What about Prime Minister?
Can't you hear me?
Get lost. If you don't, you'll end up the same as him.
Got it?
Yes.
Chairman has never been out of touch for this long.
Shouldn't we file for a missing person with the police?
You can't contact Chairman Kang?
He left writing on the first screen of his computer, and it looks like a suicide note at first glance.
He also resigned from his position as the CEO.
I know it's not something to ask you, but I had no choice.
I'm resigning as the CEO, and I'll give up everything I have.
Everything seems to collapse in a blink of an eye,
so I feel miserable, but it's all my responsibility.
Since there's no way to atone for those who suffered because of me,
I'm going to take it all on myself.
Die. If anybody resists dying, you'll kill everyone,
and you'll die at the end as well.
Then it'll be over.
So I'm saying, pay back with your life!
If I really have to die, I'll do so.
Do you have any idea in mind?
I asked for his confession, but he disappeared.
I guess he decided to pay for his wrongdoing.
It's good.
[Secretary Cha]
I heard this through the legal team.
Chairman granted all of his rights and shares to you.
And he gives his personal property to Ms. Da Bi. He wrote a will saying that.
It is said that he entrusted the management of it to the legal team until she became an adult.
It makes me have ominous thoughts.
[Chairman Kang Yoon Kyeom]
The person you are trying to reach has their phone turned off. It'll be connected to the voice mail after the beep.
You'll be charged once connected.
I told him to die.
I told him to pay back with his life.
If Chairman Kang dies, I'm the one who killed him.
I shouldn't have said such harsh words.
Chairman Kang is not a weak person like that.
Let's look for him. Don't worry about it.
Have you heard of the term "twin flame"?
It's when one soul is split into two, like a twin.
The two souls instantly recognize each other the moment they meet; they're lovers.
It is said that Twin Flames
will meet each other,
no matter what.
At the moment of life and death,
Twin Flames can find each other.
If I have to die, I'll do so.
I met you and got dragged into you like fate.
You were similar to me, and I fell for you like crazy. And to you who recognized me,
I could show my true self.
I can't live without you.
I love you.
Chairman.
♫ All the days I endured, pinching my hands ♫
How did you come here?
I was so scared,
that something happened to you.
What I said to you before, I didn't mean it.
I shouldn't have said something like that.
♫ You don't have to hold back in case I get hurt ♫
♫ I hope I can be your every day ♫
♫  In all your moments,  ♫
♫  I will be there  ♫
♫ No matter what anyone says ♫
♫ My bursting love for you ♫
♫ Even if everyone else turns their backs,  ♫
♫ I won't take a single step away from you ♫
[Prime Minister Han Pan Ro]
We couldn't connect to the person, so you'll be connected to voicemail—
Is he not picking up his phone now?!
What are you doing? Please stop it!
You stay quiet!
He's been ordering me around the whole time!
And now he's ignoring me! Does he think I'm a pushover?
Who does he think I am? He totally took me wrong!
Secretary Cha.
Where is my husband?
I need him right now.
If he's not around me, I think I can lose it.
Please, find my husband...
We can't seem to find him.
Chief Secretary Seo Eun Pyeong even reported him missing to the police.
Honey.
Ma'am, we have found Chairman.
Where is he?
He's in the vacation house.
But—
But what?
The vacation housekeeper says that wench came with him.
Brother!
Come out!
You're really going to ignore me like this?
Brother!
Come out!
Where is your father?
He's treating me like a loser!
It's making me so mad that I can't take it anymore!
My dad cleaned up his assets and ran away abroad.
It's just us now.
If we don't catch Lee Ra El, we'll be the ones to take the blame.
♫  I’m seeing through your eyes. And know what’s on your mind  ♫
♫  Don’t say it for now. Just stay silent under my shadow  ♫
♫  It’s just a petty game. But I won’t let you down  ♫
Lee Ra El! You're going to die tonight.
♫  Let go of all your sorrow in my arms  ♫
♫  Why do you still hesitate? Promise not to let you down  ♫
♫  I know you don’t want to let me go  ♫
♫  Don’t say a thing. I’m right next to you ♫
♫  Close your eyes  ♫
♫  From my shadowed heart  ♫
♫  Too far away  ♫
We found Chairman Kang's car from the control center of the surveillance camera.
I think Ra El is with Chairman Kang as well. But the problem is...
What is it?
There's another corporate car near his vacation house.
♫  Just feel me lose my mind  ♫
♫  I’m seeing through your eyes. And know what’s on your mind  ♫
♫  Don’t say it for now. Just stay silent under my shadow  ♫
♫  It’s just a petty game. But I won’t let you down  ♫
♫  Let go of all your sorrow in my arms  ♫
♫  Why do you still hesitate? Promise not to let you down  ♫
♫  I know you don’t want to let me go  ♫
♫  Don’t say a thing. I’m right next to you  ♫
♫  Close your eyes  ♫
♫  From my shadowed heart  ♫
♫  Too far away  ♫
♫  To go back in time  ♫
[Eve]
Do you have a wish?
I hope there's no rage inside of my heart.
I can't find Da Bi, Honey!
[Da Bi]
Da Bi!
No...
I think Ra El got abducted. Please retain every surveillance camera video around the vacation house.
Stop the car!
Die!
What about you, Chairman?
I want to love the person I love endlessly.
♫  Hold me tight  ♫