To be honest Be honest
Fold
Flip it
Here
During this phase, it will become a little boat
Xiaochuan, Xiaozhou
Let's call it Xiaozhou
Let's go on a trip after I graduate
Where?
Anywhere
We haven't traveled yet
Go, wherever you want
Ok
Travel is not worth it
You haven't started work yet
If you want to spend money
Let's go on a trip
Great
Brother, let's go on a trip
Travel, where do you want to go?
Look at me
Beijing, ok?
Brother, look at me
Look at me
Beijing
Take me to Beijing, ok?
Ok
Come on
Brother, bye
Ok, bye
Brother, I will come back
I'm back to school
Did you bring the eggs?
In my bag
Bye
Xiaozhou, when will you come back?
20th, dad, mom, brother
Bye
Xiaozhou
The End
Li Dada didn't tell the truth
The first time he met Shen Xiaozhou
Should be at Han Chao Club
But he deliberately hid this statement
I checked
Han Chao Club belongs to Jinghai Group
You think Li Dada didn't kill Shen Xiaozhou
Another person
Then why did he report it?
I don't know
I want to continue to investigate
Since we have found Shen Xiaozhou
Another abnormal life profile
Should be clear about the details
Li Dada's case
Zhao Hougang is not responsible for it
He admitted the crime
Don't inform Shen Xiaozhou's family yet
Then continue to investigate
I'm back
Jinghai Group
Did you eat?
No
Didn't you say you would take us out to eat delicious food?
Yanyan is with the waves
Thousands of miles
Where is the spring river?
Wu Yueying
Don't tease my dad
My mom made it early
We both finished eating
Yue Zhao Hua Lin
Street 4
The cloud is flowing in the wind
I rely on you
Part of it
I'm curious
I came back to be a song
I posted a Weibo that night
Or someone's special
I actually just
I don't know what that is
Remember I told you
Cloud line
20 years ago
I don't know that girl
She has a child
Do you want to hear
My favorite profession
Is the police and doctor
Because he saves people every minute
Every minute
Make this world more lovely
Believe me
You can do it
You will be a good cop
If one day
I want to go by myself
Don't ask me why
what
Why are you here
Didn't I go to the tea
Where are you now
Where do i go
ACT has approved
Do you have any questions for me
No need.
If you think it's time to investigate, then investigate.
There's still some time.
Let's go to a place first.
The dead can't open their mouth to speak.
Have you thought about this question?
There are tens of billions of people in the world.
But the only ones who can open their mouth to speak
and help them find justice
are the police officers who are in charge of the case.
Sometimes there's only one, but no one else.
They are the only bridge between justice and them.
They are their only hope.
So you must catch the right person.
Since I was a police officer, I've been telling myself
that I'll be the first to file a case.
The first case you encountered was in 1995 in Yunxian, right?
He was my mom.
I saw your name on the record.
The record says that you two were in a relationship.
When I got into the police university, the first summer vacation,
he proposed to break up with me.
It was very sudden and decisive.
After that, I didn't hear from him for three years.
After that, I graduated and was assigned to the court.
When I went home to visit my family,
I happened to run into his case.
I learned about his experience in those years.
I finally understood why he had to break up with me.
He didn't want to leave me in that kind of life.
That kind of life is too bad.
If there really is such a day,
it means that I've left the best of me to you.
Just remember it.
Do you think that
he looked like Shen Xiaozhou at the time?
Very much.
But I never knew
that he had a child.
I
didn't know that he had a child.
He's not your son.
With your sharp eyes, you never checked my DNA.
I hesitated.
You hesitated.
How did you get rid of me?
You checked my DNA.
To be honest, I was quite happy at first.
I thought you abandoned my mom.
Because you look a little cold.
Later, I understood you.
I hope you are really the one.
I'm sorry.
It's best this way.
If it's true,
I'll delay the achievement.
How did you and my mom know each other?
That year, I met Li Yunchuan.
His name is Li Yunchuan.
He was in the senior year.
He had already studied for two years.
He didn't come to school.
Every time I saw him,
I thought he was a student.
He didn't like to wear school uniforms.
He didn't like to have long hair.
He didn't have nails.
He liked to ride a bike like a boy.
He sat on the road and drank soda.
He ate lamb skewers.
He is two extremes.
But I like him at once.
Maybe people who are nervous
are more attracted by those who are free.
Because they want to be like you.
What's strange is
he noticed me.
He knows my name.
You want to see the sea?
You can call me Lian Haiping.
You're old and don't be stupid.
Who is better than you?
I got to know him.
I realized he didn't mean to pretend.
The family is in a bad situation.
Without mom,
Dad is always on the table.
I think he should be angry with the world.
So...
So he made himself look like
a bad girl.
In fact, it's a self-protection.
When he was with me,
he was so real and cute.
The police and the doctor,
are you talking about him?
I've never been in a relationship.
I like to make trouble.
You're a good boy.
It's okay.
Just do it.
Just like before.
Is that case hard to solve?
No.
Soon the suspect was locked up.
He's been pestering her for years.
He's a lawless scoundrel.
He does everything bad.
What he wants,
is rarely what he can't get.
But he didn't listen.
He was afraid that he could resist.
Until one day,
he was chased and jumped into the river.
It's reasonable.
Because I have this relationship with him,
I can't participate in the investigation.
But I can't let go.
I can't leave.
I secretly joined the arrest.
And I hurt the murderer.
I shouldn't be so impulsive.
I should do better.
I should find more evidence
to prove my innocence.
I didn't go to the provincial court.
I chose a new position.
And I'm here.
I'm released.
I didn't expect you to have a chance
to be a good man.
I just want to see you.
I have time to go home.
To see your wife.
I'll send you the address.
Yes.
He came to our place
to be a performance guest.
He's a college student.
He wants to make some money.
He's the son of President Zhang.
He's the son of Zhang Haoyuan.
He introduced him here.
He plays the pipa very well.
The guests have good feedback.
It's about half a year.
He has one or two performances a month.
Just performances?
No other shows?
Of course not.
Just performances.
We're a high-level club.
We don't have that kind of stuff.
Besides, playing pipa
is also a way to promote our traditional culture.
Right?
Is there surveillance at the show?
No.
We're all guests.
We have to protect their privacy.
You're breaking the rules.
No matter how high-level the club is,
it's also a public entertainment place.
Why don't you monitor it?
Monitoring?
Yes.
There are several big shows outside.
Can you show us the footage?
Well...
Officer, I heard that this case has been solved.
Is it necessary?
Whether it's necessary or not,
you or I know.
This is the first time he's been here.
It's a video.
Look, he's dressed up.
Traditional Chinese clothing is high-class art.
Take out all the surveillance footage.
You should avoid it.
Okay.
Look.
What would you like to drink?
Spring water.
Enjoy.
It's okay.
It's been kept for three months.
Look at June 2.
I'm afraid we can't find anything.
In such a place,
bad things are done by the police.
Not necessarily.
Not everyone will pay attention to where the surveillance is.
He's here.
He came by himself.
He's out.
He came out in less than 20 minutes.
He hasn't changed.
He hasn't started performing yet.
He's finally back.
How long has it been?
28 minutes.
What does he have at hand?
Money?
What did he do here?
This is Li Longhe's car.
How can Shen Xiaozhou know Li Longhe?
Could it be Li Dada?
There's a driver.
Li Dada drives by himself.
He won't use this car
After Shen Xiaozhou left here
He went to Yang Tao
Yang Tao said
He was in a bad mood
And cried
How many secrets does Shen Xiaozhou have
That we don't know
Sorry, sorry
You didn't call me before
The chairman is not in the company
I came here for nothing
Where is he now
We can go to him
Tell me first
Ok?
I'll tell you
Sorry, it's not convenient
Just give me an address
This is not convenient either
What convenient
We are police
I know, comrade police
It's really not convenient
I'm not good enough
So
Please ask the director of the bureau
Call our chairman
Ask him in person
Interesting
Officer, wait a minute
Chairman personally approved
This is his address
Which Constitution
Let's drop the oil first
I'm sorry.
You're really something.
You let them take over the whole place.
This place
will be destroyed sooner or later.
Your Chairman.
Captain Lian.
You're here.
My son just got caught.
He's just on vacation.
I'm sorry.
Here, have a taste.
Green organic pollution.
I only eat my own vegetables now.
What kind of fertilizer do you use?
Garlic.
Young man.
What do you think organic means?
It's the taste of my childhood.
Since you know we're coming,
I'll be frank.
Shen Xiaozhou may not be Li Dada's killer.
Do you know Shen Xiaozhou?
Yes.
Good.
Are you in the car?
Yes.
He was in the car for 28 minutes.
What happened?
If you can speak a little slower,
I'll be more willing to answer.
Excuse me.
What happened in these 28 minutes?
You're talking too much.
A few months ago,
when Shen Xiaozhou first came to the club
as a guest,
I noticed him.
He was well-educated and well-educated.
He was born with a good will.
He's also good at studying.
It's rare.
As I got to know him more and more,
I started to respect him more.
Later, I wanted him to work for our group.
That day in the car,
I gave him a contract.
I told him that
as long as he signed it,
it would be done.
Contract?
Unfortunately, he refused.
He said it wasn't his profession.
He wanted to do his own profession.
By the way, I also invited him
to come to the Green Ecological Park.
I wanted to hear his opinion.
He gave a five-star review
to this tomato.
Did he return the contract to you later?
No.
Without signing the contract,
it's useless.
Then, June...
Then,
on June 19,
the night of the crime,
do you know where Li Dada is?
I don't know.
I rarely contact him.
We rarely meet.
Where were you at that time?
Where was I on June 19?
Check it for me.
June 19,
at night,
you went to meet
our representative from theスolons.
This is the video.
Jinhai No.1 sold well.
I gave awards
to those who were outstanding.
The meal was expected.
The chairman was there as well.
It was sold out by eleven.
Is there another problem?
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting all this time.
Can I contribute a pack of organic protein to Gui Bao's brother?
There's a toilet here.
No need.
Brother,
I've heard about you.
You're the best at solving cases.
I've always respected the cause and the effect of peace.
I respect you.
The cause is the cause.
During the peace period, the police are the cause.
I'm sorry.
Tinkai No. 1 is selling very well.
You can go and have a look if you have time.
If you like it, tell me.
But we'll follow the process.
I won't let you make mistakes.
Thank you, Chairman.
My lover has really been there.
I'll definitely go and have a look if I have time.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Gui Bao's brother
This is not a proof.
There's a video and a house certificate.
There was a surveillance camera at the gate of the farm.
It's been taken down now.
There's a mark on the door.
Why did you take it down?
I'm afraid people will know who came to Nongzhou on the 19th.
Shen Xiaozhou has been there?
No way.
It's dozens of kilometers away.
And we don't even know how Shen Xiaozhou left that street.
And the contract.
We haven't seen it either.
What?
Shen Xiaozhou didn't return it to Li Longhe.
He didn't throw it away.
He's not at school.
Could he be at home?
We didn't notice it last time.
What if he was wearing it on the day of the crime?
You think about it.
Why would he wear it?
And is it really a contract?
Get back where it is.
Come on.
Are you okay?
He's back?
I've added a paper bag with cowhide paper.
It's about this big.
I've never seen it before.
Like this.
Xiaozhou used this before.
He didn't want to throw it away.
It's for Hai.
Xiaozhou made this when he was a kid.
He lost it to Hai.
Hai.
Can I have one?
Sure.
Hai.
Did Xiaozhou give you this USB?
Here.
No.
Yes.
This USB shouldn't be broken.
Sometimes, Xiaozhou would come back with a computer
to write a thesis.
He used it to save it.
He shouldn't have left it.
Did Chen Xiaozhou put it in by himself?
I don't know.
This...
This is...
He said there were bad guys on TV.
Stealing USB.
Bad guys on TV.
Right?
Yes.
Hai.
Can you go to the police with us?
Yes.
Hai, he...
We need to get some fingerprints.
We go to the police.
To the police.
Okay.
Let me write it.
Hai.
What are you holding?
A little cover.
Okay.
Director Lian.
Xiaozhou has a clue.
Okay.
Director Lian.
The four fingerprints on the box.
Only Xiaozhou and Hai's fingerprints on this USB.
No other people's fingerprints.
Hai won't lie.
Xiaozhou won't take it if he doesn't give it.
Open it.
Okay.
I need a password.
Can you crack it?
It takes time.
Okay.
It's open.
How do you know?
Xiao Zhou.
Is there any special meaning in this number?
It seems like...
It seems like it's the birthday of our family.
Xiao Hai is 18th.
Xiao Zhou is 30th.
Xiao Zhou.
Do you have a diary or a chat log?
It's all professional information.
Is there any hidden file?
It's all here.
Let's share it.
Let's look for it together.
Okay.
You can go back after you finish eating.
Thank you.
It's all your fault.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't I notice anything?
I feel like I've read half of the environmental protection.
I didn't understand anything.
I'll go back to sleep.
So,
Li Long He's suspicion can be eliminated?
We still need to investigate.
He's not here to fight against the evil.
What else can he do?
Between him and Shen Xiao Zhou,
it's not as simple as he said.
Hai Piao.
I shouldn't have reminded you of your experience.
Did you invest too much personal feelings
into this case?
What do you mean?
You've been looking for evidence that it wasn't Li Da Da
who killed Shen Xiao Zhou.
If Shen Xiao Zhou was really killed by him,
shouldn't you come up with your own logic
and re-evaluate it?
It's a case of a rush.
It's a rush.
It's okay to follow.
Qiu Ju and I can give you time to work.
The problem is we have to have a deadline
to make a statement.
Give me two more days.
This is the testimony of the case
of Li Da Da killing Shen Xiao Zhou.
Look.
The details are basically correct.
There's nothing I want to know.
What do you want to know?
I want to know
what happened to Shen Xiao Zhou
when he was killed
at 4 p.m. on June 19th.
Yuan De.
If you have time,
check the USB drive carefully.
See if there's anything hidden.
Okay.
I keep thinking
there's something
that he wouldn't
write down this password.
Maybe he wrote it
to be on the safe side.
To be on the safe side?
Leave it to us.
Should the police
put personal feelings into the case?
The old police
will never put personal feelings
into the case.
If they don't,
it's a kind of self-protection.
But can you control it?
The deeper you investigate,
the deeper you get into it.
Sometimes,
in the most desperate,
in the darkest place,
you need to be strong
and keep going.
Don't flinch,
as if your heart is having trouble breaking.
Once you're satisfied and calm,
you feel so much better.
So,
Have you seen this person?
No, I haven't seen him.
I haven't seen him.
Thank you.
Come on, get in the car.
Come on, follow me.
Is there anyone else? Follow me.
Brother, do you have a car?
Police, is your car an ambulance?
I...
Yes, no.
Police, I'm just a civil servant.
I'm not a police.
I'm a car inspector.
Do you come here every day?
Where do you park your car?
I...
I'm a case inspector.
To be honest.
To Qianlong Bay.
I don't come here every day.
I only come here once a week.
Once a week?
No wonder.
Yes.
I'm here to let the workers in the village and the police station
go into the city to buy things.
15 yuan per person is enough.
Did you come here on June 19th?
June...
I'll check the schedule.
June 19th.
Coming.
Have you seen this man?
He's so similar to this man.
Did he really go to Li Yunhe?
He's here.
We need to get the evidence of Shen Xiaoshu going to Li Yunhe's house.
Then we can confirm it.
Get your luggage in the car.
Hurry up.
Be careful.
He got off the car here.
Can I go now?
Go.
Six kilometers from Li Yunhe's farm.
So far.
How did he get there?
Ask them.
If someone has pulled Shen Xiaoshu,
they will remember.
Master, have you pulled this man?
I don't remember.
Hello, police.
Have you seen this man?
No.
Master, have you pulled this man?
I haven't seen him.
Who didn't get off the car today?
There is.
Our car's owner, Xiang, didn't come today.
How many days has he not got off the car?
About 30 days.
He's been here for a long time.
Do you have his phone number?
Hello, the number you dialed is busy.
It's off.
Can you take us to him?
We'll pay the car fee.
The police are so polite.
No need to pay.
Xiang.
Don't knock.
No one.
He left early the day before yesterday.
Look, I told you.
He went to the third floor.
Did you see him go?
I saw the car go.
It's still not dawn yet.
Besides, his car is good.
He's riding a bicycle.
Where are his parents?
His parents are gone.
He has a girlfriend.
He works in the provincial city.
Where does he work in the provincial city?
Xiang is so good.
He sells seafood in a high-end restaurant.
I heard that a foreign crab can sell more than 1,000 yuan.
I was joking with him.
This is not crab.
This is for food.
Why doesn't he follow the provincial city?
What does he do in his hometown?
He's tired of working in the provincial city.
Our police station is busy.
There are many cars.
Xiang has been thinking about it.
He said he would come back to marry his girlfriend after two years.
He will also open a farm.
There are seafood here.
Why do we eat foreign food?
He should be back.
He usually goes there for two or three days.
If Xiang sent Sheng Xiaozhou,
I'm afraid they have already found Xiang.
How do they know Xiang?
You forgot.
There was a surveillance camera at the gate of the farm.
Xiang's car is easy to recognize.
Xiang was threatened by them.
We have to find him.
You're back.
Captain Lian.
I have a new discovery.
I have read Xiang's USB drive several times.
Most of them are academic papers.
The title and content are clearly marked.
But these two files are different.
I just copied them out.
These two papers
mainly talk about the soil pollution of a chemical plant.
The title is not clear.
And the content has been deleted.
Someone deliberately deleted the name of the chemical plant
and the name of the environmental assessment agency.
I have to find out the name of the chemical plant.
I have to find out the name of the chemical plant
and the name of the environmental assessment agency.
But I found that
Look.
Isn't this very familiar?
Local?
Yes.
This chemical plant
is no longer a chemical plant.
It has been used as a commercial housing.
It's now...
Jinghai No. 1?
Yes. And I also found that
the environmental assessment agency for Jinghai No. 1
is Lv Cheng Environmental Protection Technology Company.
Lv Cheng?
The conclusion of these two reports is
that the soil pollution of the chemical plant
has been repaired and is no longer harmful.
But I always feel something wrong.
I don't understand.
What does this mean?
I don't understand either.
I just feel very suspicious.
The environmental assessment agency for Jinghai No. 1
is Lv Cheng Environmental Protection Technology Company.
Lv Cheng Environmental Protection Technology Company
is a company that has been working on the development of
the chemical plant for more than a decade.
It is a company that has been working on the development of