GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
Any casualties?
We lost three soldiers and four members
of the disease control platoon.
One major was heavily injured.
Most of the Joseon test subjects are dead.
How beautiful was it?
How did it move?
Just how fast was it?
Tell me.
Tell me how perfect it was.
6 HOURS EARLIER
Excuse me, Major.
I haven't seen the floating spores
in a while now.
Help!
Somebody help me!
Lights!
Quickly! Now!
Aim!
Do you see anything?
No, sir. I can't make anything out!
Help me.
Please, somebody help.
Help me!
I don't want to die.
Please… Please help me.
Shut the door.
Shut the door. Now!
Don't stop!
Shut it now.
I said, shut the door.
Hurry up!
Help me, please!
Please! Help me, sir!
Shut the door. Do it now.
I don't want to die. Please help me!
Help me, Major Endo!
- Let go.
- No!
No, I won't!
- The door won't close!
- No!
It won't close because of you!
Let go!
Major Endo!
Asshole!
Answer me.
Was our experiment
a success?
Please…
destroy it.
What you have created…
is a calamity.
Before it's too late,
please destroy
that creature.
A calamity, you say?
I see.
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN OBSESSION AND PERSEVERANCE
EPISODE 3
SIGNAL
The tea is very fragrant.
All thanks to you, Mr. Jang.
My tea ceremonies have become
twice as enjoyable
thanks to the elegant cups
you procured for me.
Your pronunciation of the Joseon tongue
has become much more natural.
Also thanks to you and the great teacher
you introduced me to.
Oh, I heard that Ongseong Hospital
has shut down.
Have you heard anything?
Well,
I did hear in passing
that an unknown infection
has spread in there.
The thing is, I've since lost contact
with a friend who was admitted there.
If you know anyone inside,
I was hoping you could ask them
about what it's like inside
and when it might open again.
Is this because of the girl
named Myeong-ja?
If so, it would be best
not to look for her.
There is a Joseon saying that goes,
"A drowning man will grasp at straws."
It means that a desperate man will cling
to anything, no matter how trivial.
I'm that drowning man, Lady Maeda.
You're more than capable of brushing off
my husband's threats, aren't you?
If they were mere threats,
I would've done so.
But I think he's serious this time.
So?
I intend to take this seriously too,
so I can survive.
You can't enter
Ongseong Hospital right now,
but even if you do,
you won't find what you're looking for.
So, you should look for another way,
Mr. Jang.
I'm advising you as a friend.
I need the blueprints for the hospital.
You have pull
with the Governor-General's Office.
Please bring me the most detailed prints.
What's the point of getting the blueprints
if we have no way in?
The hospital is shut down.
All outsiders and even the suppliers
have been denied entry.
There is no way of slipping in.
Bring them to me before the day is over.
They say it's an infection.
God knows what disease it might be.
We might all kick the bucket.
I'll go in alone, then. Okay?
What if it's a lie?
What if that sleuth girl lied
to save herself?
It's possible, isn't it?
The hospital's closed. There's no way out.
And the infection is spreading.
She could be lying about finding Myeong-ja
to save her own skin!
- Do you really think so?
- Think about it.
How can she be in a hospital reserved
for high-ranking Japanese officials?
There's no way she's there!
I'll bet my entire fortune of 380 won.
How can you be so consistently unlucky?
What?
Every card you draw is crap.
Every bet you make ends in a loss.
Every time you gamble,
you get your pockets totally cleaned out.
Hey, when has that ever happened to me?
Myeong-ja is definitely in there.
I just had it confirmed by Lady Maeda.
Ishikawa's wife?
Did that woman tell you
that Myeong-ja is in there?
Did she?
That broad said that? For real?
I'll be getting inside Ongseong Hospital
by 10:00 p.m. tonight.
Please prepare accordingly.
WE FOUND MYEONG-JA
Send a signal by 10:00 p.m.
to the east wing of Ongseong Hospital.
Any recognizable signal will do,
such as smoke or a flame.
You won't find what you're looking for.
Please find a way
to get them out.
You should look for another way,
Mr. Jang.
So, what has Jang Tae-sang been up to?
Well, he's been busy all morning
moving about the town.
But…
But what?
His route has been a bit strange.
Mahjong?
I win!
Yes, sir.
He played mahjong for an hour
at the general store of Wang the Chinese.
FIREWORKS
The next round is double.
Will you accept?
Sure!
And then?
He rode a rickshaw around the streets
of Bonjeong for 30 minutes.
- He just rode around the streets?
- Yes, sir.
Then lastly, he visited…
A tailor shop?
Yes, sir. He seemed to be getting
a new suit tailored.
I'd like a suit in the bold style
that's popular these days.
Yes, sir.
This American-made pure wool
just came in from Tokyo last month.
I think you'd prefer
the second option of fabric far more, sir.
It was sent over from the Moonlight Bar
just last night.
I'm here for afternoon cleaning.
Go in.
Yes, sir.
CLEANING SUPPLIES
Have you delivered the note?
I passed it on to someone we can trust.
By now, it should be
at the House of Golden Treasure.
By the way,
are you certain that Myeong-ja is in here?
It seems so.
Actually, last night…
Don't shoot him.
He's on our side.
- What?
- But that's a Japanese soldier.
No, I'm not!
I'm from Joseon.
I really am from Joseon.
Now, let's take a look here.
It's in good condition.
But it's rather old.
It was my family's source of income
for the past ten years.
I sent my eldest
to medical school with it.
The most I can give you is 90 won.
Will you still pawn it?
I don't need the money.
Instead,
could you please find my son?
I heard he was evacuated from Bongrim
after getting wounded in the battle.
But I've lost contact with him.
I was drafted while attending
Gyeongseong Medical School.
In Bongrim, China,
I got injured during battle
and was sent here, Ongseong Hospital.
After recovery, I was assigned
to the disease control platoon.
Disease control?
It seems that this hospital also has
a human experiment lab underground.
I saw countless Joseon people
lose their lives…
with my own eyes last night.
What happened last night…
was due to anthrax.
I witnessed something like this
in Bongrim.
An entire village
was stamped out by anthrax.
It was so horrific
that I still remember it to this day.
Those damn bastards!
Did you happen to see a young man
in his early 20s among the dead?
He is medium-height and has a black spot
next to his right ear.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't examine all the bodies.
Many Joseon people are still being kept
in the underground prison.
That's where I saw Myeong-ja as well.
Don't move
until we finish sterilizing the area.
It's dangerous,
so please stay where you are.
You could die
just by touching the anthrax.
So don't move and stay in that corner
until everything is sterilized.
All right?
You have to help me.
Please find Commissioner Ishikawa
at the Police Bureau.
Tell him I'm here.
Myeong-ja of Spring Moon Hall…
No, tell him Akiko is imprisoned here.
I'm sure he will reward you handsomely.
Please.
Please tell Ishikawa.
Tell him that I'm here, will you?
Shut it!
Keep quiet. Stay back!
But there was nothing I could do for her.
Because I was in the same boat as them.
What are you doing?
Get it together, Josenjing!
Don't spill your filthy vomit!
You Josenjing!
Filthy Josenjing!
There was only one way to escape
this living hell.
Mother.
Please forgive me!
Don't waste your life.
The time will come when your death counts.
You can die then.
Who is she?
Well,
I don't know
who the woman in the drawing is.
But I do know who drew this.
He's Japanese.
He calls himself a painter.
His name was
Sachimoto, I believe.
What are all these?
What have you drawn?
Tell me more.
Who does he work for? Where does he live?
Do you like Chinese food?
At 8:00 p.m. tonight. Sahaeru restaurant.
I'm afraid I have no luxury
to enjoy Chinese food at the moment.
I'm talking about Sachimoto, not you.
We arranged to meet at Sahaeru tonight.
- Tonight?
- At 8:00 p.m.
Don't be late.
You must be running
an interesting experiment.
I heard you lost
an entire disease control platoon,
along with stacks of Joseon test subjects.
I only wish that your experiment
will have strategic value for us.
What do you mean?
Tokyo has been burned to ashes
from the recent air strikes.
We are in dire need
of a powerful weapon that could
turn the tides of the war in our favor.
How about we make use
of that creature down below?
It's too early to reach any conclusion.
Its intelligence, its cognitive abilities,
and whether it could be tamed or not
haven't been confirmed yet.
Every living thing in this world
can eventually be tamed,
just as we have tamed Joseon.
I've only gone down
to the second basement.
This is the underground prison.
And Myeong-ja…
PRISON
…was here.
How many guards?
A pair of guards are stationed
every ten meters.
They are all armed.
Getting her out is going to be
as difficult as getting in.
But…
if you get her out,
is there a way to escape the hospital?
Let's wait in our positions
until we get a signal from outside.
You should head back to your platoon.
No, I'll never return to that place again.
If they search the ward looking for you,
it will cause us more trouble.
They might even find out about these two.
Then the entire operation would be over.
We should all be able to escape.
I'm sure of it.
I'll see you later, then.
Please…
don't forget about me.
Do you recognize it?
- The layout of this floor.
- Yes.
It's like the underground laboratory
back in Manchuria.
LABORATORY
It's worth trying, don't you think?
You remember what happened in Manchuria.
What went on
in that underground laboratory.
What horrors the people went through.
- Chae-ok.
- If the same thing is happening here…
shouldn't we try
to do something this time?
Let's wait at least
until the signal arrives.
It's already been 30 minutes.
Who are you waiting for anyway?
A woman.
A wooman?
Not "wooman." A woman.
There she is!
Good work. Get yourself something to eat.
Oh, excuse…
Look who it is.
Jang Ttai-sang of Golden Treasure.
Could you let me through?
I have urgent business to attend to.
Welcome. This way, please.
I think we have
some unfinished business to settle first.
Okay. I get it.
If that's what you want,
come to my shop tomorrow morning.
Sound good?
- Sir…
- Yeah.
You must be hungry.
Here, it's Joseon hotteok.
Try it.
Yes, sir.
So good!
These Josenjing folks
really know their way around food, huh?
Sir…
Do you think he'll be okay?
Mori.
Our job is to observe, not intervene.
We observe, report,
and receive orders.
That's all there is to it.
- Yes, sir.
- Go on, try a bite.
Hang on. Wait.
Just a second.
We can resolve this with money.
No need to bring swords
into this fight, right?
Settle down, guys.
How much money do you want?
Golden Treasure.
Golden Treasure!
What about it?
Give us the House of Golden Treasure.
Then I'll spare your life.
Let's not kid around.
I told you, I'm quite busy right now.
I'm supposed to meet someone at 8:00 p.m.
A very important person!
Would you look at the time?
Look, it's almost time!
I'll be off.
Hey, you should think carefully
about who means more to you.
Many apologies,
but you're just not my type.
Please don't force me
to think so dearly of you!
- Hey, Jang Ttai-sang.
- Tae-sang!
It's Tae-sang, not Ttai-sang!
Say my name again.
Do you wish to die?
Of course not.
I might be a luckless guy,
but I never wish to get killed
by a bunch of scum.
Jackass!
You there!
What's going on?
Look here.
I'm Jang Tae-sang
of the House of Golden Treasure.
These thugs are attacking me
for no apparent reason.
Help me, Officer.
We're just teaching
this stubborn Josenjing a lesson.
You can just go on your way, sir.
Look, they are all brandishing swords!
My life is in danger!
I don't want you causing a scene,
so go easy on him.
Yes, sir.
Officer.
Officer!
See that?
This is the Joseon you're living in.
And you're nothing but trash
with a lot of money.
Filthy and pathetic
Josenjing
trash.
Boss!
You're right.
This is the Joseon I'm living in.
So give it a rest.
I'm already pissed off as it is.
Look!
Josenjings never die!
He's one tough nut.
This won't do, Father.
If we wait here any longer,
we will be wasting the whole night.
I'll go out and look around the ward.
If this place has the same layout,
there should be a vent
that leads into the underground lab.
- And the vent would be…
- Connected to the rooftop.
Chae-ok.
Should things get out of hand,
you must return without hesitation.
Do you understand?
I'll be back.
Hurry! Get a move on!
The blueprints?
I got them as I was told to.
But is this the right thing to do?
We are basically pushing him
right into his grave.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Master Jang calls the shots.
Is Tae-sang upstairs?
No, he's out. What's the matter?
An urgent matter has come up.
Where is he right now?
I'm not sure.
- Tae-sang!
- Sir!
Master Jang!
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll go after him.
Sure.
You're getting into sword fights now?
For heaven's sake!
What kind of rotten pricks
would be foolish enough to mess with you?
Wait here.
I'm going to report this to the police.
We'll go to the hospital first.
Get the car ready.
Right, the hospital. Okay.
Did you get the blueprints
for Ongseong Hospital?
Of course I did!
They are downstairs…
Forget about the blueprints.
Let's wrap the wound up
and go to the hospital.
Yeah, the hospital first.
I'm fine. Show me the blueprints, Mr. Gu.
Disinfectants and antibiotics
aren't going to heal this wound.
We don't have much time left
until 10:00 p.m.
Sir.
The blueprints now, Mr. Gu!
Tae-sang, please!
What could possibly be more important
than your own life?
Is Myeong-ja worth
getting stabbed over like this?
Is she really?
- Mrs. Nawol.
- I don't want to hear it.
Shut your mouth and go to the hospital.
Is that clear?
Right.
You're right, Mrs. Nawol.
Myeong-ja means nothing to me.
But…
those bastards are using her
as a ridiculous excuse to take my stuff.
They're claiming what's mine as theirs
without a speck of shame!
They even took our country.
They can take anything.
I suppose so.
But…
I'm going to hold out to the end.
They can beat me up and knock me around,
but I'll fight like hell for what's mine!
If I run away because they threaten me
and let them take what is mine,
they will never get to learn
a proper lesson.
Am I wrong?
You…
You were stabbed.
You're seriously wounded, okay?
This kind of wound doesn't hurt me.
What hurts me is not a sword.
It's my broken pride.
You're Yeong-chun.
I apologize for visiting at this hour,
but there is someone
who wishes to see Master Jang.
Wang. Open the door!
It's Gu from Golden Treasure!
Wang!
LABORATORY
Mr. Sachimoto.
I've been out to buy some new supplies.
There are a lot of items.
Could you let us pass?
I'll send him out
as soon as I unload them.
I can't allow that.
No outsiders are allowed
to enter the hospital.
Then go ahead
and report directly to Director Ichiro.
Pardon?
The director ordered me to bring these in,
so there's no choice.
You better tell the director yourself
that you can't allow us in.
Are you here to save us?
What?
I saw you coming down from the vent.
Please save us.
Help us get out of here, please!
Hurry up!
Damn it!
Come on out.
Oh gosh.
I nearly suffocated in there.
This way.
CLOSED
What's going on?
Are you sure this is the meeting place?
This is the only cleaning supplies room
on the first floor I know of.
The signal…
I think our timing was off
because the signal was delayed.
The night breeze of Joseon
is so refreshing.
Let's drink here.
Yes, sir.
I found whiskey in the storage room.
So I snuck it out.
Hey. Be quiet.
Don't shoot.
Who are you?
- Fireworks.
- What is that?
Chae-ok!
Forgive me.
I'm late.
What a sight.
They succeeded.
I'm not so sure.
I hope they did.
No, I'm not sure what's going on.
Yes, of course.
Fireworks are banned in Gyeongseong.
Yes, sir! I'll find the culprits
and report them to you immediately.
Yes, sir!
I'm heading over to the bureau. Get ready.
Yes, sir.
How beautiful.
Have you found Myeong-ja?
Where is she? Did you get her out?
You can come out now.
Careful.
There we go.
Wait.
Where's Myeong-ja?
Get these kids out of here first.
What are you talking about?
Who are these kids?
If you take the kids out of here,
I'll go and find Myeong-ja.
You have something to show me?
Yes.
Move.
Get in there now!
What is this place?
I'm going to make that creature
recognize me.
Every time I ring the bell,
it will remember
and know that I'm feeding it.
It will know who its master is
and whom it must obey.
That's how I'll tame it.