THE UNCANNY COUNTER 2
Hey, Mun.
-Mun.
-He'll wake up.
Mr. Ma?
Yes?
Who are you?
Thank you. I'm truly grateful.
Grateful for what?
You saved my grandmother.
You're my savior and hero.
I see.
You must be So Mun.
She told me a lot about you.
But I was just doing my job.
No. I promise to repay you.
I will protect you no matter what.
That's my job. Your job is to study hard.
-Thank you.
-Hold on.
Hold on. I need to get ready.
This is where we part ways.
Lee Chung-jae got caught.
I just need to kill him.
I just need to get my revenge.
Nothing else.
You're right.
Your revenge is all that matters to you.
You were always the same.
The one who has changed completely…
is me.
Now that Mun has lost his power,
my desires have changed.
What are you doing?
Come to think of it,
their powers were nothing
compared to yours.
You can read and erase memories.
You can see the territory
and interact with it.
But even with those powers,
you can't use them to their full extent.
You and I will be one.
Then, I will truly become invincible.
How did it go with Mun?
Mun.
What's going on?
Did he wake up?
All the more reason
to absorb your power.
You can absorb the territory's power
like them.
Ma Ju-seok.
What are you?
One thing is certain. I'm not like you.
You're different from me?
Is getting revenge
the only desire you have?
Is that it?
Can you even do it?
Mun is back.
In any case, without my help,
you'll never get your revenge.
No.
I don't need your help anymore.
Why?
Why you?
Why did you have to be
the one to get that power?
Why?
Why not me?
Why you?
What was that immense power just now?
I was able to move under my own free will.
It was only for a brief moment,
but I could control Ma Ju-seok's body.
-Wi-gen!
-Wi-gen! Seriously!
We missed you, Wi-gen.
How are you feeling?
You must've gone through a lot
while I was gone.
You must've been so shocked.
What happened?
Did Mun sign the Counter contract again?
No.
He didn't need to do that.
He didn't need to do it?
Are you saying he came back
without even signing the contract?
Mun.
Your hair…
You didn't sign the contract.
Our relationship goes far beyond
a simple contract.
He's a child
who can do uncanny things with ease.
Gosh, I didn't have time
to make my own kimchi.
I hope this is good.
EPISODE 10
-There you go. Eat up.
-Have some kimchi too.
My goodness, look how he eats.
Mo-tak, serve him another bowl of soup.
Sure thing.
-I want more meat.
-All right.
Koreans need kimchi
to stay strong, you know?
Eat up and take your time.
You must've been famished.
It's so crunchy.
What is this? Did you make it?
What?
That's the chef's secret.
Have some water too.
No, drink warm water instead.
It'll help you digest.
Mun, try this.
Thank you for protecting me.
Don't be absurd!
I will never again
abandon my family and run away.
Thank you for being patient
and believing in me.
We're not helpless without you.
If we had more time, we would've summoned
Hwang Pil-gwang and Ma Ju-seok.
Of course. Hey, Mun.
You should've been there.
I flew in the air and landed a punch--
It was all thanks to me,
because I showed up
with my huge submachine gun.
And Hwang Pil-gwang ran!
I even cleaned up the mess afterward.
That hotel probably looks
like a seven-star hotel by now.
Hey, let me take some credit too.
You have to know that I played
a big role in capturing Gelly.
I already know.
You told me many times already.
You could hear us?
I told you to take turns to care for him.
Were you boasting all that time?
I just thought I'd entertain him
while he was asleep.
Me too. I thought he'd be bored.
Me too.
So…
Well…
What happened to Ma Ju-seok?
Mun, you just woke up.
Let's take it slowly, okay?
No, I'm okay.
Do you think Ma Ju-seok
and Hwang Pil-gwang have teamed up?
No.
He will never side with Hwang Pil-gwang.
When Mun woke up,
the territory opened up wide.
It covered the entire city.
Did you see anyone?
Hwang Pil-gwang? Ma Ju-seok?
The area was so large
that I couldn't locate them.
But Hwang Pil-gwang was trying
to stab Ma Ju-seok with a piece of glass.
Don't tell me
he's planning to kill Ma Ju-seok
and consume his power?
Maybe.
He probably thought
he couldn't absorb Mun's power.
Then, what we were fearing the most
could actually happen.
The evil spirits could become one.
It'd be our first time facing
a fully-formed evil spirit.
It's a risky situation,
but it's also an opportunity.
We can summon Ma Ju-seok while he's alone.
We may not know Pil-gwang's plan,
but we know where Ma Ju-seok is headed.
Lee Chung-jae.
What's going on?
Does Ma Ju-seok really know
about our hideout or not?
Ma Ju-seok knows where we are? How?
There's one more thing you should know.
What is it?
I think Ma Ju-seok met your grandmother
while you were unconscious.
Why would he?
She's been like this since yesterday.
She tells me to go away
whenever I come near.
She keeps clamoring for me
to call her darling.
By the way, how was the contest?
You must be exhausted from the trip.
You should rest.
I'm okay, Grandpa.
Grandma.
Darling.
Oh. Darn it.
What are you doing up here?
Darling. Call my darling.
Get up.
Why are you out in the cold?
Don't do this. He's gone!
Darling!
Play with me.
Let's play.
You said Mun-yeong told you
to play with me.
You said she told you that.
Mun-yeong is gone, ma'am.
What?
I was lying.
Min-ji is gone too.
Treasure is gone as well.
Everyone is gone.
That's not true.
Mun-yeong is here. She's there.
She's over there.
Then can you ask her a question?
Can you ask her
if Min-ji is doing well up there?
Jeez!
My darling isn't gone.
He said he'd come.
He promised to come back
if I stayed healthy and ate well.
Ma Ju-seok.
Punish Lee Chung-jae!
Punish him!
Don't try to solve it with compensations
and investigate all his crimes!
Investigate all his crimes!
Punish Lee Chung-jae!
Punish him!
Don't try to solve it with compensations
and investigate all his crimes!
Investigate all his crimes!
Punish Lee Chung-jae!
Is everything ready?
Yes, the Regional Investigation Unit
is here to back us up.
But…
will Ma Ju-seok really show up?
He hasn't made a move yet.
He would never miss a chance
to get his revenge.
So let's stay alert.
Yes, sir.
I hope nothing bad happens.
Investigate all his crimes!
Punish Lee Chung-jae!
Punish him!
JANGMUL NURSING HOME
With Lee Chung-jae's arrest,
it appears inevitable that the police
will reopen the housing fraud case
against Baekdu Planning & Construction.
It's been revealed that some politicians
are also involved.
The authorities are now on alert
and will investigate the source
of the retrieved 120 billion won.
They will also discuss…
Min-ji.
…how to help the victims…
Ju-seok.
-Do you accept the charges against you?
-Anything to say to the victims?
Do you feel no guilt?
Damn it.
You devil!
That crazy…
Damn it. Let me go.
Are you sure my safety is guaranteed?
Do your job!
I heard you haven't caught Ma Ju-seok yet.
Are you sure I can be seen in public?
You scared?
You better keep me safe.
Do you really think
I was the mastermind behind this fraud?
I was a thug
who never went to high school.
I'm just a pawn.
The mastermind is someone else.
Are you finally ready
to talk about Mr. Hwang?
Keep me safe
if you want to get what you want.
Who knows?
The mastermind could be scheming
something else as we speak.
Let's go.
DEATH PENALTY FOR LEE CHUNG-JAE
YOUR DEATH CAN'T MAKE UP
FOR ALL THE VICTIMS' DEATHS
Worthless scum!
You bastard!
Lee Chung-jae deserves the death penalty!
You deserve to die, you devil!
Give me back my money!
ATONE FOR YOUR SINS
Nothing?
My nose is telling me
that everything is fine so far.
All right. I hope your nose works.
JUNGJIN PENITENTIARY
Mun, how's everything there?
It's quiet so far, Ha-na.
JUNGJIN PENITENTIARY
I can smell it.
I'm sure of it. I smell Ma Ju-seok.
What? Ma Ju-seok?
Where are you?
What?
What's going on?
What's wrong?
It can't be.
Mo-tak, what's going on?
Mo-tak.
Something's wrong with the vehicle!
-Move.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, what's going on?
Damn it.
Ma Ju-seok.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
Oh, no!
Ma Ju-seok.
Mo-tak.
Is everyone okay?
Stop or I'll shoot!
Ma Ju-seok took the bus.
What?
-The tires…
-Mun!
-Mo-tak!
Mr. Ma.
Where are you taking me?
This is a crime.
You're committing a crime!
Mr. Ma, I'm begging you.
Just let me go.
Mr. Ma!
LATE LEE MIN-JI
Min-ji.
They caught those scammers.
It all seems meaningless now.
But I hope you can let go
of your resentment now
and feel better.
Ju-seok.
What should I do with him?
He listened to you more than anyone else.
Who will stop him
now that you're gone?
Damn it.
Get out.
I don't want to hurt you.
Hey! Don't leave! Where are you going?
Come back, you bastard!
Yes. Feel free to take your revenge now.
Once you kill him, I'll become…
Damn it!
Don't come near me!
Back off, you devil!
That's right.
You turned me into a devil.
I became one to kill you.
That's why
both of us must die.
What? What are you talking about?
What's that sound?
What are you doing?
Damn it! What the hell are you doing?
Over there.
Turn left here.
MEMORIAL PARK
Wait, this is the way to…
The memorial park?
He's near Ms. Lee's columbarium.
He's taking Lee Chung-jae there.
Damn it!
You're gonna kill me, you lunatic!
What is this?
This is the place.
This is where Min-ji lies.
What?
You can make it up to her by dying.
And I will also pay
for my sins with my death.
Ma Ju-seok! What are you doing?
No.
Mr. Ma, I'm begging you.
Don't kill me!
If you let me live, I'll repent
and beg for forgiveness…
You bastard! Don't do this!
I don't know what's going on.
The bus moved on its own.
I'm telling you it's the truth!
Yes.
Lee and Ma Ju-seok
are the only ones inside.
I don't know what he's up to.
-Ju-seok?
-I think the bus is going to explode.
Are you trying to kill us?
Ju-seok!
It's dangerous!
You need to get out of there!
Ju-seok!
Get out of there.
You need to get out of there!
Mother, it's dangerous.
Ju-seok!
Don't come near me!
Stay away!
No, Ju-seok.
Control your anger. Let's try.
It's all over now.
Move aside, Mother.
Please, Ju-seok.
I can't lose you again.
No.
If you still want to go, kill me first.
What's the point of living like this?
How could I go on living?
Why did I…
What's wrong with me?
What's wrong?
Are you confused that you can't control
your own body?
I'll show you
that this body
doesn't belong to you anymore.
No!
Lee Chung-jae!
-Come here.
-Lee Chung-jae!
-Go away!
-Jeok-bong! Where is he?
Over there!
Aren't you tired of running?
-Don't be such a baby.
-It really hurts.
Where's Ma Ju-seok?
Over there.
No.
Kill her!
You were annoyed by the old hag too.
She's just another obstacle
in the way of your revenge!
No.
No. Mom.
No!
That crazy bastard,
How could he hurt his mother?
Ms. Chu! Ma Ju-seok's mother is hurt!
Hurry up!
Yes, this is it.
My body feels so much lighter.
Don't tell me
you can absorb the territory's--
Die!
Something…
Something's wrong.
Mr. Ma.
Mr. Ma!
Mun!
-Mr. Ma!
-Mun!
Mr. Ma!
Hey! What happened?
Snap out of it! What's going on?
Something's wrong.
The evil spirit absorbed
the territory's power.
What?
Didn't you say only a complete evil spirit
could absorb the territory's power?
That's why we had to stop Hwang Pil-gwang
and Ma Ju-seok from joining forces.
The fact he could read the territory
was already inexplainable.
He had that power.
What does this mean?
Does it mean Ma Ju-seok gets stronger
whenever Mun summons the territory?
Yes.
The territory no longer belongs
to just the Counters.
Summoning the territory recklessly
could make the evil spirit stronger.
A bigger problem is
as it absorbs the territory's power,
the evil spirit within Ma Ju-seok
takes more control over him.
He didn't hesitate
to harm innocent people.
Even his mother, of all people.
Will Ma Ju-seok
eventually be consumed by the evil spirit?
Something…
Something's wrong.
Mr. Ma.
He wanted to stop.
It's true that the evil spirit
had a tighter grip on him,
but he did want to stop.
He knew something was wrong
and hurt himself to stop it.
He regretted what he did.
That means we still have a chance.
It means he still has the will to resist.
Right?
Mun, you shouldn't have let him go
like that today.
He shouldn't have gotten away.
Before he goes completely out of control,
we should've caught him today.
What do you mean?
Did you deliberately let him go?
He wasn't an evil spirit
in that moment.
No. He has always been…
an evil spirit.
Exhausted already? Come on.
Try harder.
Try to fight back harder.
Get out
of my body.
That's impossible now.
Your rage summoned me.
And I made your rage erupt.
As much as your rage has grown,
so has my power.
I told you.
Without my permission now,
you can't even die, Ma Ju-seok.
This isn't it.
This isn't what I wanted.
Then what?
Did you think everything would end
with your sweet revenge?
Don't be too upset though.
I will get you your revenge
no matter what.
Against Lee Chung-jae, Mun, and also…
your lonely mother.
I will kill them all!
Okay.
So, did Mo-tak go straight
to the police station?
Yes.
I see.
Will Ma Ju-seok's mother be okay?
I hope the memories I erased today
won't haunt her in her dreams.
Of course not. You took good care of her.
She left without a single wound.
Mun is going to look after her tonight.
I'm worried about him too.
So much has happened
right after he woke up.
My God. I know.
But I agree with Mo-tak.
The evil spirits keep getting stronger.
We can't be soft on them.
Can't we just try fighting him
without the territory?
We did a great job last time at the hotel.
And this time, Mun will join us.
And the evil spirits are split.
You're right.
He wouldn't just sit still like this.
What?
If Mr. Hwang failed to kill Ma Ju-seok
just because of the territory,
he wouldn't give up on taking his power.
He'd try to get it one way or another.
So why hasn't he made a move yet?
You're right.
JANGMUL NURSING HOME
Are you awake?
I didn't know you were here.
When did I fall asleep?
I went to see Min-ji today.
You did?
Yes.
Now that the scammers have been caught,
she can now be at peace in heaven.
I needed to tell her that.
You did well.
I was hoping that Ju-seok…
would return.
But he won't, right?
Even though the scammers
have all been caught,
he still has no desire
to come back, right?
I had a dream.
In the dream,
Ju-seok was a little boy.
And he was sitting alone on top of a hill.
When Ju-seok
first came to the orphanage,
for the first few months,
all he ever did was sit on this hill
that overlooked the fences.
He said his mother would return,
and he said he was waiting for her.
It was Min-ji who helped him
come down from that hill.
Ju-seok…
is waiting for her now.
Who will help him now that she's gone?
I asked you to protect me.
How can you call yourselves the police?
You call that protecting and serving?
We're not here to protect and serve you.
I should've let that bastard kill me
so you'd all get fired.
Is this why you wanted to see me?
Just to talk nonsense?
If you can't catch Ma Ju-seok,
at least catch Mr. Hwang.
Ma Ju-seok needs to know
that Mr. Hwang is the person
he should go after, not me.
You're leaving? Fine.
Then I'm going to go public
with the evidence that I have.
Evidence?
About the housing fraud
and Mr. Hwang being the mastermind.
I might die because of your incompetence.
So I should at least reveal the truth.
Is this all a joke?
You took the fall for him two years ago.
And now, you're blaming Mr. Hwang
for everything?
What are you talking about?
It was his scheme to begin with.
I was just his pawn!
Do you want me to sit still
and wait for Ma Ju-seok to kill me?
He escaped from jail,
so what makes you think he can't break in?
Do you really have any evidence?
Are you intrigued now?
Promise you'll get me out
and put me in witness protection.
Promise me you'll hide me
where he can't find me.
Where is the evidence?
2 YEARS AGO
It's 120 billion won.
You're going to take it all
behind my back?
You're quite ambitious for a pawn.
Did you think I'd be your pawn forever?
You're finished, you bastard.
You're out of this game.
At the end of this game…
you're the one who dies.
What a heinous devil.
Now that we have proof,
we can put him behind bars.
With this proof, he'll rot in jail.
But once people find out about this video,
they will also know
that Hwang Pil-gwang was behind the fraud.
Then Ma Ju-seok will go after him.
He will make Hwang Pil-gwang pay
for deceiving him.
This is a huge problem.
Ma Ju-seok is a ticking bomb right now.
But we can't hide this forever.
We must summon him
before the video goes public.
We need someone
who can bring him down from the hill.
What if we just try…
to persuade him?
Persuade him?
I was able to wake up from my coma
because you were all waiting for me
and supporting me.
I wouldn't be here right now
if it wasn't for you all.
Mun.
What's gotten into you this time?
Maybe Ma Ju-seok is the one
who's desperate to put an end to this.
If we can persuade him
while he still has a will of his own--
Mun.
Do you think the evil spirit is like you?
Plus, how will we persuade him?
There's no way to find him now,
except to just wait
for him to go after Lee Chung-jae.
The territory.
Why don't we use the territory?
The territory?
He can read it.
Mun can summon it and talk to him.
If he can accept the fact that summoning
the evil spirit is his only way out…
Yes.
We'll be able to summon him
without getting anyone else hurt.
Plus, we are out of time and options.
The human part
of him is being swayed right now.
This could be our last chance
to persuade him.
Hey, Doctor.
Did the detective call you?
We don't receive any calls.
It could be urgent.
You should be more flexible.
Hey!
Ask the guard if I got any calls.
Go back to your cell if you feel better.
Damn it.
He should give me a call
if he saw the evidence.
Why is he not calling?
This won't do.
Hey, Doctor, let me make one phone call--
Mr. Hwang!
What's happening?
I doubt you've been locked up.
Did you just walked through the wall?
Damn it. Are you guys ghosts or what?
Mr. Hwang.
I was never going to rat you out.
So…
Let me explain what happened.
No. You did well, Chung-jae.
You can't hide it forever.
The truth should always come out.
What?
I'm just thankful that you're still alive
in this important moment.
JANGMUL NURSING HOME
Mr. Ma.
Can you hear me?
Fortunately,
your mother is okay.
Ms. Chu took good care of her.
And she erased all the bad memories.
If we had got there just an instant later,
she wouldn't have made it though.
No.
No, Mom.
However,
it's okay.
I know…
that this isn't what you wanted.
I know that you wanted to stop.
And I also know…
that it's not too late.
No.
It is too late.
I can't go back now.
Come down from that hill, Mr. Ma.
I'll make everything right.
So…
you should…
return to your old self
when you see Ms. Lee again.
I hope our baby takes after you.
I hope our baby
has your cute face and kind heart.
Thank you so much
for always protecting me.
Min-ji.
Will I be able
to see you again?
Let's not give up.
I won't give up on you either.
Come back, Mr. Ma.
Mun.
I need to meet him.
No. Don't do this, Ma Ju-seok!
Put your hands up!
Don't move.
I just want to talk. Okay?
About that guy.
About how Lee Chung-jae died.
And the truth
about the Baekdu housing fraud.
Things like that.
Hold on.
So…
Do you think Ma Ju-seok will come?
He will.
I know he will.
He'll come.
We were confident
that Mun would wake up too.
Let's believe that he'll come.
He was someone we trusted.
He should be here by now
if he was really persuaded.
Hey, Han-ul.
-What?
-What is it?
Okay, I'm on my way.
Damn it. Lee Chung-jae has disappeared.
Was it Ma Ju-seok? Did he do something?
What is this? Damn it.
Hwang Pil-gwang.
Stay here in case Ma Ju-seok comes.
-The rest of you, let's go find Hwang.
-Okay.
-Mo-tak.
-An unidentified man
has barged into a broadcasting station.
We found Hwang Pil-gwang.
This unidentified man claims
he wants to reveal the truth
-about the Baekdu housing fraud.
-Hwang Pil-gwang.
-What's she saying?
-He voluntarily came to the press.
Let's hear our reporter.
Where should I begin?
MAN TO REVEAL THE TRUTH
ABOUT BAEKDU HOUSING FRAUD
I doubt you're interested
in the deaths of nameless individuals.
Then how about me killing Lee Chung-jae?
Or,
should I talk about how I'm the mastermind
of the Baekdu housing fraud?
If not, then how about…
how I killed…
Ma Ju-seok's wife.
MAN CONFESSES TO MURDERS
That bastard.
It was in here, Ma Ju-seok.
The truth behind your wife's death.
You won't get your revenge
without my help.
Who do you think killed your wife?
Was it Mr. Park who brutally murdered
your pregnant wife?
Sadly, you haven't arrived
at the end of the truth. No.
You're nowhere near it.
Why are you suddenly
confessing to everything?
Because I…
had to find you.
-It's Ma Ju-seok!
-That's him?
Ma Ju-seok.
I'm pregnant, so please don't kill me!
-No!
No!
Congratulations.
You've finally discovered the truth.
Yes. It was me.
I am responsible for the deaths
of your wife and baby.
So all this time, that rage of yours…
should've been directed at me.
Die.
Yes. That's it, Ma Ju-seok.
I will live inside you…
forever.
No.
Does Ma Ju-seok
no longer exist now?
THE UNCANNY COUNTER 2
Ma Ju-seok killed Hwang Pil-gwang
after all.
He should be eliminated on sight.
You want us to kill him?
He will find you through the territory.
-There's a dead body…
-No!
-Han-ul!
-We still have a chance.
We can summon him and save everyone.
That's enough!
I will kill him.
You evil spirit!
Hurry and run!
-Mun!
I'll end this fight.
Thank you for everything.