(My Perfect Stranger)
(Kim Dong Wook)
(Jin Ki Joo)
(My Perfect Stranger)
In retrospect, it was truly an odd night.
The darned weather, the crazy GPS,
and the cell phone.
And that was when it showed up in front of me.
In there, the manual explained how to use the time machine.
The time machine that shows up in novels or movies.
Have I ever even imagined a world without my mom?
When I say, "Mom," no one in this world...
can answer now.
Exactly a year from now, I will die in the year when I turn 35.
That's because the culprit who kills me is the real culprit...
of the serial murder case in Woojung-Ri in 1987.
This was also found at the scene of my murder.
That was the culprit's signature in 1987.
Mom.
We have just arrived in the year, 1987.
And there's no way to go back.
We're stuck here.
(My Perfect Stranger, Episode 2, The Reason We Can't Return)
KSBC Anchor Yoon Hae Jun who had gone missing...
is suspected to have been murdered by the river in Gangwon Province.
The discovery of the murder scene shocked many people.
The pool of blood found at the scene was tested for DNA. And it showed...
it belonged to Anchor Yoon.
The whereabouts of the anchor are still unknown.
People are wondering if this will be a murder case without a body.
("KSBC Anchor Yoon Hae Jun Has Been Missing for a Week")
("Is It a Murder Case Without a Body?")
(Episode 2)
Gosh.
Goodness.
Darn.
Gosh.
At 10:40pm on May 9, 1987,
I had just arrived here,
and my only way out of here...
had completely been destroyed.
Gosh. I can't believe this.
(Celebrating the Hosting of Seoul Olympics)
Come on. What's up with today?
Wait.
Are you okay? Your forehead is also...
Yes. I'm okay.
Oh, my.
How many foreheads am I going to break today?
I ought to take better care of my shoulders now.
(Jidong's Steamed Buns and Dumplings)
(Sun and Moon Record Shop)
Gosh.
I'm sorry. I'll explain everything.
Sorry?
You must already be in a state of shock.
But the situation is worse than you'd expect.
We have just...
arrived in the year, 1987.
And there's no way...
to go back.
We're stuck here.
Are you serious?
Yes. Don't be too scared. I'll do whatever it takes...
Then...
This is real. Goodness.
What...
Excuse me.
You're laughing?
Did you hurt your head severely?
No.
Wait. Are you okay?
Sorry.
Come on.
(Beware of dogs)
So he's telling me this is real?
Mom is alive now?
Welcome.
Hello.
(Moon Night)
Mom.
Hey! One, two, three, four!
- The one on the left. - Yu Ri.
Yu Ri!
Yu Ri. Where's the restroom?
Find it yourself.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(Moon Night)
- Mom. - What?
I'm not dreaming, right?
Please, don't do this.
It's real.
This is really happening.
She's real.
Mom.
It's me, Yoon Young.
Weren't you scared?
How could you leave like that?
How was I supposed to live?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mom.
It was just that I was kind of embarrassed...
that I ignored you in case I looked too shabby.
I didn't want to...
show it to you.
That's why I ignored you.
I'm sorry for what I did, Mom.
I thought...
there would be a lot of time left for us.
I thought you'd wait for me.
You look the same, Mom.
Are you...
Do you recognize me?
- Yes. - He opened his eyes.
Goodness, you're the treasure of our town,
and you could've died before your time.
Mr. Yoon!
Stop! Stop hitting me.
I didn't hit you. Seeing how he's bleeding,
I think we should take him to the hospital.
- Right. - No, it's all right.
I need to look for someone.
Goodness,
- you can't die yet, Mr. Yoon! - Oh gosh, this can't be happening.
How can you die when you saved all our kids?
Remember the super glue incident from last month?
You do, right, Mr. Yoon?
This won't do. Carry him on your back!
Oh, right. Get on my back.
- No, it's fine. - Get on his back.
- I'm still alive! - Hurry.
- Just get on my back! - Get on his back. Get a grip.
- Stop it! - I'm totally fine.
Go on. What were you going to say?
Are you...
Are you high on super glue?
What are you saying?
Are you going to hit me or something?
I just want to go home.
Mom...
Mom, what's wrong with you? Why would I hit you?
Mom.
Mom, it's me, Yoon Young.
Mom, don't cry.
I'm sorry!
Gosh, that hurts...
Oh, my love
When the breeze open the window
Let your moonlight smile shine
My dream of happiness will come true
Oh, my
What was that? Come on.
Stop right there!
- What's wrong with him? - Darn it.
We will start our crackdown on minors.
Those who have your ID on them, take it out.
Those who don't have it...
better turn themselves in.
- Hurry up and get out. - Get out.
- Get out. - Get out.
I'm really fine. I can walk.
No, Mr. Yoon.
- Stay still. - We must go to the hospital.
It's that way.
- Okay. - Hang in there.
Seriously...
There was a blood stain on her forehead too.
And she had a scarf with red dots on her neck.
- She was just like... - Stop!
- Where? - Sorry?
Hello, sir.
Oh, hey.
Where did you see her?
Where did the girl with a red-dotted scarf go?
That way.
Gosh. Goodness.
You can't go in there.
Dong Sik is there, though.
- Dong Sik is here? - Yes.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Take out your IDs in advance and get them ready.
Put your hands up straight.
Excuse me. What's going on?
Can't you see?
They're checking our IDs.
Take yours out already.
Unless you want to end up at the police station with them.
So that's how the IDs look like here.
There are IDs that look different from this?
That means you're a spy.
I think you made the wrong choice of words.
Sorry.
You punks. What are you doing here?
- Mr. Yoon. - Mr. Yoon.
"Mr. Yoon?"
I told you numerous times to get your act together.
How dare you come to a night club when you're high school seniors?
Come out here.
Mr. Yoon...
Please forgive us!
- Seniors? - Forgive us.
- Mr. Yoon. - What are you waiting for?
Come here.
Mr. Yoon!
- She's not in our school. - Yes, you.
Why are you feigning ignorance there?
Mr. Yoon!
What do you think you're doing?
Detective Baek Dong Sik.
Five days from now,
right after 2 murder cases and 1 missing case,
he suddenly quits his job after having worked diligently.
He's someone who will leave this town and go off the grid.
He goes off the grid for 30 years.
What did you say?
What's wrong with a teacher taking his students?
How could you put it that way?
The police are taking offenders,
and you shouldn't get in the way like that.
Don't try to threaten the youngsters by calling them "offenders."
Why don't you do your job and catch the real criminals?
What did you say?
Because you didn't do your job right, things got mixed up.
What you just said...
What do you mean by that?
Goodness, I appreciate your work, Dong Sik.
- Gosh, sir. - Hey.
Goodness, you're a father,
but you can't go home when it's already late.
This won't do.
- I'll give a scolding to Chief Kim. - Look at your clothes.
- You brat. You're out of your mind. - Dad.
- It's nothing like that. - You should go home, at least.
You should go home.
I'll take you.
- Oh, will you? - Yes.
Then shall I get in the police car since it's been a while?
Yes, sure. Let's go.
Hold on.
Come to the principal's office until 8am on Monday.
- Let us go, sir. - Yes, let's go.
Sure.
- Follow me. - Dad.
Dad!
Detective Baek?
Yes, I'm coming, sir!
(Moon Night)
Thank you. Have a safe trip home!
Wait.
Where are you going?
I'm going to take care of the things I couldn't because of someone...
I wasn't supposed to save.
Who are you, by the way?
Are you finally curious about my identity?
It was too hectic back there, so...
Besides, things are...
quite extraordinary right now.
You know that it's extraordinary,
yet, you're poking around here and there?
Are you here for a tour?
Why on earth did you go into a nightclub?
That's...
What about you?
Who on earth are you? How come you look so natural...
in this place at this hour?
You're him, right?
The one who hit me with a car.
It's beyond my understanding why it took someone of sound mind...
that much time to figure that out.
Yes, it is me.
Follow me.
You'll understand it faster if I show you.
So, this is not a normal car. It's a time machine.
And you're a time traveller.
I got hit by this car...
and travelled back to 1987. Is that the story?
- That's amazing. - "Amazing?"
That's what you think, seeing my car like this?
I'm not the one who caused this, am I?
Why didn't I think of that?
Why did I think it was only my problem?
Why did you get hit?
What?
How and why did you end up being hit by my car?
Is there a way to get hit?
I got hit because you hit me as the driver.
No, you don't know how this works.
This car can't bump into things.
It becomes transparent.
I've been travelling between countless points in time...
at least twice a day for the past two months,
but this never happened.
You didn't just get hit but also followed me here.
Which of us is likely to be a variable here?
A variable.
Does anything come to mind?
The music. Isn't it the music?
- What? - Right. It was a Sanullim song.
It was so loud that I was hurting my ears outside.
Laying silk in my heart
What does that have to do with this?
Did you make a call or something?
Make a call?
(Speaker)
Hello.
What? Hello?
You did.
Isn't it likely to lead to an accident...
when you do such a thing while driving?
Look. It's designed not to crash in the first place.
It can't be covered by insurance here, anyway.
What are we arguing for?
Gosh.
I was just asking to see If it could help me fix it.
Do you have a place to get back to?
You said you were a teacher here.
It looks like she didn’t really watch the news.
I was just on a trip.
The timeline you live in is my home ground too.
I just got a job to have an identity for safety.
You and I are in the same position since we don’t belong here.
Which means we could be in a dangerous situation.
Especially for you.
Hey, Mr. Yoon!
Are you all right?
Sir, I'm sorry for the trouble at this late hour.
Oh, my.
Did something happen to your car?
He seems to know a lot of people...
for a person who is not supposed to be here.
Hello, we're G-Rock. Thank you!
- Let's go! - Let's do this!
Stop thinking
And start talking
Stop the boring stuff
And start speaking your heart out
My body's fidgeting, I'm in a knot I'm hesitating, feeling unsure
My face is turning red I'm hesitating, feeling unsure
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
- Gosh. - Did I break your head?
I'm okay.
No.
I can't break 3 heads in 1 night,
so I should always be careful.
Wait. Stay away.
Let's keep that distance.
What is with him?
Are you okay? You've been walking in a weird way.
I'm all right.
I can't be covered by insurance here, anyway.
What about you?
I should be okay.
It'd get a little complicated if I died here.
It'd be the death of a person who was never born.
There is no way I can take responsibility for this.
This sweet, salty snack is the solution to everything.
Gosh. It's the worst.
Oh, dear.
Come on in first.
Drink some.
You could keep living here.
Are you cursing me?
Well, I have to crash here because I don't even have a house.
I'll fix the car by any means.
Stay here until it's fixed.
Try not to go out since it could be dangerous.
Why? What is dangerous?
Didn't you feel that way at the club earlier?
Do you have an ID?
What about a job? Do you have one?
I could be a spy.
I'll be careful.
Most of all, you could become a danger yourself.
If you drop a seed here by accident,
it'll become a tree in 30 years.
Your one action can completely change someone's future.
I'll keep that in mind.
- Hey. - Mom!
- Why are you so strong? - Let me go, Mom.
You brat! You went to a nightclub?
You want to get on my nerves just like your older sister.
- No, Mom. - Right? Shut it!
I don't need any of you. Just move out.
Goodness.
Honey, you've scolded her enough.
You can't kick her out in the middle of the night.
What? If you have complaints, get out of the house with her.
- Mom. - What?
- Mom. - How could you?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Soon Ae, take the punishment for a little while.
Oh, my.
It looks like Mr. Yoon is home.
Given the fact that she called him a teacher,
she must go to school nearby.
Her house must be in this neighbourhood, then.
Is that why I ended up in Woojung-Ri?
Because it's Mom's hometown?
Is that why I was sent all the way here, Mom?
Are you really okay with sleeping here?
I feel comfortable here.
If you need anything while staying here, let me know.
Clothes, food, or drinks.
Being a rich, jobless person is a dream I've had for a long time.
Enjoy it while it lasts since it won't take long.
I'm a better handyman than you think.
That's good.
Thank you for everything today.
You must've been quite frightened today.
Don't worry too much, and just get some rest.
I'll get you back home in no time.
This is killing me.
I'm utterly clueless.
Darn it.
(The first murder)
I must send her back before that no matter what.
Mr. Yoon!
(Lee Hyung Man)
Mr. Yoon. Gosh.
Hello.
It's 7am on a Sunday. What's going on, Mr. Lee?
I was wondering...
- if your forehead was okay. - Gosh.
- I see. I'm all right. Thank you. - Okay.
Then come with me.
Go where?
Don't tell me you're not going to participate...
in the Woojung-Ri Family Walkathon. I'm hosting it.
I already put your name on the T-shirt.
I see. I don't have a family here. And I'm busy.
There's someone in the same boat as you.
And that person needs a partner.
- Let's go. - Pardon?
- No. I was in the middle of... - All right.
I'm sure you'll have a blast once you get there.
Nice. That was some impeccable timing.
By the way, how can I find Mom's house?
Gosh.
Mom.
The super glue lady?
Wait. This is my mother's house?
Gosh. This is a miracle.
It's a miracle!
Why do you keep following me?
Because...
I like you.
It's fascinating.
And I missed you too.
Did your mom pass away?
Yesterday in the restroom...
Is that why you're staying with your relative?
I'm Lee Soon Ae.
That's my name.
I don't know if it's because I resemble her...
or because you've been sniffing super glue.
But don't call me Mom.
It really scares me.
Then can I follow you?
Soon Ae.
Lee Soon Ae.
(Woojung General Store)
Do you work here every Sunday?
No.
Usually, my parents take turns working here.
But they have the Walkathon today. So I'm filling in for them.
I see.
Are you going to stay there?
I have to work now.
Okay. I won't get in your way.
I'll be outside looking around.
(Kim Seung Jin)
(Ticket Office)
Yoon Young.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Your father goes to the hospital nearby.
I was so surprised to see you when we were walking by.
Are you busy?
- No. - Look how slim your face got.
- You'll ruin my makeup. - Okay.
The writer will be here?
Yes. Won't you be late for the doctor's appointment?
There was a time when I dreamed of becoming a novelist.
That's not easy.
What's the plot?
Can you give me a signed book too?
You're going to read it?
That's fine. You won't even read it.
Let's go now.
Right.
My eyes are getting bad these days. Why would I read books?
- Bye. - Okay.
- Don't skip your meals. - Okay. Bye.
I'd be alone after the breakup
And I'd cry with a broken heart
I knew I'd regret it when she left
But why couldn't I tell her that?
Gosh.
As long as I can find some members,
I can easily form a band.
But then again,
who would have musical instruments in the countryside?
(Woojung Transportation)
Hey.
(Direct)
- Thanks. - Okay.
- Gosh. See you tomorrow. - Thanks.
- I'll be there tomorrow. - Bye.
Bye.
Goodness.
- Did everyone get off? - Yes, they did.
Gosh.
How can he not be on time for the bus?
Mom liked reading books.
If it weren't for us,
she would have read all the books she wanted.
This...
can't be a coincidence.
How did I end up meeting Mom when she was 19?
I'm sure there's a reason behind that.
I really want to turn back time, Dad.
If I could go back to the past,
I would go way back.
So that Mom wouldn't have to...
love you or me.
I'll make her live happily...
all her life by herself.
I'll make sure she lives.
Mom got married in 1988.
And she said she had met Dad a year ago.
How can he miss the bus? Seriously.
What time are you looking to take the bus?
Are you all right?
I think...
I need to go to the hospital.
Oh, gosh.
(Woojung General Store)
Soon Ae, what happened?
He suddenly flopped down after seeing me.
My heart suddenly...
It started beating like crazy.
It was as if ten or more drums...
were being played.
- Oh, my. - Careful.
- What's your name, by the way? - Sorry?
I'm Baek Hee Sub.
And what's your name?
Oh, gosh.
Wait, you're the first forehead.
What are you trying to pull here?
I need to talk to you.
Soon Ae, get back inside.
- So... - Come here.
So it's Soon Ae.
Come on.
Get back inside!
- You're quite strong. - Come here.
- What's the matter? - Come!
- What's wrong with you? - Just come!
They kind of look alike.
They're both so weird.
Is your forehead all right?
I guess your heart is feeling okay now.
It seems to be totally fine.
You're right.
Are your legs okay?
- Try running. - Run?
They're fine.
Since when did you speak in dialect?
Since I was born.
You're asking so many weird questions. What's going on here?
You...
Don't you dare come near Soon Ae.
Bread?
Gosh, you're studying hard as usual, our literary girl.
Hey, girls.
Come on out. We have somewhere to be.
But my mom will tell me off if I leave now.
It'll only take a second.
We want to do something fun at school tomorrow.
We wanted to plan ahead.
Plan?
Why must I do that?
Who are you to tell me what to do?
I...
am Soon Ae's BF, okay?
What? BF?
What on earth is that?
It means I'm her closest friend in this world, okay?
That's how close Soon Ae and I are.
I'm sorry about bumping into your head...
and cracking it yesterday.
Forget it.
As long as I'm here,
you'll never get a chance with my Soon Ae.
So quit now before you develop more feelings.
Why do you not like me?
"Why?"
I know who you are,
what kind of person you are,
and how light and insignificant your love is.
I've seen it all.
What...
Who are you to say that?
How would you know?
Hee Sub.
Yu Sub!
- Uncle Yu Sub? - What took you so long?
Just wait and see! You'll eventually grow fond of me.
- One, two, three, four, - One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight. - five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four, - Two, two, three, four,
Now to the legs.
- Two, four... - My goodness.
- Five, six, seven, eight. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four, - Two, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight. - five, six, seven, eight.
- One, two, three, four, - One, two, three, four,
- five, six... - five... Goodness.
Who are you waiting for?
My grandson.
(Spring, 2024)
He disappeared right here.
You can't even recognize him.
My grandson disappeared right here.
Please find him.
Some might think you cherished that grandson.
What are you doing here? You said you couldn't stand the sight of him!
- Two, three... - Two, three...
- Five, six, seven, eight. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four. - Mr. Yoon.
- Over here. - Five, six, seven, eight.
- One more time. - One more time.
- You've got this! - Let's go!
(Woojung-Ri Family Walkathon)
Come on, honey! Hurry up!
Goodness. Hurry up!
- Gosh, seriously. - We're almost there.
Gosh.
I didn't even expect to join the walkathon this year,
but I'm really glad I did.
I could only be on the sidelines and clap for them.
I see.
I heard the prize for third place is a Walkman.
I think we can win that much.
All you have is money. Gosh, you're so cheap.
The only family I have is my son,
but I sent him to the US to study.
Waiting for his return is the only joy in life.
Since when did you adore him so much?
Sorry? What have you been mumbling all this time?
You need to speed up if you want to win third place.
Third place? Right, the Walkman.
(Yoon Byung Gu)
Mr. Yoon.
Wait for me!
It's a Family Walkathon.
Why did he give me this when he wanted it so much?
(Stereo radio cassette player)
I'll only be able to fix it if I go back.
I told her not to go outside, but she couldn't even last a day.
It's almost as if she'd had this planned.
Goodness.
Gosh.
(Bong Bong Teahouse)
(Women who read are dangerous.)
What is this doing here?
Both Dad and Uncle...
seem so different.
(Woojung General Store)
No. Even if it's a prank, it's too mean.
So? You don't want to do it?
You just need to pretend to have lost it.
I can't lie about having my things stolen when I actually haven't.
And it's one of our classmates. It's too harsh.
You're acting all innocent again.
Gosh.
(Kim Seung Jin)
("A Room of One's Own")
(Lee Soon Ae)
Mom,
I know you snuck a peek...
at all my diaries leading up to college.
We're even now.
(Ticket Office)
I...
hate fake people.
Those who act like...
they don't know anything...
that has to do with bad or dirty things in this world.
People like you.
Soon Ae!
Help!
Mom!
Gosh, what should we do?
Soon Ae, are you okay?
What's wrong with you guys?
Why were you just watching...
when your friend was practically drowning?
We thought she was joking.
Is a person's life a joke to you?
I see.
Should I start joking around too?
Who are you to get involved?
How annoying.
Ko Mi Sook.
Dear Y,
from time to time, whenever I feel lonely,
I picture a small door inside my head.
I am sitting alone in a small room...
with absolutely no light.
Why is this...
This is your first novel released in 1987, "Small Door."
You wrote this...
remarkable novel when you were only 19.
Don't you know...
how many people became fans because of your first novel?
I'm the first fan of yours.
Right?
You're Ko Mi Sook, right?
How do you know my name?
Soon Ae, are you okay?
Are you sure you don't need to go to the hospital?
I'm going home.
Let's go, Soon Ae.
Let's go.
There's a big hospital at our town's intersection.
My mom's a doctor there.
If her condition gets worse, make sure to take her there.
I'll put in a good word.
Come on. Let's go, Soon Ae.
I'm sorry, Soon Ae.
See you at school tomorrow.
I'm sorry. I'm not good at swimming.
I caused such an inconvenience.
Do all those girls attend the same school as you?
Even Ko Mi Sook?
Yes, we're friends in the same class.
They just stood and watched you drown. How are they your friends?
You can be honest with me.
Do they bully you?
No.
They were just joking.
"Joking?"
How is that a joke, Soon Ae?
Can you just pretend it never happened?
Still, they're the only friends I can talk to...
at school.
People don't really seem to like me.
So no one wants to talk to me.
That's why...
I need to continue being friends with them.
And everything needs to be a joke.
So...
So what I'm saying is...
I want to die.
Hey, Lee Soon Ae!
What are you doing over there? Hurry up and come inside.
Please keep what happened today a secret.
Go back inside.
(Congratulations on hosting the 1988 Seoul Olympics.)
Have you ever...
realized how someone felt,
but it was too late?
If only I had realized a little earlier.
If only I knew a bit faster,
everything could've changed.
But that's not the case here.
In this place, it's not too late.
Nothing has happened yet.
I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can go back just yet.
There's something I must do here.
(My Perfect Stranger)
I need to go to school.
If I remove my makeup,
I don't look my age.
Do you think that makes sense?
You want to go as a student, not a teacher?
I need to see your ID for real this time.
Her identity is verified?
She is a senior in Class One at Woojung High School.
What happened?
Aren't you glad to see me?
Unbelievable. What nonsense.
The list of prime suspects.
Three people.
I'm going to move as close as possible.
I'll blend in with them and keep my eyes on them.
The school is my starting point.
(My Perfect Stranger)