[Defying the Storm]
[Episode 19]
It seems I made a mistake.
What's this all about?
There are three "Nian Zhong".
What's the difference?
Dairong.
This Zhong means "middle",
as well as the "Zhong" in China,
not the Zhong that means "terminate".
Do you know that?
When Zujia was practicing divination,
he made January the first month of the lunar year.
You are so knowledgeable.
- It's just the origin of the first month.
- Sister!
Haichen?
Sister!
Haichen!
Haitang?
It's Haitang.
Haichen!
Sister.
Uncle Ling!
Haichen.
Yuanyin.
- Haitang.
- Uncle.
Uncle Ling.
Uncle Dairong.
Hello, hello.
We finally meet here.
Uncle Ling, are you okay?
We finally met.
It's a surprise that we can meet here.
Although we lost Zeng Mu,
we met Haitang.
That's right.
I'll change one word of Yan Jidao's poem.
That is, although you came a long way here,
we smile after we met.
That's right.
Let's go.
Okay.
I'll pack the things.
That's right. Hurry up.
[Jinma]
Be careful.
The bazaar is about to close.
Please have a look.
Hello.
How far is it from here to Kunming?
Kunming?
This Jinma is the landmark of Kunming.
You have arrived in Kunming.
We are in Kunming now.
We are in Kunming now!
Let's go.
[Jinma]
Secretary General, all people are here.
Say something.
No word can express my happiness
to see us reunite here.
You've been so tired on the way here,
and you didn't eat anything delicious.
Just eat.
I...
I want to call your names today.
Ling Wenyue.
Yes, sir.
Chen Dairong.
Meng Haichen.
Yes, sir.
Meng Haitang.
Xu Yuanyin.
Yes, sir.
Li Donglai.
- There are still us!
Don't worry.
When you entered Fuhua University,
I'll surely call your names.
Remember,
you should study hard.
I'll be waiting for you.
- Okay!
Come on, let's eat!
Let's eat.
[Welcome the tour group
from Hunan, Guizhou and Yunan]
Come on.
We're almost there.
Here.
Look, this tree is so fragrant.
Please, come in.
Be careful.
Don't push, be careful.
Come in.
Please, come in.
Be careful.
Look, how's it?
Look how happy they are.
Haitang.
I'll take you upstairs.
Yuanyin.
Let's go.
Where are they?
Where are they going?
Go inside and have a look.
Just go.
Okay.
Come on, here it is.
Wait for me.
Mom planted these flowers.
There are flowers in Kunming in all four seasons.
I can take you to the flower market someday.
Without Shuan delivering food for us,
mom and Mrs. Meng had a ridged field in the backyard.
They said they would
plant sweet broad peas, sword beans,
eggplants, towel gourds and cucumbers there.
Haitang.
There is a forest
of crabapple flowers on Yuantong Mountain.
In March,
there are many crabapple flowers.
But you are here late and missed the flower season.
Haitang.
Qianying.
Just let her go.
How's it?
It's beautiful.
This is a garner, right?
Yes, it is.
All the holes on the ground
have been repaired by mom and Mrs. Meng.
And I also helped.
Well, Yuanyin.
This is your room.
And this is the room for my mom and dad.
And, here.
This is Haitang's room.
And this is Haichen's room.
This is the room for Uncle Meng and Aunt Meng.
And this one,
guess whose room this is.
Whose room is it?
It's yours.
Go inside and have a look.
Donglai.
This quilt is for you.
I just aired it, it's still warm.
Don't touch it.
Take a shower first.
You can't go to bed if you're dirty.
I need to cut the hair for you.
Step aside.
I'll clean the room for you.
Mrs. Meng is so nice.
All moms are the same.
They are all wordy.
♫ I looked at the falling sunset ♫
♫ I heard the whisper of the sky ♫
♫ Who knows the direction of wind ♫
♫ Where will it fly to ♫
♫ I looked at the yellow sand in the dream ♫
♫ All memories faded ♫
♫ In the dark night ♫
You experienced
so many difficulties on the way here.
Now you have a home.
You deserve to live a better life.
♫ The wilderness is all covered white ♫
♫ When can we arrive at the destination ♫
♫ When the snow melted, I'll get an answer ♫
♫ Red snowflakes bloom in the wind and rain ♫
♫ The way to travel far and the home under banyan ♫
♫ That's the answer of time ♫
♫ It flows quietly ♫
♫ To search and to light ♫
♫ To pass winters and summers ♫
Zhang Qi?
Nianqiao.
Why are you here?
Where is Zhang Qi?
Haitang.
When Hanguang Squadron had a battle in Jiangyin...
What do you mean?
[A letter for Haitang]
This is the letter
you asked me to give Haitang before.
Now you're still alive.
Take it back.
Give it to her if you have the chance.
Why?
It would be painful to be with a pilot.
Besides,
I have become like this now.
Then can you hide it
from her for the rest of your life?
After some days,
she'll not be in love with me after some days.
It would be okay,
if she meets me then.
No, I can't do it.
Zeng Nianqiao.
This is an order.
You...
He left this letter to you before the battle.
I don't want the letter, where is Zhang Qi?
Nianqiao, where is Zhang Qi?
Miss Haitang, please
regard reading this letter as talking to me.
When you are reading this letter,
it means I won't appear in your life anymore.
Zhang Qi!
Meng Haitang!
I'll always remember the day
when you sat on the wall covered
with crabapple leaves and looked at me.
I'll place it on 019,
as the navigation tower.
That picture has been on my warplane for a long time.
I hoped it would be
the navigation tower when I land in my life.
But when the fire of war
devoured my warplane and that picture,
I think,
luckily, it is this picture
that accompanied my warplane
and me into the fire of war,
but not you.
Haitang.
Let me take the war, calamity
and darkness away from you,
so only the beautiful memories can be with you.
Please live for me.
I only hope you can remember
you met a man like me in your life.
A letter from Zhang Qi.
Ms. Meng, what's wrong?
Ms. Meng, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Shixing.
Did you write the diary as I asked you?
Not yet.
Then start to write it from today.
I'll write a diary, too.
Writing a diary is like writing to our minds.
Ms. Meng, Ms. Meng.
Ms. Meng.
What's wrong?
Ms. Meng, will you stay
in Shouchang middle school and teach us?
Yes.
Your headmaster said you need a teacher.
There are still two months left in this semester.
I'll leave after this semester.
So, you'll leave after two months?
Yes.
I need to go to school in Kunming.
It's just,
I still don't know
whether I'll continue to go to Normal College,
or go to study in department of history.
Zhang Qi.
I finally heard from you.
But you're leaving me.
I don't believe what you asked Nianqiao to tell me.
You are still alive
and waiting for me to find you, right?
The poem, Lament in Jiangnan,
is about prosperity and decline
of Liang in the South Dynasties.
It embodies the author's sorrow
for the chaos suffered by his country and people.
Okay.
Let's read Lament in Jiangnan one more time, okay?
- Okay.
There are so many people in the world.
For me,
there are only two kinds of people,
which are you and others.
I'll also remember
your smile and tall figure
under the crabapple tree.
Zhang Qi, if I can't find you,
I'll try to become you.
To fall in love with the sky,
to fall in love with flying in the sky,
I'm fortunate to have met you.
Zhang Qi.
You let me know
there was someone like you in the world.
And I'm fortunate to fly with a person like you,
and hug a person like you.
[A letter for Zhang Qi]
During the Anti-Japanese War,
a large number of scholars who moved south
shined dazzling light in this short history.
They were dependable and modest.
They devoted their lives to learning and teaching.
The various thoughts
and cultures produced in this period
can also be seen as a kind
of cultural resistance against Japan.
[Department of History]
Three lower jawbones
of Lufengpithecus lufengensis.
No problem.
Five skull fragments.
And nineteen upper and lower dentitions.
That's right.
Lanshan.
There are so many boxes left to be checked.
We may work until midnight.
Is Qianying going to have supper at Gao Aiju's house?
Yes.
Haitang will come back from Mengzi today.
Qianying and Donglai will pick her up at the station.
Then they'll have supper at Aiju's house.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Look at this skull.
It's so beautiful.
It has been millions of years.
It's not easy for it to be preserved like this.
Yes, it's so well preserved.
What's wrong with him?
No, no.
The teacher has eaten someone.
It's so scary.
No.
I need to go back and tell them.
Stay here.
[Canteen]
Watch the step.
Be careful.
Please.
This is...
Nianqiao found a house for you.
Do you like this place?
Although I like it,
I can't afford to live here.
You paid for my hotel accommodation.
I won't live in such a good place.
Aunt, aunt.
Please sit down first.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Aunt.
You don't have to pay for these.
Huansheng...
well,
Chunlai's pension has been sent to Family Ding.
In all these years, he gave his money to poor comrades,
so he didn't save much.
I've discussed with the Captain.
We'll be responsible for your future life,
just like the tradition in Jianqiao.
What's the tradition?
Ding left nothing in his entire life.
This is the only thing that he left.
This is a commemorative coin.
It used to have two sides,
but he changed it to one side.
I think,
to save the country by aviation,
is what he wants in his life.
Will the government admit
that Chunlai sacrificed for the country?
Yes.
After the air battle on 14th, August,
Mr. Mao Zedong issued an article.
He wrote, all front-line troops,
whether it's army, air force or local forces,
they all fought bravely.
This reflects the heroic spirit
of our Chinese nation.
With supreme enthusiasm,
CPC would like to extend
the salute of national revolution
to all patriotic compatriots
and patriotic troops in the country.
The salute of national revolution?
Yes.
Good.
It's a worthy death for Chunlai.
Please help me
to fulfill Chunlai's last wish.
Don't.
I wasn't blaming you.
Stand up.
Aunt, please sit down.
This is our rule.
There will be sacrifices in war.
I won't blame you.
Chunlai is my wingman.
I took him to the sky,
but I didn't let him land safely.
He was my best brother when he was alive,
as well as my guide.
Now he has sacrificed.
I'll regard his mother as my mother.
I'll treat you
in the same filial way as he will.
My mom died when I was little.
I haven't called mom for a long time.
Are you willing
to let me call you mom?
Stand up.
Just stand up.
Mom.
Minster allowed me to stay with Mom
in Shang Village for three days.
You can go back to Wujiaba first.
Okay, I'll pick you up after three days.
Take care of yourself.
Yantai! Yantai!
Yantai!
Did anything happen?
Mom.
Don't worry, I'll go and check it.
Yantai! Yantai!
They are heading to Fuhua University.
Fuhua University?
When I was looking for you,
I wandered around here for a long time,
so I know that's Fuhua University.
They also came from Hangzhou.
I heard
the teachers and students from Peiping
are not getting alone well with the locals.
I'm afraid anything would happen.
Calm down, calm down.
Please calm down.
Calm down.
[Fuhua University]
Calm down, calm down.
Please calm down, okay?
Tell us, where are you hiding the kid?
Your kid is not in our campus.
Impossible.
Brother, Yantai must be in there.
Or, they have eaten him.
We need to get in.
Where is Yantai?
Give us the kid.
Or we will burn this school.
- Burn this school!
Villagers, villagers.
Take care of those antiques.
I'll explain to them.
Be careful.
Just go.
Everything has a reason, right?
Yes, you need to be reasonable.
What's your reason?
You tell me your reasons.
Follow that woman.
Come on.
Go.
When I was delivering the meal for you,
I saw you holding a skull.
It's you.
What's that?
Please let me explain to you.
The skull I was holding is not a human's skull.
That's a fossil of an ape.
It has been preserved for eight million years.
Eight million years?
Are you kidding me?
That's right.
Think about it.
Is there a huge difference
between the skull I was holding
and the human skull now?
That skull's eyebrow bones
are very broad and protruding.
Its nose is flat.
Its jaws are also very protruding.
And it doesn't have a lower jaw.
How could this be the skull of a human?
That's right.
That's the fossil of an ancient ape,
not the human's skull.
It's a stone.
Yes, that's a stone.
We don't understand what you said.
- Give us the kid.
- Give us the kid!
Calm down!
Supervisor Bai.
Supervisor Bai, you need to uphold justice for us.
These are bad people.
It's midnight now.
Who are making trouble here?
They are the guests I invited.
Anyone who dares to make trouble,
is betraying my order.
Open the door!
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang, are you okay?
Haitang, why are you here?
Come on.
We heard something happened when we came back.
Yuanyin and Qianying went to look for my dad.
I'll save you out of here first.
Wait.
We should find
those tortoise shells with words on them now.
Break the window!
Come on.
No.
No, I must stay here.
I need to protect these antiques.
These are Wenyue's treasure for a life time.
You can leave first.
Go, just go!
Haitang, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Don't move!
Bury your head in your hands.
And get on the ground.
If you keep moving,
I'll shoot you in the head!
Get on the ground!
Zhang Qi?
Supervisor Bai, it's not because of us.
It's their fault. They eat people.
My kid Yantai must have been eaten by them.
Kid, tell Supervisor Bai about it.
Everyone said,
there are outsiders that will eat villagers.
Yantai took us here to catch that cannibal.
But after we entered there for a while,
we couldn't find Yantai.
He must have been eaten by them.
That's right.
They must have eaten him.
Give me back my child.
Please wait.
We found the kid.
Yantai.
Naughty boy.
Where did you go?
You can't take care of a kid?
He sneaked in and ate food in Fuhua canteen.
He drank the rice wine,
so he fell asleep.
Now we've found the kid,
don't say teachers in Fuhua University eat humans.
Okay.
Everything has been figured out.
You said teachers in university will eat humans.
People will laugh at you when they hear this!
The folk custom in Shang Village is not so good.
Enough.
It's midnight now, go home.
Let's go back, villagers.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go back now.
Well, Mr. Ling,
I heard there was a gunshot
when I was looking for the kid.
Lanshan!
Is it Zhang Qi?
Haitang!
Are you okay?
Don't move!
Who are you?
How dare you make trouble here?
Lanshan!
Mom!
Let's go.
Lanshan!
Coming.
Ling.
- Lanshan.
- Haitang.
Check Haitang.
What happened?
Did you see Zhang Qi?
- No.
Haitang, sit down.
- Haitang.
Haitang, are you okay?
Captain Zhang.
It's you.
Are you okay?
Haitang...
Haitang is there.
Ms. Xu.
Don't tell Haitang
I have been here.
Why?
Please.
Captain Zhang.
Help me.
Who is he?
The Captain of Jianqiao Hanguang Squadron, Zhang Qi.
Zhang Qi?
The one Haitang is waiting for?
Wake up.
We can't put him here.
We need to send him back.
No problem.
I'll send him back.
- Be careful.
- Hold on.
Be careful.
You, too.
Be sure to send him back.
Okay.
Come on.
Hurry up.
The next one.
Secretary General Meng.
Supervisor Bai.
Thank you so much.
What happened here?
I'm late.
There was a misunderstanding
between people in Shang Village and teachers here.
They caused trouble to you.
Supervisor Bai.
As far as I know,
the situation is not like that.
There are many bandits
in Shang Village and on Luofeng Mountain.
Fuhua University is in a dangerous situation now.
Supervisor Bai, can you
send soldiers to suppress bandits?
It would be better if you can
send some soldiers to protect our university.
So,
my army would be bodyguards of Fuhua University?
Supervisor Bai, let me tell you,
Fuhua University is
one of the top universities in China.
About the antique room,
many of the ancient books
and tortoise shells are national treasures,
needless to say the professors and teachers.
They are the talents of the nation.
Supervisor Bai.
You should keep them safe.
Secretary General Meng.
I can send soldiers to suppress the bandits,
but I have a condition.
You need to open
a teacher-training class at Fuhua University.
I can send you some students.
You have a Normal College, right?
Then they can study there.
Well...
you can't enter Fuhua University so easily.
I welcome the students,
but they need to pass the exam.
You're right.
But,
my army can't be easily dispatched as well.
Well,
I'll report to Mr. Chiang first.
This report will be passed to him one by one.
After he approves it,
we can discuss how to dispatch soldiers,
and whose soldiers to dispatch.
Let's discuss it next year.
Supervisor Bai, Supervisor Bai.
Here's the thing.
You want a teacher-training class?
Okay.
I agree on behalf of Fuhua University,
but the number of students is limited.
We'll only accept five students.
Okay, let's do as you said.
Okay.
But there are six students.
I'll add one more person. That is my girl.
Secretary General Meng.
If you can educate my daughter well,
I'll give you about 1.3 acres of land
under Luofeng Mountain.
You can move the Law and Business College
in Mengzi to this place.
That's a deal.
Okay.
Ling Wenyue didn't go to the antique room at once,
but he stayed there and explain to the villagers.
It means he really doesn't have that.
Director.
How should we deal
with the five people that Supervisor Bai caught?
Tell Baifei's subordinates,
don't let them reveal anything.
Just regard them as villagers
who are making trouble.
Okay, I'll do as you said.
Also,
about the spy I asked you to put around Ling Wenyue...
Qi, why are you so heavy?
I haven't taken care of anyone.
You need to hold on.
We're almost there, hold on.
Be careful.
Sit down and have some rest.
Is this your home?
Zhang Qi's mom!
Your son is back!
Are you okay?
Did your wound ache again?
How could you be so careless?
You're injured.
- You can't run.
- Mom...
Mom.
Donglai.
Donglai!
Did you wake up?
Yes.
Look.
I've made chicken soup for you.
You've been lost for more than two years.
You must have missed the dish I cooked.
Mom.
Come here.
What's the smell of this chicken soup?
It's foul.
You don't know how to cook
since you haven't cooked for long?
Naughty boy.
Qi is ill,
so I added his favorite bamboo shoots in chicken soup.
Qi is not as strong as you.
Mom.
Give me a reason.
From yesterday,
I felt he was more like a real son to you than me.
What did he tell you?
Why did you accept him as your son?
Is it because he is handsome or he is rich?
Donglai.
Zhang Qi and your brother are like brothers
that have experienced life and death.
I lost my kid.
If he hadn't accompanied me like a real son,
I wouldn't have known how to go through those sad days.
Mom, don't be sad.
Well,
go to see if Zhang Qi wakes up.
You had a good sleep last night.
But he had a fever and didn't have a good sleep.
Okay.
I'll go after I drink the soup.
What?
Is he really alive?
Yes.
But,
he didn't want me to tell you he is still alive.
Great.
Haitang...
Where is he?
I'll look for him.
Haitang.
Haitang, be careful.
Haitang, why did you come out?
Nianqiao.
Why did you lie to me?
I...
Zhang Qi is still alive.
Where is he? I'll find him.
Haitang, you can't go there.
Why?
Haitang.
♫ A high wind is brewing. Ripping the thorns ♫
♫ Seize every day to seek justice ♫
♫ Shed tears to our sweet love ♫
♫ The date of return is yet to come ♫
♫ The faith and zeal in heart ♫
♫ Life and death hanging by a thread ♫
♫ Sincerity blooms all over the land ♫
♫ See the man of iron raise his gun ♫
♫ The pursuit in the words of scholars ♫
♫ Guard every inch of our territory with life ♫
♫ Look back in the end. My love for my homeland stays ♫
♫ The faith and zeal in heart ♫
♫ Life and death hanging by a thread ♫
♫ Sincerity blooms all over the land ♫
♫ See the man of iron raise his gun ♫
♫ The pursuit in the words of scholars ♫
♫ Guard every inch of our territory with life ♫
♫ Look back in the end. My love for my homeland stays ♫