[You Are My Heartbeat]
[Puttichai Kasetsin]
♫ I don't understand why my heart trembles when I see you ♫
[Davika Hoorne]
♫ In my dreams, at night and during the day, why do I still long for you? ♫
♫ I can't stop my heart beating out of rhythm like a delirious person ♫
[Jackrin Kungwankiatichai]
♫ I've really fallen in love with you. The more you try to flee, the more I want to find you ♫
[Carissa Springett]
♫ The empty space in my heart, come and see, and you will know that it is boundless ♫
♫ Is there enough space for you to settle there? ♫
[Penpak Sirikul]
♫ I'll be happy if we have each other. Do you believe my words? ♫
♫ If we love each other, we will know ♫
[Thanakorn Chinakul]
♫ I didn't think that I would love you, so I let you go ♫
[Mintita Wattanakul]
[Benjawan Artner]
♫ I didn't think that I would love you, so I let you go ♫
[Pentivat Don Juancharo]
♫ In the end, I fell madly in love ♫
[Oliver Poupart, Mayurin Pongpudpunth]
♫ I don't understand why my heart trembles when I see you ♫
[Khemarat Soonthornnont, Virahya Pattarachokchai, Wisawa Kittankachorn]
♫ In my dreams, at night and during the day, why do I still long for you? ♫
[Ratawan Tonahongsa, Kirin Simon Young, Pokchat Thiamchai]
♫ I can't stop my heart beating out of rhythm like a delirious person ♫
[Junya Thanasawangkul, Phuchong Yothapitak]
♫ I've really fallen in love with you ♫
[Ratawan Aomitsong, Nattharat Kornkaew, Pareena Busayasiri, Thanchanok Yutthasarnsiri]
♫ The more you try to flee, the more I want to find you ♫
[Wayne Falconer, Pongpangt Phetbuntoon, Jirakitlya boonkroongsupya, Tharakhet Phetsuksai]
[Nathapatsorn Simasthien, Bhurith Polymeek, Thanaboon Wanlopsirinan, Chayanit Torcharoen]
[Executive Producer Warattaya Nilkuha]
[Director Saratswadee Wongsomphet]
I said that because we are the same.
Do you know why?
Because we are both his children.
- You're not my dad's daughter.
- But your dad said I was his daughter.
I only want to know about Kanghan.
If you want to know about Kanghan,
you have to do something.
What happened? Who is that?
You've tricked me so many times.
It's time to go home to visit Grandma.
Din, where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Don't try to run away.
I arranged the launch of the website,
and wanted to announce you as the new director.
But you ran away.
I had to apologize to the guests.
Did you apologize or did Brother apologize?
Din.
Why did you sign the contract with KKPP?
Because I think KKPP is a good clothing brand.
Their clothing is affordable and covers a wide range of target groups,
including children, teenagers, office workers, and the rich.
I also wear KKPP clothes.
Their clothes are well sewn,
of good quality, and do not shrink after washing.
- The quality...
- Nobody asked you.
KKPP is worth our investment.
No. Because it's an inferior clothing brand.
Nobody wants to wear it.
I'll wear it.
The longer I wear it, the more I like it.
I won't dislike it.
Then have a try.
If you buy their clothes, I'll burn them all.
I'll make you stop liking it.
Your wish will come true on the day I die.
- And I...
- Enough, Din.
You know the chairwoman doesn't like KKPP.
Why are you doing it?
It's for the little happiness of my life.
Can't you learn your lesson?
I think you learned your lesson from being deceived.
Do you want to get hurt again?
Cancel the contract.
Pay the penalty.
Don't let this happen again.
If you want me to go back to the company,
you must work with KKPP.
If you don't want to, I won't go back.
Grandma, think about it.
Do you want me to work with KKPP,
or do you want me to disappear again?
Why are you against the chairwoman?
I think you respect Grandma too much. Did you notice that?
I did. I respect Grandma very much.
But if it weren't for the chairwoman,
an orphan like me wouldn't have been here today.
Don't try to fight.
Remember, your mother abandoned you.
Lom, you're abandoned.
Lom, someone is here to see you.
Mom, I'm coming.
She's not my mother.
Khun Premyuda will take care of you instead of your mom.
Be a good child, understand?
Turn around and say hi to her.
Hello.
But you don't have to listen to Grandma for everything.
I've had enough. I'm tired of having to listen to Grandma.
I want to live my life.
I want to be with someone I love.
Well, if one day you fall in love with someone Grandma doesn't like,
you'll understand why I'm doing this.
[Samitivej Hospital]
Congratulations. I heard your mom can go home tomorrow.
I'm so happy for you. Your mom has a long life.
Thank you.
The longer my mother lives, the more someone hates her.
My mom will live a long time.
You're in the hospital. Do you want to have your body checked?
Why should I do that? I'm fine.
You're physically healthy,
but I don't think you're mentally healthy.
You shouted at me yesterday, but you're being nice to me today.
Is there a problem with you?
I just want to thank you.
Thank me for what?
Although I told Dad that I didn't want you to work for the company.
I changed my mind. Because I know
how useful you are to the company.
That's the report of the last quarter.
Khun Sira, do you have anything to add?
I want to add lingerie to our New Look website this quarter,
because now women have strong purchasing power.
Okay.
And we must win the International Lingerie Show Competition.
Because I want to use it for the website launch.
About the designer. Did Cindy Wang reply to us?
She replied to our email five minutes ago.
She agreed, didn't she?
She... She refused to work with us this year.
Why?
She just found out she's pregnant.
She wanted to take a break and prepare to be a mother.
However, Khun Sira you don't have to worry.
I already had an open call for designers.
We're sure to make it to the International Lingerie Show Competition.
Get it done as soon as possible. I want the designer to start work within this month.
It's over. The fortress blew up.
[KKPP]
Hey, I don't know whether Khun Chanaratee told Khun Kansinee or not.
What should she say?
I'm going to tell you something. According to the latest information,
she's no longer the chief designer of our company,
because Khun Papop wasn't pleased with her.
Khun Kansinee is confident that she'll become the head of the Design Department.
But she failed,
because Khun Papop offered the position to his stepdaughter.
What did you say?
Oops. Khun Kansinee, you're back from Milan.
I asked you.
Who did Khun Papop make the head of the design department?
Here's the contract.
If you need to amend anything, just amend it.
[Labor Contract]
[Position: Head of Design Department]
Thank you for offering me the opportunity to work here.
But...
I refuse to be the head of the design department. Is it okay?
What's your reason? Can you tell me?
I would rather not get into trouble with Hom.
Let's put the job aside.
Do you think you have a problem with Hom?
I think you do.
Because no matter what, Hom will be against you.
If you don't have power,
Hom will bully you even more.
Don't worry about me.
I'll do my best to bear with her.
And I won't mess up my job.
Kanghan, sometimes you need the power
to fight someone.
If you could overcome others with kindness,
your mom would have won a long time ago.
I know. You are willing to work here
and willing to stay at my home
because you need to take care of your mom.
I'm sorry.
I failed to take good care of your mother.
I allowed Hom to exercise her will.
If I don't take this position,
who will take it?
Kansinee.
There was a department head meeting today.
Why didn't you go to the meeting?
Did your mom tell you that with my dad backing you up,
you don't have to work hard but wait for your paycheck?
See? I told you that you should see a doctor.
You have a mental problem.
You were good that day. But you went mad again today.
And I didn't go to the meeting this morning
because I had checked that the design department didn't have to attend the meeting.
So,
I came to say hi to your dad.
Do you know why? Because I'm a cultured and polite person.
I know I should respect other people's parents.
Good. It's good that you're polite.
You should respect me later.
Because I'm the new head of the Marketing Department.
What? You are the new head of the marketing department?
Wait a second.
[New Head of Marketing Department]
It's done.
So everyone knows that you're the new head of the marketing department.
- I'm not a friend you can joke with.
- Of course not.
I don't make friends with mean people.
Hey.
You're showing off to me about your new position
because you want to surprise me. Right?
Then, I can be surprised again.
Are you the new head of the marketing department?
Secretary, she's the new head of the marketing department.
Head. Applause.
Enough.
I told you that because you should report to me on every job from now on.
Wait. I work in the design department, not the marketing department.
Why should I report to you?
Because your first job is related to my marketing department.
The first job?
Don't worry. No matter how bad your design is,
I'm sure you'll find a way for our company to win.
Hello, everyone. My name is Riu.
Hello, everyone. My name is Atichart.
I just got back from New York.
I graduated from Parsons School of Design with a degree in design.
[Watch this video if you're sleepy]
And this is...
Sorry.
Then...
Thank you very much. We'll get back to you.
This way, please.
Hello.
Hello, everyone. My name is Kansinee Vaalikone.
You've been working at KKPP since you graduated.
You've never changed jobs.
Why do you want to work at GU Center?
I... want to improve myself.
I want to be a renowned designer.
GU Group is a top group with a high profile in Asia.
If I could work here,
I would go further in my design career.
Do you think she's lying?
Why do you think you'll have a better career working at GU?
My dad used to say that our lives are like a tree.
If you plant the tree in a little flowerpot,
no matter how well you take care of it,
it can't grow well. Because it's limited.
But if we get a bigger flowerpot for the tree, it will grow better.
I want to get a bigger flowerpot for myself, so I can grow better.
Are you sure working here
will help you realize your dream?
From your work experience at KKPP,
you've won many awards.
And you beat us for some of your awards.
GU lost because you didn't have a good designer like me.
If you hire me,
I'll make sure GU never loses.
You like Kansinee
because her resume says that she used to work at KKPP. Right?
It's not. I like her because she's good.
You just interviewed her, didn't you?
Don't you think she's good?
You know that KKPP will participate
in the International Lingerie Show Competition in a few weeks. Right?
Did you have finished designs before you quit your job?
I have finished designs.
But I didn't give them to KKPP.
Did you bring your designs?
Yes.
Thank you.
Did you design these yourself?
Yes.
Why do your previous designs look so different from the designs on your phone?
From what I've seen of your previous designs,
you like simple colors and lines that aren't overly complicated.
But the patterns and colors
of the designs on your phone look different.
Looks like you paid more attention to detail.
And you focused on dark and light color rendering.
To put it simply, they look younger and more fashionable.
Because...
the theme of this competition is fashion sense.
I just adjusted my designs to be more fashionable.
Khun Sira, it looks like you're interested in my designs.
Yes. I'm interested.
And I really want your design.
It's easy if you want it.
I'll give you the design...
if you hire me.
I would like to hire you.
I like Khun Kansinee because of her designs.
The designs she brought were beautiful in their entirety.
But if you look at their colors and patterns separately, you can clearly see the difference.
They are hardly the same.
But as a whole, they are all conspicuous.
Since when are you good at design?
Well. When I studied abroad, I met a designer.
Female.
- Look.
- Oh, it's beautiful.
Why isn't she dressed?
She felt hot. So she took them off.
I want to be as good as you at drawing.
Do you want me to teach you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let's start from here.
Here are the clothes.
Dress.
Eyes.
- And the eyes.
- Yes.
Eyes.
Good work.
Try to draw it yourself.
Okay.
Okay. Hold it.
Your drawing is beautiful.
Thank you.
Are you a designer?
The lines are beautiful.
I just saw a painting that combines Asian and European elements.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Girl, call me when you're done.
Okay.
You're saying my first design
will be sent to a lingerie competition. Right?
Yes.
And our KKPP company has won the championship for five consecutive years.
But you don't have to be anxious.
Although our company has won the championship for five consecutive years,
we almost lost last year's championship.
We almost went to worship Buddha. Sādhu.
No wonder she wanted me to do this project.
What did you say?
Who is our competitor?
Our competitor is the design department of GU Center.
GU Center?
Yes.
Don't hate me for gossiping.
They weren't worth taking seriously before.
But after Khun Sira took over,
he spent a lot of money recruiting excellent designers.
Khun Sira?
Yes.
Khun Sira.
You said you dumped a grandson of the Kukitcharoen Family, didn't you?
Look. He is the heir to the Kukitcharoen Family.
Why doesn't he seem to know you at all?
Khun Kheetika, the chairman wants to see you.
Ms. Kansinee submitted her resignation?
Yes.
I heard that Kansinee just signed a contract
with GU Center's design department.
She's our competitor.
Now that you're worried, do you need me to get someone to help you?
Why would Kanghan need someone else's help?
She's the head of the design department.
If I don't take this position, who will take it?
Kansinee.
Then I can work as her assistant.
You just want to be an assistant?
Really?
Really.
You know why I stayed.
In that case, I don't need power.
When my mom gets better,
I'll go back to my old life.
- But I'm worried…
- You don't have to worry.
Although I don't have the power,
I have my own way of fighting.
What do you say?
Are you incapable of managing?
How long do I have?
Three weeks.
It doesn't matter if you can't do it.
I'll contact a designer in Milan to do it.
I dare not entrust the company's reputation to someone as undignified as you.
Sir, please wait and see.
Three weeks.
I will do it,
and I will do it well.
I'll wait and see.
[Lingerie Young Designer Awards 2021]
[KKPP]
Okay, come on.
- Khun Kheetika, why don't you go in and wait for me? I'll take it.
- It's okay.
We all work for the company. We should help each other.
- Really?
- Then... Please send things in later.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
Okay.
Excuse me. If you are a staff member, please show your badge.
Oh, okay.
I guess I forgot to bring it. Please wait a moment.
Okay.
- Maha.
- Yes.
Tissue. Alcohol.
- Here.
- Get the alcohol.
- Okay.
- How could it be him?
Are you all right, Khun Sira?
Excuse me.
Stop!
Are you going to run away after you hit me?
I didn't run away.
I'm just going to get my stuff.
Stop lying.
How do you know I'm lying?
You can't measure your heart rate without your watch.
So you can't tell if she's lying.
What? Are you crazy?
What company do you work for?
Didn't your company train you?
If you hit someone, you must apologize.
I didn't do anything wrong. Why should I apologize?
It was you who hit me.
Get out of my way.
No.
Apologize to me first.
All right.
What?
What do you want to do?
I want to do what I did.
You did it to get my attention, didn't you?
I understand.
I just ate papaya salad with raw crabs.
- My breath is not bad. Come on.
- Hey. Let go.
- Come on.
- Maha.
- Let go.
Stop, stop, stop!
You can't do this to my boss.
My boss is the manager of the GU Center.
So what?
You think you can look down on others just because you're rich?
Someone might be afraid of you as the boss. But not me.
What's wrong with her?
Tissue. Alcohol.
Here. Wipes and alcohol.
How are you?
[Lingerie Young Designer Awards 2021]
If that's the case,
I may have to disqualify GU and KKPP.
You are banned from this year's competition.
I hope you understand.
Okay.
Your lingerie is made of different materials.
But the design is the same as mine.
How can you copy my design?
- Try to draw it yourself.
- Okay.
Hold it.
Your drawing is beautiful.
Thank you.
Are you a designer? The lines are beautiful.
I just saw a painting that combines Asian and European elements.
It looks beautiful.
Have we met somewhere?
I've never seen you before.
You may have seen me
when you were copying my design.
How dare you?
Forget it. You don't have the brain to think about design.
How could you have the brain to remember me?
Thank you, you can leave.
You two. Look me in the eye.
Is this the time to do that?
All right. Maybe I can tell who lied.
Look me in the eye.
What? Are your eyes a lie detector?
I won't do it. I said the truth.
If you don't do it, it means you lied.
Hey, you.
Your employee copied our company's design.
Why did you do that?
My dad gave you the opportunity.
But you ruined the reputation of my dad's company.
Aren't you going to ask me if I did what he said I did?
I know it's stressful to be responsible for big projects.
But you shouldn't copy. It's unprofessional.
Are you talking about me or talking about yourself?
- Hey.
- Come on.
I work for GU.
I have to protect GU's reputation.
So,
Khun Chanaratee, what are you going to do about it?
I heard you just got promoted.
You should be decisive.
Forget it if you don't dare.
I understand. That's...
what new executives do.
I'm firing you from KKPP.
My company doesn't need people who copy other people's designs.
You did copy GU's design. Right? What do you have to say for yourself?
Generally, before the show starts, designs are the secrets of each company.
How did you copy GU's design?
- Do you have a contact inside GU?
- Please answer my question.
You didn't plan this plagiarism alone, did you?
Please answer my question.
Please explain yourself.
Let's go.
Khun Sira, who do you want me to get?
Din, of course.
Oh, okay.
You just need me to get Khun Din. Right?
I don't need to get that woman. Right?
Get both of them, of course.
Oh, okay.
If you ask me one more question, you don't have to get them.
You should pack your things and quit.
I'm clear.
Khun Sira, actually, you want...
- Aren't you finished?
- I'm clear. Excuse me!
Din, let go of me.
I won't.
I told you to let go.
When will you stop avoiding me?
Hey, I'm not avoiding you.
Then why did you drop out of language school?
Where did you go?
It was a long time ago, Din.
I think you know why I dropped out.
I don't know. That's why I've been looking for you.
I looked for your contact, email, and address.
Because I wanted to ask you why you dumped me.
I did all those things
because I wanted you to know that I didn't want to have anything to do with you.
I think you understand now.
I don't understand.
All right.
Listen up.
Because I only saw you as a friend.
But you wanted more than that.
It made me feel uncomfortable.
I tried to tell,
but you wouldn't listen. Do you know why?
Because all you thought about was yourself.
I don't believe it. We were more than friends.
See? You only think about yourself.
You never think about other people's feelings.
I never considered to be more than friends with you.
We were close because we were orphans.
What about our dreams?
Dreams are just dreams.
You should get back to real life.
I never considered you to be anything
but a friend and a brother.
A brother?
You're still so willful.
You must get what you want.
Right, you're from a rich family.
There should be plenty of people who spoil you.
Don't talk to me like that. Okay?
You know why I'm doing this.
Why?
Because you consider me to be a woman who can be bought with money.
You and your grandmother can buy anything, but not me.
I never wanted to buy you off.
Everything I did was because I loved you.
But I never loved you.
That's why I changed schools, changed numbers, and changed emails.
I did everything to make you understand that I didn't want to see you again.
Did I make you that uncomfortable?
If you weren't wealthy,
and you didn't have your grandma's mall,
you'd just be a loser.
How could I love you?
Thank you for telling me what you really think.
Then, from now on, if you ever see me again,
please don't pester me.
It would be better if you could act as if we never knew each other.
If that's what you really want, it's okay.
From now on, I no longer know a woman named Kanghan.
♫ I can only say goodbye in my heart ♫
♫ If this love has to hurt, I will keep it all to myself ♫
♫ Since you deserve to be with that someone who is perfect for you ♫
♫ Let it be me who suffers and be the one who ends this love ♫
♫ But it's all worth it because I have finally learned what it's like to love ♫
We meet again, Kheetika.
Din.
Are you looking for Din?
Din...
Your name is Kheetika, isn't it?
Then I'll get this straight.
How much money do you need to leave Din?
Don't think you're getting paid for sleeping with my grandson.
Here's your break-up fee.
What a bad day!
That's what I wanted to say.
You're pestering my grandson again, aren't you?
I've never pestered your grandson.
He's the one who's pestering me.
Din pestered you..
because you seduced him first.
I should say you want to tie him down.
You finally got a high degree.
But your mind is as dirty as ever.
I'm not like you.
Although you are getting older,
you still have no brain.
You shouldn't talk to an elderly person like that.
That is very disrespectful to you.
Apologize to the chairwoman.
I'm so sorry.
Are we related? Who are you to teach me a lesson?
Where are you going?
I still haven't settled the score with you for copying our company's design.
In that case, you can go and claim compensation for damages.
But if I have proof that the person who copied it is your people,
you should prepare to pay me for damages.
I really want the Kukitcharoen Family's money.
I'm happy to spend your money.
[You Are My Heartbeat]
[Preview]
We finally have a chance to live together.
Don't abandon me.
Then let's move out from here.
Sorry.
Come on, Hom.
Please stop bullying Kanghan.
Please give us a chance to live together. Okay?
What if I say no?
[Behind the scenes]
Kansinee.
Her resume says she works at G KKPP.
Let's start over.
Wow.
OST: Jackie Jackrin - "Let's End This"
♫ I never loved anyone before ♫
♫ Until I met you, the one my heart was looking for ♫
♫ But Heaven must have made us meet, even though it was just a dream ♫
♫ After waking up, it all disappeared ♫
♫ If this love has to hurt ♫
♫ I will keep it all to myself ♫
♫ Since you deserve to be with that someone who is perfect for you ♫
♫ Let it be me who suffers ♫
♫ And be the one who ends this love ♫
♫ But it's all worth it ♫
♫ Because I have finally learned what it's like to love ♫