♪ I chase stars and the Moon ♪
♪ My horse neighs in the snowstorm ♪
♪ I hold up my sword ♪
♪ Cut off my hairs along with my sorrow ♪
♪ The world is vast ♪
♪ In this life of mine ♪
♪ I have taken both paths
of love and hate ♪
♪ A lone wild goose flies in the clouds ♪
♪ The sky in the background is glaring ♪
♪ The heaven and the earth
are all in my heart ♪
♪ A jug of liquor and a spark
are enough for me ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be a good day
full of all kinds of feelings ♪
♪ Like the cloud in the wind ♪
♪ There’s nobody
I can share my life with ♪
♪ Sometimes I owe others
and sometimes they own me ♪
♪ It’s merely a dream ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be a good day
that flies by ♪
♪ I’ll still be tender like yesterday ♪
♪ Running toward that rainbow ♪
♪ And hug you ♪
♪ Come in to the outdoor teahouse
for a cup of tea ♪
♪ My brothers all like things spicy ♪
♪ Hustling and bustling ♪
♪ Mahjong is of course a must ♪
♪ Some stubborn kid
does not listen to advice ♪
♪ He gets up in midnight
to sweep the courtyard ♪
♪ Oh my dear liquor jar ♪
♪ Fill up my cup ♪
♪ And let’s drink ♪
= Overlord =
= Episode 33 =
The morning court begins!
Long live Your Majesty!
You may rise.
I feel less energetic than before.
I only hope that the Tang people
can be like real brothers and sisters
who love each other.
My children
help each other.
Prince Zhao and Prince Jun
assist the Crown Prince conscientiously
to govern Tang well.
Your Majesty, you are the true emperor
and in the prime of your life,
you will stay healthy and strong.
Long live Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
If there is no more report,
then the morning court will end.
- I have something to report.
Father.
What I’m going to say
concerns the safety of the nation.
Okay, Prince Zhao.
You go ahead first.
Father.
I want to accuse
a concubine of conspiracy.
Who?
Concubine De.
How could it happen?
What’s going on?
Prince Zhao, are you sure?
Concubine De is your mother.
Prince Zhao.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Your Majesty,
Prince Zhao has been
suffering from serious sickness.
He is semi-conscious.
He always talks gibberish.
Let me take him down for treatment.
Prince Zhao. Prince Zhao!
Hold on.
Prince Zhao.
What’s the crime of Concubine De?
Since Concubine De
entered the Palace,
she has committed many murders,
including the royal family members
Empress Dugu,
Princess Huayang who
died young in Taoist Temple,
Prince Jun’s biological mother Cui,
and the future emperor of Tang,
the Crown Prince.
What?
I have something to say.
Prince Zhao,
go on.
Concubine De
hates your
beloved concubine and princess,
so she killed them.
She is dissatisfied with
the Crown Prince being the future emperor,
so she tries to kill him
and puts poison on his personal objects.
Therefore,
the Crown Prince has been weak
since childhood
and suffering from serious illness.
But...
But they checked my diet,
the physicians did not find anything.
Of course they can’t find it.
Because the poisoned object
is this.
Sacrifice Concubine De to save him.
And also
what happened to Prince Jun in mausoleum
was done by Concubine De.
We found malm
only for building mausoleum
from the Shence Army
who protect Concubine De,
which proves that Concubine De
damaged the mausoleum.
Are you sure
about what you said?
Prince Zhao.
Concubine De cares about you,
it’s fine that you don’t
pay your filial duties,
but you even slander your mother in court!
Please investigate it, Father.
I am guilty.
Please punish me.
Bring Concubine De here.
Summon Concubine De!
Greetings to Your Majesty.
Is what Prince Zhao
said true?
All he said is true.
This is...
Quiet!
Your Majesty.
What Concubine De committed
is unforgivable.
I think Concubine De
should be given death penalty.
And Prince Zhao
should be abolished
and driven out of the Palace.
Counselor Pang
should be dismissed and exiled.
No.
Your Majesty.
Prince Zhao exposed Concubine De’s crimes,
he has made amends.
As for the crimes of Concubine De,
we need to investigate carefully.
We can’t wrong her
or let her get away from the punishment.
Therefore, I think
Concubine De should be imprisoned
in Court of the Imperial Clan.
We can convict her later.
Pass on my order.
Imprison Concubine De
and the rest of her henchmen immediately
and confiscate their property.
Abolish Prince Zhao as common people.
Imprison Counselor Pang
in Court of Judicial Review.
Close down Pang’s Mansion.
The Crown Prince will handle it.
Yes, Father.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
= Forever Love By Emperor Daizong =
Are you here to laugh at me?
Listen.
His Majesty won’t kill me.
Even if I die
and there is only a skeleton left,
I’m still more prominent
and noble than
you two bastards.
Did you kill my master?
What does
the fancy carp mean?
I have killed countless people.
If you want me to make a list,
I’m afraid I can’t finish it
within ten days and ten nights.
Yes.
I killed them all.
So what?
You killed His Majesty’s
beloved Cui and Dugu.
You also want to
pull the Crown Prince down.
But Princess Huayang was so young,
how could you do it?
You did all the bad things,
aren’t you not guilty at all?
Can you still fall asleep?
Are you not afraid of harming
the happiness of your future generations?
If I’m not living well,
nobody will!
I know
I was never
the most important person for His Majesty.
But it does not matter.
I knew it clearly.
Do you know what you need
to live beautifully
in the Palace?
You need power!
With power,
our Pang family can enjoy wealth forever.
But you guys
have to fight against me.
And you
seduce my Zhao.
You should be killed!
You should all be killed!
Kill!
Kill you all!
= Deceased Mother
Spirit Tablet of Lady Cui =
Her Grace can finally rest in peace.
Mother.
You must have blessed me in heaven.
Your grievances finally come to light.
But it’s too long ago
and we couldn’t find your bones
and bury you well.
Today, I swear in front of your spirit.
I will only
marry Long
and take care of her forever.
I will never fail her.
When will we return to Silver City?
We should pay homage to your master
and let her rest in peace.
No.
It’s not that simple.
It doesn’t look like
Concubine De knows the fancy carp.
She didn’t have any response
when she heard my master’s name.
My master won’t say
meaningless words to me,
and won’t leave me useless clues.
Would it be that Concubine De
killed too many people and forgot it
as she said?
So I used words to make her talk.
She knows clearly about
your mother, the late empress
and the Princess.
But she didn’t mention
a word about my master.
And it’s only half a year,
it’s impossible that she forgot it.
I think
there must be something that
we don’t know.
But who would that person be?
Are you satisfied now?
Long Aoyi must think
I am the murderer who killed her master.
This is what you should do.
It has been a mutually beneficial
relationship for us.
Your Pang family do things for me,
I help you make Prince Zhao
ascend the throne.
Didn’t the Pang family do enough
for you?
You control Du Changfeng
and the Ministry of War.
My brother and I
have done countless
illegal things for you.
But once something goes wrong,
you just push us out.
Prime Minister,
you do play the cards well.
Your Grace, you told me
you have taken care of these things.
= The lips should be able
to take back the food. =
It was found when they
searched your residence.
Fortunately, two minions found it.
What to do with them?
Do you need me to teach you?
You broke the rules first.
Your Highness.
Why are you sitting on the ground?
Don’t catch a cold.
Your Highness, eat something.
You didn’t have anything
in the last three days.
You...
What if your health is harmed?
I met Eunuch Zhai
from Prime Minister’s Mansion
on my way here.
He asked you to clean up
after you have the meal
and go to see Concubine De.
If you lie to me,
I won’t spare you when I am a ghost.
Don’t worry, Your Grace.
Only when you die,
will His Majesty
wipe out the crimes of you and Prince Zhao
for the sake of his feelings for you.
And then I can
help Prince Zhao ascend the throne.
Your Grace, you have to think about
what to say and
what not to say later.
Prince Zhao’s safety
depends on your mouth.
Rest assured.
I know how to do.
Mother!
Prime Minister, thank you for
letting us see each other!
Sorry, Mother!
Zhao, come here.
Mother.
In the Palace, the mother’s honor
increases as her son’s position rises.
If you don’t give me out,
you will get yourself in trouble
and get yourself killed.
Besides,
I forced you to do it.
Zhao.
You are a good boy.
You are brilliant
and courageous.
Unfortunately,
you are too soft-hearted.
It’s my fault.
I should have made Li Qingliu...
You won’t end up like this.
Now I understand it.
I understand the efforts
you and Uncle made.
I know my fault.
You must remember my words.
Now,
either he dies or you die.
You can’t be indecisive,
generous,
or show mercy to
Long Aoyi and Li Qingliu.
I...
Prince Zhao.
Her Grace is investigated
because Long Aoyi set a trap.
But why would she
be so cruel
about my mother?
Who else but Li Qingliu?
Right now, only Prime Minister
can save you
and bring down Li Qingliu.
Zhao.
You can’t act rashly now.
You have to
listen to Prime Minster.
I...
Mother... I...
Come here.
Let me take a good look at you.
You lost so much weight
in these days.
Mother!
Mother, what’s wrong with you?
Physician!
It’s too late.
Prince Zhao.
Her Grace gives up her life for you.
That’s all because of Long Aoyi
and Prince Jun.
You must never
fail her again.
Mother.
Your grandfather gave it to me
when I got married.
He hoped your uncle and I
can achieve something in the Palace
and keep making our
Pang family strong.
Now I give it to you.
From now on,
this hairpin is like me.
Zhao.
Promise me
you will revenge for me.
You have to swear to me.
Mother.
I swear
Li Qingliu will die.
And also,
Long Aoyi.
This is my good Zhao.
Mother.
Mother!
I heard last night
there were officials of
Court of Judicial Review
gathering outside Concubine De’s palace.
Decree from His Majesty,
Concubine De died last night.
The morning court is canceled,
please go back.
= Tang rules all the land =
Greetings to Father.
Qingliu, you are here.
Come here.
These beautiful
lands in front of you
are all mine.
They all think
becoming my woman
will assure them of
a lifetime of prosperity
and being respected.
But do you think
they are happy?
When your mother Zhenzhu died,
I was not by her side.
Now Concubine De is dead,
I was not by her side, either.
Will they blame me?
Father.
They are gone. Please don’t be sad.
Sad?
You don’t know.
The Emperor is passionate
but also fickle.
Now I have
made an explanation to your mother.
I guess she won’t
blame me
when we meet again.
= Prince Zhao’s Mansion =
They are all swayed easily by the wind.
They only see advantages
and avoid disadvantages.
Except for the Prime Minister,
those courtiers
all rush to deal with
those poisonous papers
for the Crown Prince.
Or they get together around Prince Jun!
When the dragon leaves water,
even ants can step on it.
Aren’t all the people
in the Palace like that?
Only you
are still by my side.
Prince Zhao.
Master Long?
Lady Long.
What are you doing here?
I want to talk to Prince Zhao in private.
Please excuse us for a second.
Where is he?
Why doesn’t he come with you?
Is he satisfied now?
I am worried about you.
Qingliu is also shocked by
the death of Concubine De.
Shocked.
The criminal Concubine De was malicious
and killed his mother.
Isn’t he angry? Doesn’t he blame me?
What Concubine De did
has nothing to do with you.
I hope you can
pull yourself together soon.
Are you here to comfort me?
Listen,
I don’t need it.
I want my mother
to be alive by my side.
Not just a cold relic.
How can I not understand your sadness?
That’s how my master died in my arms.
Nothing is permanent in life.
Sorry for your loss.
Go away.
I don’t need your pretense.
I will come to see you later.
By the way,
have you
ever seen any fancy carp
on Concubine De?
What are you doing?
Fancy carp?
You killed my mother
for Li Qingliu.
Now you are here
to ask me for my mother’s relic?
Long Aoyi.
I take you
as my closest person besides my mother.
But you are so cruel to me.
You are such a heartless
and malicious woman.
You misunderstand me.
Let me go! What are you doing?
Is this your child with Li Qingliu?
My master was killed
by someone in the Palace.
Only in this way
can I enter the Palace.
Aoyi.
Promise me,
leave Li Qingliu.
Leave Chang’an.
I will help you find the murderer.
I will avenge you.
All right?
If you insist on staying with Li Qingliu,
I’ll tell Father
about your fake pregnancy!
From now on,
you are no longer
my brother of Longzhu Gang.
Aoyi!
= Prince Jun’s Mansion =
There is still no clue
about the fancy carp pattern.
And Concubine De just died.
It’s not easy to track down
the person behind her.
You mean they threatened Concubine De
in some ways?
But that person is too strong.
It’s always a step ahead of us.
Every time there is any clue,
it would be wiped out cleanly.
That person can make
Concubine De take the fall,
his power must be above Concubine De.
Counselor Pang has lost his power.
Will it be...
Prime Minister?
Prime Minister has been an official
for decades.
He is upright and fair,
he has never been
accused of any wrongdoings.
If it’s him,
he would be too shrewd and deep.
I don’t believe there is any perfect plan
in this world.
I’ll ask Yan Bin to investigate it.
We will find some clues.
Let me see.
Did he hurt you today?
It’s just too much for him to take.
He should be fine after a while.
Will he be desperate and tell...
Don’t you know about
Prince Zhao’s childishness?
Besides, he and my master
are cross-age friends.
Verbal decree of His Majesty.
Long uses her fake pregnancy
to collude with people in the Palace
and form a clique to pursue
her own interest.
Court of Judicial Review
will handle this case.
Take her away.
How dare you!
What should come will come.
Wait for me, I’ll be back soon.
Let’s go.
Don’t drink anymore, Your...
You can’t keep drinking.
Why is there no more wine?
Go buy more wine.
Your Highness, I know you feel sad.
You drank too much.
Let’s go back
and have some sleep.
You will feel better the next morning.
Right?
Leave me alone!
Your Highness.
My mother died!
I don’t have a home!
What are you looking at?
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
I only have my mother.
But I killed her.
God wants to punish me.
Mr. Zhao, be careful.
Mr. Zhao,
let me find a carriage to take you home.
No need.
The lamb tonight
is pretty good.
- It’s him.
- Thanks for your praise.
Mr. Zhao of the Ministry of Penalty.
Go back, go back.
Mr. Zhao.
Go back.
Take care.
What’s wrong?
Your Highness.
Those who hurt my mother...
Your Highness!
Must die!
Your Highness, don’t be impulsive!
Your Highness!
Zhao Jin!
Prince Zhao.
Your Highness, calm down.
Your Highness.
Mercy, Your Highness!
Today
I’ll use your life
to honor my mother!
No!
Well, how is the torture instrument?
We are old acquaintances.
No need to entertain me
with such a big house
and so many gifts.
That’s very kind of you.
With your statues now,
of course I need to do some work.
Since we are old acquaintances,
let’s make it easy.
Sign this paper
= Confession =
and plead guilty.
How can I plead guilty
without knowing my crime?
Admit that you approached Prince Jun
through a fake pregnancy
and attempted to make
the royal blood impure.
You interfere in court affairs
with Qinglong Firm.
What is your plan?
Last time I was accused of collusion.
This time you still
accuse me of collusion.
Du Changfeng.
Is all your head filled with water?
Can’t you think of anything else?
You are making me force it out of you.
Squeeze her fingers.
Mr. Du.
She is the Lady of Prince Jun.
If we put her to torture,
what if...
His Majesty ordered me to
interrogate the criminal strictly!
Yes.
If it’s Prince Jun, I won’t see him.
Let him reflect himself in his mansion.
Your Majesty,
Prince Jun asked me to
present this letter to you in person.
He said there are
many doubts about this case.
= From your son, Qingliu =
He begged you to see it.
Okay, I see. You can leave.
Master.
Will it help with you kneeling here?
Lady will be dead
by then!
Master.
Say something, Master!
♪ I embarked on the journey
when I was young ♪
♪ Now I have experienced everything
and I’m still alone ♪
♪ I ever lost myself and complained ♪
♪ Nobody knows what I have experienced ♪
♪ Clear up the mist and warm the loner ♪
♪ You are smiling like before
in Spring breeze ♪
♪ Time blurs the pain of separation ♪
♪ I’d like to be with you
for the rest of my life ♪
♪ Let’s watch the desert ♪
♪ Let’s watch the misty Spring rain ♪
♪ Let’s watch the secular world ♪
♪ Let’s watch the mountains and roads ♪
♪ Let’s watch ever-changing clouds ♪
♪ Let’s watch blooming
and withering flowers ♪
♪ Let’s watch people missing each other ♪
♪ Let’s watch the boundless sea ♪
♪ Clear up the mist and warm the loner ♪
♪ You are smiling like before
in Spring breeze ♪
♪ Time blurs the pain of separation ♪
♪ I’d like to be with you
for the rest of my life ♪
♪ Let’s watch the desert ♪
♪ Let’s watch the misty Spring rain ♪
♪ Let’s watch the secular world ♪
♪ Let’s watch the boundless sea ♪
♪ Sparks are still shining in your eyes ♪
♪ I look forward to the day
we get together ♪