♪ I chase stars and the Moon ♪
♪ My horse neighs in the snowstorm ♪
♪ I hold up my sword ♪
♪ Cut off my hairs along with my sorrow ♪
♪ The world is vast ♪
♪ In this life of mine ♪
♪ I have taken both paths
of love and hate ♪
♪ A lone wild goose flies in the clouds ♪
♪ The sky in the background is glaring ♪
♪ The heaven and the earth
are all in my heart ♪
♪ A jug of liquor and a spark
are enough for me ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be a good day
full of all kinds of feelings ♪
♪ Like the cloud in the wind ♪
♪ There’s nobody
I can share my life with ♪
♪ Sometimes I owe others
and sometimes they own me ♪
♪ It’s merely a dream ♪
♪ Tomorrow will be a good day
that flies by ♪
♪ I’ll still be tender like yesterday ♪
♪ Running toward that rainbow ♪
♪ And hug you ♪
♪ Come in to the outdoor teahouse
for a cup of tea ♪
♪ My brothers all like things spicy ♪
♪ Hustling and bustling ♪
♪ Mahjong is of course a must ♪
♪ Some stubborn kid
does not listen to advice ♪
♪ He gets up in midnight
to sweep the courtyard ♪
♪ Oh my dear liquor jar ♪
♪ Fill up my cup ♪
♪ And let’s drink ♪
= Overlord =
= Episode 7 =
Take a coin.
You and I each pick one side.
Drop the coin vertically into the water.
The person whose side faces up
when the coin falls
to the bottom will win.
That’s fair.
Step aside.
May I ask this is...
Master of Longzhu Gang, Long Aoyi.
Right now I am the
personal maid of Master Li.
My job is sweeping the floor.
Sorry for making you laugh.
Interesting.
They have a study partner.
Master Li has a gambling partner.
That’s all right.
Pick your side and make a bet.
There are no rules for
this kind of gamble.
You can’t cheat either.
How much do you want to bet?
I don’t need you here. Go back.
Gamble without me,
do you have confidence to win?
Do you?
Make the biggest bet
you can afford
to scare Mr. Shen away.
Only in this way can you get what you want
without actual winning or losing.
Let’s be decisive.
How much?
The biggest.
To show my sincerity,
I’ll bet the deed of my Silk Manor.
Well...
Yan Bin.
The deed?
= Deed =
That’s a big bet.
- That’s too much.
- Deed...
Look.
Bet once and bet the biggest.
Master Li is generous indeed.
I like it.
But
I didn’t bring
anything valuing that much.
How about
I write down my deed in Jiangnan
as my bet?
You mustn’t do that.
Your deed in Jiangnan
is more valuable than mine in Silver City.
Then I’ll raise you one-year selling right
of my three stores in Silver City.
Well...
- How do you want to raise?
- One-year selling right...
Well...
I...
I’ll have to bet my
Silk Store in Jiangnan.
Mr. Shen.
You mustn’t do that.
This old man can’t take
such a fierce bet from Li Qingliu.
With one more straw,
he will crack.
You two must think it through.
Once the coin falls into the water,
the loser
will lose all his property.
Are you sure about that?
We bet on the head side.
Place your bet.
Sir, you can drop the coin anytime.
Stop!
You have shown me
your sincerity.
I’ll take you as my friend.
As for the contract,
we can sign it later.
About this gamble...
Just forget it.
That’s not having fun.
This is risking life.
You are making fun of me.
Wait!
Send Master Long back
with my sedan chair.
Never mind.
A bullock cart is better
than a sedan chair.
I can’t ride a horse.
The Cui Yingying played by Gengzi
= Dock =
is really like our master.
They are basically the same person.
Gengzi, we are talking about you.
In the Yingying Liuyao yesterday,
you played two roles.
Goodness!
Go away.
You are a big mouth.
The Cui Yingying you played
is really like our master.
Do you have a crush on her?
Bring me the soil cutter.
- Shave his lanugo!
- Come on...
Shave his hair!
Do it, don’t just talk about it!
Master!
Master is here.
Greetings to Master!
Thank you for tiding Silk Manor over.
I’ll drink three bowls of liquor.
Master.
Master drinks like a fish!
Bravo!
I will still be busy for some time.
You know the drill.
If anything happens,
just go to Second Master Lyu.
If you have to see me,
you can go to Xiaoqin
and wait for your turn.
Yes, Master!
Master, what are you busy with?
Master, please ascend to the seat.
Please.
Everyone, please have a seat.
We need to follow the rules.
But we can also change the rules.
Since you chose to follow me,
you have to stick to my rules.
Inform other brothers in the gang
that from tomorrow,
the oblong table discussion
of the twelve districts of Longzhu Gang
will be changed to
square table discussion.
On the square table,
there is no chairman, no status.
We welcome equal discussion.
Everyone can speak up freely.
I’ll sit here today.
Chef, serve the main dishes!
Everyone, it’s time to eat!
Let’s eat!
Thank you, Master!
- Thank you, Master!
- Pour the liquor.
Come on.
- In terms of beauty and decisiveness,
- Fill the cup.
Master is ten times better
than Cui Yingying!
Of course!
Come on.
To Master.
Come on, you guys.
Let’s drink!
To Master!
Be careful.
You can move it away.
Shuisheng.
Move this away, too.
Were you scolded again?
No, sister.
Today I should withdraw
the wages previously deposited.
Deduction of wages?
No, sister.
We have an internal bank
where we can deposit
our spare wages.
The interest is 30% of the principal.
30%?
You can get three pennies
with ten pennies,
thirty pennies with one hundred pennies.
A tael of silver...
But it’s only open for
internal stuff
to retain workers
who might be lured elsewhere.
No wonder
he always acts like a dork.
It turns out that
he puts all his efforts on this.
Chubby. Stop chatting, come to work.
Hurry up.
Coming.
Master.
Let me ask you one more time.
This is all the money
of Longzhu Gang.
Master, is it really reliable?
Rest assured.
Li Qingliu is a vicious man,
but I have to admit
he is something in business.
Perhaps we should learn from him
about how to make money.
Have you changed it into bank note?
It’s a total of
fifty-three thousand taels.
Master.
Aren’t we
looting a burning house?
There is no better time
to extort money
from Li Qingliu.
Xiaoqin.
Listen, I did the math.
With that interest,
we will have the money
to start a small business
three months later.
Half a year later,
we can buy each brother
an acre of land.
Maybe a few more years later,
I can buy the Silk Manor
and make Li Qingliu
become my prisoner.
I’ll let him serve tea for me.
No.
I’ll let him bring me water
to wash my feet.
These are
semi-finished products
because of the lack of accessories
like flower embroidery, beading
and leather edging.
Everyone, hurry up about it.
Hope we can sell them early.
Chubby.
How’s your relationship with me?
But in case...
If I lose the money,
I’ll accept the result.
I won’t blame you.
Okay.
I know you won’t reject me.
Master.
You are slacking again.
Come with me.
Is this the box for gold thread?
It’s too small.
How much can it take?
A strand of gold thread
is as thin as a hair.
But the price is
twenty times higher
than the pure gold of the same amount.
The box is intact.
The brass lock is not broken.
But the stuff inside is gone.
I guess
someone copied the key
and unlocked the box.
But I always feel
there is something being overlooked.
That’s why
we haven’t found any clues.
Don’t underestimate
the skill of unlocking.
It has different schools.
You mean
there is a secret technique
that ordinary people don’t know?
So are you
begging me?
You tore off my post
but made no progress so far.
With your efficiency,
you would have been
kicked out long ago.
I think of someone.
Mr. Tan. Mr. Tan!
Mr. Tan!
= Toad Brew =
Toad brew of five years.
I was wondering who it is.
You are a master now,
you must’ve forgotten your
drinking buddy long ago.
Sorry, Mr. Tan.
The former master abdicated,
leaving too many affairs for me.
Today I am here
to pay my filial duties.
Go ahead.
What’s bothering you?
I can’t hide anything from you,
Mr. Tan.
The toad brew
is your stingy master’s favorite.
I asked her for it several times,
but she wouldn’t give it to me.
Why is she so generous this time?
A word, please.
An inch of rosewood with an inch of gold.
Boy, this is a treasure.
Don’t miss the point.
Look at the lock on it.
Little girl.
Who is this fine-skinned boy?
I’m Li Qingliu from Xinsilu.
Sounds like a girl’s name.
I mean, little girl,
you two should change your names.
I’m just saying it.
Don’t take it personally.
The name is like the lock.
Also like a young bird,
once you open it,
the sound would be different.
Interesting.
But this lock
has been opened only once.
- What?
When Li Jun’er opened it,
it was the first time.
How is that possible?
Well, look.
There is no nail in this box.
It’s well sealed.
Someone used some skill
to rotate in the middle
and opened it without
picking or unlocking the lock.
Then he took it out and closed the box.
You mean
the stuff inside can be taken out
without unlocking the lock?
Do you know who masters this skill?
It comes from Lingnan
and remains a secret.
Even I
don’t know the trick.
Do you know
where I can find the carpenter in Lingnan?
I’ve never seen that person before.
This skill
is all about mastering your fingertip.
It is said if one practices it
for a long time,
the finger will bend
like a crouching tiger.
I knew you wouldn’t let me down!
Sir.
This is five hundred taels.
If we find the gold thread,
I will pay good money to you.
Little girl.
You picked an eligible boyfriend!
No.
Tell him
I won’t take the money.
But if you
get married someday, don’t forget to
prepare a large jar
of toad brew for me!
You are doing it again.
Don’t match me up
with any random guy.
Well, haven’t you taken him down yet?
Let me teach you one trick.
As long as you two sleep in one bed,
even the enemy
would become family.
I said it’s not like that.
I feel sleepy again.
I’m sleepy!
Who is any random guy?
Hurry up.
Serve the good stuff!
There is a chicken
in the belly of the sheep.
Is this
the stuffed mutton of legend?
But at this time,
Master Li is...
Don’t worry. I checked it.
Li Qingliu and Yan Bin
won’t come here at this time.
Thank you for your care
during these days.
I am a person who
would share my wealth
with my friends.
Please enjoy the dinner
of liquor and meat tonight.
Thank you!
Level and vertical, stick to the rules.
Level and vertical, stick to the rules!
Come on!
Let’s make a circle.
Come here.
- Come on.
Hold hands.
Tonight,
I’ll teach you a dance of Guo Manor.
When we danced at Guo Manor,
we would hold hands
and interlock the fingers.
Come on.
Let’s go round!
Let’s go round! Come on!
Come on.
That’s interesting.
They can touch hands in public this way.
Go round!
What’s wrong, Master Long?
- But...
- It’s okay.
If we go up there and touch their hands,
we can see it more clearly.
When we danced at Guo Manor,
if I were a man,
and I had a crush on a girl,
I would pick her palm like this.
If she agreed,
she would pick my palm back.
But if she rejected me,
it wouldn’t be awkward
because she didn’t know it.
Go to Chubby. Hurry up!
That’s kind of interesting.
Come on.
Pick palm...
Master.
Come on.
Next time you...
It’s not the time for joke.
Watch their hands.
Let’s go round!
Yes.
Come over.
No one has bent finger. One, two, three.
No, there’s one missing.
Where is Dongzi?
He said he would come later.
He had a run and went to the latrine.
Go on.
Come on.
Come on!
He’s is not here?
It was an excuse. Let’s go.
= Righteous Spirit =
Silk Manor’s Dongzi disappeared last night.
We can’t get in touch with him.
Well...
Can’t get in touch with our undercover?
I don’t believe it!
On one can make trouble
for us in Silver City!
Master Qiyan, if we can’t reach him,
why don’t we just give him up?
Are you stupid?
He has the gold thread.
If we can’t reach him,
our efforts would be wasted!
Give him up?
He can pierce through the sky
with his mouth!
Listen,
if anything goes wrong
with the gold thread,
I will use you to fix the hole!
Dongzi stayed out all night.
Seems that there is something wrong.
Does he live alone in this single room?
Yes.
The supervisors from other cities
all live in a single room.
He is too poor.
He only has a pair of ragged socks.
Do you deduct wages?
Dongzi is in charge of
the accounts of shipment.
His salary is higher than others.
What is going on then?
Did he use all the money
to drink and please girls?
That’s impossible.
I never saw him
in Wuyun Pavilion before.
The bed is a mess.
But strangely, it is cleaner than others.
What are you doing?
There must be a trick about the bed.
Lie here, too.
Why?
Here is a clue. Believe me. Come on.
Rest assured.
I won’t sleep with you even
I want to have an eligible boyfriend.
I would rather sleep with Xiaozhao.
Xiaozhao…
Hurry up.
Come on.
What’s going on?
Don’t look.
Don’t look. Don’t look!
Go away. Go away!
Get up!
It is a smoke screen.
What is this?
The name of a black gold shop
in the Southern City.
Black gold shop.
There should be a name tag.
Where is the name tag?
Looks like he deposited the money
at that place.
He didn’t deposit the money at our bank.
He had to went through the trouble
and went somewhere else.
No, it’s not like that.
This black gold shop
is not like other banks
or pawnshops.
Not a ray of sunshine
in the broad daylight
or a drop of rain can get into that place.
It’s not hot in summer without using ice.
It’s neither cold in a snowy day
without setting fire.
It’s amazing,
just like Arcadia.
You mean
it’s warm in winter and cool in summer,
with constant temperature in four seasons?
That sounds right.
The spring is coming,
the gold thread is pure.
If you don’t weave it or dye it in time,
it would be oxidized rapidly by heat.
Unless you...
Keep it under thermostatic preservation!
I see.
Working with guys like you
is like working by myself.
If anything happens,
I have to take care of it all by myself.
All by myself.
Wonderful.
How did you feel, sir?
Why didn’t you bring Yan Bin out today?
It would attract unnecessary attention
with too many people.
Who will pay attention to you?
What about your maid?
Xiaoqin is my sister.
You might as well ask Yan Bin
instead of asking me.
What do you mean?
Yan Bin grew up with me since childhood.
His taste
won’t be that bad.
What do you mean by that?
My Xiaoqin doesn’t deserve that fool?
Watch your words.
Your words are not that nice, either.
The girls of Longzhu Gang
are reckless and know no rules.
The three obediences and four virtues,
you have nothing.
Xiaoqin is not a good match for Yan Bin.
What is a good match?
You’re still thinking about
the eligible boyfriend
Mr. Tan talked about?
I told you
no one wants your Silk Manor,
and no one likes
you two idiots.
You...
I...
They’re just two idiots!
They never take me when they go out.
Why do you blame our girl?
Let’s drink.
Have a taste.
I remember one thing.
Today I saw
the two of them
doing that
in bed.
Doing what?
I don’t know. But I feel like
your Master Long
was seducing our master.
She seduced your master?
Are you blind?
Sit down.
Really.
But the problem is
our master can’t touch any girl.
It must be Master Long
who took the initiative.
Well...
How did she take the initiative?
Let me think.
It should be...
Like this.
Hey!
Do you know the way or not?
Do you think the entrance to the
black gold shop is that easy to find?
Go ahead if you can find it.
Here we are. The entrance.
Deposit or withdraw?
- Deposit.
- Withdraw.
Deposit or withdraw?
- Deposit.
- Withdraw.
Deposit or withdraw?
Withdraw.
Time, name and your card.
Deposit, we want to deposit.
Well, still in the old box.
Name.
Dongzi, D-O-N-G-Z-I.
There’s already a Dongzi inside.
Why is there another Dongzi?
This is a whole crate of pepper?
Forget about it. Let’s go.
Over there!
How did you get on the roof?
No time for talking. Chase him!
Dongzi, don’t run!
Don’t come over!
Don’t force me.
You are all forcing me!
Have you ever thought about me?
Who forced you?
Give me the gold thread.
You won’t say it, I won’t say it,
he won’t say it.
No one would know it.
No one would do anything to you.
They won’t let me go.
I have no way out.
Dongzi, come down first.
Let’s talk.
Master, sorry!
It’s not that simple.
Otherwise I wouldn’t have
ended up like this.
I’m afraid. I’ve regretted!
I know you have your reason
to do that.
How much money do you need?
Come down first. I’ll give it to you.
You can pay me back later.
Don’t come over!
If you come over, I will...
I...
I’ll destroy all the gold thread!
Let’s talk.
Dongzi.
If you give me the gold thread,
I promise Li Qingliu and I
won’t do anything bad to you.
Or let’s die together!
Put me down! Dongzi is running away!
Dongzi!
He is dead.
Now Dongzi is dead,
we lost the clue of the gold thread again.
Gold thread.
It’s such an unlucky day.
I have to take this drunk home.
Pour me another drink.
I can still drink.
= Xinsilu =
Get up! Get up!
Hey!
= Xinsilu =
Is anyone there? Open the door!
Open the door!
Get up!
Is that you, Junjun?
Don’t leave me.
I missed you so much.
Hey!
Councilors.
Let me tell you something.
When I was poor,
I really liked an ancient sword.
Now I miss it very much.
Can you help me find it?
Isn’t that the story of Liu Xun and
the Empress Xu Pingjun?
Now I miss it very much.
Don’t leave me, Junjun.
This is my favorite story.
First it was Dachun, now it is Dongzi.
We’ve found the gold thread,
but those who are related to it all died.
If he needed money,
stealing the gold thread was too obvious.
Besides, there are so many
valuable things in the Silk Manor.
He wouldn’t be so stupid.
I’ve clearly drawn a line
and told you to stay away from me
at least for three feet.
You don’t listen to me
and pull rank on me.
= Xinsilu =
Actually, I have something else
to tell you.
I have a crush on you.
How is it possible?
I would have passed out in the past.
It’s not reasonable.
Master.
What’s wrong with you?
= Unforgettable Love =
Unforgettable...
Yan Bin.
Let me ask you something.
I have an old friend. Yesterday...
Old friend?
I don’t think you have other friends
but me.
I mean yesterday,
I saw a little girl in danger,
and I held her in my arms
under circumstances beyond control.
But...
I didn’t have the reaction I used to have.
Held her in your arms?
A little girl?
Well...
You didn’t have any reaction?
Isn’t that strange?
This is not that strange.
The small kids can’t tell the difference
between men and women.
Well...
What if she is older?
How old?
Like Nanny?
Younger.
Well...
Younger,
just like Master Long.
What are you talking about?
Of marriageable age.
It’s the right time
to get married.
It means you have a crush on her.
♪ I embarked on the journey
when I was young ♪
♪ Now I have experienced everything
and I’m still alone ♪
♪ I ever lost myself and complained ♪
♪ Nobody knows what I have experienced ♪
♪ Clear up the mist and warm the loner ♪
♪ You are smiling like before
in Spring breeze ♪
♪ Time blurs the pain of separation ♪
♪ I’d like to be with you
for the rest of my life ♪
♪ Let’s watch the desert ♪
♪ Let’s watch the misty Spring rain ♪
♪ Let’s watch the secular world ♪
♪ Let’s watch the mountains and roads ♪
♪ Let’s watch ever-changing clouds ♪
♪ Let’s watch blooming
and withering flowers ♪
♪ Let’s watch people missing each other ♪
♪ Let’s watch the boundless sea ♪
♪ Clear up the mist and warm the loner ♪
♪ You are smiling like before
in Spring breeze ♪
♪ Time blurs the pain of separation ♪
♪ I’d like to be with you
for the rest of my life ♪
♪ Let’s watch the desert ♪
♪ Let’s watch the misty Spring rain ♪
♪ Let’s watch the secular world ♪
♪ Let’s watch the boundless sea ♪
♪ Sparks are still shining in your eyes ♪
♪ I look forward to the day
we get together ♪