Your Highness.
Yes.
It's me.
Did you see it clearly?
Evidence and evidence.
They are all here.
What do you want me to do?
You're smart.
First,
I want you to take out half of the silver in the treasury
to repair the ancestral temple for the late emperor.
Second,
I'm very comfortable as the Empress Dowager.
I don't mean to abdicate.
Understand?
What?
Don’t you understand me?
I understand.
As long as you finish what I told you to do,
I will pretend
what you did.
If you fail,
even without evidence,
I'll kill you.
to kill you.
I understand.
Your Majesty, please allow me to report.
I'm ashamed.
Last night, I dreamed
the late emperor told me
about the renovation of the ancestral temple.
he was very pleased.
May I ask Your Majesty
to ask Your Majesty to repair the ancestral temple for the late emperor
to comfort the late emperor.
Since the late emperor came to my dream,
it's my duty.
I will immediately
to repair the ancestral temple.
Although the treasury is not rich,
it can't make His Majesty criticized by his descendants.
I second it.
I agree.
Mr. Wen Hua is indeed the most respected person of the late emperor.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
My apologies.
Leave the renovation to the Imperial Astronomy Bureau.
Yes, Your Majesty.
One more thing.
I want to make Ji Mingyue the empress.
Please pick an auspicious date too.
You mean the Empress Dowager?
Yes.
Please don't, Your Majesty.
This is against the ethics.
Please think twice, Your Majesty.
I second it.
Those bastards.
I clearly informed them two days ago.
They should have agreed today.
How dare you
and disobeyed me.
Something is wrong.
Please think twice, Your Majesty.
He Lian Jin.
How long do you think you can be arrogant?
Court adjourned.
Go.
Send a message to He Lian Cheng.
If he still hesitates,
and doesn't want to fall out with He Lian Jin,
I'll change to someone who listens to me.
Yes.
I'll go now.
Everything is ready, except the East Wind.
Ji Hong Zhen.
Don't let me down.
I miss you so much.
You didn't even call me after returning to the capital.
I'm busy.
I don't have much time left.
I'm destined not to be with him in this life.
Since we've expressed our feelings,
I should make him happy.
If I don't see you,
you can come to see me.
Junior general is unparalleled.
Of course you can come and go freely in the palace.
Lord Huo.
Her Highness summoned me.
Please inform her.
Her Highness is taking a nap.
It's fine.
I'll do it later.
There are so many talented people in the court.
Why must you praise Huo Lingyu?
You're too capable to be greedy.
with high moral sense.
Loyalty and gentleman.
Who knows if he's ambitious or low?
What?
Well,
why did you summon him today?
I have something to discuss with you.
We received news from the Empress Dowager.
General He Lian went to Her Majesty's chamber two hours ago.
and hasn't come out yet.
Why didn't you report it earlier?
I deserve to die!
Bitch!
Since you can't live without a man,
I'll let you sleep with him tonight.
Pass my order.
Seal the Empress Dowager's chamber.
As a woman,
I believe I can punish you.
Yes.
I'm on it.
A letter from Yanhua Palace
Even the people of the Heavenly Camp
can't save her for a while.
The Heavenly Force doesn't only acknowledge the Shen family.
When you become my woman,
and give birth to my child,
Everything of the Shen family
belongs to the Ji royal family.
General He Lian is here early.
Not early.
I'm here to report the latest secret report to Her Highness.
I sneaked into the palace.
I just came here.
Just like
Look at your eyes.
Your eyebrows are too light
Only the nose is okay.
Weak figure
and looks ordinary.
General He Lian has been staring at me.
Is there anything wrong with my outfit today?
Nothing.
Lord Huo's clothes are too thin.
I'm worried that your salary is not enough.
JeoTE.
General He Lian, you must be joking.
Besides what we just talked about,
there's another big thing.
Lord Huo.
Change the dynasty.
you will be promoted by the law.
I will arrange for you to take the exam.
The gentry are poor.
and selected a group of scholars.
Fortunately, after we clean up the court,
after we cleared the court.
I thank you on behalf of all the scholars.
You must solve the question well
and choose a capable official
who can work for the people and the people.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The future candidates
are all your disciples.
Lord Huo, the Empress Dowager paved the way for you at such a young age.
You're really lucky.
If there's nothing else, you may leave.
As for Ji Hong Zhen,
we'll wait for the moment he can't hold back.
General He Lian, please wait.
It's fine when I was in the North.
We're in the palace now.
You don't have to care about your reputation.
but please
think more about Her Highness.
Huo Ling Yu.
Do you know why I lost?
You are indeed a gentleman.
What brings you here
at this hour?
I miss you so much.
I can't wait any longer.
Do you know what you are talking about?
Mother is very resourceful.
Of course she knows that I want to make you the empress.
You're the one who made the officials oppose.
Liao is not a barbarian place.
The concubines never say that their father died.
Since all the ministers refused,
it means it's inappropriate.
Your Majesty should have given up on this delusion long ago.
I am the emperor.
In this world,
is the land of the king.
and lead the land
Are you a minister?
All women in the harem belong to me.
Including you.
Mother.
You always know that I like you.
In the future,
in the future?
Why do you have to resist?
Ji Hongzhen, do you really like me?
No.
You just can't accept it.
Your life is too smooth.
You were born to be the Crown Prince.
I'm inferior to him.
above all.
A great man.
Servants.
No one dares to disobey you.
You think highly of yourself.
So,
you can't accept my rejection.
That's why you always want me.
These are not important.
What matters is you've lost your magic.
You're no match for me.
A tyrant is forcing the bow.
It's not fun.
Ji Hong Zhen.
Do you know why I don't like you?
Because you're not only arrogant,
and weak.
You're a greenhouse flower under a rich roof.
You came from a noble family,
but you're still a pitiful bug waiting for others to arrange.
You dare not defy your father,
or your ministers.
You are self-abased.
Ji Hong Zhen, do you think you are the emperor?
In fact,
you were just a puppet.
Shut up!
Ji Hong Zhen was disrespectful
and forced me.
Please seek justice for me.
General He Lian, please do me justice.
Your Majesty, you are confused.
The late emperor just died.
His Majesty forced Empress Dowager
You are...
You don't even care about courtesy and shame.
Mother, are you trying to slander me?