Act.
Fang Shuai.
Mother.
Are you trying to slander me?
I'm here today
to discuss the renovation of the ancestral temple with my mother.
She wanted to hurt herself because of her heart disease.
I accidentally hurt my eyes.
I was kind enough to check.
but I was stripped of such a big hat.
What a joke.
You...
Ah!
I offended you.
Do you have any proof that I hurt my mother?
But the wound on my face can't be fake.
Also,
you didn't summon me
in the middle of the night.
Are you trying to rebel?
You mean...
In order to frame you,
to frame you.
Really?
She has lost her magic.
She lost the eagle eye of the Shen family long ago.
and slandered me.
It's reasonable.
I'll say it again.
Do you have any evidence
that I hurt my mother?
As you can see,
When we came in,
there were Imperial Guards outside Yanhua Palace.
If it weren't for General He Lian's mastery,
and stopped them,
How can we get in?
Outside the Yanhua Palace,
are all Your Majesty's soldiers.
Before the Empress Dowager slanders you,
before she slanders you?
and your soldiers
to stop her?
What do you mean
to gather at Yanhua Palace?
You also said that I lost all my magic.
I must have a way to protect myself.
You've been coveting me for years.
In order to get me,
to get me.
I'm scared.
Go.
Bring the witness here.
I shall take my leave.
Your Highness.
Tell me what you saw and heard.
It's time to let you know
what the new emperor
is a traitor who killed his father.
Zhao Zhongliang is my godfather.
He takes good care of me.
He often asked me to do some relaxing work.
Two days before His Majesty's funeral,
I was working in His Majesty's chamber.
His Majesty summoned the Crown Prince that night.
and left.
I was dozing off in the corner
I was trapped behind the screen.
His Majesty blamed the Crown Prince for rebellion.
The Crown Prince pleaded guilty
and then killed His Majesty.
I was scared.
so I took a leave.
There will be news of His Majesty's funeral in two days.
and the death of my godfather.
Who are you?
How dare you bite the emperor?
How many heads do you have?
Ji Hong Zhen.
Not only did you kill your father,
but also colluded with Baili Jinghong
and corrupted the law.
The evidence is solid.
The ledgers of the gold corruption case are all here.
I didn't want to kill so many people.
But you all came here.
Then die!
Guards!
Where are they?
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
The North Army didn't fail the mission.
The Imperial Guards in the city have surrendered.
Got it.
You may leave.
Yes.
Ji Hong Zhen.
Her Majesty has long known your crime.
She has secretly deployed elite soldiers from the North to the capital
to control all of you.
Your Highness.
This matter is very important.
We have to hand it over to the Three Ducal Ministries.
Now,
Please
stop struggling.
Surrender.
Please surrender.
Stop struggling.
What can you get
What can you get?
If 9th Brother becomes the emperor, you'll be the regent.
is no different from being my empress.
Ji Mingyue, what do you want?
And you.
You are all deceived by her.
I have the edict of His Majesty.
Tomorrow morning,
to the public tomorrow morning.
I won't bother you.
Guards!
Take her down.
You foolish subjects have been tricked by her.
Today,
for your help today.
Thank you very much.
It's late.
Please go back and rest.
We shall take our leave.
Lunar.
Your eyes...
What's wrong?
You don't like it because you're blind?
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Mr. Wenhua,
You were the late emperor's teacher.
You are most familiar with the handwriting of the late emperor.
You will read the edict.
By God's will, the emperor summoned
I'm in charge of the state.
I'm diligent in governing and never tired.
As an old man,
deeply felt that my life would not last long.
So I left this edict.
The love of the Zi family
will get tired.
The Crown Prince is eccentric.
He can't be adopted.
The moon of the Lady of the Moonlight
to inherit the throne.
The youngest son, Ji Hongjian, will be the Crown Prince.
Respect this.
Here comes His Majesty.
Long live Your Majesty!
Long live the Crown Prince!
What is this?
The Demon Queen has ascended the throne.
How can a woman be the emperor?
Isn't this a dream?
Other than the capital,
other people are starving to death.
Who cares who is the emperor?
This demon queen has done many evil things.
and shameless.
I heard that when she was in the North,
she took off her clothes
to please Baili Jinghong
dancing in public.
Don't talk nonsense.
If you are so capable,
Why don't you become the emperor?
If you keep fooling around,
I'll kill you!
Why are they fighting?
Stop fighting!
Stop!
Get out of the way!
Release!
I'm going to have a baby soon.
I can live my life.
I can guarantee the future.
will be sent to hide one for painting.
I have been living in my chest for a long time.
The people, the people, the people, and the paintings.
Come on.
I'm in the class now.
Great!
The proctor is the new Grand Secretary of Hanlin Academy, Huo Lingyu.
[He shall be punished by the law.] The Han Que Academy is in charge of the border.
Sheng Hengdeuk is guilty.
Who is he?
I've never heard of him.
I heard she's the trusted subordinate of the Demon Queen.
A trusted subordinate of the Demon Queen?
The proctor is our future teacher.
Why did you choose such a legendary
Could it be a good-for-nothing fool?
I don't know.
Don't talk nonsense.
The country is in great trouble.
Yes.
He just
who was favored by serving the empress
and got promoted to fifth rank.
and became a Grand Secretariat.
A person like him
is a disgrace.
Impossible.
Do you have anything else to report?
Fine.
I have something
to ask you.
Especially Mr. Qian.
What can I do for you, Your Majesty?
How dare you ask me?
You're corrupted.
and occupy the fields.
and molested a decent woman.
and caused her tragic death.
All of them are capital crimes.
Guards, take him away.
Execute him immediately.
and confiscate the whole family.
Your Majesty.
I'm innocent!
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, I'm innocent!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty.
According to the law, the officials above the third rank of our dynasty
should be handed over to the Ministry of Justice.
and be executed after autumn.
I second it.
I agree.
I will hand the evidence
will be handed over to the Ministry of Justice.
If you are wronged,
I'm willing to issue my own decree.
the Ministry of Justice
by the Ministry of Punishments.
Your Majesty,
I, Qian Youqian, have been beheaded.
The innocent is innocent.
I believe that besides money and food,
all of you are clean.
I hate corruption the most.
bully men and women.
and bully others.
I hope you
to rule the world with me.
Long live Your Majesty!
Court adjourned.
Please tell us.
Mr. Wen Hua, are you free today?
Yes.
It's not convenient today. I'll invite you to have tea another day.
Do as planned.
The first one on the list.
Kill!
Yes.
corruption, selling official nobility and bullying civilians.
All these insects
will be counted as one.
From today onwards,
I'll settle the score with them one by one.
Are you sure you won't let Huo Lingyu get involved?
No.
Don't do anything to him
like last time.
I've already paved his way.
Mr. Crown Prince.
I'm a clean student in Han Lin.
The head of a poor family.
The master of the world.
Sometimes I envy him.
You are
to him.
What?
You think I'm not good to you?
It's the best
with you.
A new dream without dust
The road ahead is wrapped with fingerprints
Half smile, half cruel
Half thought and hatred
Love me and me, I'll save it
Wish I could follow me and make up stories
The same illusion
To help those who are devoted
A distant star
A star that plucks the light from afar.