[English subtitles are available]
[Viva Femina]
[Episode 7]
So after that,
I played the piano
just to kill time.
No matter what,
playing the piano
is a bonus for people.
A bonus?
In that case
am I a ten out of ten yet?
Of course not.
Why?
Where am I losing points?
Because when you talked about
your mother,
there seemed to be
some resentment.
No, you misunderstood me.
I have no resentment
towards my mom at all.
In fact, I sometimes
feel really grateful to her.
Because she made me realise
early on, that we're individuals.
We are not the same.
We can have our own ideas
and thoughts.
But we don't need to compromise.
Actually, after spending time with you,
I think
some of your characteristics
are quite similar to her.
You're a little distant
and mysterious.
Ten points deducted for what you just said.
When chatting with women, it's taboo to say
you resemble my mom.
You look like my ex-girlfriend.
I meant the sense of distance
between us.
The sense of distance is not mysterious.
It's a sense of security.
I thought being closer would feel more secure.
Not for people who're like hedgehogs
it isn't.
Do you have spikes?
You'll need to be close enough to find out.
Being close enough
requires courage.
This wine is really good.
Let's go to my house.
Didn't you say you like
drinking at home?
Let's go.
No.
How is the video coming along?
Director Lin.
It's done.
Let me see.
I'm very honored
to be a friend
of Lijia Alliance.
I also recommend it
to more sisters.
Together, let us have...
Pause it.
This won't do.
Your editing...
You can't put the
technical explanations at the back.
It makes us look unprofessional.
Also,
Xia Ling's part is so good.
Shift it forward.
She is influential.
Put it in front of
the part on postpartum therapy.
Hurry.
I just sent this
to Director Kang.
She said it's okay.
And she specifically asked
for those two clips
to be placed away from each other.
Just shift it forward.
I have the final say, not Director Kang.
Where are you?
I'm upstairs.
It's hard to find
this wine that has my mother's name.
I think I'll
give you the whole box.
Remember.
Drink it slowly.
You want me to take the whole box of wine home?
Aren't you going to keep some?
Yes.
Didn't you think it was delicious?
You...
Do you need me to send you home?
I can call a taxi.
Right?
Tell me when you get home then.
Okay.
Be careful.
Remember to take your stuff with you when you get home
and send me a message.
Okay.
Sir, go, quickly.
Hello?
Hey, when are you coming back?
Why?
Nothing.
You didn't go to Xin's
parent teacher meeting today, right?
I wanted to
discuss something with you.
I've been having meetings
all day at the company today.
There are too many things to do.
All kinds of meetings.
I'm really overwhelmed with work.
I still have meetings to attend.
Why don't you go to bed first?
I'll look for you when I'm back.
Bye.
Thank you for today.
Not at all.
I know more
about school stuff.
You two had dinner together?
She insisted on it.
What did you talk about?
Just some nonsense.
By the way,
I told her that
Shen Hang is coming back.
Why did you talk about this with her?
After all, she is Mrs. Shen.
it's not good
to keep these things
from her.
By then,
when the boss is back and living outside,
if you go out every day,
Mrs. Shen will be even more uncomfortable then.
Indeed.
You're so thoughtful.
How many people in the world
can be so
smart and capable like you?
What's wrong?
Are the financing issues
too troubling recently?
You have gray hair now.
You're going too far today.
This is too much?
You're home, right?
Rest early.
Good night.
♫I thought there were too many impossibilities♫
♫So, forget it♫
♫How many times have I turned around and restrained myself♫
I'm home. Good night.
♫Yet I look away♫
♫I thought it's over but at the next moment♫
♫Sparks fly♫
♫I finally see my own and your...♫
♫choices in our hearts♫
What do you think?
My brother is fine over there.
He's fine.
Let me tell you.
Your sister-in-law has given birth.
While we
can still walk,
we should go and take care of her.
Don't mention it.
Didn't you see
the stuff that your aunt brought?
Nappies,
little clothes and little shoes
enough to fill a whole box.
I said
everyone uses diapers now.
Who would use this?
What do you know?
If they run out of diapers
suddenly,
wouldn't this
save the day?
My aunt is always worrying about others.
I saw your Moment.
That kid is very cute.
He's chubby.
-Right? -Right?
Like my brother.
Shan,
do you think
having a child is good?
You know,
as a couple,
having a child
makes it a real home.
Don't blame me for nagging.
I just want to talk to you
from the bottom of my heart.
Women
should have children.
If you give birth earlier,
you can recover well.
If you keep delaying it
until you're in your forties,
you won't be able to give birth.
Yes.
Auntie, does your back still hurt?
My dad told me
he made an appointment
for you with a specialist.
Why didn't you go?
Don't listen to your dad.
He did take care of Ms. Zhao
but he can't let his own
daughter suffer at the expense
of an old colleague.
Recently, I told him
to prepare to
take care of your child.
Guess what he said.
Kids are, what?
Here to collect debts.
See.
Is this what a father should say?
I don't like to hear it.
Let's not care about him.
Shan, tell auntie.
When do you want to have a child?
I haven't thought about it yet.
Do it quickly.
Look.
Zheng already
has a daughter.
But you two don't have children.
Zheng must be
focused on his daughter.
Shan,
don't blame me for being rude.
Some things have to be considered.
I know
you're doing this for my own good.
I'll think about it.
Let's eat.
I ordered so much but you're not eating.
-Come on. -Thank you.
This fish is very good.
Ziyou,
I specially ordered
their signature for you.
You can try it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Shen always mentioned
that the cosmetic medical center
is well-managed
all thanks to you.
Thank you.
It's mainly because
Ms. Lin is a good leader.
I always thought
you're a career woman.
The kind with short hair and professional outfits.
But I didn't expect
to be stunned
meeting you for the first time today.
You're stunned by this?
You're exaggerating.
Ms. Li, why did you
ask to meet me?
Well,
I think you know
the group has always
paid close attention to the cosmetic medicine industry
and hope to achieve breakthroughs
in this sector.
But for now,
there are almost no
professionals in the group.
In the medical center,
there's also no one who understands
the group's vision.
So I hope
to learn more from you
and gain some
professional knowledge.
For basic
professional knowledge,
the internet is really amazing now.
Really.
If you search for stuff online,
it's all there.
And it's very accessible.
Everyone can understand it.
But
for more in-depth knowledge,
you may need to gain it
through experience.
Maybe what you get from that
would be the most real.
If I try to tell it to you now,
I don't think
I can explain anything clearly.
I know.
But to be honest,
I
will be joining the center
as the representative of the group
and will be working with you.
As a rookie,
I would want to find
a great mentor like you
so that I can join the company
more efficiently.
Great.
Our medical center
has been wanting to
share closer ties with the group.
But Mr. Shen is
too busy with his work.
Actually,
he didn't pay much attention
to our medical center previously.
This is
a good opportunity.
Indeed.
It's indeed
a good opportunity.
So, when
you join the company
as the group representative
and we are working together,
I'll report all the details
to you
at that time.
What do you think?
Of course.
It's up to you.
Thank you.
Their pastries are really good.
Right?
Before I knew it,
Lijia Alliance
has been around for ten years.
In the past ten years,
we've been through a lot
and we also had great achievements.
Today,
our clients aren't just distinguished guests,
but also precious family
of Lijia.
Lijia United has always upholded...
Ms. Kang.
People are our priority.
I heard
you left with Dr. Nie yesterday.
Whose gossip are you listening to?
We all know it.
We will use our tenth anniversary
as a new starting point.
We can give old and new customers
the best
cosmetic medical experience.
I'm very honored to be
a friend of
Lijia Alliance.
At the same time,
I also recommend it to my sisters.
[The 10th Anniversary of Lijia Alliance]
[Pelvic floor muscle rehabilitation offer]
Let's have
a better life together.
I sincerely recommend...
Which version is this?
Hello, Chief Editor Liu.
I'm sorry.
The video
from our hospital
has some issues.
Some issues?
It's doing well.
It's exceeded 10,000 views.
Thank you very much
for your promoting our video.
But this is not
the final version.
Yes, so I need you
to remove it first.
Then I'll send you
the final version
as soon as possible.
OK?
The video can be deleted.
But the data on the saves and shares
is very valuable.
And my tech team
has already seen the edited
and shared version.
It's useless to remove it.
It's all over the internet.
Chief Editor,
I have a question.
who sent you this version?
I agreed to release the video.
You agreed?
Why?
What do you mean why?
I think it's good.
That's my decision.
What do you mean?
This has a negative impact
on Xia Ling.
It's the same for
Lijia Alliance.
Haven't you thought about it?
It's my Lijia Alliance.
What are you talking about?
If you don't feel well,
go home and rest.
I'll solve the problem first.
Our biggest problem now
is our sales.
Look at those hospitals.
Those doctors
exposed themselves
and shared which celebrities they did plastic surgery for.
Once it's exposed,
the hospital's business will be great.
We're not even exposing anything.
At most, it was just a hint.
That's all. It's okay.
Could you not have
discussed it with me?
I am
the boss of this company.
This is my hospital, right?
Do I have to
report everything to you?
Besides,
Xia Ling is your client.
If she has any problems,
you can solve it.
Postpartum therapy
is a good treatment
for women.
If she can promote
this treatment,
she should be happy.
Lin Qianyu.
This is not how you do things.
Don't teach me how to do things.
What we lack now?
We lack virality.
What era is it now?
We can't make money
just with technology and quality.
We can only earn money
when we're exposed and viral.
Then, we'll no longer just be
a simple medical center.
We would be
a medical brand
that can thrive on the internet.
This complements the strategy
of Shen's group.
Isn't that great?
Have you ever
valued my credibility?
Do you care about
customer privacy?
Why are you speaking
just like
Shen?
This type of popularity
will hurt our clients.
You're making money on a bad conscience.
I make money on a bad conscience.
Who says I can’t make money on a bad conscience?
Lin Qianyu.
I don't know you anymore.
Please.
Who doesn't know who now?
Aren't you making money too?
You used this hospital
and me to make money?
I want to make money.
Everyone wants to make money.
But I've never made money
by betraying my friends and hurting my clients.
I'll solve the problem first.
Don't say this type of thing
ever again.
Ms. Xia, come down.
Why do you recommend this treatment?
Can you tell us
why you
did this treatment?
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang, Ms. Xia really isn't here.
Can you contact her?
I really need to see her now.
Ms. Kang,
Ms. Xia won't see anyone.
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Xia really isn't here.
Let her in.
Ms. Xia,
I'm really sorry.
I came here
to discuss a solution with you.
How can we
minimize the impact
of this.
Listen to what they said about me.
She claims to be
a women's advocate.
On shows,
she acts like she's all that.
In real life,
she has to rely on this
to please men after all.
And this.
Gosh.
Poor Xia Ling.
If I still need to
do this treatment in my 40s,
I'd rather die.
It's not over yet.
How dare she
This kind of advertisement?
Not every woman
is like her.
Shameless.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't let you in
for an apology.
Apology is the most pointless thing
in the world.
Can the apology
delete this video?
Can the apology delete this comment?
Also!
You come with me.
Miss Xia Ling, come down.
Can you accept our interview?
You should know
what they are doing here
today.
You tell me.
How should I
get out of this building today?
I let you in
just so you could experience
how I feel now!
Ms. Xia,
no matter how angry you are now,
you have the right.
I'll take responsibility for this.
I will try my best
to give you
a satisfying answer.
Kang Ziyou.
I always think
you are a person who does things with sincerity
and won't be led by
the benefits.
I guess I was wrong.
From now on,
my trust in you
is gone.
I think the letter from my lawyer
has been sent.
I advise you
that you'd better not
waste your time here.
Go back and find
a lawyer.
Zhao.
Zhao!
Send her out.
I'm really sorry.
She's out.
Chen Zhe.
Good job.
Kang Ni.
Are you sure you won't join
the Yingzhou Art Group?
Your piano skill level
is very high.
You've passed
the most difficult sound-based exam.
You have met the strict entry requirements.
Many kids
want to join the group,
but they can't meet these conditions.
It's not easy
for those with bad grades
to apply for a good high school.
You
go back and discuss it with your parents.
If that's what they want,
please ask them to sign it
to confirm it.
You turned it down?
Chen Zhe turned it down too.
He has the capital to do it.
People with bad grades like us,
without these extracurricular activities,
how can we compete with them?
Wang,
I don't care
what method you use.
Remove all the videos
from the channel.
Prepare a new video.
Release it online immediately after she withdraws it.
Well...
Ms. Kang, Ms. Lin...
Leave her out of it.
She doesn't know
what she's doing now.
Not only that,
you have to create new hashtags,
capture people's attention, and generate positive feedback
to the project.
Press down
on the bad voice.
Understand?
Should we
make an apology statement?
Of course!
Be sincere, and make it quick.
But the apology statement is usually
made
after the settlement.
I just went to Xia Ling's place.
She refused to
reach a settlement with us.
We were wrong.
So the apology statement
must be very sincere
so that we can have the right to talk about
the compensation with her.
The company has not yet determined
who is responsible for this incident.
Isn't it too early
to talk about compensation now?
I'm sorry.
We're having an internal meeting.
The group attaches great importance to this.
So Mr. Shen sent me here
to communicate with you first.
He'll be here after the meeting.
Ms. Kang,
if you have the time,
can you please come out
and have a talk with me?
What do you want to talk about?
We can talk here.
Ms. Kang,
about what you said just now,
should we start to do it?
Yes. Hurry up.
You can wait a moment.
Don't worry.
The group is working on a solution.
Please
come out with me first.
You start to do it.
Hurry up.
Let's go, Ms. Kang.
Where are we going?
To Ms. Lin.
So we can
solve this problem together.
The group just received the lawyer's letter
from Xia Ling.
So this is not a problem
that can be solved
by the cosmetic medical center itself.
So, Ms. Kang,
you must think about clearly
who's responsible for this matter.
I think now the group wants to
solve the problem
and minimize the impact too.
It's not too late to account for this
after we settle this matter.
Ms. Kang.
The group is preparing
for its IPO.
So everything
is very important.
Since it has happened,
the fire can't be covered.
Only by finding the person who set the fire
and dealing with it
can the crisis PR team
can stop the fire
from burning the group.
So, Ms. Kang,
you have to think clearly about
whose fault it is.
Ms. Lin.
You two are friends now?
Not that close.
It's an emergency.
Let's get straight to the point.
Li Wen said
that the group is also studying the solutions.
That's right.
The group
takes this matter seriously.
But Mrs. Shen,
you don't worry too much.
The group has always supported
our cosmetic medical center.
So I'm here today
to
communicate with you and solve the problem,
not to criticize you.
Criticize me?
I'm afraid you don't have the right.
Of course.
I'm just here to get to know
the initial situation.
That way,
Mr. Shen can make a better judgment before he comes.
Mr. Shen should not always be on your lips.
What?
You must
get between me and him.
Who the hell are you?
Mr. Shen sent me here.
Mr. Shen can send you
wherever he wants.
But you can't come and interrogate me here.
How about this, Li Wen?
You've probably got some idea of
what's going on.
Why don't you go back
and report to Mr. Shen?
Okay.
Let's report it here.
Hello, Mr. Shen.
I'm in Ms. Lin's office now.
But something might have happened.
I wonder,
can we talk now?
No, I'm on my way.
It's more serious than I thought.
Ms. Kang,
you should be in charge
of the promotional video,
right?
Yes, I'm in charge.
So you didn't pass the requirements accurately
to the film cutter?
Of course,
we deliver the requirements to the cutter accurately.
Then why didn't he
follow them?
I left halfway.
That should be considered negligence.
But before I left,
I told him
all the requirements clearly.
But why did you leave?
I had an appointment with a friend.
Is it Dr. Nie?
Yes, so what?
You know.
The company has rules that
prohibit office romance.
I didn't know
the company had such a rule.
Besides,
it's not a romance yet.
We're just friends.
I think
asking about these trivial matters
is a waste of time.
Shouldn't we
focus on finding a solution?
We should come up with a solution.
After that,
if the group believes it's my fault,
at that time,
it's not too late to punish me, right?
No.
Everyone will make mistakes.
How did you know this matter?
I've talked to the film cutter.
He told me
Ms. Kang was called away by Dr. Nie.
And before the video was done,
you...
Actually, I think
Kang Ziyou is right.
Our priority now
is to solve the problem.
Actually, I think
this situation
may be a good chance for us.
Why don't we
have business cooperation with Xia Ling?
Take this opportunity
to turn the topic to charity.
And let her
be the ambassador
of this project.
So we can not only change the public's opinion,
but I believe many negative comments
will be eliminated.
What do you think?
The group won't pay for
this corporation.
The business cooperation you just mentioned
must need
funds.
And at this critical moment,
to persuade Xia Ling,
the money
won't be a small amount.
And we can't
guarantee
the result.
So the group won't
pay for this
only based on a possibility.
Then let Ziyou talk about it with her.
She has a private relationship with Xia Ling.
I don't think
Xia Ling will turn us down at this moment.
Besides, if she
refuses to cooperate with us now,
these negative reviews
will follow her forever.
Am I right?
Who is responsible
for her negative image?
Well...
You want me to think of a way,
and now I have come up with one.
Why don't you two think of a way?
No matter what method you use,
should we have to reduce the damage
to Xia Ling first?
Isn't it good now?
We give her money
and our business endorsement.
And we can help her turn public opinion around.
It will reduce the damage.
Lin Qianyu, can you think better?
If you didn't ask the film cutter
to edit the video like this,
would the current situation
be like this?
It is my idea.
But you didn't review the video either.
Why am I the only one to blame?
Yes, I didn't.
I am responsible for my own.
But you can't
just think
that you can solve everything
with money, right?
Money can't solve all problems,
but it can solve
part of them, right?
Can you be
more positive like me,
face it, and solve the problem?
Stop always complaining about me,
OK?
Don't use the verbal trick as a boss
to put us off.
I know what I should do.
I also want you to know
what you're doing right now.
This is the office.
Do you know who you're talking to?
I know.
I'm speaking with someone
who claims to be my friend!
Mr. Shen is here.
Tell me.
What happened?
Well.
Ms. Kang was supposed to
supervise the film cutter
in order to complete the promotional video.
And then...
Alright, I don't want to hear the details.
I want to know
the result.
Who should
take the responsibility?
I think
we don't need to worry too much.
Although this matter is tricky,
it can be solved.
It also exposed
some shortcomings
in the management.
It's not too late for us to see it.
As long as we can...
What happened today
proves that the company
has many problems with the management.
Once this problem appears
it will affect
not only Lijia United,
but the reputation
of the whole group.
Understand?
You always say that you want to brand yourself.
Is there anyone like you
to slander the brand?
What happened today
is the most
unforgivable behavior
in my view.
Everyone here,
no matter who it is,
as long as I believe it's your responsibility,
please resign, leave,
and bear all the consequences.
Even if it is
Lin Qianyu's responsibility.
If she can't do the job right,
I'll let someone else do it.
Mr. Shen is right.
This matter
indeed exposed
some problems
in our management.
We should reflect on ourselves.
Li Wen,
as the group's core member,
has the ability
to compensate
for our management's mistakes.
I believe
if we communicate more with the group,
we'll avoid this problem
happening again.
I think
Ms. Lin's suggestion is quite good.
Through business cooperation,
we can work with Xia Ling
and make her
the brand ambassador of this project.
Overthrow the public's opinion and make it a hot topic.
Turn all negative opinions
into positive ones.
Do you think,
at this critical moment,
she can agree to our request?
Someone in the company
is quite close to her.
Do something.
It's possible.
OK.
I'll leave this
to you.
Okay.
If you want Xia Ling
to agree to this,
we must find the person who made the mistake,
make the person take responsibility,
and give her an answer.
The core problem of this matter
lies in
the lack of the review process.
Besides, Ms. Lin only
brings up a suggestion.
The person who is directly responsible
should be the one who is in charge of the review and passing.
Ms. Lin, what do you think?
I...
About this matter...
Mr. Shen.
It's my fault.
I was away from work
when editing
and failed to
fulfill the obligation of supervision and review.
I'll take this responsibility.
But I think
the most urgent thing
is Xia Ling.
I think
we should find a good solution
to help the company overcome this difficulty.
Director Kang is right.
Our priority now
is to help the company pull through
as soon as possible.
I'd also like to thank Ms. Kang
for her years of dedication
to Lijia United.
How about
you go home first?
After we discuss
a follow-up solution,
we'll inform you.
Last night,
it was me who asked Director Kang out.
So in terms of responsibility,
my fault is bigger.
What do you do in this company?
You're a doctor.
Are you in charge of
the company's operations and management?
No.
But the source of the mistake is me.
-So... -Mr. Shen is right.
I'm in charge of the operation.
So it has nothing to do
with Dr. Nie.
But I still want to say that
Xia Ling is our client.
We can't just
stand aside and watch her
fall into the whirlpool of public opinion.
Xia Ling is not the only one
who falls into the whirlpool.
The whole group too, okay?
Because of
your mistake at work,
it caused
such a loss to the group.
So I think
your resignation
is the only right thing to do.
OK.
Excuse me.
Kang Ziyou.
What are you doing?
This is not right.
You're taking the blame.
As long as it can solve the problem,
I'll take the blame.
Did you solve the problem?
You were solved!
What else can I do?
The internet
is full of humiliation and mocking
for Xia Ling.
So many people
are waiting at her door.
They just want to shoot her face.
She can't even get out of the door.
What can I do?
What else can I do?
It's meaningless for us
to say this now.
It's all our fault anyway.
I should bear
whatever I can.
I can't do anything else.
No.
Will things get better if you run away like this?
Run away?
You think I'm running away?
If you hadn't
dragged me out that day,
all of this
wouldn't have happen.
Are you telling me that you regret
what happened that day?
I regret it so much.
If I could go back,
I would never go out with you.
All the mistakes
happened
when you appeared.
I know.
I really don't understand.
Why does everyone
want to join the Yingzhou?
I play the piano for my own happiness.
Why are you here if you're not happy?
My grandma always said
how important this art group is.
She just wants me to join it.
How can I say no?
Let me ask you a question.
Will the basketball shooting machine change
because of your expectations?
How it's possible.
That's it.
If your grandma's expectations
can change you,
then you're even worse than
a shooting machine.
You're worse than a shooting machine.
At this moment,
I will impart
a knowledge point to you.
What knowledge point?
Chen Zhe's first law.
One should be like this basketball.
I don't care if you can make it
or not,
just be happy when you shoot.
[Pingbo City Yingzhou Art Group]