[English subtitles are available]
[Viva Femina]
[Episode 16]
Our family
didn't use to be so rude.
I'm talking to you.
I didn't go.
How would I know?
You have classmates there, right?
You can chat with them
and ask around.
I don't know.
If that doesn't work,
you can ask Li Wen.
Why should I ask her?
Can't I handle
a little thing like that?
Come here.
Do you think
everything I do for you
should be taken for granted?
Of course.
Surely, I can't ask my dad
to find a new one, right?
How could you say that?
Don't treat me as the enemy,
okay?
I want to get along with you.
Actually, we can form an alliance,
right?
You make your dad happy.
I'll make you happy.
Okay?
Forget it.
Just take care of yourself.
But don't worry.
I will find a way
to let you enter Yingzhou.
Pack up your stuff.
Your dad is coming back.
Where have you been?
Why are you still up?
Please answer my question.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I had a business dinner today.
I didn't want to go.
But as you know,
my relationship
with my colleagues
has been tense lately.
And Director Luo
called me personally.
I couldn't refuse.
I wanted to
tell you.
But at that time,
you were talking on stage,
so I couldn't tell you.
Meng Yushan.
I know
you care about your job.
I know you care about
about your appraisal.
I can be considerate and care about you.
I can do anything.
But I don't understand.
Why can't you look at it
from my point of view?
Please understand me.
If you care so much about your work,
why did you...
Why did you marry me?
I...
Didn't I watch the show
with you today?
I just left a little early.
-Was that a little early? -It's not a big deal.
Why not, Meng Yushan?
Let me tell you. Usually,
when I ask you to watch matches with me,
you say you're busy.
It's fine if you don't go.
That's that.
Today?
What day is it today?
Today is
so important to me.
I just wanted to give you a surprise.
I specially asked Sang Ruowei
for a chance
to go on stage.
I prepared
a big surprise.
I wanted to share an important day
with you.
I had a lot of things
to tell you.
But where did you go?
Am I even on your mind?
Am I still your husband?
Am I just a bro
who sleeps on your bed?
What's wrong with you today?
You won't get off my back.
I apologize.
I was wrong.
I'll apologize, is that not enough?
Alright?
Why are you apologizing to me?
Finish what you
didn't finish saying on stage.
Say it now.
Think about it.
I'll apologize, okay?
I'm sorry. Is an apology not enough?
Say what you didn't finish saying on stage.
-No need. Stop arguing. -Tell me now.
I'm listening, okay?
Stop fighting. I'm really tired.
I can't take this anymore.
I'll leave, okay? I'll leave.
Kang Ziyou likes me.
Why do you look down on me?
Fine.
See if I'll come back.
♫I thought there were too many impossibilities♫
♫So, forget it♫
♫How many times have I turned around and restrained myself♫
♫Yet I look away♫
♫I thought it was over but at the next moment♫
♫Sparks fly♫
♫I finally see my own and your...♫
Here.
♫choices in our hearts♫
Let me show you a different me.
I'll show you
the peak of my life.
♫I walk up to you bravely♫
Don't stand me up again.
My very important friend
♫Turn the missed opportunity into a re-encounter ♫
is my wife,
Ms. Meng Yushan.
♫We know each other, we don't speak but we have so much to say♫
Kang Ziyou likes me.
Why do you look down on me?
♫I'll hold your hand through the storm♫
♫I walk up to you bravely♫
♫Once I pressed pause, now I choose to continue♫
♫I see expectations in your eyes♫
♫I walk up to you bravely♫
Nini, get up.
I made you
egg rolls and sandwiches.
You can't eat that.
It was keep for a long time and it's cold.
Wait a minute.
It'll be ready in a minute.
Ms. Xia.
Ziyou.
Have you contacted the editor?
I'm trying.
I've found the company
that he used to work at.
They said they would inform me
immediately if they have any news.
Ziyou,
all my hope is
on you now.
Don't let me down.
Ms. Xia,
I'll do my best,
okay?
Okay.
That's all for now.
Nini.
Beauty Kang.
I learned it online.
Take a look.
I did a pretty good job.
Try it.
I've already eaten.
Have it yourself.
Nini,
I'm really sorry
about that thing with the Art Group.
But it was an accident.
After you left,
I went to your teacher.
I told her clearly that
you are not willing
to join the Art Group.
What did she say?
The teacher was a little angry.
She said
she won't agree for the time being.
I'm going to school.
Wait for me.
I'll drive you.
It's not easy to get a taxi today.
Kids nowadays are really annoying.
No, no.
What's wrong?
My stomach hurts.
You have a stomachache? Why?
Nini.
What's wrong with you?
My stomach hurts.
Can I come in?
No!
Why do you suddenly have a stomachache?
Did you eat
the cold food in the morning?
I told you not to eat it.
Kang Ni.
How many times have you had diarrhoea today?
Is this your first time?
It happened three times today!
Three times?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Who is it?
Zhenghao.
Dr. Meng.
Can you put me in the queue?
I-I-I know
it's your lunch break.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Dr. Meng.
My medicine is gone.
You need to prescribe more for me.
And I think the strength of the medicine
is not enough.
Have a seat and talk slowly.
Is the medicine not working?
Next week,
my mom will come again.
She doesn't know about my resignation.
If I can find a job this week,
it'll be okay.
She didn't approve of me
being in this industry in the first place.
It's even worse if she finds out.
I told you
someone was following me, right?
I think I need to find
another place to live now.
Let me get you some water.
Don't move.
I don't know
if I'm having hallucinations.
I don't think so.
Dr. Meng.
Only you can save me now.
Please prescribe more medicine for me.
Okay?
Under what type of circumstances
do you feel like this?
I always feel it.
I think
I can feel that the stalker
is a man.
No, wait a minute.
That may not be the case,
because sometimes
his steps are very light.
It could be a woman too.
A while ago,
I interviewed at a company.
Then, I was completely
unaware of his existence.
Let me tell you.
It's really not easy
to find a job in my industrynow.
Everyone is competing
to see whose price is lower.
If you take a small job for 10,000 yuan,
others will accept it at 8,000 yuan.
I really don't know
how to tell my mom
when she comes.
Do you know?
Also, I heard that
the person who got into trouble
for the video that I edited
s-s-seems to
be in the news again.
They say her husband cheated on her
or something like that.
Would they think that
that has something to do with me?
Does everyone
want to put all the blame on me?
want to frame me?
Listen to me.
Don't have such an aggressive...
Meng Yushan, let me kindly remind you that
you don't have to go for
tonight's gathering.
What are you doing?
Alright, go on.
Go on.
Don't come over.
What are you doing? Don't come over!
Don't come over!
Zhenghao! Zhenghao!
What are you doing?
That's my colleague.
Don't come over.
Don't choke yourself.
Zhenghao.
What's wrong, Zhenghao?
Wake up. It's me.
Who are you?
I'm Dr. Meng.
Who is she?
She's my colleague.
How do you know each other?
She's the one who followed me.
How do you know her?
Did someone send you two
to frame me?
No.
Let me ask you.
Are you in cahoots?
Are all of you
trying to frame me?
No one wants to harm you.
I'm just asking you.
Zhenghao.
Put it down.
What are you doing?
Director.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Let go.
Director.
-Director, are you okay? -Who is this?
Did you eat
something dirty?
Just the rice balls.
I told you
the rice balls have been kept for a long time,
but you insisted on eating them.
Why didn't you throw them away then?
It's nothing serious.
You just have a stomachache.
Take your medicine on time.
In the next few days,
don't eat
raw, cold and food that irritates your stomach.
Okay.
Nothing else from me.
Get the medicine on the first floor.
Okay, thank you doctor.
-Let’s go. -Let’s go.
Slow down.
You scared mom just now.
You were yelping so badly in the toilet.
I told you
you can't eat things that've been
in the fridge can't be eaten.
Yet you insisted on eating it.
Don't go to school today.
Take a good rest at home.
I'll ask for leave from your class teacher.
Who said I'm not going?
The doctor said I'm fine.
I'm going.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
Let me send you.
It's none of your business.
I don't care.
It's all bandaged.
Director,
is your hand okay?
It's just a scratch.
What do you think about this?
I added the patient to the queue at the last minute.
The patient said
he had hallucinations.
He suspected someone was following him.
He's also very concerned about how confined the space is.
He kept watching the door.
When Wang Meng
suddenly pushed the door to enter,
it broke his sense of security.
Whose responsibility do you think it is?
My responsibility.
He's my patient.
Besides,
it happened in my clinic.
But Director,
this patient
can't handle
all kinds of pressure in his life.
I think he should proceed to
the next step in treatment as soon as possible.
Can you
find a way to follow up on
this patient's condition?
To be honest,
I really admire your sense of responsibility
towards your patients.
But you've been in a trance lately.
You brought your personal problems
to the hospital.
And...
you failed to adapt
in your crisis intervention.
Now the hospital management knows all about it.
I don't want to scold you anymore, okay?
Go back and wait for the notice.
Sorry, Director.
Go. Go.
I knew you were following me.
What do you want?
I need your help.
I won't be involved in
anything that you do anymore.
I know that you were
affected by this.
But look at Xia Ling.
She was screwed over so badly.
So?
So you have to come out and say
that the video was edited.
You knew it all along.
Only you can prove it.
Prove it. I can prove it.
How can I prove it?
You want me to stand out
and tell the truth.
Yes, you'll be free.
I'll become a target.
They'll attack me and take revenge on me.
No one will take revenge on you.
We will protect you.
Aren't you from the cosmetic center?
Didn't you
say I was stupid?
You tricked me!
You guys are too cruel.
You made me lose my job.
Now you want me to stand up for you?
If I really
stood up,
you will kill me,
right?
I'm warning you.
Stop following me.
I'll call the police.
Listen to me...
Mom, why are you free today?
Don't you have many activities
to attend?
Now, I think all those activities
are boring.
I asked Qiu to decline them.
By the way,
recommend some books for your mom.
Recommend some books?
You don't read.
What's there to buy?
Besides,
aren't you leaving soon?
Who says I don't read?
Can't I
read books
and nurture my emotions?
Sure, sure. Nurture your emotions.
Well,
see if you like anything.
Let's buy them all.
Normally,
it's hard to ask you out.
What happened today?
You came out as soon as I called you.
Well...
Did something good happen?
Are you in love?
The old tree has blossomed, right?
Be quiet.
What old tree blossomed?
Mom,
can you be more serious?
I'm not serious?
If I remember correctly,
this your first time dating, right?
Mom, I'm leaving.
Don't be so sensitive.
You...
Then I'll take
a musician for example.
Bach, for example.
His music
sounds
very normal.
Look at Beethoven.
He's different.
His music
makes people
extremely passionate.
Extremely...
Mother. Stop. Stop it.
Do you think
this conversation should be the one
between a mother and a son?
So what?
You're an adult.
What will happen
if I ask about some details
in your relationship？
You even want to know the details?
Yes.
Are you a pervert?
You're the pervert.
Come and sit down.
Tell me.
No.
Then what am I going to say?
Details.
OK.
Everything was fine.
But, when I was careless,
I found she had left.
She left?
Yes.
What does that mean, Mother?
There are only
two possibilities.
The first one
is that she really had something to do and left.
It was too late.
What could she do?
For example, when you were young,
I had to go back.
I had to go back to take care of you.
Right?
What's the second possibility?
The second one
is
that she doesn't like you at all.
Thank you.
Mother?
What a coincidence.
That's right. What a coincidence.
It's okay. I fell.
Why are you here
when you're working?
I met a client
who is around here.
It's so distant.
Why are you here?
I'm here for physical therapy.
Don't you know
I'm here for physical therapy?
That's right.
Hurry up.
Get a doctor.
It's okay. It's just a small cut.
What small cut?
Such a deep one.
You're bleeding a lot.
It needs to be stitched.
Doctor.
There's no need.
I don't know.
If it doesn't work,
you can go to ask Li Wen.
Do you know
Ms. Zhao Xu
of Yingzhou Art Group?
We had some contact.
What's wrong?
Go to her in a few days
to see if the art group
can add one more place
to put Shen Hang in.
Ms. Zhao is quite unique.
This may be a bit difficult.
That's why I ask you to do it.
You have to figure it out.
Also,
Shen Hang asks you
to do it.
If you fail,
or if there are any difficulties,
you can explain it to him yourself.
Okay, I'll try.
Does it hurt?
No.
It's nothing, Mother.
I'll go to work now.
Why are you avoiding me?
Are you so reluctant
-to stay with me? -No, I'm not.
Sit with me.
I
have to go back to work.
I'm not avoiding you.
What work do you need to go to?
How can you go to work like this?
I'll call Qianyu
and ask for a leave.
You can...
No, Mother.
Don't call the boss
for leave at will.
If I don't go to work
just because of a small cut,
it'll have a bad influence.
What small cut? It was stitched.
It's not that serious.
How did you get here?
I drove here.
I didn't see your car.
You mean here?
There's no parking space here.
The car is parked
right next to a mall
over there.
Good.
I'll be done in ten minutes.
Tuina.
Wait for me.
-I'll get a ride. -No.
Unfortunately, Mother.
I have an appointment today.
The car needs maintenance.
Let me call a taxi for you?
Okay?
Really?
Are you lying to me?
No.
No?
I know
when you lie.
Tell me
what happened today.
Why didn't you
go to work in your work time?
You came all the way here
and fell.
-What's wrong with you? -Enough, Mother.
I'll tell you the truth!
I resigned.
You resigned?
Why did you resign?
Were you fired by your boss?
Or did you want to leave?
I want to leave.
Why?
I'm tired.
I want to rest for a while.
Why are you tired?
During this period,
you want to rest.
You don't want to work.
You're unemployed.
Just during this period,
can't I take a break?
I know what you're worried about.
Don't worry. I have savings.
Didn't you pay your savings
for the housing expenses?
Didn't you use them to buy a house?
Tell me.
How much money do you have now?
Don't care how much I have.
Things about Kang Ni
won't be delayed.
You won't worry about it.
How old are you?
Why do you make me so concerned?
I'm so angry.
Well,
since you've made up your mind,
this is the only way.
Luckily, I have some pension
to support you two.
There's no problem.
But I have something to say.
Let's live
whatever conditions we have.
Anyway, before I'm cremated,
I'm relieved
when you two are all right.
Yang Wanru.
It's your turn.
Go pick up Nini.
I'll go home
and cook for you.
Stop ordering takeouts.
They're expensive and unhealthy.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Coming.
Look at my waist.
OK.
Given your waist,
you should work less,
and rest more.
How can I be unoccupied?
I'm used to being busy.
Leave things
to others
who should deal with them.
Don't burden yourself
with everything.
I just think
I don't know
what happened to my chest.
I feel a little stuffy.
Stuffy?
You can't be careless.
You'd better
go to a big hospital
and check it.
Not only the stuffy chest and painful waist
that we can see directly.
At this age,
what we fear are those diseases that can't be seen.
You need to get a physical examination often.
It's okay. I'm strong.
I'm not that delicate.
You
worry too much.
When you get old,
you should let it go.
Your children and grandchildren make their own fortunes.
You should pay attention
to your health.
Living a few more years
is better than anything.
When Nini goes to college,
I'll get through it.
Is that okay?
Come in, please.
Ms. Lin.
Here are the data and accounts
that you need to check.
Put them there.
What's wrong?
I've been dealing with
our debts these days.
When I checked the accounts
and purchase list,
I found some numbers didn't match.
Have a seat.
What happened?
It happened
after Director Kang left.
And,
Director Li Wen
has been using the computer for financial affairs.
Who else knows about this?
No one.
I immediately report it to you
after I found out.
Okay.
Go back first.
I have to say
you can send me directly your resume
with connections.
You're quite capable.
I'm flattered, Mr. Chen.
To be honest,
I don't have a post
suitable for you now.
I know.
I don't intend
to change my job.
So, why?
I think it's enough
for you to have a general impression on me.
You spent so much effort
just
to impress me?
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
As far as I know,
Mr. Shen relies on you a lot.
What is the reason
making you feel
you still need my attention?
Going up
is human nature.
That makes sense.
But,
I value loyalty the most.
Of course.
But as you know,
loyalty should be also measured by money.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's serious. Are you okay?
Ms. Lin.
Let me make an introduction.
This is Mr. Chen from Yinhai Group.
Mr. Chen.
This is Ms. Lin from Lijia United.
She's also Mr. Shen's wife.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Good.
You're bothered
to take care of Li Wen.
My child is waiting for me at home.
I'm leaving.
Bye, Li Wen.
Bye, Ms. Lin.
Bye.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Is this
the so-called private affair?
I'm done with the private one.
I came to do some business.
Why can't I remember
we have business
with Mr. Chen?
But Yinhai Group might not be the same.
Don't bluff me about the group.
Ms. Lin,
my feet are injured.
Why don't you give me a ride?
I have to be your driver?
After all, I'm your employee.
Enough.
Look at your heels.
It's not that bad.
Stop acting like this.
Let me ask you.
What do you want from Mr. Chen?
It's just about business.
What kind of business
needs you to lean on someone else?
I'm just responsible for
what my boss told me to do.
As for how I did it,
the boss usually
wouldn't ask.
Based on my understanding of Shen,
he would meet a chairman at such a level
in person,
rather than send you to do it.
Looks like you don't know much
about Mr. Shen.
Is that right?
Then,
let's call Shen.
Let me ask
whether he sent you
to meet Mr. Chen.
Or it's you who embezzled the money
to make a deal with others?
Wait.
Embezzled the money?
You misunderstand
that I'm the one who embezzled the money?
What else?
Who else could it be?
Ms. Lin, here's the thing.
There's something
that happens in the group.
So, Mr. Shen
needs the capital turnover
from the medical aesthetics center.
Mr. Shen didn't tell you?
Ms. Lin, you should have told me earlier.
If this happens again,
I'll report it to you.
In this way,
you can know what I'm doing.
But I think
you can keep it in your heart.
After all, I don't think
what Mr. Shen did is appropriate.
Ms. Lin,
if there's nothing else,
I'll leave.
By the way,
if I have any news
about Ms. Zhao Xu,
I'll tell you.
Go.
Miss Li,
is it about Shen Hang again?
I told his mother.
There's really no place for him.
I know.
But it was then.
It's now.
It's the same now.
The places are limited.
Hello?
It's me.
Coming.
Who are you looking for?
Hello.
Is this
Kang Ziyou's home?
Who are you?
I'm Nie Yunze.
What are you up to?
I'm a doctor.
I'm not asking about that.
I'm asking
what's your relationship with her?
And what do you want from her?
I'm her friend.
Ex-colleague.
Boyfriend.
So, is she at home?
She...
It's okay if she's not home.
I'll come later.
It's okay. She'll be back soon.
Come on.
Come in.
It's not good to stay outside.
The door. The door.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Little girl,
are you related
to Kang Ziyou?
I'm her second aunt.
I'm here to see her.
No.
It's my honor to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Well.
In my hometown,
my position in the family hierarchy is high.
It's okay.
You
can call me the second aunt just like Ziyou does.
Yes.
Sit down. Why are you standing there?
Don't be so formal.
Nice to meet you, the second aunt.
What do you think
of my niece?
She's fine.
Does she trouble you?
Not bad.
Why are you here?
Return the car.
What do you like about Ziyou?
Why are you here?
I...
She is my...
We introduced ourselves.
Yes, we did.
I wasn't used to it at first,
but I'll try to get used to it.
What happened to your hand?
I fell.
Ziyou,
you're an adult.
Can't you be careful when you walk?
You're more like a middle schooler than me.
What
brings you
here?
Yeah, the car is fixed.
I come to return it to you.
Thank you.
Yes.
And...
Well...
You should talk outside.
Don't disturb my homework.
Here.
Thank you.
Put it here.
You're here.
Uncle Zhao.
Did I wake you up?
I'm sorry.
-Come on. Lie down and go to sleep. -It's OK. I was just taking a nap.
I can't sleep
without alcohol.
Did you buy some?
You still want to drink?
What else do you want?
No way.
Drinking is bad for your health.
Go to sleep.
I can't live a hundred years without drinking.
What are you talking about?
There is so much trouble in life.
With alcohol,
it won't be a problem.
Do you believe it?
No.
Really?
No, sleep.
When did you hide a bottle of liquor?
You even hide it in your bed?
Don't let your father know.
If the nursing worker finds out,
it'll be a big deal.
Give it to me.
Give it to me. Be good.
You can't drink it.
I'll be angry. Give it to me.