Idiot.
It shouldn't be so beautiful.
Are you over me?
No.
Now that I think about it,
I never even tried.
It's just not great timing.
Is it because...
- by any chance...
- By any chance, what?
Let me guess. Your sister in high
school is actually your daughter.
Wrong.
- What are you doing?
- I know.
You and Kim Seok Joo are actually brothers.
Then, you're the CEO's son? Is that right?
Wrong.
- What am I doing right now?
- I know! Well...
is that a wig? How bald are you?
What are you saying? This is my real hair.
Can I pull it?
It's real hair.
How come your brain spins so fast?
I wasn't valedictorian for nothing.
Wow, gosh! I look like I'm out of my mind, huh?
It's okay. I feel out of it, too.
When will we ever be okay?
- I know.
- Right? We don't know.
Anyway, I've made my decision.
I'll get through to you.
Once I've made up my mind,
I've got to see the end of it.
I'm going to go for it.
I'm telling you, okay?
Watch me.
♫ I feel nervous, but I don't know why ♫
♫ Faint butterflies in my stomach ♫
You didn't have lunch yet, right?
I'm working on a new menu item. This is for you...
What are you doing?
♫ You vibrate as if shocked ♫
What did the doctor say?
It hasn't gotten worse, has it?
Hyung.
Maybe the results are wrong.
It doesn't feel real yet.
Hey.
Let's eat. It won't be good if it gets cold.
Let's eat.
♫ Come closer ♫
♫ The red sunset ♫
♫ Night and day meet briefly ♫
♫ Like us from back then ♫
♫ Like falling into it ♫
♫ Pretending not to know and embrace ♫
♫ It's like waves that get pushed away ♫
Then, you mix like this...
Right, mix.
Is that Sunwoo Hae?
Why didn't you say you were here? You scared me!
Sorry. I think you and I were
looking for the same person.
- What?
- You know Jin Mu Yeong?
That Jin Mu Yeong.
He went on the show after all.
How did you convince him?
You had trouble booking him last year.
He's more chill than he seems. Nice, too.
The out-of-town shoot ran into trouble,
but he stayed behind alone to plant the trees.
I hope that comes through in the edit.
That's what we do.
I know it must've been very unpleasant that day.
I sincerely apologize.
I remember this feeling.
I don't want to take it, but I have to.
My apology was sincere.
If you don't want to accept it, you don't have to.
You know you're out of his league, right?
That's your mom's name, isn't it?
Didn't you use it as your pen name
because you wanted to hide behind it?
You knew you'd get torn apart otherwise.
If someone involved in a fraud case was
publishing a book and selling the rights.
After the show airs today, it will get worse.
Are you concerned for me?
Even if it gets tough, stay strong.
Don't make those around you worry.
Thanks for the advice.
Enjoy your food.
Why are you so down?
Did you fight with ahjumma?
I should just take it like a sandbag,
but I lost my temper in that moment.
You know how to lose your temper?
I never saw that with my mom
or when we lived at Seok Joo's.
I hold back in front of the kids.
You remember things from when you were so little?
I remember both Mom running away
and holding your hand to meet Oppa.
Nu Ri, do you miss your mom?
You never ask.
I don't know.
That makes me feel like I'm betraying Oppa.
If you need someone to talk to,
you have me. You know that, right?
All right.
Can I order kimchi fried rice?
Can we get a kimchi-
Don't tell him I gave you the kimchi.
Keep it a secret that you're seeing me.
When are you two going to make up?
You've been doing this through me for 10 years.
Regarding this matter,
Hae needs to forgive me first.
Wow, this!
I used to take pictures of Hae
with this when he was little.
Aigoo, so pretty.
Right. When are you giving me the film?
Oh, no.
Here. Thirty-six bags.
You haven't called once.
Ahjumma! Hello.
Here. Take this and go.
I'll call you.
A minor now? Seriously?
- Is this why you left the house?
- Noona!
Seriously? She's like my daughter!
Right, you're seeing a girl who
could be your daughter!
Let's go to the police.
Come over here! Come!
You come, too.
I'm Nu Ri.
Don't you remember me?
You gave me this camera.
Right. You're Nu Ri.
The little girl that Seok Joo brought in.
- Sunwoo Hae's daughter.
- What?
Not Hae's daughter. The woman I used to be with...
I told you before I got together with you...
After Hae's mom died, I fell in love
with her mom when I was struggling...
Hey! Why do you have so many secrets
when you're not even a good liar?
You don't like it when I talk about the past!
I didn't know I'd get caught.
Look at you running your mouth again.
Who cares whose daughter I am?
Ahjussi, ahjumma, stop fighting.
Bye.
I can explain everything.
Hae is supporting her. She has a good life.
Sure, sure. I'm a sinner. I am...
- Gosh! I can't watch!
- Oh, my God!
- I'm going to lose my mind.
- You scared me.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey...
Pour it into a glass.
Hey. Don't drink on an empty stomach.
I should have drunk the soju earlier.
- Next week, let's drink before we watch.
- Sounds good.
I really can't watch.
Hae?
Hurry up!
What is wrong with me?
Why am I trying so hard to be cute...
Oh, my gosh...
Hyung, they're paying!
Thank you, come again. Thank you.
Table 7's food is ready.
Wait. Isn't the soccer game today?
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Could you turn on the soccer game?
Soccer? Got it. One second.
Things went over okay today.
Was I the only one who enjoyed it?
I also...
thought it was good.
I might have been a little funny.
I told you! You're so charming.
But Bebop actually chewed me out a lot.
- But in the edit, he came across as so supportive.
- But...
I wonder if Bebop even watched.
I bet he doesn't even know it's out.
He's probably busy making money.
Tae Rin, when you're dealing with
someone who has a lot on their mind
and is complicated, what do I do?
Be simple.
Just balance him out.
What's the genre?
Thriller? Romance? Action?
Mixed.
Well, I don't know who
you're talking about, but...
Have you kissed?
What? What do you mean?
Well...
How was it? What was it like afterward?
I kept thinking about it.
Then, you kiss him next time.
Let's brainwash him.
So, he'll only think about you.
Oh, right!
H-H-How do I do that?
If I just think about it, will it work? Will it?
You're cute.
You just saying that makes my heart flutter.
I'm jealous.
Where can I find someone who's devoted to me?
Someone who will sacrifice,
be devoted, and love me only.
Someone who would die for a purpose.
Hey. If it comes up in an interview,
don't ever say that's your type.
Keep it to yourself.
Anyway, go back to him, and...
For instance,
let's say you two are sitting
like this, eating tteokbokki.
- Is tteokbokki too spicy?
- Yes. It's spicy.
Can it be ice cream instead?
Even better.
Let's say that you're eating next to each other.
- Then...
- Then?
Then?
Then...
I'll hold him like this and go for it.
- No?
- Seriously?
- So clueless.
- Really?
You need to set the mood first!
Imagine that I'm him.
- You always read scenes with me.
- Okay.
All right. Close your eyes...
Get into it...
What are you doing?
You're just going to look?
I can't. I can't.
Why not?
I'm nervous.
Goodness. Seriously...
Just do it like this.
Go for it...
when the vibe is right.
Can you not do it when you imagine it's Hae?
What?
Hey! You! How did you know it was Sunwoo Hae?
I wanted to pretend like I didn't know.
The only men around you are Hae...
and Kim... Kim Seok Joo.
Hold on! Why are you here?
I'm not interested! No, thank you!
Who are you thinking about?
I thought you were practicing with me.
- Why am I thinking about that sunbae?
- Sunbae?
Do I have too little, I mean,
too much dopamine these days?
Last time, you said he's just a kid.
What loser are you talking about?
You're not paying attention to me!
Why would I pay any attention to you?
You're paying attention to me!
What are you into?
How far did you get?
I need to shake this off.
Let's just drink.
Okay, then. Wait...
To summarize,
you're saying I should set up a situation
and make him go berserk, right?
That's right. Kiss him, slap him, or cry.
Do something. Or all of the above.
Then, that will be all he can think about at home.
I guess that's true.
Okay, listen.
Cry, slap him, then kiss him. Right?
You could slap him first, then cry.
Here it is.
Thank you!
- You ordered potted flowers, right?
- Yes.
You're all set with payment.
You're Sunwoo Hae, right?
Oh, yes.
That's so cool. Hello.
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Flower delivery!
I saw you on TV.
You deliver these yourself?
Oh, yes.
Could you sign here?
Honey!
My husband is a huge fan.
That sitcom was so good!
Could we get a photo with you?
- Sure, could you sign here first?
- Just one second.
Honey! Come on out!
These stairs are too much.
It's just four floors. How come you're so winded?
- Aren't you working out these days?
- No.
By the way, what did you think of the show?
Was I clever and wise?
You were so goofy and lovable.
You went to a bookstore?
- No way.
- Knew it.
Hold on. Let me give you the script
for Episodes 3 and 4.
The chairs still aren't here?
They were sent to my parents'.
This box is very sturdy.
The script reviewed by the person
who sent the office chairs to your parents'?
I don't see Gi Bbeum.
I sent him to a driving school to get his license.
Aigoo.
Hello.
Excuse me.
What are you doing here? My goodness...
I'm here to see Director Bang Han Na.
I didn't know someone else would
be here, so I just bought two cups.
Thanks for the coffee.
Our actress needs a new accountant.
If you're busy, feel free
to recommend someone else.
You know Mo Tae Rin over there, right?
She's our top actress.
That's how things worked out.
If you're uncomfortable doing this
since you work with your mother...
It's okay.
Looking forward to working with you.
I'm Kim Seok Joo.
You're an accountant, too?
Yes. That's my main line of work.
When can I get my bag back?
I thought you were getting rid of it.
We can exchange it for your handkerchief.
- The one you lent me.
- You can have it.
You're not being rude to me today.
Are we using honorifics now?
Where were you going to take me
at the hotel last time?
I got curious.
I know where you can cry without
people watching inside that hotel.
Why do you know that?
I might have cried my eyes out there.
I was trying to be nice.
Yet I was treated like a piece of shit.
Cried your eyes out?
You seem cold as ice.
Of course, I cry. I'm human.
It seems like you have a grudge against me.
We can take care of that as we go.
You'll have to take it now.
It was my first radio show, so I got nervous.
Maybe that's why it reminded me
of when I was a kid.
I heard your radio show on the rooftop, Sunbae.
That voice made me cry once, too.
Do you ever think this at times?
That the gravity is pressing
down harder only on me.
I just wonder every now and then.
Why am I standing here
in the middle of it all as myself?
Maybe I'm still growing up.
You asked me why I keep crying.
Is that why you get in the water?
Well, you know...
No tax evasion.
Just a fair amount of deductions, please.
Of course. Why make a point?
You're funny.
What's funny? You're not even laughing.
Are you human or a robot?
Seriously?
Don't forget my bag next time.
She's so weird.
You know about Nu Ri's grades, right?
Yes.
A university in Seoul will be hard.
Here are schools she could apply
to with a portfolio.
She's a talented photographer,
and she works hard at extracurriculars.
- Photography?
- Yes.
She should sign up for an after-school class.
If you can't afford it, I understand.
No, I'll do that.
I'm sorry, but how are you
related to Nu Ri, exactly?
She said her older brother was coming,
but your last names are different.
We are family.
It's a complicated family situation.
You should take more interest in her.
It's a critical time.
Got it. I will.
Hello, Hyungnim.
I'm Choi Sa Rang, Nu Ri's friend.
You scared me.
Hello.
Hey, are you crazy?
Why?
Oppa.
Hey, friend...
How are your grades?
I rank first in my class.
How about you?
Me?
Why do you ask? You already know.
Grades don't make a person happy. So rude!
Your grades are even more rude.
What did my teacher say?
Did the meeting not go well?
I heard you take photos.
Did you not tell me because cameras are expensive?
It's just an extracurricular
activity I'm involved in.
Are you upset?
Show me your pictures next time.
Share this with your friends.
Not him, though.
Bye.
Does your brother hate me?
I don't know.
Cry, hit, kiss?
No. Hit, cry, kiss.
Closed?
Hello?
This is Sunwoo Hae's number, though...
Hello, did you just find this phone?
Oh, I guess not.
Can you tell me where you are?
Got it. I'll be right there. Okay.
If it's not urgent, please come back later.
This shop is the best.
Okay.
She must have grown up smelling flowers.
Sunwoo Hae!
Sunwoo Hae?
You called earlier!
Yes, hello.
He's out on an errand.
He'll be back soon. Look around.
Okay.
I'm losing steam here.
Where did he go?
I'm going to buy something.
Aigoo, I'm sorry I was staring.
It's the first time someone has come to see Hae.
I was wondering who you were.
You're her, right?
You guys must be totally smitten with each other.
Oh, ma'am!
- Change the light bulb.
- Okay.
Don't hang out in the dark.
Got it.
Here.
What took you so long?
How did you know I was here?
The class president knows everything!
So, be careful.
Are you a regular here?
You two seem close.
You don't remember?
She was our nurse in high school.
My goodness. I don't remember.
So, she retired and opened a used bookstore?
Her grandmother used to run it.
She took over about five years ago.
I see.
If I don't read something, I feel like
my head is going to be empty.
On my days off, I help out.
I told her not to put this book here...
Hey, someone must have sold a gifted book.
"We've been together for almost 100 days.
The college entrance exam will be over in 99 days."
Look at these guys, dating instead of studying.
You're right.
"I hope we get into the same school. I love you."
Since they sold the book, they must
not have gone to the same school.
How cute.
Cute?
Yes.
We're almost touching.
I know.
What are you guys doing?
Aigoo...
I left my phone behind.
I'm going to buy these books.
I mean, it took her a bunch of trips
to the flower shop to buy anything.
I'm seeing her differently now.
How did you see her?
Never mind.
The first meeting went smoothly,
so I didn't think there would be issues.
Nam Jun Ho's wife is too much.
There aren't that many female
managers in this field.
We're not the only ones who want Nam Jun Ho.
Let's decide quickly.
I hate being a CEO in moments like this.
At the end of the day, I make the
call that makes me money.
Hey! Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Do you want to ride bikes?
What?
No, I don't know how to ride one.
There's something on your face.
Where? Here?
No. Lower your head a bit.
There's nothing on my face. What are you doing?
Kiss.
- What?
- I have a plan.
I'm going for it.
Is this what you meant by getting through to me?
I don't know. I need to try to know.
Seriously?
Why are you laughing?
You're being funny.
- I'm funny?
- Yes!
Am I just funny?
♫ When I revisit a day I kept in my heart ♫
Sung Je Yeon.
What?
Want me to...
teach you how to ride a bike?
I...
want to enjoy this feeling I have.
It's been a long time. This kind of thing.
I don't know how much patience I have,
but there's one way to extend it.
Hang out with me.
I'm on vacation.
Even if you don't want to.
I want to.
Hey, hey, we're on the rooftop!
Hey, why are you...
Hey!
I think it was a cliff!
I'm sorry! I just wanted to try that once.
Do this.
I always wondered why people take these photos.
- But it's nice.
- See?
Look at your face here.
So funny.
- Hey, you're going again?
- Yeah.
- Wait a second.
- Okay.
Hello?
Oh, hello. By chance, could I get it next time?
Or, could you leave it at the door?
Is that so?
Okay, I'll be right there. Okay.
Try this on.
I have to go right now.
- Right now?
- Well...
the credit card I ordered is
being delivered right now.
Just tell them to leave it.
I have to sign for it.
Sorry.
- I'll leave, then.
- Okay.
See you later.
This was fun.
Same.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Okay.
- Get home safe.
It's raining!
How strange.
It just came on!
Why did the lights come on when I walked in?
Is it a motion sensor?
Are the flowers okay?
It was just half a day, so I think we're good.
They were hydrated, too.
It's cool that this is a refrigerator.
Some shops don't have one.
I bought this one because it has one.
Why are you here again?
Here.
To give you the photos.
What?
I had both of them.
What a strange day.
I find out about my sister's secret skill,
the power goes out in my shop,
and someone shows up at the used bookstore.
I rode a bike for the first time in forever,
and it started raining suddenly.
And you are here again.
I don't know what comes next.
In the past and now, when I'm with you,
I don't really think about my sob story.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Just stay still.
I think we have the right mood.
What... What do you mean it's right?
I'm trying to say something serious.
Were you even listening?
I know.
I've only been thinking about this today.
Hey, Sung Je Yeon!
You're thinking way too much. Okay?
Think less.
You could have...
turned away.
I couldn't have.
Sung Je Yeon, you're really strong.
Can you teach me how to ride a bike this weekend?
Hello.
When my employees whined
about wanting a spot to rest,
I didn't get why we would need that.
But it's nice.
The person leading the charge was Bang Han Na.
Fearlessly.
How's work these days?
I've been reflecting on things plenty.
Whatever you give me, I'll work hard at it.
Tae Rin is gone.
You don't have an assigned actor.
You feel a little adrift, don't you?
I have good news and bad news.
The good news is that we're
signing with Nam Jun Ho.
That's great!
You've wanted him for a long time.
The bad news is...
You have to quit being a manager.
M-Me?
- But why?
- Nam Jun Ho's wife doesn't like you.
- I don't know why.
- Do you think that's reasonable?
I don't think it's reasonable.
But I need to pick the more important thing.
The company needs Nam Jun Ho.
I'll move you to another department.
If you're not a manager, it's not a problem.
If I weren't a manager,
how could I not be a problem?
That would be the biggest problem for me.
I've worked in this field at this one company...
for six years. Six years.
While others switched jobs several
times, got raises, and promotions,
I devoted myself to this place.
Because of you, CEO.
It doesn't feel good to push out one
of my own because of his antics.
I've been grateful to you for a lot all this time.
But I don't know about today.
I'll request a vacation.
This is so shitty.
I've been running the numbers...
waiting for my pension.
I'll have to commute on public transit now.
This is a company car.
What about my place?
I'm going to have to live on the streets.
What about my rent?
I have nothing to my name.
It might rain tomorrow.
We might not be able to ride bikes.
If it rains, let's do something else.
What are you doing?
Hey. I'm working. What's up?
I miss you.
Okay.
I mean, we're seeing each other tomorrow.
Is something going on?
No, nothing.
I guess I just wanted to hear your voice.
- Want me to come over?
- No.
I heard your voice, so I'm good.
You have a customer.
Welcome. One second.
Bye.
Goodness.
How is Nu Ri doing?
Sunwoo Chan told me you're raising her.
Is that true?
Did he tell you to come here?
I saw you on TV.
When we lived together, he always
bragged about his son.
As soon as I saw you, I remembered.
He always asked for paperwork when he needed it,
but he wouldn't talk when I asked about my child.
If it weren't for the show,
I wouldn't have found you.
I thought he had abandoned her
and was putting on a show with me.
I think you both abandoned her.
I'm just getting back on my feet now.
Back then, I really had nothing.
Having a nice shop and all,
you wouldn't know what that's like.
A father's love... a mother's love...
I guess those feelings come back
when you have money.
You're young, but you must've been through a lot.
I'm not here to ask for my child back.
I know it's shameless, but I want to see her.
I'd like to see her occasionally
and get to know her.
That's all I need.
Please, I ask you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for not being too late.
I'll let Nu Ri know.
Thank you.
I see...
The kiss worked.
Hey, what's up?
Look outside.
The moon is out. Look at the moon.
The moon is out every night.
What's so special about it?
Wow, it's nice.
Nice, right?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Stop looking at the moon.
Look down, too.
What?
Why are you here?
You said you missed me.
Want to come down?
No.
I'll just watch you from here.
I can see you clearly from here
because your face is big.
Not as big as yours.
What did you come here for? To start a fight?
Are we going to keep talking like this?
You have no idea what I'll say.
I had a really hard day today.
Why?
Who was it? Huh?
What is it? Tell me.
Just work.
But seeing you...
makes me want to run over
and dance under the moon.
But I can't.
I must be getting older.
If I were nineteen? I'd run out immediately.
Today must've been hard.
Got it. Get some rest.
That day...
I told my mom she would have liked you.
Bye.
Good night.
Right, I'm on vacation.
Sung Je Yeon.
I won't be a burden.
Sung Je Yeon, what do you think
of a guy with an illness?
I'm a little sick.
Seriously...
Hurry up.
The customer can't answer the call right now.
The phone is turned off.
You'll be connected to the voicemail.
After the beep, there will be a charge.
Are you awake?
- Hyung...
- We're in the hospital.
When I got there after you called,
you were passed out.
I'm screwed.
Why? Does it hurt? Hae!
Don't close your eyes.
You can't cross to the other side!
It hurts, Hyung.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
My phone...
Hey, hey! No!
Can you take out this IV?
Hey, I'm too scared to take it out.
The medicine is still working. Just hold on.
Hyung, you have Sung Je Yeon's number, right?
- For being my agent.
- Yeah.
I didn't save it, but let me look in my call history.
I have to go...
Seriously?
You're going to do this to me, too?
Sung Je Yeon.
Hey.
How long have you been here?
Hey, why are your hands so cold?
Let's... Let's go inside.
Je-
Hey, wait.
Wait. Wait a minute.
Something happened to me today.
I tried to get in touch with you,
but I left my phone at home, so...
I...
must like you a lot.
Now that I see your face,
I'm relieved.
I was so scared.
I had all kinds of thoughts.
Is he sick?
Did he get into an accident?
I was scared to death the whole day!
And why don't you have an umbrella?
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Promise me this will never happen again.
What if...
What if I can't promise?
What?
If something like this happens again...
no matter...
how I end up going,
the end is going to be like this.
♫ Can we go back? ♫
♫ Everything was clumsy ♫
What?
We should stop seeing each other.
Why are you saying that?
♫ If I could go back ♫
I...
think I knew.
I knew, but I think I wanted to
believe that there was a reason
you hesitated.
When this is all I am...
to you.
Okay.
Let's stop here.
♫ We flow through time ♫
♫ Because of you, I can breathe ♫
♫ When I go back to my shadow ♫
♫ Greet me again as your shining self ♫
Give me a break.
♫ That brilliant season ♫
♫ I would never leave you ♫
♫ Into eternity ♫
Hyung.
Hae, where are you?
I can't come to work today. Sorry.
What are you sorry for? Don't worry about it.
Let's go to the hospital.
You passed out yesterday.
Maybe you're getting worse.
Maybe I'm getting worse.
I'm sorry.
Why does she carry this around?
"So, why are you looking?
Want to get in the vase instead of the roses?
And turn all red?"
Why does this sound like flirting?
Am I crazy?
If I leave now, will you spare me?
No.
So, you won't.
What you threw away last time.
I didn't bring your handkerchief, though.
I told you to keep it.
Isn't she going to buy chairs?
They were sent to her parents' place.
So, this is how everyone gets by.
Your bank statements, credit card statements,
a list of paperwork will be emailed today.
Today, I just need your bank
statements up to last month.
Okay.
But my authentication certificate
is on Je Yeon's laptop.
You have it stored there?
You must really trust your manager.
- We can get it reissued.
- Wait.
Let me call Je Yeon and ask her to bring it.
Hey, where are you? What's up?
- She really doesn't listen to me.
- Okay.
She has an important meeting. She had to go.
Last one.
Bye. I'm in an important meeting.
Team Leader, I heard you're
on a really long vacation.
Who am I supposed to ask questions
to without you here?
We're not managing any actors right now.
I've never taken a day off.
You have a problem with this?
I don't know.
I miss driving.
Give it to me.
Be honest. Are you quitting?
That's what it looks like.
Taking more than 10 days off?
Is it because Dong Jun got
to work with Nam Jun Ho?
Oh, that's what happened?
You have frequent transactions
at a certain stationery store.
What do you buy?
They're wasting time here, too.
I'm glad I'm an actress.
I said, what did you buy at this stationery store?
A shovel?
Well, bubbles.
I blow bubbles when I feel like smoking.
How nice. I do bubbles, too.
Which one? Bubble gun? Bubble machine?
No way.
You have to blow it yourself.
That's right. It's no fun to just press buttons.
So unromantic.
We are in complete agreement.
It only feels good when you make an effort.
I don't think we can write that off, though.
How about your car? Is it leased? Your own?
When do you have time?
- Let's blow bubbles together.
- I thought you didn't like me.
So what? There are bubbles I can't blow by myself.
Let's do it together. No ulterior motive.
You're so weird.
Do it with me, even if I'm weird.
I really want to try it.
I'll see how you do, Mo Tae Rin.
It's weird not to drink.
Welcome.
I'm still angry.
When I lie down to sleep, all I see is your face.
It's frustrating. Maddening.
Have you been drinking?
Yes, I have.
That's all I have to do right now, okay?
I thought I would seem so pathetic.
I thought I shouldn't have.
I should've just kept it cool and ghosted.
I should've held back.
I should've held back one more time.
I'm so annoyed that this is what I think about!
Today is the end.
Today is the last day I'm a mess over you.
Then, I'll forget all about you.
I'm never, ever going to...
act like I know you again!
Okay.
What is it?
This isn't the person I know.
You weren't like this.
What did I do so wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
It's all because of me.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Let go.
Hey, careful.
Don't touch me!
- Get up.
- Let go.
Let go! Let go of me.
Don't touch me.
Don't follow me.
I told you not to follow me.
You think I'm a joke?
When I saw you cry because of me that day...
I realized you probably came angry
but I might not be there.
That worried me.
I don't want you to waste yourself on me.
Hilarious.
Who are you worried about?
Je Yeon.
I'm...
sick.
It feels real now.
♫ Come closer ♫
♫ The red sunset ♫
♫ Night and day meet briefly ♫
♫ Like us from back then ♫
♫ Like falling into it ♫
♫ Pretending not to know and embrace ♫
♫ It's like love that gets pushed away ♫
♫ Like the longing that comes back ♫
♫ Like the horizon where day and night meet ♫