Mr. Lu,
something big happened. Come quickly!
I'll send you the location.
Go to hell!
I will definitely settle this score with you.
Just you wait.
Duoduo!
Let's go.
How are you feeling?
Where am I?
My place.
Your place?
Before.
You scared me to death.
Without my permission,
don't meet with anyone from the company.
Do you understand?
I...
Lie down first.
Rest well here.
I'm going to the office.
Please keep an eye on things here.
I'll be out for a while.
That's enough.
You've had too much to drink.
I'm not drunk.
Enough.
I know all these years
you've been suppressing your feelings.
This isn't the life I wanted.
What can I do?
It's time to let go.
Some things,
once they've begun,
can't be stopped.
Since I've made my choice,
I'll see it through to the end.
Since I've chosen this path,
I must go all the way.
Feeling better now?
Damn it.
I originally wanted to create an accident
so you could die quietly.
But you're too damn lucky,
escaping every time against the odds.
Damn it.
This time,
you won't be so lucky.
Hurry!
Quick!
Beat him!
I told you before,
once you're on Mr. Qian's list,
there's no escape for you.
Mr. Lu,
quickly, untie Mr. Lu!
Damn.
Mr. Lu, what do you say
we do with this guy?
Tell me who sent you.
Don't worry, Mr. Lu,
when it comes to interrogation,
we have plenty of ways to make him talk.
Yes.
It was Lu Yi.
Don't kill me.
Mr. Lu, why did you come all the way here to meet?
I wanted to see you today
for nothing special,
just wanted to show you
something.
This...
Mr. Li,
you've been my father's subordinate for many years.
I've always respected you greatly.
But abusing your position
for personal gain...
If this gets out,
it wouldn't sound very good, would it?
Have some tea.
This photo...
if your wife sees it,
you know what the consequences would be.
Mr. Lu, just tell me
what you want me to do.
No rush. When I need you,
I'll contact you.
Just tell me
what you want me to do.
Lu Tongchen and Longchuan Group's
shady dealings...
I know everything about them.
He just wants Lu Yi
to replace you, right?
Nobody's stupid.
Everyone sees what's happening,
but most people
are in cahoots with him.
There are benefits involved.
What if
I can offer them enough benefits?
Then at that time,
those same people
will be running around
serving you instead.
Come in.
Mr. Lu, you wanted to see me?
How long have you been with the company?
Less than a year.
Starting tomorrow,
you don't need to come to work anymore.
What did I do wrong?
I've registered a new company
and want to transfer you there
as the person in charge.
So I'm getting promoted?
I guess so.
Shouldn't it be Pang De?
Why would you choose me?
I've thought about it
and feel you're more suitable.
So,
go to HR to process your resignation later.
Starting tomorrow,
you'll no longer be an employee of Jindu.
This matter
stays between us.
Don't tell anyone,
understand?
Understood, Mr. Lu.
I have something to attend to later.
You and Pang De
take Anduo and the children back to the village.
Be careful on the way.
Don't worry, Mr. Lu.
Process your resignation first.
We've won this project bid every year.
Why did it fail this year?
What's going on?
Mr. Zhao just called to inform us
that they're suspending cooperation this year.
What did you say?
Suspending cooperation.
Notify all executives in the group
for an immediate meeting.
Yes, Mr. Lu.
Is everyone here?
Lu Ye hasn't arrived yet.
We won't wait.
Recently, our group's
companies have been facing one problem after another.
The projects we always secure have failed to attract bids.
Our regular partner
has announced a suspension of cooperation.
If we don't resolve this soon,
you can all prepare for bankruptcy and liquidation.
So in your opinion,
what should we do?
We've been too picky in the past,
and neglected our smaller subsidiaries.
Now we're
going to pay a heavy price.
If all else fails,
we'll have to sell the factories at a low price.
We don't have any orders for next year anyway.
If we close the factories,
the local government will definitely make us pay back
all the tax exemptions from recent years.
Um, Anduo,
there's something
I really need to tell you.
Actually, Director Lu and that female model,
nothing happened between them.
This was all a setup by Lu Yi
to frame Director Lu.
How do you know?
Well, let me tell you,
but you can't tell Director Lu.
I got this information from Lu Yi's side.
Thank you.
No problem.
Anduo.
There's something I want to tell you.
Mr. Lu was truly wronged.
The information I got
from Longchuan is absolutely true.
Also, about this matter,
don't tell Mr. Lu.
I hope you two can be happy together.
Don't worry. I won't tell him.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm leaving now.
Are you alone, beautiful?
Want to have a drink together?
Let's drink up.
I'm fine with drinking this.
But after we finish,
should we go somewhere else?
Where to?
Come with me.
Get lost.
No fun at all.
Here you are.
It's rare for you to have time to join me for a drink.
Here.
Go ahead.
What did you want to see me about?
Nothing special.
I just wanted to tell you
to stay away from those questionable women.
It affects your image.
There's only one month left before the deadline.
When the time comes,
you can continue acquiring Jindu's shares.
I won't stop you.