Why
did you go to the village
without caring about your appearance?
Seems like you know
quite a lot about my whereabouts, Ms. Long.
About you,
there's still a lot I don't know.
It seems you've spent
quite a bit of money on me.
How about this:
you give me the money,
and I'll report my whereabouts
to you 24 hours a day.
Fine.
Have a cup of coffee.
Just shipped from Panama.
Your favorite Geisha from Alps Estate.
How is it?
It tastes good.
But recently I've
started to prefer tea.
I don't have any tea here.
That's not what I meant.
Why are you acquiring
Jindu Group's shares?
To make money.
This is clearly
a losing investment.
What's wrong, Lu Ye?
Even you have lost faith
in Jindu Group?
I came to see you today
to ask for one month's time.
You can't do much in such a short time.
One month is enough.
Fine.
I'll give you one month.
Wait.
In exchange,
you need to do something for me.
What is it?
The chairman has treated me well all these years.
For this small amount of money,
I really feel like I'm betraying my conscience.
I didn't realize you were still playing your part, Mr. Ma.
I'm telling the truth.
I understand what you mean.
You think it's not enough money.
How about this,
you take this money first.
After it's done,
I'll give you a bigger bonus.
Alright.
Then I'll wait for your news.
What are you doing, mister?
Damn it!
Can you turn off the music?
It's giving me the creeps.
Creation requires inspiration.
Makeup is also a form of creation.
Cut it out and turn it off now.
You're scared of ghosts yet you're dressing up as one.
I'm not scared if I can't see myself.
Wait.
How is it? Feel anything?
Let me show you with a mirror.
No, no, no!
I don't want to look.
As long as you look scary to others.
I feel like
you're scarier without makeup.
What's that supposed to mean?
I...
I'm telling you, you'll be the first one I take away.
Damn it, you fat idiot! You scared me to death!
How's it going?
Why isn't this person here yet? My legs are getting numb.
Awesome!
What's wrong? Have we been discovered?
Where's Dezi?
Say something!
It's over.
No, talk to me. What's wrong with you? Why are you like this?
Take a deep breath. Slow down.
We're almost there.
My son.
My dear boy.
Lu Ye
Lin Anduo
Lu Yi
Long Baiqi
Yuan Xiao
Pang De
Park Ji-hwan
Phoebe
Lu Heguang
Lu Tongchen
Mr. Li
Ma Zhong
Dr. Zhu
Long Baiqi's Assistant
Lu Yi's Assistant
Old Lady in Red
Manager Sun
Director Shen
Qian Xinfa
Young Lu Ye
Debt Collector
Han Liwei
Tian Yixuan
Shen Jianhua
Xiang Haitao
Wang Kunpeng
Xiao Han
Li Nan
Shan Shuangshuang
Fu Tingting   Niu Li
Wang Yao
Zhang Yifan
Zhao Hongbo
Wu Yi   Zhang Yifan
Mu Shuaiming
Guo Xuebing
Feng Yi
Zhu Bing
Mu Shuaiming   Wei Xue
Zhang Zhonglian   Shao Kun
Shen Tong   Song Yangfang
Chen Dengke
Cao Qi   Sun Longfei
Liu Yaowen   Sun Peixiang
Zhang Yunhao   Huang Kunxiang
Sun Zhongjie   Li Yingchun
Wang Yawei
Wang Pengwei
Wang Xiaopeng   Cao Jiming
Su Xinwei   Wang Pengju
Zhou Lei
Cao Ligeng
Tang Yapeng
Zhan Yongqi
Liu Fuhao   Niu Shuo
Qian Zhen
Yang Xihe
Fan Xinglong, Zou Wendi
Zhao Lingmin
Qiu Ren
Chen Lanxiang, Yang Lu
Hou Weikun, Ren Xingkui
Zhao Yang
Liu Yanqi
Yang Qinghua
Li Yongqiang
Jia Guangchao
Wang Xiaolu, Qiu Xu
Wang Xianbo
Li Zhijie, Yuan Xinyang
Shi Zexiang, Zhao Weiqiang
Zhang Jianhui
Zhang Xianglin, Wang Bin
Ren Junguang
He Jiannan
Wu Lei, Liu Maolin
Yao Xiaogang, Zhao Gang
Li Yanhong, Wei Xiaoyong
Wang Honggang, Yin Dajun
Sima Lin, Liu Yong
Luo Guojian