Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in
the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Let’s go, Korat!
Damn it. Dad has frozen my card.
฿100,000 is fine. I’ll take it.
Do you think my dad will flip out if he finds out I sold the big bike?
I’m thinking I should buy it back.
If you want it back, pay me ฿150,000.
Thanks for your ฿90,000.
Son of a bitch, you cheated.
This big bike is yours?
Please, I beg you. Let me have my bike back.
Then beg at my feet.
I told you, right?
What’s already yours, you must take good care of it.
Special room service from the hotel, sir.
Why is this hotel staff wearing my jersey?
It’s also a special service, sir.
So you’ll get my scent on it.
You’re kinda addicted to it, aren’t you?
Well, I do have your scent all over me after last night.
That was mind-blowing, wasn’t it?
Last night? Last night what?
Think and say again.
Nothing happened.
We simply went to sleep right after wound dressings.
Then how did you get that mark there?
This mark…
A mosquito bite, probably.
A mosquito bite?
What are you doing?
Hey, Kang!
I’m gonna bite you.
Nooo!.
Kang, it’s ticklish.
One more bite from me. I’m hungry.
Kang, no!
Let me taste your blood.
Here.
What's wrong?
Did you forget something?
No.
I was thinking since I’m already in Korat.
Should I go to the training camp?
That’s a good idea.
But the coach isn’t going to chew you out, right?
It's better to face the scolding here than at school.
Plus, my jersey has your scent on it.
It gives me a 300% kicking power on the field.
I pray for you not to get kicked by the coach before anything else.
Alright. Let's get going now.
Yes, Dad.
I’ll be back home after the match tomorrow.
I’m not doing this match for you,
but for myself.
Coach,
thank you for giving me another chance.
Don’t worry. I understand how teenagers are.
I’ve been through it all. I understand.
Took you long enough.
I thought you already took my friend out of the country with you.
How is it? Your honeymoon getaway.
Sweet to the core, I bet?
Honeymoon?
Honeymoon, my foot.
Go, the coach is calling all of you now.
Go.
You go to.
You too. Head to your training.
Give it your all.
You haven’t answered yet. Do spill.
Go!
Need a hand?
Don't you have anything else to do?
Nah, Mrs. Ging is able to start walking on her own now.
She said I could go do something else.
Does this job pay you enough to afford a luxury watch?
It’s a long story.
Mr. Kong gave it to me for free.
He wants to apologize for a misunderstanding.
You know something?
Mr. Kong has such an impressive watch collection.
Some of them are worth nearly 10 million baht.
How great is it to be rich?
This friggin car is just a fraction of his money.
I wish I had a fraction of the money to get a car like this too.
I dream of traveling around the world, you know?
Me too.
I want to…
Go to America, right?
I remember how you were so obsessed with The Fast and the Furious.
You wanted to be like Vin Diesel.
Damn it!
How could you remember that?
I remember everything about you.
I just didn't expect to run into you under these circumstances.
You must be disappointed to see me like this.
I thought you had changed into a different person.
But the more I get to be with you,
the more time we spend together,
The more I see the old Name who wanted to be Vin Diesel.
That’s all it takes to make me happy.
How about this?
If we ever become rich, let’s travel the world together.
I'm not sure when that will happen, though.
But, yeah, let’s do it.
Can I ask you something?
Aren’t you upset that I asked you to work here?
Well, I know you’re worried about me.
I’m fine with this kind of job.
However,
I haven’t told my boss about this yet.
What?
So you…
So…
Wait a sec.
You skipped work there to come here, and you are yet to tell your boss?
Won’t that get you in trouble?
Tonight,
I'll have a talk with him.
Mr. Jeng,
I…
It's good that you're here.
Help me put some pepper on.
Where the hell have you been these last few days?
I have some matters to take care of.
You know me, right?
I hate liars.
I’m sorry.
I’ve been thinking about….
quitting this job.
Why do you want to quit?
I don't want to kill people.
I know I owe you a debt of gratitude,
but I just can’t go down that path.
So you want to leave me
to be a chauffeur for that rich family?
You knew?
For the sake of being my favorite,
I'll let you quit
after you finish this one job for me.
Aren’t you going to Korat to cheer on Kang tomorrow?
You know I have to attend the governor’s birthday party tomorrow.
Yes, I know.
I just double-checked in case you’ve changed your mind.
Like father, like son.
Do you remember when you were young?
You were angry with me and stayed at your friend’s place for weeks.
You only returned home after I reached out to reconcile with you.
I remember.
I was quite stubborn back then.
Not all that different from how you are now.
Finish up your work and get to bed.
I'm going to sleep as well. My head is heavy.
Good night, Mom.
Hold on.
Why did you decide to give in and reconcile with me?
I spoke quite harshly to you back then.
Matured people know they can’t always be 100% right.
It’s a matter of being able to accept when they’re wrong.
Fortunately,
I learned to do that early on.
That’s all.
[Sailom: I secretly recorded Kang practicing for you.]
We’re going to the restaurant where the governor’s party is, right?
Um.
Uh…Change of plans.
Can you do me a favor and deliver this to the governor for me?
I’ll take another car.
Where are you headed?
Korat.
Kang, you’ve got this!
Mr. Kong! Hi.
What brings you here?
I’m not busy, so I want to watch Kang play.
But I just received a message from my party that I have a meeting this evening.
I must leave soon.
Do you also like playing football?
I’m obsessed with it.
I was a school athlete when I was young.
Girls went crazy when I was on the field.
Seriously?
Kang never told me about it.
That’s because I never told him.
I was afraid it might put too much pressure on him if he knew.
So I let him do whatever he likes to do.
But doing that also made him feel neglected.
I’m sorry. I just…
It’s okay. I understand.
Can I ask you?
What has my son told you about me?
He’s upset because you don’t encourage him to try anything.
He feels worthless.
He feels like he’s good for nothing.
He even vented his anger by bullying other students at school.
But I already taught him a lesson.
I must be a really bad father.
I’m sure you have your reasons.
Yes.
It’s a promise I made with my wife
before she passed away.
How did it go?
Not bad. I got to see the governor in person.
No, I’m talking about you quitting working for Mr. Jeng.
How did it go?
He allowed me to quit,
but he asked me to do one last task for him.
Don’t tell me that he asked you to kill someone.
No.
Then why the concerned look on your face?
I need your help with quite a few things.
Gosh.
Medic!
Ouch.
Argh. It hurts.
We’re screwed.
Tell me about it.
Yeah!
Nice!
That was awesome.
Hey, you could even score from a free kick.
No sweat.
Wow. Awesome!
Your drink.
Thanks.
How’s Guy doing?
He’s still being examined by the doctor.
You were amazing on the field.
You scored 5 goals by yourself.
My boyfriend is here. I must show off.
What a whipped boy.
Is everything alright?
You know what?
I got back into football
to show my dad I can do everything without relying on his help.
What a shame.
He couldn’t witness it after all.
Actually, he was here.
But he had to leave early for an important meeting.
He was here?
Yes.
Kang,
you really mean a lot to him, you know?
That's bullshit.
Then why does everything seem like the opposite?
You know what he has done to me.
What if he had his reasons?
What are his damn reasons?
Is it because I’m so incapable that he can’t stand to watch?
I talked to him.
What he told me is not what you think at all.
It’s a promise I made with my wife
before she passed away.
A promise?
Back then, I was very strict with Kang.
Can you imagine the kind of father kids hate?
I disciplined him when his grades dropped.
I scolded him when he played video games.
My wife had to intervene every time.
I see.
Then my wife fell seriously ill.
She gave me her last wish.
I still remember her words to this day.
“Don’t be too harsh on Kang.”
That’s why you…
Yes.
It’s quite hard for me.
If I’m strict and put pressure on Kang,
that means I’m being too harsh on him.
The only way I don’t have to be that
is by letting him be.
Whatever Kang wants to do or to become,
I should let him.
I keep telling myself every day, “Don’t have expectations.”
“Don’t put any pressure on him.”
But what happened that day made me realize
that what I’ve done might have always been wrong.
The truth is…
he actually wanted to have expectations of you.
He just couldn’t do it
because of that promise.
Hey, want to join us for a feast. It’s on Coach.
Nah, I think I’ll pass.
I should head home.
What’s waiting for you at home that’s got you in a rush?
My old man.
Let’s get going.
Sure.
Can I ask you to take my stuff with you?
No problem.
See you.
What happened?
Grandma.
How’s the patient?
I’m sorry
that my brother caused this trouble.
I believe that your brother didn’t do it.
No matter what happens,
I will go through this together with you.