Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Then I’ll go try out for the school football team.
I’ll be a school football player who also makes it into a public university.
Aren’t you being too ambitious?
Because I have my wind, this windmill can spin.
And I'm sure I have your full support. I see no reason why I can't achieve it.
Kang, you’ve got this!
You’re one hella talented rich kid, the most talented one in my eyes.
So I got to be an athlete because you pulled some strings?
A kid like you, without my help, what do you think you can accomplish?
Where are you going?
Anywhere but here.
I don’t know where you want to go, but I’m going with you.
So?
What’s the plan?
Where do we go from here?
I’m not sure yet.
But I won’t rely on my dad’s money anymore.
So he’d stop claiming that, without him,
I couldn’t do anything on my own.
I might as well just snap this card in half.
Wait. Hold on.
Do you really think that’s gonna impress him?
You’ve got a point.
Good. I think…
If his money is still sitting untouched in there,
it will make him too happy.
He might think I’ve finally grown up the way he wanted.
I’m gonna spend all his money.
What?
Hold on. What crap did you just say?
I’m going to withdraw all the cash from this card.
I will splash it all out until my dad begs me to stop.
I’m gonna wipe out his money.
(What the hell?)
[Please enter amount - 20,000 baht - Confirm]
Woah.
Why is there a ฿20,000 limit per withdrawal?
It’s so annoying. My cash advance limit is ฿100,000.
Stop talking and stash the money.
Do you want to attract thieves?
Let’s go explore.
And spend it all.
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere.
Hey. Put the money in the bag already, Kang!
Woah.
Since we were already planning on coming here.
Let’s go, Korat!
I'm starting to feel hungry. Let's find something to eat.
Let's go.
I've looked it up.
There’s a must-try noodle place around here. I'll take you there.
Nah.
We’re super rich now.
How about I treat you to a good meal?
Let this daddy pay.
Daddy?
What’s the treat, Daddy?
We’ll have this.
This, this, this, and this.
What?
My brother is disappearing with Kang?
Uh... Mr. Kanghan?
Yes, I can't get hold of either of them.
Do you have any idea where they might be?
I can help search for them.
You don't need to.
This isn't the first time Kang has behaved this way.
He'll be home in a few days.
I have to be in a meeting now.
Damn. We’ve finally spent it all.
It's surprisingly challenging to spend all that cash.
Come on.
So this is the hardship of the rich.
Now you have used up the money.
What are you going to use for the days to come?
I can cash out more tomorrow.
A hundred grand for today, I’ll get another hundred grand tomorrow.
I have no idea what to spend it on.
How about I use it to pay off your debts?
What?
No. Keep it for yourself.
Let me ask you this.
If I were to wake up tomorrow with no money,
with absolutely nothing,
would you still like me?
Read my lips carefully.
I…
like…
you.
I used to have this thought, though.
If my life weren’t so tough, what would it be like?
Should I be your sugar baby? I don’t have to struggle this much.
Why not?
I’m expensive.
Doesn’t matter. I’m rich.
Really?
But it’ll have to be tomorrow to become rich again.
I’ve got no money left today.
I have to wait until tomorrow?
Yes, tomorrow.
That’s too long.
I don’t believe you are completely out of cash.
Completely.
Seriously?
Seriously.
I still see some in your bag.
Sorry.
I don’t have much cash left, so the best I could do was just this.
“Just this”? This is fancy as hell to me.
Fancy, my foot.
The furniture is outdated.
I'm not even sure if this room has a water heater.
I doubt Kang will show up.
He's probably out and about with Sailom at the moment.
If I had known, I wouldn't have come either.
See? You guys have this bad habit.
Now my friend has become a bad boy too.
Normally, Sailom never ghosts me or leaves my texts unanswered.
Who knows?
It could be your friend who has a negative influence on my friend.
It’s your friend.
Hey, hey, hey!
Cut it out already.
Go run.
Got it, Coach.
It’s your friend.
This side!
- It’s your friend rubbing off on mine.
- Come on. This is no good.
- No, it’s your friend.
- How can we beat anyone? Be stronger!
[Please enter amount - 20,000 baht - Confirm]
[Sorry. This card has been suspended.
Transaction declined, please contact your bank.]
Damn it. Dad has frozen my card.
What?
Damn. I should have maxed out that card.
What a shame.
Seriously.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Do you think I should get those kids a new ball?
Come on. You should worry about your own ass first.
Your once wealthy self is now broke.
Do you have money to buy anything for them?
I do.
I’m rich.
I’ve got an asset I can turn into cash.
Come on. The resale price of this model is ฿200,000.
I didn’t use it that often. The condition is near perfect.
The bike’s condition is good.
But look at you, you two look like thugs.
You don’t even have a document to prove your ownership of this bike.
Give it to me straight. Did you steal it?
Look, here's a picture of me with this bike.
Do I look like the owner now?
Alright.
I can give you ฿80,000 max.
Come on. Just ฿80,000?
Can you offer a little more?
Do you plan to profit from this and achieve financial freedom?
฿80,100 then?
Are you serious? Don’t be joking.
Fine, ฿100,000!
Take it or leave it.
Can we get ฿130,000?
No.
฿100,000 is fine.
I’ll take it.
Hey!
Now we’re talking.
Alright, deal!
Damn it, Kang.
You idiot!
Yeah, like that. Good.
How’s that?
Now shoot!
Yeah.
Very good.
How is it?
Do you play better with these football shoes?
Yes.
Good, right?
Very good.
Let’s have a drink.
Come on, kids. Get your drinks.
Yo. Yo. Yo!
Come on. Get your drinks.
This will make you refreshed.
Shit. I gave away all of them.
I don’t have one left for myself.
Oh, oh. They’re all gone.
Look. I’ve got an extra one
My boyfriend is so thoughtful.
But sorry, this can is reserved just for me.
It’s all mine.
Super duper good.
You sure you’re not sharing that with me?
Um.
You sure?
Sure?
Hm.
Sure, sure?
Hmm.
- Really sure?
- Hmm?
Oi, Kang!
Are you giving it to me?
Argh, Kang!
I feel so refreshed.
Don’t finish it all. Save some for me.
What?
No.
What the hell?
No, I don’t want it now.
No, Kang. I don’t want it.
I’m good now.
I don’t want to drink it anymore.
No.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Do you think my dad will flip out if he finds out I sold the big bike?
Then what’s already yours, make sure to take good care of it.