[Eternal Brotherhood 2]
[Episode 14]
You two, go check over there.
you two, go over there.
After him!
I'm here!
Retreat!
General, I came too late to your rescue.
You're here. That's all that matters.
General, are you alright?
Third Brother,
I've met with the guards from home.
That blade is too valuable.
I'll keep it for you for now.
Third... Brother?
I am King of Light of Yuanzhou.
I finally made it back to my hometown.
I've already run out of my rations
before I could gather any supplies.
Even my blade is gone.
So miserable.
It's alright.
I...
What?
Prince Ka Dun is coming
to supervise the battle himself?
That must not happen!
Just tell him
there's a plague outbreak in Yuanzhou.
The situation is very serious.
I'll invite him over
once it's under control.
My Lord,
maybe we shouldn't keep hiding the truth.
We must win a solid victory
to give the prince a proper explanation!
Where are the soldiers I asked for?
They've arrived. 50,000 soldiers in total.
I wanted to win a swift victory
and take the sacred temple in one strike.
But we ended up stirring a hornet's nest.
Just dealing with the uprisings everywhere
has drained too much of our forces.
Let's stick to the original plan.
Strike directly at their headquarters!
Notify all units
we'll set out immediately.
Attack Bulu Village!
Kill King of Light!
Yes!
The team is still searching for supplies.
I'm afraid we won't be able
to hold out much longer.
Report!
Lu Di is leading
50,000 North Clan soldiers,
marching straight toward Bulu Village!
It seems they intend to take the village!
Don't panic!
Thankfully, Lord Xiu left us this pouch
before he left.
Surrender?
Next time. For sure.
Definitely.
No one is guarding the village?
What is King of Light up to?
King of Light is cunning.
This must be another one of his tricks.
Eyes. Watch your eyes.
I am the first deputy general
under King of Light.
On behalf of all the villagers here,
we surrender!
[We surrender]
Come out now.
What trick is King of Light playing now?
My Lord, I'd like to know that too.
King of Light heard that you, Lord Lu Di,
were coming with 50,000 soldiers
to attack Bulu Village,
so he packed up and fled last night.
When everyone else knew
King of Light had left,
they also ran off.
Only us—the old, weak, sick, and crippled—
were left in the village.
We know King of Light can't be relied on.
Instead of fighting a hopeless battle,
it's better for us to surrender.
My Lord, please be magnanimous
and merciful.
We're willing
to offer Bulu Village to you!
Don't move!
My Lord, the gates are open.
Please enter.
My Lord, it seems
there really aren't many guards.
We've brought enough soldiers this time.
Even if King of Light set a trap inside,
we don't need to be afraid of him.
Nobody move!
Guys!
Let's begin our show.
Stop.
Control the rhythm.
If we overact, he won't believe it.
My Lord!
Bulu Village has surrendered!
We won't fight back!
Please enter!
My Lord!
My Lord, what did you hear?
Nobody move!
Tell them to retreat.
My Lord, there's an ambush
outside the village.
If we go in now,
we'll walk right into their trap.
My Lord, wise move.
Watch your eyes.
King of Light
is not that clever.
Such a cheap trick
can only fool rookies.
I won't fall for it.
My Lord, what should we do now?
We have already won!
That's what we'll do.
I've seen through King of Light's trick!
The outcome is clear!
We surround the village
and wait for them to run out of supplies!
Wise as ever, My Lord!
-Wise as ever, My Lord!
-Let's go.
Hurry.
Wise as ever, My Lord!
[Surrender]
That actually worked.
Lu Di's army
has really retreated.
Looks like
they won't attack us anytime soon.
Being his subordinates
really taxes the brain.
He solved Bulu Village's crisis
even though he's in Imperial Capital.
He's worthy of the title of King of Light.
King of Light?
That's right.
But I haven't reported it
to Zichuan's court.
I got the news from my scouts.
They say King of Light
always wears a mask.
He's been leading Yuanzhou's races
to fight against the North Clan.
But his identity hasn't been confirmed.
Di Lin, you haven't reported it
because you think this King of Light...
I'm not sure.
But wearing a mask and playing mysterious—
that does feel like something he would do.
He's pretty good at playing tricks now.
Wait.
Even if he really is King of Light,
he's still a traitor to the family
since he openly
fought against the North Clan.
So,
that isn't really good news.
By the way,
take a look at this.
The Liufeng family?
This is a letter from Liufeng Ming.
He said Liufeng Shuang
has betrayed her family.
If it weren't for their internal turmoil,
I wouldn't have easily taken
three cities in a row.
The letter says
Liufeng Shuang
fled from the Liufeng family
towards Zichuan.
They want us
to keep an eye out for her whereabouts.
If we capture Liufeng Shuang,
they're willing to open up
the five border provinces
and won't engage Zichuan
in any military conflict for three years.
That's so insincere.
Given the current situation,
they're unable to launch any big campaigns
within three years anyway.
But no matter what,
we still need to find her first.
Whether we use her to trade for peace
or as a deterrent
will be entirely up to us.
Do we have any news on her whereabouts?
The letter was received this morning.
But two days ago,
my scouts found traces
of the Black Tiger Gang's members
outside the city.
The Black Tiger Gang?
The Liufeng family's assassin group,
right?
Yes.
That means
they failed to intercept Liufeng Shuang.
It's very likely
that Liufeng Shuang
has entered Imperial Capital.
Liufeng Shuang, female,
fierce-looking, skilled in disguise,
and highly trained in martial arts.
Anyone who reports her whereabouts
will be heavily rewarded.
Looks like the Zichuan family
has some misunderstandings about you.
Sinister and cunning—
that's their biggest misunderstanding.
Every victory we've won
was open and honorable.
I can hardly accept
such undeserved praise.
But it seems
they now know we're in Imperial Capital.
The Black Tiger Gang probably knows too.
We...
I think we'd better leave first.
If we want to go to the Lin family,
we have to pass through Zichuan.
And we still need medicine for injuries.
Imperial Capital is our best option.
Besides, there're lots of people
in Imperial Capital.
It makes it harder
for the Black Tiger Gang
to track us down.
But I suppose the inns in Imperial Capital
are now under strict surveillance.
Where exactly should we go?
Let me ask you,
if the Zichuan family is hunting down
a woman with everything they've got,
where is the one place
she would never go?
Mr. Peng, it's rare to see you come.
[Mingyue]
I didn't expect you to show up
for the courtesan competition today.
Mingyue, you are the best
in Chunfeng Garden.
Why would you care
about the courtesan's title?
Who are you?
It's you.
You still owe me money.
And you dare show up here?
Well, here I am.
Come upstairs with me.
Didn't you defect from Zichuan?
Imperial Capital is looking for you now.
You've got some nerve coming back.
Do you want to die?
Why did you come back this time?
Mingyue,
I'll be straightforward with you.
This time, I need you to help me find
a grain merchant.
Mind you, a big one.
That's it?
That's it.
Okay. But you'll have to wait a bit.
Today
is the courtesan selection.
Once it's over,
I'll handle it for you immediately.
Okay. I'll be right here,
waiting patiently for you to return.
Okay.
Two people?
With so much money,
why don't you stay in an inn?
Can you stop asking questions now?
See that woodshed?
You stay there tonight.
Although this place is quite shabby,
it's relatively safe.
What's wrong?
One of the two people
who just walked past
was wearing our family's jade pendant.
Why would someone from our family
be in Imperial Capital?
That might explain how my whereabouts
got leaked.
Should we go to another place then?
No need.
You go to the woodshed first.
I'll go inside
and see what I can find out.
Okay. Be careful.
She's interested
in this kind of thing too?
Whether you are old or young,
as long as you're here, you're our guests.
Today, you lucky folks are in for a treat.
Every single lady from Chunfeng Garden
is present and dressed to dazzle!
Today is the day
for selecting our monthly courtesan.
If any lady catches your attention,
spend as much money as you can on her.
Chunfeng Garden's ladies
love nothing but money.
The lady with the most silver
and silk coins before her
will become Chunfeng Garden's courtesan
for this month.
And the guest who contributes
the most to her victory
will get the chance to drink
under the moon
and spend the night with her.
-Great!
The selection of the courtesan begins now!
Let's go.
It's me.
Zhang Asan? What are you doing here?
I'll help you lure them away.
Hide first.
How am I supposed to hide here?
Just dance with them.
Start dancing, and it'll be fine.
Hurry up!
Hurry. Go now.
I'll help you deliver it.
-Great!
Gentlemen.
Get out of my way!
Are you looking for a lady?
A lady in casual clothes just walked past.
Did you see her?
A lady in casual clothes?
I remember.
There was indeed a lady in casual clothes
going out from here.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Let's go.
Goodbye, gentlemen.
-Great!
I announce
the courtesan today is...
It must be Yu!
Yes, yes!
The courtesan today
is Yu!
Why?
We all spent money!
That's right!
Quiet!
It must be me who spent the most money.
We spent money too!
We all spent money!
You're not convinced, huh?
Then take out your money,
and let's see who has more!
I can't believe Yu.
She left without saying a word.
Didn't I tell you to stay in the room?
You always cause me trouble.
Who's that lady just now?
She took the courtesan's title from me.
In my heart,
Mingyue, you're
the only courtesan.
Just now,
I was just helping my friend.
You're very rich now.
This time,
I've repaid all the favors I owed you.
Oh no, my blade!
That guy is indeed from Imperial Capital.
The Black Tiger Gang is here too.
We can't stay here any longer.
I have ample grain stored
in the granaries in the northwest.
How much do you want?
A lot.
How much is "a lot"?
Enough to feed a whole city.
A whole city?
Why do you need so much grain?
Mr. Feng,
you know what? My hometown, Bulu Village,
barely has any grain left now.
Bulu Village?
It's not because we don't have money.
It's because we have no rice.
Isn't it in Yuanzhou?
Yuanzhou was given
to the North Clan long ago.
Besides, even though you don't have grain,
you can't ship grain
from the Zichuan family.
No.
A transaction of this scale—
if the North Clan finds out
the grain is from the Zichuan family,
it could easily spark serious conflict.
Even I'd be in deep trouble.
Well, I'm sorry that your hometown
has fallen into the North Clan's hands.
I do sympathize with you.
I really want to help you with this.
Well...
Still, no.
Mr. Feng,
don't worry about the money.
I promise
I will pay in cash
for every batch.
It really isn't about the money.
The deal is big
and involves two clans.
If something goes wrong...
Alright. How about this?
You buy grain
in Zichuan on behalf of me.
No need to ship it directly to Yuanzhou.
My men
will handle the delivery in Zichuan.
Even if the cross-border shipments
are ever discovered,
they'll only trace it to my men.
In this regard,
it's truly risk-free for you.
Buying grain on your behalf?
Since the peace talks with the North Clan,
the borders have been stable.
Zichuan has been able to
devote itself fully to production.
With abundant rainfall
in the south this year,
statistics from
the Ministry of Government Supervision
show that the grain and textile output
over the past quarter has completely
returned to pre-war levels.
Yes, the success of the peace talks
is of great significance.
The credit should go to Di Lin.
The successful outcome
of the peace talks today
proves how far-sighted he was back then.
Thank you for your praise, My Lord.
But there's one thing worth our attention.
Go on.
While Zichuan's production
of grain and goods is rising,
our treasury and military reserves
are far from sufficient.
As far as I know,
the most important reason
is the existence
of smuggling along the borders.
Many supplies have been sold
at high prices to Yuanzhou,
and even to the Lin family.
Merchants seek profit.
That's only natural.
But why has the Lin family purchased
so many supplies?
That's what should concern us.
The Lin family has always been close
to the Liufeng family.
Those supplies are likely
for the Liufeng family's use.
The Liufeng family is currently
in the midst of internal strife.
But once they catch a breath,
they'll surely pose a threat
along our borders soon.
Everyone,
do you have countermeasures in mind?
In fact, the issue has existed
for a long time.
I wonder if you remember
the Supplies Restriction Act?
I remember.
The Supplies Restriction Act
was enacted during Lord Yuanxing's tenure.
It has never been enforced over the years.
The act was established
precisely to prevent
what we're seeing now.
It's just that back then,
frequent border conflicts
made restoring order the top priority,
not the regulation
of agriculture and commerce.
But now, Zichuan is enjoying
its most peaceful period.
It is the perfect time to reintroduce
and enforce this act.
How about this?
Let
the Ministry of Military and Legal Affairs
oversee this matter.
While monitoring the border trade routes,
they can also gather more intelligence.
Di Lin.
Without intelligence,
we're doomed to fail.
With intelligence, victory can be secured.
To know both yourself and your enemy
is the sure path to winning every battle.
Understood.
Mr. Feng, what took you so long?
I've been waiting for you.
Don't even ask. The goods aren't coming.
I came to let you know
our deal's off.
What happened?
You haven't heard?
Early this morning, Imperial Capital
issued a revised version
of the Supplies Restriction Act.
They're tightening control
over all border trades.
And
the Ministry of Military and Legal Affairs
is investigating.
I'm well aware of their methods.
You'd better find someone else. Goodbye.
Mr. Feng!
The Ministry of Military and Legal Affairs?
Am I beautiful?
Yes. You're the most beautiful of all.
Xiujia, here. Have some water.
Get some rest.
Why are those ladies from Chunfeng Garden
gathering in our shop?
He's back?
He's finally back.
Di Lin.
King of Light?
Di Lin,
you don't really think
I betrayed Zichuan, do you?
I sided with the North Clan
for one purpose only—
to kill Lei Hong
and avenge Lord Ge.
You planned to return to Imperial Capital
with Lei Hong's head
and claim your reward.
But Divine Emperor tricked you.
He appointed you
as the Grand Marshal of Yuanzhou.
With no way to prove your innocence,
you had no choice but to stay in Yuanzhou.
Di Lin, you know me best.
I don't need to explain anything.
Since your heart is with Zichuan,
why did you become King of Light?
Di Lin, becoming King of Light
was a pure accident.
The Xiu Battalion's men and I were running
guerrilla operations in Yuanzhou.
The North Clan was oppressing
the Yuanzhou people and even tried
to desecrate the sacred temple.
So I led my troops
and drove out Lu Di's men.
That Elder Budan in Yuanzhou
thought very highly of me.
He insisted I become King of Light.
So you're saying they forced you?
Yes.
You were very reluctant, huh?
Of course.
Talk properly!
Di Lin, you have no idea.
I thought long and hard.
Since things had come to that,
how could I just walk away?
If I left right after the battle,
they would still be disorganized.
They'd still be bullied by the North Clan.
So, after much consideration,
I reluctantly agreed to be King of Light.
It seems it was really against your will.
Indeed.
But do you know
that confirms your betrayal of Zichuan?
Don't worry.
Once I defeat the North Clan,
I'll return to Zichuan with Yuanzhou.
You brat.
You didn't even send a letter.
Yilin and I were so worried about you.
Di Lin, I'm sorry.
I should have come back to you sooner.
It's been so long.
How have you been?
We've been fine.
You didn't just come back
for a bath, did you?
I came back this time
to ask you
for a small favor.
You're King of Light.
You're asking me for a favor?
Di Lin,
it's the new act.
I came back to Zichuan
to raise grain.
But with the new act,
I can't get anything out of here.
I'm at my wit's end.
That's why I came to you for help.
Okay. I'll figure something out for you.
But...
You're not asking me for money, are you?
Of course you have to pay.
I...
Can I get a discount?
No.
So heartless, Di Lin.
You know I've been having
a hard time in Yuanzhou.
I'm so pitiful...
Fine.
I can help raise some grain privately.
But if you want long-term supplies,
you'll still have to buy from Zichuan.
You can't take advantage of Zichuan.
As long as I get the grain, it's fine.
Let's go find Yilin.
Di Lin.
I can't see Yilin.
Why not?
With my current identity,
meeting him would only bring him trouble.
You know his temper.
If he sees me and acts on impulse,
he might tie me up
and take me to Lord Chieftain.
Lord Chieftain doesn't really like me.
But tomorrow is his wedding day.
Wedding?
Let's have a drink. Just the two of us.
Now?
Aren't we drinking later anyway?
That's different.
Later, it'll be noisy and chaotic.
None of those drinks
will truly reach your heart.
Come on.
Look what good wine I brought you.
Monkey Brew?
I haven't seen this wine
for a long time either.
A few days ago,
I got it from a wine merchant
that Xiujia knows.
I specially prepared it for you.
Back in Yuanzhou's military academy,
every time Xiu drank this wine...
♪ I remove my heavy armor ♪
♪ And take off the weary mask I wore ♪
He would make a scene.
Just thinking about it
♪ By the lamplight, knees drawn close,
we speak of a dream ♪
still makes me angry.
♪ We drink and laugh till morning gleams ♪
♪ Your torch still burns bright ♪
Come on. Today is your wedding day.
As your big brother,
I'll make a toast to you.
♪ Lighting that rugged path
through the cold night ♪
♪ Where we once parted ways ♪
Too bad Xiu is not here.
I'm here.
♪ Glory remains engraved ♪
He's here.
Yes.
♪ The friend who vanished from view ♪
He's here.
♪ Was never truly gone ♪
♪ I stayed silent, just waiting
for your voice ♪
Let's drink this toast to Xiu as well,
who's far away.
Come on.
♪ Let go of the burdens of the past ♪
♪ Open a dusty window ♪
♪ It's hard to have a few true friends ♪
♪ Stand by each other till life's end ♪
Lord Si Yilin is getting married tonight.
We should drink heartily!
No going home sober!
-Okay! No going home sober!
Let's go!
My Lord,
why are we following the Palace Guards?
I planned to leave Imperial Capital
after recovering.
But now they're not only checking people.
Since the new act was enforced,
inspections everywhere
have gotten much tighter.
Now, if we want to leave the city,
we'll need a special travel permit
or an access token from one of
Zichuan's classified departments.
You're targeting
one of the Palace Guards' officers?
Didn't they just say
Si Yilin is getting married today?
We'll do it
after they eat and drink enough.
It'll be much safer that way.
Si Yilin,
the most outstanding young talent
of the Zichuan family,
and Li Qing are getting married
on this auspicious day.
As the Chieftain of the family,
I'm very happy
to officiate at their wedding.
Yilin,
congratulations on your wedding.
Ka Dan, I attended today's wedding
on your behalf.
I remember
the first time you fell for him—
it was right here.
At that time, Si Yilin
was listening to you saying "thanks".
But he just stood there,
♪ A gentle smile,
you blossom in my heart ♪
with no expression at all.
♪ Dreams take shelter in my chest ♪
♪ From this vast world,
I'll never let you go ♪
♪ I give my all along
your path of flowers ♪
♪ Through sun and moon,
this love will never die ♪
♪ I fall for you eternally ♪
♪ In the boundless sea and sky,
I long for no end ♪
But later, you told me
you clearly saw
♪ You drift in the river of my dreams ♪
that his ears had turned bright red.
That was when you fell for him.
♪ One thought turns to fate,
a thousand yearnings ♪
I miss those days so much.
♪ It's you ♪
At that time,
Xiu was in Imperial Capital too.
♪ In my world,
you're like cloud and mist ♪
♪ Coming and going, so distant ♪
♪ Though life and death are far apart,
my soul clings to you ♪
♪ It's you ♪
A toast...
♪ I wish to grow old
with you through time's changes ♪
to the mistake that began...
♪ Let love bear witness ♪
but never ended.
♪ A gentle smile,
you blossom in my heart ♪
♪ Dreams take shelter in my chest ♪
♪ From this vast world,
I'll never let you go ♪
♪ I give my all along
your path of flowers ♪
♪ Through sun and moon,
this love will never die ♪
♪ I fall for you eternally ♪
♪ In the boundless sea and sky,
I long for no end ♪
Ning.
♪ You drift in the river of my dreams ♪
♪ One thought turns to fate,
a thousand yearnings ♪
♪ It's you ♪
♪ In my world,
you're like cloud and mist ♪
♪ Coming and going, so distant ♪
♪ One thought turns to fate,
a thousand yearnings ♪
♪ It's you ♪
Your Highness,
it's the first snow tonight.
♪ In my world,
you're like cloud and mist ♪
Drinking alone
might make you catch a cold.
♪ Coming and going, so distant ♪
It's cold.
I have a special heater in my carriage.
♪ Though life and death are far apart,
my soul clings to you ♪
Let me take you home tonight.
♪ It's you ♪
♪ I wish to grow old
with you through time's changes ♪
♪ Let love bear witness ♪