[Eternal Brotherhood 2]
[Episode 19]
[Si's Mansion]
Apply the medicine
according to the prescription.
Change it twice a day.
When will he wake up?
The wound nearly reached
his liver and spleen.
He's lucky to be alive.
As for when he'll wake up,
it's up to fate.
I see.
When Si Yilin wakes up,
let me know immediately.
Okay.
The assassins have been captured
by the Ministry of War.
I'll go back first
to prepare for tomorrow's trial.
I'm sorry.
Let me ask you, how is Si Yilin?
He's still unconscious.
Don't worry, My Lord.
He'll live.
Those two people
dared to attack
a Zichuan general in broad daylight.
Such blatant lawlessness
must be severely punished without mercy.
Let Di Lin handle the trial.
He'll give a fair judgment.
It's almost time, right?
The water's about to overflow.
When the bubbles are like fish eyes
and faintly audible,
that's the first boil.
When they rise
like a string of pearls by the rim,
that's the second.
It's not the time yet.
Only at the third boil will the flavor
truly infuse into the brew.
By then, what everyone remembers
is the taste of the tea.
No one will care about who sold it
or where it came from.
Then how do we reach that third boil?
As long as we
don't extinguish the fire underneath,
we don't need to worry
the tea won't be fully brewed.
But Chieftain...
I think if Lord Chieftain
really wants to take action,
after Lord Ge Shan was injured,
those people won't have a chance.
Si Yilin has followed
Lord Chieftain for years.
They look like father and son,
but in fact... they are not that close.
Compared to us,
of course Lord Chieftain
is closer to Si Yilin.
But compared to the clan's stability...
Gentlemen, the tea is ready.
Si Yilin is my subordinate,
but he is also my family.
If Si Yilin knows Lord Chieftain
came to see him personally,
he'd be deeply moved.
Thank you
for taking care of him these days.
When he wakes up,
let me know immediately.
Okay.
Stop.
I smell some fragrance.
Fragrance?
Help!
Stop.
You're saying Luo Jie rescued a carriage
of women from Jialai District
from the North Clan?
That's right.
He ran into one of them who had escaped,
and rescued all of them.
How do they look?
They are quite attractive.
Are they all married?
What does that have to do with you?
It has everything to do with me.
Baichuan.
Yes.
From now on, those women
shall be placed
under top-level protection.
You shall
personally oversee everything.
Before we arrive in Jialai District,
I want them to be glowing
and plump.
Send them back to Jialai District?
That's right. We leave tomorrow.
Tell everyone:
all men
should stay away from that carriage.
Is Lord Xiu
really interested in those women?
They are not just ordinary women.
They're a gift from Heaven—
a key to open Jialai's gates.
It's really Jialai.
We're home.
Come. Be careful.
Yeah.
This scene
makes me want to recite a poem.
Be careful.
The savior of Jialai.
Chief had a point.
Control the inner desire,
and you'll control
the hearts of Jialai's people.
I heard
Jialai's governor
is a young beauty.
Are you sure?
I'm Commander Hu Cheng of Jialai.
I express gratitude to you
on behalf of the governor.
You're too polite, General.
It's a heroic tale
that we risked our lives
to save those women
from the enemy,
but for the sake of justice,
the Yuanzhou Alliance Army
should still be responsible.
Since the governor heard
that you traveled so far
to return the women,
she's been unable to sleep every day.
And she's been thinking
of your kindness every day.
Thanks to King of Light this time,
Jialai...
will face a calamity.
What?
Take them down!
What's going on? What's wrong?
We rescued them! How is that wrong?
Rescuing people isn't wrong,
but we rescued the wrong people.
Those women were probably sent
as gifts for them.
Well, General,
I surrender.
You ungrateful bastards!
I should have hijacked
all those women!
Then you'd have no gifts to give!
I think I can unlock this.
With what? Everything's gone.
Try poking it with this.
That's going to take forever.
Chief, what should we do?
What else can we do? Sleep.
The governor
wants to interrogate King of Light.
-He's here for you.
Who's here for me?
This is Jialai's specialty,
the ox blood tea.
[Jialai's governor: Pang Xiya]
It's specially for honored guests.
It indeed tastes good.
It has
a primitive flavor of raw meat and blood.
This is our first meeting,
and you drank the ox blood tea so calmly.
King of Light is indeed
no ordinary person.
I'm flattered.
You invited me to drink tea
in your room on our first meeting.
Jialai's governor
is no ordinary person as well.
My name is Pang Xiya.
My name is King of Light.
You can also call me
Light, King, or Light King.
King of Light
never reveals his true identity.
Always so mysterious.
But I respect you.
You are the only female governor.
And you're imposing. I admire you.
I guess being invited for tea
right after you set foot in Jialai
must make King of Light
a bit nervous.
And I guess
those women were gifts for Lu Di.
Unexpectedly, I intercepted them
and returned them openly.
Lu Di must think
Jialai has sided
with the Yuanzhou Alliance Army.
Now you must be
more nervous than me.
If I give you to Lu Di,
I'll surely be rewarded.
Why should I be nervous?
The North Clan
has been defeated repeatedly
by the Yuanzhou Alliance Army.
You're afraid of offending Lu Di,
and also afraid of taking the wrong side.
You invited me to your room
at this hour for tea.
I guess you already have a plan
although you're flustered.
King of Light, you're indeed
clever and perceptive.
Then I'll be straightforward.
Jialai District can be
on friendly terms with the Alliance Army.
We can even pledge allegiance.
I sense a "but" coming.
That's right.
But you have to marry me.
I'm a lazy man.
And I like to bully my subordinates.
I often deduct their salaries.
I'll take care of everything at home.
And your subordinates' salaries—
Jialai will double them.
I love drinking,
especially at pleasure houses.
I might not come home for 10 or 15 days.
Jialai has many women,
more than anything else.
If you like,
you can have 8 or 10 each night.
I promise you won't
see the same face twice in a month.
I have two subordinates.
One is knowledgeable,
and the other is skilled in martial arts.
The knowledgeable one
knows every military text in history.
The other one can take on 10 men at once.
It has to be you.
I don't really want to do this either.
It's just that every city
that can supply water to Jialai
is under control of the North Clan.
If I can't trust you completely,
I really can't
break off with the North Clan.
I can provide water too.
Then how are you
any different from the North Clan?
If you don't marry me,
Jialai can't stand by
the Alliance Army without worry.
Before you arrived,
I'd already considered every outcome.
The best case:
you fall for me
and propose marriage yourself.
The middle ground:
we admire each other
and have a marriage of convenience.
As for the worst case...
Is it to kill me and give me
to Lu Di to beg for forgiveness?
I'll give you one day to think it over.
Come on. Bottoms up.
Our governor is indeed awesome.
She's made King of Light fall for her.
Of course.
Come on. Drink.
Chief,
I think
you might as well just marry her.
You won't lose out.
If you really can't do it, let me.
Instead of talking nonsense,
you should save your energy.
My Lord, please come up with a solution.
Have you ever heard of a saying—
"Fortune favors the virtuous"?
Chief, did you dig that with your eyes?
With your head?
What Chief meant
is that brain is a handy thing.
Remember to use it next time.
Come on. Let's go.
Lord Xiu had this all planned
from the start.
You guys escorted the women to Jialai.
I followed you secretly with a team.
Even if anything went wrong,
Lord Xiu had the terrain maps ready.
I'd dig a tunnel to save you.
Thankfully,
Xiu took precautions in advance.
Otherwise,
he would have to marry the governor.
Let's go.
The governor is quite good-looking.
She's just a bit old.
Good-looking? Her hair's all split ends.
Her skin is dull and not glowing at all.
She must have stayed up too late.
You're right.
Who are we?
The Xiu... Pretty and attractive.
A perfect match.
Brave and resourceful governor,
if any of us could marry you,
it would be a blessing
for the Yuanzhou Alliance Army.
My dignity has been hurt.
A few days ago,
Lord Ge Shan
of the Ministry of Government Supervision
and Lord Si Yilin, the commander
of the Palace Guards,
were both attacked.
Lord Ge Shan was slightly injured,
while Lord Si Yilin was severely wounded.
The assassins were captured on the spot.
They will stand trial today, in public.
Bring in the prisoners!
-Heroes!
Ding Cheng, the evidence against you
for attempted assassination is conclusive.
Do you have anything else to say?
During the attack on Ge Shan,
we accidentally killed a coachman.
He was around 30 years old.
Surely he had a wife and children.
I know the pain of losing
someone you love.
So I'm willing to take full responsibility
for his death.
As for Lord Si Yilin,
he once led us through blood and fire.
I'm very sorry
that I had to harm him.
But I don't regret it.
Very well.
Ding Cheng, the culprit,
and Chang Li, an accomplice—
you are guilty of treason and murder.
According to Zichuan's law,
I sentence you to death.
You'll be executed in three days.
I object!
Wayun has stood
as Imperial Capital's shield
for centuries.
Every son and daughter of Wayun
on the battlefield
disregarded life and death!
But what have we received in return?
We've received
weak armies and miserable people!
We lost
the 23 districts in Yuanzhou!
But Imperial Capital is still crawling
with greedy and corrupt officials!
That's right!
Someone has to shed blood
to wake the world.
Someone has to clear the way
for Zichuan's future.
We are willing to be those people.
Even if we die, we die for a worthy cause!
-Die without regrets!
My Lord!
This is a petition
signed by 10,000 citizens
from Wayun and Imperial Capital.
They're warriors who have fought bravely
for the clan.
They deserve a special pardon!
-Pardon!
You're awake. Do you feel any discomfort?
What about the two who attacked me?
They are still on trial.
Have they been sentenced?
Not yet.
But just now, Wen He sent a message.
A petition signed
by 10,000 citizens has been delivered,
pleading for their pardon.
Given your current condition,
you can't go there.
If there's something you want to say,
you can write it down,
and I'll deliver it for you.
I have to go myself.
My Lord,
someone at the trial submitted a petition
signed by 10,000 citizens,
requesting clemency for the two assassins.
I see.
Looks like you had anticipated this.
How dare you!
You two
are guilty of treason and murder!
And you've incited the public!
Your crimes are even more heinous!
According to Zichuan's law,
you shall hang yourselves!
Execute immediately!
You're all in this together!
If you won't release them,
we'll save them ourselves!
-Save them!
Anyone who obstructs the law
will be punished as an accomplice!
-Release them!
Let me go!
I'm not guilty!
-Release them!
Let go! Let go of me!
Wait!
-Release them!
Di Lin.
What are you doing here?
I have something to say.
Please give me a moment.
As the plaintiff in this case,
I want to withdraw the charges
and request leniency.
I am the commander of the Palace Guards.
My soldiers love and trust me,
but I failed to lead them
to bring victory back to Zichuan.
That is my dereliction of duty.
I bear the responsibility.
I failed to maintain order in Zichuan,
causing Lord Ge's injuries.
And I made the people want to rebel!
That is my negligence!
Therefore,
I'll take responsibility for their crimes.
I deserved that stab.
But it doesn't mean I forgive you.
Nor does it mean you're not at fault.
I just want you to understand
you can't escape
the consequences of defeat.
I know you're disappointed in Zichuan.
You want Zichuan
to be a fair and strong clan.
But with the North Clan still a threat,
you can't turn your blades
against your own people.
If you really think
that my death
can solve this problem,
I'm willing to sacrifice myself.
Warriors.
Brothers!
You all have shed blood for this clan.
So what is this clan?
It's your home!
A home
will never abandon its people.
Nor will it ever abandon its lands!
Eventually,
you will have
the respect and dignity
you deserve.
-Well said!
That's right!
Well said!
Di Lin.
The law is the law.
Crimes must be punished.
But Di Lin,
this is our own problem.
But justice can be tempered with mercy!
-My Lord.
Release them!
Release them now!
Justice tempered with mercy
is the very spirit of law.
They did something wrong,
but they did it for a reason.
And Si Yilin has withdrawn the charges,
requesting clemency.
As for the compensation
and the restoration of Wayun,
the clan will give you an explanation.
-Long live the chieftain!
Lord Ge.
Lord Si Yilin,
there's something I'd like to say to you.
A kind heart can't tame wolves.
I had no choice. I'm a soldier.
Foolish one.
My Lord, you were put
in a difficult position today.
Lord Chieftain's presence made you
a villain who punished the heroes.
Our chieftain, Lord Canxing,
sees clearer than anyone.
He's the one
who asked me to handle the case.
He's also the one
who asked me to release them.
Thus,
the Three Central Offices
will no longer act recklessly.
I've become the heartless one
in the people's eyes,
while he has won the people's hearts
and saved his dignity.
The law can be bent
due to his words.
Fairness and justice
are not as important as political balance.
Our Lord Chieftain
has placed everyone over the fire,
while he stays untouched.
Lord Chieftain,
the refugee crisis
spiraled out of control.
Everyone has been punished.
As their commander,
I should accept severer punishment.
Indeed, you should be punished.
I accept the punishment.
Do you know why you should be punished?
Not because you did something wrong,
but because we need to give
an explanation to the people.
You'll be suspended.
Someone else will handle the affairs
at the Ministry of Government Supervision.
We can't attack the Liufeng family now.
When there are too many refugees,
they'll become vagrants.
Once vagrants become bandits,
the world will fall into chaos.
Everything you said before was correct.
Thank you, Lord Chieftain.
Our priority now
is to comfort the refugees.
I understand.
Then I'll take my leave.
Okay.
Lord Chieftain,
I thank you on behalf of the people.
Safe journey.
Doctor, how is my father?
This is a case of atrophy.
His limbs are weak and feeble,
unable to be used for now.
My prescription
can only delay the decline.
If it worsens to the point
where he can't speak,
there'll be nothing we can do.
Is there really...
Is there really no other way?
As long as you can cure my father,
the Liufeng family
will reward you handsomely.
Doctor, please figure something out.
Help her.
I do have an ancient prescription.
But it's said
it's hard to find the medicine.
Even if you find it,
I'm not sure if I can cure him or not.
No matter what,
I'm willing to give it a try.
The peak of the mountain,
the horn of the dragon.
Where heaven and earth bleed,
swallows return home.
What does that mean?
Doctor, thank you for your guidance.
What did he mean?
What he meant is
the medicine is in the far east.
The prescription is written on the paper.
It depends on you whether you can get it.
Now that I know the general direction,
I'll go find it myself.
I'll go with you.
You're an elder of the Lin family.
I can't waste any more of your time.
When I come back with the medicine,
I'll thank you properly.
It's a promise then.
A promise.
They say a wise man
submits to circumstances.
In my opinion,
King of Light, you're the wisest of all.
They also say the prettier a woman is,
the sharper her mind is.
Governor, you are also impressive.
Aren't we a perfect match then?
No.
The more alike two people are,
the more likely they are
to clash.
So,
you don't like any of these robes?
They're too flashy.
They don't match my style.
I'm
a low-profile and extravagant person.
Why don't we hear
what your subordinates think?
They've followed you for so long.
They must know your preferences well.
I think the first one is good—
noble and elegant.
This is not about which one is good.
In my opinion, they're all great.
It's like they're tailored for him.
My Lord, choose whatever you like.
I'm not afraid of death!
But I know you definitely won't do that.
Shut up.
One more word
and I'll walk out naked!
That sounds good too. I like that.
No. I think the first one is good.
My Lord!
Water's seeping into the dungeon!
My Lord, after so many years with you,
I'm truly reluctant to part from you.
But at the thought
that you're finally going
to be someone else's trouble,
I'm somewhat relieved.
I bade you farewell by the river.
You're already married when you return.
I never expected
that Lord Xiu is getting married.
I didn't expect it either.
All these years,
I always thought
you were too heartless for love to matter.
I never expected you
to have such a relationship.
I'm so frustrated.
How did I suddenly
become such a crybaby?
Chief.
I hope in the future, when you get drunk,
someone will take you home.
When you earn money,
don't hand it all over.
Keep some for yourself.
I can't bear to part from you.
I can't go on.
Well, why are you crying?
Stop crying.
Chief!
Is the Xiu Battalion
going to break up just like this?
I'm so sad.
Don't be sad.
I'm sad too. I'm heartbroken.
I never thought I, the Flower of Yuanzhou,
would now...
King of Light!
Did you dig the tunnel?
Why did you choose that location?
I did it to save Chief.
The earth near the underground river
is soft. It's easy to dig.
There really is
an underground river beneath Jialai?
You've solved the water source problem?
We've been under the control
of the North Clan
because of the water shortage.
Can you find another location
to drill for water?
He's my subordinate.
I'll answer your question.
Xiya, I...
Call me Governor.
We're not that close.
It shouldn't be a problem.
That's great.
If we can break free from their control
over the water source,
my people
will no longer be at the mercy of them.
Jialai's independence
will be within reach.
Come on, get up.
Stop crying. Sit.
If Li Nong solves
the water source issue,
does that mean
we don't have to get married?
With water, who'd still want you?
Wake up.
I suddenly feel a bit upset.
It's like I bought a rope to hang myself,
but suddenly,
the rope broke.
Still, you helped Jialai find the key
to breaking free from their control.
It's credited to you.
So, if Li Nong stays
to help you solve the water source issue,
does that mean
the Yuanzhou Alliance Army and Jialai
have reached an agreement?
Of course.
Good. It's a pleasure working with you.
Come on.
Hello. Don't be afraid.
I just want to ask
if you know what this note
means.
I don't know.
Are you from the North Clan
or the Alliance Army?
Don't talk to the people riding horses.
If we run into the North Clan's men,
we'll be arrested.
Sister,
go ask Elder Budan at the sacred temple.
He knows everything.
Hurry, let's go.
Okay, thank you.
I, Lin Yu, request an audience
with Elder Budan.
Are you from the west?
Yes.
He's been waiting for you.
The peak of the mountain,
the horn of the dragon.
Where heaven and earth bleed,
swallows return home.
Let me ask you a question.
Go ahead.
To cure your father,
would you harm innocent people?
Of course not.
My father has taught me since childhood
that villains must be punished,
but the innocent must never be harmed.
Now I can answer your question.
Many people know the meaning
of this note,
including me.
But those who can decipher
the positive meaning of this note
might only mislead you.
Mislead?
You are a kind person.
Among Ke City, Jialai,
and Pingyang District,
there are a few mountain passes
with lax management.
Smuggling of forbidden items
happens there.
There,
you may find clues to what you seek.
Thank you. I'll set out immediately.
Elder,
this could harm the Dragon Race.
Why did you still guide her?
This is fate.
She will walk towards the light.
I've compiled
the water distribution
and redirection methods near Jialai.
I put them into a booklet
with illustrations.
Please take a look, Governor.
Have a seat.
Sit!
It's clear, detailed,
and easy to understand.
Let's get to the main point.
Most of the districts in Yuanzhou
are under the control of the North Clan.
It's not just a matter
of weak military strength.
The main reason is
they don't have sufficient resources.
If we could share the technology
of water sourcing and irrigation
across Yuanzhou,
maybe we could
help them change their fate.
But promoting it
to so many districts one by one
would take too much time.
So, I want to host a banquet
in Jialai.
We'll invite the envoys
not under the control of the North Clan
to learn the technology here.
We can also take this opportunity
to unite all of Yuanzhou.
It's an excellent idea.
Water is essential.
Now that the water source issue
can be solved,
I believe no one would say no.
Yeah.
But...
since you'll host a banquet in Jialai,
it wouldn't be too much if I charge you
some venue fees, right?
You really don't make any deal at a loss.
But I like that.
In that case,
I'll charge you some tuition fees too.
In my name,
send invitations to the districts.
Jialai will host a banquet.
Good.