♪Cheering for time travel♪
♪Till I wake up to see a baby♪
♪A woman with three suitors♪
♪They say I'm fickle♪
♪The scholar confesses all with drinks♪
♪The guard just gives her a stony face♪
♪The regent waits in the moonlight♪
♪The title
of Empress Dowager brings pity♪
♪Palace farces play daily♪
♪Endless plot twists♪
♪That glimpse of you that day♪
♪Made my heart flutter♪
♪Peach blossoms♪
♪Bloom one by one in my heart♪
♪Who do I love♪
♪I guess with no direction♪
♪Who's pretending♪
♪While the truth slips by♪
♪Pretense becomes true as years flow♪
=The Empress Dowager On A Second Spring=
Let's talk this out.
Let her go.
Zhao Chengtian, put it down!
Calm down.
Whatever you want.
Even if I die today,
I'll take you with me.
We'll be lovers in the underworld.
Uncle.
Drop the blades.
Drop them!
I've waited so long for this day
to finally wed you honorably.
But all of you
have ruined it!
The Empress Dowager has long been mine.
She even bore me a child.
None of you shall take her from me!
She never bore your child.
The First Prince is His Majesty's son.
His mother was my maid Rong.
To protect the prince,
Rong met a tragic end.
The Empress Dowager
sacrificed her reputation.
Zhao Chengtian.
How many people
and children have you killed
in this palace?
No.
No!
You're lying.
You're lying, right?
The First Prince is my flesh and blood!
Jiang Rong also belongs to me!
Why didn't I meet you first
in the imperial garden back then?
What?
Your Grace,
this is the concubine
the Crown Prince selected today.
From our first meeting,
you imprinted on my heart.
I never regret
meeting you.
Don't!
Uncle.
No.
Save him! Save...
Don't...
Don't save me.
I never wanted the throne.
I did this for you.
If we meet again
in our next life...
Zhao Chengtian.
Don't
let us miss each other,
okay?
=Episode 22=
Zhao Chengtian.
(Two years later)
Now, the war ends.
The world is at peace.
This is the prosperity we envisioned.
About your "next life" proposal,
I'll need time to think.
But
let's save next-life discussions
for next life.
I want to live this life well,
live every single day well.
It's getting late.
Let's depart.
Wait.
Zhao Chengtian.
(Tomb of the Regent)
His Majesty selected a royal clan child
to carry your lineage.
When he comes of age,
he'll come to visit you instead.
You have a descendant.
Go.
Why are you here?
As the Crown Prince's tutor,
shouldn't you be guarding him?
Why come here?
When will you be back?
I knew I couldn't hide it from you.
I didn't tell anyone
because I couldn't bear the goodbye.
When will you come back?
When I miss Xiao Hu,
I'll return.
You ran here earlier,
like when you were a child.
Child?
How so?
Clear-eyed, carefree.
Yu Feng.
Stop!
Put me down!
Seeing you this happy
makes me happy too.
Thank you
for protecting me.
You should leave now.
Before I change my mind
and kill Cheng Ziru.
Come! Hurry!
Let's go.
Don't miss me too much.
Winter is almost here.
I wonder how He An and Xiao Hu
are doing.
If you want to return,
I'll accompany you.
I just miss Xiao Hu.
Besides,
everything in the palace
is no longer our concern.
How can you say that?
Have you forgotten?
We swore before my sister.
As long as we are alive,
we'll protect He An and his reign.
Really?
I don't remember that.
You and she were like sisters,
and on her deathbed,
she summoned us
to entrust her son to us.
Did you forget?
I invited you here today
to ask a favor of you both.
Your Majesty,
there's nothing
we can't discuss between us.
Sister.
What are you doing?
I know full well
my health.
It is already at its limit.
Your Majesty.
I want to request
that after my death,
you two take my son under your care,
so he may survive
in this merciless palace.
I know it's difficult,
especially with the Regent
watching closely.
I wonder if you two
would agree to this.
Come.
Sit.
I promise you.
I swear
as long as I remain in the harem,
I'll keep him safe.
Sister,
I'll protect He An.
So
the Empress Dowager was remarkable.
A heroine!
Absolutely.
But
your memory is really bad now.
What do you mean?
You even forgot
our first time.
You...
But I remember
all the crucial things, don't I?
Rong,
you've suffered
a lot.
It was worth it.
If you want to return,
I'll go back with you.
Didn't you mention
migratory retirement?
We could stay in the palace
during winter to enjoy warm service
and go to the hills
in summer to cool off.
Like migrants.
That sounds good,
but
I'm the Empress Dowager.
My return is expected.
What identity would you use to return?
As the Emperor's uncle?
Yeah.
Wait,
don't I have another role?
Your male consort.
I knew you'd mention that.
Any regrets?
None whatsoever.
I regret nothing of all this.
We often can't distinguish
right from wrong.
All we can do
is let flowers be flowers,
trees be trees,
clouds be clouds,
and let us
be us.
Awake.
It went smoothly.
A boy, 3.35 kg.
Successful surgery.
I'm your attending physician,
Cheng Ziru.
(The End)
♪Cheering for time travel♪
♪Till I wake up to see a baby♪
♪A woman with three suitors♪
♪They say I'm fickle♪
♪The scholar confesses all with drinks♪
♪The guard just gives her a stony face♪
♪The regent waits in the moonlight♪
♪The title
of Empress Dowager brings pity♪
♪Palace farces play daily♪
♪Endless plot twists♪
♪That glimpse of you that day♪
♪Made my heart flutter♪
♪Peach blossoms♪
♪Bloom one by one in my heart♪
♪Who do I love♪
♪I guess with no direction♪
♪Who's pretending♪
♪While the truth slips by♪
♪Pretense becomes true as years flow♪
♪Dawn bells wake the dreamer♪
♪Sunlight bathes crimson walls♪
♪You said meeting me♪
♪Was your most beautiful surprise♪
♪Peach blossoms♪
♪Whose heart do they touch♪
♪Love resides within you♪
♪It brings sweetness to us two♪
♪My heart races♪
♪In this life, we refuse
to pass by as strangers♪
♪Lovers shall share
the moon's eternal grace♪
♪Dawn bells wake the dreamer♪
♪Sunlight bathes crimson walls♪
♪You said meeting me♪
♪Was your most beautiful surprise♪
♪Peach blossoms♪
♪Whose heart do they touch♪
♪Love resides within you♪
♪It brings sweetness to us two♪
♪My heart races♪
♪In this life, we refuse
to pass by as strangers♪
♪Lovers shall share
the moon's eternal grace♪
♪Peach blossoms♪
♪Whose heart do they touch♪
♪Love resides within you♪
♪It brings sweetness to us two♪
♪My heart races♪
♪In this life, we refuse
to pass by as strangers♪
♪Lovers shall share
the moon's eternal grace♪