=Seal of Love=
(Season 1)
=Episode 16=
(With these flowers,
you indeed look more handsome.)
Qing Chen,
don't be so sad.
She's a mere demon.
Besides,
Sang Luo was...
Get lost!
Lord Qing Chen of the Immortal Spirit Sect
turns out to be dumb.
It should be...
May I
adore you,
Master?
Unhappy?
Let me tell you a joke.
I'm not unhappy.
If you feel sad
for him,
how about you cry
like a little girl?
I'm your master
and the Demon Queen.
Like a little girl?
Right.
You're the strongest.
You have supremacy in the Demon World.
He and I are from different worlds.
We're not meant for each other.
♪In regret someone's no longer happy♪
(Fusheng,)
(what should I do with you?)
Forget him
and be with me, all right?
♪Year after year♪
(Don't do this, My Lord.)
(If you forcibly remove
the Heart Sorcery,)
(I'm afraid...)
Say no more.
(Actually, if you take out
Mu Yao's heart,)
(the Heart Sorcery will be removed.)
(I can)
(do it for you.)
But in this case,
Qing Chen will bother Fusheng.
♪Letters by letters I weep as I write♪
I will not
give him the chance.
(But My Lord...)
Am I
not clear?
(You are.)
Looks like
I'm more narrow-minded than you.
♪Can you take a look back♪
♪Just one look♪
Yuan.
Yuan?
♪In the next life
May everything be in peace♪
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love
I just can't get over it♪
♪Dying together only exists
in the legend♪
♪Memories fade away♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken
for someone merciless♪
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
♪Dying together only exists
in the legend♪
♪Memories fade away♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken
for someone merciless♪
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪