- I don't think I can watch it. - Do we need to actually watch it?
It's my first time watching it.
(Iron Girls 2)
(The girls challenged themselves to learn how to box.)
(Is this something we can do?)
(No one...)
(imagined...)
(that they'd learn a combat sport.)
(Their goal was to become...)
(a boxing champion.)
(They had to fight against...)
(the fear of a 1-on-1,)
(the fear of taking punches, )
(the fear of limits, )
(and the fear of injuries.)
(They worked hard to overcome all in the past 4 months.)
(They had their first tournaments.)
(Then came...)
(the last tournaments.)
(The stage where they'll burn every moment)
(The last story of Iron Girls 2)
(Let's briefly go back in time...)
(to last May 15.)
(Iron Girls 2, Long-Term Training Project)
- Hold on a second. - What?
- What did you have? - Rock-paper-scissors, my foot!
- What should we do? - That's the starting point.
I had never seen anything like it.
How is it different from the skim jump?
(What's today's training everyone is surprised about?)
Hey, there's no end in sight.
The training you'll do today is running up the stairs.
- Running up the stairs. - Do we need to run up the stairs?
- These stairs? - All of it?
It's the same as the ski jump.
How did you find this place?
- There are more stairs. - Yes.
(Aren't these stairs all?)
What are we going to do?
The stairs training course you'll do from now on...
has the 1st section with 252 stairs.
When you go up, you'll come across a flatland section.
You'll have time to recover.
(A flatland section for recovery)
The last section has 130 stairs.
(The 2nd section with 130 stairs)
(The course is complete after climbing 382 stairs.)
(Start, 1st staircase, flatland, 2nd staircase, end)
(The training course has a total of 3 sections.)
(The highest elevation is 209m.)
And this is a mini-project of Iron Girls 2.
You'll come here three times and record your time.
What?
(With the term of 45 days)
(1st, 2nd, 3rd)
(Through 3 sessions of the stairs training, )
(they must succeed in shortening their time.)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Get ready.
(The 1st stairs training starts.)
Go. All right.
(First staircase)
(In Ah takes the lead.)
What's up with her?
(Taking long strides)
(Stamina Queen Uie goes up 2 stairs at a time.)
(Ju Hyun and Sae Rok follow.)
(Groaning)
Go.
No. It's okay. You can do it.
How do you do this?
This is impossible.
(Meanwhile, Uie takes the lead.)
(She passes the two-thirds point of the 1st staircase.)
(She keeps going up 2 stairs at a time.)
(She becomes the 1st member to clear the 1st staircase.)
(Then comes the flatland section.)
(Since it's the flatland section, )
(Uie runs as she recovers her stamina.)
(She keeps running without stopping...)
(and enters the second staircase.)
(While Uie climbs up toward the endpoint)
Let's go.
(The member who was going last, Sae Rok, passes Ju Hyun.)
It's like a dessert.
All right. Run.
All right. Let's go. We need to keep going.
(Sae Rok begins to speed up.)
You need to compete against each other.
Let's try a bit harder. You're nearly at the endpoint.
(Uie is close to the endpoint.)
There you go. In Ah, let's go.
(In Ah, let's go?)
(In Ah, Uie)
(In Ah is close behind her.)
In Ah, that's good. In Ah is coming.
(When running on 2 feet gets hard, she crawls on all 4s.)
(The Simba Seol mode is on.)
(In Ah, Uie)
Uie, run until the end.
You're nearly at the end. Let's go.
She's coming.
There you go. Make a turn and come up to the finish line.
All right. Come up here.
There you go.
Okay.
Well done.
(Panting)
(She has exhausted her stamina.)
(Simba Seol is still going on all fours.)
(Groaning)
Come on. You're nearly done.
You can walk. Just don't stop. There you go.
Grit your teeth and climb up the stairs.
(Simba Seol never gives up.)
You're nearly done.
Okay. In Ah reached the finish line.
(Simba Seol passes out as well.)
I can't recover.
Let's run toward the end.
Run toward the end.
There you go. That's good.
Sae Rok, Ju Hyun is coming behind you.
(The last spurt)
Come on.
(The two of them don't stop until the very end.)
- Keep going. - There you go.
(Sae Rok: 6 minutes and 8 seconds)
- Keep going. - Okay. Well done.
- Keep going. - Ju Hyun, hurry up.
(Ju Hyun: 6 minutes and 12 seconds)
Okay.
(Collapsing)
Their facial expressions are real.
- That's a great record. - Well done.
- I'm exhausted. - Everyone did their best.
- Seriously, it was unbelievable. - They gave their all.
Seriously.
(Even Uie can't recover.)
I didn't expect it to be hard...
- from the start. - I know.
I had confidence at first.
(The high-intensity training made her confidence disappear.)
Two sessions remain, so good luck.
You need to fight against your record.
- Okay. - Stay alert.
(Thus, they began to improve their stamina...)
Nice form.
(through the rigorous physical training.)
Faster.
One, two, hook, hook.
Keep the angles right.
(For 45 days, they focused on their physical training.)
(45 days later, June 29)
Didn't you guys miss this place?
- No. - It has been a month.
- Not at all. - We need to shorten our records...
by 1 or 2 seconds, right?
Just 1 or 2 seconds?
What?
- That's... - Captain, I did my best then.
- Uie did too well from the start. - Yes.
You can shorten it by 20 seconds.
- Did you say 20 seconds? - You can shorten it by 20 seconds.
- Get ready. - I'm scared that I'll do worse.
(The 2nd stairs training)
Let's go.
It's slippery.
You need to get used to it.
(Taking long strides)
Watch the stairs.
(Captain Uie gets ahead today as well.)
(The younger members follow her.)
(One member stands out.)
(During the 1st training, she groaned...)
(and fell behind as the weakest member.)
(After just 45 days, she runs without getting exhausted.)
(She's running next to In Ah who did well in the 1st training.)
(Uie continues to climb up 2 stairs at a time.)
(First staircase)
(So far, Uie has cut down her time by 10 seconds.)
(Uie speeds up and runs.)
(So far, In Ah has cut down her time by 5 seconds.)
(So far, Sae Rok has cut down her time by 25 seconds.)
Let's pick up the speed.
Run as you shake your arms lightly.
Catch a breath.
(Sae Rok, Ju Hyun)
(End, Uie, In Ah, Sae Rok, Ju Hyun, start)
(Uie is halfway through the second staircase.)
There you go. A bit more.
(Uie's 1st record was 4 minutes and 33 seconds.)
(She has less than 30 seconds left to shorten it even by 1 second.)
Let's give it the last spurt.
There you go.
(She must shorten her time even by 1 second!)
The last spurt. There you go. Well done.
Well done. There you go. Keep going until the end.
Okay. Well done.
(Uie completes the 2nd training.)
(Ju Hyun, Sae Rok, In Ah)
(The members arrive one after another...)
(as if they're proving that their effort hasn't been wasted.)
This is insane.
Okay. Well done.
Well done.
(In Ah completes the 2nd training.)
Sae Rok, you're nearly done. Faster.
Sae Rok, you're nearly done.
There you go.
Let's shorten the time further.
Keep going until the end.
There you go. Well done.
(Sae Rok completes the 2nd training.)
Ju Hyun, you're nearly done.
Stop.
There you go. Well done.
Well done.
(She passes out right away.)
I'm exhausted.
(They used up every ounce of their energy.)
(Iron Girls are sprawled on the floor today as well.)
It isn't a good idea to lie down after reaching the finish line.
(Please stop.)
It's better to get up.
Get up.
Here's something to drink.
It's really high-intensity.
How does it put people in this state in 4 to 5 minutes?
- Did it only take 4 to 5 minutes? - You know...
In Ah, you're sweating so much.
Isn't it water? It's water, right?
- No. - It has to be water.
Look at her nose bridge.
There's sweat on her nose bridge.
I could feel that you guys did your best.
- All right. Uie. - Yes?
Your 1st record was 4 minutes and 33 seconds.
Your second record is...
four minutes and...
thirty...
Please.
Seconds.
(She shortened her time by 3 seconds.)
- Uie. - You shortened it by three seconds.
- Uie is crying. - Okay.
You shortened it by three seconds.
That's big.
In Ah, you came in 2nd. Your 1st record...
was 5 minutes and 22 seconds.
(1st record: 5 minutes and 22 seconds)
Your 2nd record is 5 minutes...
(2nd record: 5 minutes...)
and 13 seconds.
She came in faster.
(She shortened her time by 9 seconds.)
She shortened her time by nine seconds.
(Simba Seol shortened her time by 9 seconds.)
- That's insane. - Nine seconds is impressive.
- Sae Rok, you came in third. - Yes.
- Your first record was... - Yes.
- six minutes and 8 seconds. - Six minutes and 8 seconds.
Your second record...
is 5 minutes and 33 seconds.
(She shortened her time by 35 seconds.)
- That's incredible. - Sae Rok, that's incredible.
- Hey. - She shortened it by 35 seconds.
See? She reached the finish line very quickly.
- That's incredible. - The members told me...
- that my stamina had improved... - That's right.
During practice.
But even when I heard those words,
I couldn't tell if my stamina had improved or not.
Even though I was far up on the staircase,
- I wasn't out of breath. - Right.
I was like, "What? Why can I keep going?"
"Did my stamina improve?"
I felt like I was going up with ease.
The fact that I have the strength to run...
- makes me happy. - That's right.
Sae Rok.
I told you that you had improved.
One person can't congratulate her from the bottom of her heart.
Park Ju Hyun.
Your first record was 6 minutes and 12 seconds.
Your second record...
is 5 minutes and 44 seconds.
(She shortened her time by 28 seconds.)
- Ju Hyun! - You shortened it by 28 seconds.
I beat the past me.
This is proof that you guys have worked hard.
- Well done, everyone. - Seriously.
- We've done so well. - Well done.
(All Iron Girls succeeded in shortening the time.)
(Afterward, they focused on boxing once again.)
(The first sparring)
(The second sparring)
(The third sparring)
(Then they participated in their first tournaments.)
(45 days later, August 13)
We're back.
- Okay. - It's for the stairs training.
In Ah needs to recover before the tournaments.
- She shouldn't push herself. - Ju Hyun has...
- an injury as well. - Yes.
Ju Hyun, you have bad knees as well.
The inflammation could get worse,
so I don't think you should do the training today.
You came here because you wanted to do it,
but please just time the members' performances.
- Okay. - Let's do that.
Okay.
All right. This is the last stairs training.
Get ready.
(The 3rd stairs training starts.)
(They go up the stairs quickly.)
(Sae Rok...)
(runs up two stairs at a time!)
(Her speed is similar to Uie's.)
How are they so good at this?
I won't be able to keep up.
(First staircase)
(So far, Uie has cut down her time by 17 seconds.)
(So far, Sae Rok has cut down her time by 33 seconds.)
They're so fast.
(Panting)
I can't keep up.
(I can't keep up.)
(Running)
Uie!
(Uie can be seen between the trees in front of the second staircase.)
No way!
(No way!)
(It hasn't even been 3 minutes.)
- Uie, the record is unbelievable. - This is incredible.
Uie, don't stop.
Hey, Uie!
(Ju Hyun cheers Uie on at the top of her lungs.)
(Uie)
(Advancing quickly)
(Uie goes up the stairs without hesitation.)
Is that Sae Rok behind her?
(Sae Rok is close behind.)
(She loses speech because she's so surprised.)
(Sae Rok is not far behind Uie.)
You've slowed down for the stairs.
(Checking the time)
Uie, you need to speed up.
You need to speed up a bit.
(Okay.)
- That's good. - Uie, hurry up.
- Uie, run for five seconds. - You'll make a record.
- Five seconds. - Keep going until the end.
Keep going until the end.
There you go.
(Uie completes the 3rd training.)
No way.
Sae Rok, if you speed up, you won't regret it. Hurry up.
- Beat Sae Rok of the past. - Come on.
- Beat Sae Rok of the past. - Hurry up.
One, two.
- Run for five seconds. - One, two.
Eight, nine, ten.
- Hurry up. - You're nearly done.
- Come on. - You're nearly done.
- That's it. You're nearly done. - That's the finish line.
Go to the finish line.
This is incredible.
- Okay. You're done. - All done.
Okay.
(Sae Rok completes the 3rd training.)
- You know.. - Well done.
Until the halfway point, I couldn't keep up with Sae Rok.
- Really? - Yes.
(Sae Rok did her absolute best without stopping once.)
That's the sound you make when you're drained.
I'm exhausted.
(Groaning)
All right. The records are here.
You had the third session of the intense stairs training.
Uie,
your 1st record was 4 minutes and 33 seconds.
Your 2nd record was 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
All right. Here comes the third record.
It's four minutes...
(She shortened her time by 3 seconds between the 1st and 2nd records.)
and five seconds.
(She shortened her time by 25 seconds...)
(between the 2nd and 3rd records.)
Four minutes and 5 seconds.
- She cut down 25 seconds. - My goodness.
- That's incredible. - You're lying.
You're lying.
The thing is, I know that it's true.
That record isn't a surprise.
She was like a monster down there.
(She cut down the time with monstrous speed.)
I could see you, Uie.
You looked like a branch.
I didn't think that it was you,
- but it was you. - Was it me?
We were at three minutes then.
It was insane.
- That was why I screamed so much. - Four minutes and 5 seconds.
Then I'm really curious about Sae Rok's record.
- What was up with you? - I...
Sae Rok,
your 1st record was 6 minutes and 8 seconds.
(1st record: 6 minutes and 8 seconds)
Your 2nd record was 5 minutes and 33 seconds.
(2nd record: 5 minutes and 33 seconds)
The last one, the third record...
(She shortened her time by 35 seconds...)
(between the 1st and 2nd records.)
is 4 minutes and 48 seconds.
(She shortened her time by 45 seconds...)
(between the 2nd and 3rd records.)
(Glancing over)
- All right. - You're lying.
It's true. I lay down and looked at the timer.
You're lying.
- Really? - She cut down the time...
by 45 seconds.
- What? - Forty-five seconds.
So, 35 seconds and 45 seconds.
I feel like...
her record should be better...
- since she was so fast. - Really?
I can't believe I made it into the 4-minute range.
That's incredible.
- I'm proud of myself. - That's incredible.
- Well done. - Well done.
- I'm proud of you. - You worked hard.
Your hard work...
- didn't betray you. - I'm in the 4-minute rage?
Everyone, if you want to beat me...
It's the Iron Girls Challenge.
- Everyone. - You have to try it yourself.
Yes. Then you'll know how we feel.
(The Long-Term Training Project was a big success.)
(Also, )
(they did push-ups on the first day of the boxing training.)
(Ju Hyun couldn't bend her arms properly and kept trembling.)
(Even Stamina Queen struggled.)
(4 months later)
(Uie)
(The angle of her bent arms improved dramatically.)
(Ju Hyun)
(Their push-up skills improved along with their stamina.)
This is a feat for me.
This is a big improvement for me.
(She improved dramatically in 4 months.)
(And...)
(Sae Rok couldn't even do the basic postures before.)
(Our Sae Rok has changed.)
(She maintains a straight posture without falling over.)
(After consistent training, she can do consecutive push-ups with ease.)
(Iron Girls have improved a lot.)
(9 days before the final tournament)
(In Ah's training log: Worn out after hard training)
(Sae Rok's training log:)
(The tournament is just around the corner. Pull yourself together.)
(Wait for the right time and throw a lot of punches.)
(Ju Hyun's training log: Even if my knees are burning, )
(I'll give it my all during the match!)
Take a break.
Is your wrist bad?
Yes. I got two shots,
but it's been feeling numb all day.
(Uie's training log: I can get my wrist treated after the match.)
(I'll think of it as a glorious wound...)
(and try my best without regrets.)
(Right before achieving their final goal, they can't stop here.)
(The day of the final tournament)
(The 4th Korea Sports Council President's Cup...)
(National Amateur Boxing Tournament)
(Finally, the day of the showdown)
(At 6am, Incheon Seonhak Stadium)
We've worked hard for today.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's the big day. - It's finally the big day.
(Staring)
Did you come here by plane?
She looks like a pilot.
I drove here.
- You did? - She came here in a fighter jet.
- I'm in combat mode right now. - Good.
It's interesting that you have items like this at home.
Finally, today is the day...
of Iron Girls' second tournament and final showdown.
It's been four months.
You've prepared a lot for this day.
You've trained really hard.
How are you feeling now?
This tournament is different.
I want to show off what I've practiced.
Whether I win or lose, I'll keep going...
until I feel like I can't do better than this.
Ju Hyun is pulling off the boxing I like really well.
- Really? - Yes.
- She's incredible. - She's amazing.
I will keep throwing my one-twos...
and land more punches than my opponent,
even if I get hit a lot.
I'll clearly show people what One-Two Uie is like.
Then I will leave the ring without any regrets.
"I'm ready to take the hit." This means a lot.
- Right. -Those with that determination...
won't panic, no matter what happens.
- That's really scary. - Uie used to be afraid of punches,
but she has changed in four months.
- Yes. - Right.
I'm...
Silver Sae Rok.
- I'm Silver Sae Rok yet. - Right.
I'll try hard to win gold and become Keum Sae Rok.
Did you dream of becoming a soldier before?
You sound like a soldier when you give a speech.
She's so lovely.
Will you live up to your name today?
- Yes, I'll live up to my name. - All right.
You'll be Keum Sae Rok again after this tournament.
Yes. I'll get my name back.
- Okay. - Good luck!
In Ah. Actually...
I'm someone who's been knocked down once.
All that's left now is to get back up.
(She's equipped with the determination of Simba Seol.)
I tell the other members to give it their all,
but I'll give you a different order.
- Don't give it your all. - I won't.
Just do it like you did...
- during practice. - I'll just try to have fun.
- I'm serious. - Right. Just try to enjoy it.
I'll think of it as sparring.
Good. Regardless of win or lose, just give it your all
and show what you've trained in the ring before you leave.
(Reaching out her hand)
- I'm hungry. - Are you hungry?
- I'm hungry. - Sure.
Ju Hyun says she's hungry.
She's been trying to lose weight.
I've never felt this hungry before.
- You've moved down in weight. - Yes.
Right. Your weight class has changed.
- Yes. - Right.
- How did it go? - I've been working out,
- Yes. - so I've been losing weight.
So I thought it'd be better...
to move down in weight and try my best.
That's what the coach and I discussed.
So I'm in the under-51kg division.
Did you lose some weight then?
I've lost a little weight.
I've been eating chicken breast and brown rice for a few days.
I see. You managed to lose weight.
So I'm really afraid now.
- With the clothes on... - I know, right?
- Yes. - I know how it feels.
Right.
Ju Hyun is...
- in the under-51kg division. - The under-51kg division.
In Ah and Sae Rok are...
- in the under-54kg division. - The under-54kg division.
- Actually, we had another goal. - Right.
Uie's goal was to gain 1kg of muscle mass.
Sae Rok's goal was to lose body fat.
- Yes. - To lower body fat percentage.
Did you weigh yourselves?
Uie.
- Did you succeed? - You succeeded.
- Did you succeed? - Uie succeeded.
- I succeeded. - Really?
It's 24.1kg.
(Changes in Uie's body composition)
(Height: 172cm)
(A month ago, Weight: 52.4kg, Skeletal Muscle Mass: 22.9kg)
(A week ago, Weight: 52.5kg, Skeletal Muscle Mass: 24.1kg)
(Skeletal Muscle Mass: Plus 1.2kg, Body Fat Mass: Minus 2kg)
- It changed from 22.9kg to 24.1kg. - Yes.
That's not easy.
My body fat percentage has dropped by two percent.
And I've gained 1kg of muscle mass.
(Changes in Sae Rok's body composition)
(Height: 169cm)
(A month ago, Weight: 53.2kg, Skeletal Muscle Mass: 21.9kg)
(A week ago, Weight: 53.4kg, Skeletal Muscle Mass: 22.9kg)
(Skeletal Muscle Mass: Plus 1kg, Body Fat Mass: Minus 1kg)
(Impressed)
That's amazing. Seriously.
- You've worked really hard. - Right.
And you've eaten well.
Now, let's go in...
- and weigh in first. - We have to do this.
Go into the stadium.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Yes.
(Congratulations on the Boxing Tournament.)
This is huge.
(Feeling nervous)
This is really big.
There's only one ring.
(A huge ring)
This is really huge.
This is the standard ring that professional boxers compete in.
(This is where the boxing tournament is taking place today.)
This is an amazing place.
This is the stadium where the Incheon Asian Games took place,
and where Shin Jong Hun won the gold medal in boxing...
in the Asian Games.
The previous tournament was held in Seoul,
but this one is called the National Tournament.
It's a national tournament.
(Like its name, boxers from across the country participate.)
I'm so nervous.
(The final tournament venue for the history of Iron Girls)
This is really huge.
- Why are there monitors here? - Monitors?
Are there monitors?
(In front of the judges' seats)
(In front of the coaches' seats)
(There are monitors in front of the audience too.)
(Electric scoreboards that display scores from each round)
After Round One is over,
the scores are announced on the monitors.
- My goodness. - The judges' scores?
The coaches can see that.
And even the audience.
(The judges, coaches, and spectators can see the scores.)
After the first round is over,
you can see if you're winning or losing.
I don't want to see that.
(She can't breathe.)
I'm so nervous.
(They feel even more nervous...)
(with the increased scale.)
This is where the boxers register.
I see.
(They leave their worries behind they register first.)
Affiliation, Iron Girls.
(This is already their second time filling out the boxer ID.)
(They get their boxer ID issued...)
(and undergo medical checks first.)
Please go to the weigh-in room.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Take this. - Thank you.
- Weigh-in. - Now, finally...
- This is the important part. - Let's hurry and weigh in.
(This is a nerve-racking moment.)
- Next. Please come in. - Come in.
- Name? - Park Ju Hyun.
Yes. Show me your boxer ID.
We will take your weight. Please get on the scales.
- Here? - Yes. Please get on it.
Stay still.
(Ju Hyun must weigh under 51kg to pass the weigh-in.)
- It's 50.58kg. - It's 50.58kg.
(She passes with 50.58kg.)
- Yes. - You passed.
Get off the scales.
(She maintained her weight successfully.)
Good luck.
Yes. Please get on the scales.
(In Ah starts the weigh-in for the under-54kg division.)
Stand still.
- It's 53.82kg. - It's 53.82kg.
Get off the scales.
(The weight from the previous tournament)
(Determined In Ah maintained her weight perfectly.)
(In Ah passed the weigh-in in an instant.)
(In the meantime)
- I'm so nervous. - Don't be nervous.
(She feels extremely nervous after taking off her shirt.)
I'm so nervous.
State your name, please.
- Keum Sae Rok. - Okay.
Hang on a second.
(Sae Rok's goal is to stay under 54kg as well.)
- It's 53.10kg. - Yes.
You passed.
(Sae Rok passed easily.)
- Bye. - Bye.
- Thank you. - Good luck.
State your name.
- I'm Uie. Kim Yu Jin. - Okay.
(And it's finally Uie's turn.)
(Uie must weigh under 51kg to pass.)
Please get on the scales.
Stand still.
(Her first attempt to lose weight)
(Did she succeed?)
It's 50.84.
(She passes with 50.84kg.)
- You passed. - Yes.
(It would've been close if she had kept her shirt on.)
Thank you.
Good luck.
(Sobbing)
(Uie succeeded in losing weight.)
I'm 50.8kg.
- I did it. - That was so close.
(Surprised)
Thank goodness you had your shirt off.
(She thanks her t-shirt too.)
We all succeeded.
- What should we eat? - What are we eating? Let's go.
You should recover.
- Eat something nutritious. - Let's eat.
(Amazed)
What's that?
(There's something on the table.)
- What... - What is this?
Gloves?
Are these glove rice cakes?
How did you think of this?
How did you make this?
It's so cute.
- They're so cute. - Seriously,
this is so thoughtful.
- How did they make them? - It's such a thoughtful gift.
- Let's eat and recover. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Okay.
Recover.
Cheers.
(Making a toast with gloves)
(Taking a pleasant bite of the rice cake)
(Uie, who has successfully lost weight, enjoys a hearty meal.)
(Ju Hyun, who was hungry, also takes a big bite.)
This is so delicious.
(Ju Hyun, who was feeling hungry, also takes a big bite.)
I'm feeling great now.
That's a relief.
A total of 280 boxers are competing in today's tournament.
Among them, 47 are female boxers.
They are divided into middle school, high school, 20s, 30s, 40s, and 50s.
There are even boxers in their 50s.
Today is the preliminaries,
and if you win this, you'll be in the finals tomorrow.
(Preliminary rounds today, final rounds the next day)
- This is a big competition. - They're divided into many groups.
(This is a big competition.)
The round duration is different today.
Let me tell you about it.
Each round is 1 minute and 30 seconds.
And the rest period...
- was 40 seconds before. - It was 40 seconds.
In this tournament, it's one minute.
(The rest period is 1 minute today.)
What?
That's enough time to have a meal.
You can even go to the restroom within the extra 20 seconds.
(They get an extra 20 seconds for the rest period.)
But I'm not the only one who can rest for one minute.
- The opponent rests too. - That's true.
That's not good.
Let's go back to 40 seconds.
Our strength is stamina.
That's my strength.
You have to try harder.
- So the opponent can't recover. - Right.
I have to finish it in Round One.
Lastly, I'll tell you about the order of play.
The first boxer is...
Seol In Ah.
The match number is 12.
Park Ju Hyun. The match number is 14.
Uie is next. The match number is 15.
- Again? - Yes.
Our turns are all lined up.
Lastly, Sae Rok's match number is 17.
We can say you are fighting almost back-to-back.
Right.
- So... - Of course.
The coach will be really busy.
He almost has no time to take a break.
This is my second time...
participating in a boxing tournament,
and I'm fighting against the opponent whom I met again.
- What? - Right.
We're fighting again. Can you believe this?
(The match list was announced a week ago.)
(The name that is familiar to Ju Hyun...)
(is found on the match list.)
(The final match of the last tournament)
(The very opponent who cornered Ju Hyun like a zombie)
(She is facing the same opponent she fought so hard against...)
(in the preliminary match once again today.)
After I found that out,
I've been seeing her face in my dreams.
I'm serious.
It's random, isn't it?
It is drawn up randomly using the computer.
- Then how did this happen? - Actually,
I've fought the same opponent before.
There were 80 boxers entering, and I met the same opponent again.
- It happens. - It does.
- That's interesting. - You should accept the fate...
- and just fight. - Right.
(Even Ju Hyun, who is always positive, is feeling nervous today.)
(Now, it's time to accept their fate.)
(1 hour before the preliminaries)
(The opening ceremony begins in the stadium.)
(Ryu Seung Min, the president of the Korean Sports Council)
(The spectators are filling the seats.)
(The boxers change into their uniforms...)
(and start warming up 1 by 1.)
(A fierce battle for the ticket to the finals)
(Iron Girls get ready to take the field.)
(Wrapping their hands with resolute determination)
(Finally)
(The preliminaries of the final tournament begin.)
(The battle in the ring begins once again.)
Again, one, two.
Good. Again.
(It's time to prove their blood, sweat, and tears...)
(of the last 4 months on the ring.)
- Then you hit me like this. - Yes.
When you stand straight, it's not easy.
When the opponent hits you, you should lower your body.
You should lower your body like she does.
And two.
(For a match with no regrets)
(To defeat yesterday's me...)
(and today's opponent)
Let's go to the ring.
(Let's go to the ring.)
Stay calm.
(Iron Girls enter the stands on the 2nd floor.)
- Good luck. - Thank you.
(As they enter the stadium, )
Let's do this.
(the tension intensifies.)
Gosh, it's hot.
I guess our acquaintances are sitting over there.
(Iron Girls)
(On the opposite side)
(The banners rooting for them are hanging on the opposite side.)
(The fairy of the ring, Rocky Keum!)
(From Stamina Queen to Boxing Queen!)
(Every moment of our fierce fight is a champion.)
(Our cheer leader, Ju Hyun's father is present again today.)
(Today, not only the family and friends of Iron Girls, )
(but also the athletes who trained with them came to cheer them on.)
(Wrestlers: Kwon Young Jin, Park Hyeon Yeong)
(Former Special Forces soldiers: Kim Ji Eun, Yang Hae Ju)
(Fitness athlete: Hong Beom Seok)
Where are our moms?
(Ju Hyun, I'm here.)
(In Ah's parents are here.)
Ju Hyun, let's send them a heart together.
(Seeing their parents, their tension melts away for a moment.)
Our dads are making a heart together.
(In Ah's father, Ju Hyun's father)
(Relax, girls.)
The women's tournament is about to begin.
(The boxers are waiting on the 1st floor.)
(So soon?)
(In Ah, who's fighting first, is extremely nervous.)
I'm scared.
(The members feel nervous too.)
It's okay, Uie.
(The last match of the men's tournament is over.)
(In Ah's match is drawing near.)
My turn is the match after next.
Should In Ah start warming up? Is she going now?
All right. Let's go.
(In Ah heads to the ring.)
Good luck.
(The members see In Ah off with trembling hearts.)
Let's do this.
(In Ah shakes off her fear and heads to the ring.)
- Thank you. - Good luck.
(10 minutes left before In Ah's match)
(In Ah enters the stadium.)
(She arrives at the glove room.)
(She has her clothing and hand wraps checked before a match.)
All right. Let's go.
(She has her attire checked before the match.)
Head.
(She puts on the headgear.)
Okay.
Just stay calm, okay?
- I'll have fun. - Yes. Just have fun.
Just do it like you're sparring.
Let's go.
I'll have fun today.
(She wants to enjoy this moment with a light heart.)
(And the opponent In Ah will fight against today)
(Tak Ye Won, 20s, under 54kg)
(Boxing experience: 7 months)
(Taekwondo experience: 6 years)
Is In Ah's opponent strong?
- There. - There she is.
(They found the opponent.)
I'm not sure. She has long arms.
I think so.
I guess they're about the same height.
(The opponent has a long reach.)
You get the feeling 30 seconds into Round 1.
Who did you come to root for?
- Iron Girls, of course. - Really?
In Ah is up next, so you should root for her together.
- Sure. We will. - All right.
(He successfully recruited a cheering squad.)
(The previous match is over.)
In Ah is up next.
(Finally, it's In Ah's turn.)
First, try a jab in the stomach,
give a feint,
and then a high-low combination.
Stomach, a feint, and a high-low combination.
Let's go.
She's coming.
(Seol In Ah steps up.)
Let's go, Seol In Ah!
(With everyone cheering, )
(she steps into the ring.)
(Now all that is left...)
(is to give it her all.)
A lot of people are cheering her on.
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(Ju Hyun and Uie, who came down early, )
(also cheer for her.)
(To the center of the ring amidst the enthusiastic cheering)
Don't lower your head, and don't grab. Touch gloves.
- Back to your corners. - Good luck.
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
- Stay calm. - Seol In Ah!
(Preliminary Round, Under 54kg: Seol In Ah versus Tak Ye Won)
(Round 1 begins.)
Good.
You can do this.
Let's go.
(In Ah's first body jab)
(They throw jabs at the same time.)
(In Ah throws a straight as she steps back.)
Circle around. Go back in.
In Ah, you got this.
Keep doing your footwork.
Circle around. Strike.
One, two. That's right! Circle around. Yes.
Nice.
(In Ah lands a straight while her opponent swings and misses.)
(In Ah follows up with a jab.)
(Dodges)
You're doing great.
(In Ah uses her quick footwork to keep her distance.)
Punch.
(In Ah lands a jab.)
Punch. That's it.
That's it. Good job.
- Nice. - KO.
(Blue Corner is given a standing eight count.)
(In Ah threw a powerful straight, )
(followed with a right hook.)
(The crowd goes wild.)
(You go, In Ah!)
(That's my daughter.)
(Cheers erupting from all around.)
(The standing eight count begins for In Ah's opponent.)
(The referee checks the boxer's condition.)
Keep it up like this.
Give a feint. Yes.
(Remaining time: 30 seconds)
(In Ah evades and lands a jab.)
- You got this! - Seol In Ah!
(They throw a jab at each other at the same time.)
Go up and down. Throw a hook.
Focus.
Yes. Again.
That's it. One, two.
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
Throw a punch. Throw it!
That's it.
(In Ah landed a clean right hook.)
(She lands another right hook.)
(Round 1 ends.)
In Ah.
(1-minute break)
Sit.
Breathe.
You did great,
but you're backing up too much.
And everything you throw is landing, so keep throwing.
It would be even better if you throw a hook after.
What did I tell you to do?
- Jab, then a cross-counter. - Yes. Jab, then a cross-counter.
And finish with a hook.
- Jab, cross-counter, hook. - Yes. Finish with a hook.
You're doing great. Great movement.
(The Blue Corner also discusses their strategy.)
Don't rush.
Youre stepping in just enough for the opponent to strike.
She's quick.
Wait for her to attack, then land a double hook.
It doesn't matter.
Don't be intimidated, all right?
(While the boxers prepare for Round 2,)
(the judges tally up the points from Round 1.)
Gosh, Round One is...
(What is In Ah's score for Round 1?)
(In Ah, Ye Won)
(In Ah, her opponent)
In Ah got ten points for everything.
(In Ah wins Round 1, with 10 points for everything.)
It's 10 to 9, 10 to 8, and 10 to 8.
That's a huge difference.
She's leading by a landslide.
In Ah's confident,
and she said she's feeling great.
- She's doing amazing. - Yes.
Seol In Ah, you got this!
(Will In Ah be able to carry the momentum through Round 2?)
(Round 2 begins.)
The vibe is good.
You can tell she worked hard.
- Seol In Ah! - You got this!
(Round 2, Under 54kg: Seol In Ah versus Tak Ye Won)
Yes.
(In Ah lands a right hook.)
That was nice.
(She quickly evades her opponent's attack.)
(In Ah waits patiently, watching for the right timing.)
There's no need for In Ah to rush.
It's her opponent who should be rushing.
You got this!
- Seol In Ah! - You got this!
(She throws a jab in her opponent's opening.)
(And then attempts a hook.)
Attack.
She can't find her way in.
That's it.
Gosh, that was close.
More. Go short.
You're doing great.
Nice.
- You're doing great. - She can't find her way in.
Try it. That's it.
Move closer. That's too far.
Keep going.
(The opponent pushes her way in and lands a valid strike.)
That's it. Nice.
- Nice. - That's it.
(A cross-counter)
(The opponent strikes back with a double hook.)
(Another cross-counter)
If you want to fight, she'll fight back.
- Seol In Ah, you got this! - You got this!
- Seol In Ah! - You got this!
(Stop)
(Listen for the stop signal!)
(The referee warns the Blue Corner to keep her head up.)
In Ah, do a high-low combination and a hook.
(Got it.)
Fight.
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
(A high-low combination and a hook, just as she was coached)
(Another high-low combination and a hook)
- Nice. - Nice.
(A high-low combination and a hook)
Yes!
(Round 2 ends.)
You did great.
(Right after the round is over, cheers erupt from all around.)
(Did you just see that?)
Yes!
(The Iron Girls cast in the cheering section go wild.)
(Ju Hyun gives them a round of applause.)
You did great.
I did what you said twice.
Good job.
(They gather in the center of the ring for the results.)
Thank you.
(The most nerve-wracking moment)
(Everyone is quiet, waiting to see what happens.)
(Blue Corner showed speed and tenacity.)
(In Ah showed her powerful offense.)
(Which boxer will be going to the finals?)
(Seol In Ah wins.)
(Seol In Ah advances to the finals.)
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(Even the crowd is in a festive mood.)
Okay!
That's my In Ah.
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
- Seol In Ah! - Yes!
Blue Corner, Iron Girls.
- Great job. - Great job!
(In Ah leaves the ring, overwhelmed with emotion.)
(Ina overcame her injury and made an incredible comeback.)
- Guys. - Good job.
Give it your all. I'll be cheering for you, okay?
(Uie and Ju Hyun are preparing for their next match.)
Park Ju Hyun, you got this.
- I wasn't even worried about you. - Fight in a jazzy style.
Coach.
(She quickly leaves, so Ju Hyun can focus ahead of her match.)
- You were great. - We cheered for you.
Thank you.
I really did my best.
(That's the best compliment she could give herself.)
Rocky!
I'll be cheering for you really hard.
- I love you. - Just fight like youve practiced.
(You got this!)
(The crowd congratulates In Ah.)
Seol In Ah!
- Captain Kim! - Sit here in the cheering section.
I'm in the cheering squad now.
- It's Ju Hyun. - Gosh, In Ah.
Did you see me do a high-low combination and a hook?
- Twice? - What happened out there?
You were incredible.
I gave it my all.
(In Ah's win was solidified by...)
(a perfectly executed high-low combination.)
(This was the best moment in today's match.)
You were really great.
Of all the Iron Girl matches, yours was the most professional.
- Captain, - Seriously.
You told me I was going in too hard, and I should save up my energy.
And I really took note of it.
Boxing is so fun.
It was amazing.
(Ju Hyun is waiting for her match.)
You got this.
It's your fate. Just accept it.
I was destined to become the Zombie Boxer.
(She'll be face-to-face with the fighter from her past match.)
I think you're the best. Seriously.
Come on.
(Ju Hyun arrives at the glove room.)
Sit.
I'm fighting against her again.
(Ju Hyun is facing an opponent she fought in her first match.)
(Lee Bo Ra, 30s, under 54kg)
(She is the one who pressed Ju Hyun like a zombie in the first match.)
(Ju Hyun won, )
(but it wasn't an easy match.)
She might start as soon as the bell rings.
(She might start attaching as soon as the bell rings.)
Prepare for that, okay?
- Keep swinging the hooks. - Okay.
I think I used...
my arms a bit too much.
Just now?
It's okay.
You warmed up enough.
It could be better. Don't worry about it.
(Coach Kim comforts Ju Hyun, who is anxious.)
(She quietly waits for her turn, )
(and tries to settle her mind.)
The next match is from the women, 30s, under 51kg,
Park Ju Hyun, of the Iron Girls.
(Ju Hyun steps up.)
(Calmly, as always, )
(Ju Hyun heads to the ring.)
- Ju Hyun, let's go! - Ju Hyun, let's go!
- She saw us. - She saw us.
She winked at me.
(Ju Hyun gets on the ring.)
Breathe.
- Ju Hyun, it's nothing. - Park Ju Hyun!
- This is... - Park Ju Hyun!
- Park Ju Hyun! - Park Ju Hyun!
Don't panic, and just relax. Take it easy.
Just do as you always do, okay?
If you keep close, she can't do anything.
She doesn't have that experience.
She's Zombie Fighter.
She's an aggressive fighter who presses in.
Ju Hyun, please. Let's go.
Keep your heads up. No holding.
Hitting below the belt is a foul.
Shake hands.
Step back.
Ju Hyun, there's no reason to get nervous.
Make a feint with a jab,
and two hooks. Okay? As soon as it begins.
(Preliminary Round, Under 51kg: Lee Bo Ra versus Park Ju Hyun)
(Round 1 begins.)
Let's go, Ju Hyun!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- That's it. - Okay, nice.
(Like the last match, the opponent presses in.)
- Keep going in. - Stop.
Stop.
- Stop. - She's pushing too much.
Red, no pushing with your head.
(The opponent got a warning for keeping her head low.)
She kept her head too low.
She had her head on the opponent.
- She was pushing with her head. - You can't do that, right?
You can't push too much.
Box.
(The game resumes.)
- Throw a punch. - That's it.
- Go in. - That's it.
(Another valid jab)
Good.
(Ju Hyun makes use of her hit and defensive tactics.)
- That's it. - Good.
- She's coming in. That's it. - Once more.
(The opponent charges in again.)
(The opponent's right hook)
Circle away. That's it.
(She circles away.)
(One, two)
Good. Circle away.
(The opponent presses in again.)
Keep hitting.
You need to use it.
That's it.
- Good. - Good.
(A slugfest goes on.)
Circle away.
(Ju Hyun's left hook and dodge)
(The opponent's left hook)
(A flurry from the opponent)
Circle away.
It's not easy for her to get out.
She's fighting so hard.
- Stay calm. - Park Ju Hyun!
- Park Ju Hyun! - Let's go!
(She got hit with a valid strike with her arm in lock.)
(Jab)
More! That's it! Yes!
(Jab, right hook)
You need to hit more. Don't back out too much.
(Ju Hyun's jab, the opponent's hook)
- That's it. - That's it.
Ju Hyun, don't wait.
Just go in.
She's waiting too long.
- That's it. - Stop!
Don't hit the back of the head.
Red, keep your head up.
- Keep your head up. - Box.
- The head... - Stop!
(Round 1 ends)
Round One is over.
What else can she do when the opponent keeps digging in?
- She can't help but hit the back. - I know.
The opponent has her head down.
- She's going like this. - Yes.
(They check the score for Round 1.)
I see it.
I can't tell with the first round.
(What is the score for the intense Round 1?)
(Bo Ra, Ju Hyun)
(Opponent, Ju Hyun)
Red is 10 and 9.
- She lost, right? - Yes, just by a bit.
It's a bit tricky.
It was a bit tricky, because she stepped back too much,
and she only hit when she got hit. She shouldn't do that.
After the opponent uses up her strength, she takes a rest.
That's when she should go with a flurry of strikes.
- She waited too long, right? - She just kept waiting.
Breathe.
You're really doing great now,
but you're getting hit by such easy strikes.
When she makes a jab,
- you can dodge to the side. - Yes.
Then you have to attack right away.
She keeps holding me, so I can't go.
It's okay. Forget about that.
After two hooks, dodge, and strike a one-two.
Just do that. Do that, and you will win.
- Okay. - Alright?
Ju Hyun is also tense right now.
She can't do anything other than reach a punch.
She can't do anything if you press in.
Just keep pressing in.
As soon as they announce the ten seconds, just press in.
You can do it. Okay?
Deep breaths.
What are you going to do?
Jab, dodge,
- Okay. - and then a one-two.
Just throw lots of punches.
Throw lots of punches and dodge to the side.
- Okay? - Let's go.
Let's go, Park Ju Hyun!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Jab, dodge, and a one-two.
(Round 2 begins.)
- Let's go. - Let's go, Park Ju Hyun!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(As planned, jab, dodge, one, two)
Just do that. That's it.
Yes, just do that.
(She continues on with jabs.)
That's it.
Good job.
Hit more.
- That's it. - That's it. You need to keep going.
Here she comes. Punch. That's it.
(After watching the timing, Ju Hyun attacks with a flurry.)
(A strong jab)
(Two, one, two)
(A finishing right hook)
(Good job, Ju Hyun.)
Again! That's it!
(The opponent gets low again.)
Stop!
(She ends up losing her balance and falls.)
(The opponent gets another warning.)
Don't keep your head down.
She got too many warnings.
She got the same warning over and over.
She needs to get points deducted.
She keeps getting in trouble for having her head down.
Box.
(The game resumes.)
- She's coming. - Hit!
That's it! Good!
She needs to strike more.
More. I know you're tired, but more.
(She keeps circling and throwing jabs.)
More.
That's it.
(A one-two between her guard)
- She's coming in. Hit one. - Let's go!
(The opponent drives her to the corner again.)
Circle away.
(She tries to dodge by circling out, )
(but the opponent keeps pressing in.)
(Due to the opponent pressing in, it's hard to make a single punch.)
That's it.
Hey, come on.
Hold it. That's it.
That's it. Dodge out.
That's it.
She's using her head to...
Don't push.
(The opponent ends up getting a fourth warning.)
Ju Hyun, cheer up.
(Dodging after a jab)
(A slugfest until the end)
Stop!
(Round 2 ends.)
You did well, Ju Hyun!
(Ju Hyun poured out all her strength.)
You did well.
- Sure. - Step back.
(Now, only the results remain.)
This is going to be hard to judge.
She did get hit a lot at the end of the first round.
(From the very start, Red Corner came in strong...)
(by pressuring Ju Hyun with endless attacks.)
(Ju Hyun displayed smart moves with hit and withdraws, )
(and proved her skills in Round 2.)
(Everyone outside the ring watches...)
(with the same tension.)
Please.
No, Ju Hyun will win.
(What will be the result of this intense match?)
Please.
No, Ju Hyun will win.
(What will be the result of this intense match?)
(Red Corner wins.)
(Ju Hyun loses.)
Thank you.
You did well.
- You did well. - You did well.
- Good job. - Good job.
Good job. It's okay.
(Ju Hyun leaves the stadium despite the regrets.)
Good job.
(Endless applause to Ju Hyun who did her best)
- Thank you. - And now...
I had a lot of regrets.
I didn't get to show everything I learned.
That's what I regret.
But when I lost,
I was actually glad that I lost.
All that I've done,
getting hurt and being in pain,
and everyone who helped me came to my mind.
(Everyone who cheered for Ju Hyun)
As I overcame this fear,
I gave my all.
I think it was a good experience.
So I'm satisfied.
(Because she gave her all, she has no regrets.)
- Thank you. - Good work.
(Ju Hyun leaves the stadium with relief.)
- Good job. - Thank you.
(The audience cheers Ju Hyun up.)
Good job, Park Ju Hyun.
- Keep it up. - Thank you.
(And...)
Ju Hyun.
(she finally meets In Ah and Captain Kim.)
- It was... - You were amazing.
All your double hooks were accurate.
If you gave your all in the last ten seconds...
in Round Two,
the judges would've moved. It's a bummer.
- Good job. You were amazing. - Her punches were strong.
- Let's go. One-Two Uie. - Let's go!
(Next is Uie's match.)
(The extreme tension...)
(makes her want to retch.)
I always try my best to watch my members.
But at the time, I couldn't see anything.
I barely remember it.
(She moves to the glove room full of tension.)
Let's put it on.
- Does it fit? How is it? - Yes.
(Putting on the head gear and the gloves)
(Glancing)
(Yun Bo Ra, 30s, under 51kg)
(Boxing experience)
(1 year and 5 months)
(Uie also stands up.)
As if you're playing. Try a one-two again.
Jab. Keep your guard up.
(Extreme mind game even before the start)
One-two. And the hook.
That's right.
(Uie sets off.)
(It's time to enter the ring.)
(Despite the tension, )
(she moves forward.)
(The unavoidable head-on match)
Go, Kim Uie.
- Go! - You can do it!
- Go, Kim Uie! - Go, Kim Uie!
- Uie! - Uie!
- Uie! - Yun Bo Ra!
Yun Bo Ra!
(The stadium heats up.)
- You've worked hard until now. - Yun Bo Ra!
Just do your best today. Imagine this is sparring.
- No need to be intimidated. - Yes.
- Go, Uie! - Come forward.
- Uie! - Go, Yun Bo Ra.
Don't drop your head.
Don't grab each other.
Keep it above the belt.
Shake hands.
- Yun Bo Ra! - Yun Bo Ra!
- Uie, just keep calm. Okay? - Yun Bo Ra!
This is only sparring. It's okay.
(Round 1, Under 51kg: Yun Bo Ra versus Uie)
Bo Ra, keep it long. The left hook.
Body. That's right!
That's right. Good job!
You got it. Yes!
(Stop)
(The Red Corner is warned.)
She hit with this.
She hit with the open blow.
The opponent has a strong punch.
It's considered cheating because it was an open blow.
(The game resumes.)
You got it. Yes!
(Uie's flurry of one-twos)
Yes!
(Uie's one-two versus the opponent's low)
Uie, focus on that. That's good.
You're punching her every time. Good job.
- Kim Uie! - Kim Uie!
(The opponent's swinging hook is wide.)
Stop.
(Red Corner is warned again for the open blow.)
- Box. - Kim Uie!
- Go, Yun Bo Ra. - Uie!
- Good job. - Good.
You got it!
Fight back.
Punch. Yes!
Fight back. Yes. Fight back again.
(Uie's flurry of one-two again)
Keep it up.
Keep it up. Fight back. Yes!
(As the opponent continues to try a hook...)
Just focus on that. Yes.
Yes!
Again. Yes. Keep going.
(She fights back with infinite one-two.)
Like a submachine gun.
(Uie's valid strike 1)
(Uie's valid strike 2)
(Uie's valid strike 3)
(Uie's valid strike 4)
(Uie's valid strike 5)
(Uie's valid strike 6)
(Uie's valid strike 7)
(Uie's valid strike 8)
- Kim Uie! - You can do it!
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
(A valid one-two strike when the opponent tries a hook)
Punch. Yes!
(Round 1 ends.)
Sit.
Every one-two you tried worked.
- Was it good? - Right?
You did great. Just keep it going.
- It's nothing hard. That's it. - Yes.
- Okay? - Yes.
Breathe.
(Meanwhile, in the Red Corner)
Check the score.
(Checking the score)
(Uie won Round 1.)
- She's winning. - Totally.
Oh, that's a relief.
You're doing great.
If you can, circle around and try a one-two.
Try a feint.
Give a feint and punch her when she approaches.
And try a two when the opponent tries a jab.
- Then try to punch her, okay? - Yes.
Give your lead hand and wait for the opponent's jab.
You're only trying one-twos. Your face is unguarded.
Punch. Okay?
Do your footwork and punch.
Go for the low-high. Okay?
Give a feint. Don't be intimidated.
- Uie! - Uie!
(Round 2 begins.)
(Uie tries one-two first.)
Punch. That's right.
(The opponent fights back with the right hook.)
Yes.
(Followed by a slugfest)
Good job. Keep trying one-twos.
Punch. Yes!
Good job. Again.
(The opponent fights back with a hook.)
You saw her hook.
Jab and punch. Yes. Good job.
(After the one-two, )
(she tries a left hook.)
Let's go. One-Two Uie!
- Let's go! - You can do it!
(Stop)
(Red Corner is warned for the third time.)
Time out.
(The game stops.)
(Iron Girls, give your fiery punch!)
(Uie waits in the neutral corner.)
- Uie, stay there. - Go, Kim Uie.
Put your hair in.
- Because it's blocking your view. - Uie!
(The head referee helps her organize her hair.)
(Waiting for the head referee's direction)
(Red Corner is ready.)
You can do it!
(The match resumes.)
(The opponent's big right hook)
(Accurate one-two right on time)
Yes!
Yes.
Nice.
(The opponent's right hook again)
Stop.
(Red Corner is warned for dropping her head.)
(The match resumes.)
Give a jab and punch! Yes!
Yes. Focus on that!
(A series of large hook from the opponent)
(Stop)
(Red Corner is warned for the open blow again.)
Box.
(The match resumes.)
She's approaching. Be careful.
- Back. - Yes.
Yes. Good job. Punch.
Throw a one-two.
Punch! Yes!
(The last slugfest)
Nice.
Yes. Good job.
Feint. Yes.
- Good job. - Really?
(The audience sends applause...)
(to the boxers who did their best.)
Good job, Kim Uie!
Good job, Yun Bo Ra.
(Uie did her best with the one-twos.)
(It's time for the objective judgment.)
Look forward.
(Everyone becomes quiet...)
(and waits for the result.)
(Uie wins.)
Thank you.
(Even the audience finds the joy of victory thrilling.)
(Uie advances to the finals.)
Thank you.
(Uie's sports high school senior)
Good job. Keep it up.
Thank you.
Good job.
- Good job. - Gosh.
(Now, Uie can leave the ring with a smile.)
Good job, but...
I was...
You seemed to be a little nervous...
- Yes. - because it was your first day.
- It was my first preliminary round. - Let's do better tomorrow.
- Okay? - Yes.
- Let's do better tomorrow. - Yes.
(Sighing in relief and joy)
(Stops)
Let's go quickly, so I can root for Sae Rok.
(Let's go quickly, so I can root for Sae Rok.)
Good job.
(With noticeably lighter steps, )
Hey.
(she faces the members.)
Uie, come here.
- You were amazing. - Really?
She's doing great.
(The last player is Sae Rok.)
(Tension sweeps in.)
(She must make her 4 months of effort worthwhile in 3 minutes.)
Keep calm.
(Glancing)
(Kim Yu Jeong, 30s, under 54kg)
(Boxing experience: 5 months)
(She must win to advance to the finals.)
(Sae Rok is calmly setting her mind.)
- Let's go, Keum Sae Rok! - Let's go, Keum Sae Rok!
Oh, Sae Rok.
(She worked hard in the past 4 months.)
- Go, Keum Sae Rok! - Let's go!
(It's time to prove her effort.)
Sae Rok.
A two and a hook, okay?
After the two and hook, what matters the most?
Keep your lead hand forward, so she can't hit you, okay?
This is not a big deal.
(The coach cheers her up until the end.)
(Sae Rok finally enters the ring.)
Mouthguard.
(The head referee checks her gear before the game.)
Keep calm. When Round One begins,
give a feint, and walk and punch.
Punch.
Let's try that.
Number one.
Focus on the hook, okay?
(The opponent also gets her gear checked.)
Keep calm in Round One.
You can do it.
- Let's go, Sae Rok! - Stand here.
- Let's go! - Don't drop your head.
You cannot hit the back of the head.
No holding. No below.
Bow.
To your corners.
Okay. Sae Rok. You can do it.
- Let's go, Keum Sae Rok! - Let's go, Keum Sae Rok!
(Round 1 begins.)
(Round 1, Under 54kg: Keum Sae Rok versus Kim Yu Jeong)
(Sae Rok tries to attack first.)
Yes.
(She throws a one-two-one.)
Yes. Punch. Good.
She can't hit you at all.
Good job. Yes.
- Number 1. - Number 1.
(Sae Rok's accurate straight)
(A series of one-twos)
- You're doing great. - Number two.
- Number two. - You're amazing. Just keep it up.
(Attacking and dodging)
(Due to Sae Rok's long reach, the opponent's attack doesn't work.)
Jab.
- Go. - It's your chance. Yes!
(Dodging the opponent's one-two attack)
Good. Yes.
(Sae Rok's valid strike 1)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 2)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 3)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 4)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 5)
Nice hook.
Keep it up.
She's approaching. Watch carefully.
She's approaching. Fight back.
Fight back. Yes!
Yes. Fight back.
(Sae Rok keeps a distance and continues to gather valid strikes.)
(Sae Rok's straight jab)
(A series of one-two-one)
Yes!
- Circle around. - The lead hand.
(Sae Rok keep her lead hand up, )
(looking for her chance without a break.)
- Punch! - Yes. Good job.
- The lead hand. - Keep calm.
Punch. Try it.
- Block. Yes! - Yes!
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
Yes. Good job.
(The last flurry of one-two)
You're doing great.
That's awesome. Yes!
Stop.
(She makes endless valid strikes to the end.)
(Round 1 ends.)
Good job!
Okay.
It's all about confidence.
(Tallying the points for Round 1)
(What's the result of Round 1?)
(Sae Rok won in Round 1.)
She swept Round One.
Sae Rok!
(Cheering as loud as they can for their proud Sae Rok)
- Sae Rok! - Good job.
You're doing great.
You're punching the opponent every time.
Every one-two you tried worked.
You know what I mean?
If the opponent tries a jab, hit two on that timing.
Do you remember this?
Just focus on that.
Keep up the good work.
Even if the opponent approaches, no need to get worked up.
Just keep up what you were doing.
Okay?
Look. When she reaches,
you block and dodge your head.
Punch as you dodge your head.
Punch as you block with your lead hand.
Fight back as you dodge.
Good job. That was incredible.
Let's make the last round great. Okay?
(Only one round left until the finals.)
(Round 2 begins.)
(Round 2, Under 54kg: Keum Sae Rok versus Kim Yu Jeong)
Dodge and punch. Yes.
(The slugfest begins.)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 1)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 2)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 3)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 4)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 5)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 6)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 7)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 8, The opponent's valid strike 1)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 9, The opponent's valid strike 2)
(Sae Rok's valid strike 10, The opponent's valid strike 2)
- Punch. - Keep it up.
She can't approach you.
- Let's go, Keum Sae Rok! - Let's go!
She's approaching. Punch. Yes!
(Straight right on the face)
(Making one-two using her long reach)
Yes!
(Bombarding with one-two)
(The opponent's two hands hook...)
(versus Sae Rok's endless one-two)
The opponent's face keeps getting lifted.
That's crazy.
One more time.
Yes. Punch. Yes!
(Sae Rok's endless one-two attacks)
You're doing great!
- Yes. - Fight.
Keep your lead hand up.
(The opponent tries a hook.)
There isn't much time left.
(There isn't much time left.)
Dodge and punch. Yes!
(Sae Rok's series of valid strikes)
Good job. Keep it up.
- Yes. - You can do it.
(Jab, jab, straight)
(Sae Rok's one-two versus the opponent's body blow)
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
- Good job, Sae Rok. - Ten seconds!
- Ten seconds! - Yes!
Sae Rok, only ten seconds!
(Sae Rok attacks to the end.)
Stop.
(Round 2 ends.)
- That was crazy, Keum Sae Rok! - That was crazy, Keum Sae Rok!
- Did you do your best? - Yes.
You won.
(Because she did her best, she has no regrets.)
Good job.
(Good job.)
(Only the results remain.)
(Sae Rok had many valid strikes.)
(The opponent threw punches to the end.)
(Everyone waits for the result quietly.)
- We won! - We won!
(Who will get to advance to the finals?)
(Keum Sae Rok wins.)
(Keum Sae Rok advances to the finals.)
(Good job, Keum Sae Rok.)
- Thank you so much. - Keum Sae Rok!
- I learned so much today. - Good job.
- Thank you. - Keum Sae Rok!
- Keum Sae Rok! - You've improved so much.
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
(Good job, Lucky Rocky.)
That was crazy, Keum Sae Rok!
(Iron Girls celebrate from the bottom of their hearts.)
- Keum Sae Rok! - Very nice.
(Sae rok thanks the audience with a bright smile.)
Good job. Sae Rok, you need to cool down right away.
If you don't cool down right now,
then you'll have a muscle ache tomorrow.
So you need to work out right now. Okay?
(The hardcore coach won't give her a chance to rest.)
I'll cool down, Coach.
- Yes, let's work out. - Yes.
- Ready to start? - Yes.
(Sae Rok puts on the gloves again even before catching her breath.)
Jab. One-two.
(A quick cool-down routine)
One-two. Yes. Cut.
Keep your head low.
(While Sae Rok is cooling down...)
You blocked everything with that.
You blocked everything.
And two.
- Sae Rok. - Sae Rok.
Good job.
(Iron Girls gather after the preliminary round.)
- Good job. I knew you could do it. - Uie.
- Good job. - Let's circle around.
(Iron Girls gather after the preliminary round.)
- Good job. - Yes.
I can't believe it.
In Ah won...
by 10 to 8 multiple rounds.
That means the gap was big.
And Uie...
If you meet a player like Uie,
- she's very tricky. - True.
I mean it.
She kept throwing punches that earned points.
It was like a submachine gun.
Hit once, and she would counter three times.
All of them earned her points.
From what I saw, Sae Rok barely got hit.
- Did I see it right? - Sae Rok...
- She barely got it. - Right?
Sae Rok, you were the best.
- Sae Rok... - She only got punched twice or so.
Her punches were hard. The opponent's headgear...
- flew up numerous times. - Totally.
A little more, and Sae Rok would've scored a KO.
- Yes. - She did really well.
Also, Sae Rok, you used your lead hand well.
- Yes, your guard was great. - You defended yourself well.
- Gosh, we're proud of you. - Well done.
Ju Hyun may have lost, but she fought well, right?
- For real. - She lost but fought well.
- It was such a close game that... - Exactly.
It could've gone into overtime.
The back-and-forth made the loss all the more disappointing.
- But Ju Hyun did really well. - You lost but fought well.
- Ju Hyun's match... - Good job.
Was a bittersweet one.
The pressure must have been greater since it was a revenge match.
Even while doing theater, Ju Hyun practiced...
every free minute, and I knew that very well.
You may have lost today, but it was still a great match.
- Stop it. - Congratulations on third place!
She's crying.
What?
- What? The medal? - Oh, gosh.
(Ju Hyun's bronze medal)
Bronze medal?
- It's quite big. - The medal is huge.
- It's the bronze medal. - Wait.
- Bronze medal. Right. - Nice.
I forgot that I won the bronze medal.
You lost but fought really well.
Guys.
(Everyone congratulates Ju Hyun.)
- Well done. - Well done.
- You fought well. - Thank you.
You fought really well.
- This is making me... - Well done.
Emotional.
I did my best. It wasn't easy at all.
Yes, you went all out.
Good job. You did really well.
I'm so proud of you. You really gave it your all.
- You won. - Well done.
Good. Great job.
Here.
Thank you.
(Giving the medal to her mom)
- It's heavy, isn't it? - Yes.
It was really tough.
Great job. You did everything you could.
No need for long words. Just accept it.
Admit it.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
(After thanking her parents)
- Ju Hyun. Ta-da. - Here you go.
- A round of applause for Ju Hyun. - What is it?
It's a certificate.
I can't remember the last time I got one.
Award certificate.
Women's 30s, under 51kg, third place,
team Iron Girls, name Park Ju Hyun.
This certificate is awarded...
to the individual mentioned earlier for placing as stated...
in the 4th Korea Sports Council...
President's Cup National Amateur Boxing Tournament
From Chairman Choi Chan Wook on August 31, 2025.
(4 grueling months of effort)
(The moment of accepting the results)
- You did really well. - Let's hug her.
- You did an amazing job, Ju Hyun. - For four months.
- We're proud of you, Ju Hyun. - Well done.
You gave it your all...
- while doing your play. - Good job.
- Smile. - Thank you for all your effort.
- Smile now. - Well done, Ju Hyun.
- Don't cry. You did really well. - Great work.
I'm sure she's feeling a mix of emotions.
- Stop crying. - Give it to me.
It's been 20 years since I last received a certificate.
- You did really well. - Good job.
Good luck. Give it your all until the very end.
- Well done. - Stay strong until the end.
(The next day)
- Hi. - Hi.
- Here comes the boxers. - Hi.
One day, we'll miss saying hi like this, won't we?
- It's finally the last day. - That's right.
- It's the finals. - Yes.
- It's the finals. - It's the end of a long journey.
- Did you get some sleep? - I slept for seven hours.
(A full 7 hours of sleep)
- Nice. - For real.
I also slept for eight hours.
- I slept for ten hours. - What?
- What? - What?
Isn't too much sleep bad?
- Hold on. - Are you okay?
- I bet her muscles are dead now. - You slept way too much.
- Did you space out? - No, listen.
- What a shocker. - After a big feast,
I kept dozing off...
- and was about to pass out. - You were tired.
Once I went to bed, I slept like a baby.
- Good. - Besides fighting, boxers burn...
- a lot of energy cheering on... - True.
The other fighters.
- It's natural to be tired. - Totally.
What's a bummer is that...
Ju Hyun couldn't make it to the finals.
But the other three members did.
Either way, the Iron Girls are one team.
- Yes. - Yes.
Let's aim for winning all three gold medals and prepare well.
- Please. - Right?
This will be my last boxing match of my life.
Really?
I'm going to give it everything today.
I plan to burn this afterwards too.
Today will be my final time in the ring.
- Stop it. - That's why...
I'll give my very best and step down from the ring.
- Good. - I love that kind of determination.
- Same. - What she just showed means...
she's going all out and leaving no regrets.
- I'd like to say a few words. - Go ahead.
Thinking, "I'll do my best today."
"I'll pour my heart and soul into it," is great,
since today's the last match.
But don't get carried away because of it.
- Yes. - You know what I mean, right?
The moment you get hyped in the ring,
- your punches go wide... - True.
- and your guard drops. - Right.
That makes it harder to beat your opponent.
- Stay calm. - Always stay calm, got it?
- Yes. - Great. It's the last match.
- Let's go. - Give it your all in the ring.
- Okay. - Let's go warm up.
- Come on. - Let's go.
(All our moments of fierce fighting make us champions.)
(For the grand finals, )
(many people have gathered.)
(It's a big day for everyone.)
(The boxers are getting ready by warming up.)
(The Iron Girls are warming up for the last time.)
(Breathing out)
If I stop doing footwork, it's over.
That's it.
The world of competition is ruthless.
Let's give everything I've prepared...
over the past four months in that ring.
- I've got nothing to be afraid of. - Yes.
I've grown strong,
and I believe I can grow even stronger.
I want to say proudly that it was truly intense.
(The women's finals begin.)
(The Iron Girls head to the stands.)
- Good luck! - Good luck!
(Auntie Sae Rok)
(As the matches progress, )
(they become more nervous.)
(They try to calm themselves down.)
(The tension from the finals is hard to shake off.)
I'm so nervous.
There's no need to be nervous.
Just do it like you did.
Your opponent is just as nervous as you. Think about it.
- They're extremely nervous too. - True.
This is a battle of who can stay calmer.
- Got it? - Yes.
(In Ah feels more nervous...)
(as she's the first member to fight in the finals.)
Is it her?
The one wearing "Kyungbuk."
The boxer in front of the guy in the black top.
Most likely.
We should get ready.
Shall we head downstairs?
- Good luck. - Relax.
- Put your mind to it. - Coach.
Just keep doing what you've been doing, okay?
- Relax. - Good luck.
(In Ah heads to the finals first.)
Forget everything else. Just do as much as you did yesterday.
All you need to do is give it your all.
It's already happening.
- True. - Right?
You can't turn back time.
Just relax and step out of the ring after sparring.
- Got it? - Okay.
(The other members are as nervous as In Ah.)
Is she here?
Warm up your body here. Good.
(In Ah has entered the stadium.)
(While the earlier matches are still going on, )
(In Ah watches them as she warms up.)
(Meanwhile, her opponent is getting ready for the match.)
(Park Yu Gyeom, 20s, under 54kg)
(Boxing experience: 3 years)
(10 wins in 10 matches)
(An undefeated, skilled fighter)
(A tough fight is expected.)
Let's do well.
Just do what I practiced.
Why don't you warm up?
(She warms up to relax.)
Light one-twos. Punch. That's it.
One, two, dodge, punch, and hook.
(Practicing her one, two, dodge, punch, and hook combination)
Yes, and pull back.
After you punch, bring your guard back up.
Do that, and you won't get hit.
Keep it up, and you'll get plenty of chances.
(The match immediately ahead has begun.)
(In Ah heads over to the glove room.)
(The final challenge to become a champion)
Breathe.
(Catching her breath)
(Preparing to pour out all the effort of the last 4 months)
Your opponent is nervous too.
She has arms and legs, just like you.
- She's just another human being. - Okay.
There's no need to be intimidated.
She's not some alien, right?
Step into the ring and execute all your strategies.
(Stay strong and stick to what you know.)
(You can do it, Seol In Ah.)
Hit me in the forehead.
- Let's go. - Pull yourself together.
Okay.
(Time to bring the long journey to a close)
Good luck, Seol In Ah.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Good luck.
(Partly worried)
(In Ah is starting today's team finals.)
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(The other members cheer her on more than ever.)
(In Ah responds brightly to their support.)
Good.
(She has given her best in every moment.)
No matter the outcome, stay calm. Okay?
Give her some water.
(Let's fight calmly, in my style.)
The outcome doesn't matter. It's like a sparring session,
just like the ones we've done so far.
For real.
You've done well up until now, okay?
(In Ah has done well up until now.)
Come up.
Seol In Ah!
- Good luck! - Good luck!
Let's go!
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(Park Yu Gyeom)
(The finals are fierce, even in the cheering section.)
- After a feint, - Park Yu Gyeom!
- jab at her abs, - Park Yu Gyeom!
Then go low and high, okay?
- Relax. - Good luck, Seol In Ah.
- I'll have fun. - Good luck, Seol In Ah.
- Good, relax. - Good luck.
- Be careful of your heads. - Yes, sir.
Don't grab your opponent or hit below the belt.
Touch gloves.
- Good luck. - Thank you.
- I'm in your care. - Corners.
Go all out in the ring. Got it?
(3 minutes to pour out the results of the last 4 months)
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Good luck.
(Round 1 begins.)
(Round 1, Under 54kg: Seol In Ah versus Park Yu Gyeom)
(The opponent lands a valid strike first.)
(A strong punch that made In Ah's head turn)
(In Ah counters immediately.)
(The opponent corners her, targeting both low and high.)
(In Ah pivots and escapes.)
(In Ah lands a powerful right hook.)
KO. That was almost a knockout.
(Cross-counter)
- Turn. - Turn.
Turn and punch.
Feint.
- Punch. - Feint and turn.
Punch. That's it.
(The opponent's left hook lands perfectly.)
(Walking in with a left hook)
That's it. Just like that.
(In Ah's full-power hook)
(The opponent staggers.)
(But she counters immediately with a hook.)
(A back-and-forth one-two combination)
(After dodging the opponent's hook, )
(In Ah goes for a hook.)
(In Ah's jab follows a right hook.)
(The opponent throws both hand hooks.)
(And a body shot.)
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
Pivot. Well done.
(Pivoting as she lands a punch)
That's it. Good.
Turn.
Yes, pivot.
- Stop. - Okay, stop.
(Round 1 ends.)
- Well done. - Really?
Well done.
My lips are busted.
Are you okay?
(In Ah's mouth got busted from the opponent's strong punch.)
Good job.
(The opponent has used quite a bit of her stamina.)
(While catching her breath and pulling herself together, )
(the stadium is buzzing with excitement.)
(Park Yu Gyeom)
(Even the cheering battle is neck to neck.)
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(We can't lose.)
(The stadium is heating up.)
(In Ah versus Yu Gyeom)
(The results of Round 1 are revealed.)
(In Ah versus the opponent)
- We lost Round One. - She's good.
- We lost Round 1, 9 to 10. - Seol In Ah!
The opponent is incredible.
(It's not an easy match.)
- From what I see, - You're right.
In Ah needs to land perfect jabs.
There's no need to throw hooks at the same time.
All the opponent does is throw hooks.
- Exactly. - Hooks are fine,
but she should be landing jabs and then back out.
(In Ah should focus on jabs.)
Go slower.
Everything's good, even your footwork.
After a feint, snap a punch to her face right away.
Dodge and punch twice.
Just dodge and punch twice, got it?
Can you do that?
You understand, right?
All she does is move in.
What good are hooks if you can't reach her?
After two jabs and a right hook, use your left hand.
Make better use of your left hand.
(Round 2 strategy: Follow the jabs with consecutive hooks)
(Second out.)
Connect it with a hook.
Dodge immediately, okay?
(It's the final round.)
Dodge to the side.
(The last 1 minute and 30 seconds will decide the winner.)
(Round 2 begins.)
(Round 2, Under 54kg: Seol In Ah versus Park Yu Gyeom)
(In Ah's valid strike: 1)
(In Ah's valid strike: 2, The opponent's valid strike: 1)
(In Ah's valid strike: 3, The opponent's valid strike: 2)
(In Ah's valid strike: 4, The opponent's valid strike: 3)
(In Ah's valid strike: 5, The opponent's valid strike: 4)
- Counterattack. - Counter!
Turn.
(In Ah makes a big turn around the ring.)
(The two boxers wait for the right timing.)
(The referee signals them to attack.)
(After dodging, )
(In Ah lands a one-two immediately.)
Pivot.
(It turns into a full-on slugfest.)
- Turn. That's it. - Turn.
- Turn. Pivot. - Turn.
Here she comes.
Cross-counter.
- Cross-counter it. - Dodge.
She's tired. Attack.
That's it. She's drained.
(The jab landed perfectly.)
- It's the last match, In Ah! - It's the last match!
It's the last one.
That's it. Good. Well done.
(Another powerful jab)
(The strong blow snaps the opponent's head around)
- Yes, for real. - One more time.
- One more. Jab. - Jab.
Just jab.
- Jab, In Ah. - Jab.
Here she comes. Well done. Try again.
She's going to attack. Counterattack.
- Both boxers are exhausted. - In Ah.
Counterattack.
(Both landed hooks simultaneously.)
Again.
(And a straight jab.)
- That's it. Again. - More.
- Try it again. - She's coming.
- She's tired. - Yes.
(Tired, her guard is down.)
Stop.
(Round 2 ends.)
Thank you.
Well done.
Round Two is over.
- Good job. - Well done.
Great work.
(In Ah came back after giving it her all.)
You did really well.
In Ah won Round Two.
(The crowd is still excited.)
It's a close match.
She won Round Two.
- Yes, she did. - Now...
- Round One... - It's a battle of small punches.
In Ah lost Round One by a narrow margin.
She still has the potential to win.
- Seol In Ah! - Seol In Ah!
(Voices united with desperation, )
(everyone anxiously waits for the decision.)
(But the opponent's team is just as desperate.)
(Amidst the excitement, both boxers return to the center.)
(Both fighters gave it their all, putting on the best match possible.)
(Who is the winner of this match?)
(At that moment, the white sign is held up.)
(Head referee)
It's a tie.
(The white sign indicates a tie.)
(Since In Ah won Round 2, the scores are now tied.)
(They return to their corners for a re-evaluation.)
(The stadium is filled with tension once again.)
(Everyone patiently waits for the re-evaluation.)
It's a tie. Hold on.
Can there be a tie?
In Ah lost Round One,
- while she won Round Two. - Right.
That turned into a tie.
What happens now?
(If the white sign indicating a tie is held up, )
(the 3 judges decide the winner through a re-vote.)
(The re-vote proceeds rapidly.)
(Returning to the center of the ring for the result announcement)
- Great job. - Thank you.
(The two fought fiercely until the very end.)
(Heavy hooks thrown from the start)
(The opponent took the upper hand in Round 1.)
(Did the opponent win with her unmatched skills?)
Since In Ah landed many punches in Round Two,
she looks set to win.
Please.
(With relentless attacks...)
(and precise, valid jabs, )
(In Ah dominated Round 2.)
(Did In Ah win by taking the momentum in Round 2?)
- Please, I beg you. - Please.
(As time passes, everyone grows more desperate.)
(Who is the winner?)
- Please, I beg you. - Please.
(As time passes, everyone grows more desperate.)
(Who is the winner?)
(Seol In Ah wins.)
(2 judges voted for In Ah.)
(Seol In Ah wins the national tournament.)
- Great work. - Thank you.
(After enduring the long and tough months, )
(In Ah has reached the top.)
You fought well.
We won.
(The Iron Girls celebrate together.)
Yes, this is only fair.
(And so do their families.)
Gold medal, Seol In Ah of the Iron Girls.
(Gold medal: Seol In Ah of the Iron Girls)
Congratulations.
Unbelievable.
(4 months of blood, sweat, and tears led to this moment.)
Silver medal, Park Yu Gyeom of the Kyungbuk Gym.
(The opponent fought fiercely until the end.)
- Thank you. Great work. - Thank you. Great work.
(Today's match was fierce and thrilling.)
Well done.
- Good job. - In Ah!
(Seol In Ah of the Iron Girls is now a boxing champion.)
Let's go. Well done.
You did really well.
We won.
It's the result of my hard work.
- I felt really proud of myself... - Let's go.
And happy.
(Today's result feels even more priceless and satisfying.)
- Thank you. - Oh, my gosh.
- A gold medal. - Yes.
(Kim Min Jung, In Ah's first tournament preliminary opponent)
- Congratulations. - Great work.
My baby.
- Congratulations. Really. - Congratulations.
Well done, In Ah. You did an amazing job.
- Good luck. - Congratulations.
You were awesome.
Keum Sae Rok, I love you.
(The first champion of today's tournament)
- I love you, In Ah. Great work. - Good luck.
- Do everything you want to do. - Go on upstairs.
(The tournament hasn't ended yet.)
(Uie is about to fight her last match.)
Relax. Warm up your body. Shake.
(Uie tries to relax by warming up.)
Let's do ten one-twos.
One, two, three, four.
(Focusing in fighter-mode)
Don't forget about your lead hand, okay?
Okay, good.
(All preparations are complete.)
(The match right before Uie's begins.)
(Uie enters the glove room.)
Breathe.
(The headgear she's worn countless times)
- How is it? All good? - Yes.
(Tightening her gloves one more time)
Two, one, two, backstep, one, two.
Keep your lead hand up. Don't forget about your lead hand.
Nice.
(Who will Uie face in the finals?)
(Shin Han Geul, 30s, under 51kg)
(Boxing experience: 1 year and 6 months)
(Amidst a strange tension)
Well done. You've done really well until now.
Just do your best in the ring.
- Okay? - Okay.
Winning or losing doesn't matter.
Getting this far is already a job well done, Uie. Got it?
(Let's give it my all and step down without regrets.)
(The opponent, fully warmed up, )
(heads to the ring to cheers from the crowd.)
(Uie sets off, her eyes full of determination.)
- Kim Uie! - Kim Uie!
(They start to cheer at full volume.)
(The final hurdle before claiming the gold medal)
(Uie sets forth.)
(The other members cheer loudly for a nervous Uie.)
All right. Take a deep breath.
(Heading to the ring after a deep breath)
Let's go.
- Uie! - Uie!
- Uie! - Mouthguard.
- Thank you. - Kim Yu Jin!
Uie, relax.
- For real. It's okay. - Okay.
Take it easy.
(Time to unleash everything she's trained for)
(Finals, Under 51kg: Uie versus Shin Han Geul)
Watch your heads and low blows.
No clinching. Fight fair.
- Corner. - Good luck.
Look at the height difference.
Let's gain points.
Fight as you've been doing.
(Round 1 begins.)
(Round 1, Under 51kg: Uie versus versus Shin Han Geul)
- Uie! - Uie!
- Go! - Uie!
(Uie's one-two preemptive attack)
(The opponent counterattacks immediately.)
That's it!
(The opponent's powerful punch that made Uie's head turn)
(The opponent stays low...)
(and attacks deeply.)
She's a tough opponent with a UFC-style approach.
Go for it.
Move in.
Attack. Again.
Well done. Yes, that's it, Uie.
(A jab when the opponent moves in)
(An attack utilizing her long reach)
Turn. Nice one.
(Uie punches without a break.)
- Good. - The opponent is struggling.
"Her reach is long, and the punches just keep coming."
She's flustered.
Hurry up and move in.
Move around. She's going to attack. Wait for it.
That's it.
Punch.
(Uie's endless one-twos)
(The opponent's jab targets openings.)
(A wide hook follows.)
- One, two, three, four, five, six, - Yes.
- seven, eight, nine, ten. - Turn.
- That's it. One-two. - Nice.
- Turn. - Use your waist.
One-two after a feint.
Land a one-two, Uie. Attack her first.
(They continue keeping each other in check.)
Number one.
Yes.
(Uie's valid strike 1)
(Uie's valid strike 2)
(Uie's valid strike 3)
(Uie's valid strike 4, The opponent's valid strike 1)
(Uie's valid strike 5, The opponent's valid strike 2)
(Uie's valid strike 6, The opponent's valid strike 2)
- Number one. - That's it. Turn.
- Turn. - Yes.
Turn. Well done. Again.
- Another one-two. - Number one.
Number one.
- Okay. Uie won Round One. - Stop!
(Round 1 ends.)
(Uie is on a roll.)
- Nice, Uie. - Uie won Round One.
She's earned crazy points.
- For real. It was 1, 2, 3, 4, - 3, 4,
- 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. - 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
To think she'd earn points like that.
- What? How come? - What?
(The results of Round 1 are revealed.)
(Blue Corner wins Round 1.)
- Shin Han Geul! - What?
- But why? - Uie lost?
- Shin Han Geul! - We lost Round One?
(Taken aback by the shocking result)
Why?
Didn't she land four times as many hits?
Her punches must have been...
too weak to score points.
The judges were looking for more damaging strikes.
(The opponent's hits were more powerful than Uie's.)
Well done. You did well.
- Let's attack her with jabs. - Okay.
Jab is the answer. After some feints,
back out after a good punch. Just jabs, okay?
The opponent throws hooks when she moves in, right?
- Yes. - Be careful of those.
After you punch, you immediately back out.
- Turn after your punch. - Okay.
Either turn and punch or turn and pivot out.
- Got it? - Yes.
Attack her with jabs.
You were amazing.
- You're the best. Well done. - After a right hook,
jump forward.
You need to punch again.
Add some head movement.
- You're doing well. - I agree.
- This is the last round. Got it? - Yes.
(Round 2 begins.)
(Round 2, Under 51kg: Uie versus Shin Han Geul)
- Uie! - Uie!
That's it.
(The opponent throws a right hook, )
(followed by a jab.)
That's it!
(Uie counterattacks with a one-two combination.)
Wait for it.
- That's it. - Lower your body.
There you go. Lower your body and get up afterward.
- Go in! - Now!
(A slugfest begins.)
(Uie's one-two...)
(versus the opponent's hooks)
(Uie wraps up with a jab.)
(The opponent ducks and throws a hook.)
Try it again.
Uie, try it again.
Now is your chance.
Get in there.
- Get in there. There's no time. - Get in there.
(The opponent sends a flurry.)
(The opponent's right hook)
(The opponent's right hooks 2)
(Then comes a jab.)
Get in there.
There you go.
(The opponent throws a right hook again.)
(Uie continues to attempt the one-two.)
She shouldn't rest.
- She needs to be more aggressive. - Keep going!
Keep going!
Come on!
Uie, don't rest!
Try it again. There you go.
- Keep going. That's right. - Again. There you go.
- Good. - Good.
Keep going.
Don't rest. There you go.
- There you go. Try again. - There you go.
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
Get in there.
(Uie's jab)
- Again. Try it again. - There you go.
(Uie keeps throwing jabs.)
There you go. Again.
(Round 2 ends.)
Well done.
- Well done. - I did my absolute best.
You did well.
(Uie gave the match her all until the very end.)
(She ends the last match without any regrets.)
- She didn't do badly. - But Round Two...
Let's shout, "Uie, let's go!" Set, go.
- Uie, let's go! - Uie, let's go!
(She goes to the center of the ring for the results.)
Thank you for your hard work.
(They exchange greetings of respect.)
(It's time for the results.)
(The opponent moved in and threw hooks without hesitation.)
(Will the opponent win for her heavy punches?)
(Uie used her long reach to throw one-twos nonstop.)
(Will Uie win for her endless one-twos?)
(What will be the result of Uie's last match?)
(Blue Corner wins.)
(Uie loses.)
Thank you for your hard work.
(She shares a passionate hug with the opponent.)
Well done.
(Despite the loss, )
(Uie smiles brightly since she has overcome her fear.)
It's okay.
Kim Yu Jin, well done!
(You did very well.)
To be honest, I thought to myself, "What if I have regrets?"
(Silver medal)
(Silver medal: Uie of the Iron Girls)
But my heart felt so light that I didn't have any regrets.
I'm very happy.
(I'm very happy.)
(Meanwhile, )
(Sae Rok is the last boxer of the finals.)
Don't get nervous. Why would you get nervous?
You boxed yesterday too.
Don't get intimidated. Why would you get intimidated?
(The finals are more nerve-racking than the preliminaries.)
(The opponent has the boxing experience of 2 years.)
(Sae Rok takes deep breaths due to nervousness.)
It's okay.
You can do it.
It's nothing.
(She steels her heart before the final match.)
- It's Sae Rok's turn. - It's Sae Rok.
I hope Sae Rok wins.
Sae Rok, let's win gold.
(Iron Girls' last match is even more nerve-racking.)
Let's enjoy it without any regrets.
No one can beat the person who enjoys herself.
That's right.
(With each step, )
(she goes to the ring for the final match.)
(Sae Rok, good luck!)
I love you.
(She walks past Uie.)
(Keum Sae Rok is up.)
Do your best, okay?
Hold on.
(Keum Sae Rok enters the ring.)
(She calms her mind one last time.)
Sae Rok, please do well.
This is precious.
(Nervous)
Touch gloves.
(Iron Girls' last match)
Good luck. Stay calm.
(It's time to put an end to the 4-month journey.)
(Finals, Under 51kg: Keum Sae Rok versus Anonymous)
(Round 1 begins.)
Box!
(The opponent attacks first with hooks.)
Circle around.
(Sae Rok circles around right away.)
- Circle around. - Go in there.
Good. There you go.
There you go. Circle around. There you go.
(Sae Rok's straight)
(The opponent's right hook)
(The opponent closes the distance in an aggressive way.)
(Sae Rok keeps her lead hand forward and looks for the right timing.)
(The opponent's valid strike: 1)
(The opponent's valid strike: 2, 3)
(Sae Rok's jab)
That's right.
(The opponent's hook)
One more time.
Mind the left side.
Slow down.
(Sae Rok's flurry of one-twos...)
(versus the opponent's right hook)
Stop.
(Listen to the stop signal!)
- Blue Corner, don't lock arms! - Keum Sae Rok!
(Blue Corner gets a warning for locking arms.)
Box.
(The match resumes.)
- Go first. - There you go.
(Sae Rok's straight)
(The opponent's right hook)
(The opponent throws a flurry of right hooks.)
(Sae Rok circles around.)
There you go.
Take it to the end.
Go. Circle around.
Stop.
Don't push.
Don't pull.
(They get a warning for pushing and pulling the arms.)
Box.
(The match resumes.)
Stop.
(Round 1 ends.)
She's aggressive, right?
It's okay. Sit down.
Sit down. All right.
I think she fell behind a bit in Round One.
A little bit.
There wasn't a big difference.
(Round 1 was fierce.)
(What will be the results?)
Sae Rok fell behind in Round 1 with the score of 10 to 9.
I hope she hits the opponent more.
I hope she stretches out her hands more for jabs and hooks.
- The punches she throws land. - I know.
She just needs to throw jabs.
All of your punches are landing.
Both your lead hand and rear hand are coming into contact.
Attack first.
You can attack first.
Be careful when the opponent does this.
Cross-counter or go, two, one, two. Okay?
What should you do when the opponent follows you?
Pivot and attack.
Pivot and attack right away. Remember that.
Okay? Breathe.
Seconds out.
She needs to throw many punches.
If she wins this round,
the judges will have a re-vote. So, she needs many good punches.
She shouldn't save them in this round.
She needs to attack a lot.
You're doing well. This is the last round.
All right.
(It's the last chance to pour in 4 months of effort.)
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Keum Sae Rok, let's go! - Keum Sae Rok, let's go!
(Iron Girls' final round)
(Our last 1 minute and 30 seconds)
- Let's go. - Sae Rok, let's go.
(Round 2 begins.)
Box.
(Round 2, Under 54kg: Keum Sae Rok versus Anonymous)
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 1, 2)
There you go. That's it.
(A strong straight punch)
(A slugfest begins.)
(The opponent follows her persistently.)
Pivot.
(Sae Rok pivots quickly.)
- Pivot and attack. - Good!
Pivot and attack.
There you go. Pivot and attack right away.
There you go.
- That's it. There you go. - That's it!
(The opponent's right hook, Sae Rok's straight)
(Sae Rok's left hook follows.)
(She follows it up with the one-two.)
(One, two)
(Dodging)
That was amazing. Well done.
- Sae Rok, you can do it! - The opponent is exhausted.
- The opponent is exhausted. - Sae Rok, go in there!
She needs to get in there.
- Punch! There you go. - Yes.
There you go. Throw the one-two.
There you go. Pivot.
Pivot and attack.
Do it again.
(The opponent attempts a hook.)
There you go. Go in there.
(Sae Rok gets past the guard and makes a valid strike.)
Get in there!
(The opponent strikes back with a hook.)
(The opponent's left hook)
It's the last round. That's right. Go in there.
Go in there. The opponent is exhausted.
(Sae Rok's jab gets past the guard.)
- Go in there. - Stop.
(Blue corner gets another warning for locking arms.)
Box.
(The match resumes.)
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
There you go! That's right!
There you go! That's good!
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 1)
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 2)
(Sae Rok's valid strikes: 3)
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 4)
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 5)
(Sae Rok's valid strike: 6)
(The opponent's valid strike: 1)
That's good. Do it again. There you go.
There you go. That's good.
Well done.
She'll win this round.
- She'll win this round for sure. - She'll win this round.
You can't say that she lost.
Sae Rok, well done.
You used up your energy. Well done.
Well done.
(Sae Rok used up her energy for the last match.)
It was the best you've done.
You did an amazing job.
- I have no regrets. - You have no regrets. Let's go.
(After a match that left no regrets, it's time for the judgment.)
I think Sae Rok will win.
Please.
(The moment of the last judgment)
Sae Rok has to be the winner.
- Round Two was amazing. - That's right.
(Sae Rok attacked more aggressively in Round 2.)
(What will be the result?)
(The white sign indicates a tie.)
It's a tie.
- It's a tie. - Good.
(Sae Rok wins Round 2.)
It's a tie.
Sae Rok had more valid strikes.
Please.
Please judge fairly.
- Please. - Please.
(The re-vote makes people hold their breath.)
Please.
Sae Rok threw more punches in Round Two.
Many more punches.
She has a chance of winning.
(The opponent showed heavy hooks.)
(Sae Rok pressed her with a flurry.)
Please.
(What will be the result of the fierce match?)
- Red. - Red.
- Red! - Red!
(Keum Sae Rok wins.)
(The members are happier than anyone.)
(Keum Sae Rok wins the national competition.)
Nice.
That's right.
She won all the points in Round Two.
(We're proud of you, Keum Sae Rok.)
- Well done. You worked hard. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - You worked hard.
(After a fierce match, Sae Rok took the victory.)
(Staggering)
Please come forward.
Gold medal, Keum Sae Rok of Iron Girls.
(Iron Girls' last boxing champion is born.)
She fought very well.
My voice is hoarse.
Sae Rok won gold like the meaning of her last name.
(Keum Sae Rok became Gold Sae Rok.)
Seriously, you fought well.
(She shares her happiness with her coach.)
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
You won in the end.
(Sae Rok leaves the ring with a light heart.)
- Keum Sae Rok! - Go down slowly.
(The family members cheer happily as well.)
I love you guys.
(Now that the burden is gone, she shows a big smile.)
I was so happy...
that I had a gold medal around my neck.
I felt proud. I was like, "Is this right?"
(4 months ago, 2 minutes in the ring seemed to last so long.)
(Sae Rok was the weakest member of Iron Girls.)
(However, with tenacious effort, )
(she pushed hard until the end without giving up.)
(Sae Rok became the champion.)
(I did it!)
Keum Sae Rok!
(They have a tearful reunion after everything is over.)
You did well. You did really well.
(They know how hard Sae Rok has practiced.)
You did well.
You did really well.
You turned the tables in Round Two.
- You came from behind and won. - You came from behind and won.
Sae Rok won gold like the meaning of her last name.
I got my last name.
I'm Gold Sae Rok, not Silver Sae Rok.
Everyone did a great job. Seriously.
Everyone was the best.
(Iron Girls poured out their energy without regrets.)
I poured out my everything.
I did my absolute best.
Seriously. You did well.
I'm sad that it has ended, but everyone did well.
Seriously.
(The challenge was beautiful since they did their best.)
I'm on the verge of tears.
Cry, In Ah.
It's okay to cry today.
We did it.
(The two of them won a gold medal in the end.)
You did really well.
- You did too. - You were incredible.
- The punches were well-timed. - You know,
the Best Boxer in the 20s Award went to...
- In Ah. - Really?
Really?
(Was In Ah named the best boxer?)
- Hey. - She deserves it.
- She deserves it. - We heard news that In Ah won...
the Best Boxer in the 20s Award.
- She deserves it. - That's right.
(She bursts into tears.)
Cry.
(She overcame injuries and achieved a beautiful result.)
We heard news that In Ah won the Best Boxer in the 20s Award.
- She deserves it. - That's right.
Of course. It was the best match.
- Go and receive the award. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - There goes In Ah.
Here comes the best boxer in the 20s.
The best boxer in the 20s.
(Congratulations.)
Here comes the best boxer in the 20s.
She trained for four months.
(For the past 4 months, )
(she used all her might to test her limits.)
(She experienced the hardship of an injury.)
(But In Ah got back up...)
(and won the Best Boxer Award.)
In Ah, let's go!
(That's why this moment makes her even more emotional.)
You won the Best Boxer Award too.
- Please come this way. - Congratulations.
(It's time to go on the podium.)
My goodness.
(In Ah goes on the podium.)
This is incredible.
(You're cool, Seol In Ah!)
There's a certificate too.
The Best Boxer Award for the women in the 20s division...
under 54kg.
The winner is Seol In Ah of Iron Girls.
(Amateur Boxing Championships, The best boxer, Seol In Ah)
- Shake hands. - Thank you.
Guys!
This is insane.
- How should I hold it? Like this? - We're proud of you.
Shouldn't this be on the news?
Please put it on the news.
She's cool.
- She's incredible. - I'll take a photo.
She's incredible.
- Is number one in the frame? - Yes, it is.
(Today's achievement is even more precious.)
You're the best.
One, two, three.
- Don't cry. - This platform is...
- Let's do this. - Shall we do that?
I can't believe I'm here with you guys.
Everyone worked so hard.
One, two, three.
We're done.
(The final tournament ends.)
Here comes the champion.
It's over for real.
All right. Well done, everyone.
- The results are the best. - We're done.
Let's go over today's results.
Two gold medals.
One silver medal. One bronze medal.
We have gold, silver, and bronze medals.
We have all three.
(They won precious medals after the 4-month journey.)
And Sae Rok's nickname used to be Silver Sae Rok.
- It became Gold Sae Rok. - That's right.
She got her last name back.
- Sae Rok. - Dad!
I got my last name back!
(Congratulations.)
Also... Seriously, I didn't expect this.
- The best boxer in the 20s... - The Best Boxer Award.
Is Seol In Ah.
I've become the Lion King.
(Simba Seol became the Lion King.)
Seriously.
To be honest, I wondered at times...
if the coach was training the members too hard.
But he achieved these results.
Our coach played a big role.
Wear my medal.
(They give their medals to the coach.)
To the coach.
He'll pull his neck muscles.
- He'll pull his neck muscles. - Here.
I'll hold it for now.
(He's moved.)
When I first received the offer to be on the show,
I got hung up on the results.
Because of that,
I used a strong tone with you guys, so it must have been tough.
(But he watched them do their best right by their side.)
Steel yourself and box without any pressure, okay?
(He realized that the process was more valuable than the outcome.)
I realized that the process was more important.
It really was an honor to work with you guys for four months.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It was an honor for us too.
I remember a moment from the beginning of the season.
Was it when you sparred against a middle schooler?
I thought, "It'll be hard."
You turned away when you took a punch.
I was so certain that it'd take more than a month or two.
You took many punches.
(To an expert, Iron Girls' challenge seemed impossible.)
I thought, "It'll be hard." I thought it was impossible.
(But Iron Girls achieved their goals through an insane amount of effort.)
I was so impressed.
Watching you made me look back upon myself.
Again, I was very moved.
- Captain Kim kept our minds strong. - That's right.
- Thank you so much. - He rooted for us every day.
- He gave us physical training. - That's right.
A round of applause for the captain and coach!
(A round of applause for the captain and coach!)
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you so much.
When I think about it,
all four of you have a gold medal each.
- That's right. - That's right.
(Seoul Boxing Association President's Cup Boxing Tournament)
(Women in the 30s division under 54kg 1st place, Uie)
(Korea Sports Council President's Cup Boxing Tournament)
(Women in the 30s division under 54kg 1st place, Keum Sae Rok)
(Seoul Boxing Association President's Cup Boxing Tournament)
(Women in the 30s division under 51kg 1st place, Park Ju Hyun)
(Korea Sports Council President's Cup Boxing Tournament)
(Women in the 20s division under 54kg 1st place, Seol In Ah)
Everyone became a champion.
Congratulations.
(All Iron Girls became a boxing champion.)
(Looking back on the past 4 months)
Well...
Iron Girls was...
very difficult for me.
My physical strength was very lacking.
Although I had tried all sorts of sports,
my physical strength was very lacking...
compared to that of the members.
"When I enter the tournament,"
"I won't be able to do anything in Round Two."
(Knowing what she lacked, she trained harder.)
(She analyzed and studied the boxing techniques endlessly.)
(Compared to 4 months ago, )
(her physical strength improved dramatically.)
My opponent got exhausted,
but I held out until the end.
I truly have no regrets.
I was sincere.
I was truly passionate.
Entering the ring was enough to scare me.
My heart beat so fast.
I kept retching.
(Uie became more nervous than the other members.)
I mean,
what if I came down the ring...
without the chance to do anything I've practiced?
That thought scared me the most.
(She stood out as the ace in terms of stamina.)
No matter how much I punched the mitts...
and had the supervised sparring with the coach,
I didn't seem to get better. It made me upset.
(Uie became small when it came to boxing.)
(However, she got back up again.)
(Uie dedicated herself to training.)
I did my best.
(I did my best.)
Had I thought, "I should've tried a bit harder,"
I would've cried on the spot.
But my heart felt so light that I didn't have any regrets.
(Uie showed the biggest smile on the ring.)
I'm very happy.
(I'm very happy that I had a match I didn't regret.)
I'm not ashamed of how I've trained in the past four months.
The first and the biggest wall...
was the fear of hitting and getting hit.
Being someone who rarely gets scared...
or nervous,
I thought, "Doing this won't be a problem."
But when I watched the members box...
before my eyes,
I was shocked.
(Watching people box made her scared of boxing.)
Tears fell down my face.
(Fear came before excitement.)
But there was no way around it.
I just had to do it.
(Despite her busy schedule, she improved her stamina.)
I kept trying to overcome...
the fear inside me.
(Ju Hyun entered the ring countless times.)
I think the process played a part...
in making me stronger and more level-headed.
I never thought that I'd achieve something like that.
It's a big change.
I think it was a good experience.
(She achieved an unimaginable growth in the past 4 months.)
(And...)
I had never thought...
of stopping due to an injury.
(She became exhausted on the ring and sustained an injury.)
It was the hardest.
I had practiced with all my might,
so needing to stop...
because an injury was very...
(The injury was hard to accept since she had worked very hard.)
When I thought about the members, production crew,
coach, captain, and family members...
who were worried about me,
I wondered if I was being too stubborn. But in the end...
(July 31, Thursday: I want to box. August 1, Friday: I want to box.)
Even when I was taking time off due to an injury,
I really wanted to box.
It's so much fun.
It's so much fun. Seriously.
(She enjoyed boxing more than anyone.)
It's fun to watch myself grow.
It's fun to try again after doing something badly.
(In Ah was the happiest when she boxed.)
The entire process is fun.
That was why I made an effort to recover quickly.
(In Ah trained passionately since she liked boxing very much.)
In the end, I returned...
and entered the ring.
(In the end, she entered the ring again.)
It made me very happy.
The sense of accomplishment is so big.
Being on Iron Girls always makes me realize...
how I can lead a fun life...
and set up a happy routine.
(A sense of accomplishment and joy followed after she overcame all.)
My expectations and imagination...
weren't as great as the ending I had today.
(Iron Girls overcame the time of fear through sweat.)
(Uie, Keum Sae Rok, Park Ju Hyun, Seol In Ah)
(There were big and small injuries, )
(but the four of them overcame all and entered the ring.)
(What's the takeaway for Iron Girls?)
I'm really proud of myself.
I was very scared,
but I pulled through until the very end.
I like myself very much.
The impactful lesson was,
"I can do anything I set my mind to."
(I can do anything I set my mind to.)
I was so moved when I realized...
that hard work actually paid off.
Unbelievable!
I used to think, "There's no way I can win a medal."
But it actually happened.
I gained so much confidence. I can do it too.
I can do it without getting scared.
The one who challenges herself to do what she likes...
and puts in the effort is invincible.
For four months,
I dedicated myself fully to the boxing training.
I want to thank...
everyone who has sparred with me for my sake.
Just as we were serious about boxing,
our opponents...
competed with all their might.
I thought it was very cool.
For 2 rounds of 1 minute and 30 seconds each,
we fought to the best of our abilities...
and wrapped up with a smile.
I think that's the charm of boxing.
(The charm of boxing)
The more I learned about boxing,
the more I realized, "I need to focus on myself."
Seriously, every sport is a fight against oneself.
"Who your opponent is doesn't change a thing."
"You just need to do your own thing."
Overcoming yourself is more important...
than the outcome.
I think...
I've won the fight against myself.
I couldn't have done this by myself.
The days I trained alone were the absolute worst.
A group of 3 was more fun than a group of 2.
A group of four made me happier and more passionate...
than a group of three.
My teammates always told me that I was the best.
I received a lot of love, so it was nice.
- I love you. - I love you.
- We can do it. - I love you.
(Iron Girls finished yet another race...)
(together.)
- Iron... - Iron...
- Girls! - Girls!
(Cheering you on in your fight)