[Begin Again]
♫ I love you ♫
[Episode 13]
Just a sec, I'll be right down.
Okay.
You are still here?
I'm waiting for you.
We finished early today, let's go for a ride.
Don't worry.
Leave tomorrow's matters for tomorrow, okay?
They've all gone.
The sky won't fall.
Alright, where shall we go?
You'll know soon.
♫ Together we'll chase into the sky ♫
♫ With love, it guides us soar and fly ♫
♫ In your loving embrace ♫
♫ I find my place ♫
♫ Pure and free ♫
♫ Together we will ♫
♫ Write our symphony ♫
♫ With every breath ♫
♫ I'm enchanted by you ♫
♫ Wrapped in your arms ♫
♫ In this magic room ♫
♫ Just you and me ♫
♫ I'm under the spell ♫
♫ I am bound by your love ♫
♫ Every step is intertwined ♫
♫ Everything feel is right ♫
♫ All I need is you ♫
♫ My only missing piece ♫
♫ Nowhere to hide ♫
♫ Together we'll chase into the sky ♫
♫ With love, it guides us soar and fly ♫
♫ In your loving embrace ♫
♫ I find my place ♫
♫ Pure and free ♫
♫ Together we will ♫
♫ Write our symphony ♫
♫ With every breath ♫
♫ I'm enchanted by you ♫
♫ Wrapped in your arms ♫
♫ In this magic room ♫
♫ Just you and me ♫
Let's go.
What about mine?
- Do you need it?
- Why not?
Why don't you give it to me?
I thought you might say,
"I have to work tomorrow,
maybe I shouldn't drink now."
You said that.
Get relaxed today and the sky won't fall.
Leave tomorrow's matters for tomorrow.
Nice.
Wait.
If I drink, how will I ride my motorcycle?
Leave tomorrow's matters for tomorrow.
Let's walk back, I'll take you home.
Be careful.
Didn't we come to the lighthouse last time?
- Hide here.
- Why?
Here.
What?
Do you want to go up
this lighthouse and take a look?
Can we go up there?
Just avoid the security,
then it's okay.
I don't think it's appropriate.
What if we get caught?
If you get caught, you'll be fine.
What if I get deported?
I've already looked into it.
They patrol only once every three hours.
So after he leaves now,
we won't run into him again.
And I used to do this when I was a kid.
At worst, we'll get a warning.
You won't get deported. Don't worry.
Are we going? Let's go. Okay.
Go in.
Can we really come up here?
No, I snuck you up here.
Hurry up.
I cover you from behind.
Let me carry your bag.
No need.
Should we go further inside?
Be careful.
I'll just take a look.
Be careful. What are you doing?
I just take a look. Come here.
Why should I come over?
I'm afraid of heights.
Okay, don't come over.
You asked me to come over
and then tell me not to move.
- Stop moving.
- Help!
Forget it, I'm scared. Help!
It's alright, just take a look.
It's very beautiful.
Ming.
Don't shout.
We have a reservation.
He knows we are coming up.
You lied to me.
This is fun.
Haven't you always said you wanted
to see the night view of Macau?
I've thought it over. And I think this might be
the best spot.
Indeed, it's very nice. What a view.
♫ Eyes ♫
♫ Every passing car ♫
♫ Each face becomes familiar ♫
Look, such a big and round moon.
♫ You tore it out of me ♫
It's beautiful.
♫ A heart full of unbelief ♫
♫ A part that others rarely see ♫
♫ She suffered enough ♫
♫ Knowing that I won't walk away ♫
♫ If you could tell ♫
Thank you.
♫ I can see life in these hands that I held ♫
♫ Time ♫
♫ Illuminating the day ♫
♫ Every passing glance won't feel the same ♫
♫ Light's dancing off you now ♫
♫ Just to be someone ♫
♫ You teach yourself avoid the sun ♫
♫ Conclusions made we're on the run ♫
♫ She suffered enough ♫
♫ Knowing that I won't walk away ♫
♫ If you could tell ♫
♫ I could feel life in these hands
that I held ♫
Let's go.
- So soon?
- Let's go down.
We've just come up.
Going back.
Why?
[GALAXY ARENA]
Thanks.
♫ I'm moving ♫
Okay.
♫ My own brand ♫
♫ A new reality ♫
♫ Where I'm free from all illusions ♫
♫ Then comes the ambiguity ♫
♫ Every day ♫
♫ Cavalry ♫
♫ Taking your breath away ♫
♫ And if you can't find me ♫
Welcome, please go in.
- Hi.
- Junhao, you've finally arrived.
Then let's go over first.
Elvis.
Mr. Qi, long time no see.
Have you played golf recently?
You look in great spirits.
I've played quite a bit.
Charles says you're quite confident
about this race.
Yes, due to some mistake
last year, I missed out on the championship.
But this year, I'm very confident
to reclaim the championship that belongs to me.
I just like
your confidence.
Thank you, Mr. Qi.
Right, I almost forgot
to introduce you.
This is Josephine, Chen Jiahui, my girlfriend.
This is Mr. Qi,
the President of DEVE's Asia-Pacific region.
I've long admired you, hello, Mr. Qi.
Hello, welcome.
You!
We've been working together
for such a long time.
Having such a beautiful girlfriend,
yet you only introduce her to us now?
It is improper.
Yes, it's quite improper.
Mr. Qi, thank you for
always supporting Elvis.
Actually, I saw DEVE's biannual exhibition
in Paris before.
I really like your work.
You understand jewelry?
Of course, good jewelry
can bring energy to people.
Who wouldn't like it?
Your girlfriend is much more charming than you.
Of course, my life is quite boring.
Unlike Josephine.
Mr. Qi has always been
very forward-thinking.
Regarding this time's lover series jewelry,
I believe we could
have more ways to collaborate.
Mr. Qi, there is a phone call.
- I'll take a call.
- Please, go ahead.
I really think it works this time.
Bro, trust me.
Let's just…
Let things take their natural course, okay?
- I'll go talk.
- About the endorsement…
I'll go greet people, you two chat.
Hello, thank you.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
I noticed today
you're not quite the same as usual.
Well, how do I put it?
Very humble.
Don't you get used to
such a humble me?
No.
I think
that you racers are quite hardworking.
Not only do you acquire skills,
but also work hard to pull in sponsorships.
You've worked hard.
Racing, it's
a game of capital.
Without sponsorship,
it's very difficult for a team to operate.
We had to do this.
Elvis.
Go ahead, I'll wait for you here.
- Go ahead.
- Just a moment.
Excuse me, Miss.
Are you Elvis's girlfriend?
Yes, and you are?
I'm Doumoto.
I am also a racer, just like Elvis.
- Nice to meet you.
So, are you here in Macau
to accompany him for racing?
No, I live here.
So you guys met in here?
Yes.
You probably don't know him
that well, I assume.
Almost two weeks.
- Two weeks?
- Yes.
Two weeks.
Interesting.
That makes sense.
I don't quite understand what you're saying.
They just said
DEVE is about to promote
the lover series jewelry.
If Elvis just starts dating recently,
it would indeed help
to enhance his public image.
Elvis is not that kind of person.
You've only known him for two weeks.
How well do you know about him?
You must have missed when his manager
made a point to talk to Mr. Qi
about the new series.
Just a
friendly reminder.
I hate to see you become a victim.
That's all.
Thanks for reminding me.
Please mind your own business.
It's okay. I think the competition…
- Jiahui.
- Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Right, Mr. Qi just mentioned
I shouldn't be photographed with a model
for the lovers series jewelry.
It should be the two of us.
Yes.
You two have a very good vibe.
Only a real couple
can show such a natural love.
- Isn't it?
- Of course.
I'm very willing to.
But I need to respect
my girlfriend.
After all, she's not a public figure.
So I think she has
the final decision.
Such a professional matter,
I think it should be left to
the professionals.
Don't rush.
After his race,
let's discuss it then, okay?
Right. Races come first.
- Of course.
- Focus on the race first.
You'd chat, I'm leaving.
Goodbye. Come on. I'll see you out.
There's hope this time.
Well done, Jiahui.
Wait, that's enough, right?
My task is done, okay?
Okay.
Let me take you to the marketing department
to meet people.
Just five minutes.
- Okay? Come on.
- Okay.
Wait, what?
Go meet the marketing department guys. Come on.
- Then wait for me.
- Go ahead.
Come on, let's go.
Haven't we all met already?
Hello, Elvis.
Can I take a photo with you?
- Okay, come on.
- Thank you.
Here.
Done.
I'll take one for you.
Thank you.
You want a photo too? Okay, just a moment.
- What you said is no problem
- Investor.
- Thank you.
Come here, Elvis.
Let me introduce you to this person here.
Where is Jiahui?
Where's Jiahui?
- She went out.
- Just went out.
Why?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I'm leaving.
You keep socializing.
Hope you can successfully
secure the endorsement.
The race is about to start.
- Let's not meet again.
- Take care, sir.
Focus on your race.
I might have been
unable to control myself just now.
I hope it won't bother you.
It's fine, let's go.
Wait.
I have something
to tell you.
Because once you leave Macau,
I don't know when
I will have the chance to see you again.
But I don't want to leave any regrets.
Stop it.
It's late. Let's go back to rest.
Wait, why do you reject me?
I just want to talk.
I don't require a definite answer or anything.
I think you should feel
that I really like you.
And I can also feel from your responses
that you feel the same.
So,
I think we can…
But so what?
It's not going to work.
Right now, I can foresee
our end.
What is there to talk about?
Aren't we just talking now?
We haven't even started,
why must you condemn it to death?
Then what are you worried about?
Long distance?
Can't see each other?
More than this.
What else?
I'm here on a business trip.
Once my project is finished
and the proposal is complete,
I'll leave, I'll have to go back.
I never expected
I would meet someone here,
I might like someone,
I might…
I might start a relationship.
All of these are
out of my plan and my imagination.
If we start
just like you said, and then?
We'll return to our busy
and complicated lives.
We can't meet for a long time.
We'll keep in touch by phone.
And every day, we'll just say
"Good morning. Good night. I miss you."
And then?
Then those love feelings
will all be gone.
In the end, we
won't even be friends.
I can understand your worries.
But what if I tell you
that none of what you just said will happen?
I can go to your place.
What about Zhen Qiang?
Abandon it?
I'm talking about us.
We are no longer
of the age to do as we please.
Our lives now are about more than love,
we also have many responsibilities.
We have families, we have jobs,
and we have our own lives.
I can't possibly ask you
to completely give up
everything you have in Macau
for our relationship.
Why do you think so extreme?
I'll go to you, it doesn't mean
that I won't come back to Macau.
Isn't love between two people simply
about mutual tolerance and acceptance?
Can you just live in the present?
Can you put aside your worries?
You don't need to consider how I feel.
Nor should you think about the future
whether it's good or bad.
Don't worry about my family.
Just ask yourself.
Even if you tell me
that you don't like me at all, I can accept it.
I just want you
to ask yourself
what you feel
and what life you most want
right now.
Let's just be friends.
We can't.
♫ Using all my strength ♫
♫ Still, there's no response ♫
♫ The city is strange and cold ♫
♫ I'm used to ♫
♫ Every day's routine ♫
♫ Day by day ♫
♫ Spinning as usual ♫
♫ Occasionally there will be cracks ♫
♫ A bit of unease and fear will show ♫
♫ Yet afraid to be seen ♫
♫ I'm also used to ♫
♫ Hide all the emotions ♫
What time is it? There's not a soul around.
There. Look.
- Where?
- Right there. Don't you see?
- There?
- Just kidding.
♫ Stay by my side and don't go away ♫
♫ In this city ♫
♫ There's a light that's turned on for me ♫
♫ It's okay, don't be afraid ♫
♫ You have to believe ♫
♫ You have lived well enough ♫
♫ Even if I'm a bit nervous ♫
♫ Tears ♫
♫ Can't hide the stubbornness in your eyes ♫
♫ I can understand the way you are ♫
♫ I believe in you ♫
♫ You are already strong enough ♫
♫ Even if stumbling all the way ♫
I really like you.
♫ You must live as your own self ♫
♫ Don't be afraid ♫
♫ Every time you think of giving up ♫
[Chen Jiahui]
♫ Don't want to lose it ♫
♫ I'm no longer ♫
♫ Using the casual tone ♫
♫ Pretending to be brave ♫
♫ I also hope someone would come close ♫
♫ Stay by my side and don't go away ♫
♫ In this city ♫
♫ There's a light that's turned on for me ♫
♫ It's okay, don't be afraid ♫
♫ Don't be afraid ♫
Why are you here?
Just got off work.
Every time I see you, it's at night.
Thanks to the fate.
What about you? Where have you just been?
Dressed so smart.
Just finished socializing.
Can you racers do something serious?
It was the sponsor's social event, bro.
I know.
What about the race?
How's the preparation going?
It's alright, okay.
Doesn't sound okay, bro.
What about that girl you mentioned?
Forget it.
What about you?
Any news?
She's back.
That's good.
But I got rejected.
She thought
long-distance love
won't work out.
[I want to say]
[I hope you]
What is love exactly?
I'll drink one.
Don't.
You have to race.
It's okay, just one can.
Your coach will blame me.
He couldn't find you anyway.
Two men trapped by love.
- Here.
- Just a bit, it's okay.
Don't worry.
Love.
I once heard a story
about love.
One day, Plato asked Socrates,
"Master.
What is love?"
Socrates told him,
"You walk into a wheat field,
then you pick a wheat ear out,
and you must not look back."
Plato went, but after just a short while,
he came back empty-handed.
Plato said,
"Master,
I got to the wheat field
and I found a very beautiful
and full wheat ear.
But I did not pick it.
Because I thought
I would find a better one.
As I kept walking,
and went almost the end,
I found that on my way,
every single ear I came across
was not as good as the first one.
So I came back empty-handed."
Bro.
You just got rejected.
Never give up.
- Never give up.
Come on.
- Be careful.
- Be careful ahead.
Be careful.
No problem.
- Miss Mai, your coffee.
- Okay, thank you.
Here, this one.
Take them to the Director and others.
Okay.
Right.
Have the external partners arrived?
I just saw Fish.
It seems that Mr. Le didn't come.
Okay, got it. Go busy yourself. Thank you.
Okay.
- Here, Mr. Qiang.
- Ask her later.
- Coffee.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
- Thank you. Put it here.
Okay.
Good morning, Miss Mai.
Good morning, Fish.
Today we have ample time for shooting.
We can take our time. There's no need to rush.
- Great, thank you for communicating.
- I should.
Right.
Is Le not coming today?
Right, I forgot to tell you.
Tomorrow, we are going to shoot
the restaurant.
We need to
shoot the dishes at that restaurant
within ten minutes after they being served.
After ten minutes, they'll remove the dishes.
Ten minutes? How are we supposed to do so?
That chef is worried about
if we don't shoot the dishes
in ten minutes,
the dishes wouldn't look good
after ten minutes.
So I had Le go communicate with them.
Okay, I see. Thanks.
Okay.
Pour me a glass of water, please.
Meng.
Right.
- Don't move. Raise your hands.
- How do my legs look?
Take a video for me.
- A video, okay.
- Right.
I'll walk over from this side.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
- Can you help us take a group photo?
- Sure.
Okay, thank you.
- Is it okay?
- Take a look.
It's pretty.
Want us to take one for you?
My husband is very good at taking photos.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
Meng, where have you gone?
Why didn't you tell me?
I-I was looking for that razor.
I can't find it.
Why did you put away the razor?
My shirt…
Where did you put it?
I-I can only see your shoes now.
Where have my shoes gone?
Why? Why can I only see your shoes?
Where are my shoes?
Why do you always have to put my things away?
Y-You put them away so quickly.
You should tell me.
[Xu Jianming]
What's the code for my suitcase?
I remember it is…
It's your birthday, right?
How can't I open it? D-Did you change it?
Is it here?
[Lily Garden]
Mom.
You're finally back.
Who is this boy?
His name is Frank.
He is my client.
He can only understand Mandarin.
Hello, Frank.
Come in.
Here, change into slippers here.
Sit here.
I thought you gave me
a grandson.
Come on.
Your dad hasn't come back yet,
let's wait for him.
Frank, what do you like to eat?
Biscuits?
He's allergic to wheat bran,
can't eat biscuits.
Then have some fruit.
Here.
Wait.
Go wash your hands.
It's very dirty outside, lots of bacteria.
Where is grandma?
She's in the room.
Grandma.
Grandma, what are you doing?
Winter is coming.
I need to knit a sweater for Ming.
He's afraid of cold.
But grandpa has already…
Grandma.
I'm back.
Who are you?
Why are you here in my room?
♪ Moonlight so bright ♪
♪ Shining on the ground ♪
♪ Tong, go to bed ♪
♪ Tomorrow your mom
is going to plant seedlings ♪
♪ And your grandpa
will take the cattle up the hill ♪
♪ Moonlight so bright ♪
♪ Shining on the ground ♪
♪ Tong, go to bed ♪
♪ Tomorrow your mom
is going to plant seedlings ♪
♪ And your grandpa
will take the cattle up the hill ♪
Grandma.
I am Tong.
Tong?
You're talking nonsense.
Tong isn't this old,
and doesn't have hair this long.
Don't lie to me.
♫ The sun creeps in, it catches ♫
♫ The leaves quietly and wakes the treetops ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ The wonderfulness without any sign ♫
♫ I listen to the breeze
with the tune of the sea ♫
♫ I'm about to embrace the unknown ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ Nothing is predictable ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫