[Begin Again]
Hello, Shaohui.
Why is there
so little information on Chloe Liu?
Nothing else?
You can take a look
what events she would attend.
You can…
Parent-child sports day?
Send me the information. Thanks.
Want to have some chocolate?
Hello, Howard. I'm Casey.
Chloe Liu will participate in
a parent-child sports day next.
I plan to go take a look.
It's a good chance to meet her.
Get a child?
I'll arrange it.
I can do it.
- What?
- Take me with you.
Where to?
Parent-child sports day.
You must be joking.
Is there anyone more suitable than me?
Tell me the time.
[Episode 11]
Over there. Jianming.
Dad, Ms. Meng.
Jiajia, you have grown up into a pretty lady.
You're becoming more beautiful.
Ms. Meng, you haven't changed a bit.
I saw you once you came out.
Dad, where is mom?
Didn't you arrive together?
Look at you.
Running all over the world after graduation.
It's been a long time not seeing me.
Now you see me,
yet you don't even ask how I am.
No need.
Your face is radiant
and your stature is tall and straight.
I can tell
Ms. Meng must have taken good care of you.
You are good at fooling me.
Jiajia.
Mom.
I've missed you so much.
Alright.
Don't keep your dad and aunt waiting.
- Let's go over there.
- I'll get it.
Let's go.
Where's your boyfriend?
He is still working.
Besides, we haven't seen each other
for such a long time.
I want to spend more time with you guys.
Right, Mom?
Yes, it's Hao, right?
If he is here,
how do I have some private talk with Jiajia?
- Let's go.
- Go.
Thank you.
Hello, these two. Thank you.
Wait. There are four of us,
and you've ordered two cars?
I was afraid that there wouldn't
be enough space for all your luggage.
This is not appropriate.
You're too extravagant.
Jianming, let Jiajia accompany her mom.
You go after her.
Let's take one car. Come on.
You guys get on the car.
Let's go.
- See you then, Jiajia.
- Okay.
Look, I led my first trip
to Mont Blanc last month.
- Various landforms.
- Oh my.
It's so attractive.
Nice.
If you want to go, I'll go with you.
How about I give you a discount?
Sure.
Then you should settle
the money for raising you first, okay?
You're quite a slick talker now.
So usually,
you've been travelling around,
how do you find time to date a boyfriend?
Finally?
You must be holding it in so hard.
Hurry up and tell me. Don't change the subject.
You told me he's
in hotel management.
And you are a tour guide.
How did you two start
dating?
Is he handsome?
Show me some photo.
What for?
You'll see him in person.
- Be careful.
- Thank you.
Could you please help us with the luggage?
- Dad, Ms. Meng.
- Okay.
I've got you the room keys.
Dad's.
- Mom's.
- Good.
You guys go upstairs and rest for a bit.
See you at the restaurant.
Then I'll go upstairs.
See you later.
Dad, you should go rest too.
You go in first. Go in and wait for me.
What's wrong, Dad?
You've got a tan.
This is fashionable now. It looks good.
It looks good.
Healthy, right?
- If you need anything, go to me.
- Okay.
You…
You are living well, right?
No, Dad. You go upstairs and rest.
You go keep Ms. Meng company.
- See you tonight.
- Okay, 6:30 PM.
6:30 PM.
Hurry up.
That's impressive.
You're watching racing?
Why are you suddenly so interested in racing?
Not really.
I've recently met a handsome guy.
He's a race car engineer.
I thought to know more about his interests.
Then, we would share the same interests.
You
are going on dates again?
Who is it?
The last time we went to the bar…
The time we danced?
Yes, that time.
After that, we've had meals
together a few times.
But I think he's not the kind
of flirty guy.
I think
he's quite special.
So this time, keep your eyes wide open
and be discerning.
Got it?
I will. Don't worry.
The Europeans are good at racing.
So much faster.
Who said it?
It's just because car racing is
a sport that started in Europe.
And over the years,
they already have a very mature method
to train racers.
And they have professional teams.
Chinese racing is
just a late starter.
It doesn't mean we aren't fast enough.
And I think the Chinese racers,
whether in terms of talent,
or the effort put in,
are in no way inferior to them,
and working even harder than them.
It's just a matter of time.
Sooner or later, we will surpass them.
Are you okay?
I just said,
"The Europeans are good at racing."
I get it.
You're nervous about Elvis.
- Who is Elvis?
- Are you?
That racer Elvis.
Han Junhao?
- What's wrong?
- He's dating Joe.
No way.
My client Han Junhao is dating Joe.
How could I not know? That's crazy.
It's true, Casey.
You've been so busy lately,
so you have no time to care about us.
It's true.
- They are dating.
- Wait, wait.
Joe, is what she said true?
More than true,
she's too cute.
I just said,
"The Europeans are good at racing."
And Joe had a big reaction.
- I was just stating a fact.
- So was I.
What's up? Looking for me?
I think, wait, I want…
Let me digest this first.
What's the situation here?
You are dating Han Junhao.
No, don't listen to her.
She said you're in love.
You know her.
She's such a drama queen.
That's true. She is.
Right. What's the matter?
I'm here because…
- You are.
- Stop it.
I'm here because
- the company is organizing an auction.
- Okay.
We're talking about business here.
- Chloe Liu will be coming to Macau to organize
- Forget it.
a charity art exhibition
- related to children's autism.
- Cool.
And the company wants to collaborate with her,
so I'm here to discuss with you
on how to promote this. Do you have time?
Yes.
- Let's go inside and talk.
- Sure.
Where are you guys going? Wait for me.
No gossiping during working hours.
Then we'll talk after work.
[Macau Grand Prix]
Ryan.
Charles, long time no see.
- You guys came quite early.
- Right.
Elvis.
- Hello.
- What's up, bro?
- Hey, bro.
Uno and the others said
Elvis has been on the upswing lately.
How is it?
- Any chance to win against Doumoto this time?
- Definitely.
Let me tell you,
just wait and watch the good show.
Elvis will definitely nail it.
You too. Do your best.
Don't let that kid win.
Look at him.
- He's even filming a documentary.
- Great race.
Being so high profile.
Young guy.
Having some achievements,
it's only right to be showy.
Nice to see you, man.
I hope you'll get a good position
at the qualifying draw.
Otherwise,
you'll never catch up with me.
You are so confident.
Of course, my opponents
usually are confident.
And I'm happy to give them some hope.
After the race is over,
I'll then give them despair.
Everyone, please take your seats.
- Go for it.
- The sign-in starts now.
Racers' meeting is about to begin.
This spot.
This spot on the turn back is crucial.
- Okay, come on.
- Come on.
Justin.
- Go back first.
- Okay, got it.
What's wrong?
About what Doumoto said just now,
did you take it to heart?
I just ignore him.
- I'm going.
- See you on the track.
- Cheer up.
I'm off.
Okay, then I'm relieved.
That's it for today. Rest well.
I have a meeting with Jeremy.
- I'll go ahead then.
- Then I'm leaving.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Where do you go when you're in a bad mood?
[Chen Jiahui]
I'll take you there.
Sure, see you later.
When you usually clear your mind,
you'd come here?
Scared?
I came into here on my walk.
It's very quiet here, very poetic.
It's wonderful to pass by
these little monuments.
It allows me to momentarily
detach from the reality.
And every time I see the inscriptions
on these monuments,
I would feel
like I'm reading
a miniature novel.
I would think about
what these people did in life,
and what kind of lives they went through.
When they were in Macau,
which places they had been to.
And I would wonder
who wrote these loving inscriptions
for them.
Every time I feel upset, I would come here.
If you stand at the end of life,
looking back in life,
you might
let go many things
you can't figure out.
All the monuments here
date back to the 19th century.
Two months six days.
So he only
existed in this world
two months and six days.
He was a little baby.
When I first saw him, I was feeling sad
just like you.
I can't help worrying about him.
He's so small, so soft,
lying here all alone.
Must be feeling scared.
So every time I come here,
I'd stand here for a while
to talk to him.
Let's go.
George Chinnery.
You know this person?
He had a great impact on Chinese oil painting.
He is also one of the descendants
who brought oil painting to China.
Really?
Compared to Giuseppe Castiglione's paintings.
Because Giuseppe Castiglione
focused on depicting noble life,
but his paintings
are all of ordinary people among the masses.
All from
the ordinary life,
very touching.
Because of him,
the customs and culture of the coastal areas
of 19th-century China
could be recorded.
He kept a record of this land
until he died.
What do you think
was the reason
he stayed in Macau?
Maybe
he felt a sense of belonging here.
There were ties that bound him
or people he couldn't bear to leave.
So, what's
the story behind it?
It must be a very beautiful love story.
After staying here for a little while,
I've really calmed down.
As you slowly walk around here, you'll realize
that those things we long for
don't seem that important anymore.
Everyone is born to die.
So when we are alive,
let's enjoy and be unrestrained,
considering our lives to be
a huge amusement park.
Don't expect us to be perfect
at everything we do.
After all, life is all about experience.
Sometimes, just
look down to watch the ants moving house,
or look up at
the birds flying across the sky.
And feel the moment, that's enough.
After reading this,
if she had only suspected
that Mrs. Xun's death in her previous life
was related to her husband…
Meng.
Can you lower the volume
of your phone?
Sorry for disturbing you.
Why are you listening to this now?
Just for fun.
I find it quite interesting.
Stop what you're doing for now.
We're going out to eat later tonight.
Take your time to pack when we get back.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You're going out to eat dressed in
this?
What's wrong? Do you think it's not suitable?
It's just
a little plain.
Then I'll change into something else.
How quickly time passes.
Last time I saw Jiajia,
she was just a junior in college.
Now she's bringing her boyfriend
to meet the parents.
I even brought a gift for Jiajia.
When do you think
is the right time to give it to her?
Hello, okay. I'll come down right away.
She just got a boyfriend.
Don't take it that seriously.
What happens in the future is still uncertain.
Alright, Jiajia is here.
I'm going down first, you hurry up.
I'm not ready yet, just wait for me.
- Jiajia.
- Mom.
I'll do it myself, thank you.
Did you rest well?
Very well.
Over there, Dad, Ms. Meng.
This way.
How should we sit?
Mom, sit here.
Dad, Ms. Meng.
Well, Jiajia.
Sit between me and your mom.
Hao will sit here. He'll be here soon.
He…
We've come all the way from Beijing.
He didn't come to pick us up at the airport,
and he's being late for dinner.
No, Dad.
He took leave to pick you up,
but something came up at the last minute
and he really couldn't come.
He's probably still busy right now,
should be arriving soon.
He will be here soon.
Xu, are you in such a hurry?
Now that we're here,
we can wait a bit longer.
Then, waitress, bring me the menu.
I'll order some dishes first.
Mr. Xu has already
ordered the dishes for today.
If needed, we can serve the dishes at any time.
- Mr. Xu?
- Hao.
Then what did he order?
- What did he order? Let me take a look.
- This is the menu.
- I won't disturb you anymore.
- Dad is still the same,
acting like a scholar.
Being meticulous in everything.
He's been this way since his youth.
So boring.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
Really sorry, Aunt.
Xu Junhao.
Just call me Hao.
Hao.
Jiajia, you didn't tell me
your mom is so young and beautiful.
I thought you were sisters.
Nice, Hao. You are really a sweet talker.
This is Jiajia's dad.
Hello, uncle. I'm Hao.
This is Jiajia's aunt.
Hello, hello.
Uncle, I'm truly very sorry
for being late today.
I've been working the whole day today,
and really couldn't come.
I sincerely apologize to you. I'm sorry.
Xu, is the menu that funny?
Greet him.
- Waitress.
- Waitress, come on.
Uncle, nice to meet you.
Tired of standing? Have a seat.
Take a seat.
Well, your surname is Xu, right?
- Yes.
- Then I'll call you Xu.
That's fine.
What do you do for work?
Actually, I am in charge of
this hotel management.
For entertainment, public relations,
or any aspect, I'm in charge.
Your Mandarin is quite good.
Thank you.
How many people in your household?
How many people are there in your family?
Well, apart from my parents,
I am the eldest son,
and I have a younger brother,
who has just entered society
and has started working.
And I have a sister
who just started sixth grade.
What do your parents do?
When my parents were young,
they started a restaurant.
And they have been running it for decades.
Now in Macau, it is somewhat
renowned.
Are you still living with your parents now?
Uncle, don't be kidding.
I have moved out a long time ago.
I rented a house.
That means
you still don't have your own house.
If getting married, I would buy a house.
Wherever Jiajia likes to live,
that's where I will buy.
That easy?
You are young, yet not modest at all.
Uncle, I am not that young anymore.
I am already thirty-seven.
Actually, I know
that many people say
that marriage is not about money,
just being in love is enough.
But I know
that Jiajia is your precious one.
If she is with me,
she should not suffer.
Anyone can say sweet words.
But it may not be the case
when it comes to the real thing.
Xu, you are here in Macau
to check on his family background?
- No, no.
- Hao, don't take it to heart.
Jiajia's dad
is always like this,
having been
a teacher all his life.
He's quite
serious.
No, not serious at all.
If I had such a beautiful
and outstanding daughter
like Jiajia,
I would ask the same.
It's quite normal, right?
- A senior manager…
- No.
- really knows the techniques in talking.
- Not at all.
Dad, it's been so long.
Today, let's just have a meal.
Let's serve the dishes.
Come on, let's eat.
- Waitress, serve the dishes.
- Alright.
Hurry up.
This is our hotel's specialty dish,
Yuan Yang mixed rice.
Please enjoy.
- Yuan Yang mixed rice.
- Right.
Eat up.
Uncle, are you feeling unwell?
The weather in Macau
really isn't like Beijing.
Too humid, right?
If you need a dehumidifier
or aromatherapy, or you don't like the pillow,
you can tell me.
No. I'm from Shanghai,
so I'm pretty used to it.
Don't overthink it.
We are here
to come see you,
and also visit Macau.
Macau is really nice for travel.
Actually, Macau has a lot
of sightseeing spots and scenery
that you can explore.
Like Macau Tower.
The Macau Tower is great.
It's romantic to go there at night.
You can overlook
the entire night view of Macau,
which I really like.
- And the world-famous bungee jump.
- What?
Bungee jump.
Jumping from height, Mom.
I've seen it on the internet.
I want to go.
I-I can arrange it.
Let's go together.
I really can't do this with you.
I can't do bungee jumping either.
Once I stand in that height,
I want to find a place to hold on to.
I always feel like I'm going to fall.
I can't go.
Indeed, the view is just so-so.
Actually, there are many other
beautiful places in Macau.
Do you like desserts?
How about the egg tarts?
Let's eat first.
The dishes are getting cold.
Right, let's eat first.
Hao ordered these
specialty dishes.
Please try.
Since we have so many dishes
perfect with drinks,
let's have a drink.
Don't.
Okay.
Uncle, what kind of alcohol
do you like to drink?
We have all kinds of foreign liquors here.
Whiskey, brandy, cocktails,
and liquor as well.
What do you like to drink?
Xu, don't be anxious.
We've just arrived in Macau today.
I want to go out for a walk later this evening.
Maybe another day.
Hao, so you are
a local born and bred in Macau.
Yes, I am
But during high school,
- I went to America.
- Just like you.
After finishing university,
I worked a few years and then came back.
You've had quite rich experiences.
Jianming, don't just talk, have some food.
Actually, Xu
is not that talkative.
Seeing you, he's really talkative now.
Meng, you eat some.
Don't just look after Xu.
- Dad, try that Wagyu beef.
- Right.
Hao knows you like Wagyu beef,
so specially chose this restaurant.
Eat while it's warm, uncle.
It's A5 Wagyu beef, you'll definitely like it.
Authentic.
Thank you, daughter.
It has Wagyu beef that dad loves to eat,
mom is not that important.
- How could that be?
- Aunt.
Jiajia told me
you like eating Cantonese cuisine,
especially sweet and sour pork.
This is made with black-haired pigs.
Try it.
Hao, you are nice.
You've thought everything through.
This chef's cooking is impressive.
Right? I particularly appreciate this chef too.
Our group recruited him back from Guangzhou,
just thinking
to alter the style
of the dining experience.
His color adjustment
and the seasoning are precise.
Then I'm relieved. If you like it,
we'll have this chef for the wedding.
Wedding?
What did you just say?
The wedding between me and Jiajia.
It's next Wednesday.
Got it.
Eat up, it's getting cold.
[Chen Shiyu]
Ms. Wei, the proposal for Tianqin Entertainment
has been sent to your email.
Okay, I'll take a look.
[Proposal for Tianqin Entertainment]
[Chen Shiyu]
[The Art of Game Theory:
Life Is Full of Art of Game]
- Hello, Ms. Wei.
- Has the new guest candidate
settled yet?
Of course.
But it seems they are being discussing.
Professor Xu.
Which Professor Xu?
I think his name is Xu Jian…
What was it?
Xu Jianming?
Yes, that's Xu Jianming.
Ms. Wei, you know him?
Kind of an acquaintance.
Okay, leave this to me.
You don't have to worry about it.
Right,
are you adapting well in Macau?
I'm doing quite well.
Okay.
Then enjoy your vacation.
If you need anything, just contact me.
- Good night.
- Okay, thank you.
Wait, let me tell you. I really can't get it.
How old is he?
Then how old is Jiajia?
Then why did she fall for this old folk?
Give me the coat.
You were fine during the meal.
What's wrong with you now?
At dinner, didn't you see?
He talked so sweet.
What a slick talker.
I really don't understand it.
He must have fed Jiajia
some sort of love potion.
They haven't known each other long,
and they're already preparing for the wedding.
If she really marries him,
then Jiajia will be doomed.
Okay, take your medicine first.
What?
Jiajia is not a child anymore.
She must have picked this guy for a reason.
She's your daughter. Don't you know her?
During dinner tonight,
the two of them seemed to get along well.
As the saying goes,
children have their own blessings.
If you get anxious and upset,
might just get your blood pressure raised.
Okay.
She's not your daughter.
It's easy for you to say so.
[Xu Jianming]
Are you there?
I'll come over for a chat?
- Where are you going?
- Me?
I'm going to find Tang Wei.
I need her to be on my side.
She's her mom, right?
She can't be irresponsible.
If you're tired, go to bed early.
- Another one, please.
- Right away, sir.
- Sir, your drink.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
- A glass of lemonade, please.
Alright.
Don't you have a drink?
Let's talk business first.
About Jiajia getting married,
did you know in advance?
Wait, why are you looking at me…?
Do you think I knew all along,
and deliberately kept it from you?
Jiajia has been with you since we divorced.
Whatever happens,
it's always been just the two of you
discussing.
I don't believe
she didn't give you the slightest hint
for getting married.
Jiajia is also your daughter.
Don't you know her?
Right.
She'd talk to me
about those trivial things.
But when it comes to choose a major,
decide on a school,
and the job to take on after graduation,
she would only tell us
after figuring it all out on her own
and making up her mind. Right?
Maybe you should ask her more often,
and care more about her.
As a mom, maybe you should know
what she's busy with
and whether she's dating or not.
Don't just work all day.
Of course, Jiajia wouldn't dare to bother you.
Professor Xu, I am not here
to argue with you.
My daughter suddenly said to get married,
I was also very surprised.
And my concern
is no less than yours.
I-I'm not trying
to blame you.
Jiajia wants to have a lightning marriage.
As parents,
we are completely in the dark.
We know nothing about
who the man is
and how his family is.
Are we just going to…
Are you okay with it?
Just marry our daughter off like that?
I always feel
Jiajia has grown up.
She has her own opinions
and her own thoughts.
If she has already determined to get married,
that means she has already thought it through.
The child is not our accessory,
nor is she your student.
So, don't impose your prejudices
upon her
and doubt Jiajia's judgment.
So, what should we do now?
She has already made an appointment with me.
Tomorrow, I will have a good chat with her.
If there is any result,
I will tell you.
So I wasn't in again.
Wait.
See the way you talked
to her boyfriend tonight,
and that sarcastic tone.
How could she dare to invite you
to talk with her?
When you see her,
you must criticize her right away.
Professor Xu, you calm down.
Hold back your desire to control.
Don't say
anything unpleasant
to the child.
You make it very difficult for her.
Tang Wei.
Jiajia is not only your daughter.
She is also my daughter.
You may think that everything I do is wrong.
You may think
I am both childish and ridiculous.
You may think I am good for nothing.
But on this matter,
you can't side with the outsider.
You drink less and rest early.
Jianming.
Why did you drink so much?
Alright, let's go back.
Let's go, take it slow.
No need.
- I didn't drink much.
- What? Hurry up.
No. No need to support me.
I-I can walk on my own.
- Alright.
- Don't support me, I can do it.
Such a grown-up
and you are still so silly when drinking.
All these years,
you are still the same,
haven't changed at all.
Okay, stop it. Let's go back.
You are nice.
You've always been nice.
Okay, okay.
But I'm not bad either.
Why are you always right?
No matter whatever I do or say,
I'm always wrong.
Well,
in your eyes, I'm always
like a child, right?
♫ The sun creeps in, it catches ♫
♫ The leaves quietly and wakes the treetops ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ The wonderfulness without any sign ♫
♫ I listen to the breeze
with the tune of the sea ♫
♫ I'm about to embrace the unknown ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ Nothing is predictable ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫