[Begin Again]
I did some research last night
about where we are going today.
Today, we are not going
to the tourist attractions.
Besides, didn't we agree
I'm in charge of today's schedule?
- Yes.
- Don't worry. I will definitely show you
a Macau beyond your expectations, okay?
Okay.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Okay.
Hold on tight.
[Episode Three]
Junhao, our goal
is not to achieve the fastest lap time,
but to achieve a good
- average lap time.
- Okay.
This position is really crooked.
Take something to prop it up a bit.
Xia, here.
- It's arriving this afternoon, right?
- Yes.
- Then unpack it. It's going on display tomorrow.
- Okay.
- There are four pieces inside, right?
- Yes.
Make this spot a bit brighter.
And make this spot a bit darker.
Actually, your three fastest sections combined
are way faster than your fastest lap today.
But just like last year,
they didn't happen in the same lap.
Let's talk about the T7 low-speed corner first.
It's very similar to Macau's hairpin turn.
But there's a problem with you
taking the low-speed corner.
You're being too aggressive.
Of course, it will bring you
slight improvement in lap time,
but it will also increase tire wear.
I don't suggest you focus on that.
So, next up,
we should practice hard
on the T14 section. Try it out.
The shadow on the side needs to stand out,
otherwise there's no contrast right now.
Alright, I understand.
- Put this one over there.
- Okay.
Put the square one over here.
It's too small over there.
It's almost set.
- See if there's anything wrong.
- No.
I'll come over an hour early tomorrow morning
to make the final confirmation.
Okay, don't worry. It will be done well.
Where is this?
You'll know later.
Wait, I'm not here for tourism,
but to scout the location.
I know. But you promised me yesterday
that you'd follow my schedule today.
I have to work on a proposal.
♫ The sun creeps in, it catches ♫
♫ The leaves quietly and wakes the treetops ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ The wonderfulness without any sign ♫
♫ I listen to the breeze
with the tune of the sea ♫
♫ I'm about to embrace the unknown ♫
How is it? Seeing the sea for the first time?
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
I've growing up by the sea, you know.
♫ Nothing is predictable ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
I just haven't seen the sea in a long time.
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
Do you feel like returning to your hometown?
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
Can we play a game?
I'll think of something in my mind,
and you can
ask me some questions.
I will answer "yes" or "no".
- Is it the sea?
- No.
Is it a color?
What do you mean?
You should ask about a specific color.
Food?
Right.
- Getting closer.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So…
It's edible.
- Is it something we've eaten these days?
- No.
No?
Raw or cooked?
That's two questions.
- Okay.
- The first is "No", the latter is "Yes".
- Okay, so it's cooked.
- Yes.
Cooked.
Meat?
Yes.
Cooked meat.
- Something that flies in the sky?
- No.
- Something that runs on the ground?
- Hmm.
Cooked meat, running on the ground.
Getting closer.
- Beef?
- No.
- Pork? Pork product?
- Yes.
See, is it efficient?
Soon, I think you could guess it.
You are smart.
Cooked, processed,
pork products.
- Sausage?
- No.
Here's a tip.
It's not something
with a single ingredient.
Well, is the other ingredient eggs?
Really?
Pork, eggs.
Something processed with pork and eggs.
You are amazing.
Chinese or Western style?
Okay, one question at a time. Chinese style?
No.
- Western style?
- Yes.
Western style, pork, eggs.
Western style, processed.
- Pig filet and eggs?
- It's close.
You're so smart. It's very close.
But,
just one step away.
What is one step away from pig filet and eggs?
No, that's not the name.
Don't tell me it's the pig filet and eggs meal.
No, how could it be?
- Very close.
- What could it be?
Just pig filet and eggs.
Very close.
But it's not this name.
One word.
McMuffin?
Because you are Mai,
and you are perfect.
- What's wrong?
- Thank you.
One more thing.
In the mainland China,
McMuffin
is not available all day.
So in here,
you are perfect
the whole day.
What?
Is this the Portuguese style architecture?
Yes, this area used to be
where the Portuguese officials lived.
Now it has all been turned into museums.
Look at this pavement.
It was all laid out using ballast stones
by the sailors.
In this way, the Portuguese style
was integrated into Macau.
And now this place
has become the backyard for Macau residents.
I can tell that.
Indeed, everyone here looks very relaxed.
How long haven't you had a vacation?
Vacation?
I can't remember when was the last time
I had a vacation.
There are so many clients to deal with,
and so many proposals to make.
I don't even think about taking a vacation
when I have time.
If I have time, I would get some sleep first.
Then if you could take a day off tomorrow,
what would you like to do?
If I could take a day off tomorrow,
I'd like
to watch a sunset leisurely.
I want to watch
a pink sunset
like in Altay.
When the sun sets,
the whole sky
would look like being dyed
with thousands of pink roses,
complemented by the clouds in the sky.
The whole sky
would feel like soft and sweet.
And you would feel like
being melted by it,
which is soul-healing.
Of course, I haven't seen it with my own eyes.
I've only seen it in my friend's proposal.
Come with me.
- Where are we going?
- You'll know later.
Hurry up.
Where to?
We're almost there.
Although we don't have
a pink sunset like in Altay,
we have a golden sea.
♫ And I really don't know what to do ♫
♫ Should I resist or let you go ♫
♫ Or should I listen to my heart ♫
♫ My body and soul ♫
♫ Just reach out to you ♫
♫ I know it's not right ♫
♫ But it's so hard to fight ♫
♫ And I must confess I love you ♫
Here, let's drink.
Fine.
Just take a sip, don't drink it up.
I don't care. I'm drinking it up.
Miss, you really beat me.
Don't you want to find the feeling of Marlena?
Alright.
- I'll drink with you.
- That's the spirit.
Want to go dancing?
Of course.
But we have to finish this drink first.
Fine.
Let's go.
Let's go dance.
Thank you for today.
I really didn't expect
to see such scenery in Macau.
If I had come alone,
I definitely wouldn't have found it.
See? I told you to trust me.
What is this?
Is this a performance?
This is a band's performance
that I wanted to show you today.
Rhesus, hello.
Hello.
You know him?
My dad's friend.
I'll go buy you a drink.
Why don't you wait here for me?
Okay.
- Okay, don't go around.
- Okay.
Why standing there?
Macau is so small that brings us together.
Here comes fate.
Beauty, come and play.
Come play together.
- No.
- Anyone takes her in? Hurry.
No, I can't dance.
Wait, I can't dance.
I can't dance.
- What?
- Let's dance.
I can't dance.
We meet again.
You know each other?
Yes.
- Isa.
- Hi, Isa. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
And your name?
Joe.
Elvis.
- You dance?
- Me?
I don't think so.
No? Well,
- Joe here, an amazing dancer.
- Really?
- She loves to dance.
- Are you serious?
- Sure.
- What do you want?
Definitely, handsome guy, go for it.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Teach me how to dance.
I'm going to have a drink.
- You're going to teach him dance here.
- Thank you.
Like this.
Want to have a drink?
Sure.
Han.
You're here.
- Y-You are…
- Ella.
- Don't you remember me?
- No.
I was drinking there. Long time no see.
- No, I don't recognize you.
- Wait.
- Let's have a drink.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Wait, we don't know each other, right?
Of course, we know each other.
Don't you remember me?
Wait, I am Ella.
We have seen each other
in the server room last time…
- Have a drink. Come have a drink.
- Wait.
I'm a bit tired. I'm going back first.
- What about you?
- Leaving so soon? Don't go.
Don't stay out too late.
Got it.
Let me know when you get back, bye.
You don't recognize me?
I really don't recognize you.
I sat over there. Don't you recognize me?
Where are you going? Have a drink.
- Where are you going?
- How about this?
Join my friends for a drink.
Hello.
Ella. We're good friends.
Wait, what are you doing?
I'll take you home.
What's wrong?
You just want to have dinner with me, right?
You're not getting out of the car, are you?
If you don't go, I will. Okay?
Really? Don't go.
Wait, how do I open this car door?
Come back and open the door.
I'm getting off.
- I'm out, close the door.
- Okay.
What?
Wait, what do you want?
- Do you have to do so?
- Yes, I do.
Could you please get off now?
I'm going back.
Don't get mad.
Go.
Do you have to do so?
Yes.
I haven't felt this relaxed in a long time.
Didn't expect Macau to be this charming.
There are much more charming places
in Macau
waiting for you to discover.
Are you available tomorrow?
Tomorrow, I really need to stay in the hotel
to get the proposal done.
How about the day after tomorrow?
I'm going home the day after tomorrow.
Have a safe journey.
Your bag.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Not at all.
These are beverages and some food
I bought just now.
You can have them during your work overtime.
Thank you.
By the way,
do you remember
the water from Lilau you drank?
Then you will definitely come back.
I really have to go back.
I still have a meeting to attend.
Let's go. I'll send you there.
No, thanks. It's just around the corner.
Then be careful.
I'm glad to have met you in Macau.
Thank you for your help these past few days.
I'm also very glad to have met you.
- Bye.
Miss Mai, I've read the proposal
you worked on overnight.
Those photos from Macau are so beautiful.
Rui, hold on.
Mai, are we
just missing a slogan?
Do you find a suitable one that we sent?
Too conventional.
We need to…
We have to impress the clients
- once they see the slogan.
- Sorry to interrupt, Miss Mai.
Actually, it's too late to change now.
Ms. Maggie has already
sent the proposal to Director Tong.
- Alright.
- We're waiting for her feedback.
Then let's wait. We can only wait.
But Miss Mai, before the presentation tomorrow,
I think we still have time
to come up with a new slogan, right?
Then today, I can
touch up the pictures.
Anyway, we're waiting
for Director Tong's feedback.
No hurry. Once it's done,
let's celebrate tonight.
Director Tong said it's worth a try.
I knew it. Mai, this will surely work.
- I just think these photos…
- Okay, that's all for today.
Everyone, thank you. Thank you all.
- Thank you all.
- We can definitely use them tomorrow.
[Xinghao Hotel invites you to a meeting
to discuss the promo proposal tomorrow.]
Wait.
Wait, take a break.
What's wrong with you today?
You usually can run a few laps with me.
Whose
age is bigger?
It has nothing to do with me.
I didn't sleep well last night,
so I'm not in good shape today.
What's wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
No.
You usually fall asleep once you go to bed.
Except for those few years working
in Hong Kong, you had trouble sleeping.
You usually sleep quite well.
Don't make me like a jobless and carefree man.
You have no work trouble, so…
You're trapped in love.
I study philosophy.
Every day, I have to think about
how to pursue myself and something big.
Love has nothing to do with me.
Don't make me die laughing.
I'm your mom.
I understand you.
Who is it? Do I know her?
- Who is it?
- Nobody.
Tell me, who is it?
Nobody.
- Nobody?
- Nobody.
- I'll interrogate you later.
Interrogate?
Take it slow.
[Mai Youge]
What's wrong?
It's not just recently.
You know, the store is always busy,
from five in the afternoon
to five in the morning every day.
Your dad is always anxious,
has to worry about everything himself.
He's getting old.
So I advised him
to close the shop a bit earlier.
Every time I told him so,
he didn't take it seriously.
You knew him.
How could he let go?
You two have put all your effort
in Zhen Qiang Store.
Whenever he goes to the store,
he gets motivated,
beaming with joy.
Whenever he rests at home,
he hides in the study to drink tea.
So it's better to let him
do something that makes him happy.
I understand. Of course, I know him.
But I am worried
if one day he really can't hold on,
he would keep it from me.
Don't think about these. It's alright.
Don't worry. I have resigned and come back now.
I will put more effort
in the store.
Okay? I promise you.
From now on,
for trivial matters like grocery shopping,
just leave them to me.
Trivial matters?
Grocery shopping is a top priority.
The freshness of ingredients matters the most.
You must not be careless.
You sound like my dad now.
Really?
Why don't I feel it?
It's a waste if you don't be an actress.
You know what? Your acting is so good.
Miss Mai.
Let me introduce you.
This is our Senior Vice President, Mr. Xu.
- Hello.
She's Marketing Director, Amanda.
He's New Media Operations Manager, Chuck.
- Hello.
This is Mai Youge,
Customer Manager from EMG.
She's here to present the proposal today.
- Shall we get started then?
- Okay.
Hello everyone. I'm Mai Youge, Customer Manager
from EMG.
Our entire planning team
is also participating
in the meeting remotely online.
I will first present the proposal
on behalf of EMG.
After it,
if you have any questions,
please feel free to ask.
Then they will
provide some targeted elaboration online.
This is the theme
of our proposal.
Excuse me.
This theme of yours,
what does it have to do with our hotel?
Right, Mr. Xu. I understand your confusion.
But I hope you could be patient,
and I will explain it to you.
Undoubtedly,
Xinghao Hotel
is a top-tier hotel brand in the world.
However, with the booming tourism industry
in Macau in recent years,
in fact, among the top hotels,
there have also been
competitive situations.
Therefore, we believe
that Xinghao Hotel's promo
should not focus
on showcasing the hotel itself anymore,
instead,
through our promo,
letting the audience understand
that choosing Xinghao Hotel
means acquiring
a brand-new travel experience
and a type of
distinct lifestyle.
So in the promo, we decided
to combine the scenery, unique culture,
regional cuisine of Macau
and Xinghao Hotel.
We want to fully display
the fusion
between Eastern and Western cultures in Macau
and the coexistence of historic culture
and modern culture.
Our goal is
to strongly bind Xinghao Hotel
with Macau Culture and Tourism,
to let the audience feel
the unique charm of the Greater Bay Area.
The audience will then want
to travel to Macau.
And when they do come to Macau,
Xinghao Hotel will
become their top choice.
Everyone knows that it's an era
of short videos.
If a video can't capture its users
in the first three seconds,
meaning it has lost its users forever.
Therefore, we decided
to use the Macau Grand Prix GT Cup event
sponsored by Xinghao Hotel
as the opening scene.
We will turn the streets
into racing lanes,
and replace traffic lights
with racing start lights.
Excuse me.
Can you give me a lift?
That is to say,
at the very beginning of the promo,
we should let the audiences feel
that Macau is a city full of the unknown,
making one
feel excited.
This is a kind of misattribution of arousal.
Through some
extreme situations,
we make everyone feel
a sense of excitement.
From now on, as long as you're in Macau,
I can take you to have tasty food every day.
You walk slower than during the day.
But after the excitement,
we will also unfold
the Macau's living atmosphere
and cultural heritage.
Macau is a city
with a slow pace, romance,
and the warmth of life,
where one can truly let their guard down
and enjoy the city at that very moment.
So when everyone
finishes a day of exploration,
they will surely want to find a place
that can bring them
the same feeling,
to carefully savor the day.
At that moment,
Xinghao Hotel
will become their best choice.
It's like under the most dazzling lighthouse,
finding a haven
that's quiet and comfortable.
[Lilau's History]
So that's my proposal. Thank you all.
Do you have any questions?
- I don't have any question.
- Chuck.
- I think it can pass.
- Amanda.
Good.
Thank you for coming today.
That's it for today.
- Okay? Thank you.
- Okay.
You are welcome.
Thank you.
- Mr. Xu, we…
- Talk later.
We will tell you any news the earliest.
Thank you.
Okay, if there are any questions,
please contact us immediately.
How is Marlena's proposal?
Nothing. We haven't figured out
what the problem is.
Final check it again. Joe, come here.
Tell me,
which one is Marlena's most outstanding work?
It is definitely
the series she collaborated on
with her former lover,
the performance art
about the emotional conflicts
between men and women.
It directly confronts darkness and violence,
and bravely explores the edges of human nature,
fighting against the world with her very self.
That's why her works
are so impactful.
Thus, public opinion on her
is so controversial.
Some believe she is the greatest artist
of the twentieth century,
while others think she is insane.
Not everyone can understand her.
Just like you,
you are completely different from her,
overly protective of yourself,
always staying in your comfort zone.
And everything
must be under your control.
Actually, not really.
I guess when you date,
you are the one
who brings up the breakup, right?
Because you know
the more you love someone,
the more vulnerable you are getting hurt.
You wouldn't let yourself be so.
I think
if you fall in love
willfully and recklessly
without considering the consequences,
maybe then you would understand her.
[Zhou Huafu]
Hello.
Are you here to look for someone
or see a doctor?
T-To see a doctor.
What's your problem?
Well, lately,
I don't sleep very well.
Please, sit.
Take out your hand.
Stick out your tongue.
Roll it up.
Another hand.
- How old are you this year?
- Thirty-one.
- Only thirty-one?
- What?
It's like I'm having
some serious problem.
What is wrong with me?
You have a sleep problem
- for over a year, right?
- Yes.
Young man, if you have worries,
just talk to your friends.
Once you speak out, everything will be clear.
Holding it in
can easily turn into sickness.
Right. Do you prescribe some medicine?
It is a mind illness.
Once you solve the knot in your heart,
everything will be well.
- Okay.
- Go over there.
Come on, take off your clothes.
Wait, are you going to acupuncture me?
What? Just lie down.
No, I'm scared.
I don't acupuncture.
Just check on your waist.
Take off your clothes.
Not acupuncture?
No. Don't be afraid.
Such a grown person, afraid of acupuncture?
If it hurts, just shout out.
Is it that much?
Stop, be gentle.
- This is so painful.
- Your life is so thrilling.
Yes, my profession is indeed thrilling.
- Your profession?
- Yes.
Young man,
don't get so thrilling.
There is a limit.
Once it's gone, it's gone.
Take care of your body.
Wait, have you misunderstood my profession?
What?
Anyway, take good care of your body.
Don't exhaust yourself.
Come on. If it hurts, scream out.
Be gentle.
I really can't stand this.
Hui, time to go.
- Wait a moment.
- Shall we reschedule for another day?
No, lie down.
I must get it done today.
It's you again?
Seeing a doctor.
I get it.
Did you hurt your back
from playing too hard last night?
No, you've misunderstood me.
Uncle Zhong, I'm leaving.
- Remember…
- Remember not to catch a draft. Rest assured.
Does it hurt?
It's right then. If it hurts,
let Uncle Zhong give you a good massage.
Enjoy the massage before you go.
Don't you need the massage? Leaving now?
She's back to work.
Come on.
Lie down, come on.
Where does she work?
Both she and my granddaughter
work at the gallery,
and they are doing quite well.
You could go support her, at Xinghao Hotel.
Xinghao Hotel?
Dr. Zhong,
the technique you're using now
is much comfortable than before.
Maybe I'll get a membership card.
What?
This isn't a beauty salon.
Your actions just now
were just the preliminary moves, right?
Why does it still hurt so much?
[Zhen Qiang Store]
♫ The sun creeps in, it catches ♫
♫ The leaves quietly and wakes the treetops ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ The wonderfulness without any sign ♫
♫ I listen to the breeze
with the tune of the sea ♫
♫ I'm about to embrace the unknown ♫
♫ Dreaming, oh, dreaming ♫
♫ Nothing is predictable ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫
♫ Why not dance with your heartbeat ♫
♫ And swing your dress ♫
♫ At this moment, forget ♫
♫ About all the worries ♫
♫ Why not carry cute curiosity ♫
♫ To dance in the wind and the sea ♫
♫ Keep looking ♫
♫ All the wonderful answers
have been predicted ♫