Have you heard of
Black Rock?
It's a ring from the White Water Security Company.
How much do you know about the water security company?
I only know that
is similar to Black Rock.
Its main job is security service.
I know nothing else.
Hei Shi?
Yes.
You found the right person.
I have a friend
who specializes in this in Iceland.
Just say that.
the black stone.
Black.
It's so big and wide.
It's decorated in the furniture.
That’s awesome.
I didn’t expect Mr. Yan to know this.
Aren’t you in stock business?
Steward Bai.
In our business,
in our business.
I see.
Mr. Yan is really professional.
In that case,
can you tell us
what stocks you bought recently?
Let me follow you.
and make some money.
I bought it.
Which stock?
Oh.
The one I bought
That one
What was it again?
Forget it.
Let me tell you.
006171.
I’m very optimistic about this stock recently.
and bought a lot.
How much
this stock?
Mr. Yan, don’t you remember?
It can’t be.
As a professional stock analyst,
you should remember
the stock price clearly.
Sorry.
I'll tell you
Let me tell you.
Today's
stock price
231 dollars.
That's a lot different.
Mr. Yan.
Are you really a stock analyst?
Or...
you're lying to me?
Forget it.
Just do it.
Steward Bai.
Don't worry.
I have a habit.
It starts at 9:30.
I mean
the price today.
Check your phone.
Oh.
You're back.
How did it go?
Ms. Lena.
We're done talking.
I'll tell Mrs. Gu and Mr. Gu
to Mrs. Gu and Mr. Gu.
But...
Xiao Tang.
doesn't match our young master's personality,
we don't have to be friends anymore.
in case
cause unnecessary trouble again.
Ms. Lena.
Okay.
Thank you
Thank you.
Okay.
Xiao Tang's parents.
Goodbye.
Have some coffee.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Have some coffee.
Coffee.
Episode 4
Why doesn't Gu Peng Peng like to be friends with me?
Does he hate me that much?
Xiao Tang.
In our life,
meet many people.
But not everyone likes us.
If Gu Peng Peng says he doesn't like you,
then forget it.
I hope you can be friends
and someone who likes you.
Thank you, Mom.
Sleep.
Baby.
Come on, give me a kiss.
Kiss, baby.
Good night.
Xiao Tang said
Gu Peng Peng doesn't want to be friends with her.
Forget it then.
Judging from what Steward Bai said today,
he wants to use Gu Peng Peng to approach the Gu family.
It won't work.
Looks like we have to figure out a way
to join the elite parent board meeting that Mrs. Gu manages.
What about Mrs. Gu?
Although she is the Honorary Chairman,
but he rarely participates.
the management of the board.
[The actual manager is someone else.]
The other parent.
Amanda.
That piano star.
is handsome.
Go get close to her.
Why me?
You can try.
if you can use a handsome trick.
Honey.
Although I'm
very charming,
But
I'm a wife now.
I can't take any more handsome tasks.
Do you know that?
Go to sleep.
I've investigated everything.
Amanda not only likes music,
but also has other hobbies.
sports car.
racing,
she likes them all.
She likes it.
Armanda is in the garage.
Look at me.
Performance.
What do you think?
Isn't it cool?
Is this okay?
Is it too oily?
It's okay.
As long as it works.
Oh.
What a coincidence.
Ms. Amanda.
I didn't expect
we are in the same team.
You are...
It's me.
Mr. Sugar.
We met before.
At school.
Why are you taking a ride today?
Nice car.
It's just for fun.
Your car is cool too.
It's well modified.
It took some effort.
Oh.
Ms. Amanda.
I didn't put in a lot of effort.
Young-joon, keep it for me.
Let me see.
Oh.
The whole flow structure
Amanda's car engine has been modified.
The turbo increase can reach up to four sides.
or even higher.
I think your turbo increase
your turbo pressure.
Tsubaka!
Oh Ba!
Amazing.
Young-joon, you already installed it.
She used carbon fiber.
Carbon fiber material?
Although it's expensive,
but weight loss.
You ran fast.
It's okay.
It's not expensive.
She also changed the exhaust system.
You also used 4-2-1 joules.
and demolished the three-yuan irrigation.
and the voice cooler at the back of the exhaust tube?
You...
Moto can smell it.
It's done
It’s not smell.
Mr. Yan.
It really opened my eyes.
I didn't expect
love cars so much.
Amanda.
To be honest,
there are
in my garage.
Do you want to
take a look?
My pleasure.
Success.
Let's follow the plan.
Ta-da.
Of course.
Ms. Amanda.
This garage
is just a part of my collection.
There's one on the second floor too.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sugar.
Too modest.
LOE
LOE.
The lines are smooth.
The height is low.
The stability and curve must be very good.
Wow.
limited edition.
Pick any one you like.
Which one do you like?
Take it.
Are you crazy, handsome?
I borrowed all these.
Don't make stupid promises.
That's too kind of you.
How can I
such a big favor?
Oh.
Speaking of which,
I do have a small thing
that you can help me.
What is it?
just tell me.
Oh.
Thank you.
Actually, my wife and I
want to join our parent board meeting.
I'm sorry.
It's too noisy.
What did you say?
I said I'll say it again.
Actually my wife and I
want to join.
It's too loud.
What did you say?
I'll speak louder.
My wife and I
want to join our parent board meeting.
Actually, my wife and I...
What are you doing?
Who is it?
Ko Rang.
How dare you copy me?
Good timing.
You said
you wanted to join the parent board meeting.
I've made up my mind.
Wait.
Ms. Amanda.
Why did you join the parent board meeting?
You're not even a parent.
Let me introduce.
Mr. Ko's child
just transferred to our school.
Ah.
Sister.
Let's talk about the parents' board meeting.
Last time...
Sister.
Actually...
I know.
Blow it.
Actually, my wife and I
want to join the parent board meeting.
I'm finally done.
You want to join the parent board meeting too?
This is hard.
There's only one spot for the parent board meeting.
Please wait.
After my daughter's birthday tomorrow,
after my daughter's birthday tomorrow.
Sister.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I don't know what your dad thinks.
I'm fine with it
Let's have a battle.
What do you mean, Jason?
Don't you need an explanation?
Jason.
This is our mission.
What's wrong with them?
You two can pretend to be a family of three.
Me and Ko Rang.
Isn't it easy to find a kid?
Why are you making a fuss?
Hello.
I'm the new transfer student.
My name is Ko Ho.
And my Hao Hao
is a good boy.
I'll keep an eye on Xiaotang at school.
Stop pretending.
You're here to make trouble.
I didn't say
to help you.
Bai Haoqing.
The Swan Lake on the right side of Chengdu.