Please have a seat.
Our boss will be here soon.
Thank you.
Don't move.
Ms. Sara.
What do you mean?
Mrs. Smith.
Why don't you tell me
Who are you?
Answer me.
You're not good at disguising your identity.
If you can't think of a way,
Honey.
Learn from me.
A flamboyant and confident acting.
My name
Nam Chae-yun.
A personal bodyguard.
Your father paid me to protect you.
Nonsense.
My father passed away five years ago.
Your father was gone five years ago.
But he paid me ten years in one go.
And I...
Don't move.
And I'm a bodyguard with principles.
Even if the employer is dead,
I will keep my promise
and finish my job.
Do you think
I would believe you?
That bastard who prioritizes men over women
doesn't care about my life at all.
or spend money.
to hire a bodyguard for me.
Shut up!
You ignorant brat.
How could you say that about your father?
You know nothing about him.
He told me
the most regretful thing
in his life
that I didn't tell you
he loves you.
He values men over daughters.
But do you know
Among all his children,
among all his children.
Boss.
I can't stand it anymore.
Can you wait until I finish?
I have no idea.
Of course,
he once said something very despicable.
He said
it would be great if Sara was a son.
He doesn't dare to face you.
He doesn't even dare to let you know
he hired a bodyguard
to protect you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have told you this.
Boss.
Don't listen to her.
She approached you
to approach you.
How dare you say that?
Let me ask you.
Yesterday,
Sara was unconscious in the hotel.
and was almost assassinated.
Where were you?
How did she know I was assassinated last night?
Let me ask you again.
When Sara was poisoned
and almost died,
where were you?
Say something.
Do you think
because of this loser?
Without me,
you would have died 800 times.
Useless thing.
What are you waiting for?
Sit down.
Don't you want to buy me dinner?
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you
wrong about you.
Nam Chae-yun.
What a nice name.
Better than Smith.
than Smith.
Actually,
I did something wrong too.
Can you
tell me more
about my father?
No hurry.
I'll tell you later.
What I'm curious about now is
how you know who I am.
I saw you
I saw you.
Xiaorou is my daughter.
She just transferred to your daughter's class.
Xiao Rou is your daughter.
Aren't you my bodyguard?
You don't even know that?
I'm only responsible for your personal safety.
I'm not interested in anything else.
Besides,
you know I'm a burden.
I'm not staring at you 24 hours a day.
Bodyguards have their own lives.
Since we've made it clear,
you don't have to protect me in secret anymore.
You...
to be my personal bodyguard.
I'll pay you.
To be honest,
I quite like you.
Being with you
is much more comfortable
with those stinky men.
You did a good job.
Now,
Sara's bodyguard.
We're one step closer
to the Gu family.
It's not that easy.
Sara still doesn't trust me.
Being your personal bodyguard
to be your personal bodyguard.
But I have a few conditions.
Anything.
To ensure your safety,
I need to investigate your work
and the environment
in your life,
including
the backyard of Yin Yue House.
Not there.
In that case,
I can't work.
You know what?
What is the most important thing
What's the most important thing
It's trust.
No trust.
I can't work.
Except this,
I can promise you
anything.
I won't force you.
But there's one thing
I have to know.
is your personal relationship.
You were murdered twice in a row.
I found out that your husband hired a murderer.
Don't worry.
My husband
has been officially arrested today.
He won't
have a chance.
But according to my investigation,
this matter
has something to do
with the Gu family.
You know about the Gu family?
She still doesn't allow me to enter the backyard.
And whenever I mention the Gu family,
she would end the topic.
My family and the Gu family
are friends for generations.
Don't worry about that.
The Gu family doesn't like to show up in public.
So let's stop talking about
is over.
It means
about me.
Walk step by step.
We have to take it step by step.
Now we have
a good start.
Let's celebrate.
But
I found something else.
Sara seems to have some serious disease.
Disease?
And strangely,
the backyard of Yin Yue House
is the most secured place.
Go back first.
Come to me tomorrow.
But I saw it there.
Rou.
However,
Xiao Rou is her daughter after all.
It's not strange
It's not strange.
Forget it.
Let's drink.
Bye.
Actually, drinking
not just drinking.
but
together.
Stay longer.
Thank you.
Gosh.
Red is gone.
Rou.
Rou!
Honey.
Mrs. Gu's butler.
There must be something important
in his black box.
I'll go meet him.
Nam Chae-yun.
Let me introduce.
This is my husband.
My daughter, Xiaotang.
I heard that
Xiaorou is sick.
She's worried.
So I came to see you.
Auntie.
Where is Xiaorou?
Is she okay?
Xiaorou is resting.
She's fine.
It's just malnutrition.
Auntie.
Can I visit Xiao Rou?
I brought her flowers.
Thank you.
It's not convenient today.
I'll tell Xiao Rou
you came to see her.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
I have an appointment today.
I can't entertain you.
Let's make an appointment
next time.
By then,
get to know this gentleman.
Please leave today.
Okay.
Send them off for me.
Didn't you say she was seriously ill yesterday?
Why are you acting like nothing happened today?
I'm confused too.
Xiao Rou's illness is too sudden.
Xiaorou.
I need you.
Please help me.
Okay?
Xiaorou.
Will you be my daughter?
Bai Haoqing.
The Swan Lake on the right side of Chengdu.