I fainted because I was sick.
No wonder it got dark
when I entered the bathroom.
Mom.
I fainted for a few days.
I felt like I slept for a long time.
Just one day.
If I faint for a few days,
we'll be scared to death.
Xiao Tang.
Don't scare me again.
One more bite.
Xiaotang.
Xiaorou.
Are you feeling better?
I slept for a long time.
I even dreamed of you.
What did you dream about?
I dreamed
there was a mountain
There was a temple in the mountain.
An old monk is telling stories in the temple.
What is he talking about?
Once upon a time there was a mountain
There was a temple in the mountain.
An old monk is telling stories in the temple.
What is he talking about?
Once upon a time there was a mountain
There was a temple in the mountain.
An old monk is telling stories in the temple.
I don't want Xiao Rou to go back to the orphanage.
She has suffered so much psychological trauma.
She really needs a mother
who loves her so much to heal slowly.
Like me.
It's you.
But you have to think carefully.
It's not easy to be a mother.
Besides, it's not easy
to find a boyfriend.
No.
Who said that?
I'm just looking for a husband
with a child.
Don't listen to him.
Lena.
I believe you can do it.
And
you'll be a good mother.
I'm going to kill her.
This isn't the time to talk about this.
Let me show you something.
Can you be more creative?
Is there a lot of things in Black Rock?
Yes.
But don't forget,
Black Rock's bomb necklaces are shipped.
And every year,
every year.
But this one...
Look carefully.
One is black rock.
and the other is imitated.
Who gave you
Who gave them to you?
I found it at Nam Chae Hoon's house.
No.
I saw them wearing a necklace.
According to Black Rock,
there are identity chips in the necklace.
As long as we take the necklace back to Black Rock to read the chip,
we'll know
Who is it?
Maybe
we can dig into the water
through this line.
Take it back to Jason.
OK.
I'll go down and have a look.
Let's go.
Run, Ning!
Run!
Ning.
Ko Rang.
Let's go.
Ning.
Ko Rang.
Let's go.
It's Ko Rang.
[Ko Rang took the necklace.]
He didn't put a bug
in our house.
He just took the necklace.
Since Ko Rang took it,
he will tell Jason
With Jason's personality,
he must have started to suspect us.
Find someone to break the necklace.
Did he contact you?
No.
He didn't contact me either.
Ms. Nam Chae-yun.
Reporter.
How did you find out
Sara has been
in the way of adopting orphans?
Why did you choose to reveal Sara's crime
at the charity dinner
instead of calling the police?
Why didn't you call the police?
Rumor has it that you're a personal bodyguard hired by Sara's father.
Is that true?
Mr. YUN Young-joon.
Do you know
your wife is a personal bodyguard?
I’d like to make a public answer
I'll make a public answer.
I didn't expose
not out of personal grudges,
It's just a citizen's duty.
The reason why
at the charity dinner
is to use the power of public opinion
so Sara can't operate in secret
to clear her name.
As far as I know,
Sara and the Gu family
They're very close. They're very close. They're very close.
Gu House?
What is the relationship between Sara and the Gu family?
Please explain the background of the Gu family in detail.
What is your source of information?
Ms. Nam Chae-yun.
Can you explain the family background?
Nam Chae-yun!
What are you doing?
You openly challenged the Gu family.
We finally got here.
After what you did,
It's all over.
Can you use your brain?
Do you think if I don't say that,
the Gu family won't notice us?
We sent Sala to court.
Sara is a family friend.
The Gu family will let us go.
Instead of waiting for death,
we should take the initiative
and force the Gu family
to make a public statement.
Tall.
My wife is taller.
You mean...
dragging the Gu family into this?
If they still want to protect Sala,
it's hard.
I can only draw a line with Sara.
Maybe
he'll be able to be friendly to us.
I hope so.
The Gu family
is mysterious and unpredictable.
No one knows what they will do next.
The news tomorrow morning
tomorrow morning.
Hello.
Jason.
Got it.
What?
Ko Rang is dead.
Dead?
Two hours ago,
two hours ago.
So
our identity is exposed too?
Not yet.
Ko Rang died because of those two necklaces.
He almost killed He Luning.
So
Ko Rang took those two necklaces.
If he doesn't take them,
the dead
is...
Bai Haoqing.
The Swan Lake on the right side of Chengdu.