Oh
oh
Lee
What do you mean, Changxin Yin?
What did you take?
Or you didn't enjoy the party?
You dare to mention it again?
You deliberately made fun of me and embarrassed me.
You lied to me that you would buy 200,000 pieces of it.
200,000 pieces?
A pot of rotten tangerine flowers costs 200,000 pieces?
If it wasn't for you,
why would I buy those tangerines for Her Majesty?
Changxin Yin, this is your fault.
You handle it.
Are you deaf?
I bought the flowers.
How does it concern me?
You are the wife of my family.
Your money is the money of my family.
Yes, sister.
Why do you say that?
You are the one who paid the last.
Who said I paid?
You are a rich family.
You are the young mistress of my family.
Shouldn't you do something for my family?
Besides, you have so many shops.
It's enough to just buy some.
Are you out of your mind?
How does my shop have anything to do with your family?
If you don't support my family,
how can you have those shops?
Ridiculous.
I work in the business department of my family.
Why do I need your support?
Anyway, Sansi Army has sent the princess to the palace.
In a few days, Princess Jingyang will send someone to get the money.
If you don't get the money,
you will lose your wife.
I don't understand what you are saying.
People saw that you bought the flowers.
You gave the title.
You should be the one who lost the woman.
I have reminded you to be considerate.
But you didn't listen.
So I have to take the money.
You are pretending to be confused.
We had a wedding a few days ago.
We spent more than half of the money.
You have more than 500 yuan.
Where did you get 200,000 yuan?
I have no money.
I think the mansion of the duke
is the best place in the capital.
You can get 200,000 yuan from it.
Bullshit.
I have a lot of money.
If you have a better idea,
you can lose the man.
The royal family will not make you suffer because of the money.
You can save 200,000 yuan.
Brother Hong,
we don't have enough money.
If we can't,
we can take the mansion.
You are lying.
I will find a way.
Zhang Xiyin is so stingy.
Brother Hong doesn't understand me.
He keeps blaming me.
Please calm down.
You can ask the empress to lend you the money.
No.
What should we do?
We don't have enough money.
He must pay the 200,000 yuan.
Xiyin, we are family.
You can't just leave us.
We are brothers.
I can lend you the money.
But what do you want?
I have nothing.
Can you give me some interest?
We only take the money.
If you don't have it,
I can only live in silence.
Wait.
I will use the mansion's property as the mortgage.
I will lend you 200,000 yuan.
Is that enough?
Okay.
But as far as I know,
you don't have the estate.
I have it.
Then you can go and get it.
Okay.
I will go.
Xiyin,
we have finished our deal.
I have something else to do.
I won't go with you.
Isn't this Miss Li?
Miss Li, long time no see.
Miss Li, do you remember us?
Who are you?
I don't know you.
Who is here to disturb the wife of Duke Ding'an?
The wife of Duke Ding'an?
Miss Li,
you are the fiancee of Duke Ding'an.
You are the heir of Duke Ding'an.
What fiancee?
I don't know you.
Don't talk nonsense.
Li Yuewan,
you left the border overnight.
You didn't even pay us the money.
Now you pretend you don't know us.
If you don't make it clear, you don't want to leave.
Xicun, drive them away.
Yes.
You are so rude.
You don't pay us the money.
Prince Jin is here.
Who is making trouble here?
My lord,
can you give us the decision?
Duke Ding'an is going to kill someone.
Yes.
You are still alive.
Thank you for coming in time.
Yes.
Or they would have killed him.
Greetings, my lord.
Did you meet any trouble?
I just met them when I came out with my wife.
They said they were in the border.
They are here to kill someone.
I just met them when I came out with my wife.
They said they were in the border to work for you.
Maybe it's a misunderstanding.
There is no misunderstanding.
He has lived there for half a year.
My lord, it's about your wife and Duke's reputation.
Please investigate it.
No need.
It's nothing.
Don't bother.
Please rest assured.
I will find out the truth.
I will give her justice.
Chi Shu.
Take them to the court.
Yes.
Take them away.
Why are you so careless?
I came back to find you.
I just need to give them money.
I usually give them something.
I didn't know they would come.
Even if they came,
they shouldn't know our relationship.
I am a woman.
It's not good to tell others that I met a man in the middle of the night.
I just said you are my fiancee.
Enough.
If those two ladies tell you the truth,
we will be fooled.
Hong, go to Xiyin later.
You should talk to her.
Maybe it will be over.
I know.
Xiyin.
Why am I so nervous?
We are husband and wife.
It's not necessary.
I will go.
You dare to enter my lady's room?
How dare you!
I am a prince.
You are a prince.
You should be in my room.
Stop!
Xiyin, throw this rabbit out.
Go.
Let go of me.
What's wrong with him?
Hong.
Hong, why are you here?
What are you waiting for? Untie me.
Hurry.
What are you looking at?
Get out.
Zhang Xiyin, you dare to fool me.
You beat me like this.
You tied me up and threw me out.
I was lying on the food table for a night.
You are too much.
Hong, why did you go to him last night?
Why are you talking about me?
It's all because of you.
Wanwan, you should understand me.
I can't give you two away.
What should I do?
So,
you were a prince last night.
I told the court yesterday.
It's your secret.
You beat me up.
Zhang Xiyin, if you don't know how to control me,
I will help you.
Come on, drag me out.
I will serve you.
You are my maid.
You can't be the crown prince.
You can teach me.
You are my maid.
Take her.
The Crown Prince is so brave.
I dare to beat him.
You are my maid.
You can't be the crown prince.