See hit
Oh
She had an idea
Yeah
For博 differs
包是娘不好
I apologize to you today.
I'm too young to be a mother.
Xinyi, look.
I made this soup myself.
It's made of the best ingredients.
You've been treating me like this.
I'm treating you like this.
You must appreciate it.
This soup is too hot.
I'll drink it when it's cool.
Here, sister.
Have some cake to soothe your fatigue.
Thank you, sister.
If you have something to say,
just say it.
I don't know how to say it to you.
Then think it over before you tell me.
I'm done.
Sister.
Sister, you're the head of the household.
But you need to recuperate now.
I'm in a hurry to get married.
I'm embarrassed to let you work for me.
So...
So, sister,
why don't you leave the
house?
Zhang Xinyi, you bitch.
Why is the box empty?
No.
Wanwan, stop looking.
Did she hide the money in the house?
Wanwan, I...
I'll go ask her for the account book.
If she dares to hide the money,
Brother Hong will have to fix it
and make it look good.
No.
Li Yuanyuan is here.
Sister, I was just thinking about it.
How could you hand over the money so quickly?
You've already emptied the house.
Sister, why don't you check the accounts
and see what the expenses are for?
You've already made a false account.
You want to ruin Brother Hong's wedding, right?
Your Highness,
I'll be the one to tell the truth.
You tell the truth to your sister.
Shut up.
Don't try to get in my way.
Wanwan, let's go.
I'm not going.
I won't leave until I make it clear.
Look at you.
You don't know that the house
is empty.
Impossible.
How could the house be empty?
Since I married into the family,
they've been living in the house.
I used the dowry to pay off their debts.
Then I used my mother's house to pay off the debt.
Now I'm living with the Crown Prince.
Naturally, the accounts will be divided.
What she said is true?
The official's care is a waste of money.
It's a waste of money.
What about our wedding?
You're asking the right questions.
The wedding is about to start.
If the whole city knows about it,
I'm afraid that no one will know your identity.
I'll think of a way to get married.
I'll ask my mother to help me.
You're going to marry someone else?
What if the news spreads?
No.
I can't borrow money from my wedding.
How can you call me a concubine?
I know.
Let's discuss this, okay?
Hurry.
Close the door if you're late.
Yes.
Miss, Li Yuewan went into the palace.
Wait for his good news.
Miss, the day of the first day of the next month
is the day of my wedding with Brother Hong.
Congratulations.
The city is the property of the royal family.
Please come in.
Congratulations.
You're here.
Please come in.
Congratulations.
You're so handsome.
My estaburn aprender rather little.
Why hasn't Zhang Xing arrived?
The Secondary Princessusst had come!
It's really a lot of work.
Sister, please have some tea.
Sister, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
Sister, your hairpin...
Your hairpin...
The one on the hairpin is a phoenix.
The phoenix is the favorite of the empress.
Young Master, you've made a big mistake.
You've made a big mistake.
This is a capital crime.
Sister, you're trying to steal the phoenix.
You're trying to kill the whole family.
Zhang Xiyin, you're so vicious.
Go and take off your headband.
Don't let him ruin my son's wedding.
Everyone, the hairpin on my head is a golden bird, not a phoenix.
The phoenix has three tails, and the golden bird has only two.
A tail?
Young Mistress, I heard that you don't have gold here.
I brought you a headband.
Miss, how could Li Yuanyuan give you such a beautiful hairpin?
Look again.
It's a phoenix.
Only the empress can wear it.
Miss, this is a capital crime.
Take this picture and find the craftsmen outside.
Help me to get a headband.
It's really a golden bird.
No, the bride's wedding dress is embroidered with phoenix.
It's really a phoenix.
Look, it's really a phoenix.
The phoenix is the princess's wedding dress.
Could it be that you're the princess?
Or you dare to pretend to be the princess?
Nonsense! I made this up.
Don't slander me.
Everyone, I'm Zhang Shi, the emperor.
I'm the princess of the royal family.
If I say something wrong, it will implicate Zhang Shi.
How could I slander you with the whole family?
Zhang Xi, have you had enough?
Enough.
Go to the bridal chamber with Wanwan.
Mother, the wedding dress of Princess Sizizhuo is a crime.
If this is spread out and the people know about it,
I'm afraid it's hard to protect my reputation.
And sister, your hairpin...
and rouge are also the royal family's goods.
How dare she do that?
Is it because you brought your sister from the border?
Yes.
She's a victim of a major crime.
Your Highness,
I've been wondering since you brought your sister back from the border.
How could a weak girl like you save your sister?
You...
You don't know your identity.
Are you a spy from the Western Liang?
No, I was born in the capital.
When did you come to the capital?
What's your name?
Did you have the imperial seal when you were born?
Zhang Xi, are you crazy?
Prince Ji is here.
The night is like a crisis.
The proud disguise in front of the eyes.
The sadness under the disguise.
Why is there a flash of light.
The light of my sun is spreading.
You are my light.
Open the endless darkness.
Guide me to the future.
You are my light.
Let me light up the road.
Let's meet again.
The wind of time is breaking.
I'm in my heart.
The direction you are in is like a flame.
Give me the power to fly.
I'm walking towards you.