The Golden Eyes
Episode 48
Mr. Feng, have you thought about...
...designing your own ceramic?
Create artwork according to the current trend.
The Tang Dynasty Sancai you made...
...is flawless...
...but it lacks vicissitude.
A fake is after all,fake.
You can use ancient clay...
...and materials...
...but you can't replicate the humanity and society back then.
Trying to replicate these differences...
...isn't something man can do.
Yes.
Instead of... ...imitating your predecessors,...
...why don't you create your own designs?
I like antiques...
...but I also like craftwork that has yet to become antique.
Your craftsmanship is as good as those in the past.
If you hone your skills,...
...I believe that after thousands of years,...
...your craftwork will be sought-after antique.
I understand. -I understand,too.
Are you sponsoring a work station for Mr. Feng?
Yes,in Beijing.
Bei.....
Sure.
We're rich, so we can afford this.
I have to say,the cost will be 3 times of that in Gansu.
There also be...
...labour costs and transportation costs.
We're not firing clay but burning money.
Are you okay with this?
Of course!
Of course I'm okay with doing things I love...
...and earn money from it,too.
I'm more than okay with this.
All right. First,let your hand heal.
That's secondary. First,we'll determine the share allocations.
Labour costs and materials costs,too,right?
Don't worry about the costs. Anything you need,...
...just tell Xiaoyun. -Okay,thank you.
Zhuang Rui. -Okay,I'll wait for you.
Don't move.
Why is it you?
Why am I here?
I'll call the doctor.
No need.
Qin Haoran doesn't need me anymore.
You don't get anything by saving me.
The Qin family will not thank you.
You're also not a threat to the Qin family.
Miss Qin.
I have no plans to take advantage of you.
I just hope that you'll live.
Live?
Living...
...means nothing to me now.
Miss Qin.
You like amber fragrance,right?
My father once said...
...that ambergris is secreted from the intestine of sperm whales.
It floats on the ocean for a long time.
The stronger the storm, the longer it deposits...
...and the cleaner it is.
It will have a stronger smell,too.
Miss Qin.
This was just one round of storm.
You are free.
When you've recovered, you may leave anytime.
I have a favour to ask of you.
Zhuang Rui will arrive in Beijing tomorrow.
If you wish to meet him, I'll bring him here.
Zhuang Rui.
Is he all right?
Miss Qin is awake? Does she remember what happened?
She does.
Boss!
She's alive. Go to the hospital. -Yes.
She was almost killed by Qin Haoran's men...
...and trapped under the collapse.
It's a miracle that she survived this.
Qin Haoran's ruthlessness is nothing new.
However,I can't believe...
...that he would do this to his own daughter.
I've sent men to retrieve information on the Qin family.
We should get it soon.
How do we tell Zhuang Rui about Miss Qin?
So my father could return to Japan safely...
...because of Mr. Zhuang's help.
Did your father ever mention someone called Xiaoma?
There's sporadic account of events in Gansu.
Just like in Mr. Zhuang's notebook.
However,there isn't much about this killer.
He only mentioned...
...that the man was evil but was good at hiding it...
...so they let their guard down. Hence,they were attacked.
Let their guard down?
They let their guard down...
...because it was someone from the team.
So,...
...who is Xiaoma?
Leader Miao,the evidence team sent information of members...
...of the archaeological team 40 years ago.
How is this possible?
No one with the surname Ma or with Ma in their names...
...in the archaeological team.
What? No one with the surname Ma?
Not even Ma in their names.
I just remembered.
The body count of those in Feng Quan's tomb...
...with Zhuang Qiming and Nakagawa Yohei...
...checks out with the information from the evidence department.
Where is Xiaoma?
Yes.
Feifei. Feifei! Come here.
Chief Ding!
I'm on a case. Can you wait?
When are you going to give me the Gansu report?
I'll give it to you soon.
Hurry up.
There's many things to attend to from this Gansu trip.
I need to organize our clues.
Let's put Xiaoma's matters aside for now.
I'm meeting Chief Ding now. Bye.
Don't rush. Take it slow.
The truth will prevail.
I don't have time.
I have the same symptoms as your father.
I'm losing my 5 senses. Headaches...
...and dizziness are more frequent now.
Cherry blossom has 7 days.
I think I'm at the end of the 7 days.
Zhuang Rui,I'll do my best to save you.
In the desert, Kojima and Aoyama...
...risked their lives to save me.
Now,Qin Xuanbing lost her life for me.
I don't want anyone else to sacrifice for me.
I'm begging you.
Please don't tell him that I'm alive.
Why?
My presence in his life...
...does not help him at all.
I don't want him to see me...
...and pity me.
I'd rather he thinks I'm dead.
At least,...
...he can still remember me.
I don't have much time...
...but I hope before I die,...
...we can find my grandfather and Grandfather's Gu's killer.
I don't want to die with regret.
Zhuang Rui is being watched by Qin Haoran.
He's suffering from the side effects of the Golden Eyes.
There's also Xiaoma.
If I spread the news that Zhuang Rui has the 4th stone,...
...his safety would be compromised.
I know that you and Zhuang Rui are close.
That has nothing to do with this.
I just think we need to focus on Qin Haoran and Xiaoma.
Not on someone we need clues from.
Either it's evidence on the Qin family or clues on Xiaoma.
...there is no substantial progress.
Zhuang Rui is a patient and we'll make sure he's safe.
However,what if? I mean,just imagine.
If Zhuang Rui dies due to his illness,...
...all our leads will be.....
I'm sure Zhuang Rui doesn't want this to happen.
There are no "what-ifs".
Why can't you understand this,Feifei?
The Golden Eyes case is not just about Zhuang Rui alone.
It involves China and Japan.
If we lose this lead,safety of the whole society is at risk.
If the suspect finds the secret of the Golden Eyes...
...and mass replicate it,...
...the entire jade and gold industry...
...will be in total chaos!
Feifei,listen to me.
You can't use your emotions to make decisions...
...in your job. -It's not like that.
What do you mean it's not like that?
Don't let emotions cloud your judgements. Do these things.
Firstly,contact the hospital and find ways to cure the Golden Eyes.
Next,a task force will be set up to investigate...
...Qin Haoran,Xiaoma and the 4th stone.
Listen,if there isn't any substantial progress...
...within this week,...
...Xiaozhao will take over the Golden Eyes case.
I will also prepare the plan for the fake stone.
Consult Zhuang Rui about this idea.
Yes,understood.
I'll make a breakthrough from Xiaoma.
One more thing.
Finish up your investigation report.
Understood.
Why are you here?
I just came back. Why are you so jumpy?
Well,I'm writing something to Miss Xiaojia.
All right. Continue.
What..... You made copies of grandfather's notebook?
What? I did it to find a cure for you.
How does this help?
We can at least notice a pattern.
There are accounts of Nakagawa Yohei's relapse.
For example,...
...on 17th October,...
...he had eggs for breakfast and fell ill at noon.
What does this tells us?
Food high in protein...
...could worsen the illness.
Thank you,but Nakagawa Ryosuke's father is allergic to eggs.
Perhaps you should call Miss Xiaojia.
I'm afraid your relationship will be unstable.
Xiaorui,are you home?
Uncle De?
Uncle De is here. I'll get the door.
There's always someone better than you.
Since I've already made copies,...
...I might as well make more copies.
After the call with you, the supermoon appeared.
I thought I was lucky...
...but we encountered dust storm in the desert...
...and we were also poisoned.
It's a good thing we found the cave temple.
Exploring the desert...
...has always been dangerous.
It's true that you had some troubles on this trip...
...but you're back now. You're very lucky.
Next time,if you're going on any expeditions,...
...please choose somewhere safe.
Actually,our trip to Gansu is not an expedition or exploration.
40 years ago,my grandfather and a member of his team...
...went missing there.
I went there to find an answer.
Well.....
My grandfather and the whole expedition team...
...perished in the desert.
It was underneath Feng Quan's tomb.
Uncle De, I remember you told me...
...that Feng Quan had special powers...
...because he released a turtle.
That's what it says in the Eight King's article,too.
I found my grandfather's notebook on this Gansu trip.
It's written that Feng Quan didn't have the Golden Eyes...
...after letting a turtle go.
He has the Golden Eyes because of an accident.
So the myth about Feng Quan's discerning eyes is true.
Exactly. Besides that,...
...Feng Quan's life story was written on his tombstone.
We confirmed this with one of his descendants.
It means that Feng Quan's legend is true.
Feng Quan's extraordinary vision...
...is called the Golden Eyes.
The Tamamoku stones that he had...
...could bring about extraordinary ability.
I can't believe such things exist.
He left behind a few pieces of it.
Perhaps these stones allow one to possess extraordinary powers.
This was recorded in my grandfather's notebook.
They explored...
...Feng Quan's tomb.
One of the members, Nakagawa Yohei,...
...met with an accident.
As a result, he has the Golden Eyes.
However,...
...there's a young man, Xiaoma,amongst them.
When he knew the secret, he became evil and greedy.
He went after my grandfather and Nakagawa Yohei.
My grandfather died because of this.
With more valuable treasure...
...comes greater danger.
This has been the way since the past.
So,have you found...
...the one called Xiaoma?
This is our problem now.
We've been investigating.
However,no one in the expedition is called Xiaoma.
No one with the surname Ma,too.
Uncle De,look at this picture.
Perhaps you see something from this?
All the members of the expedition team here?
Yes.
Who took this picture?
Could it be Xiaoma?
If Xiaoma was not part of the expedition team,...
...could he be a local?
Uncle De,you're right. I'll ask Feifei to investigate.
Chief Ding,I've talked to the evidence team.
Xiaoma could be a local guide for the expedition team.
So he couldn't have been in the picture or in any records.
Village census 40 years ago weren't complete or standardized.
It won't be easy for Gansu police to locate this man.
This is difficult.
Then I'll go to Gansu.
I'll check nearby villages.
Okay. I'll await your news.
There will be a breakthrough this time.
Hurry up then. Remember,safety first.
Miss Qin,you have many joint injuries.
You can't delay physical therapy any longer.
Or else,...
...you may have permanent damage on your body.
I told you I'm tired.
I want to be left alone.
Even if there's permanent damage,...
...it's my choice.
You don't have to take responsibility.
Doctor,thank you.
Give me a minute with Miss Qin.
Mr. Nakagawa,I'm tired.
I know.
Your heart is weary.
I've always been curious.
You're the only heir of the Qin family...
...but you're different from daughters from rich families.
You're calm and matured.
It turns out you're not Qin Haoran's birth daughter.
With an adoptive father like him,it's indeed tiring.
You made a background check on me?
I want to give you a new identity...
...so I had to find out...
...the truth about Qin Xuanbing's background.
Qin Xuanbing has died in the cave temple that collapsed.
Compared to becoming a young lady in Qin family,...
...the identity of Kojima Maki will make you at ease.
You'll feel safer,too.
Safer?
What do you mean?
You know too much.
To Qin Haoran, you've sided with Zhuang Rui.
I'm sure he doesn't want you to live.
I know what Brother Gui did to you...
...in the desert.
Brother Gui is only one of my father's men.
He doesn't represent my father.
My relationship with Qin Haoran is complicated.
I planted a few men...
...near the cave temple.
After the collapse, Qin Haoran sent men to ask around.
About Zhuang Rui and the Tamamoku stone.
However,your name was never brought up.
Qin Haoran never intended to bring your bones back.
You know nothing.
Qin Haoran tried to save my father...
...and hurt his leg and now he's in a crutch.
I owe him that much.
Of course I have to return the favour.
Is your birth father, Zheng Chuan?
He founded Ai Xi Jewellery that took Kiev by storm.
My father gave me this...
...as my 7th birthday present.
No painting! You're a liar! Where's my present?
You didn't prepare anything!
Why would I lie to you?
Have a seat.
Hold it.
This is your present.
Thank you,father.
Happy birthday, my beloved daughter.
Qin Haoran and Zheng Chuan were close. They went to Beijing...
...to meet an investor,right?
Yes.
Father brought me along to Beijing.
However,he and Qin Haoran was attacked by a rival...
...on the way.
Attacked by a rival.
Did Qin Haoran tell you that?
After Zheng Chuan's death,...
...Xi Huang Jewellery didn't receive any projects from Beijing.
There was no document about...
...the meeting in Beijing.
I know what you're thinking.
However,I saw Qin Haoran getting shot...
...with my own eyes.
Miss,Mr. Zheng and Mr. Qin's meeting...
...should be over by now.
Father!
My father is inside!
Miss,it's dangerous!
Don't come over! Call the police!
Hurry!
Father!
What you saw...
...was the outcome.
You didn't see the alleged rival.
You didn't see how Zheng Chuan died.
The outcome is Zheng Chuan died and Qin Haoran survived...
...and took you in.
No.
It's not possible.
Qin Haoran has no reason to harm my father.
They were friends.
My father's death doesn't benefit him at all.
He even injured his leg.
Doesn't benefit him at all?
You were just a child.
A child's testimony is the easiest to manipulate.
He earned your trust and used your testimony...
...to escape police suspicions.
He later adopted you...
...and took over Zheng Chuan's Ai Xi Jewellery.
Isn't this benefit?
Do you have any proof?
If I do,we would be in court right now.
When I found out about this, I had to tell you.
The 4 bodyguards that Qin Haoran took along to Beijing...
...was fired within a year.
When Qin Haoran was reshuffling Ai Xi's Jewellery management,...
...one of your father's partners criticized Qin Haoran publicly,...
...saying that he warned Zheng Chuan...
...that Qin Haoran is a cunning person...
...who will eventually kill Zheng Chuan.
Doesn't this tells us something?
If I don't tell you these,...
...I'm afraid that when you meet Qin Haoran again,...
...you'll end up just like your father!
Enough! Don't say anymore.
I'm sorry.
I know this is too much for you.
However,I don't want to see you lying on this bed.
You have a choice.
If you want to investigate your father's death,I'll help you.
If you don't want to face all this,...
...you can choose...
...to come with me to Japan.
I'm waiting for you...
...to stand up for yourself.
Leader Zhang.
Officer Zhang,I'm sorry for troubling you again.
It's all right, but this case...
...is over 40 years old so it won't be easy.
It's okay. This is good enough.
There're about 600 villagers in 3 villages.
I don't believe that I can't find any clues.
Okay.
Excuse me,I have a question to ask you.
I'm sorry. -Thank you.
Hi,do you know the expedition team that was here  years ago?
I don't know. Ask other people. -Thank you.
Hi.
Are you from this village? -No,I'm not from here.
Thank you.
Don't force yourself.
You can do it.
Miss,are you looking for the wrong person?
Everyone in this village has the surname Li.
There are no other surnames. -Aunt,are you sure?
Yes,I'm sure.
Wife.
Have you forgotten?
There was someone who married into our village.
Old Liu married Widow Liu who was from another village.
That widow even had a young son.
How can I remember that?
When I married you,...
...Old Liu had already died.
You're right. -Uncle.
Do you remember the surname of Widow Liu's son?
I think it's Ma.
That child was stubborn. He refused to change his surname.
Old Li complained to me about it.
After Widow Liu died, Xiaoma left the village.
Do you remember where he went?
I don't remember about that.