The Golden Eyes
Episode 8
He bought a raw stone like this.
There was jade in it...
...but he was too excited...
...and cut it into pieces. The jade cost RMB8 million...
...but it was gone like that. -How much was it?
It's RMB8 million?
What a roller coaster ride.
What happened to him after that?
He's fine now.
He even saved on cremation cost...
...as he was buried.
Was it so serious? -He lost everything.
The Ru ware incident wasn't too bad...
...in comparison.
How much do you want to spend today?
RMB5 million? That's great!
I mean RMB5,000. -RMB50 million?
No,I mean RMB5,000 only.
RMB5,000?
If that's the case,you shouldn't have come here.
No,Uncle De said we should...
...watch and listen instead of talking and buying.
Yes,he is right. You may have a look since it's free.
Look at this. This was already appraised.
You can see the blue patterns in it.
It's true. -You're right.
Am I doing it correctly?
Yes.
Don't we have a machine to see...
...the inner part of the stone?
No,we don't have it.
Did you see this?
Indeed!
Can you understand it?
You've brought an expert here. -I'm not an expert.
Why don't you join us?
Since you're lucky,...
...you should have a look downstairs.
He's quite funny.
He's like my friend...
...who was buried.
Ladies and gentlemen,please be seated.
The auction will be starting soon.
Welcome to the auction.
The first item for today is Raw Stone No. 3,...
...which is also our highlight of the day.
It was found in a jadeite mine in Myanmar.
The starting price is RMB4 million.
It must not be less than RMB500,000 for each bid.
It's not expensive.
Let's bid together.
RMB4 million!
RMB4 million is accepted.
Mr. Zhuang offers RMB4 million.
Young man,do you think...
...you can get the stone at the starting price?
Stop pulling the same trick you did at Panjiayuan.
RMB5 million.
RMB5 million is accepted.
RMB5.5 million.
RMB6 million.
RMB6 million is accepted.
Is there anyone else who would like to make a bid?
Xiao Zhao,...
...how's the situation there?
I'll have a look at the exhibition hall.
Okay.
I must get the stone today.
Bing Bing has just come back.
I have to give it to her.
RMB7 million.
It is the auction of Raw Stone No. 3.
The highest bid is RMB7 million at the moment.
Mr. Xu has offered RMB7 million.
Does Mr. Zhuang want to make a bid?
RMB8 million.
RMB8 million. -No.
We don't have RMB8 million!
You can't get RMB8 million even if you sell the Yunlong pot!
Although it looks nice from the surface,...
...but no one knows the outcome.
We may lose our money.
It is the auction...
...of Raw Stone No. 3 from Myanmar.
What do you think? -It looks albumen-like...
...with high transparency. It should be a good stone.
As long as the jade is no less than 4cm,...
...we may still make a fortune.
I have no idea anyway. -He who offers RMB8 million...
...was invited by Mr. Gu Tian Feng.
He is Mr. Zhuang Rui.
Mr. Zhuang is new in antiquarian.
He's dabbling in jade industry now.
It seems that Mr. Zhuang is determined to get the jade...
...to make a mark using this half-bid raw stone.
Is there anyone else who would like to make a bid?
RMB8 million,going once.
RMB8 million,going twice.
RMB9 million.
Mr. Xu offers RMB9 million.
RMB9 million is accepted.
Do you want to make another bid,Mr. Zhuang?
RMB9 million,going once.
RMB9 million,going twice.
RMB9 million.
Sold.
Congratulations,Xu Jewellery,...
...for getting the stone at RMB9 million.
Congratulations,Mr. Xu Wei. -Bing Bing,...
...although it's expensive,...
...it's just nice as your gift.
It's okay.
You made a great effort to get the stone.
Keep it for yourself.
Xiao Zhao,I found a suspicious target.
Let's go for a drink for celebration.
It's okay.
My heart almost stopped beating just now. If no one continued,...
...the stone.....
Why are you still looking at it?
Are you addicted to it?
This is not good. Those over there are better.
Don't be sad.
We have no money to buy the stone anyway.
This is good.
It's not about the money.
The thing is you have to get a good stone.
This.....
I want to get this stone.
No,you..... -Let me have a look.
Don't make a decision in haste.
There is jade here...
...but it has too many cracks.
We should just get one from there.
Let's get this. Make the payment.
It costs RMB3,000!
Can I simply take a stone and sell it?
How much is this? -It's RMB3,000.
It's only RMB3,000. You will still have RMB2,000.
Buy me a meal tonight.
This..... I.....
What rubbish is this?
Stop!
Who are you?
Why did you run? -You're chasing after me.
Bring him back.
Mr. Yu,you should have trusted me.
The police came right after you left.
Were you stalking me?
Fine,I'll give you another chance. Where shall we meet?
Are you playing a game?
You should have known that...
...stone gambling is different from antiques.
You won't be as lucky as you were in Panjiayuan.
Who told you that?
Mr. Gu.
Why can't one get lucky in this? -You're right.
There're plenty of chances to get lucky.
It depends on your luck.
Let me have a look.
Xiao Zhuang,it's hard for you...
...to strike gold with this stone.
Without cutting the stone,...
...how can we confirm that it's not a good stone?
You mean you want to cut the stone?
What kind of jade can he get from that stone?
It's the same for everyone.
If there's jade,...
...it would be a miracle.
Don't be so pessimistic.
Didn't you say that some stones look good...
...but there's nothing in them?
However,there may be good jade in those which look bad.
Yes,nothing is impossible in stone gambling.
However,...
...there is no moss on the stone...
...and it has low transparency.
There are cracks on it,too.
It's hard to get good jade out of it.
It's as likely as...
...me having long-pointed teeth and you having horns.
Here you go.
Xiao Zhuang,we'll cut your stone first.
Xiao Zhuang,it's common to lose money in this field.
No worries,I won't lose the money.
We shouldn't be afraid of losing money...
...but we have to learn a lesson from it. What do you think?
Yes.
It's going to start. Are you nervous?
It's fun because it's nerve-wracking.
Are you excited?
No,...
...I can't take it.
All right.
You still don't have horns.
If there's no jade after the first cut,that's it.
Grandfather,are you going to continue?
No jade is found from the first cut. Just throw it away.
Mr. Xu,why don't you cut your stone now?
We must be patient. He's not done with his stone yet.
Why don't you give him some encouragement?
It's quite impossible to find jade in here.
Even if there is jade in it,...
...it may be at the centre of the stone.
Let's follow the line I draw...
...and cut it open from the middle.
Calm down.
You're so great,Mr. Gu!
Now I have long,pointed teeth.
Do you see my horns?
Mr. Gu,like you've said,...
...it's exciting and nerve-wracking.
Why don't we cut it again based on your third line?
Heed my advice. Stop.
We shouldn't be greedy.
It is worth around RMB100,000.
Stop cutting it. You may lose everything if it's cut wrongly.
Have you made up your mind?
Aren't you going to stop now?
Let's cut it one more time.
Good. You're just like me.
We'll cut it again based on the line I draw.
Okay.
Go.
Sir,cut the third line.
Mr. Gu,you're great.
You have turned a trash into a gem.
Don't be too excited. There is nothing great about it.
Have a look at mine later.
Mr. Xu,you're very confident.
What if there isn't much jade in it?
Won't you feel embarrassed by then?
You're depending on your luck but I'm depending on my ability.
Have you seen glass types of jade?
You should have a look later.
You're great,Mr. Gu!
You're great!
It's a success!
You're so lucky!
You managed to get jade out of a humble-looking stone.
Behind the mist-like crystal is a whole piece...
...of ice-type jade,with a fine shade of green!
Mr. Xu,I don't know much about jade. What do you mean?
I'll offer you RMB8 million. -RMB10 million.
Go away. Let him enjoy himself.
How can you sell it at only RMB10 million?
I'll offer you RMB18 million,is it okay?
Hold on. All of you are rich.
Let's discuss it.
This way,please. -RMB3,000.
RMB18 million.
Mr. Xu,...
...it's your turn now.
RMB18 million is a big amount.
Have a look.
I think it's not the highest price.
Cut it.
You can't increase the price anymore,right?
Let's give in to each other.
This is even better.
Mr. Xu,I'll offer you RMB10 million.
I'll offer you RMB10 million. -Mr. Xu,it's a good price.
You may get a net profit of RMB1 million.
I don't care about RMB1 million.
Cut it again.
He doesn't care about it.
Mr. Xu,let's have a talk.
Have a look.
Mr. Xu!
Mr. Xu,I'll offer you RMB20 million.
I'll offer you RMB30 million. Mr. Xu,please sell it to me.
I'll offer you RMB30 million. -He's so lucky.
Mr. Xu,...
...RMB30 million is a good price for a non-ice-type jade.
If I were you,I would have sold it.
How can you compare yourself to me?
Cut it again.
If it is green again,...
...it'll worth more than RMB30 million.
It's such a pity.
There is only an inch of jade.
It's gone.
Are you sure? Let me have a look.
There is only a bit of it.
It's gone!
My friend,no offence.
You should have listened to us.
You would have gotten RMB30 million.
Let me have a look at this RMB30 million stone.
How can it be gone like that?
Keep it properly. -Mr. Xu is different from us.
Yes.
It's only RMB30 million for a game.
You may take it.
He gave it to me...
...but it's even worse than mine.
Okay,I got it.
It's such a pity.
Are you sure it's your first time? You're so lucky.
Yes,it's just dumb luck.
If the stone was sold at the price of RMB6,000,...
...I wouldn't have bought it.
Do you know the reason?
It's because I only had RMB3,000.
You're still counting it. You've counted it for a few times.
Brother Ma,please stop the car.
What's wrong?
I want to count it again at the ATM.
Are you okay?
Brother Ma,let's have a gathering tonight.
I'll buy you a meal.
Sure.
Xiao Rui,...
...we're going to make a fortune.
Since we're getting rich,...
...we should get a car...
...and a new house.
A new house?
Isn't our house still in good condition?
Where are you staying?
We're staying in basement.
Basement?
I think it's spacious.
How big is it?
It's dozens of ping.
That's...
...as big as my bathroom.
How can you live in basement?
I have an empty siheyuan.
You may stay there.
It's inappropriate,right?
No,it isn't.
Brother Ma,we're rich. We won't take advantage of you.
We'll pay you the rental.
We're fair.
Is it so bad to live in the basement?
Zhuang Rui,I was busy just now. I didn't hear the call.
What's wrong?
It doesn't matter. I wanted to buy you a meal.
Why don't we go for supper?
Sure.
Why are you alone? Where is your boss?
Our boss has something on today. He can't make it.
He can't make it?
Is it because he is guilty?
You all are more cunning than us.
We risked our lives for you...
...but you couldn't care less about our lives.
You're not loyal at all.
Mr. Yu,don't be angry.
What about your loyalty?
You're paid to work for us.
You're clear that...
...you have nothing.
You didn't get the jade at the pawn shop.
There's no jade at the tomb of Duke Huan of Qi either.
Even so,...
...we still pay you.
This is our loyalty.
Have a look...
...at the money.
You're sensible.
Tell your boss that it is right for her to pay us.
It is compensation for our emotional distress.
Let me give you a formal notice.
Unhealthy food like instant noodles...
...should disappear from our world starting today.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Is this your father?
It's my grandfather.
I was told about the stories of my grandfather since young...
...but I have never met him.
Before I slept,my father would read...
...one of my grandfather's books.
Was it Grimm's Fairy Tales...
...or Monkey King and the White Bone Demon?
It's The Geology of China.
He studied geology while you studied history.
Both subjects are boring.
Are these left behind by your grandfather?
Let's bring them with us.
I'm not sure whether he left these behind...
...as my father said my grandfather was still alive.
We displayed all the photos of my grandfather's...
...geological exploration at home.
My father said my grandfather was adventurous...
...and wouldn't die easily.
He just changed his name and moved to somewhere...
...to have a different life.
I also believe that heroes live on.
Heroes live on!
Hurry up!
Are you free this weekend? There is a jade seminar.
Are you interested? -Thank you,Mr. Gu.
You're welcome.
Qiming and I got these stones...
...from our first stone gambling.
We almost lost all our money.
We cut the stone into two...
...and made a pair of pendants to remind ourselves that...
...we shouldn't think of getting rich overnight...
...and that we should be down-to-earth.
I didn't expect that...
...after so many years,...
...Qiming is gone...
...but I'm able to see the pendants again.
I didn't expect you to be Qiming's grandson.
Were you close to my grandfather?
We were best friends.
He went to Gansu for an excursion...
...but he didn't come back.
An excursion? Did he contact you?
What happened after that?
Hold on.
I was supposed to go for the excursion...
...but I hurt my leg.
So he went on my behalf.
I promised to buy him drinks when he came back.
I didn't expect that...
...he would be gone.
We kept in touch through letters after he went to Gansu.
I got to know his news through the letters.
I didn't understand...
...why my father always said that...
...my grandfather would be back.
He said by the time he's back,...
...the three of us would go for an archaeological trip.
However,there has been no news...
...throughout the years.
Qiming is gone,but I'm still alive.
I can bring you around for archaeological trips,too.
After losing touch with him,I'd been looking for your family...
...but all of you had moved away.
It's good to see you today.
If not,I wouldn't rest easy for the rest of my life.
Grandfather!
Xiao Rui,you're here,too.
Xiao Yu,Zhuang Rui will be your brother from today onwards.
What's wrong? Qiming and I were very close.
I'll treat his grandson like my own.
Have a seat.
I'll be your god-grandfather,okay?
Good! Call me grandfather.
Grandfather.
That's the way!
Xiao Yu,call him brother.
Are you serious,grandfather?
I'm older than Xiao Rui.
Stop talking nonsense! Is it important?
Both of you are my grandsons anyway. Are you going to call him?
Since we're all here today,...
...let's have a drink to celebrate it.
I would like to...
...go back and read my grandfather's letters.