The Golden Eyes
Episode 44
A'Lai.
Father,you're back. How is everything?
Prepare some water for everyone to wash up.
Sure.
Is there any water?
Over here.
The terrains here are complicated and it's difficult to search.
Luckily,we brought a lot of people this time.
We can search separately.
Then,we will have a bigger chance of finding it.
We have to examine this map.
Could it be here,Miss?
What a letdown! It's an adventure...
...and this popped up suddenly and we failed.
Was the Qin family bandits in their previous life?
They are bandits.
They took whatever we had.
Couldn't they be more creative?
Luckily,we came out of the cave safely.
That's right.
Luckily,Xiao Rui is fine. We can figure out others in the future.
What is there to figure out? We don't have the map.
Nevermind. The map was taken. Xiao Rui is quite upset.
When you go in later, don't pull a long face.
Give him some positive energy.
Let's go.
Let's rest for a while first.
We can think about other stuff tomorrow.
Hamu Basin is in the north...
...and Qinglong Mountain is in the south.
Aoyu City is in north-east and Liujin Town is in south-east.
To the east of Liujin Town is Kasamu Oasis.
In the middle is Sangmu'Er Canyon.
In the west are desert and poplar forest.
What is this?
A map?
Was it the one taken from the cave?
That's great. We were talking about what to do earlier on.
You even drew it out.
What is it,Xiao Rui? Are you having headache again?
Stop drawing. Just rest for a while.
No. I must draw it...
...while I still remember it or I will forget after I wake up.
That's right. Besides,...
...the Qin family obtained the map earlier than us.
They may have already departed by now.
If we have the map now,we still have time to go to Feng Quan Tomb.
They have more time to spare than us. We have to do it now.
We can leave after I pack. -There's no hurry.
The map covers a large area.
We are not able to confirm the whereabouts of Feng Quan Tomb.
I can only draw a rough sketch.
Aoyu City.
Kasa..... What are these places?
Look,this is our current position.
From the map,there are basins and valleys from north to south,...
...desert and poplar forest from east to west.
The terrain is too complicated.
It's difficult to search.
Besides,we don't have any clues on where Feng Quan Tomb is.
This means even if we have this map,...
...chances are slim for us.
That's not necessarily true.
How is the progress?
We have successfully entered the cave,...
...but we were ambushed by the Qin family.
The map of Feng Quan Tomb was taken away.
How is Zhuang Rui?
He is not well. He fainted when we left the cave.
However,after he woke up,he drew the map from his memories.
We're preparing to move again.
Protect Zhuang Rui. Report to me if there's anything.
Understood.
I have marked...
...four possible locations of Feng Quan Tomb on the map.
Send two teams to search separately.
Understood. -We are now at this location.
Liujin Town. To the north is Aoyu City.
Send someone to examine here thoroughly.
It's the most prosperous area. Perhaps Feng Quan Tomb is here.
Apart from that,...
...send another team over here.
Kasamu Desert.
There's a place called Kubuqi there.
It's very close to Liujin Town.
It is more likely that Feng Quan Tomb is in this place.
Understood.
If there's nothing in these two places,...
...both the teams must immediately go to Hamu Basin...
...and Sangmu'er Canyon. -Okay.
I'll send people over there now.
Wait.
If you still can't find it in these places,...
...then you can only search towards the west.
Miss,we seem to have forgotten a place.
Lao Zeng Inn.
Zhuang Rui and others have lost the map. They must have plans.
This is an opportunity for us.
No. Our goal is to find Feng Quan Tomb.
Other than that,any action will be irrelevant.
Miss,Zhuang Rui..... -Please focus on the main point.
Miss,Zhuang Rui is too cunning.
It's the perfect time to kill them now to prevent...
...any untoward incident. -Don't you understand my words?
Hurry up and move.
Mr. Feng!
I had searched for you.
Mr. Feng,is your hand getting better?
The doctor says it will heal after half a month.
Don't worry.
Mr. Zhuang,when I came over here to look for you,...
...you went to the desert.
Did everything go well?
Good things require effort. We still need to work hard.
Right,I heard from A'Lai that you have something to give me.
I have something to ask you.
You came to the factory to save me that day.
I asked you how you knew there's a Feng character in the Sancai.
Was it true that you were lucky?
Actually,when I was in Gui City, I knocked down a Sancai.
I saw this character on it.
We inherited this jade from our ancestors.
It's been our family treasure for over 1,000 years.
It's the Feng family's most prized possession.
However,I don't know whether I should believe it.
What do you think,Mr. Zhuang?
Mr. Zhuang.
Mr. Zhuang!
Like you've said,this is indeed a priceless treasure.
It seems that you can see many things which I don't see.
Mr. Feng. This is left by Feng Quan.
You said that it's your family treasure.
So,you are a descendant of Feng Quan.
It seems that you also know Feng Quan.
I'd made the right decision to come here today.
You're the one we have been waiting for generations.
Along with the inheritance of this jade,there's a piece of advice.
Whoever that has the same vision power as Feng Quan...
...and is capable of identifying the value of the jade...
...will be its real owner.
Now it belongs to you.
This.....
This is too much of a coincidence.
I don't believe it initially. I thought it got passed down...
...and may fall into the wrong hands.
How can there be such a person in this world?
Well,I couldn't simply throw away what's left by my ancestors.
Now I finally believe...
...that such a person truly exists in this world.
Feng Quan was indeed an unusual person.
His story and experiences sounded like a fairytale.
You have helped me a lot by giving me this jade.
Thank you. You're very kind.
You're welcome. It is our honour.
I have finally met the legendary man...
...whom my ancestors failed to find then.
We're destined to meet.
You're right. It's indeed fated.
By the way,Mr. Feng,what are the other stories...
...about Feng Quan?
I know very little about this person.
If not because of you, I would have...
...forgotten about this jade.
The mystery left by my ancestors...
...will have to be solved by you.
I'll make a move first.
Eat more.
I know.
I know Feng Quan Tomb's location.
Miss.
We received news that our men found nothing in Hamu Basin.
On top of the current Qinglong Valley,...
...there's nothing in the four possible locations...
...of Feng Quan Tomb.
Continue to go to the front. Search further.
Okay.
Get ready!
Hello,Jia.
Fei Fei,how is your progress? Do you miss me?
I really miss you,Ms. Xiao Jia.
The natural landscape here is very beautiful.
There's a desert inside Gobi and an oasis in the desert.
Although there aren't many people,it's very majestic.
If I have the chance,I must bring you here to experience it.
Why is it you? Where is Fei Fei?
She is not important. -What are you talking about?
Ms. Xiao Jia,...
...I haven't heard your lovely voice for a long time.
Why do you call me suddenly?
Who is calling you? I'm just worried about Xiao Rui's health.
I'm here. What are you worried about?
I'm very smart. I'll certainly protect everyone.
With your body size, if you're in danger,...
...it's difficult for you to even save yourself.
That's impossible. Ms. Xiao Jia, I'm responsible...
...for the journey, the people and the resources.
Ms. Xiao Jia,what happened to you? Are you all right?
Fine,that's enough. -I'll lead them back triumphantly!
I'll call you later.
Huangfu Yun,you're really thick-skinned.
How dare you claim to be the main person-in-charge.
I'm saying that so that Ms. Xiao Jia can rest easy.
Besides,I have to be strong in front of Ms. Xiao Jia.
I have to portray myself as strong.
I need to do that so that she'll marry me.
You...
...boast too much.
Actually,it's good. Ms. Xiao Jia will be less worried.
She's been worried these few days.
At least,the situation is stable now.
We also have a direction.
We were still worried yesterday...
...but we are on our way today.
Xiao Rui, I think you are capable.
I'll give you a 'like'.
Use your magical eyes to look at my passionate red heart.
Don't give me a 'like'. Praise Feng Quan instead.
He was brilliant.
There's a whole wide world behind a small piece of jade.
It's really strange. I've examined it thoroughly.
There's nothing unusual. It's just a normal jade.
All right. We might be able to reach Feng Quan Tomb...
...before the Qin family does. -That's right.
The fools will be all confused now.
They may be wandering somewhere.
It's useless for them to plot anything against us now.
Brother Gui,they're in the poplar forest. Cars can't get through.
Do I still need to follow them?
Go on. -Okay.
Miss,drink some water.
They are here.
They are already moving.
Zhuang Rui and three others are heading here in a car.
We guessed right.
This big canyon is the only place we have yet to search.
We spent many days to get here.
How did they find the place so easily?
I suspect Zhuang Rui and others have found new clues.
Miss,how about this?
We will follow them to where we want to go.
Is it possible?
Send people to follow them. -Yes.
How much further?
They are in the canyon. Cars will draw unwanted attention.
Do I still need to follow them?
You might be exposed. You may leave.
Yes.
Miss,look.
Are you certain? -Yes,look.
He's holding a map.
However,Zhuang Rui is very cunning.
Is it possible that he is tricking us?
Miss,...
...I'll bring people to kill him now and take the map.
There's no need for that.
They will be alerted if you go now.
Miss,that won't happen.
No. Just send people to watch Zhuang Rui and follow him....
...to find Feng Quan Tomb.
Why do you need to kill them?
Miss,we can let him live. Let's tie him up...
...so that he will not create trouble for us in the future.
Miss,if you have any concern,I'll do it.
What do you want to do? I know what to do.
I don't need you to boss me around.
It's really bad now.
Miss. -I have stomach ache last night.
Was it what you ate? -I starve at the sight of food.
I think you like the cricket more.
How about this? I'll give you this cricket.
I never knew that...
...others might need me,too.
...I'm capable of helping someone.
I've never suspected you before.
I've always believed in you.
You befriended me in order to use me...
...to obtain the jade.
Am I right?
Miss.
Boss said that the temperature in the desert changes drastically.
You have to take good care of yourself.
Drink some ginger tea and rest early.
Get the map.
Zhuang Rui's life doesn't matter.
Go. -Yes.
What do you want to do?
Miss,...
...I thought you'd sleep a little longer thanks to the ginger tea.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
As for what I want to do,...
...I'm going to do something you should have done earlier.
You aren't allowed to hurt Zhuang Rui.
Who doesn't allow it? Do you?
If not because of you,Zhuang Rui would have died a long time ago!
Miss,when I obtain the map,...
...I shall apologise to you again.
Brother Gui,we are in position.
Are you ready?
Yes.
If you dare to lay a finger on Zhuang Rui,I won't forgive you.
Action. -Don't!
Brother Gui. -Zhuang Rui!
One died and another was hurt. The others ran away.
It's all right,as long as we have Zhuang Rui.
It's an impostor!
Bring him away! If the impostor is here,the real deal...
...won't get to escape. Let's go! -Yes.
I knew Zhuang Rui wouldn't have been caught so easily.
Go straight from here and we'll soon arrive at the destination.
At our speed,we will find the cave before morning.
We're quite lucky. We didn't bump into the Qin family.
It seems that our plan is effective.
Starting from now, we'll act separately.
The four of us will move around the canyon...
...to attract the Qin family's attention...
...and buy time.
You'll head straight to the cave in the west from outside...
...to search for Feng Quan Tomb.
The Qin family is prepared. It's too dangerous to show up...
...in their monitored area.
I suggest for us to distract the Qin family while you...
...search for Feng Quan Tomb. -No,if they attack you,...
...you'll be in danger.
Feng Quan Tomb is very unique.
We know nothing about its location and inner structure.
Only Zhuang Rui can do this.
We are confident in distracting them...
...and buying more time for you.
Don't worry. We'll maintain a safe distance...
...and arrive at the gathering point on time.
Be careful.
We will go there.
I hope Xiao Dao and others are fine.
They're great fighters. I think they can handle it.
They will be safe.
Let's go.
Listen. We're going to act separately now.
I'm going to inform Zhuang Rui. You must keep them here.
Okay.
Be careful. -Okay.
Okay. Be careful.
Let's go.
I'm having stomach ache. -Miss,how are you?
It's here.
Here?
Is this Feng Quan Tomb?
Isn't this a sundial?
There's no one here. What's the sundial for?
This looks like a sundial but it's not.
It has an extra needle compared to a sundial.
This sundial may contain the secret of Feng Quan Tomb.
Was Feng Quan a teacher?
He even left an equation here.
It seems that it's pointless to move this needle.
It's not pointless. He's doing it wrong.
How should I do it?
Look.
What? -Feng yi wei xiang.
This is Small Seal Script, the calligraphy of Qin dynasty.
You're a history graduate. Translate it for us.
What's written here?
Feng yi wei xiang.
He yi shi zhi.
...ming ming an an, wei shi he wei.
Feng Quan didn't just leave an equation.
He left us a comprehension of ancient text.
It's Qu Yuan's Heavenly Questions, part of Chu Ci.
It may be the answer to this sundial.
It roughly talked about how the universe was formed,...
...how to differentiate light and darkness,...
...how the light in the day and the darkness at night came about.
What does this have to do with the sundial?
Sundial represents time. We should be asking this instead.
What's the relationship between these words and the time?
There are 12 hours of day and 12 hours of night.
In other words, day and night are similar.
When you add both the day and night,...
...doesn't it mean the whole day?
A day means 24 hours.
It is a day.
This is the answer.
It's open.
What a strange mechanism. So the folks in Qin dynasty were clever.
What are you talking about?
It's our intelligence combined.
Let's go.
Zhuang Rui!
Boss,we got the information. We are leaving now.
There will not be any problem.
Brother Gui! -What is it?
Brother Gui,I was ambushed and Miss escaped.
What? She must have informed Zhuang Rui.
Let's leave now. Let's go!
You're quick.
You're alone. Where are your people?
Don't get me wrong. I don't want to hurt you.
Why are you here?
I want to tell you that your plan was exposed.
Your impostor was shot and caught. Brother Gui and others are coming.
You should go. -What? Someone was caught?
Someone posed as me? What do you mean?
Maybe Xiao Dao's followers wanted to distract them.
So they got their people to pretend to be us.
Yes. -They're shot and captured?
Are they in danger? How many were caught?
He alone was caught.
Brother Gui and others are on their way here. You should go.
Stop pretending. Isn't Brother Gui your follower?
Why didn't he come with you?
Brother Gui disobeyed me...
...and even held me captive. I escaped.
Why did he do that?
Brother Gui has wanted to kill you along this journey.
I kept stopping him.
He caught the impostor yesterday and drugged my drink.
After I slept,he tortured that guy...
...and found out about your location.
Even so,why are you informing us?
You kept following us and took the map in the cave.
You wanted to be the first to find the tomb,no?
I want to find Feng Quan Tomb...
...to complete the task my father assigned me.
I never intend to hurt you,...
...especially Zhuang Rui.
Trust me,I came here to save you.
You have lied to me many times in the past.
Why should I trust you?
Xiao Dao. -She is not lying.
Ms. Qin was telling the truth.
A'Bu was captured.
Brother Gui will come here soon. We are in danger now.
Are you all right,Xiao Dao?
It's nothing. Qingshan has returned to save them.
Brother Gui have many followers and they're armed.
We must leave immediately.
What are we waiting for? -Wait.
Brother Gui won't arrive right away.
We have to hurry up.
We may be able to find the tomb.
It's all right. It doesn't matter even if they're here.
I'm here.
Me,too.
I'm representing Mr. Nakagawa to protect you...
...and ensure your safely.
Your injury..... -Don't worry,this is nothing.
Okay,let's go.
Ms. Qin,don't think of entering.
If you are injured, your father will be worried.
I did this behind Brother Gui.
With the current situation, I cannot go back now.
Ms. Miao. I want to follow you to enter it.
If you hurt Zhuang Rui,...
...I won't spare you. -I won't hurt him.
I would never do that.