The Golden Eyes
Episode 45
Why is it so dark here?
Xiaorui, I think it's a little scary.
What are all these?
This should be a rock painting that was painted with stone tools.
These patterns match the texture of the rock...
...and thus,present such an irregular pattern.
Did someone come in before us?
They activated the mechanism,...
...hence these rocks fell on the floor.
Goodness! What is that?
If I'm not mistaken,...
...the last team who entered this cave...
...was my grandfather's archaeological team.
Xiaorui,let's hurry and go.
The rocks above us aren't stable and may drop down anytime.
Let's go.
What is it? -The car broke down.
Stupid,hurry and repair it! -Yes.
It's them. They're heading West. They're going after Zhuang Rui.
No,A'Bu isn't there. They've left him at the site.
Why wait? Let's save him. -No.
Since we met them, it's a pity to let them go.
I'll hold them off.
You save A'Bu. Go. -Yes.
Come back,don't chase then! We have an important task to do.
Hurry!
Hurry and get in the car!
Xiaorui,there are many doors. Which goes to Feng Quan's Tomb?
The structure here.
Look at the structure here.
Does it look like the Bagua Zhen?
So?
Bagua Zhen comes from the Taichi image and presents a subtle array.
Life,injury,hindrance,scenery, death,dismay and opening.
These are the Eight Gates, also known as Bagua Eight Gates.
No,I don't know about those things.
Just tell us which door we should go through.
In the Bagua Zhen,there is a life door and a death door.
This means that not all the doors are safe.
Only 1 door will lead to Feng Quan's Tomb.
Then which is the correct door?
Just trust Xiaorui. Let him do it.
What happened?
I cannot use the Golden Eyes.
What is it?
Are you all right? -Are you all right?
I'm fine. The side effects of the Golden Eyes may have started.
I'll try again.
Are you all right?
Xiaorui,you may be too tired after rushing here.
No,there's a problem with this place.
What is the problem?
I cannot use the Golden Eyes.
Are you saying that...
...Feng Quan designed this Bagua Door...
...so that people with the Golden Eyes cannot use them?
Wait, what does Feng Quan want?
He designed the game but don't allow us to use strategy.
How can you play then?
Zhuang Rui,do you want to rest first before trying again?
Without the Golden Eyes, we cannot find the correct door.
How can we try?
His head is in pain.
The worst is...
...we enter forcefully.
Miss Miao, there are 8 doors here.
Without the Golden Eyes,we can't find the correct door,...
...it's the same as meeting a dead end.
So?
Zhuang Rui's grandfather didn't have the Golden Eyes,too.
He entered Feng Quan's Tomb with his own ability.
We must not find shortcuts when faced with a little danger.
So without the Golden Eyes,can we not survive?
Feifei is right.
If I have it,I am lucky.
If not,it's my fate.
My grandfather didn't have the Golden Eyes but he could enter.
I would be able to do the same.
Since this is a Bagua Door,...
...I will use the Bagua to predict.
Bagua Zhen originated from the Yellow River Map...
...and was created by Fuxi.
Sky,earth,thunder,wind, water,fire,mountain and lake...
...correspond to...
...Eight Gates,life, injury,hindrance,...
...scenery,death, dismay and opening.
Is it easier that way?
No,it's not.
Everything here is not static.
They all change over time.
What is the time now?
10.40 p.m.
It should be 40.
40 represents gold.
Gold is located at the west of the lake.
Lake leads to sky.
This is the sky.
This is the sky. Sky corresponds to the opening.
The sky opposes earth.
Earth should correspond to the death door.
Mountain is the life door.
This is the one.
Xiaorui,you are really good! -Wait.
What is it? -It's not this door.
No. Sky and earth,Qian and Kun.
I also know this general knowledge.
Everything here has been changed.
I think the purpose is to prevent those who enter here...
...from easily finding the life door.
I need to identify the location one by one now.
Move back,everyone.
Eight Gates,...
...obstruction,...
...opening.
Opening.
Follow me!
Brother Gui, there is only 1 way.
They must be inside.
They will not be able to escape this time.
Destroy the wall.
Xiaorui.
Xiaorui, you have eliminated 6 doors.
Now,there are only the life door and...
...the death door left.
One is to go to Feng Quan's Tomb.
The other...
...will lead to our graves.
It's bad. That is Brother Gui.
They cannot open the sundial mechanism...
...so explosives are used. -If they do that,...
...we will not be able to escape later. There's no time.
We must choose the door.
Xiaorui,...
...do you know which is the life door?
I'll go and ascertain now.
Are you mad? You are going to die.
This is the only way.
Xiaoyun!
How can I let you do this kind of thing?
Do you still remember?
I'm your lucky star.
Xiaoyun!
Hurry and follow!
I've told you that I'm your lucky star. Hurry and come here!
Hurry and go! Quick!
Hurry and get in!
Quick!
Why are you not going? -Hurry!
You go. I'll hold them.
Officer Miao,I leave him to you. -What are you saying?
Go! Hurry and go!
Go! Hurry!
Qin Xuanbing!
Qin Xuanbing! Don't move! Stand there!
Are you all right?
Zhuang Rui.
I want to find Feng Quan's Tomb to fulfil the task given by father.
I have never wanted to hurt any of you,...
...especially Zhuang Rui.
Trust me,I'll save you.
You've lied to me many times.
How can I trust you?
Zhuang Rui,...
...we'll go first.
The best solution is to find a professional rescue team here...
...to find her body.
Okay?
Let's go,Xiaorui. Let's go.
Here.
Someone came in here before.
It must be the archaeological team we talked about.
What are we waiting for? Let's hurry and enter.
Why are you not entering?
You have struggled with hardships...
...to find the secret of the Golden Eyes.
Go in.
Maybe there will be things that you want inside.
The price paid is too much.
I have sacrificed a lot.
So you planned all these.
It's not me,...
...it's fate.
It should not be like this.
Then how should it be?
I thought you will understand after going through all these.
Did you design the Bagua Zhen to disable my Golden Eyes?
You still manage to enter.
You really didn't use the Golden Eyes.
Go in.
Go in and have a look.
Maybe there will an answer that you want inside.
These seem to be the archaeological team's items.
Xiaorui,come and have a look.
Look,is this your grandfather?
Could it be that Grandfather Zhuang is.....
From the shape of the pelvis, this should be a woman.
This should be a man.
When Grandfather Zhuang joined the archaeological team,...
...he broke his leg from a fall and there was reinforced steel.
However,these 2 bodies are perfect with no broken bones.
So he should have escaped safely.
Xiaoyun, look at this body's teeth.
Their teeth are sharp...
...and have smaller gaps.
It seems that...
...the enamel damage is not obvious.
It should be around 30 years old.
It should be a member of grandfather's archaeological team.
This body..... -What is wrong with this body?
This body is a bit unusual.
The gaps between teeth are huge...
...and the crown is small.
However, the teeth root is exposed.
This is obviously the teeth of an old person.
Old person? How old was he?
From the teeth condition,...
...he should be more than 100 years old.
100 years old?
The rumour of Feng Quan living until 120 years old is true.
It should be.
Unknown three words and the word 'for'.
Light?
The extreme darkness will be the light.
What does this sentence mean?
Don't bother about its meaning.
This is the coffin from Qin dynasty.
There is an eye. This must be the tomb of Feng Quan.
Xiaorui,after all hardships, we finally found Feng Quan's Tomb.
Male. Name,Tai Mu.
Born in Qin Shihuang's first year of reign.
Died in sixth year of Zhongyuan.
Which years are Qin Shihuang's first year of reign...
...and sixth Zhongyuan?
246 BC to 144 BC.
246 BC to 14.....
It's around 102 years old.
Xiaorui,you will not die.
Feng Quan lived until 102 years old. You will,too.
No. You can live until 110 years old.
120 years old!
I have said that you are blessed.
I'm still waiting for you to marry.
Why? Are you not happy for being able to live long?
For me,these aren't important.
I just hope that I...
...can be like all of you...
...and leave here safely.
Xiaorui is right.
Report!
I'm Feng Quan, I have something to report!
Nonsense! It's the middle of the night. Speak!
I didn't sleep and found signs of a quake.
The stars are aligned and there is a red light.
There are unusual activities in the sky and the earth.
I think it is a bad sign.
How daring! Where is General Bai?
Don't be upset,general. He is a coward. It's his first watch.
Please don't be upset,general.
You're scared as it's your first time,I'll not punish you.
Go away.
General,please trust me. General!
Let's go. -General!
Hurry and go!
Go quickly. -General!
Attack!