[Brocade Odyssey]
[Episode 10]
Yu Yuan,
let her enter.
It seems that I underestimated your capabilities, Ms. Ji.
Ever since I was cornered by Mrs. Hua at Lei Zu Festival,
I have learned to prepare for the unexpected.
I now make two plans for every critical matter.
Preparedness ensures no regrets.
You used your authority to pressure others
and have Chief Sang work for you.
Naturally, I used greater influence
to suppress Chief Sang's actions.
Last time, it was Sang Shisi.
This time, it's the Emperor himself.
Ms. Ji,
you are using influence to suppress others
and leveraging power against power.
Is that not
what I have also done?
Not exactly.
I never had the intent to harm others.
A good person refraining from evil deeds
is not necessarily kind.
Sometimes, it is merely because they lack the ability.
Even without the flower cookies,
I still managed to produce Flushed Rose.
Do you want to know why?
Yaoting, Mother,
remember to stock up on flower cookies and other ingredients.
Flushed Rose requires a large amount of them.
The letter you sent to your family?
Were you already planning to trap me?
At first, I just wanted to try.
Who would have thought that you would take the bait
and buy all the flower cookies on the market?
Replacing flower cookies with madder
was a technique I developed long ago while researching Flushed Rose.
So what if
you tricked me?
All the flower cookies were bought up,
but no one knows
that it was done by the Niu family.
As for the money spent,
it was hardly worth mentioning.
But you lost.
Ms. Niu, I do not think that you have ever experienced
the taste of defeat, have you?
Lost?
Ms. Ji, you overestimate yourself.
If you are careless,
the registration document and flower cookies
could suppress you completely.
But to me,
it was nothing more than a minor effort.
Besides,
I have already achieved my goal.
Please take a look
at my wedding invitation, Ms. Ji.
[The bride, Niu Wuniang. The groom, Zhao Xiuyuan]
Ms. Niu, you certainly know how to put on a show.
Do you think that I would believe this?
If you do not believe it,
why do you look so pale, Ms. Ji?
Why not ask Mr. Zhao yourself?
You will see
if I am lying.
[Songxian Bridge]
Niu Wuniang told me
that you are getting married.
I want to hear it from you.
Is that true
or not?
The wedding is set for the end of the month.
Why?
Niu Wuniang fell in love with me at first sight.
When my grandfather found out,
he proposed the match to the Niu family.
That is not what I want to hear.
I want to hear your reason.
Why?
But if you go back on your word
and try to be with her again,
I will not show mercy.
Why?
That day, I went to see you
because I knew she had imprisoned you.
You knew?
Yes.
But there was nothing I could do.
So, you are marrying Niu Wuniang
because you fear she will hurt me?
I know she will not spare me.
But I am also not someone who will accept my fate just like that.
A cornered beast fights the hardest.
Do you not find it entertaining, Mr. Zhao?
Let me go!
I am marrying Niu Wuniang
because I have realized
how important power truly is.
But you have never cared about power.
That was the old me.
Not the man I am now.
When I marry Niu Wuniang,
I will become Niu Jin's son-in-law.
Marrying her will make me
the new Brocade Master
and the next patriarch of the Zhao family.
Who could resist
such temptation?
I do not believe it.
We have known each other for over a decade
and spent all those years together.
I know exactly
what kind of person you are.
You cannot fool me.
Is she threatening you as well?
We have faced many trials together.
We will get through this one too.
I wanted them dead.
And so, they died.
♪The sea surges in silence deep♪
♪The waves rise and fall as you lead♪
She did threaten me.
But giving up on you...
♪My heart, a candle's flame♪
♪Burns bright for a promised name♪
This is my own choice.
♪Love long locked in a hidden place♪
Do not give up.
♪Bound by ties too much to erase♪
We have worked hard for so long
to finally be together.
Do not give up now.
Why give up so easily? No...
Ji Yingying...
♪Year after year♪
Perhaps our love
is not as important as you think it is.
You are strong.
♪Far away, two entwined♪
You are competitive.
Maybe the reason you do not want to give up
is simply because you have never lost
even once in your life.
♪Memories entwined, stronger than love's song♪
Say that again.
♪A lifetime unfolds, a solitary bloom♪
♪Even if we part, I will hold on long♪
I, Zhao Xiuyuan,
am not as noble as you imagine.
What makes you so sure
that I will not feel jealous
if I saw you with Yang Jinglan?
Is it not perfect now?
♪The sky stretches vast, forlorn♪
I have left space for you and him to live your quiet, peaceful days together.
♪The clouds wander where you are borne♪
Enough!
This is not just insulting me.
You are insulting the love we shared as well!
♪You are my anchor, my destined end♪
♪Love has no strength to break free♪
♪Even if it ends with no decree♪
Zhao Xiuyuan,
it was you who gave up on me.
Do not use such despicable excuses!
♪Stirring ripples, a whirlpool set free♪
♪Year after year♪
♪Just for a fleeting moment to hold dear♪
♪Far away, two entwined♪
♪Yet I remain, my shadow behind♪
♪Unforgotten♪
Yingying,
I know you will be sad.
But under the weight of power,
this is the only way
I can protect you.
Give me some time.
One day,
I will hold true power in my hands.
And then, no one will ever hurt you again.
Not even me.
What do we do about this?
What do you mean?
This is outrageous!
I want to kill that Zhao scoundrel right now!
I am coming with you!
I have been waiting to punch him for ages!
Let's go!
Sure!
Do not be impulsive!
If this could have made Yingying happy,
I would have burned down the Zhao residence a long time ago.
But doing that
will only make her more upset.
I cannot drink anymore.
Continue if you wish. I am done.
Yuniang!
I...
What are you doing?
Yingying!
Look at how you plate this dish.
We have been looking for you.
The dishes are incomplete.
The moon... It is beautiful tonight.
Have a seat.
Why have you not started eating?
Did we not agree that you would begin?
Is it because the food is not good?
Or is it that our wine is not up to your standards?
No...!
It is all perfect!
So many delicious dishes!
Come, come! The wine is here!
Ting, hurry up and pour some for everyone!
Today, the Ji family survived a great calamity.
We will celebrate together tonight!
That is right! We will not stop until we are drunk!
Pour the wine!
Sure! Pour it!
Pour it...!
I am pouring...!
Tonight's gathering
is a celebration.
Nothing else matters.
Do not worry.
I am fine. You do not have to worry.
However, I have kept you all waiting today.
So, I will start by drinking three bowls.
This is the first bowl.
What a good wine, Mother!
This is the second bowl.
That is enough, Yingying.
Enough.
Next, I offer three toasts.
The first
is for Mother and Yaoting.
Thank you
for your unwavering support and care.
I know I have made you worry.
The second
is for Bloom Society!
Here!
Without the trust and protection
from all of you,
we would not have achieved success today.
Here is to everyone!
Do not say that.
Without you, we would not be here today.
Am I right?
That is right!
My butt has been through hell,
but
what happened was truly exciting.
That is a story that I will be telling for the rest of my life!
I did not know that was something to brag about.
Telling others about his butt going through hell.
We will do the same.
Come on. Let us drink.
That is enough, Yingying.
You need to slow down.
Just one more.
I want to toast
my dear Yu.
Thank you for braving the storm
to save me when I needed you.
But do not forget to pay back the money you owe me!
This wine is pretty strong, Mother!
What is wrong with you guys?
Why are you not eating?
Is something wrong with the food?
Or with the wine?
- Come on. - Smells delicious!
Everyone, let us eat!
The wine is great!
Time to eat.
- Yes. - Let us eat.
Come, eat!
Come on. Let us get some food!
Here! I want some wine!
Pour me a glass!
We are not calling it a night until we are drunk!
Yes. Let us get drunk!
Yes!
- Slow down, will you? - Here.
Mother, join us.
Everyone!
Let us get drunk tonight!
Let us get drunk!
Yes, time to drink!
[The Zhao Residence]
Once I adjust the fit of this wedding outfit,
I promise you will look dashing and radiant
when you meet your bride!
You can use the kite.
It will fly as far as you want it to.
Zhao Xiuyuan,
it was you who gave up on me.
Do not use such despicable excuses!
♪Fallen petals, scattered on the ground♪
♪Love awakens♪
♪But it fades before it grows♪
Do you know why I am giving this to you?
♪Like dust in the creek♪
It is because you do not lack wisdom.
You are already brimming with creative ideas
and destined for greatness.
You lack neither resources
nor financial stability.
It is because
you have always sought the highs and lows,
leaving no room for oversight.
♪I walk through the pain, but I still chase the dream♪
♪The road is ahead♪
♪But it feels so unknown♪
I am marrying Niu Wuniang
because I realize
how important power truly is.
♪Holding on tight, as the ropes pull me inside♪
♪To show that the soaring crimson is mine to own♪
My head hurts.
I need some medicine!
I think only spells will help.
♪Silent red, where all my memories go♪
As expected, only you know how to please me.
♪Throw the thread, and let the heartache show♪
♪Drowning in this, cannot let it go♪
♪Red like flames, that burn through my soul♪
♪I walk these miles alone, through sleepless nights.♪
♪Love in the wind, alive, it's everywhere we've been♪
♪Red blooms bright, but it dies all alone♪
Yingying,
do you know why
I married your father back then?
Your father only cares
about making brocade
and spends all his time in the embroidery room.
He may not seem romantic,
gentle,
or considerate,
but he would give up everything
for me.
When figuring out
if a man loves you
and is worthy of your trust,
it is not just about how he treats you day-to-day,
but how he acts when faced with adversity.
If a man
chooses to abandon you
for power or gain now,
he will abandon you
again and again in the future.
Losing someone like him
is not a bad thing.
You really do not need
to feel sad or upset
over someone like him.
Cry,
silly girl.
If you need to cry,
just let it out.
Once you are done,
forget those who do not deserve your tears
and focus on living a better life,
okay?
[Brocade Bureau]
Based on your condition,
it seems that you have been here the whole night yesterday.
I have something to say.
Usually,
I would not interfere in your personal matters,
but it is affecting your mood.
And when that happens,
it also affects our work.
Stop beating around the bush!
Mr. Zhao has moved on.
This is your chance to make your move.
You have never fallen for someone, have you?
It's none of your business.
If you truly love someone,
you will share in their feelings,
understand their joys and pains,
worry about their struggles,
and wish for their happiness.
As for whether you can be with them,
that will not be something you will need to worry about.
You are not wrong.
Ms. Ji must be
having a hard time right now.
But she is no ordinary woman.
She is strong and clear-headed.
I am sure that she will be fine
in less than three days.
She is just pretending to be strong.
Walking alone,
standing by oneself.
[From Classic of Poetry, Odes of Wang,Sorrow]
Those who understand her
know that she is troubled, but others might just wonder what she is thinking of.
Mr. Yang,
after keeping an eye on the Niu residence for a few days,
our men finally saw someone go up the mountain
to a secret cave in the dense forest.
We can see signs of lit candles there.
Finally, there is something.
Maybe there are lookout guards stationed there,
just like last time.
Lookout guards?
There should not be lit candles then.
Who went up to the mountain?
It was Niu Wuniang's maid,
Yu Yuan.
That is unexpected.
Niu Wuniang once used this maid
to stage an act before me
to trap Chief Sang.
Normally, someone like her
would discard
such a pawn to avoid complications.
Yet, she still trusts Yu Yuan enough
to send her up the mountain.
That means that this maid must hold some special importance to her.
What is your plan?
Do you plan to make the maid talk?
If someone
ever captured you
and asked why I came here
or what my purpose was,
would you tell them?
I would not, of course.
But it is
for my master's sake,
not yours.
It would be the same for her too.
Continue keeping an eye on her.
I will head over later.
Understood!
So, what is your current plan now?
I have not even dealt with my personal matters yet.
I cannot focus on work.
We have some goji berries, chrysanthemum petals, and boiled pig heart here.
It is great for your liver, improves your eyesight,
and calms the mind.
Okay. Okay.
I got it.
You are saying that
I am a clueless idiot
who cannot see through a person clearly.
I thought about it.
He did not really do anything to wrong me.
Here.
You should have more of this.
I am being serious.
Since my family fell into hardship,
he has been there to help,
never leaving us.
Even my own relatives
could not have done what he did.
He understands me,
lets me be free,
and never pressures me to act like a proper lady.
He even hides his talents for my sake,
enduring scorn from his family.
But our paths
have now diverged.
He does not love power itself,
but the stability and freedom
that it brings.
As for me,
I am on a different path.
Then, find someone who is on the same path as you.
Forget about it.
From now on,
I will walk my own path.
I do not need to have someone by my side.
You still cannot let go of Zhao Xiuyuan.
After all these years of knowing him,
how could I just let go?
But who says that not letting go means that
I cannot keep moving forward?
With Blossom Society gaining fame thanks to Flushed Rose,
now is the perfect time to strike while the iron is hot.
I am thinking about what comes next.
Dyeing silk is just a small part of the business.
The real work is in weaving the brocade.
Stop!
He was right.
Business is the best way to cure you!
Who are you talking about?
So the person that Yu meant is you, Mr. Yang.
I heard that you were looking for me.
What can I do for you?
I have been feeling down lately
and just need someone
to talk to,
to help clear my mind
and lift my spirits.
Then, you have got the wrong person, Mr. Yang.
I have matters to attend to.
I will take my leave.
No, wait!
Do you know where this is?
I do not want to know.
This place is called Wangyou Lake.
Leave all your worries here,
and they will sink to the bottom of the lake,
disappearing completely.
Give it a try.
[Wanguan]
For you.
But giving up on you
is my own choice.
The floating lantern costs 30 wen.
30 wen?
That is expensive! You are being ridiculous!
I have bought floating lanterns before,
and they were only about two wen.
This particular one is called Luo Shen's Lantern.
Rumor has it that Luo Shen used it himself.
Really?
Just because it is named after someone, the price skyrockets.
Only an idiot would buy it.
Come with me.
This wine from my sister is called Wen Jun's Wine.
Are you saying that
anyone who drinks this wine
is also an idiot?
Whether it is Wen Jun's Wine
or Luo Shen's Lantern,
it is just a fancy name.
Yet everyone loves
to jump on the bandwagon.
Ms. Ji,
do you not want to join the fun too?
I understand now!
Can you tell me
about some famous people from Shu?
I am not well-read,
so I would not know.
As someone who has traveled extensively,
you must have plenty of experiences to share,
even if you have not read much.
Worst case, I will share some of my earnings with you.
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Sichuan]
So dangerous, so high!
The hardships of the Shu Road,
harder than...
Get over here.
♪The curve of Spring's first thunder♪
Harder than...
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
ascending to the heavens above!
♪When I first met you, it felt like yesterday's wonder♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
The kings sought to open this land!
Yet their efforts were shrouded in uncertainty!
♪The little ripples of early summer rise♪
♪A crescent of soft yellow, your gaze in my eyes♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
Forty-eight thousand years have passed since then!
♪You painted for me, the delicate arch of your brow♪
♪A tapestry of love, woven into my heart♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
And not a soul has crossed these borders!
♪As dusk falls, with the sound of sea-bloomed flutes♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
To the west, at the mountain, lies a bird's path!
A daring passage spanning the peaks of hills!
♪We smell the green plums, and life's sweetness it roots♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
Only when the earth crumbled and mountains fell!
♪I send a silk letter to a high flower tower♪
♪Golden threads intertwining, hour by hour♪
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
Did brave men carve ladders and stone bridges!
Above, towering peaks where six dragons turn to the sun!
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
Below, waters clash and twist through unruly rivers!
Even the yellow crane cannot hope to fly past!
[From Li Bai's Hard Roads to Shu]
And apes, though nimble, lament the climb!
Careful!
♪I send a silk letter to a high flower tower♪
No matter how treacherous the Shu Road,
nothing can stop a determined spirit.
I wish you success in overcoming every challenge
and a bright future ahead, Ms. Ji!
♪With the promise of snow, and time that expands♪
♪You and I, together we roam♪
Yuniang?
- I... - What?
Yingying will not be returning anytime soon.
Do you want to vent her frustrations on her behalf?
What are we doing?
Write something for me,
but use your left hand.
[The Zhao Residence]
Will this cheer Yingying up?
It might not.
Let us go!
Move!
[The Residence of Coldness and Emptiness]
I am happy
with what we have done.
It is nice to see you happy.
That makes everything we have done worthwhile.
Do not worry.
Yingying has just lost someone
who was not right for her.
It is natural to feel sad,
but she will not die from it,
and she will not mourn forever.
You...
Have you ever felt
the same kind of sadness as Yingying?
That is a rather an inappropriate question.
You should focus on earning money
and mind your own business, not other people's.
But this is my business.
And I care about you.
Yang Jinglan!
Shh!
Keep it down.
Guo Kui, if you wake my mother,
I will break your legs!
Guo Kui, tell me,
when will I be able
to walk through your front door openly
instead of sneaking in like this?
Guo Kui,
remember,
whether it is through the wall or the front gate,
no upright man
would visit a young maiden's house
before she is married,
as it only invites gossip.
Ms. Ji,
what are you doing?
Are you trying to keep me here
for longer?
It is because you enjoy flying around, Mr. Yang.
So there is no need for you to use the door.
Or... would you prefer to go through there?
I would prefer using this one.
Well,
thank you for your advice, Ms. Ji.
I will get back to my own affairs now.
Thank you for your comfort, Mr. Yang.
One more thing...
Rest well.
Oh no!
By tomorrow, news will spread that
the fourth brocade officer in Yizhou has died.
The entire city will be in a panic,
and the court will send inspectors.
I bet that this is not the outcome you want.
Let us talk then.
Zhuge is here too.
He did not reveal anything, did he?
You are too good at fighting, Mr. Yang.
If I had not brought enough people,
you probably would have escaped.
Now that things have come to this,
let us speak openly.
You should know that you will not be
the only brocade officer buried on Mount Qingcheng.
What is the point of that threat,
Niu Wuniang?
This is...?
I know that you are being sent by the court to investigate Shu Red Silk.
Now that you have them before you,
you can use them to report back to the court, Mr. Yang.
Shu Red Silk has been missing for a long time.
Where did you find it, Niu Wuniang?
It is better
if you do not know.
Since you have shown me such sincerity,
I will speak frankly as well.
I came to Yizhou
solely in pursuit of fame and wealth.
Any offenses I committed before
were unintentional.
If you are willing to take me in,
I am ready to serve you faithfully
and follow your every command.
Look at him.
Zhuge is really excited!
He has been wanting
to achieve something great in his lifetime.
Zhuge,
now that
we have Niu Wuniang
and General Niu's support,
it will be easier to achieve something great,
will it not?
I knew that
you would be easy to convince.
I have already prepared the documents for you.
As for the official seal,
your official seal,
I will leave that to you.
All that is needed is for you
to send the Shu Red Silk to Chang'an.
From now on,
we will share the wealth
and success equally.
Protect, Ms. Niu!
What is that for, Mr. Yang?
Your people have wronged mine.
If I do not take action,
how will my people
ever respect me in the future?
You are someone of strong character, Mr. Yang.
Those who do not have a temper are the most frightening, are they not?
Before the Shu Red Silk is sent to Chang'an,
it still needs to be verified at the Brocade Bureau,
Niu Wuniang.
How about
I take a thread with me,
just for the sake of formality?
As you please.
But I must add one more thing.
Tomorrow, the silk
will be sent to Chang'an along with your certified documents.
If anything goes wrong after that,
you will be held responsible,
not me.
Do not worry, Niu Wuniang.
Ms. Niu,
can Yang Jinglan truly be trusted?
I do not trust him, of course.
But he was right about one thing.
Unless absolutely necessary,
we cannot allow
another brocade officer to die in Yizhou.
Whether his cooperation is sincere or just a facade,
we are all in the same boat now.
If it sinks,
none of us will survive.
♪Fallen petals, scattered on the ground♪
♪Love awakes, but it fades before it grows♪
♪Like dust in the creek, it slips away♪
♪Time just spins, tearing at the seams♪
♪I walk through the pain, but I still chase the dream♪
♪The road is ahead, but it feels so unknown♪
♪How can we, so small, fight against this tide?♪
♪Holding on tight, as the ropes pull me inside♪
♪To show that the soaring crimson is mine to own♪
♪Red like a vow, that's burning slow♪
♪Silent red, where all my memories go♪
♪Throw the thread, and let the heartache show♪
♪Drowning in this, can't let it go♪
♪Red like flames, that burn through my soul♪
♪I walk these miles alone, through sleepless nights♪
♪Love in the wind, alive, it's everywhere we've been♪
♪Red blooms bright, but it dies all alone♪
♪Red like a vow, that's burning slow♪
♪Silent red, where all my memories go♪
♪Throw the thread, and let the heartache show♪
♪Drowning in this, can't let it go♪
♪Red like flames, that burn through my soul♪
♪I walk these miles alone, through sleepless nights♪
♪Love in the wind, alive, it's everywhere we've been♪
♪Red blooms bright, but it dies all alone♪