Attorney Han! Attorney Han!
Attorney Han! Attorney Han! Are you all right? Are you all right?
Are you all right? Just lie down, lie down.
It's a little fast.
That's good.
You must be busy. You should leave. Thank you for today.
Take care of your health. It's important, right?
Yes, it's important.
But... the student who saved me...
Shouldn't I thank her?
She said she was late for her part-time job and left.
I thanked her on your behalf.
- Should I give you her phone number?
- No, no.
I-I'm sure you took good care of it.
Honey.
Oh, you came.
You look okay, despite everything.
Oh, my head...
I'm sorry. You were alarmed, weren't you?
That's what happens when you associate with someone like Nam Gi Ryong.
Do you know Director Nam?
He's a bad person.
Excuse me!
You left this behind.
It doesn't belong to us.
- This...
- Is it yours?
I was wondering if Director Nam left it.
Anyway, with a sharp eye,
you can tell that it obviously belongs to a female student.
It's stained with paint. Maybe an art student?
Director Nam had someone with him. A female student.
I'm okay to drive, though.
No. You have to rest a bit.
I have somewhere to drop by on the way. Is that okay?
Yes. Then, I'll sleep for a bit.
Yes, that's good.
I have to return her bag to her.
Honey...
You're... being careful, right?
About what?
The angle of your head.
My head?  What...
Then, I'll sleep.
Go to the back seat and sleep comfortably.
Hey. What are you, my boss?
That you're sleeping in the backseat?
I'm not sleeping, just thinking.
Thinking, my ass.
Hey! What kind of relationship do you have with Baek Soo Jeong?
What do you mean by a relationship? That's nonsense!
It's only been a day since her disappearance but since the start of the investigation,
you've been acting suspiciously. There's something, right?
Look. Even now, you're overly excited.
She's pretty. I'm just her fan. Her fan.
Since when? Have you ever watched any of Baek Soo Jeong's movies?
Well...
Do I even have the time to watch movies? Seriously!
Suspicious...
Hey! Don't say anything.
Just go to sleep quickly if you really want to sleep.
You're really suspicious.
Suspicious, suspicious.
Hey!
Do you really have to open that?
I'm carrying out official duties. I don't have the time to chat with you.
Wait!
Don't move.
Do you even know how to use a gun?
All you are is a traffic cop.
Usually, you're supposed to shoot the leg, but...
It's my first time, so I don't know if I'll do it properly.
What? Cha Soo Ho disappeared?
And with no contact, too?
I've told you enough to understand.
The source of an AI infection was discovered nearby, so this place is closed.
(T/N: AI = Avian influenza)
You have to turn around.
I don't know what I'm doing right now, really.
Hey, can mountain herb roots catch AI, too?
I mean, how could AI infect a neighborhood that doesn't even have a single duck?
There's no neighborhood without ducks.
- Right?
- Yes.
If Chief Ma finds out...
I thought he ordered us to do this.
Don't worry. Baek Soo Jeong's body being found only puts Chief Ma in a tough spot.
Right?
But why did you disagree with the chief again?
Delete all evidence.
Delete all traces of evidence against Kang Yeo Joo. Immediately.
Before the police finds anything.
It's also a crime to protect a criminal.
- That's romantic.
- Why are you protecting Kang Yeo Joo?
Is she that important?
Don't waste your time.
After all, the police won't be able to find the body there.
There's no evidence, too.
Body?
Is Baek Soo Jeong dead?
I only reported that Baek Soo Jeong's blood was found.
Where is "there"?
Where the police can't find the body?
It seems like you even know where it's buried.
So, where are you going to dig?
Anywhere you dig here, you'll find a body.
You said you were bringing equipment.
He's not equipment, he's a soldier.
He even got special training in Germany.
- What is he, a German mercenary?
- Yeah.
He should be here by now...
Oh, he's coming. Here! Over here!
He looks Korean.
Huh? He's of pure German descent.
Second Lieutenant Hunter.
He can distinguish smells up to 12 meters underground.
Move aside!
Corpses from the water are the worst.
The first person to discover it was a reporter?
Yeah. A political journalist.
He said there was an event nearby.
Could it really be Baek Soo Jeong?
All the other ships went to investigate,
but our ship couldn't move even though there was nothing wrong with the engine.
We stopped the engine and looked...
What is that? Could it be...?
A yellow dress was floating.
Okay. Thank you.
It seems like there's really something here.
Let's dig here.
Hey. You look as if you've lost your girlfriend.
It's sad when anyone dies.
As if this is the first or second time we're seeing this?
I feel like I'm looking at my elementary school classmate.
She doesn't know me, but I saw her on TV every day.
Stop it. You might hit a pipe.
Where am I?
Honey, where are we?
Huh? Where am I?
What's happening?
Where am I...
Honey!
Soo Jeong?
Excuse me. Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry, but can you move over?
What?
Come on, get a shot!
Please don't do that!
Why, of all nights, last night...?
Please move aside.
The body of Baek Soo Jeong who disappeared was discovered at the Han River.
Several stab wounds were found on the body.
It's being investigated by the police as a murder case.
She was at the Han River?
We did all that for nothing.
Oh my god!
Baek Soo Jeong must've committed suicide.
We'll have to eat out another time.
Why again?
I have to go and meet Woo Seong. I'm sorry, go home.
What?
Where are you going?
No! No!
You should've married Attorney Han!
Wow!  Wow—
Broadcaster Baek Soo Jeong found dead at the Han River.
The question of whether I should be involved in this investigation has already been decided.
I guess I need to talk to Team Leader Hong.
There's no point.
Why are you so interested in this case?
By any chance, do you have any kind of relationship with Baek Soo Jeong?
Aren't you the one who has a relationship with Baek Soo Jeong,
Detective Jang?
Excuse me.
Why did you hide the fact that Attorney Han was your husband?
I also don't know who your wife is, Detective Jang.
We're not even close, so why do we need to know that?
- If you're going to keep being like this—
- Hey, hey, hey!
Let's go. You know corpses from the water decompose quickly.
Allow me in the coroner's office.
I won't participate beyond that.
Or should I go to the reporters?
Because I know a lot about this case.
Only up to the coroner's office.
Did you get some sleep?
I took a taxi since you seemed busy.
Jin Ho was worried, so I'll head home after seeing him.
Okay.
Okay. See you at home.
Did you see her yourself?
Yeah.
This is... not a dream, right?
The light's not working?
I was only worried about the CCTV footage.
Even though a person had disappeared.
Worrying about the person should have been first...
I never thought she would show up like that.
There are no fatal injuries to the front of her body.
Please don't touch.
Sorry for making you wait. Let's begin.
It's all in the past. What's the use in talking about it?
Just keep living the way you did.
You said being caught cheating is
worse than cheating itself.
You said that a woman wants to be fooled, even when she knows the truth.
I know. But a person has died.
Baek Soo Jeong died.
Is it right to only care about
keeping myself clean?
If she died unfairly, we need to bring it to light.
It's a deep wound.
Yes. She would have suffered a lot of hemorrhaging.
There's a wound from a blunt weapon on her head.
A hammer or... something like it?
The trophy?
I won't know the exact causes until I carry out the autopsy.
- If there's anything I can help with—
- There will be no need for that.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
When will the autopsy take place?
Don't concern yourself with it. We won't need to see each other anymore.
I hope for that, too.
Seriously...
Please stop following us.
You said you wouldn't bother us anymore.
It might be bothersome, but could you please step away from my car?
You're aware of what happened at the Hallyu Awards, right?
Like what?
Baek Soo Jeong...
I don't want to bother you. Then I'll be off.
What about Baek Soo Jeong? Wait. That...
Ah, damn!  That arrogant... That...!  We should catch her and...!
Stop it.
Let's go.
Damn it.
Sister-in-Law!
(T/N: Can be used to refer to a close friend's wife)
- You drank a lot.
- Yes.
Where is my husband?
He's inside. You know,
men are such animals.
They always lose to their instincts.
So what I mean is that—
Hurry up and end it before your wife finds out.
Pardon?
Do you know, "An Assembled Man"?
No.
It's my novel. It will help you come to a decision.
It features a man whose package is cut off after cheating.
Wow!
Woo Seong must be really scared.
Honey, let's go.
Honey, I'm sorry.
Why did you drink so much?
Because I felt sorry toward you.
I live with the Nation's Husband. What are you sorry about?
Sorry for being the Nation's Husband.
What are you saying?
Honey, do you want to go for a drive?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to confess that I cheated.
Will this guy be okay?
She's not going to let him go.
I don't know.
Seriously...
Did she change the code?
Honey!
Honey! Open the door!
Ah, really!  What time is it now?!
Standing me up for a dinner that happens once in a blue moon wasn't enough? Now he comes home drunk?
Open the door!
So embarrassing.
What's wrong?
Don't wake up our kid and leave quietly.
To where?
You don't make a lot of money or help out at home. I don't even expect that much from you.
You should at least come home on time!
But I don't cheat on you.
I'd rather you did!
You... really shouldn't say that so easily.
- Ow! My foot!
- Oh, your foot!
It's okay.
Ah, damn!
Split up and obtain CCTV recordings from all the nearby streets, shops, garages.
Tell your family you won't be home for a while.
Rock, paper, scissors!
We don't have time! Take it quickly! Divide them like this.
Hold on, hold on!
Wait, wait!
- Just take some more.
- Let's organize them a bit!
When will you finish?
It's too much!
If it wasn't for that computer virus, we would have caught the culprit already.
By the way, why are you spending so much?
What do you mean? I'm sure I spent the same.
You're spending the most on the team!
-  You spent 500,000 won ($500) on the last stakeout!
- Hey.
Do you see him as a man now, too?
Why did you spend so much? This is too much!
That wrist.
-  I didn't.
-  And it's always you!
It's bothering me a lot.
- What about it?
- He's turning it.
Doesn't it seem familiar to you?
The cafe's CCTV footage...
When we were at the autopsy, Kang Yeo Joo was doing that.
Be careful about what now?
Hey!
You know I have a girlfriend, don't you?
Cut the crap. Let go.
Oh, sorry.
I'm too busy for this. Seriously.
Have you brought back some mountain herbs at least?
I'm not entirely empty-handed.
Grass doesn't grow underneath the soil...
but above it.
What does that mean?
I plan to look into it starting now. What this means.
This person doesn't suit our line of work...
and keeps making issues bigger.
Do you want to grab some tea first?
No.
I don't think I can talk if the car stops.
What do you want to talk about when you're this drunk?
Like... how I've been living all this time...
how it's been...
Let's... Honey...
Let's go look at the sunrise in Yeosoo.
At this time of the night?
I want to be born as a totally new person.
Should we then?
Should we go and destress?
♫  You tried so hard to hide it, your little secret  ♫
♫  I pretended not to know and ignored it.
You got used to it over time   ♫
♫  I'm sure you thought it was perfect  ♫
♫  I bet you never even looked back  ♫
♫  And I had to watch you do it all,  ♫
♫  I'll make sure you get what you deserve  ♫
♫  Feel my cold gaze.  I'm never gonna love again  ♫
♫  Try playing around with those lips again.
I'm never gonna love again  ♫
♫  Sweet temptation like sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
♫  You melt sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
♫  I fall again sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
Oh, oh!
So they do fight!
♫  Sweet temptation like sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
♫  You melt sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
She's really angry.
♫  Leave me alone  ♫
I feel like my eyes are going to pop out.
Normally, people turn the pen with their index and middle fingers, or around the top of the thumb.
Magnify it one last time.
Stop, stop, stop...
No matter how many times we look at it, it looks like the middle and ring fingers are being used to turn the pen.
Right?
Kang Yeo Joo was doing exactly that.
I think it's Kang Yeo Joo.
Sir, you can't sleep here.
Sir. Sir?
Sir! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
He was found on the roadside. I think he was ignored because he looked drunk.
Let me know when he wakes up.
Yes, Doctor.
Did I tell her about Baek Soo Jeong last night?
It was an accident.
Get out right now!
But we're on the highway! How can I get out?
- Hello.
Who are you?
Oh, I'm Writer Kang's assistant.
Right, I was told about you.
He's randomly good-looking. Did she pick him for his looks?
And why is he so well-proportioned?
Why when I'm looking my worst...
He just got up, but he's so stylish.
And what's up with that natural and decadent aura?
Attorney, Sir, you just got up?
Yes. Could you make me some hangover soup?
Honey, do you want some coffee?
She won't even speak to me.
Think of yourself as lucky. At least she didn't kick you out.
I thought you'd at least be in a cast.
If I told her, there's no way she'd let it go like this.
You said she was really angry.
I feel like I did tell her I cheated...
But... I can't seem to really remember...
Drink this and wake up.
You're going to ruin our business at this rate. Let's work already.
Right, we have a trial today!
It's a female judge. I'm sure going in there stinking of alcohol will really win her over!
Drink it up and come in quickly.
Yes. This is Attorney Han Woo Seong.
Hello. I'm the student who was riding in the ambulance with you yesterday.
Ambulance?
At the Han River?
Yes.
I'm indebted to you, and I didn't get a chance to thank you.
It's all right.
I heard you had my bag...
Oh, that plastic bag?
I asked at the hospital, and they told me you took it with you.
You have it, right?
I took it because I was afraid someone would throw it away.
After the trial's over, I'll bring it to...
Trying to make a move again...
Pardon?
Nothing, nothing. Should I send it over by courier?
If you leave it with your assistant, I'll come and pick it up.
I know where your office is.
Okay. Then I'll leave it with my assistant.
Okay.
Wait a minute. Where did I put that plastic bag?
Plastic? I threw it away.
Why would you throw it away? Someone is looking for it.
Never mind that. Where would you use that thing?
You can buy a bag anywhere these days for so cheap!
Who carries around that kind of a plastic bag these days?
It's a student, so she doesn't have any money.
She seemed like a student who barely makes money for school with a part-time job.
Then why don't you buy her a new bag?
He's looking for the plastic bag?
I guess he can't remember anything.
Just apologize for everything!
I can't apologize if I can't remember what I told her!
Why are you taking it out on me! Don't hold back!
Fight! Sue her like the attorney you are!
Is the plaintiff's attorney present?
Yes, I'm Attorney Han Woo Seong.
What is this smell?
It's been cleaned up.
Where did she put all the books?
I'm sure it's a book that's been published before.
Try and find it right away.
What are you trying to find right away?
Materials. Materials.
I mean, a junior colleague of mine is well-educated in that area,
so I asked him to help me.
You were suspicious from the start. I felt like you were hiding something.
Did she catch on?
Acting like you're working hard searching for materials in front of me,
but in the end, you made your junior colleague do it instead.
I hired you as my assistant, not your junior colleague.
I'm sorry.
You have an expression of someone who's just caught his assistant doing something extremely wrong.
It's upside down!
Geon (heaven) and Gam (moon) are on top!
Like this!
Really?
Are you sure you're a writer? How do you not know something so basic?
Are you usually unable to control your anger?
How can I not be angry?
Don't you know what we had to do to protect this flag during the Japanese colonial era?
While waving this flag, by the knife of the Japanese...
What a patriot.
But it's not Foundation Day or Korean Proclamation Day.
I don't think it's a national holiday.
Police Day?
Local government day?
Dokdo Day.
I don't think that's it either.
It's our wedding anniversary.
- Pardon?
- It's more important to me than a national holiday.
You can relax. She's putting up the flag.
I guess if she's thinking about our wedding anniversary, I didn't make a huge mistake.
Did something happen?
I think so, but I can't remember.
Should I try to find out for you?
Auntie!
Let's hang up! Yes?
Do you know what solution cleans leather?
What leather?
My leather car seat.
I need to get the smell out, too. Isn't there a good air freshener or something?
I can never drive it the way it is right now.
What happened to the seat?
What smell is that exactly?
You're talking about it like you've smelled it. Were you in my car?
I did, last week. When we went to the publishing house.
That was a good smell. A new leather smell. What it's like now is
the smell of vomit when you grind down alcohol and food together and ferment it.
It's only been two weeks since I changed the seat covers!
Sorry.
Give me a plastic bag.
How can you do this on the highway?! Try and hold it in!
Well, it's just that...
Sorry. It was an accident.
Get out right now!
We're on the highway. How can I get out?
Oh, but that's expensive.
This is more expensive.
What are you talking about? If you go to the market, there are tons of these bags.
Not just any bag, it's a limited edition from the last fall/winter collection.
Also, this bag. It's about ₩1,500,000 ($1,500)?
It should be over ₩2,000,000 ($2,000) by now.
This old thing?
Vintage Chanel. The price goes up every year.
And yet Attorney Han threw up on this very expensive bag.
My world... Do people spend money on these things?
I feel lightheaded from the smell.
I thought we weren't going to see each other again.
I was hoping for that, too, but...
We need you to come to the station with us.
₩450,000 ($450)...
Maybe it's too expensive and will feel burdensome...
Do you have any backpacks that college students might like?
This is a set of five items.
If you buy this, you get a pouch worth 10,000 won.
- This is nice. Give me this, please.
- Sure.
It's cute.
What? What's that?
It's not my birthday or my wedding anniversary. What is it?
She'll come to pick it up. Give it to her.
Tell her not to feel burdened. It's a thank you gift.
A girl?
- It's not like that.
- Then what is it?
It's not like that, I said! How can I do that right now with my head so frazzled?
It is a woman. That bastard.
Doctor, the patient has regained consciousness!
Oh, really?
Where is the patient?
Don't you have any green tea?
All right. We do have it.
Baek Soo Jeong used to be every man's fantasy.
Attorney Han's generation is like that. Even that punk, too. No more explanation is necessary.
Are you telling me to be suspicious of my husband and Baek Soo Jeong's relationship?
Isn't that... what you're already suspicious of?
I keep getting a call.
031?
What's the matter? You're not answering it?
I don't know this number.
- Go do well.
- Okay.
You're questioning me as a reference witness, right?
And I have no obligation to answer.
You asked if I suspected my husband.
Why? Do you want to answer?
I'm curious about many things in this case, too.
Let's take turns asking questions.
When I saw the photo, I could definitely tell.
The angle was... one-sided.
That Baek Soo Jeong was the only one interested?
You met PD Nam in the morning. What did he say?
It was one-sided. For Soo Jeong.
You could say... she was pushing herself on him.
It's my turn now.
Did you find any blood on the trophy?
Yes.
Now, it's our turn to ask.
Did you meet with Baek Soo Jeong?
I invited her to my house for dinner.
I was wondering why my husband was so uncomfortable...
Now that I think about it... I understand.
That's it, right? You didn't meet her again?
I can't remember.
The person you're calling is not available, and...
Great job today.
Did it go well?
It's one obstacle after another.
I keep getting a call.
It's the same number.
Just answer it. Seeing how they keep calling, it doesn't seem like a sales call.
It could be urgent.
Wait. Hold on.
Hello?
Attorney Han Woo Seong?
Yes. Who is this?
Did you forget me already?
Mr. Property Manager?
You killed her, didn't you? Baek Soo Jeong.
You ordered him to kill me too, didn't you?
Do you think I would fall that easily?!
I'm going to tell the police everything! You just wait.
It's over for you.
♫  Feel my cold gaze.  I'm never gonna love again  ♫
♫  Try playing around with those lips again.
I'm never gonna love again  ♫
♫  Sweet temptation like sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
♫  You melt sugar, sugar, sugar  ♫
I'm going to tell the police first.
You have to help me now!
The USB in my drawer, too?
There's a chance the blood isn't from the victim but the assailant.
You're type A too, aren't you?
I've never been so angry that I'd kill Baek Soo Jeong.
I was meeting someone without you knowing.
I had suspected.
Marital life is hell. If there's no trust between the couple.
I found it! Is Attorney Han on the suspect list, too?
Who said that?
Then, what did you do with it?
Are you saying Baek Soo Jeong's body was kept inside a kimchi fridge?
It's big enough for an adult body to fit into.