♪The future is a constantly
spinning spinning top♪
♪Polished by the hands of time♪
♪Yet my footsteps follow♪
♪Even in adversity,
we can pull a string together♪
♪Go whereever we want♪
♪My heart is never confused♪
♪When I set my sights on beauty♪
♪I believe without hesitation♪
♪Your gaze is so clear♪
♪Like the stars embracing the vastness♪
♪Love ignites like fireworks♪
♪Brightening the polar night♪
♪We won't be silent♪
♪I hear the pulsating rhythm
of your heart♪
♪Even if the night becomes mottled♪
♪How can love silently pass by♪
♪In the midst of radiance,
a silhouette appears♪
♪Bringing the warmth
into the palms of our hands♪
♪There's no reason
not to hold on tightly♪
♪I want you for every moment of my life♪
♪To be with me♪
=Got A Crush On You=
(Adapted from Bei Qing's novel "Got A Crush On You")
=Episode 2=
(Stardust Rogue)
Buy one, get three free.
Xingchen.
We made several orders today.
The future looks promising.
I filed for arbitration for that guy
who left a bad review previously.
Aren't you afraid he'll retaliate
against us, complaining again?
We can't let
this kind of guy off easily.
I've noticed
you've developed a sense of justice,
like a righteous hero.
Once this stock is cleared,
we need to plan
the operation of our store properly.
Since we've made up our minds,
we can't let others look down on us,
thinking we sell junk.
Let me show you.
(Wishlist)
This plan is so long.
I was too busy before
and haven't done many things.
Now,
I've listed a wishlist.
I want to accomplish everything
before turning 30.
Let me see your wishlist.
Learn to surf.
Become a qualified medical volunteer.
A medical volunteer?
Do you still want
to continue being a doctor?
Being a volunteer is different.
Do you want to join me?
No.
My small frame can't handle it.
Are you really
not doing it to see the muscular guys?
You're always watching dramas.
Look what's in your head?
Oh no.
What happened?
An account I followed
recommended a drama to me.
I haven't watched it yet.
Since we're having a break,
I can catch up with it.
(Stardust Rogue)
(I really like you.)
(Could you give me a chance?)
(Thank you.)
(But)
(I can't accept your love.)
(Why?)
(Because...)
(Because I'm already
a mother of two children.)
This is too melodramatic.
(This can't be real.)
It's 21st century now.
And this official account
still recommended me this kind of drama.
Thumbs down.
You came so quickly.
This kind of thing
should be thrown
into the designated trash bin.
This kind of intimate clothing
cannot be returned in our store.
Which intimate clothing have you seen
that supports returns?
It seems you have no understanding
of our industry at all.
It's all prejudice.
What do you mean?
I just hope you can understand clearly
before spreading rumors.
Selling these products
is not a conduct issue,
but a legitimate business.
It's you who spread rumors
about my friend, right?
I thought who it was.
You look decent.
Saying that girls are expired goods.
I think you're the trash here.
Also,
you have a girlfriend,
but you still went on blind dates.
You shameless man.
Xiaoli.
Su Qingche.
If you're here to challenge us today,
you've come to the wrong place.
I just feel a bit sorry
for snatching the items
you wanted to buy
from the supermarket that day.
If you don't like it,
just throw it away.
I think you might have misunderstood me.
First, I really don't have a girlfriend.
I never said she's expired goods,
and certainly didn't say your conduct...
I don't want to know.
Let's end this matter here.
We're even now.
Goodbye, I won't see you off.
Morning, Captain Su.
Captain Su.
You gone for a run?
I'm on duty with Qin today.
We just finished running three miles.
Alright, take a break.
Okay. Let's go.
Qin.
What's wrong?
Qin, do you have asthma?
Yes, medicine.
Hello.
I'm at Haicheng City Rescue Center.
There's a sudden asthma patient here now.
Qin.
(Haicheng City Rescue Center)
(Area A: Emergency Room)
Is she okay?
It's all my fault.
Qin suffered from overbreathing syndrome
due to exhaustion after running.
Actually, covering the nose and mouth
and doing repetitive breathing
can relieve it.
It's my lack of experience.
I thought she just had ordinary asthma,
so I didn't think
in that direction at all.
If we were a bit later...
It's fine. Don't dwell on it.
Emergency treatment requires experience.
We just need more
professional medical training.
You should go back first.
I'll be here with Lu Qun.
You go home. Don't return to the team.
Alright.
You're right.
Our medical capabilities
are seriously lacking.
We can't even help our own people
when they're injured.
What should we do?
I was thinking that we should
seek a cooperation with a medical school.
I'll go and discuss the details.
For this training camp,
first aid courses must be included. Must.
Don't worry.
This absolutely must be added.
This is a great opportunity
to expand the team.
(Haicheng University)
Come in.
Professor Li, long time no see.
Xingchen, you're here.
Have a seat.
Xingchen.
I heard that you resigned.
Yes.
You
were a top student
when you were studying.
But you should also know
how difficult it is
to get into the current medical system.
I was thinking
do you want to become
Professor Zhang's PhD student?
I've been preparing for a long time.
Good for you. I support you.
Professor Zhang's research direction
is consistent
with your thesis' research direction.
It's very suitable for you.
I also think so.
But Professor Li,
is there anything else
you wanted to tell me today?
I almost forgot.
Here. Take a look at this.
(Polar Night Rescue
Medical Volunteer Registration Form)
Back in school, you were always talking
about joining the rescue team.
Now's your chance.
Right now,
they're forming a first aid department
and urgently need instructors.
You're the most suitable.
A medical volunteer.
This is something I really want to do.
Take a look.
(Polar Night Rescue
Medical Volunteer Registration Form)
Register and gather over there.
Register over there, then gather.
Go register over there.
Then gather over there.
(It's her?)
(How could it be him?)
It can't be this coincidental, right?
Captain Su.
His physique is amazing. He's so hot.
Why are you all excited here?
Are you here to see hot guys?
We're here
for the noble cause of public welfare
- and for hot guys.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up and gather.
- Bye.
You are...
Hello, I'm an instructor
of the medical team.
Dr. Song.
Yes.
Hello, I'm Ding Weiling.
I'm one of the instructors
for this training.
Hello.
I'd like to ask
who was the man just now?
He is the captain
of Haicheng Polar Night Rescue.
The captain?
Him?
Captain Su just took over.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Please gather over there.
Please register and gather here.
(Song Xingchen's Basic Information)
Song Xingchen.
It's a small world, isn't it?
The weather is getting hotter.
I just finished training.
Perfect timing.
Look at you.
Are you training them
or being trained by them?
You have no idea.
This batch is exceptional.
Especially her.
A professional doctor
from a renowned hospital.
Also, she's quite pretty.
I evaluate based on professionalism,
not appearance.
I'm not like you.
Standby.
The rescue team's mission
is to save as many lives as possible
during disasters.
Through rigorous training,
you'll be equipped
to safeguard both yourselves
and those you rescue
when faced with danger.
This training course
includes physical fitness,
rope skills, first aid,
and radio communication.
Just because our rescue team
is a charity doesn't mean
you can treat it as a game.
The assessment in this training camp
marks the first step toward
becoming a formal member
of the rescue team.
Yes.
The rules and regulations
have been distributed to everyone.
You are volunteers now.
After passing the assessment,
you will become formal members
to take on assured tasks.
Do you all have confidence?
Yes!
Let's kick off with a basic warm-up
before the official training.
Do a hundred high knee lifts.
Attention!
Ready!
Go!
Stop.
What's your name?
Report, Sir. Xie Yuan.
Xie Yuan.
You can't wear this during training.
Why?
Do you know
what kind of injuries can be caused
by wearing unnecessary accessories
during intense training?
I don't know.
During high-intensity exercises,
a strong impact
or an accidental fall
might harm yourself
and the person you're rescuing.
Take it off.
Let me emphasize once more.
I don't expect to see
this kind of unnecessary accessories.
Once you become formal team members,
I expect not to see items like these
during rescue operations.
Do you understand?
Understood.
After the training,
there will be a contraband check.
Get ready for high knees.
(Student Dorm)
Hello, ladies.
Here are some snacks.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I'm Liu Xinyu.
A sophomore in the medical school.
How should I address you?
I'm Zhou Yiran.
I'm a flight attendant.
I can tell at a glance
from your demeanor and figures.
How about you?
I'm a doctor. Song Xingchen.
You're my senior.
Nice to meet you.
Surrender all prohibited items
for uniform storage
during the closed training.
Please cooperate proactively.
Surrender all prohibited items
for uniform storage
during the closed training.
Please cooperate proactively.
Hello, sir.
Ms. Song.
It's been a while.
It's you, Mr. Su.
I didn't recognize you.
What happened?
Did the lingerie business struggle,
making you return to doctor life?
Thanks to you,
our business is thriving.
Just these?
Yes.
I'm here for training, not a picnic.
Do you need
to personally inspect my room?
No need for that.
But I want to emphasize again.
During the training,
you must adhere
to the rescue team's rules.
No use of prohibited items.
Captain Su.
Why bother coming here
just to pinpoint my problems?
Are you questioning
the special treatment I provide?
I am a medical team instructor.
I'm here to train volunteers for you.
Yes.
You are a medical team instructor.
But you are a beginner
in the rescue team.
Is there a problem
with following the rules
during the training with everyone?
No problem.
After the training,
we will return these items
to everyone in their original condition.
During this period,
I hope nobody
uses prohibited items secretly,
causing unnecessary trouble.
Thanks for the cooperation.
- Understood.
What? This is so strict.
Captain Su said
high standards, strict requirements.
(I suppose you won't have time
for me in the next few days.)
(What about the store upgrade?)
You have to take care of that.
The necessary files
are backed up on the studio's computer.
Check it out.
(Alright.)
(Do you think)
(he might be intentionally)
(seeking your attention now?)
I don't think so.
But this is such a coincidence.
Alright, I'll hang up for now.
I'll call you when I have time.
Down.
Up.
Why does he want us to carry the logs?
Down.
He shows no mercy at all.
Up.
Stop.
Any problems?
Everyone here is a volunteer.
If you're not interested in training,
I won't push it.
But since you're here,
you should adhere to the rules
and follow the instructions.
Understood?
- Understood.
Another thirty times for everyone.
Down.
(Polar Night Rescue.)
(The top brand
of the China Public Welfare Rescue Team.)
(It has been involved)
(in nearly all
major national disaster relief work.)
(As an aspiring young people,)
(my life before the age of twenty-nine)
(was lived according to a set routine.)
(Now, there's an opportunity)
(to pursue something I've always wanted.)
(Gao Qingyin)
Hey, Xingchen.
Do you want to have a meal with us?
It's okay. I'm on a diet.
- Let's go.
- Alright.
Hi, Yizhu.
You treat her differently.
Who?
You know who I'm talking about.
If it were another girl,
you'd likely keep a ten-meter distance.
You're overthinking it.
You're the confused one here.
Do you know that?
Think back to your entire youth.
At that your school, a small place,
did you talk to a girl
for more than three sentences
besides the instructors?
Oh, right.
That neighbor, Gao Qingyin,
doesn't count.
Then again,
why does she look familiar to me?
Refined and gentle medical student.
Remember?
Could she have come
to put an end to your single life?
You touched my hair again.
Still,
why is she always so harsh on you?
What did you do to her?
I'm also curious
about who she really is.
Yizhu.
I heard Captain Lu
spent great efforts
in inviting Captain Su here.
I heard he's
from a high-ranking official's family.
Is that true?
Sort of.
So, does this Captain Su
have a girlfriend?
It seems not.
Does he have some problem?
What are you thinking all the time?
You're disrespectful.
Did you notice
he maintains a significant distance
from every girl
during the training sessions?
It's very suspicious.
Moreover,
I tried approaching him the other day.
He completely avoids women.
How did you find out?
I knocked on his door late at night,
but he never showed.
So he's gay. He should've told us.
Captain Su conducted a surprise check
for forbidden items.
214, come out.
Immersion heater
is strictly banned in the dorm.
Be careful next time.
Captain Lu, we won't do it next time.
Are you okay?
- Captain Su, please don't get it wrong...
- Alright. Enough.
Take this and come to my office.
You disregarded training
and even sold goods during training
as a medical consultant.
I said this is for personal use.
I didn't intend to sell anything.
Is there a problem? What's wrong with it?
Can you stay away from me?
What exactly do you want?
If you have an issue with me, say it.
Don't you think you have a problem?
What problem do I have?
The only problem here is your ignorance.
(Diagram Of Organs In The Body)
(Artificial Respiration)
That's all
for the theoretical part of CPR.
Take some time to digest it.
We'll practice next time.
Quiet, everyone.
It seems the power tripped.
I'll check.
Quiet.
Did I miss something?
I think I scratched you.
- Let me see.
- No, it's fine.
I'm okay.
It's late. What's the matter?
Just here to check on your injury.
Did Lu Qun ask you to come?
I came on my own.
Your wound could get infected
and still need to be treated.
It's fine, not a big deal.
Sit down.
Come on.
Take off your top.
What's wrong?
I can't apply the medicine if you don't.
Isn't taking off clothes a bit much?
If you don't want to get infected,
quit the nonsense.
Otherwise, I'll stay here.
Need my help?
Let me do it.
Can you reach your wound?
Don't be fussy. I have a light touch.
I'm responsible
for your injury.
Sorry for the trouble.
What?
I also want to apologize to you.
I've checked that thing.
It's indeed for face-slimming.
(Face Slimmer)
I'm sorry.
I was biased against you.
Still, I need to tell you
that it's essentially a stupidity tax
from a scientific perspective.
Do you know the placebo effect
in psychology?
Neurochemical events in the brain,
electrical events,
and the resulting downstream effects
are still effective,
even if it's a placebo.
It's different from a stupidity tax.
What are you doing?
Your nails are too long.
- You might hurt your nail bed.
- Stop.
Are you out of your mind?
In all my years as a doctor,
I've never done nails.
I finally got them done.
How could you?
I didn't mean to scratch you.
Are you seeking revenge?
- Your long nails...
- Stay away.
- will not only hurt yourself...
- but also easily hurt others.
- Let me go.
- Don't move. I'm almost done.
- Qingche.
Is your Chinese zodiac a dog?
You bit me?
You're more likely a dog.
Maybe even a wolfdog.
What do you mean?
Captain Su.
If you don't like women,
don't touch them.
You said I don't like women?
Do you have a misunderstanding about me?
Really?
Prove it to me.
Prove it.
All bark and no bite.
Gosh, they even meddle in nails.
I don't want
to give them an excuse for it.
But it seems reasonable.
Even if it's just an accessory,
it's risky during training.
Moreover, I scratched him.
But they didn't
mention this requirement initially.
That's because Captain Su
simply didn't know
all girls in this world
like doing their nails.
That's right.
(Lu Qun)
(What's going on
between you and Song Xingchen?)
Lu Qun, do you know what this is?
(You're using a beauty device?)
(Do you have to go this far?)
(How does he know about it?)
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Like the rhythmic beats of connection♪
♪Unconsciously♪
♪I pause in your line of sight♪
♪And your world♪
♪Who are you smiling for♪
♪In whose mind
do you linger again and again♪
♪Tirelessly♪
♪How do I cherish this fondness♪
♪If tomorrow is another sunny day♪
♪Shall we make a date at this moment♪
♪Don't let me miss you too much♪
♪If tomorrow brings raindrops♪
♪Let's hurry and find shelter
under the eaves♪
♪Come closer, and I'll hear♪
♪The resounding heartbeat of love♪
♪Reverberating in the long years ahead♪
Why are you here?
You should have
gone to sleep at this hour, right?
You're not sleeping either.
Practiced it before?
I learned it as a child,
but I haven't practiced for a long time.
Can I try it?
Not bad.
I don't know
what the matchmaker said,
but if it affected you badly,
I'm sorry for that.
I've known you for a while now.
You don't seem like a gossipy person.
There's one thing
that I don't understand.
It's so tough here.
Why join the rescue team?
Because I like it.
I wanted to do it before
but didn't have the chance.
So now,
I don't want
to go against my inner wishes anymore.
What do you mean?
Take archery, for example.
I loved it as a child.
But later, for surgical operation job reasons,
I haven't touched it ever since
for fear of hurting my hands.
Focus.
♪In a fleeting moment♪
♪Like the rhythmic beats of connection♪
♪Unconsciously♪
This bow might be a bit heavy for you.
Use a lighter one next time.
♪And your world♪
Okay.
We'll have training tomorrow.
Rest early.
♪In whose mind
do you linger again and again♪
♪Tirelessly♪
♪How do I cherish this fondness♪
One, two, one.
For tomorrow's meeting,
make sure you have those documents
ready today.
No problem.
What happened
between you two last night?
Why care so much about it?
She only put medicine on me.
You're dull.
I feel that your springtime is coming.
Stop talking nonsense, will you?
You've been acting odd these days.
Your professional habit
keeps you always distant from others.
You're quite close with her, though.
Just mind your own business.
Are you having lunch, Dr. Song?
Captain Su, are you
observing how we're doing?
You're eating too little.
You're today's lecturer.
Eat more.
You have a good memory.
Dr. Song.
The car that helps transport the dummy
had a bit of trouble on its way here.
It'll take a while to arrive.
It'll be too late.
We can't delay our training.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Now, I'll teach everyone
the correct procedure
for cardiopulmonary resuscitation.
Now, Sun Yizhu and I
will demonstrate it together.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
Firstly, we need to determine
whether the patient's breathing
and heartbeat have stopped.
Use the most sensitive part of your palm
to feel the heartbeat.
Use your earlobe to feel if the person
is breathing.
The key to performing CPR
is that the compression-to-breath ratio
is 15:1.
Continue for five cycles
in about two minutes
before reassessing the patient.
Blow gently.
Be careful not to blow too hard.
During the process, we need to observe
whether the patient's chest rises.
Then, we need
to perform repeated chest compressions
and artificial respiration.
Make sure to keep an eye
on the patient's real-time response.
Next,
let's practice in pairs.
Xie Yuan, don't you have a partner?
No, I don't.
Then I'll pair up with you.
Okay.
No, that's not appropriate.
Captain Su.
We're about
to practice artificial respiration.
It requires pairing up.
I know that.
How about you do it?
Me?
It's not a good idea
for both of us, right?
It's not us two. It's you and Xie Yuan.
Patient, are you okay?
He needs resuscitation.
Keep your arms straight.
Press harder. It's 15:1.
Xie Yuan.
I'm talking
about artificial respiration,
not kissing.
Why so nervous?
Okay.
The dummy has arrived.
Here.
Captain Su, did you...
Xie Yuan, the dummy's here.
Practice with it.
Okay.
Continue practicing.
Radio communication is a skill
that every member
of our rescue team must have.
Now, follow the instructions provided
and tune your device
to our team's frequency.
(Radio Communication
by Polar Night Rescue)
Captain Su.
I still can't get it to work.
Can you help me?
Me too. I can't either.
Yours is working now.
Here.
Hello?
Which frequency are you on?
Are you trying to communicate with aliens?
Hello?
(Hello?)
Roger.
(Roger.)
No need to hurry, everyone.
It's okay
if you haven't tuned it properly.
After you go back,
refer to the manual given to you.
Get familiar with the frequency tuning
and troubleshooting of your walkie-talkie.
We'll have a test tomorrow.
♪Your tenderness is like
the light of the polar night♪
♪Following your direction,
filled with fantasies♪
♪Days become lengthy,
the world is forgotten♪
♪Wishing to confirm
if you're just like me♪
♪Please don't shy away,
come a bit closer♪
♪No matter how distant,
bravely move forward♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪Loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪