♪The future is a constantly
spinning spinning top♪
♪Polished by the hands of time♪
♪Yet my footsteps follow♪
♪Even in adversity,
we can pull a string together♪
♪Go whereever we want♪
♪My heart is never confused♪
♪When I set my sights on beauty♪
♪I believe without hesitation♪
♪Your gaze is so clear♪
♪Like the stars embracing the vastness♪
♪Love ignites like fireworks♪
♪Brightening the polar night♪
♪We won't be silent♪
♪I hear the pulsating rhythm
of your heart♪
♪Even if the night becomes mottled♪
♪How can love silently pass by♪
♪In the midst of radiance,
a silhouette appears♪
♪Bringing the warmth
into the palms of our hands♪
♪There's no reason
not to hold on tightly♪
♪I want you for every moment of my life♪
♪To be with me♪
=Got A Crush On You=
(Adapted from Bei Qing's novel "Got A Crush On You")
=Episode 13=
You lost.
Watch out for your image.
Someone is recording.
Got it?
All is fair in war. You got distracted.
Got it.
You better not cross the line.
How's my move?
Qingyin, do you really have to do this?
I've decided to give it another try.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Qingyin got everyone coffee.
Welcome, Miss Gao.
It's nice to see you here.
- Thank you.
I bought some coffee and snacks
for everyone.
Every time Qingche gets busy with work,
he ignores everything else.
Please bear with him, everyone.
Let's thank her once again.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
She's not right.
Captain Su treats us well all the time.
What are you saying?
Miss Gao treats us better.
Are you here to check on Qingche today?
Certainly not.
I trust him completely.
Where's Captain Su?
He should be in the training room.
Yes. With Dr. Song.
I'll look for him. You stay here.
Qingche.
You got distracted,
but all is fair in war.
You taught me that.
Are you alright, Qingche?
I'm fine.
I don't need your help.
Why is she everywhere?
She's like a lingering presence
that won't leave.
Good luck to Captain Su.
Xingchen.
Even though it's practice,
you should prioritize safety.
What if something happens?
Qingyin, I'm fine.
Please get down from here.
Qingche is invincible.
He can take a fall and a hit.
Don't you know?
Xingchen.
Thank you for training
with Qingche today.
I was just too worried
about him just now.
Don't take it to heart, alright?
Sure.
But...
What's wrong?
All the recent activities involve
just the two of us.
You might have to get used to it.
How...
It's all for the charity event.
You won't mind, will you?
Of course, not.
Seeing how well you practice,
I can't help but want to spar with you.
Qingyin. Stop messing around.
I learned Taekwondo from Qingche,
you know.
I'd like to find out
if I've forgotten the moves.
Lu Qun.
- Take Qingyin...
- Sure.
It's not for you. Don't assume.
This is going to be interesting.
Qiancheng. She's your aunt.
Exactly. That's the interesting part.
Don't you know Song Xingchen?
Will she fight
if she can't win?
I can't control you,
but someone else may.
Xingchen.
If you fall later,
watch out for your bones.
You'll risk having a bone fracture
at your age.
If you lose, don't cry, okay?
I'm not good at comforting children.
One more thing.
No hitting the face.
Goodluck, Aunt Xingchen.
My leg.
I told you not to cry. How old are you?
Be gentle.
How is she?
It's just a little scratch.
Let's go to the infirmary.
I don't want your fake concern.
You guys take her to the infirmary.
Qingyin, let's go.
Can you carry me there, Qingche?
What are you waiting for? Go.
Come on, help her up.
This is too much fuss.
I guess we'll stay here.
Let her down.
Let go.
Don't go.
Qingyin.
Can you stop acting like a child?
The doctor will be here soon.
Do you really like her?
Of course, I do. She's my girlfriend.
Are you guys dating already?
Yes, we are.
So please don't mention our
arranged marriage anymore.
Aren't we in one?
Of course, not.
I don't care.
She's a vixen.
You've been bewitched by her.
Qingyin.
All along,
I've treated you as my little sister.
It's me who initiated the relationship.
So I know her very well.
After all these years,
this is my first time in a relationship.
I hope you don't make it difficult
for me.
If possible, get along well with her.
You'll find that she's a nice person.
Why did you provoke her?
She's not an easy person to deal with.
Which side are you on?
I'm definitely on your side.
But I'm doing this for your own good.
Qingyin.
Don't you know how Qingche is?
Once he sets his mind on someone,
he won't change.
Besides, I've known Ms. Song
for some time now.
She's indeed a nice person.
So I'd like to advise you
to find someone who suits you.
Don't cling to him
because it won't end well.
That's all from me.
You should take a break.
I'll look for the team doctor.
Aunt Xingchen.
I have something to tell you.
I just heard Su Qingche
telling Gao Qingyin
that he only sees her
as a little sister,
and it was him
who initiated the relationship.
He told her
not to mess with you anymore.
Did he really say that?
To be honest, I always thought
Su Qingche was acting like he's single,
especially after meeting Gao Qingyin.
But now, it seems
that it was true all along.
He and Tang are evenly matched now.
A draw.
What are you thinking about all day?
I've already said
that there's no possibility
between me and Tang Ruize.
Alright.
Seeing how biased you are toward him,
I'll add 20 points to him.
- How about 70-30?
- Mind your own business.
How's Gao Qingyin's injury?
I don't know.
The team doctor hasn't come yet.
Then why are you standing here?
If it weren't for your shout just now,
she wouldn't have been injured.
If it weren't for your push,
she wouldn't have fallen.
Well, I did it for you.
Then why don't you
go check on her for me?
And comfort her while you're at it.
Gao Qingyin has a sharp tongue.
I'm a bit scared of her.
Will you go or not?
Fine. She's your sister-in-law,
after all.
For your happiness in later years,
I'll bear this burden.
What sister-in-law?
Nothing has been confirmed yet.
Are you in such a hurry
to see her as a relative?
Alright. I get it.
Go quickly.
(Infirmary)
Be gentle.
Ouch.
Um...
Is she okay?
If you had come a bit later,
the wound would have healed already.
Gently.
Come on. No fractures.
Su Qingche isn't here. Stop wailing.
Is it really fine?
This is just a scratch.
Keep an eye on her.
I have something to do.
Tell me if you need anything.
Sorry.
You got hurt because of me.
Have some water.
I don't want your fake sympathy.
You and your aunt are just the same.
Aggressive and ruthless.
You wanted to compete with her.
But you won't admit your defeat.
I won't admit defeat.
I have my ways.
Fine.
Then let me tell you.
As long as it's someone
Song Xingchen likes,
she won't easily give up either.
Your rank isn't even enough.
I'm leaving. Good luck.
Are you going to leave me here alone?
Otherwise?
Do you want me to carry you?
That works too. Wait a moment.
Carry you like this?
Qiancheng! Get out!
Okay, if you said so.
Call me if you need anything.
Xingchen.
You're here.
I've been waiting for you.
I did teach Gao Qingyin Taekwondo,
but
it was when we were...
Alright, you don't need to explain.
I already know what you said
to Gao Qingyin just now.
Qiancheng wanted to check on Gao Qingyin
but accidentally overheard.
I'm sorry to make you annoyed.
As long as you're firm
in your position and attitude,
other things don't matter.
You sweated, right?
I'll get you some clothes.
I want to wear yours.
My clothes are only
for my girlfriend to wear.
When it comes to opposite-sex clothing,
I only wear my boyfriend's.
Song Xingchen.
It seems you lost our game.
You lost too.
Since you lost, I want a reward.
What reward?
We just launched LYS products.
I want you to help me boost sales.
Why does it sound like an online scam?
- Boost or not?
- Boost.
Remember to leave a good review.
Sure thing.
You lost too. What's my reward?
Captain Su, we...
We have a meeting later.
I'll go prepare first.
Let's go.
Change your clothes.
Hurry up.
Why didn't you say you were coming?
I've already completed your reward.
I saw it in the backend.
Not bad. Exceeded my request.
What about my reward?
Alright, what reward do you want?
I've bought the ingredients.
I want you to cook me a meal.
Are you sure?
Have you thought about it?
It takes courage to eat my cooking.
I have the courage.
I've even prepared stomach medicine.
Alright.
Also,
it's my first time officially
coming to my girlfriend's house,
so I have to prepare a surprise.
Do you like it?
Impressive.
Alright, I'll show off
my cooking skills today.
Let's go.
Be careful with your fingers.
Can I cut it like this?
It's fine.
You can cut it into any shape you want.
Make sure I look good on screen.
Got it.
You look good from any angle.
Be careful.
I'm already looking forward to it.
It's heavy.
I'll serve the rice.
The water for the rice
seems a bit too much.
As long as the water covers the rice,
a joint of one finger is enough.
Alright.
And this tomato scrambled eggs.
The tomatoes seem a bit overcooked.
The meat...
It seems a bit overcooked too.
Have you not taken enough
self-defense classes?
Coach Su.
I've taken enough.
Do you still want to eat?
Yes, of course.
It's delicious.
Really?
Really. Try it.
Try it.
How is it?
Not tasty?
Is your sense of taste malfunctioning,
Su Qingche?
Don't eat it.
Don't.
I want to eat.
Don't move.
Don't eat it. You'll get diarrhea.
I won't.
Really?
It's really delicious.
How did you do it?
As long as it's made by you, I love it.
What are you looking at?
I want to drink beer and eat duck neck.
Go get them for me downstairs.
It's so late,
and you still want to eat and drink?
Do you have no conscience?
I didn't eat anything just now.
Okay. I'll go now.
I'm going to take a shower.
When did you come back?
I just got back.
I also bought fried chicken.
I'll stay with you
until we finish eating.
Okay.
(Viewing history)
"Virgin Boss Wants To Marry Me".
"My Rescue Team Boyfriend".
I didn't read those. It's Xiaoli.
Did Han Xiaoli come by a few days ago?
Alright, she didn't.
I read those. Is that not allowed?
It's allowed, but it's not necessary.
What do you mean?
Your boyfriend, me,
is the captain of a rescue team, right?
So what?
Now I'm right by your side.
So we've almost finished eating.
Isn't it time to sleep?
It's not even 10:00 p.m. yet.
It's early.
Then what do you want to do?
Well, I bought something.
Can you help me try it out?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Su Qingche.
How could you
really attack me?
I didn't do it on purpose.
You did it on purpose.
Let's start again.
Bring it on.
Su Qingche!
One hit is not enough,
so you hit me twice?
How could you?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Lies. I'm quitting.
Don't quit.
It's fun.
Let's play a different one.
Which one?
Log Wobble.
(Haicheng City Go Tournament.
Title: "Emerging Go Player".)
(Salt)
(Sugar)
Nice pajamas.
I got changed the moment I arrived.
What is it? Still angry?
Since you come early to apologize,
I'll let you off for now.
But when you leave later,
take the game console with you
and throw it away.
Throw it away?
What?
It was a lousy game.
What's wrong? Here. Sit.
I think
I get a stiff neck in my sleep.
How come?
Let me have a look.
Is it here?
Better now?
Yeah.
- Massage a bit harder.
- Okay.
It can get even better.
Really?
Tilt your head a bit to the right.
By the way,
which fruit do you prefer
for breakfast?
Su Qingche.
Are you trying to break my neck?
Easy.
The process may be unpleasant.
But try moving your neck a bit now.
It's better now, right?
Yeah, it does.
But you still shouldn't surprise me.
As long as you're better now.
Let's have breakfast now.
I made it for you specially.
My neck seems to be better now.
I like to play some nice music
when I have breakfast. Is that okay?
Sure, go ahead.
Su Qingche.
Is that me...
Is it good?
Leave me with some dignity, Su Qingche.
You're mean.
Grandpa.
Kid, you're here.
No need to buy things for me.
What's wrong with your leg?
Someone bullied me.
Who is it? They're audacious.
Tell me about it.
I'll teach them a lesson.
A woman. A particularly annoying woman.
A woman?
Sit down.
Sit down and tell me
what happened exactly.
How could this woman be so audacious?
Tell me. What happened?
I just came back from Qingche's place.
It happened right in front of him?
Why didn't he do anything?
Who is this woman?
It's the one from the blind date.
The blind date? Who is it?
The one who owns the lingerie shop.
She used to be a doctor.
Right, I remember.
But they're over now.
It didn't work out. They ended it.
It's Song Xingchen.
Grandpa, look. She did this.
Your injury looks serious.
I don't understand though.
You two don't know each other
and are hardly connected.
So how did you get into a fight?
Due to a public welfare event,
she's always pestering Qingche,
and she's jealous
of how well he treats me.
She's in the rescue team too?
This is tricky.
I think she's using the event
as an excuse to get close to Qingche.
Maybe it's because of her job,
she's very open-minded.
She keeps looking for Qingche,
ignoring the fact
that they are a man and woman alone.
Interesting.
How is it now?
Is that woman pursuing Qingche?
Grandpa, you can't be this desperate.
Song Xingchen
made me sick the other day.
Even though I'm a dedicated model,
I can't handle the cold.
There were like seven
or eight fans blowing right at me.
Seven or eight fans?
That's too much.
This woman
has a problem with her character.
She's disloyal.
While still involved
with her ex-boyfriend,
she's getting close to Qingche.
She's entangled with her ex-boyfriend?
No, this won't do.
This is a matter of morality.
This is bad.
She's a vixen.
Grandpa.
You must hold your bottom line.
You can't let a woman
like her into your family.
If what you say is true,
I'd rather have Qingche
stay single forever
than have this kind
of woman into our Su family.
Grandpa.
You have to step up at a time like this.
Qingche listens to you the most.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely step up
when the time comes.
Grandpa, I'm back.
Why did you come?
Your knee is better?
I'm fine now.
I just got some groceries
from the market.
I'll help if you cook.
I bought these at the market by myself.
They are fresh.
(Online shopping)
The joy of online grocery shopping?
Someone must have put that in.
Qingyin.
Avoid coming
to the Rescue Centre in the future.
Why?
You're not a member of the rescue team.
It's not good for you to be there.
You'll bother our training.
Is it because of Song Xingchen?
I don't want to repeat this again.
Didn't I make it clear to you?
I don't want anyone
to misunderstand our relationship.
I didn't clarify it
in front of the others
and Grandpa
because I want to leave you
with some dignity.
Qingche.
I'm telling you.
A home only feels like a home
when there's a woman.
Look. Just now,
she was washing vegetables,
and you were cutting them.
That scene was heartwarming,
very heartwarming.
Grandpa, enough.
Please stop with the matchmaking, okay?
Who's the one dating? Me or you?
You.
That's it.
You have to start dating though.
You haven't
given me a definite answer until now.
Of course,
I'll arrange blind dates for you.
I beg you. Please stop arranging them.
I have someone I like.
Really?
If you have someone you like,
bring her back for me to see.
This thing
must be put on the agenda.
What's the deal
with your former blind date?
Did Qingyin tell you something?
What can she tell me?
You two grew up together.
She always takes your side.
You're lying.
So what did she tell you?
Why do you care?
Is it true you're dating the woman?
Yes, we're dating.
You should bring her back for us to see.
I'm planning
to wait
until our relationship gets more stable.
Besides,
aren't you the one who finds her?
The matchmaker
only told me a little about her.
I haven't even met her.
Good.
Stop worrying about it. Okay?
Who else will worry about you then?
To be honest,
my choice of a granddaughter-in-law
is very straightforward.
Her profession, appearance,
and even family background.
Those aren't important.
The key is that she must
have a good character.
Yes, I know.
You can't have one foot in each boat,
juggling between two relationships.
That's bad, a matter of principles.
Also,
she must be mature.
No matter what she does,
even if it's running an online store,
she must
do things steadily and reliably,
not giving others a chance
to find fault.
Okay, I understand, Grandpa.
Rest assured.
I know what to do and my limits, okay?
Your limits?
You say it like you
have many experiences
and have been in several relationships.
You better follow my standards
to find your partner.
Your limits?
Happy Kitten?
Grandpa, try this fish belly.
It's very tender.
You have some, too.
Grandpa, I'm done eating.
I still have materials to read,
I'll leave first.
I'll come with.
No.
You accompany Grandpa and chat with him.
Go home soon.
Grandpa, I'll clean up later.
Kid.
Don't be so anxious.
Regarding
Qingche and Song Xingchen,
I will consider it carefully.
Grandpa.
don't you think
Qingche should find someone
who knows everything about him?
Yes.
I understand what you mean.
But you must remember this advice.
All things have their fate.
A melon forced to grow is not sweet.
Grandpa.
If I don't force it,
someone else will eat it.
Then remember this.
Ignore the words of the elders
at your peril.
Alright. Eat.
Here, have some more meat.
Stop thinking about this matter.
That's right.
(Stardust Rouge)
The response
to Gao Qingyin's photos is really good.
Our popularity has increased a lot.
This proves that our vertical approach
is quite effective.
The new approach
we designed suits LYS very well.
Let me check Weibo.
Everyone's praising our website
for its high-end design
and that it's different from the norm.
But some are also praising Gao Qingyin.
Why do we
(Mentions: 502, Comments: 23, Likes: 12)
have so many messages on our Weibo?
Let me see.
Look.
(Netizens: That's so sweet.)
(They're hugging.)
(Netizens:
This is like a real-life TV drama.)
(When will this happen to me?)
(Dear boss, how much should I
buy to get a handsome guy?)
(Both man and woman look stunning.)
(Simply outstanding.)
(I want to visit the store.)
You guys look so great together.
When the video went viral,
many people traced it back to us.
This is great.
Not only did it
create buzz for Polar Night,
but it also brought us a lot of traffic.
Looks like we
need to commend Qiancheng for this.
But I've noticed
someone's boyfriend secretly
purchased our products.
If I didn't know, I'd think he
bought them for someone else.
Here I am, thinking about promotions,
and you're teasing me.
I wouldn't dare.
But I've already shipped the goods.
The address is Captain Su's house.
By the way, I have some sorting to do.
I'll be at the warehouse.
Go ahead.
Why are you here?
To celebrate
the store's increased sales.
I also brought your favorite drink.
What's up?
I have a training session in Sucheng,
and hope you can accompany me.
No problem.
I was just
thinking of going sightseeing.
But most importantly, to be with you.
But I don't know if you're ready.
Ready for what?
I need to evaluate my teachings.
Right here?
You're in danger now.
A villain tightly
hugged you from behind.
What should you do?
Hold the villain's arm firmly
and strike backward at his crotch,
which will temporarily immobilize him.
Not bad.
Now,
the villain hugs you tightly
from the front,
and you can't break free.
What should you do?
Form your hands like a bowl
and press them on his ears,
causing pain to his ears
and gaining an opportunity to escape.
He's hugging even tighter now.
Don't your ears hurt?
Why aren't you letting go?
No, they don't.
You're so good-looking
that I can't feel pain.
You're here.
You guys continue.
Pretend I'm not here.
Where are you going?
You want me to send all these out today?
Don't we have free labor?
Thank you.
Captain Su.
If you come here more often,
we wouldn't need
to hire someone to pack things.
You never needed one
in the first place. I am the packer.
Who is it?
Coming.
I'm coming.
Wang.
Old Mr. Su, this
is your grandson's delivery.
I saw it when I finished work
and brought it over.
Who's the sender?
Happy
Kitten.
Okay.
Why are you staring? Go home.
Happy Kitten?
Sounds like it's from a girl.
I'll open it and take a look.
It's a package, not a letter,
right?
I need to check it.
So many things?
What is this stuff?
Smells pretty good.
Facial cleansing oil?
What's this?
Shaving cream?
What?
What is this thing?
Silky smooth.
(Rose soothe)
Unlocks the secret of a woman's body.
Wait. What is all this?
The two of you showing off on screen
have caused an uproar
in the comment section.
It works really well.
You even promoted Xingchen's store
and brought them some traffic.
Are you guys going to Sucheng together
for the upcoming task?
Good work, bro.
What are you thinking?
We're not staying together.
As for you,
you better oversee everything here
and don't make mistakes.
It will be fine.
I know what to do, so don't worry.
Are you sure?
Personnel arrangements
and who will be going?
Tell me.
It's definitely going...
(Grandpa)
Your phone.
Hey, Grandpa. What's up?
(Su Qingche.)
Come back home immediately.
I...
(Immediately.)
What's going on?
Look at this. What is this thing?
Vulgar and indecent.
Chaotic private life.
What a disgrace.
Report.
My private life is extremely healthy.
It couldn't be healthier.
You call this healthy?
I think you're a pervert.
With such moral character, who would
dare match you up with any girl?
Didn't I tell you last time?
The last one was pretty good,
so no more.
Wait a minute.
Is it that one with an indecent job?
Did she send all these things to you?
But she's
not doing anything indecent now.
She now runs a women's supply store.
Come on. It's still the same.
But why is she
sending you all these obscene things?
I feel embarrassed just looking at them.
Grandpa. These aren't obscene things.
These are things
that women often use.
You don't know these products,
so you shouldn't judge them.
I believe you're a reasonable person.
Regardless of that,
How could a woman send these things
to a man for no reason?
I can't accept that, either.
This is her business.
It's legal and reasonable.
You can't judge her character
based on what products she sells.
Once you meet her and get to know her,
I believe you will be satisfied.
But these...
these are all women's things.
Can you use them?
I don't know.
I bought them to support her business.
You bought them?
To support her business?
Yeah.
Not bad, kid.
You've improved.
You know how to win a woman's favor now.
Fine. You've already bought it anyway.
But take them away.
They're an eyesore.
Grandpa, why don't I
apply some on your hands?
- Go away.
- It's moisturizing.
Take them away. Quick.
Hurry up.
Are you not going to try it?
(Stardust Rouge)
Stardust Rouge?
♪Your tenderness is like
the light of the polar night♪
♪Following your direction,
filled with fantasies♪
♪Days become lengthy,
the world is forgotten♪
♪Wishing to confirm
if you're just like me♪
♪Please don't shy away,
come a bit closer♪
♪No matter how distant,
bravely move forward♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪Loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪