♪The future is a constantly
spinning spinning top♪
♪Polished by the hands of time♪
♪Yet my footsteps follow♪
♪Even in adversity,
we can pull a string together♪
♪Go whereever we want♪
♪My heart is never confused♪
♪When I set my sights on beauty♪
♪I believe without hesitation♪
♪Your gaze is so clear♪
♪Like the stars embracing the vastness♪
♪Love ignites like fireworks♪
♪Brightening the polar night♪
♪We won't be silent♪
♪I hear the pulsating rhythm
of your heart♪
♪Even if the night becomes mottled♪
♪How can love silently pass by♪
♪In the midst of radiance,
a silhouette appears♪
♪Bringing the warmth
into the palms of our hands♪
♪There's no reason
not to hold on tightly♪
♪I want you for every moment of my life♪
♪To be with me♪
=Got A Crush On You=
(Adapted from Bei Qing's novel "Got A Crush On You")
=Episode 1=
(Purple Flavour)
As a doctor, Song Xingchen
dresses like a female star every day.
Right. The hospital's performance
requirements are so strict.
She ranks last every quarter.
If everyone
in our hospital is like this,
not wanting to make money,
we'll have to live on air together.
She relies on being good-looking.
I guess she got promoted
to attending doctor due to her looks.
Those who know, know.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Congratulations, Xingchen.
Today, we're here to celebrate your promotion
to attending doctor.
Come, let's
congratulate Xingchen together.
Mr. Zhang always takes care of you.
Shouldn't you have a drink with him?
Everyone.
Thank you for coming today.
Also, thanks to Mr. Zhang
for nurturing me over the years.
I'll toast to everyone.
Let's raise our glasses.
Congratulations to Xingchen's promotion
to attending doctor.
Cheers.
- Congratulations, Xingchen.
- Congratulations.
Today's gathering
is not a promotion banquet.
It's a farewell dinner.
I've resigned.
Resigned?
Why did you resign?
Between professionalism and performance,
I think professionalism
is more important.
Of course.
Thank you for taking care of me
over the years.
Goodbye, everyone.
(My name is Song Xingchen.
29 years old this year.)
(Originally, I was)
(a sensible and excellent child.)
(I obediently
met my family's expectations)
(and got into medical school.)
(I did my residency
and went through the standard training.)
(With the recommendation of my mentor,)
(I started working
at a private hospital.)
(Following the normal trajectory,)
(I'd apply for a professional title)
(and become a renowned doctor.)
(But now,)
(everything has changed.)
Here.
Have you really thought it through?
Of course. Otherwise?
You've planned this for a long time,
Song Xingchen.
Well done.
Of course, it's not that simple.
I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
But this is also good.
Anyway,
I couldn't stand it long ago.
For the sake of surgery,
you not only need to focus on academics
but also take shifts regularly
to care for patients.
There are times when you don't sleep
for two days and nights.
Doctors are all like this.
That's not something to complain about.
But...
I joined this hospital
after I graduated.
I still have some feelings for it.
But people have to aim higher.
I still have to go for further training.
You're already preparing
for further training now.
How about joining me
in starting a business?
Me?
A women's supply store?
What's wrong with that?
Okay.
For the happy lives of the ladies,
I'm willing to put in all my effort.
Let's go. Let's welcome
the upcoming 30s together.
Cheers.
(Honor Certificate:
Outstanding performance in the 2014)
(Haicheng City Go Tournament.
Title: "Emerging Go Player".)
You're already preparing
for further training now.
How about joining me
in starting a business?
I'll treat you to some meat.
(Oh no.)
(I seem to have promised Xiaoli
to help her with the store.)
(Song Xingchen.)
(Stardust Rouge)
(Recipient:)
Thanks.
You're welcome.
(Why are they almost expired?)
(Stardust Rouge)
Hello?
Why did you
send me a bunch of old stock?
It's a month away from expiration.
(How can you get this price
if it's not old stock?)
(They're not expired
and are authentic, right?)
That's true.
But I can't sell them at all.
Who would buy a bunch
of almost expired things
and keep them at home?
(We only handle delivery, not sales.)
(You have to solve it yourself.)
How can you...
Hello?
Xingchen, you're here.
Come in and sit.
About what you told me yesterday...
I had too much to drink yesterday.
Don't take it to heart.
We agreed to eat meat together.
I can't.
Xingchen.
There's a problem
with this batch of goods I bought.
I heard about it.
This is a good opportunity.
How is this an opportunity?
It's a big pit.
I can jump in by myself,
but I can't drag you in with me.
Crisis is an opportunity.
If you let me invest at a low price now,
it's a good deal for me.
I estimate the value of your shop
to be 300 thousand.
I'll contribute 150 thousand and myself.
If we make a profit, we split it 50-50.
Isn't that a good deal?
I know you mean well,
but
it's really troublesome this time.
I really don't want
to drag you into this.
Look at me.
Don't worry.
Even if it's a big pit,
we can level it.
Ms. Han, look forward working with you.
What are you hesitating for?
You may lack confidence in yourself,
but don't forget who I am.
When things are tough,
Song Xingchen
will overcome all obstacles.
Alright.
We need to sell this batch of goods
within two months.
Since it's called "Stardust Rouge",
we need to get on the go.
(Beilun District
Binhai New City Hospital)
On ultrasound, there's nothing wrong.
But the child in the belly
changes every day.
We can't do the check every day, right?
I wanted
(Office of the director)
to do a comprehensive examination again.
Money is a small matter.
(Office of the director)
Mainly, we want to buy peace of mind.
Our hospital
just updated its equipment last month.
I think it's especially suitable
for families like yours.
It seems like Song Xingchen
doesn't want to work anymore.
Exactly.
Everyone in our department
knows the performance metrics.
But she pretends not to know.
She doesn't want to do this and that.
She ranks last in the metrics
every quarter.
She's the best at pretending.
Really.
I admit I'm not as good as you all
in terms of quota.
I'm just decent in my specialty.
(Welcome to Block No. 11 Fashion Street)
Look. What's that?
It's a puppy.
Isn't that dangerous?
Hey, kid, what's going on?
A little dog climbed up there.
What should we do, Miss?
What's happening?
Sir.
Is there a tenant on the third floor?
We should go up now to save the dog.
Third floor, right?
No one here.
They've all gone abroad.
The door is locked. You can't get in.
I'll call for rescue.
Don't worry.
Be careful!
Be careful.
Impressive. I feel scared just watching.
Come over here.
Here.
Come here.
Come on.
Be careful!
Quick. Let's help
to catch it.
Here it comes.
How about that man?
Hey, what's up?
(Don't forget today is your duty day.)
Got it.
I'll be there soon.
Here. Hold it.
It's fine.
It's just its front leg
is twisted.
Take good care of it.
Be more careful.
Don't leave the dog
in a dangerous place.
Understood.
- Thank you, Miss.
(Haicheng City Rescue Center)
We're here
to announce something important.
Let's welcome the new captain
of Polar Night Rescue,
Su Qingche, Captain Su.
Hello, everyone. Su Qingche here.
Let me introduce Captain Su first.
Captain Su graduated
from the International Security Academy,
the most authoritative institution
in the field
of counter-terrorism worldwide.
Captain Su has also served
in international rescue missions
and worked as an instructor
at the Lorburg Counter-Terrorism School.
As you all know,
Polar Night Rescue
is a purely voluntary team.
We don't get paid.
As part
of the government's rescue force,
we have to go
into the heart of disasters.
Now, I take on the role of captain.
It won't be much different
from Captain Lu.
I just hope
to strengthen
and expand our grassroots rescue force,
help more people,
and establish Polar Night Rescue
as a prominent rescue brand.
Let's welcome Captain Su.
Xingchen.
How come you have time
to come home for dinner?
Is your work not busy?
Yeah, it's not busy.
Private hospitals
are different from public ones.
They have specific quota
and are very busy.
How come you have some free time now?
I had been working overtime before,
so it's my turn to take a break now.
A while ago,
a few old friends and I had a gathering.
You won't believe it.
Someone knows Mr. Zhang
from your department.
How is he like?
He's fine.
Good.
How about this?
Let's arrange a meal
with Mr. Zhang some day.
Dad, can you two stop meddling
in my work?
Okay, we won't meddle in your work.
But for other things,
you have to let us handle them.
We have...
arranged a blind date for you.
(Su Qingche)
I won't go on a blind date.
Do you even know what type I like?
You even have a type?
I like handsome ones.
What's the use of handsome guys?
I mean handsome as in...
Forget it. You won't understand.
I've seen this information.
This young man has a good background.
Look. He is excellent.
Are you going or not?
Alright,
let's arrange a meal with Mr. Zhang
and talk about your career.
Shall I call him now?
I'll go.
I'll have to eat more now
in case I lose my appetite tomorrow.
(The Most Outstanding Volunteer
in Haicheng City: Lu Qun)
Come on. Get up. Let's continue.
I'm done.
You're crazy.
No more?
Yeah.
Really? Is it that tiring?
No one confronts their buddy
so aggressively.
You didn't practice enough
and have regressed.
The firefighting equipment here
is insufficient.
The equipment
should be inspected every six months.
Dude.
We're just a charity.
We don't have money to get those things.
Is it a money problem?
It's a safety awareness problem.
Alright.
Dude, you just took office today,
and you're nagging at me.
Are you a robot?
What's the use
of constantly training me anyway?
Tonight, when you go home,
pick a handsome outfit.
Get ready for your blind date tomorrow.
How do you know about the date?
Well.
Grandpa is concerned about you.
Being his only grandson,
you're never at home.
Of course, he wants
to find a woman to tie you down at home.
I wonder what Grandpa does to bribe you.
That's not cool.
Don't say that about Grandpa.
He didn't bribe me at all.
Anyway,
Grandpa asked me
to send your resume to the matchmaker,
including your assets,
your most handsome photo,
and your home address.
Most importantly,
I wrote your resume, so good luck.
(Han Xiaoli)
Hey.
How did it go, babe?
Have you confessed today?
(Not yet.)
My mom wants me
to pick between spilling the resignation
or going on a blind date.
I picked the blind date.
How's the guy
your mom found for you this time?
Can he meet your approval?
(How long
since you were in a relationship?)
(Before, you didn't have time.)
(This time,)
I think you should find a suitable one
and give it a try.
If I can find one,
why do I need a blind date?
Besides,
my focus now is to manage the store
and pursue further studies.
Even if I really want to date,
what I expect is a mutual
and balanced love.
That's right.
The so-called blind date
is to let a group of people
who are least skilled
in wooing the opposite sex
try their luck
with the most challenging catches.
Ms. Song, be careful.
No, it's this man who should be careful.
I'm going to mess it up.
What are you planning to do?
First, deliberately be late.
Second, wear revealing clothes.
Third, argue about everything.
No man
can endure this three-pronged attack.
I wish you success then, Ms. Song.
(I'll be waiting for you at the store.)
Okay. Miss you.
(Bye.)
Bye.
(Restaurant No. 1 Building)
(Su Qingche)
(I deliberately
dressed like this today.)
(It should be enough to scare him away.)
(Su Qingche)
You're Su Qingche, right?
Ms. Song?
That's me.
Nice to meet you.
(It's her.)
Take a seat.
Ms. Song.
You're 15 minutes late.
I didn't even notice.
Why come on a blind date?
Family requirements.
That makes two of us.
(Su Qingche)
Based on the profile here,
you're a firefighter?
Not a government official.
And you are...
A doctor?
Not anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm not a doctor anymore.
My current identity
is the manager
of a women's supply store.
(Stardust Rogue)
What did you say?
You heard me.
You should update your profile.
I see your profile
isn't very reliable either.
International Security Academy
and Counter-Terrorism School's
instructor.
Are you a counter-terrorism enthusiast?
Ms. Song,
are you questioning my profession?
Probably only naive girls
will believe in your crafted image.
You're acting quite well.
Looks about 30% convincing.
Ms. Song, you have high standards.
Alright, let's get to the process.
If you don't mind,
report your height, weight,
salary, savings,
and family relationships.
Sir.
Isn't it a bit impolite
to look at people like this?
Sorry.
I was just thinking,
have we met somewhere before?
Do you think this tactic works on me?
Let's get to the point.
Sorry.
I don't want to answer those questions
you asked earlier.
Then, Mr. Su,
is there anything you can reveal?
House?
Car?
Exes?
It's all in the profile.
How can I tell if it's exaggerated
just by looking at the profile?
Speaking of profiles,
your profile
has a big gap.
It's not favorable for your blind date.
What gap?
(Song Xingchen)
Is it you in this photo?
Of course, it's me.
(Song Xingchen)
It's an exact match.
Any objections?
No objections.
Just a friendly reminder.
It says in your profile
that you have no dating experience.
Have you been single since childhood?
Why act innocent?
It seems you have
a high opinion of my profile.
That's not the case.
I just feel like you go for wool
and come home shorn.
You're not very emotionally intelligent.
You're quite good at talking.
So sharp-tongued.
You're not too shabby yourself, Mr. Su.
(Gentle personality, pure and lovely,
a wife material?)
(Successful career, refined gentleman,
handsome appearance?)
(- Unreliable.
- Unreliable.)
In that case,
I won't accompany you any longer.
You should hurry to the next date.
Next date? What next date?
You have another one?
Do you really not know,
or are you pretending?
(Stardust Rogue)
Unbelievable.
(Grandpa: I want to eat durian.)
(Stardust Rogue)
(No, I placed the order
just for the free gift.)
(Now you tell me that you don't have it.
Bad review.)
I'm back.
Hey.
How was your blind date?
He looks okay.
But we only met for about 15 minutes.
And we argued from start to finish.
Did he win?
Of course not.
But I achieved my goal.
I just wanted to make him back off.
No further follow-up.
What's wrong with you?
Babe, let me tell you.
Our store's flawless record
was just shattered a moment ago.
What happened?
This afternoon, there was a customer.
When delivering the item to her,
the delivery man was half an hour late,
and the free gift was missing.
I begged and pleaded.
My lips are almost worn out.
She said our "Deliver what's promised"
is false advertising
and insisted on giving us a bad review.
This is like a beauty
having a mole on her face.
Is there anything we can do
to salvage this?
Our previous gifts
were all given out.
I asked her
if we could give her other gifts,
but she refused.
She insisted on the previous one.
She even said
that if we don't give her
the previous gift,
she'll add another complaint.
Alright, I got it.
I'll go to the supermarket
right away and send it to her.
You quickly tell her
that we'll send her
triple the gifts as compensation,
and she must cancel the bad review.
Wait a moment.
The supermarket ones are expensive.
Isn't this a loss-making business?
Babe.
A good start is half the battle.
We can't die at the starting line.
I'm going now.
Excuse me.
Is there still stock of this?
You can check over there.
Okay, thank you.
You have a girlfriend
and went on blind dates?
Don't that something Security Academy
teaches moral education?
International Security Academy.
It's about the same.
A small suggestion.
This one works better.
Is she a twin?
Grandpa.
I bought durian for you.
How was it?
How was what?
What how was what?
Where did you go?
Oh, the blind date.
Not for me.
How so?
Is there a big difference
between the person and the photo?
Is she not good-looking?
Or is her height not suitable?
It has nothing to do with those.
Then it's the personality.
Were you stingy with your words
and made the atmosphere awkward,
scaring her away?
I didn't.
What do you mean you didn't?
You sure did.
You, being a vigorous young man,
why aren't you
showing any insight in this aspect?
You always hang out with those men.
What kind of success can you achieve?
I came back, didn't I?
Didn't I return to the country?
Since you're back,
don't go anywhere else.
Just work well in the rescue team.
Learn from Lu Qun.
See how he interacts with girls.
In this aspect, he's strong.
Grandpa, are you joking?
Lu Qun doesn't even choose
when looking for a girlfriend.
Shouldn't one look for a girlfriend
whose values align with their own?
Oh my.
You're this old,
and you've never been in love.
Now you're talking about values?
Don't use that to hoodwink me.
I still think
that building a career first
before starting a family is good.
Here we go again.
What does "building a career first
before starting a family" mean?
Or is it "starting a family first
and then building a career"?
Both are nonsense.
At each stage of life,
you have to do things suitable
for that stage.
If you date when you're in high school,
that's early dating.
If you're at your age,
and you still don't have a girlfriend,
you must have a problem.
I'm talking about something serious.
Are you ignoring me?
Get up. Stand up.
Wait. Is militarized management
still necessary for my age?
Doesn't what I say matter?
It does.
Alright, spill it. What's going on?
Report.
I did try to get along well,
but the difference
between our working domains
is too large.
I don't think we will have any
common language.
Didn't the matchmaker say
she graduated from medical school
and has a corresponding job?
As for you, you're in the rescue team.
One rescues the dying
while the other assists the injured.
Isn't that a good match?
How is she not for you?
She told me herself
that she's no longer a doctor
and is now selling lingerie.
Selling lingerie...
She runs a women's supply store?
Yes.
But...
Wait. Even if she gave up
on becoming a doctor,
she could have opened a pet shop
and become a vet for pets.
That would have matched her.
Exactly.
Alright.
Let's forget about this.
Since you think it's inappropriate,
then so be it.
By the way,
I'm planning
to visit my old comrade recently
and might not be home for a few days.
So, tonight,
why don't we have something to drink?
Sure.
I'll whip up some side dishes.
Great. Come on.
Let's go.
It's fine if he's not interested.
Why did you
say my daughter's conduct is an issue?
(Well, why did your daughter
open that kind of shop?)
(Don't you feel embarrassed about it?)
(That guy is young and successful.)
(Your daughter is almost thirty)
(and will be too old
if she doesn't marry soon.)
(Do you understand?)
(Get her to find a decent job.)
You better explain it to me clearly.
What indecent thing
is my daughter doing?
(I'm even embarrassed to say it.)
(How did you educate your daughter?)
(If this continues,)
(I won't introduce anyone else to you.)
Give it to me.
Please inform Su Qingche
that before
accusing someone of misconduct,
he should
examine his own moral character.
Why is he blind dating
when he's not single?
Is he a rascal?
How dare he look down on my profession?
How shameless and hypocritical.
If you say I'm too old,
then what is he?
A rotten cabbage no one wants?
Chen.
Did you say your blind date
already has a girlfriend?
Mom.
Since you have the money,
use it to buy skincare products.
Can you stop wasting your money
on blind dating websites?
Also, about my photo.
Can you not use
my 18-year-old photo?
You look pretty in it.
Stop.
I feel something's not right.
He said
that you have an indecent job.
What does that mean?
That's right.
What does that mean? Explain.
I resigned.
- What?
No wonder you kept refusing when asked
to meet your superiors.
Turns out you've already resigned.
If you've resigned,
what's your current job?
I opened a store with Xiaoli.
What store?
A women's supply store.
- What?
You.
Song Xingchen, you've gone too far.
You should have some limits
when helping your friend.
You can invest in her store,
but how could you give up
such a good job?
You're just having wild fantasies.
You haven't experienced
the harsh realities of society.
Old man, quick.
Go and find your ex-colleague
and get her back to work.
Get her job back.
Wait.
What's wrong with me
opening a small business?
Moreover, I'm only
helping Xiaoli with her store.
Once she gets through this phase,
I'll continue my studies.
A small business?
You gave up being a doctor
for a crooked job.
I can't even say that I'm your mother
because it's so embarrassing.
Dad.
Ma'am.
Calm down.
The child
has her own life plans.
That's very natural.
Let's support her, okay?
Chen, go on with your matters.
Remember to come home often.
I'll make you soup.
Thank you, Dad.
Song Xingchen.
Come back here!
Ma'am.
Calm down.
Am I still your boss?
Of course.
You're the boss of this family.
Yet you always flatter your daughter.
I wouldn't dare.
Over the years,
she had been such a good child,
but now she's turned into this.
Nothing about her seems right,
and it's because of your indulgence.
Wait.
Ma'am, listen to me.
Let's just consider this
as her rebellious phase.
Do you think opening a shop is easy?
Just let her try it out.
She doesn't know what failure is.
Let her experience failure
and face setbacks.
As she said,
she'll continue her studies
if she fails.
Do you really think she's eighteen?
I'm asking you.
Are you going to do something?
- Will you do something?
- I will.
All you do is mess with these things.
Will you take care of this?
Will you?
I will.
I certainly will.
(Han Xiaoli)
(These expired products
are considered hazardous waste.)
(The garbage collection station
is open from 7 a.m. to 9 p.m.)
(Later, head to the store)
(and handle it, Chen.)
What about you?
(I stayed up late to post listings
and urgently need to catch some sleep.)
You say my conduct is not upright
and even humiliated my mom.
I'll give everything back to you.
(First prize. Champion)
Everyone.
Look at the cabinet on the right.
They are all the honors
Captain Su received.
On the left
are all the awards
and medals
that my beloved ex-captain received.
All of you should learn from them.
Looks like Captain Su is quite capable.
Alright. Stop chatting.
The food is done, so come and eat.
Sure. Coming.
Let's go. Time to eat.
Hurry up.
Here. Sit.
These are home-cooked dishes.
Eat whatever you like.
Have some.
I'll go.
Who is it?
Do you have any dietary restrictions?
This fish has a bit more spice.
Are you Mr. Su Qingche?
I am.
The sender is Happy Kitten.
Please sign for it.
Is that so? Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
Happy Kitten?
Qingche.
You have a package.
It's from a Happy Kitten.
What kitten?
What are you talking about?
Is it something embarrassing?
Why not open it here? Right?
- Right.
- Open it.
Qingche.
(Stardust Rogue)
Didn't know you were freaky.
Qingche.
Don't worry.
I've already warned them.
This matter won't spread anymore.
Can you tell me
what my current image
is within the team?
The sexy prince
who just returned to the country.
(Group chat: That's so embarrassing.)
(The sender is called Happy Kitten.
Hands down to the captain.)
Lin Mu is really something,
gossiping and adding you into the chat.
That's so dumb.
(Grandpa: Come home
and explain who is Happy Kitten.)
They're purely gossiping.
But you seem
addicted to ratting me out.
I'm curious as to how you
managed to report
to my grandpa behind my back
while telling me
that you'll never betray me.
I just used a little sweet talk.
Oh, right. Qingche.
Didn't you want to talk to me
about expanding our team's influence
and cooperating
with various sectors of society?
I put in a lot of effort
and finally secured a rescue exercise.
Yes.
Only by expanding
our rescue team's influence
can we receive more rescue missions.
Right.
But
you, don't change the subject on me.
How would I dare to change the subject?
I just want to save you some dignity
so everyone can forget about this.
Do you want my help
in saving yours?
No. I don't have any dignity.
No need. Don't me mad.
You can scold me,
but don't touch my hair.
Then you'd better remember this lesson
and keep your mouth shut.
♪Your tenderness is like
the light of the polar night♪
♪Following your direction,
filled with fantasies♪
♪Days become lengthy,
the world is forgotten♪
♪Wishing to confirm
if you're just like me♪
♪Please don't shy away,
come a bit closer♪
♪No matter how distant,
bravely move forward♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪Loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪