♪The future is a constantly
spinning spinning top♪
♪Polished by the hands of time♪
♪Yet my footsteps follow♪
♪Even in adversity,
we can pull a string together♪
♪Go whereever we want♪
♪My heart is never confused♪
♪When I set my sights on beauty♪
♪I believe without hesitation♪
♪Your gaze is so clear♪
♪Like the stars embracing the vastness♪
♪Love ignites like fireworks♪
♪Brightening the polar night♪
♪We won't be silent♪
♪I hear the pulsating rhythm
of your heart♪
♪Even if the night becomes mottled♪
♪How can love silently pass by♪
♪In the midst of radiance,
a silhouette appears♪
♪Bringing the warmth
into the palms of our hands♪
♪There's no reason
not to hold on tightly♪
♪I want you for every moment of my life♪
♪To be with me♪
=Got A Crush On You=
(Adapted from Bei Qing's novel "Got A Crush On You")
=Episode 19=
You're here.
I'm sorry.
Why is he here?
Because you're not.
That's why I came.
Since you're here,
I should leave.
Xingchen. Happy holidays.
Thanks.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry.
I had no choice today.
I know. I understand.
But I was really awkward just now.
If not for Tang Ruize,
I would've been desperate
to find a hiding place.
Should I thank him, then?
During my time in Hezhou,
he helped you solve the store's issues.
Should I thank him too?
What are you trying to say?
I just feel
that even without me by your side,
he could somehow make up for my absence.
Su Qingche.
I've been waiting for your safe return.
I don't want to argue with you,
especially not today.
Why is he here?
I'm not explaining today's events.
You've had a long day.
Go home and get some rest.
Don't bother driving me.
♪Wandering for a long time♪
♪Walking alone through the streets♪
♪The gentle glow of streetlights♪
♪For whom does the wind pause again♪
♪Some words♪
♪Refuse to find a way out♪
♪Loving sincerely and bravely
stands as enough♪
♪Those heartbeats♪
♪Once dreamed of belonging♪
♪Yet, some outcomes
should never be forced♪
♪Until the day I witnessed♪
♪His heart unveiling for another♪
(Happy Holidays!)
♪I now fathom that some souls♪
♪Merely become another's essence♪
♪I ardently cherished each passing day♪
♪But all that lingers
are repetitive memories♪
(Su Qingche: Happy Holidays!)
♪Embracing the missed moments of youth♪
(Galaxy Mansion, Block C)
Coming.
What are you doing here at this hour?
Surprise.
Happy Holidays.
Aren't you touched?
I never said I wanted flowers.
You've been working so hard
for multiple days in a row.
Aren't you tired?
Are you worried about me?
I'm fine. I'm not tired at all.
Thinking about seeing you
revives me in full spirit.
Wait.
Can't you be the person I used to know?
What happened to being buddies?
What if I say
I don't want us to be buddies?
Forget it.
I'm not your prey.
You're not my type either.
Anyway, I'll continue to try.
One day, you'll fall for me.
Just leave already.
Don't stay here
and disturb my rest.
I'll leave the flowers outside.
These are all your tricks.
Who wants your flowers?
Professor Tang.
You have a letter.
Thanks.
(To Mr. Tang Ruize,
Office of Academic Affairs)
(Recommendation Letter)
After finding that child yesterday,
I rushed back.
But when I got there,
Tang Ruizhe was there too.
He even gave her a bouquet of flowers,
making it look like they were on a date.
I knew I was at fault
because I was late.
Anyway, I felt really uncomfortable.
She left afterward
without replying to me.
I get you.
If I were you,
I would've felt wronged too.
It just feels
like I could be replaced at any moment.
But I can't do anything about it.
Rescue work used to be my top priority,
so I didn't understand,
but now it does feel different
to have someone worry about you
and wait for you.
True.
It's hard to balance work and family.
I was indeed at fault yesterday.
I promised her
we'd spend Qixi Festival,
so she booked a restaurant
and took the effort to dress up,
but I couldn't arrive on time.
Wait. It is your fault,
but what's strange
is that Tang Ruize was there.
Did he come on his own?
Or did she tell him?
She invited her ex
just because you were late.
Shouldn't she explain herself?
I'll definitely ask her about it.
I'll see her in a while.
I can't stand the silent treatment.
So, have you talked things
out with Su Qingche?
We almost had a quarrel.
Given the situation,
I didn't want to explain.
Oh, my.
If I were out on a mission,
I would've felt guilty
for not being with you
when you were in trouble.
But suddenly,
your ex shows up
and I happen to bump into him
spending the evening with you.
Don't you think
I'd be extremely jealous?
Anyway, I can't bring myself to say it
unless he asks.
Professor Tang is here.
I'll leave you guys alone.
I have to deal
with the video account matters.
Sure.
What brings you here?
Nothing happened between you
and Su Qingche yesterday, right?
We're fine.
Do you need me to explain to him?
No, thanks.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I should've thanked you.
I came over today
to discuss something with you.
What's up?
(Recommendation Letter)
A recommendation letter?
This way, you can apply
for their Ph.D. program this year
instead of next year.
How did you get my information?
I got it from Professor Li.
Thank you.
I didn't expect
you would remember all of it,
but I can't take it.
Why not?
I'm looking to apply for another major,
but still, thank you.
Isn't it OBGYN?
OBGYN
has many different research aspects.
I know about this school.
It doesn't offer that specialization.
I never knew that.
Should I get someone else to help?
No, thanks. I got it.
But I appreciate your help,
and I'll repay you for it.
I wasn't of much help anyway.
Alright, then. I'm leaving now.
Wasn't that
the specialization
you were going to apply for?
I got it.
You're doing this because Su Qingche
might mind, right?
Not entirely.
It's a great favor.
I can't repay him.
That's true.
Su Qingche.
Why are you here?
I came today
to talk to you about two things.
Go on.
The first thing
is about last night.
Xingchen dressed up
and ordered a table full of dishes
just to accompany you.
Yes.
You were going to rescue someone.
You were going on a mission.
You were not wrong.
But as a boyfriend,
do you think you were being reasonable?
I know all of this.
I'll explain it to Xingchen,
and I will apologize to her.
Okay.
Second thing.
Xingchen wants to study further.
Do you know about it?
I know.
Then how much do you know?
If she doesn't pursue further studies,
she won't have a chance at all.
Is she going to pack parcels every day?
She studied medicine
for so many years for nothing.
Even so,
I asked a professor
to write her recommendation letter.
but she refused.
She's afraid that you would mind,
so she wants
to distance herself from me.
So I hope
you can persuade her
to cherish this opportunity.
Even if Xingchen is strong
and independent,
she's still a girl.
She needs care and protection.
If you're a man,
you should reflect on yourself.
I'm done.
You're done shopping already?
I heard you rejected
Tang Ruize's recommendation letter.
Did he look for you?
Hasn't going abroad for a PhD
always been your dream?
Why don't you accept it?
If you accept,
you won't have to wait another year.
You can immediately do what you want.
I'm happy with my choice.
Anything wrong?
Xingchen.
Listen to me.
I just don't want...
I just don't want you
to give up what you really want to do
because of me.
You came today
just to talk to me about this?
I came to apologize to you.
I'm sorry for last night.
I was wrong.
It won't happen again.
But today, Tang Ruize came to see me,
and I think he's right.
I don't want to be a burden to you.
I don't want to be a burden
in your life.
So?
Do you want me to call Tang Ruize now
and get the opportunity back?
No need for you to call.
I can call for you.
Xingchen, calm down.
Let me analyze...
Get out.
I don't need anyone's help.
I can handle
everything in this shop,
including my personal matters,
myself. Leave.
♪In our story♪
♪Tragedy fills every scene♪
♪Yet you've been
guarding the same place all along♪
(Haicheng City Rescue Center)
♪To your reluctant expression♪
♪But I still can't take you away♪
♪I don't know, I don't understand,
the two of us♪
♪Endure the sadness,
we need to overcome it all♪
(Song Xingchen)
♪If only in this moment♪
♪Forever staying in the day
you held my hand♪
(Draft: Sorry for being
too harsh in the afternoon.)
♪If only in this moment♪
♪Could I hold onto my yearning♪
♪Memories staying
in this most familiar scene♪
(Draft:
I just don't want to owe favors.)
♪Only you♪
Open the door.
It's late. What's wrong?
Sir, you know it's late.
So why are you not sleeping
and clown-dancing here?
I've been kept awake downstairs
by your noise for three nights straight.
Then you may have neurasthenia.
Hurry up
and go to the hospital for a checkup.
Wait.
Wait a moment.
I have neurasthenia?
You're quite interesting.
Do you have any sense of reason?
Madam.
I'm dancing at my house.
I am not dancing at your house.
Why do you care?
Who's your madam?
If you want to dance, you can,
but can you go to somewhere else?
Dance in the square downstairs
as you like.
Nobody will bother you
even if you dance to the sky.
You...
You have such a strong smell of alcohol.
Are you drunk?
Disturbing me in the middle
of the night after drinking?
I only drank half a bottle of beer.
- I'm very clear-headed.
- Alright.
I don't care
how many bottles of beer you drank.
Go back where you come from.
Otherwise, I'll call the police
and say you're harassing me.
Oh my, why did you sleep here?
I'm so annoyed.
There hasn't been
a single good thing lately.
Someone moved in upstairs.
He dances at home every night.
It's so noisy.
I can't sleep at all.
Let me tell you.
You should report him to the management.
Let them handle it.
I did that.
Once the management went there,
he quieted down.
But as soon as they left,
he started again.
The most ridiculous thing is,
he even blamed the management,
saying they disturbed his rest
at midnight.
What... What kind of person is this?
He made noise until 4:00 a.m. every day.
Just when it finally stopped,
I couldn't sleep.
What about Su Qingche?
Are you still not talking to each other?
It's all because
of Tang Ruize's recommendation letter.
Su Qingche thought
that I refused Tang Ruize
because of him.
So, you refused Tang Ruize's help,
but when Su Qingche found out,
he felt like he was dragging you down.
I rejected Tang Ruize
because I don't want to owe him a favor.
Also, I want to draw clear boundaries.
Why did he react so strongly?
Babe.
Yes, the mission of a best friend
is supposed to curse men with you,
but
as an onlooker,
I think Su Qingche
is a person
with a very proud personality.
He will absolutely not allow himself
to become your burden
or someone who causes trouble.
He probably feels
that he's caused you
to make this decision,
which might hurt his self-esteem a bit.
What about you?
How's you and Lu Qun?
Has he come to see you again?
He came.
But
my heart is firm.
Since he doesn't want
to set clear boundaries
with those girls,
I don't need to play games with him.
True.
Let's focus on our work.
You're right.
I'm so sleepy.
(Haicheng City Rescue Center)
Let's take a break for now.
Let me announce a mission.
In the past month,
Qin has been shooting videos
for our video channel,
and the response has been very good.
Especially the one with Lin Mu.
It has over a thousand comments.
So, the team has decided
that starting today,
we'll have a weekly update.
Everyone needs to participate.
No excuses will be accepted.
For the next episode,
Ding Weiling, it's your turn.
Sure, no problem.
In our video channel,
there's high interest in videos
about women's self-defense techniques.
I hope you can create a video
about how women
can defend themselves after an attack.
But you need a male team member
to partner with.
Who wants to do it?
I'll do it.
I can do it too.
Count me in.
I'm up for it.
Getting beaten up, right?
I have experience.
Are you addicted to acting or what?
Didn't you just shoot one recently?
As Captain Lu said,
rotating appearances
is the rule we set today.
So, the previous ones don't count.
Right, Captain Lu?
Lin Mu is right.
Everyone
should learn from Lin Mu.
Have self-discipline in training
and be proactive in tasks.
It's you, then.
Yes, sir.
Ready? Three, two, one, go.
The first move,
when someone taps your shoulder.
Wait a second.
Lin Mu.
Can you act a bit creepier?
Yes, that's it. It's perfect.
Let's continue.
The first move.
When someone taps your shoulder
from behind...
Hey, little girl.
First, grab their hand
and twist it backward.
Okay, cut.
Lin Mu, don't forget
to act creepy.
Okay.
Ready? Three, two, one, go.
Now, let's learn the second move.
When someone approaches you
and you feel threatened...
Let's go have a drink with me, babe.
Hey, what are you doing here?
You...
The third move.
When someone grabs your throat,
hold their shoulder and do this.
Okay, cut.
I think we have enough material
for today.
If it's not enough,
I'll get your help again.
- Okay.
- Good work.
Good work.
What's wrong?
- I'm fine.
- You're bleeding.
Call Sun Yizhu.
Okay.
- Are you okay?
How are you?
Easy.
Did you get hurt?
- No, I'm fine.
- Let me check.
How'd you get hurt?
I heard a kid
fell into the sewer yesterday.
It was Lin Mu who responded to the call.
Maybe he got hurt back then.
I was careless.
When I jumped in there,
I got scraped by a rock by accident.
It's nothing serious.
Excuse me, please.
It's no big deal.
I'll reapply antiseptic
and rebandage the wound.
Sun Yizhu,
someone's looking for you.
Okay.
Give me a minute.
It's okay. I'll handle this.
You go ahead.
I got this.
Okay.
Bear with it.
Does it hurt?
No.
Why push yourself with a leg injury?
Don't you know that I'm rough?
I know.
But with all that hugging,
I didn't want someone else to do it.
I've never seen an idiot like you.
Don't be so reckless next time.
Got it?
Yeah.
It feels so nice
to be cared for by you.
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Where do you live?
What's wrong?
I need to take responsibility for this.
Come on, I'll take you home.
I live in Haicheng's Yongshu District.
Room 302, Unit 4,
No. 32 Yingcheng Street.
Let's go.
Does Lin Mu stand a chance?
What do you think?
Have you ever seen Weiling
so concerned about a guy before?
Isn't it so?
(Qiancheng, I need your urgent help.)
(You have to help me.)
Bro.
I have classes this afternoon.
(Gao Qingyin will also be there.)
She'll be there too?
(Yes.)
Okay.
Send me the address.
I'll be there on time.
(Sure.)
You're aquaphobic and can't swim.
Why'd they assign you to a job like this?
Anyway, I've sorted it out with them.
We'll avoid modeling underwater.
The water's heated, by the way.
Since I'm here,
I'll be cooperative.
There's something I forgot to tell you.
Our modeling job this time
involves Qiancheng.
Qiancheng?
Why would he be here too?
I heard he was called in
as a last-minute replacement.
Fine.
He'll make me look good in the shot.
Nothing else matters.
Aren't you upset?
Upset?
Why should I?
I never said I wouldn't work with him.
Didn't you previously
include him on your blacklist?
Don't worry about it.
I've attended freediving classes.
It's just posing in a mermaid tail.
I can manage it.
Qingyin, you're finally here.
Shall we start, then?
Sure.
Qingyin.
What a coincidence.
It surely is.
Last time on the beach,
didn't you say you couldn't swim?
I'll try to keep up.
Okay. Thank you for that.
What's going on with you guys?
The water's too cold.
Isn't supposed to be heated?
We're really sorry.
We were told
that the heat pump broke down
halfway through heating.
There's nothing we could do.
Nothing, huh?
Fine.
You don't keep your word.
Qingyin, let's go. We're not doing this.
It's okay. I'm not that fragile.
But you have other jobs later.
It's okay. I can manage. Let's get ready.
Let's work together.
Same to you.
Come on, let's do it again.
One more take.
Go down a little further.
Okay, come on up.
Gao Qingyin.
Anyone there?
Help...
What's happening?
Hurry and get in there.
Qingyin.
Qingyin, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Put this on quickly.
Who's there?
It's me, Qiancheng.
I'm alone here. Come on in.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sorry about earlier.
It's okay. You didn't mean it.
But you can't swim.
Why jump in to save me back then?
I was worried about you.
So I jumped on the spur of the moment.
You're really stupid.
Don't do this anymore.
Where's Mengnan?
She went to buy something.
Lend me a hand.
If you keep staring,
I might catch a cold for real.
I'm sorry.
Qingyin.
You're different today.
How am I different?
Our partner
didn't follow your instructions
to raise the water temperature.
Not only didn't you get angry,
but you also cooperated with me.
What kind
of a person do you think I am?
There are all sorts
of problems happening at the set.
What else can I do if I don't cooperate?
But about the photoshoot for Stardust?
I heard about it.
Come on, please.
I disliked Song Xingchen back then,
so I deliberately teased her.
If I lacked professionalism,
could my work schedule be so full?
I came here to work,
not to pick fights.
Thanks for today.
What are you doing?
Qingyin almost drowned because of you.
How dare you come to find her?
- I came over...
- For what?
You can't even swim.
Aren't you afraid others
would laugh at you?
Mengnan.
Am I wrong?
I think he did it on purpose.
Alright. Take a good rest.
I'll leave first.
It's fine, Qingyin.
Don't be afraid of him.
Alright. He's just being kind.
Nothing happened to me,
so there's nothing to be upset about.
How can I not be upset?
Besides, he and Song Xingchen
are in cahoots.
Come, let me
help you blow-dry your hair.
(Haicheng City Rescue Center)
(Lu Qun: Didn't you say you
want to be buddies with me?)
(There's a gathering tonight.
Will you go?)
(Lu Qun: If you come, it means you
see me as a buddy,)
(or else it means you
agree to let me pursue you.)
(Han Xiaoli: Okay.
Send me the time and address.)
Yes!
(No pornography, gambling, and drugs)
Here she comes.
Xiaoli.
You came.
You look pretty in this.
Lu Qun.
Is this the person you wanted to bring?
Yes, she's my...
She's my buddy,
so no one is to make her drink.
What should I call you?
I'm Han Xiaoli.
Hello, I'm Liang Heng.
I'm Lu Qun's schoolmate from university,
but I'm from a different class and batch.
Lu Qun.
Is she also in your group?
What group?
No.
A group. A group of people came today.
Look at all those people.
You came.
What do you think of the crowd tonight?
There's quite a lot of people.
Of course.
Drinks.
Go have fun.
No. I'll be over there.
Call me if you need anything.
I've prepared cheerful ones,
active ones, cute ones,
and reserved ones today.
Aren't cheerful
and active the same type?
Well, not exactly.
They're divided into older
and younger ones.
Younger ones are considered active,
while older ones
are considered cheerful.
They're different,
and depends on your liking.
My taste is similar
to that of high school girls.
How about the school bully type?
You're in luck. I am the school bully.
Dear junior, you...
By the way, I wanted to ask you
about what's going on with Su Qingche.
Xingchen's neighbor
has been driving her crazy recently,
and he's making things worse.
That guy's stupid.
Give him some time,
and I'll talk to him.
What about Miss Song again?
My God.
Recently,
an annoying neighbor moved upstairs
and would start tap dancing
every night after 11.00 p.m.
He wouldn't stop
until early in the morning.
It has almost driven Xingchen crazy.
Has it? No worries. I'll take care of it.
Lu Qun.
Come and have a drink.
Okay. I'll be there in a minute.
I need to go and entertain my friends.
Go ahead.
You should go and pick a song.
What are you guys up to?
Hey, I haven't seen you before.
I'm Lu Qun. You?
I know you.
I'm Xia Wan.
My WeChat ID is Nini.
Have we met?
Don't you remember?
It's fine. I'll remember today.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, beautiful.
Are you bored?
No.
I'm enjoying playing on my phone.
It's fine. I'll have a drink with you.
Sure.
Great.
What were you guys talking about?
I'll talk with her here.
You can just talk over here.
What's the topic?
Fine.
We're done here.
Let's...
Let's chat on Wechat.
Sure.
You guys talk.
Did you add his Wechat?
Didn't you hold this gathering for me?
What now?
You can.
Well, how
about playing rock, paper, scissors?
Drink until we drop.
Game on. Let's see who wins.
Zhou Yao, help me get two glasses.
Sure.
Excuse me.
I'd like to request a song.
Miss Xia, can I invite you for a drink?
Thanks but no need.
But how did you know my name?
I heard your friends
calling you that earlier.
Hello, I'm Xia Wan.
Hello.
Can I add you on Wechat?
Sure.
Here.
(Han Xiaoli)
Done.
(Galaxy Mansion, Block C)
Xia Wan.
(Go to Hell, Playboy)
(Xia Wan: Everyone, this is Seven.)
(Show her our chat history.)
Seven? What chat history?
(Lu Qun: I like you a lot, really.)
(I've never met a woman)
(Lu Qun: I'm drunk. I miss you.)
(as special and unique as you.)
(Of course, I won't like anyone else.)
(Have you heard of the song,)
("only have feelings for you"?)
(Xia Wan: We've all been
deceived by Lu Qun.)
(We initially wanted to confront him,)
(but he acted completely innocent.)
(We couldn't get anything out of him.)
(You're the seventh one already.)
The seventh one?
A leopard indeed can't change its spots.
How dare he
pretend to have changed his ways?
How about we set him up?
I'll get Lu Qun to come out.
If he doesn't apologize to us,
we'll give him a beating.
Lu Qun, just you wait.
♪Your tenderness is like
the light of the polar night♪
♪Following your direction,
filled with fantasies♪
♪Days become lengthy,
the world is forgotten♪
♪Wishing to confirm
if you're just like me♪
♪Please don't shy away,
come a bit closer♪
♪No matter how distant,
bravely move forward♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪
♪Fall in love with you♪
♪Longing for you to hold my hand
in the dark night♪
♪Yearning for you
in my most helpless moments♪
♪Gentleness remains♪
♪Unable to break free from the curse,
lingering in the heart♪
♪Loving you♪
♪Wishing for you to take me on a journey
through the clouds♪
♪Longing for you
to spend day and night together♪
♪Eager to tell you♪
♪I'm loving you♪