Suer, what's wrong with you?
Hey, what's gotten into you?
You're not staying over at Nao's place today?
- Can you not say that name?
- You don't want to be friends with him anymore?
No. I don't want to be friends anymore.
- Move. Nao's coming.
- It's not a big deal. We're just here to eat. Come on.
- Hey, where are you going, Field?
- We'll be late.
Wait, Suer.
- What?
- Is there something you want to tell me?
You can keep a secret, right?
Then I'll tell you my secret on Saturday.
I'm worried about you.
Hey, there's definitely more to this.
Hey.
It suddenly started raining.
Yeah.
It looked gloomy since this morning.
And it's freaking cold (Nao )too.
- Nao?
- Yeah, cold.
Right.
Really Nao.
What's with you? Why are you repeating everything I say?
Why? Are you the only one allowed to say "Nao" (cold)?
No.
But it's the rainy season now, right?
Yeah, it's the rainy season.
It's Duennao (Winter) season.
It's the rainy season.
No. I want it to be Duennao (Winter) season.
Shit.
Wait a second.
Room Nine just walked by. Why are you reacting so hard?
Got something to tell me, Suer?
What?
Wow, look at those lovesick eyes.
Who are you looking at?
No one. What are you talking about, Mick?
- Shut up.
- Aha!
Field.
What's wrong with our friend lately?
One minute he's annoyed, the next he's smiling.
Yeah, I've noticed.
I'm starting to get scared.
Damn, I really want to change seats.
Want to sit next to me?
I think he's gone crazy.
Class dismissed. You can all go home now.
Thank youuu.
Finally.
What are you doing after this?
Going home.
Hey, Suer.
- We're going to the game café. Wanna come?
- Yea.
The game café?
Come with us. You can't practice today anyway.
The field's completely soaked.
- Sure.
- Let's go play some games, buddy.
Alright.
Today...
Sword fighting game?
Dota.
- No idea. What should we play?
- I don't feel like shooters today. I wanna play something...
- Build houses? Minecraft?
- Let Suer choose.
Sure, Suer.
What do you want to play, Suer?
Where'd you get that gun from?
I'm heading home.
Huh? You just got here.
What's wrong with you?
I'm... sad.
Sad about what? You were fine a second ago.
Just go.
- Hey, come play with us.
- Get home safe.
- Suer.
- Shit!
Damn it! Why the hell are you yelling, idiot?
So, are you going home today?
- Why are you asking me?
- I'm just asking.
- Then why ask me?
- So I can know.
Ask someone else to hang out.
Who?
I don't know.
See ya.
What the hell is wrong with you, Suer? Damn it.
Whoa.
What the hell is this lump?
What is this?
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
What is he spacing out about?
What the hell are you guys doing?
What's gotten into you guys?
Come on, we're just messing around.
- Hey, sorry.
- Did you buy alcohol?
I bought milk.
Do you drink milk when you're sad or something?
Why would I drink alcohol?
I'll drink when I'm old enough.
Anyway.
What are you sad about? I noticed it at the game café.
You know, Nao saw you looking sad.
He was totally confused.
And what did you tell Nao?
I just told him you were sad.
What?
Well...
Why?
You said you were sad,
so that's what I told him.
You...
- You told him that?
- Yeah, of course.
Why? So are you finally gonna tell us why you're sad or what?
Otherwise, I'm not asking anymore.
If...
I tell you guys...
you better keep it a secret.
Mm.
I think...
I like Nao.
What?
Can you say that again?
Yeah, I like Nao.
Nao, not Nue?
Why though?
"Why" what?
Why do you like him? Just curious.
I don't know.
I...
just realized one day that I liked him.
That's what I wanted to tell you guys today.
What do you think?
What should I do next?
Are you seriously telling me
that you've been sitting there all sad...
because you already got rejected?
- Heh. Not yet.
- Huh?
Then what are you sad about?
Well...
- I felt hurt.
- Hurt?
He smiled at someone else. I didn't like it.
Oh my god, what is this?
My friend has a childish side like this?
You're ridiculously sensitive.
I never knew you were like this when you liked someone.
What about you guys?
What do you think I should do?
Suer.
Hey, wake up.
- Suer.
- Shit.
- Why are you yelling?
- Wake up. We've got studying to do.
- Study what?
- For the exams.
Exams?
What exams?
Midterms. Don't tell me you forgot.
Whatever.
Do you think it'd be a good idea if we went to study at Nao's house?
- Would it?
- Look at you, getting up that fast.
Of course it would. Don't you want to see what Duennao is like when he studies?
What do you think?
If I were the one tutoring Duennao...
wouldn't I look cool?
- Like a smart guy.
- Hah, a smart guy?
What smart guy? You haven't paid attention in class at all this semester.
You've been bombing every graded test.
How are you supposed to be a smart guy?
I think...
you guys... seriously...
should call me Tiger instead.
- Why?
- Yeah.
We've been calling you Suer since kindergarten.
Nah.
Tiger is better because...
Duennao is the only one who gets to call me Suer.
Oh, come on.
I don't even know what to say anymore.
So, are we going to study or not?
Why don't you call and see if he's free first?
- Me?
- Who else?
Of course it's you.
Sup?
Uh... you...
interested in studying together?
For midterms?
Yeah. Dan's gonna tutor me this afternoon.
- Let me join too.
- Sure.
And Mick...
- and Field too. Is that okay?
- Yeah, sure. My friends are coming too. Apo and Tul.
Yes!
See you then.
- What the hell are you waiting for?
- A shower.
Wow. A minute ago, you didn't even want to get out of bed.
Whoa.
This place has such a nice vibe.
There's a garden too.
Yeah, of course. It's Dan's garden.
By the way, where's Nue?
Isn't he studying with us?
Dan went to the market with mom. He'll be back soon.
Hey, Nao. Can I use the bathroom?
The bathroom? It's over there. Just go downstairs and you'll find it.
Okay.
Actually, I'll go too. I kinda need to use it.
- There's only one bathroom.
- That's fine. I'll wait downstairs.
Why are they in such a hurry?
- Suer.
- Huh?
Are you feeling better now?
What?
You can tell me if something's bothering you.
- Are you okay?
- Hey, I'm gonna use the bathroom for a sec.
Dude, Field's already in there.
Does he really have to go that badly?
What the hell are you guys doing?
So you could be alone with Nao.
The two of us went through all for you, you know.
Thanks a lot, assholes. You were messing with me more than helping.
And now that you're out here, won't Nao get suspicious?
Oh, right. Didn't think of that.
Hey, Nao's coming.
Shit.
Where's Suer?
- He's in the bathroom. Guess he has diarrhea.
- Yeah, yeah.
I figured. I saw him rushing downstairs.
You assholes.
What the hell are you laughing at?
My photo. It's freaking hilarious.
- Let me see.
- No way. It's an embarrassing shot.
How can I show you? I look ridiculous in it.
Just a little bit.
I'll send it to you later.
Mm. Electrolytes.
Didn't you have diarrhea?
Oh.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're so fast at math.
Whoa, shit.
Why'd you get startled?
I was just asking.
How are you so fast at math?
Got any tricks?
I don't know. It just comes naturally.
Such a smart-person answer.
- Just do it.
- Fine, I'll do it.
What kind of multiplication is that? How did you even make it through middle school?
Hey, everyone makes mistakes sometimes.
I'm not a calculator, you know.
I'm not studying with you anymore. All you do is roast me.
Can you blame me?
Yelling at me isn't gonna make me smarter.
You could just talk nicely to me.
Come on, Tul.
He's basically a kid.
He only listens when the teacher speaks gently.
Whether I yell or not, look at him.
Think he's listening? Who's he texting anyway? Some girl?
Hey.
Hey, Mick.
Don't tell me it's little Yayee.
Damn, he's serious.
They'll break up soon enough.
Hey, that's way too mean.
Hmph. I'm sulking now.
Don't think it'll be easy to make it up to me,
Mr. Tula.
Annoying.
Want to go sit with Field?
Nah.
What are you doing, Dan? Still not asleep?
I can't sleep.
Worried about something?
Yeah.
What about? Midterms?
That doesn't seem like something you'd worry about.
Sorry.
I didn't want you to worry too.
But sooner or later, we're going to have to face it.
You mean...
about Chat?
Don't worry.
I'll protect you myself.
Come on, let's sleep.
Sweet dreams, kiddo.
Kiddo? You were only born nine minutes earlier.
Do you even have the right to say that?
Little kid.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself, Dan.
I know you're the type to do that.
Because you're the oldest sibling in the family.
This is something I want to do anyway. It's okay.
Then I'll study hard...
so you won't have to work so hard. Okay?
Thanks, but it's okay.
Just do what you want to do.
Neither Mom nor I have ever stopped you from doing what you want.
So don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Mm.
- Sweet dreams.
- Sweet dreams to you too.
Hey, Suer. Feeling better?
Hm?
Your diarrhea, remember?
Oh, right. Yeah, my stomach still hurts.
That bad?
Should you go to the hospital?
You've got an exam tomorrow. Are you okay?
What are you smiling about?
Nothing.
No need to see a doctor. Some rest should do it.
Okay.
Then I'll have my mom make you some bland food, okay?
I'll be right back.
Mm. Electrolytes.
You'll recover faster.
Thank you.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Can I talk to you about something?
You know...
Do you remember that guy named Chat I told you about?
There's actually more to it than that.
When I said we're not living together anymore...
the truth is, he's in prison now.
He got convicted of robbery.
And when he was living with us...
- He'd come home drunk and abuse us.
- Abuse you?
Aunt Maew and Nue too?
And now...
he's about to get out of prison.
I'm scared that...
if you keep staying here...
you might end up in danger too.
I'll handle it myself.
What are you worried about?
Did you forget what I told you?
Yeah.
Well...
you're in the mafia.
But...
I don't want anyone else getting dragged into this.
It's fine.
It's nothing serious.
I'll take care of it.
But...
Think of it as repayment.
For taking care of me.
This is such a small thing.
It's just one person.
What can he really do?
Hm?
Yeah.
So...
Don't stress about it.
I'll handle everything.
Okay?
Yeah.
Still, thanks a lot.
Get some more rest.
- This one's delicious.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I put a lot of effort into it.
- There's so much food.
- Yeah.
This curry is really rich.
Thank you.
Tiger, aren't you sick? Why don't you sleep in a bed?
You won't be comfortable on the couch.
Dan, come sleep with me.
Uh, I don't want to trouble anyone.
I'm already feeling much better.
I can just sleep on the couch.
It's no trouble at all. Rest until you're fully recovered, okay?
Hm?
- What do Duen and Dan think?
- I'm okay with it.
- Whatever you want, Mom.
- Great, you haven't slept with me in ages.
We're going to have a long gossip session tonight.
Here, this one's better.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Can you reach it, honey?
- Thank you.
Hey.
What a relief. Exams are finally over.
But we still have the football tournament.
Time really flies, huh?
We'll be in Grade 11 soon.
And I'm turning 17 soon.
I'll be 17 before you.
You should start calling me big brother.
You're only two months older than me and want me to call you that?
I'm seven years younger than Singha and I still don't call him that.
By the way, about your brother...
Aren't you going to talk to him?
- Talk about what?
- Just... have a proper conversation.
I'd rather die than try talking nicely to him.
Why?
- Just once.
- No.
Just once. Invite him to dinner or something. I'll come too.
- You'll come too?
- Yeah.
I'll sit there and be nosy. So you won't feel awkward.
I don't even know if he'll show up.
You have to try. He even showed up for the parent-teacher meeting.
True.
- But you have to come with me.
- Easy.
Even though your brother looks scary.
Where should I arrange to meet him?
Leave that to me.
(My N'Suer)
What's up?
Singha.
You...
today—
Actually, have you been free lately?
Anytime. When are you free?
What is it?
I need to talk to you about something.
Something serious.
Mm.
Just set it up.
I'll send you the location.
Yeah.
Ben.
This is serious.
Get over here right now.
Meet me here.
Singha.
What's up?
The place you sent me is right, isn't it?
Suer sent me this place.
Wrong place?
No, it's right.
I should be asking if your brother pinned the right location.
I don't think it's wrong.
Let's go.
Hey, your brother's here.
Duennao?
Yes, it's me.
Uh, have you ordered anything yet?
Not yet.
Then let me recommend our new menu item.
The melon bingsu is really good.
The smoothies here are great too.
- Does your brother drink smoothies?
- How would I know?
- Then ask him.
- You ask him.
Suer, you ask.
What did we agree on?
Hey.
Do you drink smoothies?
Yeah.
Order whatever you want.
What did you want to say?
Your brother's talking to you.
- I know.
- Then answer him.
I don't like you.
So?
Suer.
How are you supposed to talk like that?
What did I tell you?
Okay.
This is the only time
I'm going to talk to you seriously.
No bias.
No emotions.
But if we still can't understand each other after this,
I'm done talking.
I...
don't like the way you talk to me.
Why are you laughing?
See? You always look down on me.
Come on, Nao. Let's go.
We shouldn't have come.
No, that's not it.
Well.
I'll wait for you over there.
Why?
Because I don't like it.
I want us to get along.
Sometimes,
there's no reason for us to fight at all.
But you're always messing with me.
Or do you dislike me so much that...
- you can't even talk to me nicely?
- What about you?
Do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
I just...
don't like what you've done to me.
Okay.
From now on, I won't speak badly to you anymore.
Is that all you wanted to say?
One more thing.
I've decided.
I'm going to work with our family.
Didn't you tell me
that I shouldn't have friends or people I care about?
Because they...
would be in danger.
But I've made up my mind.
I don't want to lose anyone.
I'll protect everyone myself.
You've made your decision?
One more thing.
I'm entrusting my people to you.
Keep them safe.
Because right now,
there's nothing I can do.
I understand.
Thank you.
Mm.
I should get going. I've got something to do.
Wait.
I have a football match tomorrow.
I'm the captain too.
If you're free, come by.
How did it go?
Nothing much.
Singha, stop crying already.
Ben.
My little brother...
Suer...
Has he grown up that much already?
Yeah. People grow up with time.
No, that's not it.
Earlier, he wouldn't listen to anyone.
He wouldn't listen to anybody.
But now he's telling me
he wants to work with me.
Because he wants to protect others.
And he even thanked me.
It's good that you two talked things out.
So,
what about that gang leader kid?
How's he doing?
Anything unusual?
No.
Nope.
I don't know.
You're useless.
What do you guys think?
What should I do next?
Do you want him to know that you like him?
I...
I want him to know, and I want him to feel the same way.
But I don't know if he does.
Well, if you ask me, there are several possibilities.
First,
he might already know you like him, and he likes you too,
but he's too scared to say it.
Second, if Nao knows, he might open his heart to you.
But third,
Nao knows that you like him,
but he doesn't feel the same and would rather stay friends.
Or fourth,
he knows you like him, but he's not okay with it.
Once he finds out,
he cuts you out of his life.
Shit.
I don't think Nao would be that cruel.
I don't think it's number four.
At worst, it'd be number three.
Better as friends.
Would that really be okay?
Damn it, I don't want to be just friends.
Can you really be friends with someone you want to see, want to talk to,
want to take care of, and want to prioritize?
And I want to be important to him too.
Friends don't feel like that, do they?
What are you listening to?
Hey, why'd you stop it?
What?
What is it? "Friend (Doesn't) Love."
You listen to this song too?
Mick sent it to me.
Really?
So you've fallen in love these days?
- Mick just...
- Answer me right now.
Mick really sent it to me.
You're acting suspicious.
Come on, tell me. I won't tell anyone. You can trust me.
Hey, I said there's nothing, so there's nothing.
Come on, let me listen then.
Just listen to it.
Give me one side.
It's just a song. Nothing special.
Nao.
Hm?
If someone confessed to you, what would you do?
That won't happen.
Just hypothetically.
I guess I'd...
turn them down.
Right now, I'm not thinking about having a relationship.
I can barely handle my own life.
And if not now,
then when?
I don't know.
Why are you asking so many questions? Gathering intel?
Didn't you say you didn't like anyone?
Aha! Suer!
- No.
- I'm not teasing you anymore.
Just kidding.
Give me that. By the way,
what are you doing out this late?
I couldn't sleep.
Thought I'd go for a walk and get some fresh air, but then I saw you sitting here acting like you're in a music video.
Want to go for a ride?
Let me grab a jacket.
Friend (Doesn't) Love?
So? Feeling better?
A little.
The weather's nice.
Aren't you nervous at all?
Not really.
Even though it's my first time, I'm not nervous.
- I don't know why.
- So you think you're gonna win?
That confident, huh?
Something like that.
I think I have to win.
This time too.
Hey, don't put so much pressure on yourself. Football isn't a one-man game.
Yeah.
True.
But the other team is insanely good, right?
You know what we have that they don't?
What?
Me.
Suer.
- That's exactly what's making me even more stressed.
- Asshole.
Suer.
I bragged to my mom I'd score two goals.
Make sure you pass me the ball.
Don't I always?
Okay.
Suer.
- Do you think we'll win?
- I told you, we'll win. You've got me on your team.
Everyone else has been training together too.
What are you worried about?
If we win, we win together. If we lose, we lose together.
That's all.
Yeah.
Win together.
You're such a scaredy-cat.
This field is huge.
Holy shit.
There are so many people.
Yeah. I was fine before.
Now I'm getting nervous.
Yeah, you're making me nervous too.
Come on. Coach will call us soon.
Let's go.
The Provincial Youth Football Qualifiers.
Come up here. Where are the seats?
Dan, where's Duen?
I can't see him.
There he is, Mom. He just arrived.
Duen!
Mom's over here!
Go, Duen!
Great job, son!
Duen's team is ahead, Mom. There's still a chance.
Come on!
- Great job, Duen! Great job!
- You're amazing, Duen!
- They won, Mom!
- Really?
One, two, three, yay!
We won! Yay!
Amazing!
Let's go.
See? I told you, man. We're awesome. We're freaking amazing.
Man...
You did great, Nao.
I'm exhausted.
- What's up?
- Huh?
Tired.
Hey, I'm gonna go see Singha first.
Just for a bit. He's leaving soon.
Okay.
Be nice.
- Duen!
- Let go!
- Let go, damn it!
- Let me go!
Dan, what's wrong?
What's happening?
- Let go!
- Why are you grabbing us? Let go!
Mom! Dan!
Duen, help!
Help Mom!
Chat!
Let go!
You bastard!
Long time no see.
Still got a big mouth, huh?
You scumbag.
Get them in the car.
- Hurry up.
- Duen!
- Let go!
- Move!
Help! Somebody help!
Why are you following me?
Relax, Nao. It's me.
- Ow!
- Tiger.
I've missed you.
So? Wanna move to Chiang Mai with me?
Sure. North or south, I'll go anywhere.
You two are glued together.
We're best friends, that's why.
Right, buddy?
So, what's up with that girl?
I think I'll give her a chance. She's pretty cute.
Come on, let's get some barbecue.
What about me, Nao?
I like you too.