My daughter is missing.
Ma'am, please try to calm down.
She's missing,
and her phone is turned off.
I see.
And the name?
It's Nam Yoon-seo.
Is that your name, ma'am?
No. My name is Kim Hye-joo.
Nam Yoon-seo is my daughter's name.
When was she born?
In 2008. She's in 8th grade.
She attends Jicheong Middle School.
What's your home address?
It's 14, Sumyeong-ro 3-gil, Sinyang-gu.
What's your phone number?
Look. I think my daughter
ran away from home.
As in it was voluntary?
You don't think she's been abducted
or gone missing?
Abducted?
It's uncommon,
but it's also a possibility.
It shouldn't be ruled out,
particularly with women or teenagers.
Why do you think she ran away from home?
Did she text or leave you a note?
No, she didn't.
But we had an argument earlier today.
You had an argument. I see.
Has she ever run away from home before?
No, she's not the type to do such a thing.
This is
the first time this has happened.
PRELUDE
13 HOURS AGO
BOOK CONSERVATION
Let me confirm everything
we've talked about until now.
First of all,
I'm going to restore the ripped, damaged,
and tainted pages such as these.
As for the new cover,
I have both thin and thick boards.
And I'll be using the latter.
As for the cover,
I'll be using this silky one
that you've already picked out.
Then I'll insert a photo of your son
on the cover.
Take a look at this sample.
Could you feel around the edges?
Right. I'm going to make an indentation
and insert his photo inside.
Okay.
I can't wait.
You can look through that
while I double-check your request form.
Sure.
Goodness.
So you fixed all of these torn-up books.
I found my son's baby book recently
while moving.
I recalled hearing about
book conservation studios, so I came.
I'm really glad that I visited you.
Goodness.
Ma'am, are you married?
-Yes.
-I see.
Do you have a child?
Yes.
Son or daughter? How old are they?
My son is 22,
and my daughter is in 8th grade.
He's 22?
Goodness, you must have
gotten married very early.
I expected your child
to be in elementary school.
My son is 22 years old as well.
Goodness.
He used to be so adorable.
But these days, he never replies to me.
And if I nag him out of frustration,
he just looks all sulky.
He'll be the death of me.
When he was little,
we were pretty much attached at the hip.
Who knew our sons
would grow apart from us, right?
Jeez, I can't help but envy moms
who have daughters.
You can be honest with me.
Don't you love your daughter
a bit more than your son?
Of course not. I love them both equally.
I've confirmed everything.
I'll contact you once it's completed.
You can pay half the amount today
and pay the rest when you pick it up.
-Okay.
-Please check.
-Thank you so much.
-My pleasure.
-Goodbye.
Is it going to rain?
ALARM
Right.
WOMEN'S CLINIC
Hye-joo!
Hey, I thought you were running late.
That's what I thought too.
I thought you weren't coming.
I felt bad about not showing up very much.
The moms are going to love it.
They're all eagerly waiting to meet
the mom of the class president
and top student.
That's why I haven't been going.
Yoon-seo doesn't receive any help from me.
Fine. Good for you.
-Here.
-This looks delicious.
-It's been a long time.
-I know.
Here you go. Eat up.
I heard Yoon-seo doesn't
even take a lot of after-school classes.
Does she have a tutor?
No, she only goes to after-school classes.
Come on. You don't need
to be so secretive.
Or do you help her with her studies?
Not at all. I'm not involved whatsoever.
She studies on her own.
She just takes after her dad.
Goodness. What does your husband do?
Is he a professor?
Well…
He just has a regular job.
Your husband is the professor.
At Seoul National University, at that.
Right. Let's have brunch
at his school this Sunday.
There's a cafe with a nice view.
-Sure.
-Okay.
Then should we meet at 11 a.m.?
-Sure.
Ji-soo, you're coming with Hye-joo, right?
Yes, that's the plan.
To SNU?
What for?
Hasn't Yoon-seo told you?
Tell me what?
-Let's come here again.
-See you on Sunday.
-Okay.
-See you Sunday.
-At 11 a.m.
-Let's go.
-That place was nice.
Sorry for not telling you sooner.
Getting our kids' names
in a professor's thesis
will open many doors for them.
They all do it.
Only those without
connections can't do it.
Why would you say no
when the opportunity is given to you?
I appreciate the offer,
but I'll pass.
Do you mean that?
Yes.
I'll get going then.
Okay. I have patients
in the afternoon too.
See you next time.
Bye.
SONMAT NOODLES
Hey.
FREE FOOD FOR CHILDREN,
TEENAGERS, AND PREGNANT WOMEN
NO NEED TO SHOW YOUR WELFARE CARD.
JUST ENJOY.
-Thank you for the meal.
-My pleasure.
No, you don't need to show that.
I told you before.
Come back once you finish that.
You're welcome even if I'm not here.
You can order dumplings to go.
Children eat for free here.
Come again.
-Thank you.
-Sure. Goodbye.
Gosh, I'm so stuffed. I can't breathe.
You ate so much. Did you not have lunch?
Of course I did.
I actually had lunch outside.
But she wouldn't have eaten if I didn't.
That's why I ate.
However, your food tasted so good
that I just couldn't stop.
I thought I'd never be able
to cook like Joong-do's mom.
-Maybe I'm close now.
-Why would you compare yourself to her?
She has her style,
and you have your own as well.
Jeez, look at you brown-nosing me.
-Were you grocery shopping?
-Yes.
I want to make some short ribs
for Ji-hoon.
Lucky him.
I should get going now.
I've been strangely busy all day.
I need to pick up some perilla oil too.
I recently found a place that extracts
the oil without roasting the seeds.
So I'm trying them out.
It's near Taeyang Apartment.
-What's funny?
-You spoke in dialect.
I did?
Yes, you said, "It's near
Taeyang Apartment," in a dialect.
Where's your hometown?
North Chungcheong.
I see. Which area?
Ask if they have domestic sesame oil.
Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
-Goodbye.
Did I say something I shouldn't have?
She doesn't like talking
about her hometown.
She's been through a rough childhood
so she must not have many fond memories.
Gosh. I see.
But still, she's successful now.
Don't be ridiculous.
She doesn't have any money.
She donates all the money she earns.
No, I'm not talking about money.
I mean she's very happy.
Good job.
-One, two, three.
Hello, ma'am. Hello.
-Hello.
-Hye-joo, long time no see.
Have you been well?
Yes. How about you?
We've been good as always.
Oh, these?
We still receive them
along with some cash.
The donor is still anonymous.
We were too busy this morning,
so we're finally moving them in now.
Then let me help.
-No.
It's okay.
All right. I'll call before
I stop by next time.
Okay. Call and stop by
when we're not too busy.
I will. See you next time.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
Who is she?
She used to work with us.
I see. She's a social worker?
No, she's not.
She was just a contract worker.
I think she started as a part-timer.
I'll head inside, then.
-Okay.
-See you.
Her husband is the district assemblyman.
An assemblyman for Sinyang-gu?
-Exactly.
-No way.
What's the name
of the district assemblyman again?
I'm Nam Joong-do of the Daehan Party.
Dear citizens,
I am standing here today
to speak against
the repeated illegal land speculation
engaged by my fellow assemblymen.
I am here today with a great sense
of responsibility and a heavy heart.
For this country to be free of corruption,
we must eradicate
all illegal real estate speculation
by members of the National Assembly.
NEW BILL TO ERADICATE
ILLEGAL REAL ESTATE SPECULATION
The sister-in-law of Kang Soon-hong
of the Nation and People's Party
-purchased farmland in Youngsan last year.
-That little…
Recently, that land was chosen
to be redeveloped by the MOLIT.
Damn it.
He claims that he had no part in…
I promise to eradicate
real estate speculation.
In addition, I request once again
that a special investigation
led by experts
be held as urgently as possible.
How did Kang Soon-hong
get elected for the fifth time
when his family members take turns
causing controversies?
His wife's wealth got him elected,
so he's returning the favor.
We don't need family men like him.
I can't help but think this way
whenever such incidents occur.
It may be a blessing for Assemblyman Nam
that his late mother was
the only family member he had.
His wife doesn't have any family either
and she keeps to herself.
That's not always a good thing.
He started off as a list member
and finally managed to run for office.
But she's never shown up
to any of his campaigns…
No, she's never shown herself
in public at all.
The other wives do their best
to win over the electorate.
This is what everyone's been thinking
during the last general election.
According to Mr. Jang,
she had allowed her husband
to run for office under that condition.
She apparently didn't want
any part in his political career.
In a way, Assemblyman Nam is…
How should I put this?
What's to think about?
He's the perfect husband.
Not many husbands would
ever go that far to protect their wives
regardless of what people say
behind their backs.
Did you have a big fight yesterday?
No.
You got pretty riled up talking about
other husbands just now.
Are you okay?
About tonight's dinner…
Ms. Woo wants to see you.
Okay.
Hello, Assemblyman Kang.
Who was he again?
Are you a secretary?
It's Assemblyman Nam Joong-do
of the Daehan Party.
I see. You're an assemblyman.
Goodness.
My apologies.
You just looked so young
that I thought you were
an assemblyman's secretary.
That's okay.
When you were my age,
you were a secretary to the late
Assemblyman Kim Myeong-jae.
I understand the confusion.
-That's…
-Goodbye.
How young and brash he is.
DAEHAN PARTY CHAIRWOMAN
WOO JIN-SEOK
I'm sure you're busy preparing
for the National Assembly inspection.
When did you prepare all this?
I envy your youth.
I've been hearing that a lot today.
I was only elected four times so far,
but 15 and a half years
have passed in the blink of an eye.
The Nation and People's Party is probably
to blame for some of these gray hairs.
I can count on you, right?
We have eight months
until the general election.
The timing is just right.
I'll do my best.
Sure. I don't worry one bit.
You're the best our party has to offer.
Do you like the view here?
The eighth floor isn't that low.
Haven't you been using
your office on the tenth floor
since your first election?
Yes, that's correct.
Why didn't you come down during this term?
Did you feel like you didn't deserve it
because you were
only a list member last time?
Not at all.
I signed up for the same room
because I wanted to remain humble.
Humble?
Eight years of humility
is more than enough.
Once this general election pans out,
you'd be elected for the third time.
You'll be able to pick
any office you like.
Would you like this room instead?
I'm a bit tired of that view now.
No, I'm fine.
Or sign up for the room
on the sixth floor that the president used
during his time as an assemblyman.
The competition for that room
is quite fierce.
But if you want it,
I can pull some strings.
I couldn't possibly do that
during my third term.
I'm content with my current room.
You sure aren't greedy.
I can't say that I'm not greedy at all.
Why else would I be here?
You see,
none of the offices
anywhere in this building
have a view of Bugaksan
like the Blue House does.
That's right.
As long as you're in Yeouido, that is.
Pardon my thoughtlessness.
Your current office
will soon become the office
that the assemblymen will compete to have.
-Hello.
What's next?
You have an interview with SBC.
Honey, I'll be home
around midnight tonight.
Guess what?
I got called young twice today.
-And for dinner…
-How do you like having a young husband?
Okay.
DEOKSUNG MILL
HOW DO YOU LIKE HAVING A YOUNG HUSBAND?
Jeez.
Good for you.
But I'll always be younger than you.
Come on. We're almost the same age.
-Are you here for oil?
-Yes.
No one's in, right?
She must be out.
Her granddaughter passed away.
I'm sorry?
She was a university student.
She hanged herself.
NAMGOONG SOL
She fought with her boyfriend,
and he threatened to spread
some embarrassing photos of her.
But the police haven't even
arrested that bastard.
He's apparently a medical student.
They didn't arrest him
saying that he wouldn't flee.
Excuse me. Do I know you?
Right. You came by the mill yesterday.
Please eat.
How did you come all the way here?
She lost her parents at a young age,
so I raised her with the utmost care
to the best of my abilities.
But the police won't even
arrest that bastard.
ROOM 5
NAMGOONG SOL
Look.
Please sign the guest book
before you leave.
I'm so grateful that you came,
so I want to remember you.
Will you do that for me?
-It's fine.
-But still…
Right.
I have your perilla oil ready.
Don't worry about it. I'll come by later.
All right, then.
Sol used to tell me
to close down the mill and stop working.
She said I didn't have to work
because she had a part-time job.
But now I'm glad
that I didn't listen to her
to be able to have a guest at her funeral.
Thank you so much for coming.
I mean it.
Don't mention it. I'll be going now.
Go on.
CLEAN, HONEST, AND COMPETENT WORKER
NAM JOONG-DO
A special education school
next to a regular one?
That's just absurd.
It's important that we build this school
for disabled children
who struggle to travel long distances.
We only have a bus from Manil-dong
to Jicheong Station every 20 minutes,
which is just too long.
All the other buses come by
every 6 to 13 minutes at most.
-That's quite a difference.
-It is.
-Well noted.
-Please check.
We can't have such large vehicles
driving by where children commute.
Despite being a school zone,
there's too much speeding.
She's right. It's a very dangerous area.
Right. I agree.
Please give me a call
through the number on my card
if you need anything else.
Is this your personal number?
Not your secretary's?
Yes, it's mine.
I'll be picking up, so call me anytime.
I see. Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-This way.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
Thank you for your time, everyone.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Goodbye.
Good work.
Gosh, what a busy day.
Do you really answer
all their calls yourself?
Of course.
I may not be able to resolve everything,
but it provides a chance
to vent their frustrations and feel heard.
Speaking directly with an assemblyman
provides some assurance.
Some of them curse me out
as soon as I pick up,
but I'll live longer thanks to them.
I'll give you a summary
of today's discussions later.
Okay. Thank you.
We finished much earlier than I thought.
When's the dinner with our sponsor?
At 7 p.m. at Haniljeong.
SINYANG-GU WOMEN AND YOUTH SHELTER
THANK YOU FOR THE DELIVERY
ENJOY
Is that you, Yoon-seo?
-Mom!
-What is it this time?
Did you say I can't go to SNU this Sunday?
-Yes.
-Why?
My friends' parents are
pulling all the strings they can
to beef up their kids' resumes.
It's not like I asked Dad for help.
So why would you decline their help?
How can a middle school student
be credited as a co-author?
What can you even do to help
a professor with his thesis?
There must be something.
He told us to come.
You don't even know anything.
Of course I do.
You didn't even go to university.
Sorry.
That may be true,
but I know that it's absurd
for you to be credited as a co-author.
Dad would have said no too if he--
There you go, bringing him up again.
Stop using him as your excuse.
Why can't I do what all my friends do
just because of him?
Jeez. This is so annoying.
Yoon-seo, we're not done talking.
Forget it. I won't go, all right?
Yoon-seo, stop right there.
Yoon-seo.
Did you lock the door? Open up.
Go away. I'm going to study.
Really? You're going to be
in serious trouble, young lady.
Nam Yoon-seo.
I'm sorry.
He texted me saying he was almost home.
Why the long face? Is it Yoon-seo?
She's acting out more and more.
She's going through puberty.
Ji-hoon was the same.
I feel terrible the moment
I'm done scolding them.
Maybe it's because he's a politician,
but I don't think we're doing
as well as other parents are.
You two are doing a terrific job.
Right. Do you want to use Ji-hoon's room?
Me? Why? I already have a room.
Your room is too small
because it was
my late mother-in-law's storage room.
Had we known you'd be living with us,
we would have built a room for you
upstairs when we first moved in.
Forget it.
The upstairs is for your family.
I'm fine with my room.
Yeo-jin, you know
how grateful I am for you, right?
When my mother-in-law passed away
and I was pregnant with Yoon-seo,
I was going through so much.
Had you not offered to live together,
I wouldn't have been
able to endure it all.
Thank you so much.
-I'm home.
-Hey.
You're home awfully early today.
I should take a breather too.
You're still up? It's late.
She wanted to have a beer.
Why? Did I do something wrong?
Why? Are you feeling guilty?
Recycling is tomorrow.
I haven't done anything wrong.
-Give it to me.
-Thank you. I enjoyed it.
No problem.
Give it to me. I'll wash it with the rest.
No, I can do it.
Just give it to me.
How can you make him vegetable juice
every morning for the past eight years?
But this is the only thing
that I'm doing for him.
Exactly. I didn't bargain well.
I should have asked
for some other things too.
-Rest up. Thanks.
-Okay.
-Good night.
-You too.
You must be exhausted.
Wash up and go to bed, honey.
Why are you staring at me?
My face is flushed, isn't it?
You're pretty.
-Are you drunk?
-No.
What's with you? Go to bed.
Stop that. Just go to bed.
I came home early for once.
I can't just go to bed.
What's wrong with you?
Honey, your phone.
But I already clocked out.
It's Woo-jae. It must be something urgent.
-Pick up.
-No.
Pick up, Mr. Assemblyman.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes?
I see.
Okay.
I need to go out for a bit.
There's a wake I have to attend.
Whose wake?
Taeyang Shopping Center's leader's
mother-in-law passed away.
But isn't it too late right now?
I have a tight schedule tomorrow.
It's better to go now.
-Go to sleep.
-Okay.
Bye.
Right, the short ribs.
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
He must have been in a hurry.
It's pouring.
Yoon-seo…
I see. So she's not there?
Never mind.
She must be out somewhere else.
Okay. I'm sorry for waking you up.
-She's not at Da-som's?
-No.
Where did she go in this rain?
Her phone is still off.
Joong-do isn't picking up either.
I should go to the police station.
Can you go back home?
What if Yoon-seo returns and no one--
Okay. I'll stay at home.
-Don't worry too much.
-Thanks.
-Call me if anything comes up.
-Okay.
That's all.
I came here after that.
When we get a report of a runaway,
we start by tracking their whereabouts.
But we can't really do that
since your daughter's phone is off.
We'll go out and ask around.
Are there any places
she frequents regularly?
What was she wearing?
It was…
-Forget it. I won't go, all right?
-It was brick-red.
She's probably wearing
a brick-red windbreaker.
It's thin and has a hoodie.
She's constantly wearing it
ever since we got it recently.
Honey.
-Honey.
It's okay.
I'm sure she's fine.
Are you her husband?
-Yes.
-Please come with us.
This way.
She'll be okay.
Let's go.
-Do you know Nam Yoon-seo?
-No, I don't.
Do you know Nam Yoon-seo?
Have you seen her at school?
I don't know.
Sir!
-Have you found her?
-Not yet.
I'll park the car
-and look over there.
-Okay.
-Then I'll go that way.
-Yes, sir.
Yoon-seo.
Excuse me.
-Yoon-seo.
-Pardon?
Ma'am, since our shift has ended,
those two will take over for us.
We're regularly checking the CCTV cameras.
I'm sorry,
but could you get
a few more detectives to help us?
This is the standard procedure
for runaways.
We're doing the best we can,
so don't worry too much--
-How could I not be worried?
-Honey.
She's been gone
for more than 12 hours now.
Could you bring on at least
two more detectives?
Honey, calm down.
How could I be calm right now?
It's our child we're talking about.
Ma'am, please try to calm down.
We're doing our best.
-We're checking the cameras.
-Check your phone.
I'm sure she's fine.
HE'S ASSEMBLYMAN NAM JOONG-DO!
Don't worry.
Sir.
Are you the assemblyman of Sinyang-gu?
You're Assemblyman Nam Joong-do, right?
Yes, I am.
I wish you would have told us sooner.
One minute.
Let me report this to the higher-ups…
-That's not necessary.
-Pardon?
Please treat this case like any other.
I don't want any favors.
Honey.
Let's ask them for help.
Just this once, honey.
What if something happens to Yoon-seo?
You're her dad
before you're an assemblyman.
Please?
-I got you some coffee.
-Thank you.
Yes, Chief.
I'll put him on the phone.
-It's our chief.
-Thank you.
Hello, sir.
Yes.
You're making it a missing persons case?
I see.
I'm sorry for troubling you
on your day off.
Okay. Goodbye.
Thank you.
-Hey.
-She goes to Jicheong Middle School.
Have you seen her before?
SAUNA, GYM
INTERNET CAFE
LOOKING FOR NAM YOON-SEO
FEMALE, 15 YO, 163CM, 45KG,
BRICK RED WINDBREAKER
Can you please have a look?
Could you look at this, please?
MISSING PERSON
INCOMING CALL
She's in shock right now,
so she doesn't remember much.
-My goodness.
-I can't believe this happened.
Hello, sir. Let him in.
Mom, is this my sister Yoon-seo?
JICHEONG MIDDLE SCHOOL GRADUATION CEREMONY
Assemblyman Nam Joong-do
of the Daehan Party's eldest son
was found dead
on the banks of the Han River
around 8:55 p.m. this evening.
The police stated they found the body…
-Mom.
-…earlier this afternoon,
while they were searching the area
for Assemblyman Nam's missing daughter.
Further investigation into his death
will be carried out
once the body has been recovered.
Nam had been on probation last March
for an intoxicated assault case
at a club in Gangnam
when he assaulted another pedestrian
while drunk, resulting in injuries…
You can be honest with me.
Don't you love your daughter
a bit more than your son?
Why wasn't I…
Fine. I'd rather you disappear
than cause trouble like this!
Of course not. I love them both equally.
…more honest at that moment?
Is that why…
I'm being punished?
Ji-hoon.
So…
your son's biological mother
has passed away?
Yes.
Your son was released
from prison 15 days ago.
That's right.
Do you know his whereabouts
between that day
and the time of his death?
I went to pick him up…
on the day of his release.
You should have some.
I bought it at the market this morning.
You used to love tofu from there.
Have some. Just a bite.
Are you kicking me out now
because I'm an ex-convict?
Your room at home will still be there.
Feel free to move back in
whenever you want.
But you want this more than us, don't you?
I'll pay the rent and the maintenance fee.
There's 1.5 million won on this card.
This is for your living expenses.
Once that's gone, you're on your own.
You must have a lot of money
to get me a house and some allowance.
It was meant to be your college tuition.
Keep the house tidy.
And come home to eat at least once a week.
Answer me, will you?
Okay.
Don't drink too much.
And call your dad.
Take care of yourself.
Bye.
Here.
I bought you something to wear.
Ji-hoon.
Why don't we stop
breaking each other's hearts now?
Stop beating around the bush.
You want me to just drop dead
instead of ruining Dad's career.
-Ji-hoon.
-You can stop pretending.
You know that's what everyone wants.
How could you even say--
What?
Has that never occurred to you?
Not even once?
Fine.
I'd rather you disappear
than cause trouble like this!
Are you happy now?
Is that what you wanted to hear?
That's all.
On the day of his release,
I drove him to his new place.
So, have you seen him since then
until the day of the accident?
No.
Just yesterday,
I was going to visit him
with some homemade dishes…
I see.
What about you, sir?
Did you meet with him?
No.
All right. First of all…
we found one gram
of methamphetamine in his pocket.
No.
That couldn't have been his.
-Ji-hoon would have never--
-Honey.
And the phone he had with him
turned out to be a burner phone.
A burner phone?
Are you sure?
Yes. The phone he had under his name
is still currently turned off.
But the last signal
was from about 4.5km upstream.
We're currently looking for it.
We're checking all the CCTV cameras,
but there was heavy rain
at the presumed time of his death.
And there aren't any cameras
near the Han River.
Truthfully,
we're having some difficulties.
Although…
a waiter at a club in Gangnam testified
that he had seen your son
at the club alone, drinking heavily,
just a few hours prior to his death.
We've obtained CCTV footage
of your son there.
The autopsy result will come out
in 10 to 15 days.
The forensics team will have
to look into his phone,
but judging by the circumstances
and the absence of any signs of trauma,
it's most likely
that he drowned after losing his footing
while under the influence
of alcohol or narcotics.
We don't know how he obtained
the methamphetamine,
but since he's dead,
we won't be able to prosecute him,
and the case will be closed.
Mom! Dad!
Mom…
Mom.
I just wanted to make you and Dad
worry about me.
Since I didn't have to go to school today
I was planning to
stay at a sauna somewhere far from home…
So why is Ji-hoon…
Why…
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
No, Yoon-seo.
It's not your fault.
Yoon-seo…
SINYANG FUNERAL HOME
THE NATIONAL ASSEMBLY
OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Please don't bring in any more.
REST IN PEACE
SNU COLLEGE OF LAW ASSOCIATION
DAEHAN PARTY CHAIRWOMAN
WOO JIN-SEOK
I'm truly sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
This is Mr. Bae Gyeong-guk,
Taeyang Shopping Center's leader.
Hello. Thank you for coming.
I can't believe this.
My mother-in-law's funeral
took place here,
and her coffin was borne out this morning.
Stay strong.
Thank you.
Honestly, his son must have been
such a headache for him.
His son got into trouble right before
the last general election
and almost cost him the election.
This could actually be for the best
with the next election around the corner.
The least you can do
is keep your mouths shut…
if you can't empathize with him.
-I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Hello, ma'am.
Are they her relatives?
I think she's…
I think it's Ji-hoon's
maternal grandmother.
His mother's side?
I mean, his biological mother's?
Yes.
By the way,
I had no idea her husband
was an assemblyman.
How did you hide it from everyone?
2 WEEKS LATER
Hello?
Are you really moving out?
It's only been one month.
Yes. I'll call you once everything is set.
Okay. Goodbye.
DEATH CERTIFICATE
NAME: NAM…
Hello, ma'am.
Hello.
Were you away on a trip?
-Pardon?
-That box had been empty for a while.
THANK YOU FOR THE DELIVERY
ENJOY
I'm sorry. I've been quite busy.
Please, don't apologize.
Did you visit somewhere nice?
Goodbye, then.
Goodbye.
Hello.
I'm sorry, but who are you?
I'm--
I'm sorry, I couldn't hear you.
What did you say?
I'm pregnant.
Excuse me?
I'm…
pregnant with Ji-hoon's baby.
The police found
a gram of methamphetamine
in the pocket of Assemblyman Nam's son
whose body was found 15 days ago.
According to Sinyang Police Station,
they found a small resealable bag
containing one gram of methamphetamine
as well as a burner phone.
To investigate the details of his death…
You're pregnant…
with Ji-hoon's baby?
Yes.
TROLLEY
How could they do this
to someone who just lost his son?
We're in Yeouido.
You know how it is in politics.
What does she want?
She wants a place to stay.
She has nowhere to go.
Your son was caught on the camera
at the entrance of the restroom.
Is Ji-hoon really the father?
I guess you don't want to believe it.
I'll get an abortion.
Everyone is a stranger at first.
She's not just a stranger!
That's enough.
Are you here to blackmail them?
Assemblyman Nam Joong-do of
the Daehan Party must take responsibility
and step down from his office.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim