Third: Today,
both of us and our eight friends
Third: are doing a fashion show with mud-dyed tie-dye fabric.
Talay: Let’s go!
Junlan: Let’s go.
F4: I saw others dressing minimally,
simple and casual.
F4: We went the opposite.
We wore black, leather jackets, and sequins.
Junlan: When you see the other groups,
Junlan: even if they look classy, it doesn’t look expensive.
After the show, post the finished look on Instagram
and tag each other as collaborators.
We have a special reward for whoever gets the most likes
within 15 minutes
And the ones who got the most likes are Talay and Junlan
(Talay is awake.)
(Intouch is still asleep.)
(F4 is awake.)
(Dokyun and Junlan are exercising.)
(Third blow-drying his hair.)
(Zhuojie cooking)
(Huh?)
(Smells like delicious food)
(So tasty...)
(Dreaming of eating food)
F4: Today, I’ll be doing makeup for Third
F4: Using foundation
and Chat brand cosmetics
Third: That’s right.
F4: First, use foundation, shade 1.5 Vanilla
(Foundation first)
(Shade 1.5 Vanilla)
F4: First, use foundation, shade 1.5 Vanilla
Third: Vanilla, yes
F4: Just squeeze a little bit
and use Chat’s brush too
F4: Dab and press lightly around your face
F4: Let the brush press the foundation in like this
F4: Then dab it right on the face like this
F4: This foundation can be used by Thais.
(Usable for Thais)
Third: Yes.
Third: Because it matches Thai skin tones.
(Suitable for Asians)
Third: And also for Asians.
F4: That’s right.
F4: Lightweight but with strong coverage
just a little goes a long way, and the price is affordable too
F4: Next, we’ll use blush stick
from Chat as well.
(Cream blush stick)
F4: Next, we’ll use blush stick
from Chat as well.
F4: The color is beautiful, shade Sweet Melon
F4: Here, look at the color
(Pretty sweet color)
F4: And the technique is to blend
for a natural flush as usual.
F4: Use the same brush and dab around
F4: After that, smile
F4: And the color is set nicely on the face.
F4: That’s it, just brush a little on the nose.
Third: But if you don’t have a brush, the other end has a built-in one.
F4: Yes, exactly
Third: That lets you blend it in.
F4: Very easy to use.
F4: That’s it for this simple makeup look.
F4: Using Chat’s foundation and blush stick
F4: You can buy them at leading stores nationwide.
(Go grab one!)
Third: That’s right.
Junsu: What’s today’s mission?
(Morning in Zhuojie’s style)
Zhuojie: Good morning, F4. Good morning, Third
Junsu: Good morning
Junsu: Good morning, good morning everyone
Porsche: Good morning
Junsu: Good morning everyone
Dokyun: Hello
(Ready for a high-five)
(Jawoon pretends not to see.)
(Pretends to walk away)
(I’ll clap my own hand then.)
(Today you’re done for, Jawoon!!!)
Talay: Hello
Junlan: Hello
Talay: Hello everyone
Junlan: Hello everyone
Talay: Hello, you lowlifes
(Lowlifes!!)
(So harsh!!)
(So you guys are second-class, huh)
Talay: I slept so well, I don’t want to touch you anymore.
(Story from yesterday)
Last night, Talay and Junlan
completed the mission with the most likes,
so they received the special twin bed room.
(Story from yesterday)
Junlan: This is my dream bed!
Junlan: Oh my god
(Story from yesterday)
Junlan: Guys, that's for girls...
(How was last night?)
Junsu: How was last night?
(Junsu cares about last night.)
Junlan: Why?
Junsu: How was last night?
(Junsu cares about last night.)
Talay: I slept soundly.
Junsu: Slept soundly?
Talay: No one walked around my bed.
(Too straightforward)
Junsu: Because of him?
Talay: No, nothing
Junlan: There’s even a bathtub upstairs
Junsu: A bathtub?
Junlan: Yes.
Junlan: And we took a hot bath.
Jawoon: A hot bath?
Jawoon: You guys...
Dokyun: Really?
(Took a bath together??)
Jawoon: Did you guys bathe together?
Junlan: No, no, no!
Talay: No, no, no!
Junlan: No, no
Zhuojie: Jawoon, you must sleep together, bathe together
Zhuojie: Do everything together, everything
Junlan: It was very good, everything was nice.
Junlan: Don’t be jealous
Hello everyone
Let’s recap, so you don’t forget the mission:
You must gather money to reach the goal
to go on a journey together and see the beauty of Thailand.
As of today, how much money do you have left?
Intouch: Right now we have 13,000 baht left.
(Remaining balance: 13,000 baht)
Intouch: Because we spent almost 2,000 baht yesterday.
Today all 10 of you must go complete a mission.
Please draw lots to choose the location
for today’s mission.
(Draw now)
: Let’s all go together.
: Yes, let’s all go together.
Dokyun: Grab a paper, grab one
Dokyun: Porsche, grab the blue one
Talay: Yellow, red, green, purple
Talay: Bangkok
Junsu: What’s the location?
Porsche: Napak Muaythai Gym
Dokyun: Muay Thai?
Junsu: Muay Thai
Zhuojie: Let me tell you, even if three came
none would dare fight me.
Talay: No wonder you did cardio this morning.
Porsche: I think the one most suited is Zhuojie.
Junlan: I soaked yesterday.
Dokyun: There’s also one upstairs?
Zhuojie: Me alone, versus Junlan
(Ready to fight!)
Zhuojie: I just want to fight Junlan.
Junlan: Jeremy
Zhuojie: Like this—translate for me
(Huh? Translate what??)
Even five Junlans wouldn’t dare fight me.
Junsu: He said even if there were five like Junlan, they wouldn’t beat him.
(“Even five Junlans can’t beat Zhuojie.”)
(Show-off battle)
Today everyone must do the mission at the Muay Thai gym.
If you’re ready, go get prepared.
Talay: So it'll be done as a team.
Looks like everyone knows Muay Thai
and is especially excited for this mission.
Not sure if the Muay Thai they’ll face today
will be like the Muay Thai they know.
(Travel time: 1 hour)
Junlan: 1 hour?
Talay & Intouch: Yes, 1 hour.
(Travel time: 1 hour)
Talay: You can sleep first, I’ll sleep too.
(The driver can’t sleep though.)
(Travel time: 1 hour)
Junlan: I'm not going to sleep, I already drank too much coffee.
Junlan: I drank too much coffee, I can’t sleep
Talay: Me too.
(Traveling from The Horizon Khaoyai - NP Muay Thai Gym)
F4: Jawoon, have you been shocked yet today?
(Shocked in the morning)
Jawoon: Shocked already
Jawoon: Shocked every day
(Shocked every day)
Porsche: Shocked by everything?
Jawoon: Yes.
(Shocked by everything)
Jawoon: Shocked by everything
Jawoon: Muay Thai is good for diet.
Porsche: Yes, it’s great cardio.
(Muay Thai = exercise)
Jawoon: Yes.
Jawoon: Helps me eat more
(Muay Thai = food)
(Muay Thai = exercise)
Jawoon: Helps me eat more
(Not even training yet, already talking food)
Porsche: Basically, you just want to eat more.
Jawoon: Yes.
Jawoon: Eat big, big, big, big
Jawoon: Okay, okay, okay
(Sounds weird)
Jawoon: Muay Thai, eat big big, yes yes
(Thais confused #2)
Jawoon: No Muay Thai, eat...
Jawoon: Eat small small small small
(Means just a little??)
Porsche: A little bit
Jawoon: A little bit
(If not confused, you’d be more confused.)
The 10 guys arrived at today’s mission site.
(Mission site: Napak Muaythai Gym)
The 10 guys arrived at today’s mission site,
which is Napak Muaythai Gym.
(Mission site: Napak Muaythai Gym)
And the coach for today’s mission is
Prajanchai P.K. Saenchai Muay Thai Gym
A fighter hailed as a genius boxer of this era
(Thanks to One Championship for the photo)
Prajanchai gained worldwide fame by defeating the ONE world champion.
He has faced legendary fighters.
(Thanks to One Championship for the photo)
Will the Boys Lost guys be able to handle it?
Talay: Hello
Porsche: Hello
Everyone: Hello
Coach: Hello
Coach: Let me introduce myself.
I’m Prajanchai P.K. Saenchai Muay Thai Gym.
Coach: Today, I’d like to welcome
all of the Boys Lost in Thailand cast.
Coach: Are you all ready to train with me today?
Talay: Are we ready?
Everyone: Ready!
Everyone’s spirits are sky-high
The first thing you need for training like a Muay Thai fighter is shorts
With nametags for everyone as well
Coach: Go change into your outfits
Talay: Go, let’s go!
Talay: Change outfits!
Coach: Today I’ll teach you that
for Muay Thai fighting.
Coach: Everyone must have a master,
so you need to perform the Wai Khru ritual.
Coach: Today I’ll first teach you
the Wai Khru Muay Thai.
Coach: I need one person who thinks he can be the leader.
Step forward.
Talay: That team over there
(The PE teacher has to lead, right?)
Porsche: Go ahead, you Zhuojie
Talay: Seven
Porsche: Stand in front
(Shouldn’t you ask first?)
Porsche: Go in front
Talay: Come forward, come forward
Coach: Okay
(First time for the boys to practice Wai Khru Muay Thai.)
Wai Khru Muay Thai
is an important and sacred ritual of Muay Thai.
It shows respect to teachers and masters,
and brings blessings and encouragement before stepping into the ring.
The dance is also a warm-up and a way to stretch.
(Oh, not yet?!?)
And prepares the muscles before the fight.
It’s a unique identity of Muay Thai,
unlike any other martial art.
Coach: Okay.
Coach: Next, stretch your legs.
At first it may look easy.
Coach: Lean forward.
But good Wai Khru Muay Thai
is not just about correct movements, but also grace.
And at the same time, it must be strong,
able to intimidate the opponent.
And this is probably the boys’ first time
learning Wai Khru from a real fighter.
Coach: Okay.
Coach: Bring your guard up, everyone, and sway forward.
Coach: Sway forward, then sway back.
(Can’t understand. Just watch.)
Coach: Raise it up, sway forward again, and reset stance.
Coach: To the left.
Coach: Okay.
Coach: Bring up your guard and sway forward.
(Looking good in stance)
Coach: One.
Coach: Sway back again. One, two, reset stance.
Coach: Sweep your hands forward.
Coach: One, two, three, and return to guard.
(Dokyun loves this.)
Coach: And then sway back.
Coach: Okay, everyone.
Dokyun: Yes, because Jawoon already likes Muay Thai.
Dokyun: When he came to Bangkok,
he even signed up for Muay Thai classes.
Dokyun: He’s good with punches, but Wai Khru... not at all.
Dokyun: But I did it nicely, right?
Dokyun: Because my hands are pretty.
Coach: No need to rush. One, two, three, four.
Coach: Left hand up, spin.
Coach: One, two, three, four, guard.
Coach: Sway back.
Coach: Reset stance.
Coach: Turn that way, everyone. How do you turn?
Coach: Okay.
Coach: And roll up.
Zhuojie: Yes, this is my first time practicing Muay Thai.
Zhuojie: But before, I saw it on TV sometimes,
and also saw matches between
Chinese fighters and Thai fighters.
Zhuojie: So I had some understanding.
Zhuojie: And I’ve always wanted to try Muay Thai myself.
Zhuojie: After trying today, I realized
it’s really different from what I saw on TV.
Zhuojie: As an athlete,
I already care about competition.
Zhuojie: And this time, it’s not just about experiencing another culture.
Zhuojie: Muay Thai is another unique part
of Thai culture.
Zhuojie: I also want to learn it properly.
Zhuojie: But from the beginning, during Wai Khru,
Zhuojie: because of communication issues,
Zhuojie: there were many things I didn’t understand or couldn’t remember.
Zhuojie: It made me feel frustrated with myself.
Coach: Very good, boys. Very good.
Coach: And next, this is today’s mission.
Junsu: Thank you.
Everyone: Thank you.
Live like a boxer.
If you succeed, you’ll receive 4 money
and four puzzle pieces.
Station 1: jump rope.
Everyone must take turns jump roping
for a total of 1,000.
Coach: Okay boys, everyone.
Coach: This is station one,
or the first mission.
Coach: I’ll give you one rope.
Coach: Everyone takes turns, one at a time.
Coach: Total of 1,000 times.
Coach: But with a time limit of 10 minutes.
Coach: If within 10 minutes,
Coach: everyone alternates until reaching 1,000...
Station one: jump rope.
Total 1,000.
Ready? Let’s go!
(Player 1: Junsu)
Jawoon: Fighting, fighting, fighting!
(“Oh, awesome!”)
Jawoon: Oh, Junsu, Junsu!
(50 times)
Junsu passes 50 jumps easily,
leaving the team speechless.
(What is this?!)
Zhuojie: Another 30 seconds, Junsu!
Zhuojie: 30 more seconds!
(Amazing)
(100 times)
(Super fit, Junsu)
(Go for a thousand!)
(Warming up already)
(150 times)
Passed 150 already.
Talay shouts wow — Junsu, you’re amazing!
Zhuojie: How many?
Zhuojie: How many now?
(So serious)
Zhuojie: How many already?
(Getting tired)
(200 times)
(Junsu finished with 216 times.)
(Player 2: Zhuojie)
Junsu: But the rope is really heavy.
(What’s so funny, bro?)
(250 times)
Dokyun: That’s really good.
Zhuojie: Don’t laugh at me.
(Jump! Don’t stop!!)
Zhuojie: Don’t laugh, okay?
Junsu: How many now?
(300 times)
(Slowing down)
Junsu: 30 seconds, 30 seconds, okay?
(Zhuojie finished with 126 times.)
(342 times)
Coach: 342.
(Player 3: Dokyun)
Junsu: 340.
Zhuojie: Whoever jumps fast, go first.
(400 times)
Junsu: 10 seconds, 10 seconds!
(Dokyun finished with 86 times.)
Only three minutes passed,
but the boys already reached
(Dokyun finished with 86 times.)
428 jumps — nearly halfway.
(428 times)
(Player 4: Junlan)
Six boys haven’t jumped yet.
This mission seems doable.
Junsu still holds first place
with 216 jumps.
Zhuojie is second with 126.
Dokyun is third with 86.
Let’s see how many Junlan can add.
Junsu: 10 seconds!
Junsu: 5, 4, 3... okay, done, done!
(500 times)
(Junlan finished with 72 times)
(Junlan finished with 72 times.)
Coach: 500 already.
Coach: Close! Very close!
(Player 5: Talay)
(Focused)
(Concentrating)
(Mind ready)
(Body not ready)
(Jumping rope or teasing friends?)
Coach: 22 times already, faster, more!
Junsu: Talay, Talay!
(Doing difficult tricks too)
(540 times)
(Talay finished with 40 times.)
Coach: I know who already jumped.
(540 times)
(Talay finished with 40 times.)
(Player 6: Porsche)
Looks like Porsche isn’t good at jump rope at all.
Zhuojie: It’s okay, it’s okay. No worries.
(Supportive teammate)
Zhuojie keeps encouraging him nonstop.
(578 times)
(Porsche finished with 38 times.)
Coach: Hurry, next person.
(Player 7: F4)
Junsu: No, no, no!
Talay: Go, go, go!
(606 times)
(F4 finished with 28 times.)
(Player 8: Third)
(617 times)
(Third finished with 11 times.)
(Isn’t it too fast, Third?)
Dokyun: Intouch
Dokyun: Go for it
Talay: Intouch
(Player 9: Intouch)
(Great form)
(639 times)
(Intouch did 22 times.)
(Huh??)
Great form but Intouch could only do 22 times.
(Player 10: Jawoon)
Let’s see how much the 10th person, Jawoon, can do.
Dokyun: 300 left
Zhuojie: Hurry up
(“Faster, faster, faster”)
Zhuojie: Faster, faster, faster
(“Go, go, go”)
Dokyun: Go, go, go
(“Faster, faster, faster”)
(Cheering or pressuring??)
Coach: 700 already
(700 times)
Dokyun: 700 now, just a little more
Zhuojie: Tell him if he’s tired, just rest. No need to rush
(Encouragement overflowing)
Dokyun: If you’re tired, you can switch with someone else.
Zhuojie: Faster, faster, faster
Jawoon: Be quiet, damn it
(Be quiet~)
(Jawoon is focusing.)
Junsu: He said keep it down.
(779 times)
(Jawoon did 140 times.)
Everyone’s jumped already,
but we haven’t gotten that far.
The next person needs to speed up to catch up with time
Junsu: Today, right?
Junsu: Today feels good
Junsu: Maybe because I got to use my body a lot,
Junsu: so I think this mission
Junsu: might suit me the most.
(877 times)
(Junsu did 87 times.)
Dokyun: Go, go, go
(Zhuojie’s about to fly.)
(893 times)
(Zhuojie did 16 times.)
Porsche: How many left?
Dokyun: Out of all the filming we’ve done, I like today the most.
Dokyun: Because I really like moving my body.
Dokyun: And today we got to do an activity
that let me move like this for the first time.
Dokyun: I’m really okay with it, because just having fun is enough.
Dokyun: Happiness is enough.
(965 times)
(Dokyun did 72 times.)
With just 35 times remaining,
will they have the strength to keep going?
(1,000 times completed)
Coach: If it's 8 minutes, it’s really close.
Coach: Today, everyone has completed Station 1.
This mission started with Junsu.
His strength, jumping in place of others
(Junsu opened with 216 times)
Got up to 216 times.
Followed by Zhuojie, who kept up the great form
(Zhuojie followed up, total reached 342 times in the first 2 minutes)
342 times without even looking tired.
But the other eight friends could only jump a little each.
So in the last three minutes they had to speed up.
And they finally completed the mission.
Next Station, Station 2
The ten boys must take turns dragging the tire back and forth
Ten rounds, within five minutes
Coach: Okay kids, right now
Coach: We’re at Station 2
Coach: Or mission two that we must do
Coach: This Station is called “Tire Drag 5 Minutes”
Coach: But what makes it harder is
Coach: Nong Tiger will be sitting on the tire
(Tiger Roiliem Phra Ajarn Chai Napak Muaythai Gym)
Coach: It’s not an easy task
Coach: And if everyone finishes within five minutes
Coach: That means the mission is a success
Coach: Can you all do it?
Everyone: Yes!
Coach: Over there, two pairs. This side, three pairs
Coach: This one’s three pairs
Coach: This is the first pair
Coach: One, two, let’s go, go
(Round 1: Zhuojie - Dokyun)
(Round 1 success!!)
Talay: Go, go, go
Coach: Go, go, go
(Round 2: Porsche - Jawoon)
Talay: Go, go, go
(Round 2 success!!)
Coach: Switch the tire, quickly
Coach: Go, go, go
(Round 3: Intouch - Third)
Coach: Faster, faster, faster
Talay: Reach this line
(Round 3 success!!)
Talay: Spin spin spin
Coach: Then the mission will be complete, hurry
Zhuojie: Just one minute
Porsche: Hurry up
(Round 4: F4 - Talay)
Porsche: Come on, come on, come on
(Round 4 success!!)
Coach: Not yet, not yet
(Waiting for Tiger too)
Coach: Last round now, quick
(Round 5: Junlan - Junsu)
(Round 5 success!!)
Halfway done, they made good time.
Second half starting, but Zhuojie doesn’t look too good.
Zhuojie: Actually, the amount of exercise
wasn’t as tiring as regular training.
Zhuojie: But since it was my first time doing this.
Zhuojie: And I really gave it my all.
Zhuojie: That’s why I’m so tired.
Coach: For tire dragging, I think it’s heavy.
Coach: Because, first,
Coach: Even boxers who drag tires
Coach: Without anyone sitting
(Round 6: Zhuojie - Dokyun)
Coach: If we run with just the tire
Coach: It’s already exhausting and tiring.
(Round 6: Zhuojie - Dokyun)
Coach: But here, there’s also someone sitting.
Coach: The rider already weighs 60 kilos.
Coach: And with the tire too
I think it’s really heavy for normal people
(Round 6 success!!)
Dokyun: Go, go, go
Dokyun: Straight ahead, straight ahead
(Round 7: Porsche - Jawoon)
(Porsche slipped!!)
(Round 7 success!!)
Porsche: Go, go, go
(Round 8: Intouch - Third)
(Round 8 success!!)
Coach: Go there and come back, hurry
Two rounds left
Talay: F4
(Round 9: Talay - F4)
Talay: Let’s go
(Draggers 1)
(Round 9: Talay - F4)
(Passengers 1, 2)
(Round 9 success!!)
Coach: One more round, one more
Coach: Last round, everyone, hurry
Talay: Last round
(Last round!!)
Coach: Last round, quick
(Hey! Hey!)
(Junlan teasing the kid~)
Junsu: No, I can’t do this one
(Last round: Junlan - Junsu)
Coach: Okay
(Round 10 success!!)
The boys finished 10 tire drags in just 4 minutes
It was a mission that brought smiles and laughter
to them all
Coach: For today’s second mission
all the kids succeeded
Coach: But it’s not over yet
Let’s move on to the next mission
Coach: Come on, let’s go
(Station 3: Everyone must take turns kicking the punching bag
Altogether, 500 kicks within 15 minutes
After such a tough day
will the boys have any energy left?
Coach: The last mission for today is
(Station 3: Punching Bag Kicks)
(500 kicks on the punching bag in 15 minutes.)
Coach: The last mission for today is
(Station 3: Punching Bag Kicks)
(500 kicks on the punching bag in 15 minutes.)
Coach: The ten boys must work together to kick
or take turns kicking the punching bag
(Station 3: Punching Bag Kicks)
(500 kicks on the punching bag in 15 minutes.)
Coach: 500 kicks within 15 minutes
(Station 3: Punching Bag Kicks)
(500 kicks on the punching bag in 15 minutes.)
Coach: If the kids manage 500 kicks
Coach: Within 15 minutes
Coach: The mission is complete.
Porsche: Okay
Coach: Go, fight!
Talay: Last mission
Junsu: Got it
Everyone: Got it
Dokyun: Can we do it?
Everyone: Yes!
Coach: Not yet, we’ll demonstrate first.
Coach: But it won’t be me who demonstrates.
Zhuojie: What does that mean?
Talay: Demonstration
Junsu: Demonstration?
Coach: Come here
(Napak Niamprayoon, beautiful female boxer)
Coach: I’ll have Niam or Napak show how to kick.
Coach: How to kick so it counts
and which kicks don’t count
Coach: First, demonstration of scoring kicks
Coach: Kick
Coach: One, your foot must land on the ground
Coach: Again
Coach: One, two, three, four, five
(Strong sound)
(Perfect hits)
Coach: Okay
(Amazing)
Coach: Only like this will I count the points
Coach: Got it?
Junsu: Got it
Porsche: Okay
Coach: Are you ready for today’s last mission?
Porsche: Shall we?
Everyone: Yes!
Talay: Let’s go!
Dokyun: Who’s starting?
Coach: Time ready
Coach: One, two, go
(The 1st person, Jawoon)
Coach: One, two, three, four, five
Coach: Six, seven, eight, nine, ten
(Foot already hurting)
(10 times)
(Jawoon kicked 10 times.)
Coach: You, kick fast
(The 2nd person, Zhuojie)
Talay: Watch your toes
(30 times)
Talay: Keep kicking
Talay: You can do it
(I’m cheering for you.)
(47 times)
(Zhuojie kicked 37 times.)
(The 3rd person, Dokyun)
(60 times)
(70 times)
(Kicking a lot)
(90 times)
(97 times)
(Dokyun kicked 50 times.)
(The 4th person, Talay)
(More painful than expected)
(100 times)
(Don’t slack off)
(120 times)
(Starting to wear out)
(135 times)
(Talay kicked 38 times.)
(The 5th person, Porsche)
(160 times)
(Dokyun is bleeding.)
Dokyun and Zhuojie got injured from kicking the punching bag.
(Zhuojie too)
Dokyun and Zhuojie got injured
from kicking the punching bag.
(Porsche fights hard.)
(180 times)
This mission’s difficulty is not about the kicks.
(184 times)
(Porsche kicked 49 times.)
Only about making it in time.
(The 6th person, F4)
But he has to fight against the fatigue that’s built up all day.
(200 times)
(Keep fighting, boss)
(Can I handle this?)
(217 times)
(F4 kicked 33 times.)
(The 7th person, Third)
(Seems like he can’t go on.)
(238 times)
(Third kicked 21 times.)
(The 8th person, Intouch)
Intouch kicks hard and strong, leaving his friends stunned.
Could he be the village’s hope?
(260 times)
(Kick, don’t stop)
(280 times)
(Out of energy)
Zhuojie: How many now?
Zhuojie: Keep going, keep going
(300 times)
(Intouch kicked 62 times.)
(Now it’s stressful.)
(The 9th person, Junlan)
(Intouch is bleeding.)
(No one has energy left.)
Because the foreign actors
are still unfamiliar with Muay Thai.
(Junlan isn’t good at this style.)
Because the foreign actors
are still unfamiliar with Muay Thai.
(Junlan isn’t good at this style.)
They are using the wrong way to kick the punching bag.
That could lead to injuries.
(Correct kicking technique)
And this is the correct kicking technique.
(350 times)
(356 times)
(Junlan kicked 56 times.)
(The 10th person, Junsu)
(He even cried out.)
Coach: Repeatedly kicking the sack 500 times.
That’s really tough, 500 times.
Coach: I saw them kick the sack again and again.
Until the soles of their feet were scraped raw.
Coach: But they still came back to kick again.
Coach: If someone doesn’t truly love it or want it,
Coach: I don’t think they could keep going
Coach: The boys’ feet are all scraped.
But they still came back to keep kicking.
Coach: They enjoy it like they’re challenging themselves.
Trying something new.
(Can we really handle this?)
(371 times)
(Junsu kicked 15 times.)
(Zhuojie, round 2)
(Should I switch sides?)
(Let’s try the left side.)
(400 times)
(Zhuojie kicked another 29 times.)
(Jawoon, round 2)
Zhuojie: Actually, the most important thing on the field
is not your ability.
Zhuojie: But your attitude towards what you do.
Zhuojie: Every activity, I put in serious effort
Zhuojie: Challenging my own ultimate limits
Zhuojie: Even if it costs sweat or blood
Zhuojie: I will still try to succeed
Zhuojie: And make it the best I can
Zhuojie: That’s basically my mindset
(Dokyun, round 2)
(F4 treating Intouch’s wound)
(470 times)
Porsche: Doesn’t look good anymore.
(“He doesn’t look good anymore”)
Talay: Yes, yes.
Talay: It’s okay, you can rest first.
Talay: Wounds on both sides.
(482 times)
(Only 18 times left)
Zhuojie: Very well done
(Last 10 times)
Zhuojie: Very well done, Talay
Zhuojie: Go for it
Coach: 500 complete
(500 times, success!!)
Coach: Okay everyone
Coach: Everyone, today the kids have completed Station 3.
Coach: Today everyone has smoothly completed all 3 Stations.
(Completed all 3 Stations)
Talay: Is today over?
Zhuojie: Dokyun, okay
Coach: This is the reward for the kids
who completed today’s mission.
Everyone: Thank you
The reward today is
(Reward: 4 puzzle pieces, 4,000 baht cash)
4 puzzle pieces and 4,000 baht cash.
Together with the previous ones, 13,000 baht
Now in total, the boys have 17,000 baht saved.
(Saved amount: 17,000 baht)
Talay: Can I have 2,500 baht?
(Stretching after exercise)
Coach: Stretch your legs.
Coach: First pose, press your hands on your feet
Coach: This is the first pose
Coach: Then switch sides
Coach: Switch sides
Coach: After switching, next is...
Talay: A little more
(Ouchhhhh)
Zhuojie: This is a front muscle stretch
Zhuojie: Relax
(My turn for payback)
(Enough, I give up)
Zhuojie: Zhuojie is great.
(My waist is breaking)
Jawoon: Zhuojie is not great.
Talay: Not great?
Jawoon: Not great
Zhuojie: You must say “great”.
(Let it break then.)
Talay: Say Zhuojie is very great.
Talay: Happy
Zhuojie: Next
(Trust me! I studied this!)
Zhuojie: Trust me
(Is that right?)
(I’ll get you later, Zhuojie.)
(Just once before we go back.)
Coach: Today we’ve finished all tasks.
Coach: But don’t rush to leave.
Coach: We’ll have a meal together first.
Talay: Eat, eat
Jawoon: Kids, som tum is here
Dokyun: Put it here, here
Dokyun: It’s okay, it’s okay
Junsu: Let’s dig in, eat, eat
Dokyun: Let’s go, let’s eat
Jawoon: What’s this dish?
Junlan: Delicious, delicious
Coach: This is beef.
Talay: This is beef.
Jawoon: Muay Thai, Muay Thai
Jawoon: Eat big bites, okay, okay
Jawoon: So delicious
Porsche: Delicious
Junlan: Good, good
Coach: There’s more sticky rice with pork
Talay: This one’s the hungriest
Porsche: So tasty
Talay: This is from inside cow dung
Porsche: Don’t tell yet, say later
Talay: Let him find out himself
Talay: Eat soft
Coach: Kids, today I’ll pick the best athlete
Coach: But actually, everyone is good
Coach: But I’ll pick the 5 best today
Porsche: Coach said we played as a team today
Porsche: But he’ll pick the top 5
Coach: First place
(MVP 1: Junsu)
Junsu: Honestly, no matter when
being recognized
Junsu: It feels really good
Junsu: Especially in exercise
where I don’t want to lose
Junsu: Because I’m very confident in this
Junsu: I thought I must win
Junsu: When the results came out good
Junsu: I felt so grateful
Coach: Second place
(MVP 2: Talay)
Talay: Really?
(MVP 3: Zhuojie)
Coach: Third place
Talay: Two left
Coach: Fourth place
(MVP 4: Jawoon)
Coach: Fifth place
(MVP 5: Third)
Coach: These 5 I chose, when you return home
Coach: There will be a surprise, but I don’t know what.
Coach: You’ll find out at home.
Talay: Thank you
Everyone: Thank you
Coach: You’ll find out at home
Dokyun: What does that mean?
Porsche: There’ll be a surprise at home
Porsche: For the 5
Talay: For us 5
Junsu: Yes, today I didn’t feel like it was filming
Junsu: Honestly, it felt more like playing
Dokyun: Normally when I exercise
I go to the gym alone
Dokyun: But doing activities with friends like this
Dokyun: Makes exercise feel better
Junsu: First of all
Junsu: Because I did what I’m most confident in
Junsu: I felt no pressure
Junsu: And then...
Junsu: Actually, it’s not just today
Junsu: Every time I finish a mission and go home
Junsu: What I feel is
Junsu: Like memories I’ll never forget
Junsu: All of it
Junsu: Not just today
Junsu: Because from the journey, from the start until now
Junsu: It feels like a trip
Junsu: Like I’ll never forget in my life
Junsu: Especially today, I’ll never forget it
Junsu: Feels like I can’t forget it, today
Zhuojie: Actually, the person who impressed me the most was Intouch
Zhuojie: Even though in the end he didn’t go to the spa
Zhuojie: But everyone saw...
Zhuojie: Whether it was his physique
Zhuojie: When he was kicking the punching bag
Zhuojie: And when he was skipping rope
Zhuojie: Normally, he’s very gentle and doesn’t talk much
Zhuojie: He’s very introverted
Zhuojie: But when he was on the field
he really shocked me
Zhuojie: I never said it before
but he really made me feel such a difference
Everyone: Muay Thai! Yay yay
Junsu: What do you say everyone, what do you say
Talay: What is it
Talay: It’s the letter “B”
Junsu: The letter “B”
Junsu: How many, two two two
F4: And ta-daaa
Dokyun: How many left
Junlan: Four
Junsu: Either three or four
Talay: Where is it
Porsche: It’s like a skywalk
Zhuojie: I know this place!
Talay: Where
Zhuojie: Jawoon, I’ll tell you
Junsu: Zhangjiajie, Zhangjiajie
Junlan: It’s not Zhangjiajie anymore
Junlan: There’s a “B” in front
Junsu: Isn’t it?
Talay: Bali?
Junlan: Zhangjiajie is the letter “J”
Zhuojie: At first, because I didn’t pick Dokyun
Zhuojie: This thought came up
Zhuojie: Because whatever he did today, he did it well
Zhuojie: But maybe the coach’s memory isn’t great
Zhuojie: So maybe he chose wrong
Zhuojie: I feel like he did well in every aspect
Zhuojie: And the key point is
Zhuojie: I feel really happy being with him
Zhuojie: And he even spent his own money
just to buy me a blanket
Zhuojie: That really touched me, I’ll never forget it
Zhuojie: From now on, if there’s something good, I’ll think of him first
Zhuojie: I feel like he’s been so good to me
Zhuojie: I can feel his sincerity
Zhuojie: And I’ll be sincere with him too
Even though no one knows what tonight’s special prize is
Zhuojie already decided to give it to Dokyun
So he asked Jawoon to help translate into Korean
But it seemed Jawoon wasn’t too cooperative
Junlan: I think this is the name of a place
Junlan: The name of somewhere
Porsche: Maybe it’s the name of a place
Zhuojie: Boys Lost in Thailand
Zhuojie: It’s the “Boys Lost in Thailand” logo
Junlan: It’s the sea, everyone
Jawoon: Look over there
Masseuse: Hello boys
Everyone: Hello
Masseuse: I’d like to invite the five winners of the special prize
Masseuse: Please come this way
Junlan: Massage?
F4: Massage for the five prize winners
Third: Hello
F4: Who else
Masseuse: This way please
Talay: The five people who won the special prize
Junsu: Special prize
Junsu: Sit here, right?
Talay: Right
Zhuojie: Dokyun, Dokyun, come quick
Jawoon: Junsu
Zhuojie: Can you...
Jawoon: This is...
F4: Thai massage
Jawoon: Our prize, right?
Talay: The prize, yes
Junsu: Let’s lie down there, and then...
Talay: Today I don’t want a massage
Talay: I’ll give mine up...
Talay: to Dokyun
Junlan: Agree, agree
Dokyun: So kind!
Junsu: Agree, agree, Dokyun!
Dokyun: Ah, I...
Dokyun: I’m really touched
Dokyun: That Talay gave me his massage
Dokyun: Talay, thank you
Dokyun: So kind!
Junsu: Agree, agree, Dokyun!
Zhuojie: I can say that Talay and I think the same
Zhuojie: Our hearts are in sync
Zhuojie: Thank you, Talay
Junsu: This is a real massage, right?
Talay: Do you want to go swimming?
(Dokyun liked this.)
Junsu: It’s so...
(So good)
Jawoon: So good!
Dokyun: The massage is really great
Talay: We can just massage each other
(We can just massage each other.)
Junsu: Good good good
Intouch: Very relaxing
Talay: Same here
Junlan: Feels good
Porsche: No thanks
F4: Just kidding
(Is my neck going to break?)
(Selfie of the ones without massage)
(Lucky draw)
Jawoon: Lucky draw!
Talay: Lucky draw?
Zhuojie: Jawoon, quiet
F4: I want a massage.
Jawoon: “Good night,” okay?
Junsu: Hey
Junsu: What are you doing, Talay?
Talay: Nothing
Junsu: Nothing?
Junlan: Bye everyone
Everyone: Bye bye
Please draw lots to pick today’s missions
Dokyun: You, not me
Junlan: Jeremy
Zhuojie: One, two, three
Extreme Sports at Fountain Tree Resort
and Atlantis Adventure World Khaoyai
Everyone: Extreme sports!
Jawoon: Let’s go!
Everyone: Adventure! Adventure!
Junlan: Orange one.
Junsu: Let’s go!
Talay: The real deal
Talay: Everyone ready?
Everyone: Ready!
(The BOYS LOST gang hits the field!!)
Talay: Careful not to hurt your armpits, everyone
Want a taste? Want a taste?
Jawoon: A bit spicy
A bit spicy
Jawoon: So delicious
Jawoon: It's raining.
Jawoon: I’m shocked.
Dokyun: More?!
Jawoon: Shocked
Jawoon: So delicious it’s shocking