(You must go out and complete missions)
(to earn money and retrieve puzzle pieces.)
(Location: Khao Yai Farm Village)
To earn money and retrieve puzzle pieces.
(Very hard)
Junlan: Very hard.
(Collect ingredients from various stations within the time limit
to cook dinner according to the assigned menu.)
Let’s go!
But not everyone will be working today.
Today we got the puzzle pieces.
The six dishes we must cook today,
(Green Curry / Sour Curry with Shrimp)
Porsche: We have two curries.
(Stir-fried Basil / Stir-fried Morning Glory)
Porsche: Two stir-fries.
(Fried Egg / Omelet)
Porsche: And two egg dishes.
(Tom Yum Kung?)
Dokyun: Tom Yum Kung?
F4: No, this is sour curry.
Porsche: It’s hot.
Zhuojie: If you need it, I can cook anything.
Third: So chaotic.
(I’m not comfortable with everyone.)
Talay: I’m not comfortable with everyone.
Talay: The one person in this project like that is Intouch.
(Silence...)
Junlan: He shuts himself off.
(So good!)
Jawoon: So good.
Talay: It’s only the third day.
Junlan: Yeah, but you know what, I...
Junlan: I really look forward to spending more time
with you from now on.
Talay: Me too.
(07:00 AM)
(07:30 AM)
(08:00 AM)
Zhuojie: Morninggg~
Intouch: Good morning.
F4: New mission!
Zhuojie: I’m so tired.
Good morning.
Everyone: Good morning.
Your mission is to save enough money
to experience the beauty of Thailand together.
Your goal is 30,000 baht.
How much money do you have today?
Junsu: How much do we have?
Dokyun: How much do we have now?
Intouch: 13,000 baht.
Third: 40 baht too?
Intouch: 13,040 baht.
(Remaining balance: 13,040 baht)
What is your favorite Thai fruit?
Zhuojie: Mango.
Talay: Mango.
Junlan: Watermelon.
Zhuojie: Mango.
(Watermon?)
Junlan: Watermelon.
Zhuojie: Watermelon.
Zhuojie: Durian.
Porsche: Durian.
Junlan: Durian?
Dokyun: Watermelon.
Let’s see if you’ll get to work
in a fruit orchard that you like.
Pick one card.
It will be the fruit farm where you’ll work today.
Junsu: Who’ll pick?
Zhuojie: Me. I’ll pick.
Zhuojie: You?
Zhuojie: Red one?
Zhuojie: Red.
Junlan: Red.
Zhuojie: Yellow.
Junlan: Blue! Pick blue.
Junsu: Pink, pink, pink!
Everyone: Blue! Pink! Green!
(No cheating!)
Don’t cheat.
Pick only one card.
Zhuojie: Not this one.
Junlan: This one’s pink.
Zhuojie: Who picked this?
Junsu: Pink, pink!
Zhuojie: Give it to me.
Jawoon: Hurry up!
Zhuojie: It’s a place name, not a person.
Junlan: I don’t understand.
Third: Baan Mak...
(Home)
(Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm)
Intouch & F4: Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm.
Jawoon: Mango?
F4: Mak Muang.
Everyone: Mak Muang!
Porsche: Mak Muang isn’t mango.
Talay: It’s not mango.
Junsu: What is it?
Junlan: Mak Muang.
Your mission is to work at the mango farm.
(Working at the mango farm.)
Dokyun: Mango? Mango, right?
If you’re ready, go prepare.
F4: Everyone’s going?
(Yes, everyone goes!)
Talay: Everyone’s going.
Porsche: It’s like...
Porsche: You use similar words
that convey similar meanings.
Yes.
Today, all of you will go work at the mango farm.
Jawoon: Everyone?
Third: Everyone?
Junlan: Wait, wait.
Junsu: Let’s go.
Junlan: No, no, no!
Junlan: Everyone, I want to swim.
Today, all 10 of you must work.
No one gets a break.
F4: No breaks.
Junsu: No breaks.
Junsu: Everyone’s going.
Junlan: I’ll clean the house.
(Junsu the diplomat)
Junsu: He wants to stay and clean.
Junlan: Yeah, someone has to do it.
Junsu: Not allowed?
Dokyun: Not allowed.
Junsu: Not allowed!
Junsu: Let’s go do the mission.
Porsche: Let’s earn money.
Talay: Change clothes.
Junlan: Change clothes?
Talay: Yeah, let’s go change.
Zhuojie: Okay.
Zhuojie: Let’s go!
Everyone: Let’s go!
Junlan: Hot.
Porsche: Where are my shoes?
Junlan: Porsche, Porsche!
F4: Let’s go!
Junlan: Let’s go.
Junlan: We’re heading to the mango farm...
Jawoon: Can we open the box?
We’re going to the mango farm. Let’s go!
Dokyun: We’ve never been to a place like this, right?
Junsu: Tell us about the place
you visited and liked the most.
Intouch: Share about a place you visited and liked.
Junsu: That you visited and liked the most.
Intouch: Who’s first?
Junsu: Talay.
Talay: Me?
Junsu: Yes, you go first.
Junlan: Who’s first?
Porsche: You.
F4: You.
Junlan: Me? Let Zhuojie go first.
Zhuojie: No, I’m asleep.
Junlan: You go first.
Third: There’s more.
Third: There’s something below.
Talay: Below.
Talay: There’s more!
Junsu: The other question is...
Third: Yes?
(Choose one member of Boys Lost,
that you want to take on a trip.)
(Who would you pick, and why?)
Junsu: Pick someone. Why them?
Talay: Choose your favorite place.
Talay: Then pick someone from Boys Lost you’d want to go on a trip with.
Talay: And explain why.
Junlan: Last year I went to Phuket.
(Junlan: Phuket)
The view was so beautiful.
Phuket
was very memorable for me.
Intouch: Phuket
Junsu: Phuket
Talay: Phuket
Intouch: I love Phuket because
Intouch: the sea is so clear.
Talay: The sea is super clear.
Intouch: And you can dive underwater
Intouch: and see fish and everything below.
Talay: Have you guys heard of Chiang Khan?
(Talay: Chiang Khan)
Third & Jawoon: Chiang Khan?
Talay: When I went to Chiang Khan,
Talay: there weren’t many hotels.
Talay: So I had to stay in a homestay.
(Talay: Chiang Khan)
Talay: So I had to stay at a religious homestay.
Talay: They woke us up
Talay: to chant prayers in the morning.
(Talay: Chiang Khan)
Talay: We went to the temple with them.
Talay: And I learned how to make coffee.
Jawoon: Chiang Mai
Everyone: Chiang Mai
Jawoon: That was the first time I saw
Jawoon: a real white tiger.
(Jawoon: Chiang Mai)
Jawoon: A real white tiger
Talay: Oh, a white tiger!
Jawoon: Yes, a white tiger.
Talay: Did you touch it?
Jawoon: Yes, I did.
(Jawoon: Chiang Mai)
Jawoon: Yes, I touched it.
Jawoon: We talked a lot — I communicated with the tiger.
Talay: You talked to a tiger?
Jawoon: I could communicate with the tiger.
Talay: You spoke with the tiger?
Talay: In what language?
Jawoon: Sometimes I can talk to animals — just using feelings.
Jawoon: We communicated through a kind of feeling.
Talay: He can talk to animals!
Jawoon: They have great places for activities.
Jawoon: And...
Jawoon: There’s lots of delicious food.
Talay: Chiang Mai
Jawoon: Chiang Mai
Junsu: I like
Junsu: Koh Samui.
Everyone: Koh Samui
Jawoon: Koh Samui in Thailand.
Junsu: I went last month.
Junsu: It was—
Talay: Was it fun?
Junsu: Yes, it was fun and relaxing.
Third: My favorite trip was in high school.
(Third: Ayutthaya)
Jawoon: High school?
Third: When I was in high school.
Third: Yeah, because I went with friends.
Third: Like a trip to the old temples of Ayutthaya.
(Third: Ayutthaya)
Third: Visiting the ancient temples in Ayutthaya.
Talay: Ayutthaya, really?
(Third: Ayutthaya)
Third: Yes, Ayutthaya.
Third: Yes.
Third: I like history, so I went there.
Jawoon: Let’s answer the second question in ten minutes.
Junsu: Okay, ten minutes from now sounds good.
Jawoon: In ten minutes.
Talay: Members.
Talay: Pick one member.
Talay: And say why.
Junsu: I don’t want to choose just one.
Junsu: Can I pick two?
Talay: Okay.
Junsu: I’ll pick the two Chinese members.
Talay: Two Chinese members.
Junsu: Jawoon and Zhuojie.
Junsu: We don’t have a language barrier.
Junsu: So it’s easy to communicate.
Junsu: Plus we’re all the same age.
Third: I choose Junsu.
Third: Ayutthaya.
Junsu: Ayutthaya.
Third: I feel like he likes things that are local,
traditional culture, things like that.
Junsu: I like that.
Third: So like...
Junsu: After this show, take me there, okay?
Third: Okay, for sure!
Talay: It’s not far from Bangkok.
Third: It’s very close — I think he’ll be impressed.
Intouch: I choose Junsu.
Intouch: Because we have the same vibes and style.
Junsu: Yeah.
Intouch: And we both love fitness and working out.
Junsu: That’s right.
Jawoon: I pick Porsche.
Jawoon & Junsu: Porsche!
Junsu: Why?
Jawoon: Because we understand each other.
His English is really good.
Jawoon: And he takes care of me and gives good advice.
Jawoon: He really cares — he always asks me:
Jawoon: “Jawoon, are you hungry?”
Jawoon: “Jawoon, are you tired?”
Dokyun: Then I’ll pick...
Dokyun: Jeremy.
Jawoon: Jeremy.
Dokyun: Because Jeremy brings the energy every day.
Jawoon: Energy!
Dokyun: He’s truly one of a kind.
Zhuojie: You, just you.
Zhuojie: Only you.
Intouch: Shall we go this way, everyone? Let’s check.
Talay: It’s to the right.
Third: Where are we now?
Junsu: Let’s check the map.
Junsu: Okay.
(Traveling from The Horizon Khaoyai to Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm)
Junsu: But I can’t read Thai.
Junsu: But it seems like we’re...
Third: Keep going straight.
Talay: Go straight all the way.
Intouch: Let’s go, let’s go.
Junsu: So where are we now?
Talay: Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm.
Junsu: Mango.
Junsu: It’s right there.
Jawoon: Ma-ma-mango~
Talay: That’s Moo Deng (red pork).
Third: Moo Deng!
Jawoon: Moo Deng? Mango, mango!
Junsu: Let’s go party!
Dokyun: Mango
Junlan: Beautiful. So beautiful.
Zhuojie: Really beautiful.
Jawoon: So beautiful.
(Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm)
Porsche: Today, say it again
Porsche: Yes!
Porsche: Today, today we earn money.
Porsche: This is a mango tree.
Jawoon: Is this a mango tree?
Porsche: Yes.
Jawoon: This is a mango tree?
F4: Let’s take a photo.
Porsche: I don’t know.
Talay: There! A mango tree.
Zhuojie: Be careful, Junsu!
Jawoon: One, two, three!
Zhuojie: One, two, zero — jump!
F4: One, two, three!
Nan: Hello!
Everyone: Hello!
(Nan, owner of “Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm”)
Nan: Welcome to all the Boys Lost in Thailand members!
Nan: Are you all ready to help me work at the orchard today
Talay: Is everyone ready?
Everyone: Ready
Nan: Then I’ll explain
Nan: I’ll demonstrate how to harvest mangoes for everyone
Nan: What we’re seeing here are mangoes that are ready to be harvested
Porsche: What we’re seeing here are ready to...
Talay: Harvested
Porsche: Yes, harvested
Nan: So today I’ve prepared tools for everyone
Nan: We’ve got baskets, scissors, and gloves
Nan: So your hands won’t get hurt
Nan: Harvesting mangoes is actually really easy
Nan: You can gently hold the mango
Nan: Because it’s a fruit with very thin skin
Porsche: You have to be gentle
Nan: This is how you harvest them
Nan: You can cut right at the mango’s stem like this
Nan: Cut it a bit longer like this
Nan: Just like this
Zhuojie: Very good
(Of course, she’s the orchard owner.)
Nan: Great job. Okay
Junlan: Baby, baby
Porsche: Gently
Talay: Gently
Junlan: Baby
Junlan: Like a baby
Nan: So, who wants to volunteer to try harvesting?
Talay: Volunteer to harvest?
Talay: Seven, you wanna go first?
Junsu: Seven, you go ahead
Talay: Yeah, you go ahead
Zhuojie: I’ll try, I can do it
F4 & Junlan: You got this!
Junlan: What’s this?
Porsche: Jeremy
Zhuojie: Over here, over here
Porsche: Where are you?
Zhuojie: I’m right here
F4: Cut one and give it to me
Talay: That’s how to do it
Junlan: Hot
F4: Hot
Zhuojie: Did I do it?
Junsu: Yes, yes
Junsu: What are you doing?
F4: I'm here.
Zhuojie: They’re fighting over them.
F4: The basket’s full.
Junlan: No, no, no
Junsu: I want three.
Intouch: It’s heavy too
Zhuojie: Big ones, where are the big ones?
Junlan: No, no way
Junlan: No way
Third: Was it fun?
Jawoon: It was fun.
Third: A lot?
Jawoon: A lot
Zhuojie: We did it together?
Zhuojie: Final team
Junlan: Very beautiful
Nan: Great job, everyone
Nan: You harvested a lot
Nan: If you’re this good, you might have to help me harvest more often
Nan: But today, no one wins or loses
Nan: Everyone who helped me pick mangoes today
Nan: Will receive 100 baht each
(100 baht)
Nan: So let’s hand out the money now
Porsche: Everyone will get 100 baht
Talay: Thank you
Talay: 100 baht, 100 baht
Nan: Yes, 100 baht
Porsche: Is there a bonus?
F4 & Junlan: Thank you
Zhuojie: Hungry
Nan: Next, I’ll take everyone to learn
Nan: How to process the mangoes we picked
Nan: We’ll turn them into mango desserts
Nan: If you’re ready, let’s go
Everyone: Thank you
Zhuojie: It’s so hot! Where’s the bathroom?
Zhuojie: Bathroom
Zhuojie: Bathroom, please
Talay: Going in the water?
Porsche: Bathroom
Junsu: You want to go to the bathroom?
Zhuojie: Bathroom
Dokyun: That way
Zhuojie: Where’s the bathroom?
Porsche: Now we’ll learn how to process them
Porsche: What kind of desserts or snacks
Porsche: we can make from mangoes.
Porsche: The basket is full
Zhuojie: No way, you have to call me “Big Bro” first
Nan: Next, everyone, we’re going to process the mangoes
Nan: Into mango desserts
Nan: Today we’ll make three items
Nan: One group will make mango sticky rice
(Task division: Mango Sticky Rice Team)
Nan: One group will make mango sticky rice.
(Task division: Mango Sticky Rice / Mango Smoothie Team)
Nan: Another group will make mango smoothies.
Nan: And another group will be servers and customer service.
(Task division: Mango Sticky Rice / Mango Smoothie / Service Team)
Nan: So we’ll split into 3 teams.
Nan: Please group yourselves.
Nan: If you’re ready, take your positions.
Nan: This way, the first station is the mango smoothie.
(Mango Smoothie)
Nan: And in that kitchen over there, that room
(Mango Sticky Rice)
Nan: That’s where we’ll make mango sticky rice
Porsche: Mango sticky rice over that way
Nan: The serving and customer service team
Nan: Will be at the front counter
(Customer Service)
Porsche: Ohh, okay
Nan: Take your positions
Learning time before the store opens
Nan: This side will be making mango smoothies
Nan: One mango per smoothie
Nan: We’ll use a mix of fresh and frozen mangoes
Nan: Cut the mangoes like this
Junlan: Two slices
F4: Two slices
Nan: Yes, two slices. Two, three, okay
Junlan: One, two, three
Nan: Then next—
Third: Why can’t we just use frozen mangoes directly?
Nan: If we only use room-temperature mangoes
Nan: It’ll get too watery when blended with ice
Nan: This frozen one helps it thicken
Junsu: Do we add sugar?
Jawoon: Do we add syrup?
Nan: We add syrup too
Nan: Okay, okay
Nan: You don’t need to heap the ice so high
Third: Like this?
Nan: That’s about right
F4: Is it good?
F4: Let’s go!
Junlan & F4: It looks beautiful
F4 & Junlan: It looks beautiful
Jawoon: It looks beautiful
Junsu: Delicious. Really delicious
Talay: Cream cheese, passionfruit
Junlan: I want to make this one
Nan: Bring a spoon and fork
(So hungry)
Jawoon: I’m hungry
Jawoon: Can I eat this?
Junlan: No
Junlan: Sweet thief
Junlan: Not a sweet thief
Junlan: So good
Junsu: I made it
Junlan: Taste it
Junsu: I made it, try it
Porsche: Thank you
Junsu: It’s a mission.
Junlan: Mission
Porsche: The mission is to create a menu using processed mango
and serve 20 dishes within 1 hour.
Porsche: If the mission succeeds, you’ll get cash and 4 puzzle pieces.
(4 puzzle pieces)
Porsche: Okay.
Porsche: Anyone want to go somewhere?
Nan: If everyone understands, please put on your baking gloves.
Nan: Take off your sunglasses and put on your aprons, everyone.
Nan: If everyone understands that,
Nan: Please head to your stations.
Porsche: Everyone, take off your sunglasses and put on aprons.
Porsche: And if you’re cooking, wear gloves too.
Everyone: Okay!
Porsche: Is everyone ready? Let’s go!
Jawoon: Got it.
Junsu: Go! One, two, three!
Zhuojie: Nice to...
Jawoon: ...meet you.
Porsche: Welcome!
Zhuojie: Welcome!
Porsche: Yes, very good.
Porsche: Are you guys ready?
Jawoon: Like this, and like this.
Porsche: Are you ready?
Talay: And then mango...
Porsche: Let’s open the shop.
Talay: Let’s open the shop.
Porsche: The shop is now open, everyone.
Zhuojie: Everyone, listen up!
Everyone: Mango!
Zhuojie: One, two, three!
Zhuojie: Let’s go!
Everyone: Open the shop!
F4: Go, go, let’s go!
Dokyun: Mango!
Talay: Welcome!
Porsche: You’re here already?
Porsche: Zhuojie, go ahead.
Dokyun: Hello!
Zhuojie: Hello!
Zhuojie: How many? Two?
Dokyun: Welcome.
Talay: Hello, welcome!
Porsche: Hello, welcome!
(Countdown begins: 1 hour)
Talay: Just a moment, please.
Zhuojie: All seats are okay,
but outside might be a bit hot.
Zhuojie: Are you guys Chinese?
Junsu: Table 2?
Junsu: Where’s table 2?
Porsche: Table 2 is over here.
Junsu: One, two, three, right?
Porsche: Yes, yes, yes!
Everyone: Careful!
Intouch: Two mango smoothies.
Intouch: Okay.
Talay: Front table.
Talay: Two servings of mango sticky rice.
Porsche: We have mango sticky rice and mango smoothies.
Talay: China!
Talay: Come here quick.
Zhuojie: Welcome, welcome!
Zhuojie: The view’s nice outside.
(Dish 1 is here!)
Dokyun: Okay!
Zhuojie: It’s me.
Talay: Table M2 and M3.
(Dish 5)
Customer: Thank you!
Zhuojie: Enjoy your meal!
Third: How many do we have now?
Intouch: Two served so far.
(30 minutes left)
Intouch: Everyone’s rushing a lot.
Intouch: Because customers came in really fast.
Intouch: So we had to help each other and move fast.
Intouch: Making smoothies requires—
Intouch: If we do one cup at a time,
Intouch: It won’t be fast enough.
Intouch: So we had to put in four at once.
(Mango x4)
Intouch: Which made the smoothie a bit too sweet for me.
(Sweet x4)
Intouch: It turned out a bit too sweet for me.
Intouch: Because I tasted it.
Intouch: At first, I wondered if
customers would feel that way.
Intouch: But after tasting it at the end,
Intouch: It really was too sweet.
Talay: More customers coming in!
Talay: Hello, welcome!
(The blender is not working.)
Dokyun: Lots of orders coming in!
Zhuojie: Why’s it broken?
Dokyun: It broke?
Zhuojie: Calm down, it’s okay!
Zhuojie: No need to worry!
Third: The power button.
(Yay! It’s working!)
(Dish 11)
Porsche: Did we get the order?
Talay: Yes, all done.
(15 minutes left)
Talay: Ten minutes left, everyone!
(Final 10 minutes)
F4: Stay calm!
F4: Pretty, pretty!
(Sticky rice gang is done – 20 dishes!)
Junlan: Done, done!
Jawoon: Surprise!
Junlan & F4: All done!
Third: Our kitchen must be clean.
Intouch: Got it.
Porsche: How do you feel? Was it hard?
Jawoon: This one was really hard.
Dokyun: Trouble with the smoothie?
Intouch: Junsu said he never made one before.
Intouch: And didn’t know much about mangoes.
Intouch: So I told him it’s not hard.
Intouch: Taught him a bit on how to do it.
Intouch: And he actually did really well.
Junsu: I want to talk with Intouch more after this.
Junsu: We chatted a lot in the car today too.
Junsu: He has deep thoughts.
Junsu: Very mature thinking.
Junsu: And...
Junsu: I think we really get along well.
Junsu: If there’s a chance, I’d like to talk again.
Junsu: The bottom of the cup was a little sticky, so I want to apologize.
Junsu: Can you translate for me?
Talay: My friend wants to say sorry.
Talay: The bottom of the cup might be a bit sticky.
Talay: Thank you.
Porsche: Thanks for coming. Please visit us again!
Zhuojie: Have fun! Bye-bye!
Talay: Closing the shop!
Zhuojie: One, two, three!
Everyone: Mango!
Nan: Great job, mission complete! How was it—did you have fun?
Everyone: It was so fun!
Nan: So fun! How much money did we make today?
Nan: Let’s count!
Everyone: Three, four, five, six!
Everyone: Seven, eight, nine, ten!
Zhuojie: One, two, three, four!
Porsche: Total is 3,000 baht.
(3,000 baht.)
Nan: Okay, three thousand bath. Thank you all.
Nan: So the reward for all your hard work today
Nan: is actually monetary reward.
Nan: You’ll get half of what we earned today.
Porsche: Thank you!
Nan: And I have something to give you too.
Porsche: Puzzle piece
Junlan: Puzzle piece
Dokyun: All sky pieces
Porsche: More sky again
Junlan: Sky pieces
Talay: What?
Porsche: A mountain
Nan: This is your reward for today
Nan: Thank you so much /N Everyone: Thank you
Nan: Thanks so much to all of you today
Nan: Wishing everyone good luck
and a safe trip home.
Everyone: Thank you
Zhuojie: So beautiful
Talay: We can take one
Talay: Anyone want one?
Porsche: Are there extras?
Nan: We have ice cream for everyone
Talay: Free ice cream!
Junlan: Cute!
(So cuuute x4)
Porsche: Should we take two?
Porsche: Can we scan it?
Zhuojie: This one, this one!
Porsche: Thank you
F4: Khao Yai vanilla
Intouch: I’ve gotta come try it too
Talay: Cheers! That side finished theirs already
Zhuojie: One, two, three
(Mission: Khao Yai​ The​ Mango​ House Farm)
Talay: We’re finally home
Zhuojie: So tired
Junlan: We’ve arrived.
Dokyun: Welcome back
Junlan: Everyone!
Talay: Let’s check this out
Junlan: Not me, it wasn’t me guys!
F4: Is this the one, like in Isaan where they have—
F4: or Kanchanaburi where they have— Third: Kanchanaburi
F4: The bridge! That bridge!
Third: Death Railway
Junlan: And what about this one?
Intouch: Everyone, pizza!
Junsu: Did we pay for this?
Junlan: Why do we have pizza to eat?
Zhuojie: Where’s the bathroom?
Zhuojie: Surprise!
Gold Card #2: Food category
You may request one special meal of your choice.
Zhuojie: Something...
Zhuojie: I wanted pizza
Zhuojie: I chose pizza for all my friends
Zhuojie: To eat together
Zhuojie: Okay
Zhuojie: One, two, three—Energy!
Junlan: Jeremy!
Talay: Really?
Junlan: You? You did this?
F4: Jeremy! Jeremy!
Zhuojie: Hold on!
Dokyun: Chinese people don’t trick each other
Zhuojie: No big deal
Junsu: Let’s sit down
Zhuojie: Talay, you said you wanted cola—this one’s yours
Talay: I love you!
Zhuojie: Actually,
Zhuojie: I was going to ask for 30,000 baht
Junlan: He was going to ask for 30,000 baht
Zhuojie: But they wouldn’t give it
Zhuojie: Only food was allowed
Zhuojie: But I wanted pizza and all this
Zhuojie: We’re a team, we’re one family
Junsu: Let’s sit down, sit down
Zhuojie: My comrades
Zhuojie: Let’s dig in!
Intouch: I think he’s really sweet
Intouch: Because I honestly didn’t expect him to do this
Intouch: At first I thought he might ask for a big blanket
Intouch: Or something personal for himself
Intouch: But in the end, he asked for something for everyone
Intouch: It was really touching
Zhuojie: Two days ago I worked during the day
then practiced at night
Zhuojie: so I felt so exhausted
Zhuojie: I just wanted something high-energy
Zhuojie: But I thought—we’re a team
Zhuojie: If I get something, I want them to get it too
Zhuojie: I hope we all enjoyed that moment together
Zhuojie: Whether I could get one thing or ten
Zhuojie: I just wanted everyone to eat together and spend time
Zhuojie: That first night, Talay
Zhuojie: said he wanted cola
Zhuojie: but had to buy it himself
Zhuojie: I remembered, so I asked for it for him
Zhuojie: I hope it made him happy
Zhuojie: and that he’ll remember this time we had
Dokyun: One, two, three—
Everyone: Seventy-seven!
Zhuojie: All friends
Zhuojie: Honestly, it wasn’t tiring
Zhuojie: What made me happy
Zhuojie: wasn’t the sacrifice itself
Zhuojie: but seeing that when I took care of them, they were happy
Zhuojie: Seeing them happy made me feel at peace
Porsche: So who impressed you the most?
F4: I’m impressed by this close friend
Junlan: A close friend
F4: My close friend, who helped carry mango baskets
and ran around the orchard with me
Porsche: He’s thankful to everyone who worked together
Porsche: And he’s especially grateful to his best friend—that’s you
Porsche: You were with him the whole time
Porsche: Carrying baskets around the orchard
Junsu: They stole a lot of mangoes
Junsu: They stole so many
Junlan: No! We didn’t steal a single one!
Porsche: He stole from me too
Junsu: Right?
Junlan: Stole from him
Talay: Junlan stole a bunch of mangoes!
Junlan: No, no, no!
Talay: That’s bad!
Zhuojie: Bad boy!
Junlan: Can I explain myself?
Junlan: Because Junsu stole the mangoes from me
Junsu: What??
Junlan: I didn’t start it—he did!
Junlan: Thief!
Talay: Thief! Thief!
Junsu: He was the thief first!
Dokyun: First of all—
Dokyun: We have different nationalities and languages
Dokyun: But today, we united and worked as one
Dokyun: that was really touching for me
Junsu: Even though we speak different languages and come from different countries—
Junsu: We worked together so well
Junsu: He was impressed by that
Talay: You moved to the smoothie station, right?
Dokyun: That’s right
Junsu: He helped me a lot today
Talay: I’m impressed by Junsu today
Talay: Because when Junlan was stealing a lot of mangoes—
Porsche: He stole mangoes
Talay: He stole a bunch, and then Junsu started too
Talay: But once we told Junsu that Junlan already took a lot—
Talay: Junsu gave them back and even gave us more!
Porsche: He gave us extra!
Junsu: Yeah, yeah!
Talay: I told everyone you stole a lot of our mangoes.
Junlan: Me? No, I didn’t.
Talay: Yes, you did.
Talay: Then Junsu came and stole some too.
Talay: But I told him Junlan already took a bunch.
Junlan: Don’t you want to hear my explanation?
Junlan: He stole from me.
Junsu: No, I—
Junsu: But I gave it back, didn’t I?
Talay: Yes, and he even returned more than he took.
Junlan: Talay, yesterday we had trust.
Talay: Yeah, but you broke it.
Talay: You stole my mangoes.
Junlan: Because you picked the wrong teammate.
Talay: Really? Why?
Junlan: Yess
Junlan: Because he stole my mangoes!
Talay: No, he’s my teammate.
(This guy right here!)
Junsu: “Because you chose the wrong friend...”
Porsche: I’m thankful to everyone
for working together as a team at the café.
Porsche: Even though it was tough,
Porsche: Even though it was exhausting, we did well.
Porsche: So thank you so much, everyone.
Junlan: I feel like it was a learning opportunity.
Junsu: Learning how to steal?
Junsu: We need to protect our stuff.
Junlan: If everyone calls me a thief
for stealing from all of you...
Junlan: You trust me, right?
F4: I do.
Junlan: I have someone who trust me, so it’s fine.
Porsche: So you two are the thieves, right?
Junsu: Thieves, yeah, yeah.
Junlan: No, no, no!
Junlan: I actually really enjoyed working with F4.
Junlan: It’s the first time
we’ve been teammates, right?
F4: That’s right.
Junlan: We picked mangoes together.
Junlan: And tried to protect our mangoes from everyone else.
Junlan: It was really hard.
Junsu: Why’d you do that?
Junlan: Because I had to protect the mangoes.
Junlan: And he had to pick mangoes.
Junlan: So we did great.
Talay: I saw him sitting there with the basket.
Junlan: Because you guys were trying to steal mangoes from me.
Talay: No!
Junlan: All of you!
Zhuojie: I can only speak Chinese.
Zhuojie: I can only speak Chinese, sorry.
Zhuojie: Today, let’s not talk about mangoes.
Junlan: Not going to talk about mangoes.
Zhuojie: What I remember most is when we were inside.
Zhuojie: There were lots of people, and we had to finish the job.
Junlan: What impressed me most
was that we got through that mission together.
Zhuojie: We divided the work for a common goal.
Junlan: Each person had different responsibilities.
Junlan: But all for the same mission.
Zhuojie: It reminded me of a day
Zhuojie: when everyone practiced and did stuff together.
Zhuojie: All for the sake of winning first place.
Junlan: It reminded him of training for a basketball competition at university.
Junlan: And everyone on the team gave their all
for the same goal.
Talay: Teamwork!
Junlan: Yeah, teamwork.
Zhuojie: When you reach your goal, you feel complete.
Junlan: When we completed the mission,
it felt like winning a basketball game.
Zhuojie: Just telling the story for fun.
Junlan: Just sharing for fun.
Zhuojie: I feel like F4...
Zhuojie: There were so many people, and F4 was like...
Zhuojie: And then you were like..
Zhuojie: And then...
Zhuojie: Junsu was like...
Intouch: Actually, today I liked it the most.
Intouch: It was seeing everyone slowly break down their walls.
Intouch: Everyone started talking more and becoming much closer.
Jawoon: Compared to before,
Jawoon: I was always with Porsche.
Jawoon: But today was my first time riding in a different van.
Jawoon: It felt a bit weird, to be honest.
Jawoon: F4 told me so many things.
Jawoon: F4, it’s like when I—
Jawoon: stay like this, he’d say “Jawoon, Jawoon!”
Jawoon: So I wanted to talk more.
Jawoon: Before bed, he recommended music to me.
Jawoon: Like, right before sleep, he’d share songs.
Jawoon: And tell funny stories.
Jawoon: Even though I sing Thai songs really weirdly,
Jawoon: he’d still instantly know which song it was.
Dokyun: Intouch.
Junlan: Grab him! Grab him!
Intouch: I just want everyone to get closer and be able to talk about anything.
Intouch: Because I think we’ll be together for a long time.
Jawoon: Sorry for barging in like a meringkingkong
Jawoon: saranongkongkeng, manongmanangmub,
Jawoon: palongpongpang, nongnangnongnang in your life...
Match the look and walk the runway
with tie-dye made from natural clay dyes.
Third: It’s not very fashionable to be honest.
Intouch: Totally overdressed.
Junlan: Looks classy, but definitely not expensive.
Junsu: Junlan’s at this level, and we’re up here.
Zhuojie: Calm down.
Junsu: Calm down.
Zhuojie: No need to be scared.
We have a special prize for the person with the most likes.
The prize is a luxury shared bedroom.
Jawoon: Happiness isn’t far away.
(Don’t leave yet, there’s a post-credit scene!)
Dir: What is it?
Staff: He wants to talk to you.
Dokyun: I have something to propose.
Dokyun: Right now I have 500 baht.
Dokyun: And I want to use it.
Staff: He has a proposal. He has 500 baht.
Staff: He feels like he wants to use this money.
Dir: What does he want to do with it?
Staff: What do you want to use it for?
Dokyun: I want to buy a blanket.
Staff: He wants to buy a blanket.
Dokyun: Because my Chinese friend Jeremy
Dokyun: is cold all night long.
Dokyun: So I want to use my money to buy him a blanket.
Dokyun: Please help ask if it’s okay.
Staff: His Chinese friend said
Staff: he’s cold every night.
Staff: He feels like he wants to use his money
to buy that friend a blanket.
Staff: So he wants to ask if that’s possible.
Dir: Zhuojie?
Staff: Zhuojie, right?
Dokyun: Yes, yes! Zhuojie!
Dir: But this is a game, right?
He didn’t choose the bed with stuff in the first place.
Staff: This is part of the game, right?
Staff: Because he didn’t pick the bed with the blanket.
Dokyun: So I can’t even buy it with my own money?
Dokyun: Even if I pay myself?
Staff: Even with his own money, can’t he buy it?
Dir: It has to be bought. I’ll check the price with the team.
Staff: He can buy it.
Staff: But we need to check with the crew first.
Staff: So...
Dokyun: Is it expensive? How much is it?
Staff: Is it expensive? How much?
Dir: P’Berm, can you hear me?
Dir: An actor wants to buy a blanket for his friend.
Dir: If he has to buy it, how much should it cost?
Dir: 650 baht?
Dir: 650 baht.
Dokyun: That’s really expensive.
Dokyun: 650 baht?
Staff: Yes.
Dir: 650 baht.
Dokyun: Hold on, hold on.
Dokyun: I only have 500 baht.
Staff: He only has 500 baht.
Dokyun: Just 500.
Staff: That’s all he’s got.
Dokyun: For a friend...
Dokyun: He’s really cold.
Dokyun: Jeremy, I mean.
Staff: His friend looks really cold. Can he have it?
Dir: Alright.
Dokyun: Really? Are you serious?
Dir: Then let the staff bring it over later.
Staff: The staff will bring it over shortly.
Dokyun: And also...
Dokyun: Don’t tell the other friends, okay?
Dokyun: He asked me to say—please don’t tell the others.
Dir: Of course we won’t say anything.
Staff: It’ll be our little secret.
Dokyun: Promise...
Dir: You do realize this is prize money, right?
Staff: This is part of the prize money—you know that, right?
Staff: It’s the prize money...
Dokyun: About that...
Dokyun: I’ll find a way to earn more later.
Staff: You can always earn more later.
Dokyun: Okay, thank you.
Dir: Okay.
Dokyun: Zhuojie.
Zhuojie: What’s up?
Dokyun: Come here a sec.
Dokyun: This is for you.
Zhuojie: Really? Are you serious?
(What are they talking about?)
Dokyun: We’re friends, after all.
Zhuojie: Friends, yeah.
(Zhuojie isn’t cold anymore.)
Zhuojie: Thanks, Dokyun.
Dokyun: Don’t mention it.