You need to fast beforehand, and we'll
carry out the procedure at 8:30 a.m.
May I ask if you've tried this before?
Had an abortion, you mean?
No, this is my first.
A NETFLIX SERIES
No. Then you just
send them directly there.
-Hi, do you have a minute?
-Say hi to Mille first,
who starts as a temp until we find
a more permanent solution.
Mille-Emilie. It's hyphenated.
-Sorry.
-It's fine.
-Hi, I'm Nana.
-Hi, Nana. Nice to meet you.
People always get it wrong,
don't worry about it.
It's just that
I need to take tomorrow off.
The whole day actually.
Why?
My mom is…
-…sick.
-No.
-Yes.
-Is it serious?
No, but she started feeling unwell
last night after her concert, so…
-Your mom's a singer?
-Yes.
-How exciting.
-Yes. Thank you.
-I just want to be there for her.
-That makes sense.
Yes. That does make sense.
No. I wanted to ask you.
Have you spoken to Simone?
-No.
You see, Simone is stopping by today
to get the rest of her stuff.
And she's getting
a great severance package.
And it's just because we cannot
keep her after that journalist called.
It's really exciting.
I heard it in the kitchen this morning.
I have a client waiting,
so I'm going to go.
Let me just point out that it's so
exciting that we keep it under wraps.
Hi. Is it okay if Christina comes in now?
-I can also wait outside?
-No. Come in. Have a seat.
I saw you were free,
so I thought she could come in.
Just close the door.
-What?
-Close the door.
Oh, yes.
-Have a seat.
-Thanks.
How is everything?
Everything's fine, I think.
I had decided on the abortion.
But…
-Hi, again.
-Hi, Tobias. Come in.
Thank you.
-Have a seat.
-Hi.
-I hope it's okay I join you.
-Of course.
I have… Or…
we have decided that
even though we've split up…
we still want the baby.
Even though we're not together,
we want the baby together.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
There it is.
That's funny.
-Would you like a picture?
-Yes.
Look.
A little cutie.
I think it's because the system is new.
I'm new, so I just need to learn it.
-Hey, Nana?
-Yes?
Do you know how long it will take?
Malene is your next appointment.
-Oh, right.
-My name is Marianne.
-Oh, sorry.
-Hi!
We'll talk about
initiating a treatment, so I'll…
I think we'll need about half an hour.
Is there a parking spot where
you can park for more than 15 minutes?
-I'll find out.
-I have EasyPark, but I…
-Do you have EasyPark?
-Yeah.
-It's wonderful that you could come.
-Yes, of course.
-I have loads of time now.
-Yes.
We're busy here as usual.
Nana has a client.
-Yes. Would you like some coffee?
-Yes, I'd love some.
Let's see if the machine can
brew one of those lovely flat whites.
I'll take it black. Like my conscience.
I love your sense of humor. Come.
Nana?
-Nana?
-Yes?
-Are you ready?
-For what?
For Marianne.
Yes, of course.
I think I always knew I'd be on my own.
Yes.
-If that makes any sense…
-Sure, my husband feels the same way.
Your husband?
Didn't you just say you're a solo mom?
Yes.
-I am, but not in the classic sense.
-I don't understand.
Let's look at the treatment plan.
-Have you heard a word I've said?
-Yes, of course.
I'm sorry, but this makes me nervous.
-Yeah.
-Sorry, I got confused.
-Confused if you're a solo mom?
-Yes, or no. I'm not.
-You're not confused?
Yes. I mean no. Yes. No.
I really don't appreciate
you paying lip service to your patients.
We call them clients, not patients.
That hardly makes a difference if you
don't listen and just say some bullshit.
I'm sorry about this.
Let's start over and look
-at the treatment plan.
-No.
Listen.
That's just not good enough.
No.
It just isn't.
This is highly reprehensible.
It's our policy
because we really can't guarantee that.
No. Maybe they're just disappointed.
Yes, maybe. Good point.
Is it done, Nana?
Come on.
Wow, right in the smacker.
It probably isn't good to…
I'll just grab a cup later.
I don't need it.
It's fine.
Hey, Helle?
It's fine, I don't need anything.
I need to talk--
Helle?
Do you have a minute?
Yes.
Of course.
She excels at her work, and I've never
known her to make mistakes.
No, and I actually don't disagree, Nana.
But technically speaking,
she made a mistake and it's not okay
-when we deal with human lives.
-But it was me.
I didn't set the alarm.
We were both here, and we got drunk,
and then Simone asked me
to set the alarm, because she was tired…
-No, she was drunk. Right?
-Yes, but…
-Anyway, I forgot because…
-Because it doesn't matter.
Because a doctor doesn't
set the alarm in a sperm bank.
And certainly not if said doctor
doesn't even work in that sperm bank.
-But…
-No buts!
Simone shouldn't have gotten drunk.
Then we wouldn't have a problem.
And what now? Should I fire you?
Over a minor alarm issue? Leaving your
clients with no doctor starting tomorrow?
-Twelve to fifteen couples
-Yeah.
would have to change to doctors
they don't even know.
-I see your point,
-Can you?
but you have to understand…
-I do understand.
-I don't think you do! What?
Excuse me.
-Is it okay if I interrupt?
-Sure. Or?
Yeah, sure.
-What are you doing here, honey?
-I ran all the way here because…
Yes.
-No, honey?
-Yes.
Honey…
-No.
-Yes.
May I ask what's going on?
Yes, you may. We have a positive test.
-Congratulations. Well done!
-Yes, congratulations.
Are congratulations in order?
-Yes. Hell yes. It's all thanks to Nana.
-Yes.
-I don't know about that.
-We shouldn't forget about that.
She's very talented.
She sure is.
Thank you, Nana.
Would you please tell the new receptionist
I'm taking the rest of the day off?
Yes.
Thanks.
I love you, honey. Come.
A lot has happened since the last time.
My little company is growing rapidly.
-Last week I hired three new people.
-And you…
design clothes for animals?
-For dogs.
-Clothes for dogs?
-Yes, rainwear. Hundertwasser.
-Oh.
-Or wetdog.
-Yeah.
And I've just been thinking a lot about
what I spend my time on,
what I want to do
and my company, and I just think…
I think I've come to the conclusion
that it's not the right time to have kids.
-I'm sorry to have wasted your time.
-No. You haven't.
Don't think about it.
It's your decision, there is no…
I do need…
…to point out that the longer you wait,
the harder it'll be.
Yes, I know. I'm actually okay with that.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I'm just thinking that
if it happens, it happens.
Like how you just met your husband
in the jungle, and you had a kid quickly.
And you have two kids now, right?
I actually don't have any.
-I'm pretty sure you said two kids.
-I don't have any kids.
-But we have talked about your kids?
-Any at all actually.
A boy and a girl, right?
You'll have to excuse me for a moment.
What's happening?
Nana?
Nana, come here. Nana!
Come here. We need to call an ambulance!
Ambulance!
-We'll check for extrauterine first.
-Yes, understood.
Check for extrauterine first.
Good morning.
Is it morning?
No. That's just what you say
when someone wakes up.
-You were only out for an hour.
-And the baby?
Everything's fine.
Yes. A doctor will be here shortly,
but everything's fine.
Yes.
-That was a bit of a scare.
-Yes.
And congratulations, dammit.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
It's still a bit new.
But you know what?
I think you're going to be a great mother.
-May I ask who the lucky father is?
-He doesn't know.
It's a bit… So maybe you shouldn't.
-Just…
-Sure. Of course.
-What are you reading?
-Oh, it's not mine.
It is… It was…
I found it in the waiting room.
But it's actually pretty funny.
It's about a woman on an estate
who, after many years, realizes
that she's been in love
with the gardener all along
and when she tells him,
he's drafted to fight in the war.
It's just such a horrible
and sad situation, you know?
-Hi. Nana?
-Hi. Yes.
Glad to see you're awake.
My name is Lars, I'm a doctor.
I'm the one who saw you when you came.
-Have you had something to drink?
-I'm fine.
I suspect it was
a small vessel that ruptured
and if you're already stressed
or exhausted…
-And no blood in my abdominal cavity?
-No.
The fetus looks healthy.
It's a little fireball.
-Any questions?
-No.
-Then I'll get on with my rounds.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome. Bye.
-My daughter, Nana, what room is she in?
-Nana is right down there to the right.
The nurse asked about next of kin,
so I took the liberty of
calling your mother.
-Sweetie. Hi.
-Hi, Mom.
Hi, my little sweetie.
-And hi to you, Jens-Anders.
-Hi.
-Thank you for calling.
-Sure, of course.
-I'll leave you to it.
-You don't have to. You can stay.
It's okay, I should probably
get back to the clinic.
-Yes. Thank you.
-See you.
-Bye.
-Good-looking guy.
-Jesus, Mom.
He's a true fan.
Why didn't you tell me you were pregnant?
-Everything is a mess.
-What?
Everything is a mess.
Are you hungry?
A little.
-You can have the rest of mine. I'm done.
-Thank you.
I just love this sauce. You really forget.
Don't they have it in Sweden?
No. They give you ketchup for some reason.
I stopped by your concert yesterday.
Oh? I didn't see you.
I didn't go in. I stayed outside but
I heard the whole thing
and it was really good.
Thank you.
The way you sang was beautiful.
Without all the added stuff.
Well, they couldn't afford
bass or drums or backup singers.
-One will have to make do.
-Right.
I hadn't really listened
to the lyrics that way before
if that makes sense.
Thanks.
-I actually wrote it for you.
-Oh.
I thought you wrote it for that guy
you moved in with. That guy…
Was his name Fritz?
No, it wasn't for him at all.
That didn't last long, you know that.
No, it wasn't him.
I didn't know that.
I thought it lasted a while.
You'd just been born.
Those days where you just lie in bed.
You cried and cried
and the doctors thought you had colic.
It was so damn hard.
All my girlfriends helped me.
It was insane.
And when they left because…
Well,
they couldn't stand the noise either.
Then it was just the two of us.
And for the first time in three
or four days, you didn't cry.
And those lyrics came to me.
It is you who makes the sky turn blue
And I always think of you
Without you the day is sad and grey
It is you who brings me smiles of joy
I’ve been struck by cupid's arrow
You're my greatest love…
Would you also like some tea?
What's wrong?
What's wrong, sweetie?
-I just got tired, I think.
-You are? Come here.
Sweetie. It's also tough.
Yeah.
-There…
-I don't even know why I'm so tired.
That's how it is, sweetie.
That's just how it is.
-Your little body is working so hard.
-Yeah
Regarding the second point, I think…
I don't know what to call it. If it's…
Nana. Welcome.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm okay.
May I have a quick word with you?
Let me get this straight. So you…
Yes, I took the sperm straw
with his number on, and then…
the others must've fallen out.
I then picked them up
and I must've put them back
in the wrong place.
-And then you inseminated yourself?
-Yeah.
-Jesus Christ.
-Yes.
Do you need some water?
I think so.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Fine.
I think we should keep this
to ourselves for a while.
We shouldn't involve
the police at this point.
And besides that,
no one was seriously harmed by it.
Well, Simone kind of was.
Yes. That's true. Yes, I'll call her.
I'd like to be the one
to tell her everything.
But I'd really appreciate it
if you'd rehire her.
Yes. Of course.
I'll need to talk to Jannick, but, yes.
I will.
And what do we do with you?
Hey, Søren?
I've been fired. It's a long story, but…
I don't need any more of those.
Is it just Simone who thinks
I'm the father, or did you tell everyone?
-It would be nice to know.
-No, I didn't tell anyone.
I promise.
Everything is just a big mess.
Yes.
But it's your mess.
I actually don't know what to say.
Go away, Nana.
-I talked to Helle.
-I don't care. Get lost.
I told her everything.
I told her it was me.
It doesn't matter now. It's too late.
Please open the door.
Open the door.
I've never been so humiliated.
And you knew all along.
-Yes.
I'm sorry!
I don't care.
I don't know what to say. It was really…
stupid and bad and insane and wrong and…
And what?
Just really horrible. I…
I understand if you can't forgive me,
but can't you…
Can't you just try?
I don't know
what to do without you, actually.
-You're so fucked up.
-Yes, I am.
-And a huge liar.
-I know, but no more. Never again.
Helle apologizes, too,
and you're rehired, of course.
-And you've been fired?
-Yes, very fired.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
-Do you want a cup of coffee?
-Yes, please.
I don't have any milk.
I'll just take it black.
Like my conscience.
Too soon.
-Do you have the keys?
-Yes.
-Are we like burglars now?
-No.
-Then why are we whispering?
-It's just cozier like this.
-Like this?
-That's fine.
Now I just need to…
-Yuck. It looks like slime.
-It kind of is. It helps the scanner.
-Can you press the green button?
-The one on the right?
-Wow, it's beating fast.
-Yes. Isn't it crazy?
Bastian, I think you can
give Nana the present now.
What do we have here?
-Is this for me?
-No, for the baby.
Is it for the baby?
That's just…
…mega cool.
-With glitter and everything.
-And glitter claws.
It was his own idea.
You did a good job with him, huh?
So will you.
But you have to tell him about it.
-He's going to hate me.
-If he hates you, he hates you.
And then you'll go from there.
What should I say?
I think I would start with the truth.
Everybody has a secret
Something we don’t share
But keep to ourselves
But, darling, if I have to tell the truth
You’re the most beautiful thing I know
I think that’s what you call love
It is you who makes the sky turn blue
And I always think of you
Without you the day is sad and grey
It is you who brings me smiles of joy
I’ve been struck by cupid's arrow
You're my greatest love
In forever
Life can bring rain and sun
But everything I need
Is a little sign
To feel that you are right by my side
You are the best thing I know
I think that’s what you call love
It is you who makes the sky turn blue
And I always think of you
Without you the day is sad and grey
It is you who brings me smiles of joy
I’ve been struck by cupid's arrow
You're my greatest love
In forever
Subtitle translation by: