Damn it.
NANA L. JESSEN
FERTILITY DOCTOR
So I stole sperm to inseminate myself.
No big deal, I'm just borrowing the sperm.
That's fine, right? Or is it totally
fucked? Can I go to jail because of it?
But I could get a baby.
3 DAYS EARLIER
NO PARKING OF BICYCLES
Nana?
-Good morning, miss.
-Good morning, sir.
-In a hurry?
-Yeah, I have a consultation in five.
-It was nice when we--
-Yeah, it was nice, thanks.
-I picked some mushrooms this weekend--
-You picked mushrooms?
-Okay.
-Yes.
-Chanterelles, oyster mushrooms.
-Really?
-Really. It makes a really good soup.
-Lovely.
So if you want come over for dinner--
Sounds nice, I'm just so busy
this week. But maybe.
-Okay.
-Have a nice day.
You too.
-The new GE scanner?
-Yes.
Awesome, I've been
asking for this for ages.
It shows both the endometrium
and follicles in 3D.
The scanner is smaller, of course.
To make the vaginal penetration nicer
for the woman.
-Good morning.
What's up, Bastian?
-Did you drop out of 1st grade again?
-Can I, Mom?
-No, sweetie.
-Sure you can.
-No.
-You're smart.
I understand English, you know.
-He understands English.
-Yeah.
-Did I see you outside with Hot Phys?
-He's nice. And handsome.
A tiny bit boring.
After happy hour last Friday,
you made it sound like he'd invented sex.
I haven't got time for dating.
Too much work.
I have a great idea. Let's trade.
You'll be the single mom
and I'll be the doctor banging hot
physiotherapists and paying top tax.
Yeah…
Can you feel it?
But I suck at roleplaying.
We'll trade if I win at bowling tonight.
Nana!
-Sorry, I forgot.
-Come on!
-You forgot the highlight of the week?
-It's unbelievable.
It sure is!
-I forgot my bowling shoes.
-Do it in your socks.
-Didn't work last time.
-It worked fine.
-Get in there, and remember new--
-Wait, I remember. New…
-Andreas.
-Anton.
New Anton.
Well done. New Anton
is going to follow you around all day.
Thanks for the reminder.
Nearly done, Latifa.
I'm draining the last follicle…
now.
-You're doing great, baby.
-Thanks.
Super. I'm removing it now.
Yes.
Well done. Was it bad?
No, it was okay.
It's not the most pleasant thing
in the world.
Yes, we have five.
-What?
-We got five.
There are five.
Isn't more better?
Quality is better than quantity,
so it's great.
-How can you ascertain the quality?
-At 32, your eggs should be fine.
When I had twins, I only had three eggs,
so it's more than enough.
That's nice to hear.
-Isn't it tough to have twins?
-It's crazy!
Insanely crazy.
I never sleep, and they'll only
eat Coco Pops for dinner.
But when they're your kids,
you just think it's cute.
I just can't stand the thought
of losing another.
I don't know if I can handle it.
I felt the same way.
-You did?
-I was terrified of doing anything.
I gained 25 kg.
I was sprawled on the sofa
eating chocolate and bingeing Friends.
Ten seasons, that's…
That's a lot of hours,
in case you didn't know.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here's my number.
Please call me anytime.
Day and night. I mean it.
I really appreciate that.
-I can show you how.
-That'd be great.
-Why are the models always so mad?
-They're hungry.
Yeah.
Nana, I'm really impressed
by the way you talk to clients.
-Thanks. Hi.
-I can tell it means a lot to them,
that you involve yourself and your kids.
-Thanks.
-Which kids did you talk about today?
You have more than the twins?
You have Lea, 11, a terrific jazz dancer.
She really is.
-So you have three kids?
-And how's Malthe? Still homesick?
Oh, it was just a phase.
He just went on a school camping trip
for three days.
Wow.
-He loves Billie Eilish.
-She is great. Here you go.
Thank you.
-So you have four kids?
-It depends…
on the situation, I guess.
You have shared custody?
Okay, then. Imagine
your dentist had really bad teeth.
That won't do, right?
If it reassures them
to hear that I have kids…
then I have kids.
So you haven't got kids?
Nope.
-Want to chip in for a present for Helle?
-Sure. What have you got in mind?
-Niels-Anders suggested a sea kayak.
-A sea kayak?
-A sea kayak.
-Okay.
-She'll never use it, that's for sure.
-Never.
-She will, just wait and see.
-Wait and see?
-A sea kayak.
-She will.
-Hi, everybody.
-Hi.
Welcome to yet another
wonderful weekly conference.
Let me begin by saying how much I look
forward every day to working with you.
-Likewise.
-Thank you.
Anyway, I have good news.
The numbers are looking
even better all around…
Maybe I should say yes
to the mushroom soup with Hot Phys.
What kind of person picks mushrooms?
But he is really handsome.
And it was nice last time.
And a little awkward. Or… no, it was nice.
But if we do it again,
he may think we're getting serious.
Sex and soup…
Nana, I don't know how you do it,
but your clients get pregnant
by the dozen.
Wonderful.
Oh, and Niels-Anders has an idea.
Well, it's come to my attention
that several of our competitors
have launched an all-inclusive deal
that includes all scans and medications
so the bill doesn't come
as a surprise to clients.
Isn't that just a smart way
of tapping clients for more money?
No.
Sure it is.
No, it's more transparent for clients.
And it might just be great
for our bottom line.
Bottom line? We're not talking
about a football match.
What?
A football match?
Yeah, with lines.
-Oh, you mean back lines--
-Yeah, bottom lines.
Let me just cut in. If nobody,
for instance, me, because I'm the boss
focuses on our turnover,
we can't afford to give the odd discount
or buy a new scanner, for example.
For example.
-And other things, Niels-Anders.
-Right.
-Yes, well--
-Then…
-Fine, it's fine.
-It's not decided. Let's move on.
-One quick thing.
-Yeah?
New fruit plan.
Excuse me.
-Nana, got a second?
-Sure.
-You know, Marie--
-Your new girlfriend.
-We've been together for two years now.
-Oh, okay.
-We want to start up treatment.
-Good for you. Congratulations.
And we'd like you
to inseminate Marie.
I get it if you're like,
"Oh, boy, the boss's wife." Pressure!
"What an honor!"
No, I'm kidding!
Hi, Niels-Anders.
Don't worry. We're regular clients.
Whenever you can squeeze us in.
I'm pretty booked,
as you know.
But it'd be great to start within
the next 14 days
to fit with Marie's cycle.
Okay.
And Niels-Anders isn't free, or?
We both want you.
-Well--
-Thanks a million.
It's just…
Well, it means a lot. Thanks. I mean it.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Isn't it beautiful?
We've got a lane at seven, and I have
to file the records and clean the bank.
-Two minutes. I'll help you clean.
-Well, you really suck at that.
Jump up and let's try it out.
No way.
-Come on. Please!
-I'm busy, and I don't want to.
-Why not?
-Because.
-We've done it a million times.
-I said no.
Or yes.
-Or no.
-Or no. Damn.
Fine.
What?
-Then you'll scan me.
-No way!
What do you mean?
Okay.
-Ready?
-Yes.
Move it to the right.
Or up.
Yes. The resolution is great, huh?
Go further in.
There you go.
It's a crazy sharp image, huh?
Was that all you wanted to check?
Stay there.
Can you press the plus button?
Freeze and then plus.
Freeze.
And then zoom.
Perfect.
Press print.
Thanks.
Shit.
Three follicles.
What does it mean?
It means that…
Well, I don't know. That I have…
…five-six cycles.
So six months to get pregnant?
That's not good.
No.
Not if you want to get pregnant, anyway.
-But do you?
-Hell, I don't know.
It's just that you always say
it perhaps wasn't meant to be.
I know, but I never imagined…
…that my deadline was this close.
You know?
You're only 37. Isn't that early
to run out of eggs?
Yeah.
Some women just have
fewer eggs than others.
-Is it a genetic thing?
-Yeah.
Another great gift from my mom.
Good thing you're surrounded by sperm.
Just take your pick.
I don't know if I'm ready for that.
But why not?
I never imagined I'd be a single mom.
-How about the nice guy from Vejle?
-No, he was freakily close to his mom.
-Jacob!
-Jacob who?
-Low hairline, tall.
-I don't even remember him.
-Frederik?
-Right.
He didn't like kids.
I've got it.
HP.
HP?
Hot Phys.
No way.
Simone, you don't have kids
with a guy you banged after happy hour.
Sure you do.
So pick a guy in the sperm bank catalogue.
And fuck having a dad around.
Your turn.
Look at all the great solo moms
we help every day.
-I know.
-They manage.
I know.
I just don't think…
My mom was…
She was kind of…
I heard her hit on the radio yesterday.
What a shame you didn't inherit her voice.
I don't really know what I inherited.
All I can do is work.
-Not true.
-Yes.
No.
I still use my phone
to go to the bathroom.
-What for?
-The flashlight.
The flashlight?
The light bulb blew six months ago.
I'm no use to anyone, really.
Come here.
You've called Lise LaCour,
I can't pick up the phone,
but if you sing a message,
I might call you back!
Hi Mom, it's me.
It feels like we haven't talked in ages.
So I just wanted to say hi.
So hi.
And…
Bye.
Nana?
Damn.
-Do you need help?
-No, it's fine. I think…
I think it's gone…
All over my pants.
-Do you want to--
-Sure, thanks.
-It's good to see you.
-You too.
-You work here?
-Yeah, I work in a…
A fertility clinic.
In here. Right here.
-Congratulations, that's what you wanted.
-Thanks, yeah.
What about you?
Are you done saving the world?
No, it still needs saving.
I'm in Guatemala.
-Just home for a quick visit.
-Interesting.
What are you doing here?
That's an interesting story.
I have a meeting with the sperm bank.
The sperm bank, right.
That's just around the corner.
Okay, good to know. Otherwise,
I would've been stuck here all day.
Oh, right.
How long are you in town?
Can we meet up?
-Sure we can.
-Yeah.
This is…
-Simone.
-Mathias.
Hi, Mathias.
Nice to meet you.
-I work with--
-I'll be up in a minute.
-Bye.
-Well, I have to go.
-Yeah, I should get to work.
We'll figure something out.
-See you soon.
-See you.
-And have a nice day at work.
-You too.
Or…
Bye.
Who was that?
There you are.
-Was it an ex-boyfriend?
-No.
-It is!
-It isn't.
Why haven't you told me about him?
So we dated for six months, and then…
Yeah.
It was really nice. He was wonderful.
-Almost too wonderful.
-Oh, you don't want that.
That's why I always fall for morons.
They don't let you down.
He got a job with an NGO
in South America and…
then it stopped.
He's totally "the one who got away."
And you haven't seen him in seven years?
No.
And now he's donating sperm
so other people can have wonderful kids.
Fate brought him back for you.
He lives in Guatemala.
One date with you
and he's never going back.
He'll be the father of your baby
and you'll live happily ever after.
No.
Not going to happen.
I deleted his number back then.
Who cares if you're not going to call him?
Fucking six months.
-Your next client is here.
-Thanks, send her in.
It's good you called,
you shouldn't be worried.
Let's check if everything's fine.
This is your pulse. It's a bit high.
Is that bad?
Not at all. You're just nervous.
Okay.
Let me have a look here.
I knew it.
Great.
Is that the heart?
Yeah, a very nice, little heart.
It's beating so fast.
Well, it's pretty busy in there.
It's a little human.
It's the best sound in the world.
Yeah.
What's up?
You can never tell!
Tell what?
I just went into
the computer at the sperm bank.
Did you just get a picture?
What's this?
All the info the sperm bank has on him.
Address, sperm ID number,
and his phone number are at the bottom.
I see.
You can't tell anyone!
Relax, I won't.
I'm not even going to call him.
At first, I kept seeing you everywhere.
At the markets, on the street.
In Chile.
Which is strange. Why would you be there?
I meant to write, but…
-It was a bit strange when you left.
-Yeah, it was a mess.
It was a mess.
Strange, isn't it?
To bump into each other there.
Yeah. It's not a place you
typically run into people you know.
-Cold?
-A little.
Thanks.
It's really nice to--
Yeah.
To see you again.
You too.
When do you, like, want kids?
What?
I mean…
do you?
-You're asking if I want kids?
-Not right now, but…
Or preferably soon,
within six months' time, perhaps?
I just want to know,
because it's something I…
I…
Don't you usually kiss before you
discuss having kids?
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
I'm too much.
Can we just pretend it never happened?
-Sure, let's try that.
-Great.
It's fine.
Great.
I just went,
"When do you want to be a dad?"
-So--
-Jesus.
Let me just get this straight.
-You're just about to kiss?
-Yeah.
And you ask him
if he wants to have kids with you.
Yeah.
And he kind of balked at that.
Well, it kind of makes sense,
it is a pretty hardcore
first date question.
Is it terrible?
-No.
-Look me in the eye.
Okay.
Is it terrible?
Terrible!
-It wasn't the smartest thing to do.
-Huge fuck-up.
I'll take a break
and we'll go upstairs to the clinic.
We'll listen to some Poul
and have a tiny shot.
Can you feel it?
Let's go up to Poul.
Maybe we need two shots.
Max two shots…
Come here and hold me
Hold me and hug me
I feel like making a double.
I'll fill them all at once.
We've been adrift in outer space
Like two satellites passing by
Why did you spill it all?
But luckily, we have landed
And you are right here by my side
People like us
Need to find themselves a sweetheart
I'd really like that sweetheart to be you
So come sit down
We are off to a great start
Like a pathfinder who's back en route
GREAT TO SEE YOU. YOU'RE NICE,
I'M STUPID. SORRY ABOUT BEING BROODY
HOPE I DIDN'T SCARE YOU OFF
Babe…
Can you go downstairs and…
lock up the sperm bank?
-No.
-Yes.
No!
If the alarm goes off,
you're paying the fine.
OMNISPERM ENSURES NEW RECORD REVENUE
Fuck.
Damn.
Three follicles.
So six months to get pregnant?
That's not good.
When do you want kids?
You're asking if I want kids?
-I have a meeting with the sperm bank.
-Okay.
All the info
the sperm bank has on him.
Address, sperm ID number.
MATHIAS DAHL
No one ever needs to know.