Have you fallen?
Damn girl.
That’s a first.
There’s something about him.
It’s like there’s a connection between us.
Tom!
I know that you’re still
hurt about what happened.
And I understand.
And I’m glad you’re here.
You know what?
Prima has a new model.
She’d be the same age as Lara if–
I believe we’ll meet again.
Uhm, Jasmine.
This is Ryan Soriano, our COO.
Jasmine, can I talk to you?
Alone?
Just to let you know,
I’m done with that life.
So we both have a secret.
What’s the dirt you have on Christine?
She saw Christine the
other day with some guy.
I don’t know who the guy
is, that’s why I wanna find out.
So everything’s settled
for the contract signing.
All that’s left is the menu, just
pick from the links that I sent you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sephy.
- Thanks.
Are you visiting your parents?
Why?
Ew! I hate these clothes,
my god it’s so not me.
It’s Vince’s clothes.
I know you’re visiting your parents
when you come to the office like that.
When are you coming out?
It’s better this way, that they don’t know.
Rather than giving my
father a heart attack.
You’re right.
Oh wait, let me ask you.
How are you and your lover boy Tom?
When do you plan to
stop keeping it a secret?
I can’t help but feel guilty.
He’s bringing up the proposal again.
As long as he understands
your circumstances.
That’s what's important.
Vince and I agree even
though we have circumstances.
I mean, my parents would die if they
found out I was gay.
And on the other hand,
it could ruin his career.
In your case,
you’re the only one with the circumstance.
So you have to make sure that
he understands you.
Okay, sis?
Okay bye, sis.
Introducing the new face of Prima Beauty.
Jasmine Reyes or most
known for being a streetlamp girl
signed a contract with Prima Beauty.
According to Prima Beauty’s CEO,
Jasmine Reyes’ image is perfect
to empower young
women like her to reach for
their dreams even in the face of adversity.
Jasmine Reyes will be the face of their
new perfume line.
And there you have it everyone.
Congratulations, Miss Jasmine Reyes.
The new face of Prima Beauty.
Jasmine, congratulations!
I need to go to the bathroom.
- Sure.
- Just wait here.
Hurry up.
Congratulations, hija.
Thank you.
Technology nowadays is insane,
you just need to pose on social media
and you’ll go viral.
It’s so much easier nowadays.
Uhm, sorry but who are you again ma’am?
Oh, I’m Stella Soriano.
You’ve met my son Ryan, the COO of Prima.
Oh, and who are you?
Oh,
I just happen to be the
previous CEO of Prima,
that my ex-husband took from me,
and gave to someone else.
Oh! Jasmine,
since you’re the new face of Prima.
You need to have class.
You need to be prim
and proper, you know that.
‘Cause that’s our brand's image.
Prim and proper? Oh no.
That’s not me,
you should’ve gotten a different model.
You know what, I was
actually surprised too.
Okay.
Excuse me.
-Oh sure.
-Sure.
So, what are your future plans?
Oh Stella,
what are you doing here?
Isn’t it your bedtime?
You should enjoy being a senior.
Thank you for the rescue, Miss Christine.
She’s so full of herself.
Don’t mind her, she likes to
project her drama in life to everyone.
Don’t throw your pearls to pigs.
Your quote from that photo shoot was funny,
but I get what you meant.
Impressive.
Oh, Miss Christine,
I must have bought every single
magazine issue that you were featured in.
That’s how much I idolize you.
Thank you, I appreciate it.
Wait, are you alone?
Where are your parents?
It’s just me.
I’ve been an orphan.
Oh, I’m sorry to hear that.
It’s okay Miss Christine,
I’m here with my best friend.
She’s like a mother to me, even though
we’re only two years apart.
You know,
you’re the reason why I
have the confidence now,
because of your inspirational messages.
I really strived to finish my studies.
But, no matter what happens,
I’ll do my best to work for Prima.
But thank God, you approached me.
I don’t want to be just
a model, Miss Christine.
I really want to be in operations.
I am a Management graduate.
I know that’s why I’m impressed.
Don’t worry,
we’ll find a place for
you here in the company.
Okay?
Thank you.
Sis, I just need to talk
to you about something.
- Oh okay.
- Excuse me.
Alright, excuse me.
Thank you, Miss Christine.
Congrats again.
What are you looking at Mister Lopez?
Nothing.
Aren’t you used to people
admiring your beauty?
This is on me.
Well, starting today this is your life now.
You really made it, I’m so proud of you.
You’re overreacting, but thank you.
You’re still excited about it.
I need to pee again.
I should’ve gone to ther restroom earlier.
- Is there a restroom here somewhere?
- Over there.
There’s one there.
Okay, wait here.
Sure.
Hi, congratulations.
Thank you.
I’m also a model here, hair and make up.
Wow,
what’s it like working here?
Well, mostly it’s just my hair they see.
I’m a hair double.
Oh, that’s a thing.
Just maintain your
assets and you’ll be okay.
You know, if we have it, we use it.
Hello!
You’ve met my good friend, Chelsea.
You know what, Chelsea was also from
the perfume line.
Everything was set,
we we’re about to shoot the ads
and the line up was all prepared.
But, Christine found
someone else she likes,
and she was replaced just like that.
That doesn’t sound like Miss Christine.
I think there’s a reason why that happened.
That’s why she left when you arrived.
Don’t be so sure.
All I know is that when she
gets want she wants with you,
you’re out.
You know what, Sir?
I met your mom earlier
and you sound just like her.
In this industry, one
mistake and you’re out.
So be careful.
Oh, you're done?
Infairness the restroom
was air conditioned.
It looks nice.
Yeah it is.
- Oh.
- Oh?
I forgot my contract.
Why, where is it?
- Sir Jonathan?
- Yes?
Have you seen my contract?
The contracts are with Sir Tom.
- Ah okay, Thank you.
- Sure.
Wait.
- I just need to get my contract from Tom.
- Okay.
Hurry up.
What are we gonna do with the contracts?
I’ll take care of it, I’ll
give them to Jasmine.
- I’ll bring it to the legal department.
- Okay.
- Let’s go.
Here are the contracts, love.
Thank you.
Love
What?
Did you get it?
No, he went inside Miss Christine’s office
and locked the door.
Do you think they’re doing something else?
You think?
No, that’s impossible.
Their age difference is too big.
Why? How old is Tom?
Twenty-eight.
How about Miss Christine?
She just had her birthday,
so I think forty-two?
Wow, that’s a big age gap.
Come on, let’s go home.
That’s fine.
It’s nothing.
So, for this quarter the numbers
are looking good.
Okay,
let’s maintain those numbers.
So what’s our target for the next quarter?
Actually, that’s what I
want to bring up with you.
Considering we have a new model.
It’s somewhat risky, if we use her
as the face of the company,
the sales could decrease.
Sales could also increase,
since her story is very inspirational.
People like inspirational stories.
I hope you’re making the
right decision here Christine.
There you go again, Ryan.
Did I embarrass you in
front of the Marketing team?
Is that your ego talking?
Come on, grow-up Ryan.
You really got Dad’s style.
He trained me well.
You were just Dad’s assistant, remember?
Yes,
and I’m not ashamed of it.
I even tell our employees about it,
in our training sessions.
To inspire them, that hard work pays.
Not just because you're the wife or
son of the owner.
Okay,
my bad.
I shouldn’t have said that, I’m sorry.
I rose through the ranks, ‘cause
I worked hard for it, right?
After experiencing bruises,
broken bones,
and abuse from him.
You know I deserve this Ryan.
I rebuilt this company.
You can bring this up
with the board, if you want.
Christine,
you’re not the only one deserving.
You bastard!
Who were you with?
When are you gonna stop?
You’re too old for this!
At your age–
When will you stop?
You don’t need to shout at me.
Yes, I will shout at you.
Because you’re a cheater, you don’t stop.
You don’t want to stop!
Fine, go with them and
make their life miserable.
- Don’t you fucking shout at me!
- I will shout at–
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Mom.
Son, I'm sorry.
I can’t do this anymore.
I know it will cost me, but I just can’t.
I’m filing for an annulment.
And I know, we’ll lose
our place in the company.
Mom, what can I do to help?
Ryan, fight for your right as his son.
I wanna help you.
Okay?
He already pushed me away,
don’t let him do this to you.
Okay?
Promise?
Promise.
I will.
I’ll take care of you, Mom.
So promise me, you won’t end up like him.
No.
I know you’ll be better.
Promise me, okay?
Promise.
So what did you do this time that
your Dad punched you?
The file’s spelling was wrong.
Fuck, right?
Here’s an ice pack,
so it heals faster.
Thanks.
He punched you because
of a misspelled word?
I get yelled at when the
coffee I make is wrong.
Remember, he likes black
coffee to cure hangovers.
There was this one time his secretary
made him an instant coffee.
I was just the one who gave it to him.
He cursed me out.
That bad?
- I can’t believe you married my Dad
- You said it.
He just gaslighted you.
I didn’t know he was that terrible.
I guess, my love wasn’t
enough to change him.
I just suffered more.
I want to get out of here.
Can you come with me?
Why is Dad so bitter?
‘Cause he drinks black coffee.
Were you being funny?
Christine?
After you made love,
how often does he beat you?
Once a week?
Twice a week?
Almost everyday.
Particularly, when the business isn’t good.
There are days when–
he’s really affectionate.
You’d think he’s a changed man
and he’s sorry.
You know.
Especially when he’s not in the mood,
and I make mistakes.
So after all that, you’d
still sleep with him?
Most of the time he just forces me.
Do you love him?
Stop it Ryan, I’m your stepmom.
Aren’t you comfortable with me?
I know you didn’t marry my father for love.
You know what?
I’ve always had a crush on you.
I know how Dad abuses you.
That’s why no one will
understand you, like I do.
You know what Tin?
I remember everything.
We made love.
We had so much fun.
We’ve been through a lot.
That was a mistake and
it won’t happen again.
By the way, Mom hired
a private investigator.
You or your mother?
Stop this nonsense.
You should be thanking me.
‘Cause I’m protecting you.
Protection from what?
Huh?
Or do you mean harassment?
Time is ticking Christine, don’t let
anyone be like that missing boy toy.
Missing boy toy?
How is your boy toy?
I don’t know.
He ghosted me.
Hilda’s boyfriend?
Sorry, I thought he was your boyfriend.
Don’t do anything stupid.
And be cautious.
If you’re seeing someone,
you should tell me now.
That’s a warning.
You know what Ryan, If I
hadn't known your father–
I would assume you were just joking.
But I’ll tell you this.
You resent your father.
So don’t act like him.
Hey, bitch!
Is this you?
Son of a bitch,
this is you!
Ma'am, maybe we can talk about it.
Talk about it?
- You’re my husband’s mistress!
- I’m not, ma’am.
- You thought I wouldn’t find you.
- No, his my client–
Your husband’s my client, ma’am.
Oh, so my husband’s your customer?
Ma’am maybe–
You’re a slut.
- Whore!
- They might hear–
Ma’am they might hear you.
So what, are you scared?
You’re scared you might get caught?
‘Cause, what you’re doing is illegal.
- Police! Police!
- Motherfucker, I told you to shut up!
- Fuck you!
- Police!
- Shut the fuck up!
Tin, what’s this emergency
you’re talking about?
Your boy toy–
The one that ghosted you.
Do you have updates on him?
I don’t check anymore.
I don’t see him posting
anything on social media.
Besides, if he needs me he’ll contact me.
Can you please check,
his social media page.
Why are you so anxious?
Why are you so invested in him?
What?
Hilda, what?
Oh my god, Tin.
People are posting condolences on his page.
He died.
Oh my god, he was murdered.
My god.
How did you know?
Hilda, it’s Ryan.
What?
He mistook your boyfriend for mine
after seeing a picture of the three of us.
That’s why.
That's what he was saying, and I assumed
he was joking.
That fucking man-child.
Tin, this is my fault.
I should’ve checked on him.
I wish I could have just
let him follow me around.
‘Cause that’s how he is.
No Hilda, you didn’t do anything wrong.
This is Ryan’s fault.
Tin, we need to tell the police.
Do you think I hadn't considered that?
We don’t have evidence,
aside from what he says.
And also, Stella will find a way to
make sure Ryan doesn’t go to prison.
We don’t stand a chance, Hilda.
Please help me on this Tin, please.
I will.
Please.
Hi love.
You’re deep in thought again.
Love.
Let's not see each other for now.
Why?
Ryan is dangerous,
he’s a murderer.
I’m not afraid of him.
I’m worried for you.
You don’t even trust
that I can protect you.
People like Ryan are cowards.
He feeds on other people's fears, but
he’s weak for people who're fearless.
Say what you want,
I will not risk your safety.
We should take a break.
Don’t I have a say in this?
None.
I don't care if you get mad
at me, I'd rather accept that
than lose you because of Ryan.
Tom.
How are you?
Hey.
- Oh, what happened?
- Hey, hey.
Wait.
It was just an aggressive wife.
Again?
Well, what's new.
You know what Marie, just leave the club.
And stop whatever this is.
Leave that life behind.
What am I supposed to do, Jasmine?
How am I going to pay
the bills and earn a living?
I’m not like you.
- This is all I know.
- Yeah, all you know.
I’ve heard that before.
You know,
people can do whatever
they want if they really want to.
It's not true that you
can’t do anything else.
What will I do if I don’t have an income?
Here, this will cover our
food and monthly bills.
This is a lot– Jasmine,
you got your first pay?
Wow.
Save it.
Don’t worry about me,
I’m not your responsibility.
Wait.
I'll decide what my
responsibilities should be.
When I say this is for us.
This is for us.
Thank you.
It’s like we’re a married couple.
Come here.
Wait, it hurts.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry I forgot.
Jasmine’s very seductive.
Okay, game.
Smile.
One more.
Jasmine, are you okay? You look distracted.
I can’t– I can’t find my motivation.
Tom, come here for a sec.
Let’s motivate your model.
Look at Tom.
Imagine you’re in love with him and
you want to kiss him.
Okay?
Okay, ready.
Love.
Let's not see each other for now.
Let’s take a break.
Are you okay?
Benito.
Benito?
Benito!
Benito, you’re hurting me.
Don't do this to me, Benito.
Benito.
Lara!
Hello, Jasmine?
Can we talk?
I have a question.
Hello Christine.
I had fun Jasmine.
I enjoyed your company.
I enjoyed your company
more, Miss Christine.
I wish you were my mother.
My life would’ve been happier.
Why so serious?
What do you call it when you love someone
but you’re also attracted to someone else?
That’s cool.
I really really like him.
This is the first time I've felt this way.
I like him so much that it affects my work.
If he can't give you what you need
then let go.
I already lost my daughter.
I can’t afford to lose you too.