(A new teacher)
(North Pole Teacher)
You know the lines, right?
(The 1st class as a team of 3...)
(wasn't easy.)
(This is tough.)
(Today's homework: Memorize the script)
(Will they be able to perform without the script next time?)
(The long-awaited music director, CO KUN, has arrived.)
(The music they waited for is perfect!)
With footsteps.
(The music and sound effects will be completed with the kids.)
(TPNC has finally come together.)
(The 4 teachers' 1st night together was filled with laughter.)
(Sunday morning filled with the scent of rain)
(Tae Ri is still sound asleep.)
(Getting up)
(His sleeping pose is quite artistic.)
(He looks artistic too.)
(Startled)
(Things seem quite awkward.)
Why are you sleeping over there?
I must've felt hot and ended up sleeping down here.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
You startled me.
I had the weirdest dream.
What was it about?
All the senior entertainers showed up.
For real.
From Yu Jae Seok...
to Lee Kyung Sil.
I'm serious.
- Everyone was gathered together.
-  Why'd you have such a dream?
(The rookie entertainer dreams of other entertainers.)
(After waking up, they make their beds first.)
(Smiling)
(The Running Lover runs even today.)
Why am I the only one gaining weight?
I don't understand. Nobody else is getting fat.
Why do I get all puffy?
Well, it's because I ate a ton.
That's the only reason.
I ate too much.
(The humanization of self-reflection)
It smells good.
Hold on. Try smelling this.
This is the scent we're used to.
(Barista KUN is in the Mushroom House.)
And this is the scent of good coffee beans.
Should I say it smells floral?
You like coffee because it's like music, don't you?
- The two have a lot in common.
-  I see.
(Barista KUN's pour-over coffee)
I'm not sure if you'll like it.
- That's a small amount of coffee.
-  Right?
I always thought bland meant less coffee...
and strong meant more coffee.
No, never.
- Never?
-  The richness of coffee.
The intensity and richness of coffee...
have to do with the temperature of the water.
(Said by Barista KUN)
(Drinking)
It tastes out of this world.
Is there no need to pour water...
- around it?
-  No.
No?
The coffee ends up with an unpleasant aftertaste.
- Unpleasant...
-  Unpleasant aftertaste.
"Unpleasant aftertaste."
- Because of the filter?
-  Yes.
That prevents the coffee from having an aromatic smell.
(The curious customer and friendly Barista KUN)
(Drinking it iced this time)
Not bad.
It's much more sour.
Make it into iced coffee, and it turns into juice.
It's...
not my style.
I need to dilute it more.
It needs more water.
- Is that so?
-  Yes.
"Dilute."
I wasn't sure what you meant by that.
Adding more water will make it more enjoyable.
(Sipping)
- It's good.
-  Right?
(Having morning coffee together with Barista KUN)
Kangnam should wake up soon.
We should check...
if he's alive or not.
(Cut out for the caravan, not moving an inch)
(Knocking)
- Kangnam.
-  Yes?
It's time for you to wake up.
Got it.
- Come out, okay?
-  Okay.
(Everyone is awake now.)
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Shall we get going now?
(Today's weather: Strong winds)
It's a tornado!
Dorothy's house is going to fly away.
- When's Ms. Kim coming?
-  I want to pick apples already.
(Where are the students waiting for the teachers?)
(A vast apple orchard)
How big.
- It's huge.
-  Right?
It's red over here.
This one is big.
- How pretty.
-  The trees are so tall.
(During the fourth class)
- Hi.
-  Hello.
You see...
Would you like to visit our apple orchard?
Yes, we'd love to.
Are you inviting us over?
- Thank you, Ju Eun.
-  No problem.
- Hi.
-  Hi.
- Gosh.
-  Ju Eun.
I'm Ju Eun's mom.
- Hi.
-  Hi.
Your apple orchard is huge, Ju Eun.
We heard we could pick...
- some apples today.
-  That's right.
The kids know...
- how to pick them, right?
-  Yes.
- Let's ask the kids.
-  Go ahead.
- Even better.
-  Yes, even better.
The students could become teachers one day.
Exactly.
- Why don't we get going?
-  Okay, this way.
- Let's go.
-  Go!
Ju Eun, how do you pick the apples up there?
Using the ladder.
Using a ladder, not shaking the tree?
That'll bruise the apples.
The apples will get bruised.
- That didn't cross my mind.
-  We can't bruise the apples.
No, we can't.
She's an apple expert.
How much is it per square meter?
Well...
It's just that huge.
- I'm shocked.
-  If it's this big...
You're a rich landowner.
- Won Jin.
-  Won Jin.
- Won Jin!
-  You scared me.
- You look like the owner.
-  Come over here.
- Come.
-  He does look like the owner.
- Gosh.
-  Hurry.
You're finally here.
- Won Jin.
-  How cute.
- Hey, guys.
-  Hi.
- Hi.
- There are a lot of apples, right?
-  Hi.
- There are tons.
- Introduce him.
-  Hi.
- Do you know me?
-  I've seen you before.
He knows him.
Do you know me? Have you seen me somewhere?
Have you seen him somewhere?
- A celebrity has finally come!
-  Right?
- I'm a celebrity, right?
-  Do you know him?
- Yes.
-  You do?
The celebrity you've been waiting for is here.
- What about me? Right?
-  You're a celebrity.
Their reactions are different from when I came.
(Upset)
Guys, don't you see an unfamiliar face among us today?
- Yes.
-  Right?
Do you know who he is?
"I Live Alone."
- "I Live Alone." - "I Live Alone."
- He was in "I Live Alone." - "I Live Alone" is powerful.
An autograph, please.
- All right.
-  The kids are happy to see him.
- An autograph, please.
-  Where have you seen him?
We need a nickname for him. What should it be?
You can call me Mr. CO KUN...
or Mr. CO.
- How about Mr. CO?
-  How about it?
- Mr. CO.
-  Let's go with Mr. CO.
Guys, let's all greet Mr. CO together.
- Hi, Mr. CO.
-  Hi.
- Hi.
(A celebrity's attitude)
We've got four teachers now.
- That's right.
-  Yes.
The acting class...
- has four teachers now.
-  Four, right?
- You have four teachers.
-  Yes.
- We might continue.
-  Shall we?
Do you want to try this on, Ha Yun?
- What?
-  We can see that.
We need to pick apples today. Do you know how to do it?
- Yes.
-  Yes.
- Tell us.
-  We're the only ones unaware.
- You don't?
-  Grab one like this,
- and twist it.
-  Do you not use scissors?
- No.
-  You can use scissors.
Twist and pull.
- Twist and pull.
-  Twist and pull.
Shinano Gold, Gamhong, and Fuji.
What? Sorry?
- Tsugaru.
-  The types of apples?
- Apples.
-  Tsugaru.
- The apples.
-  Are there...
- many types of apples here?
-  Yes.
Summer King. Most of them...
- are Fuji apples.
-  What's here?
- Muji?
-  Fuji.
Most of them are Fuji apples.
We've got a handful of apple experts here.
Guide us well. We don't know how to do it.
- Okay.
-  Good.
Guys, let's split into teams and compete.
- I'm in.
-  We'll split into teams...
and compete to see who can pick the most apples.
Okay, which teacher was here the longest?
- Ms. Kim.
-  Ms. Kim...
- and Mr. Choi, right?
-  Potato Teacher.
- Potato Teacher, right?
-  Yes.
The two will stand side by side.
We will line up behind the leader...
we want to be on a team with.
- Potato Teacher or Ms. Kim.
-  No.
- Take your time.
-  Line up.
- I can't decide.
-  Hey.
- Ha Yun.
-  Yes?
Don't you want to be a team with me?
- No.
-  What?
- Don't you?
-  No.
- All right.
-  I'm okay.
- Do we line up too?
-  Yes.
We have to line up too.
- Us too?
-  Yes. Stand facing forward.
You'll be able to tell which teacher is the students' favorite.
Today was supposed to be easygoing.
- Right.
-  Whatever.
- The respect you've earned so far.
-  No?
Line up behind the teacher you like more, okay?
Go.
- Please be sincere about it.
-  Over here.
What color jacket am I wearing today? Apple red, right?
- Okay.
-  I'm good at picking apples.
From what I see,
one teacher is going to get hurt.
(Already a bad feeling someone will get hurt)
- I'm wearing apple red today.
-  Oh, dear.
Gosh, I feel bad.
I can't watch it.
(Let me look away.)
I can't...
Gosh, I feel bad.
(Changing his mind)
Another change of heart.
Someone is going to get deeply hurt.
My heart is pounding.
This is really scary.
It wasn't bad up until a minute ago.
- I'm choosing Potato Teacher.
-  What?
- He's good at picking apples.
-  It has changed.
- What?
-  I'm changing sides.
- Come over here.
-  What's going on?
- All right.
-  Five.
- Hold on.
-  Hold on.
Someone is going to get hurt for real.
Your last chance. Five seconds.
- Five seconds.
-  Five seconds.
- Five, four, three, - Five, four, three,
- two, one.
-  Let's go.
(How did the teams end up?)
- All right.
-  Why did we have to do this?
We'll settle with this result.
- I'm calling it.
-  Okay.
Turn around when you're ready.
(The result will come out right away.)
- One, two, - Two,
- three.
-  I'm sorry!
(I'm sorry!)
I'm sorry!
(Potato Teacher: 1 versus Ms. Kim: 6)
It was a pleasure until now.
- Ha Yun, let's go watch baseball.
-  Okay.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
- Listen.
-  Come on.
- The other kids kept contemplating.
-  I see.
But Ha Yun chose you right away.
- I'm serious.
-  Ha Yun.
- He's devoted.
-  Ms. Kim...
is popular with the public,
- while you have core fans.
-  By the way...
- If this gives you any comfort, - For real.
- the kids aren't all that genuine.
-  No, they aren't.
- We're picking apples, - Right.
so I'm curious why you all chose Ms. Kim.
- Apple.
-  Apple.
- Right?
-  That's the reason?
- The color.
-  I couldn't decide...
- all morning.
-  Ms. Kim is wearing...
- something red.
-  Thanks.
I'm sorry, Mr. Choi.
I'll treat you to ice cream.
He'll treat you to ice cream.
Whatever. From now on, our class will be...
- Can't you be gentle?
-  I'm sorry!
- Seriously, you're too...
-  Listen.
- What?
-  You're scaring us.
- After the voting, - Mr. Choi.
- you've become aggressive.
-  Totally.
- Your voice is...
-  No.
- I'm being gentle.
-  Calm down.
For real, we're not playing baseball anymore.
- Be gentle.
-  Okay.
-  Good.
But right now, the teams are a bit...
- Can't I just...
-  Do you want to join us, Kyung Mo?
- Okay, I wanted to be on this team.
-  Let Kyung Mo...
- change teams.
-  Okay.
Kyung Mo is going to help Potato Teacher.
Kyung Mo, we can win, right?
Yes, we can totally win.
All right, the teams have been split now.
- It's settled now.
-  To celebrate it.
Those in Ms. Kim's team,
- raise your hand.
-  Okay.
- Team Tae Ri.
-  Raise your hand,
-  Ms. Kim.
- Team Tae Ri.
-  Good.
Team Potato,
- put your hands up!
-  Yes!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
Seriously, though. Let me just say this, kids.
- I won't go easy on you.
-  Hold on.
You're too sensitive.
- Why are you so sensitive?
-  It's just...
Why did that sound so scary just now?
- We'll show them.
-  We'll show you.
Let's show them too, guys.
- Yes.
-  Okay.
- I'll get as many as I can.
-  Great.
I won't go easy on you!
- You need to be gentle.
-  What made you so sensitive?
I won't go easy on you, even if you're older than me.
We also need an expert on apples, though.
You have one.
Oh, we have an apple expert.
- Yes, you do.
-  He knows a lot about apples.
- She's also an apple expert.
-  We have one too.
- Not me.
-  Team Potato.
But we don't know how to pick apples,
so you have to teach us.
Please teach us over here.
Teach me.
- Red ones.
-  Red ones?
- You pick the red ones...
and big ones.
Big ones?
Okay, so how about this? Is this worth picking?
- This one?
-  How do we pick it?
- Show us.
-  Like this.
- You grab it like this.
-  Okay.
And you pick it sideways.
- Wait, what?
-  What? How?
- Can I try it?
-  Like this.
- And then...
-  Should I try this one?
- Yes.
-  Is this good?
-  All right!
I got it, right?
- I figured it out.
-  I'm pretty good.
It only took me half a second.
Yes, it only takes half a second.
We already won.
I'm going to treat it like a sport.
Teach Ms. Kim.
- Okay, let's teach her together.
-  Okay.
- We'll all show her.
-  How do I do it?
- This one?
-  Grab it.
There's rainwater.
Sideways?
You just pick it sideways.
My first apple ever!
Kyung Mo, if we're losing,
take the apples from their basket, and put them in ours.
- That's right.
-  Got it?
- That doesn't sound right.
-  It doesn't?
- But that's how the world is.
-  It's a bit...
That sounds like cheating.
- Let's do it. We're going to win.
-  Okay.
- Let's show them.
-  We'll show them.
We only have athletes on our team.
We're total athletes.
- I'm a good runner.
-  There you go.
You're a good runner. In 1, 2, 3.
- Hey!
-  Let's go.
Hooray, Team Tae Ri!
- Let's go!
-  Let's go!
All right!
That's so unorganized.
We were very disciplined.
We'll start, everyone?
I'll count down from five.
- Five, four, - Let's go.
- three, two, one.
-  But I don't have a basket!
Start!
All right, it's begun. Start picking!
- I don't have a basket!
-  Pick them!
Let's go!
Kids, let's start picking.
Hurry up.
There are lots of apples here!
- Come with me, Hyo Min.
-  Okay!
Let's show them our teamwork!
(They formed a 4th-grade duo.)
(Lost in it)
Collect them here.
Okay.
(Everyone is focusing on picking apples.)
What?
All right!
Should we focus on this area?
- I see lots of them.
-  Over there?
- Here? Pick these?
-  Yes.
(Mr. CO's harvest)
This is red, but...
- We can't pick it?
-  It's too small.
- Is it too small?
-  Yes.
Okay.
We still have to pick pretty ones.
Yes, good-looking ones.
All right.
You have to check them first.
Look through them thoroughly.
Are these...
I already picked them.
Do we have to take a look first?
- Yes.
-  I see.
Can you help me pick this one?
That one? I'm coming.
That one? Is this a good apple?
- Pick this one?
-  Yes.
- Here.
-  Thanks.
- How does it look?
-  Good.
Good?
The light ones...
Here!
We also have to pick light-colored ones!
That one?
- Yes, the light-colored ones.
-  Okay.
Pick the light-colored ones too.
I will.
- Pick this one? Not yet?
-  That's not...
(Failed)
(The apple taster helps the team.)
All right.
Yes! This is awesome.
It's full!
It's full.
(The taster is happy.)
We already filled our basket.
- We got them, Hyo Min!
-  Great.
Give them to Ju Eun.
No, that's okay. I'll carry these.
Okay.
(Hopping)
I'll pick it.
What do you need? That one?
Yes.
- Help us, Ms. Kim.
-  Let's go back to the basket.
- Okay. Where?
-  That one!
- Here.
-  It's so pretty.
- I can't reach it.
-  I got it, Hyo Min!
You guys are so fast.
- Here!
-  Yes!
You're doing great.
- We're losing.
-  What?
They have so many apples.
Let's go over there.
You're really good at this.
- Hey, that one!
-  What?
That one looks good!
(Stealing their apple)
Hyo Min, be quiet from now on.
You're a thief!
(A naughty 25-year-old)
Ms. Kim, Potato Teacher stole our apple.
You can't do that!
You can't steal it.
- Wait!
-  How many did you steal?
- Wait.
-  How could you...
- I didn't steal it.
-  Hold on.
- I really didn't.
-  You picked this many?
- There's no way.
-  These are ours.
They keep falling.
Let's pick them up.
These were picked by nature.
You're really good, Ha Yun.
- Gosh.
-  Ju Eun.
You're our ace player.
- She's fast.
-  You pick them so well.
(The ace players on each team lead the team.)
(The last spurt)
Won Jin, I picked a lot. Put them in the red basket.
Kyung Mo, can I pick this one?
Yes, go ahead.
(Sensing a crisis)
Hurry up!
It's an emergency! Hurry and pick them!
Emergency!
- Hurry up!
-  Are you okay?
Hurry up!
- Hurry up?
-  Yes, hurry up!
You told me not to pick random apples.
Now, you picked all the small ones.
(The taster is in a rush.)
- Okay.
-  You picked so many.
All right.
(Working hard until the end)
Everyone, you have five seconds!
Five, four,
three, two, one!
The end!
- It's over, guys. Stop.
-  Stop!
- It's over!
-  All right.
Guys.
It'll take too long to count them one at a time.
- The owner, Ju Eun's mom, - Yes.
will judge the winner.
Go and get your mom.
Here she comes.
Her mom is here.
Pick ours!
We worked hard and picked these apples.
- Right.
-  There were two teams.
Now, you will look at them. And decide who the winner is.
- Which team picked more apples?
-  Okay.
- Do you understand?
-  Yes.
It doesn't count if there are too many scratches.
- Too many what?
-  Scratches.
- Yes.
-  Like scars.
-  That's great.
- This one looks okay.
-  This one has a scratch.
- Well...
-  No.
This one's fine because it's always been there.
- It's always been there.
-  It was already there.
And everyone has a scar.
You grow up pretty only if you have scars.
Check this one.
I have many scratches.
- First off...
-  First off,
how does it look at a glance?
- This is so hard.
-  This one....
- Sorry? It's hard?
-  Yes.
If you had to give them to a customer...
If you had to sell them,
which one would you sell?
Please!
- These ones look better.
-  These ones?
Yes.
(Team Potato wins.)
(Yes!)
(Team Tae Ri loses.)
These ones are fine too.
- These aren't that bad.
-  But...
- But...
-  But those ones are a bit better.
- Just a bit. We won by a hair.
-  Yes.
- These are better products?
You should have examined them before you picked them.
We actually had...
- Kyung Mo...
-  Kyung Mo.
Kyung Mo stopped us from picking poor ones.
- Did you stop them?
-  Yes.
Oh, really?
- And he was like, - We followed his instructions.
"Come over here," and I came,
and he said, "Pick this one."
All I did was pick them.
Did you really?
(A nine-year-old's strict apple philosophy)
How does it look?
- Good.
-  Good?
(Today's MVP, Kyung Mo)
All right, then. How does it feel to win?
How do you feel, Kyung Mo?
Product value is more important.
Product value is more important?
I'm sorry, but do you own this orchard?
Everything he says is impressive.
- Yes.
-  Product value is important.
- Great work, everyone.
-  Let's give it up.
- You picked the right ones.
-  Yes.
Let's go and eat, kids.
Did you apologize?
No? Tell him to apologize.
Hey.
- Do Hyun, you have to apologize.
-  I did.
- No, you didn't!
-  He said you didn't.
- But I did.
-  But he said you didn't.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
- I'll explain.
-  Okay.
Do Hyun held Hyo Min's hand,
but there was snot, apparently.
So, Hyo Min has been feeling bad about it.
But he never got his apology.
He wants to say sorry now, but he won't accept it.
What should we do?
- What do we tell them?
-  Hyo Min,
can I tell you something?
Ms. Kim and I also argued a lot.
We fight all the time.
We were actually in a fight.
- We're serious.
-  Seriously.
We'll show you what we did.
(They tell the kids their own story.)
Look. Here's how we made up, Hyo Min.
Here's how we made up.
In 1, 2, 3.
- I'm sorry, friend.
-  I'm sorry, friend.
- Thank you, and I love you.
-  Thank you, and I love you.
- Yuck!
-  What?
- What do you think?
-  That's how we made up.
- Hyo Min, I'm sorry.
-  Whatever.
- Do it together.
-  Why don't we give it a try?
- Let's hold hands and try it.
-  Yes.
Hyo Min.
Come on, Hyo Min.
(Hyo Min gets sulky and leaves.)
But he said sorry, right?
Ju Eun, what should we do to help them make up?
No!
(Ju Eun comforts him without a word.)
- Do Hyun, are you all right?
-  Yes.
This is part of growing.
Okay.
I also got into a lot of fights in elementary school.
And I cried a lot.
But this will teach you...
how to make up with friends.
- Mr. Choi.
-  Yes?
You had Eclipse mints, didn't you?
Yes, how did you know?
I could smell it.
- You even know about Eclipse?
-  Yes.
Do you want one?
- No, it's okay.
-  No?
I got this one!
Really?
- I'll pick an apple too.
-  I picked a really pretty one.
(He picks an apple and wipes it cleanly.)
Wouldn't it be better to give this to Hyo Min?
Yes, give him this.
- Say, "Accept my apology." - Go to him.
(He got an apple to apologize.)
Hyo Min.
- Will you accept my apology?
-  "Accept my apology."
I got a good one.
Isn't it pretty?
Hyo Min looks...
- Do you accept it?
-  Will you accept my apology?
You can keep this, and I'll keep this one.
Okay, here you go.
(They exchange apples and make up.)
He finally accepted my apology.
Are you all right?
(And the kids made peace.)
When Hyo Min and Do Hyun had a fight,
I thought, "It happens to elementary school boys."
I did the same.
It's natural for them.
But I believe you need to make things clear...
before you make up.
Do Hyun gave Hyo Min an apple, right?
That was so mature.
It made me reflect on myself.
I learn a lot from them.
Watching these elementary school kids.
Yes.
Let's go have snacks!
- Yes!
-  Let's go.
Come on. No way!
- Jjajangmyeon?
-  It's jjajangmyeon.
Are those fried dumplings?
It's jjajangmyeon!
Should we start eating, guys?
- Yes!
-  Thank you for the food!
You can't wait to eat it, can you?
(Let's mix it.)
All done.
I can't remember the last time I had jjajangmyeon.
This is good jjajangmyeon.
(Slurping)
Eat slowly, okay?
It's delicious.
(Sucking)
(The teachers enjoy it as well.)
(Slurping)
It tastes better after working hard, doesn't it?
(It tastes way better after hard work.)
We can bring phones and computers.
(Enjoying)
You should come over to my house.
- Can I?
-  Yes. Today!
Can I come over today? What will you do for me?
- At my house?
-  Yes.
I'll give you ten dollars.
(I'm Kim Kyung Mo, a generous 9-year-old.)
I'll come for free. Why would I accept that?
(Reading the room)
Why am I the only one who's left-handed?
- What?
-  It means you're special.
I've always wanted to be left-handed.
Really?
(He tries using his left hand.)
(And he tries using his right hand.)
- Eat with your left hand.
-  Okay.
- Okay?
You don't have to force yourself to use your right hand.
You can just eat with your left hand.
- Is he left-handed?
-  Yes.
- Left-handed...
-  He was using his right hand...
on purpose because everyone else was using their right hands.
- Many geniuses are left-handed.
-  You're a genius.
Left-handed baseball pitchers are rare.
- You're rare. You know that.
-  Yes.
Right?
(He comfortably uses his left hand, thanks to them.)
Teacher, this is recording.
Yes, I'm recording it.
(Mr. CO brought a recorder.)
I'll show you.
- I want to try it.
-  Yes, listen to it.
- Do you hear it?
-  Yes.
Do you want to record yourself eating jjajangmyeon?
(He tries ASMR while eating jjajangmyeon.)
(So cute)
That's so interesting!
Right?
I want to try it too!
Bamboo helicopter!
Guys, isn't this so fun?
- I hear it.
-  Right?
- What?
-  Hi.
I'm their music teacher and music director.
The music I make only exists for the kids.
This is a kids' play, so I feel like...
they'll find it fun...
only if they can tell...
that they did it once it's finished.
We're going to make songs for our play...
with the sounds that you make.
Yes, I hear it.
(Squeak)
That's great. Well done.
Awesome. Just a little more.
That sounds so pretty.
(He'll use their sounds to make music and sound effects.)
One, two, three, four, stomp.
I thought I could replace the drum sound...
with their stomps or claps.
(The Witch's laughter)
That was an actual witch.
Various animal sounds.
(Various animal sounds)
I also recorded sound effects that kids might find fun.
(They make various sound effects together.)
Here goes Potato Teacher.
(Potato Teacher's horn sound)
(Blowing an airhorn)
(Stopping)
Did his voice crack?
- His voice cracked at the end.
-  Mr. Choi.
You just had a reality check, didn't you?
- No, I didn't.
-  A reality check?
You sounded so embarrassed.
- Oh, my gosh.
-  I didn't.
(On the ground)
Poor him.
- His face turned red.
-  No, it didn't.
(A red potato)
All these sounds are memories to the children...
and the teachers who worked on them.
I hope it's like...
going through a photo album after a long time.
That's what I want it to be like.
That was great, though.
All done, everyone.
Great work.
(The sounds of the acting class are coming soon.)
Guys, we have a new teacher, right?
I'd like to show Mr. CO...
what we've been working on.
Remember the Wicked Witch of the West's scene?
The one we practiced.
(They practiced the Wicked Witch of the West's scene two days ago.)
(However,)
(the kids couldn't memorize all the lines.)
(So, they gave them homework of memorizing the script.)
We can go from Page 9 to Page 12...
without looking at the script.
- Seriously?
-  Really?
- Really!
-  Everyone can?
We even made a group chatroom and practiced.
- Really?
-  Really?
- We should check it out, then.
-  We should.
Can you show us?
- Yes!
-  All right, then.
Eun Soo isn't here at the moment,
so we need someone to play Dorothy today.
- Who will it be?
-  Who will it be?
I'm Dorothy.
- Okay, thank you in advance.
-  You're Dorothy for the day.
Yes, I'm Dorothy for the day.
Let's start...
the performance.
Let's start, then.
It's set in a dark forest, and the curtain opens.
- Dorothy and her friends appear.
-  Let's go to the center.
The Wicked Witch still has her face covered.
Sniff.
I smell fire.
Scarecrow.
What? Fire? It's going to burn all my straws!
- No!
-  No!
Dorothy!
(Shivering)
We meet at last.
I knew you would go to meet the Wizard of Oz.
(Seeing Ju Eun the Witch for the first time)
But these are regular shoes.
With those shoes, I'll be the strongest in the universe,
She's good.
and I can take the Emerald Castle and Oz!
Then, I cannot give you these shoes.
The Witch shoots fire.
- Props.
-  Here.
- Fire!
-  Fire!
- Take me away.
-  I'll take you.
No!
- She's taking me!
-  Dorothy!
(He quickly sets up the lake for the next scene.)
The curtain closes.
- Great.
-  Now, the curtain opens.
First, the Witch and Dorothy.
They're having a quarrel.
- No!
-  Her friends arrived later.
(Her friends are on the other side of the lake.)
Oh, no, Dorothy.
She's on the other side of the lake.
How do we get rid of the lake... No, the witch.
And cross the lake...
- "Bring Dorothy back." - Bring Dorothy back?
So cute.
Let's save her.
But the Wicked Witch of the West is too powerful.
We won't stand a chance, even if we work together.
But the Wicked Witch of the West is made of fire,
so she'll disappear if she touches water.
(They flawlessly say the lines back and forth.)
But how do we cross the lake?
I have my strong legs,
- so I'll go and save Dorothy.
-  So I'll...
The lion crosses, guys!
(He jumps over the lake with his strong legs.)
- Put her in the lake.
-  He put her in the lake.
No, I can't believe you figured out my weakness.
Water is my weakness.
I had so many wicked plans!
Unfortunately, I must go.
Yes! The Witch exits.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Yes, the Lion has done it!
-  Yes, the Lion has done it!
- Thank you, Lion!
-  Thank you, Lion!
(Perfect to the final line)
Three stamps!
(Clapping)
- You guys are good.
-  Well done.
- Hyo Min, you were so good.
-  That was fantastic.
I've never seen them work together as one.
We told them that they should memorize the lines.
But to be honest, I never thought it was possible.
I thought that they wouldn't be able to do it since they were kids.
But that made me realize it could actually work.
They just memorized the whole script.
We had so little time.
I felt hopeful that we might actually pull it off.
Kids,
when Mr. CO KUN leaves today,
we won't be able to see him for a few days.
- I'll see you on TV.
-  I'll be back soon.
Great job today.
- Good work, everyone!
-  Thank you for your hard work.
- Thanks.
-  Bye.
- Yes!
-  Bye-bye.
- Bye, Mr. CO.
-  Thanks, guys.
It wasn't the end.
Mr. CO will definitely...
come back to see them before the rehearsal.
I'll take a photo of you too.
Will you?
(Click)
I'll be back soon.
(Mr. CO will return with his songs.)
(A new week begins after Mr. CO left.)
(Yongheung Elementary School Mini Autumn Field Day)
(The school bus arrives.)
(Eun Soo from acting class shows up.)
(Hyo Min also shows up with messy hair.)
(It's a special day!)
(Yongheung Elementary School Mini Autumn Field Day)
(Meanwhile, in the Mushroom House)
(Opening)
(Kangnam woke up early at 7:50am.)
(Unknown ingredients)
(And there's a letter.)
(Hi, Ms. Kim. It's Ahn Sung Jae.)
(Thank you for giving me the chance to cook delicious food...)
(for the children of Yongheung Elementary School.)
(I sent you the necessary ingredients beforehand.)
(I'll see you soon. From Ahn Sung Jae.)
(From Ahn Sung Jae?)
Look at all those apples.
Mungyeong apples.
(There's a guest early in the morning.)
(Anybody here?)
Excuse me?
Ms. Kim?
Hi, I'm chef Ahn Sung Jae.
It's the school's field day,
and I got the chance to cook for the children.
And the timing was good.
So, I've come here.
(Screaming)
Seriously?
(They hear the bell.)
Did the bell ring?
I'm all over the place.
I didn't even hear it.
(Surprised)
Oh, hi.
(Welcome.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- Come on in.
-  It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
-  Welcome.
Oh, boy.
- Here.
-  It's a pleasure.
- Hello.
-  It's nice to meet you.
What was it? I didn't see it.
- It's nothing much.
-  The Heart Shiitake Mushroom House?
- Yes.
-  Yes.
- It looks like a mushroom.
-  It's the Mushroom House.
- Oh, the Mushroom House.
-  Yes, come on in.
When are you leaving?
Later today.
- Really?
-  Yes, in the evening.
- You should sleep over.
-  Here?
- Is there a room for me?
-  It's huge.
- We also have a caravan.
-  Really?
- You could even sleep here.
-  Yes.
- And the wooden bench outside.
-  Right.
It's lovely here.
- Should we...
-  What time is it right now?
- What time is it?
-  What's the time?
- It's 9:30am.
-  It's 9:30am?
When does the food need to be ready?
- Noon.
-  Noon?
- Don't you need just 30 minutes?
-  Should we start?
Well,
- Thirty minutes...
-  we can start later.
- Exactly.
-  We'll take a short break.
- Yes, you just got here too.
-  Oh, I see.
- Thanks for the apples.
-  Eat up.
- We picked them ourselves.
-  Yesterday?
- Where was this?
-  Here.
That means it's from the principal.
- The principal?
-  Yes.
- What's it like?
-  It's our welcome food.
What do you think?
It's rich in sweetness.
- Right? It's so sweet.
-  Yes.
He doesn't just say, "Sweet."
- It's rich in sweetness.
-  "Rich in sweetness."
We should talk like that. "Rich in sweetness."
"It's rich in sweetness."
(She learns it right away.)
We have to come up with a nickname for you.
Did you have a nickname growing up?
- Me?
-  Yes.
- Is there an animal you resemble?
-  An animal?
- He's like...
-  You look like a polar bear.
No, he's kind of like...
- This type of animal.
-  A raccoon?
- No.
-  A squirrel?
- But...
-  It's in Australia.
many people tell me...
- that I look like that whale.
-  Whale?
What kind of whale was it?
- Orca?
-  Beluga whale?
- Beluga whale?
-  Oh, a beluga whale!
Beluga!
- I see the resemblance.
-  Beluga!
- The way it smiles.
-  He does! The white whale.
(He clearly has the face of a beluga whale.)
He does.
Should we call him Beluga Teacher?
Should it be Beluga Teacher or Whale Teacher?
Whale Teacher sounds good. It's easier.
- Whale Teacher.
-  Okay.
- All right.
-  All right.
Whale Teacher it is.
- I'll prepare the food soon.
-  Okay.
Can you tell us what you're making?
Today, tomato rose pasta...
- Rose pasta!
-  Yes.
I wasn't sure what kids would like, so...
- I bet they'll love it.
-  Rose pasta sounds great.
All the restaurants are far away from here,
- so...
-  So, I thought...
about making Korean food,
but I felt like they were used to it.
So, I'm going to use ham to make a type of tangsuyuk.
It's tangsuyuk, but some kids can't eat flour,
so I'll use rice flour and starch powder...
and deep-fry it.
- And that...
-  Ripe persimmons.
Ripe or soft persimmons. I'll use that to make the sauce.
- Oh, that sounds delicious.
-  The sauce.
- It sounds so good.
-  I'll use that and vinegar...
to make tangsuyuk sauce.
And...
Korean tenderloin steak...
and chocolate pudding with whipped cream.
You know, something soft.
I came up with those.
I'm not sure if they'll like it, though.
I hope they like it.
(It's 10am, and they have 2 hours until lunchtime.)
- We should assist you, - Yes.
so tell us what to do.
- First, wash your hands.
-  Okay.
(Act 1, Division of Labor at the Mushroom House)
- We have to trim these, right?
-  Yes, we do.
- Okay.
-  Let's chop them.
Broccolini is already washed, but...
- Still...
-  Broccolini?
Broccolini. When it ends with "lini,"
it means it's small.
- Baby broccoli.
-  It's a different kind, though.
I've never seen that before.
Pick the small leaves.
Okay.
(Plucking off the small leaves)
Kind of like this.
(She trims it just like she was taught.)
- I saw firewood outside.
-  Yes.
It would be better if you could build a fire.
- The firewood?
-  Yes.
- Do you mean this?
- This would make it better.
-  It would.
Yes.
- Should I start?
-  Yes, please.
- Okay. I'll start making it.
-  Okay.
- Please work on this.
-  Sure.
(Returning to the kitchen)
(He immediately checks the ingredients.)
Okay.
(Ripe persimmons)
With this ham...
Yes.
- Just like this.
-  Okay.
(Prepping the ingredients for deep-fried ham)
I want it to look...
like guobaorou.
I'm not going to fry small pieces.
- I'll cut them into 5 even pieces.
-  Yes, 5 pieces.
Okay.
The ham...
also contains eggs and ketchup,
so they'll go great with rice.
- That sounds nice.
-  Yes.
It's already well-balanced.
It's well-balanced.
- Right.
-  Yes, well-balanced ham.
It must be delicious.
This is perfect.
(At the fire pot)
The steaks will taste so good when cooked over this.
Kangnam!
You should check it out.
- Is it blazing?
-  Blazing.
All right.
If it's blazing,
we're going to use it in 30 to 40 minutes.
- It's going to turn into charcoal.
-  Yes, we're using charcoal.
We can add more firewood if we need more.
- I got it.
-  Yes.
(See you soon.)
Pour three bottles of milk, please.
(His next mission is to make dessert.)
- And boil it?
-  Yes.
(He pours 3 bottles of milk first.)
- For the color?
-  Yes.
(Adding cocoa powder)
Kids don't really like dark chocolate,
so I'm adding it...
to add a hint of sweet chocolate flavor.
- Do you have a whisk?
-  Whisker?
- Whisker?
-  A whisk.
I've heard of whiskey, but not a whisker.
The one you use to mix things?
- Whisker?
-  That's the one.
- Is this called a whisker?
-  A whisk.
There's a thin one and a thick one.
- The thick one.
-  Okay.
- Until it's solid enough...
-  It's harder...
because you have to tell us every little detail, isn't it?
No, I was thinking,
"You must have so many things to do here."
"I feel like I'm piling on with my cooking."
I thought you'd do everything, but we're doing all the work.
It isn't exactly the way I was expecting it to go.
- I should...
-  In my head,
my job ended with chopping those onions.
(There are more things to help him out with.)
It's going exactly as I planned,
- Really?
-  so I'm proud.
(Adding cocoa powder)
- It has to be sweet?
-  Yes.
If this doesn't make it sweet enough,
I'll have to add sugar...
- to finish it.
-  Okay.
This is... Okay.
Okay.
(The persimmons fall.)
Are you okay?
(The persimmons are crushed.)
(Flustered)
- Are you okay?
-  I'm okay.
Pretend you never saw it.
This makes it less sweet, right?
- Sorry?
-  Does that make it less sweet?
I think it'll be fine.
I think I miscalculated it.
I should have had tea...
after completely figuring out how the kitchen looks.
But I had tea as soon as I entered.
That was a bit of a crisis.
(Act 2, Whale Teacher's Crisis)
Where were you in the US?
I only stayed in California.
- California?
-  I served in the US Army.
- What? Really?
-  Yes.
- You were in the army?
- What? No way!
-  When I was in the army,
I lived in the central and the eastern US.
- Really?
-  Yes.
After I got out, I started to cook.
- Did you start as a part-timer?
-  Yes, at first.
I had no idea.
- It was...
-  Again?
(Again?)
- We should put it somewhere else.
-  The persimmon...
Yes, we'd better move them.
This...
(The persimmons are being threatened.)
(Emergency evacuation)
- That looks good.
-  What?
The persimmon is very soft.
- Sir.
-  It's all ripe.
Hey, it's a taste every kid loves.
Exactly. That was what I was going for.
It's what kids love best.
It can't be helped.
If we have the taste down, add some starch.
We'll cook it with starch until it boils.
Then this will turn thick.
- We'll cool it after that.
-  Cool it.
Kids can easily eat it then. It's simple.
We'll go with our gut.
(Eyeing the amount of starch)
- I hope the ratio is right.
-  Exactly.
(Measuring with his eyes)
Okay.
(Sucking teeth)
This will turn hard once boiled, right?
It's sticking to the bottom.
When working on something with a lot of starch and sugar,
- you should scrape the bottom.
-  Scrape?
Yes, you can mix it while scraping the bottom.
I can't tell.
(Thinking)
- I don't know.
-  You don't know?
He says he doesn't know.
- You don't care anymore?
-  He doesn't know.
(What will be the fate of this "I don't know" pudding?)
Okay.
When do we cook the tenderloin?
- Tenderloin?
-  At the end?
It's 11:00am right now.
(It's currently 11:00am.)
- We'll cook it at 11:30am.
-  Okay.
We can start at 11:30am.
We need to time everything.
If you can wash that pot for me,
- Okay.
-  I'll make some pasta sauce.
- Okay, I got it.
-  Okay.
- I'm okay.
-  Are you okay?
(Cleaning the pot)
Olive oil.
(Pouring olive oil)
Put the garlic and onion in.
- Can I put them in directly?
-  Yes.
(Focused)
Is this good?
Yes. We need some gochujang.
Add a spoon and a half.
- A spoon and a half?
-  Yes.
Stir-fry it for about a minute before adding the tomato sauce.
- All of it?
-  Yes.
(Pouring tomato sauce)
- On low heat?
-  Low.
(Stir it on low heat, and it is finished.)
(Surprised)
It's really good.
- Does it taste okay?
-  It's good.
Really? Is this sauce good?
(A bee has appeared.)
Bee!
- We're very close to nature here.
-  Yes.
- Yes.
-  It's still beside you.
Where? It really is.
Come on.
- Chef.
-  Gosh.
What do we do with this bee?
- Once it goes away...
-  Bee.
It won't sting if you stay still.
- Don't move, and it won't sting.
-  It will burn if we don't move.
It won't sting if you stay still.
When can I do the dishes, then?
You must stay still.
(He must protect the pudding even if he's scared.)
Come on, Chef. Weren't you in the US Army?
- You were...
-  He was just joining me.
You crouched too much.
I thought you were going in the pot.
I was just joining them.
Your face is red.
Don't lie.
You startled me.
(He can be a bit sloppy.)
I think this is finished.
- Okay. Can you turn it off?
-  Okay.
It's going to be rose pasta, so I will add some cream later.
Now, do you see that pot there?
- "Pot?" - Take that pot...
- The biggest one?
-  Yes.
Fill it halfway with water...
- and put it on the stove.
-  What is a "pot?"
Now, do you see that pot there?
- "Pot?" - Take that pot...
- The biggest one?
-  Yes.
Fill it halfway with water...
- and put it on the stove.
-  What is a "pot?"
- What is a "pot?" - A pot. This one.
- A pot.
-  I see, a pot.
Do chefs call it that?
I'm just used to calling it that.
Is that a "pot"?
(English vocabulary: Pot)
How much water do you need?
- Fill it halfway.
-  Half?
Yes. It's the water for boiling pasta.
Will this come to a boil?
I planned this to be simple, but it's somehow hectic.
Sauce is done, and we're waiting for the water to boil.
We'll start cooking this.
(Now, the pasta sauce is done, and the pudding is being cooled.)
(News arrives from school.)
Really? Okay.
(The kids will be an hour late due to a swim lesson.)
We're going to eat at 1:00pm.
- What?
-  We'll eat at 1:00pm.
- Then, we have...
-  Not at 12:00pm?
- time.
-  We have extra time.
Let's do what we have to do first.
- Good thing we didn't boil pasta.
-  We can do it.
I'm glad.
(They can have a tasting session.)
(The ham they cut earlier)
The ham is out.
If you fry ham, what else would you need?
It will be the tastiest thing in the world.
I've never tried fried ham before.
Me neither.
I don't know. I just thought kids would like it.
It's guaranteed if it's fried ham.
How can it taste bad when it's fried ham?
It'll be tasty for sure.
Let's test it out and try it.
- I'd love to.
-  Yes. Let's try it.
If the kids are staying outside,
it might get soggy.
We have to make sure the batter remains crispy.
I don't know what time they will be able to eat it.
Doing a test is important.
There is so much. Gosh, it's so thick.
(Testing the ham tangsuyuk)
It looks tasty.
It looks tasty already.
(Plopping)
Okay.
What a nice sound.
(Always a tasty sound)
- It's floating up.
-  Yes.
It's a texture kids love.
This will be good for sure.
(Lethally tempting)
(The visual is great.)
- It looks okay.
-  I could eat two bowls of rice.
Is it crispy?
Gosh, it's so crispy.
What a crispy sound.
(Staring)
It looks so delicious.
(The crispy sound makes us salivate.)
Sauce. What about the sauce?
Sauce? I'll make it now.
- The persimmon...
-  Ripe persimmon.
We want just the meat of the persimmons.
- What happened to them?
-  They...
- That...
-  What happened to them?
We want just the meat.
- What happened to them?
-  They...
Sauce. What about the sauce?
Sauce? I'll make it now.
- The persimmon...
-  Ripe persimmon.
We want just the meat of the persimmons.
- What happened to them?
-  They...
- That...
-  What happened to them?
We want just the meat.
- What happened to them?
-  They...
-  Did the bee eat them?
They were new.
Are they too ripe?
They're... They look bad.
- Let's move on.
-  They look bad.
It looks like someone threw them.
This is too much.
But I think it's okay.
- Is this okay?
-  We can still use them.
- I'll just use it.
-  Does this look okay?
I'll try using them.
- Really?
-  Yes.
I respect you, Chef.
This doesn't feel right.
This one is really bad.
Let's put them in a bowl.
- Should I do it?
-  Yes. Let's use a bowl.
A bowl?
(Remove the calyx and cut the persimmon in half.)
It looks delicious.
- Do I peel it?
-  Remove the peel.
It's soft.
Yes. Remove the peel like this.
(Crispy fried ham)
I have to check the seasoning.
(Adding the sauce made out of just ripe persimmons)
(Whale Teacher is tasting it first.)
(I can hardly wait.)
Try some.
I think it needs some vinegar.
- Vinegar?
-  Yes.
(These two are having a taste.)
Gosh.
Gosh, the kids are going to love it.
They're going to love it.
They go well together.
- It's...
-  The combination works.
Yes.
- They go well together.
-  It's my first time trying.
Really? It goes well with persimmons.
I always...
It's good as it is. It's really delicious.
- Yes.
-  Do you need to add something?
The vinegar isn't for the sour taste.
- It's to heighten the taste.
-  I see.
That's why.
It just needs a drop.
(A drop of vinegar for a rich flavor)
Flavor.
- That's really little.
-  Yes.
It's so tasty.
(Will kids like ripe persimmons?)
We didn't do anything to it.
- No.
-  The taste of persimmons.
They'll go, "Is this tangsuyuk?"
- Yes.
-  Yes.
Good, the water is boiling.
(Meanwhile, the water came to a boil.)
This is Granobello Filini pasta.
It's from Italy and made out of farro.
This pasta is low in sugar,
but high in fiber and protein.
So people of every age group can enjoy it.
I see.
We should try using the timer and taste it.
- Should we use a timer?
-  Yes.
Timer.
- Should I start it?
-  Yes.
(Checking for the right duration to cook the pasta)
It has been 45 seconds.
(Adding salt)
- It's been 1 minute and 50 seconds.
-  Okay.
(Checking)
- Let's cook for 30 more seconds.
-  It's 2 minutes.
- Thirty more seconds.
-  Thirty.
We'll taste it together.
It's 2 minutes and 55 seconds.
Doing that makes me anxious.
We just passed three minutes.
(The look of a chef)
In 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
We're now at four minutes.
I guess it's not hot to chefs.
- Grandmas are the same.
-  Yes.
Some grandmas grab grills with bare hands.
Exactly.
We're now at 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
I took it out at 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
(A chef's intuition)
At 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
Since I said I would make rose pasta,
could you pass me the sour cream over there?
That one?
- We won't be using this plate, - No.
but just imagine it.
(The tomato pasta will be the base.)
Okay. Serve it like this at first.
We'll put this on top for the kids to mix.
- Will it turn into rose pasta?
-  Yes, it will.
- Gosh.
-  It's different from what you know.
(After adding cream and cheese, a rose pasta is born.)
This too.
The kids can rip their basil leaves and put them in.
- Like so.
-  Basil smells so good.
It looks store-bought.
- Come on.
-  It looks like a restaurant dish.
I thought this would be okay.
It looks so pretty.
- Send it to me.
-  Okay.
It's so pretty.
- Should we taste it?
-  Yes.
This is how you turn it into a rose pasta.
- Just mix.
-  Mix?
- What is this?
-  Like so.
I haven't tried it either, but please go ahead.
- You should go first.
-  Should I?
We should think about...
whether we should give basil to them or not.
I think the kids will like it.
I think it will be unfamiliar to them.
(The basil's scent is strong, so people can be divided.)
Try it. I like basil in it,
but kids might not.
(This taste!)
Is it good?
This would be 30 dollars in Cheongdam-dong.
- It's so good.
-  In Cheongdam-dong? You're right.
It's so good!
Gosh!
It's so good.
(Delicious)
I think we could add less basil.
- Basil?
-  Yes.
- For us, it's better with basil.
-  Of course.
But I'm not sure about the kids.
But I think...
a new experience is good for them.
As a chef, it's important...
to let them experience a new taste.
It tastes more perfect with basil.
My kids don't eat a lot of basil either.
- No?
-  My son eats it,
but not my daughter.
I always debate taking it out.
In that sense...
Can't we put some on a plate and let them choose?
We shouldn't give them a choice.
There is no choice.
How cool. There is no other choice.
If they get to choose,
they'll avoid anything unfamiliar.
He's right.
- Let's try giving them some.
-  Sure.
- It's so good.
-  Let's serve it like this.
Let's settle it.
We'll now go outside.
Let's test the fire.
We need to cook broccolini in advance.
You have to cook it with scallion oil?
(They will grill the broccolini first.)
(The broccolini is covered in scallion oil and salt.)
When cooking vegetables,
I put them on high heat until they're about to burn.
Until they're about to burn.
Just before they burn.
I felt like we should have them eat some vegetables.
- Yes.
-  I wondered what would be good,
and figured something unfamiliar...
might be interesting to try.
I've never seen this vegetable either.
- Please grill it like this later.
-  Okay.
- Okay.
We're almost ready, so go ahead and grill.
Once you're done, I'll come out to grill the meat together.
Cook the broccolini first.
I'll season this for you.
Will you come out when I'm working on this?
Yes, I'll come back soon.
We only have 30 minutes left. Will it be okay?
It's fine.
He's so reliable.
- Go ahead and grill.
-  Is it one per kid?
- I'll bring a plate out.
-  Okay.
- Is it one vegetable per kid?
-  Yes.
- One per kid.
-  One per kid.
(Current status: Pasta, needs to be cooked,)
(Ham tangsuyuk, needs to be fried,)
(Steak, vegetables grilling, Pudding, cooling)
(They have a long way to go.)
All right.
(Act 4: It's My First School Meal)
It's so hectic.
- You have gloves on.
-  Yes.
Put a piece of meat in this. Please put one in.
Add some salt.
(Sprinkling salt on tenderloin)
About this much. Not too much.
Pepper.
(While adding pepper...)
Wait, do kids dislike pepper?
- Pepper...
-  Just salt it on one side.
Salt it and then repeat it.
(While frying ham...)
I hope the kids like it.
I think they'll love it.
(The reason why he's worried about the children)
When you look at children as an adult,
you want to see them happy.
I thought of foods with vibes...
children might love.
Making something tasty is important,
but I want to give them something healthy too.
Have you made school meals before?
School meals for children? I don't...
- Never?
-  Never.
It just makes me think things twice.
I see, for the kids.
(Chef Ahn came at their beck and call.)
- Should I take them?
-  Yes.
- The meat?
-  Call me when broccolini is done.
Okay.
(Passing the seasoned meat to the one in charge)
Broccolini is finished.
- Should I take them?
-  Yes.
The three at the end were burnt.
- Chef Ahn should check and decide.
-  Okay.
What do I do with the meat?
Chef Ahn said he would do it.
Chef Ahn, are you grilling the meat?
Yes. I'm coming.
He's coming.
(He couldn't hear it.)
After I take this one out, I'll go outside for a bit.
- Okay.
-  We're short on time.
We have to cook the pasta now.
Set the timer for 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
- Okay.
-  Cook for 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
- Put them in and stir it.
-  Okay.
After 4 minutes and 30 seconds, take them out.
Okay. Should I start now?
- Yes.
-  All of them at once?
Where do we put in the meat?
Meat? We have to take it out with us.
- Do we?
-  Yes. I'm not sure if it's here.
I see, we have to take it.
(The anxious potato has started to grill on his own.)
- Did you start to grill already?
-  Yes. We don't have time.
What?
The meat... He already started.
All right. Okay.
(Finally heading out to the fire)
I have to multitask...
- It's a lot of multitasking.
-  It's not easy.
(The structure makes it hard to lead everyone.)
(Rushing)
I grilled it this much.
- Let me check.
-  What do you think?
(Were they grilled evenly?)
(Rushing)
I grilled it this much.
- Let me check.
-  What do you think?
(Were they grilled evenly?)
- It's perfect.
-  Like this?
(Pass)
- Grill it like this. Do this more.
-  Like this?
- A bit more?
-  Yes.
- You have to keep a lid on it.
-  Okay.
This is it. This is perfect.
Keep a lid on it. Keep grilling.
- Are you sure you can do it? Okay.
-  Okay.
(Leaving alone)
Is this right? Wait.
(Meanwhile, at the pasta section)
(Sighing)
For 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
I've never cooked pasta right in my life.
- Oh dear.
-  Oh dear.
I'm going nuts.
- Shouldn't he be here?
-  Come on.
At the barbecue place, he was so calm.
He said, "It's all right."
Now, he's running around.
He's running.
(Beluga Whale in a hurry)
(Peeking)
(Let's go.)
(The pasta club member does her best...)
(on behalf of Whale Teacher.)
I can't see a thing.
(Tae Ri finishes the 1st round of noodles, which is 10 servings.)
Please drizzle olive oil on it.
Like this.
Why do you put the olive oil in?
- We still have some time.
-  Yes.
The noodles might get soggy.
(As they won't serve it for a while,)
(they need to prevent the noodles from sticking together.)
- We have the sauce.
-  Yes.
Please heat up the sauce.
- Syrup?
-  Warm it up.
- Warm it up.
-  Yes.
He's grilling the meat.
We'll heat it up, make the pasta,
and fry some.
- We'll run a little late.
-  Will we be late?
We'll be a little late, but it'll be manageable.
You've changed your words.
The kids are sensitive about tardiness.
My apologies.
- I feel like an amazing cook.
-  I know.
I've seen you play a cook...
- As a character?
-  in "Little Forest."
- "Little Forest?" - "Little Forest."
Were you in the series?
- Didn't you cook in it?
-  It was a movie.
I cook through the four seasons in the movie.
- You learned cooking, then.
-  So, now,
- this sight shouldn't be aired.
-  Why not?
(This sight shouldn't be aired.)
- Because of your role.
-  Yes.
- People think I'm a good cook.
-  I see.
(Sorry)
Add half of the sauce.
(She's cooking skillfully while saying so.)
- I think it is heated up.
-  Yes.
Now, pour the sauce evenly.
- Half and half?
-  Yes.
(Pouring the tomato sauce)
That's good.
- Looking good.
-  After mixing them all,
add the fresh cream.
It's healthy cream.
(Adding cheese to lots of cream)
Now, tear the basil leaves.
I love the smell.
(After topping it with basil, the pasta is ready.)
Did you finish grilling?
(The one in charge of grilling is back.)
It looks good.
- Okay.
-  Did you grill them all?
Yes, I did.
Let's go.
(The chocolate pudding is jiggly.)
- Let's bring them.
-  Let's go now.
(Fortunately, they finished cooking in time.)
I don't think I can do the field day.
I want to go to the restroom.
- It's the field day today.
-  I can't do it.
There's a field day. We're not done yet.
Gosh. It's crazy.
(Lunch especially prepared for the whole school)
- Is this the Last Supper?
-  Exactly.
What is this?
- You can serve pasta.
-  Okay.
- Then you can pour the sauce.
I hope they like it.
(Rose pasta with basil)
(Ham tangsuyuk with the ripe persimmon sauce)
(Korean tenderloin steak with broccolini)
(Chocolate pudding served with whipped cream)
(Ready to be served)
What now?
(Nervous)
- Let's go.
-  Let's go, everyone!
- Yes!
-  Yes!
(Preparing the future with health, humaneness, and wisdom)
(They're starving after swimming.)
- We're here.
-  They're coming.
Food!
- Ms. Kim!
-  Hi, everyone.
- Hello!
-  Ms. Kim!
- Yes, we're here.
-  Nice!
Ladle it.
Hello.
- They're adorable.
-  Hi.
(Whale Teacher greets them too.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- Now, get the food 1 by 1.
-  Okay.
- One by one.
-  Okay. One by one.
Good.
Take your meal 1 by 1.
- It's rose pasta.
-  Nice!
Rose pasta.
- Do you know it?
-  Yes.
This is a persimmon sauce.
Pour the sauce on tangsuyuk.
- How do you feel?
-  Pour the sauce on top of it.
- Do you feel better?
-  As for the sauce,
pour it over tangsuyuk.
- Over tangsuyuk?
-  Pour it.
You can give them much more.
(Correcting it right away)
- This is a chocolate pudding.
-  Enjoy.
- You can come back for more.
-  Okay.
- It's a persimmon sauce.
-  Thank you.
(Thank you.)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
- A persimmon sauce?
-  Please give me less.
- Did you study hard?
-  Did you want a little?
- I didn't study.
-  No?
- What did you do, then?
-  I learned survival swimming.
Do you know him?
Ha Yun, do you know him at the end?
- Yes.
-  Do you know him?
- Who is it?
-  Chef Ahn Sung Jae.
You do know him.
- What is that?
-  It's a chocolate pudding.
- Do you like it?
-  Chocolate!
- It's upgraded tangsuyuk.
-  It's chocolate with cream.
- Eat it with a spoon.
-  Okay.
Bye.
Nice.
- What is it?
-  It's rose pasta.
- Yes, it's...
-  I want it.
Hi, Ji Min.
How do you know my name?
How do you know your name?
I met your uncle at the barbershop.
- Is he Ji Min?
-  Yes.
(They met at the barbershop as if it was destined.)
(Hyo Min and Ji Min's uncle)
(The person linking the two)
- Is he Ji Min?
-  Yes.
I met your uncle at the barbershop.
Am I correct?
He told me that you were his nephew.
Ms. Kim.
(Other happy faces)
- All three of them are teachers?
-  Yes.
- All three of them.
Hello.
(The head of academic affairs, the principal)
Do you have food for yourselves?
- We have a lot.
-  We have plenty.
- Do you?
-  Too much, even.
- You have to make two rounds.
-  Really?
Yes. Come back for more.
Thank you. It looks so good.
- Hello.
-  Hi.
- Thanks for your work.
-  Hello.
Do the kids talk about the acting class?
They love it.
- Really?
-  Yes.
- Please enjoy.
-  Thank you.
- See you again.
-  Hello.
Everyone.
He's the chef who cooked for us today.
- Hello.
-  He's really famous.
Do you know him?
- We do.
-  Ahn Sung Jae.
- You're popular.
-  Gosh.
- Thank you for knowing me.
-  Why does he look so happy?
Of course, I do. Kids love me.
They all know you. You're popular.
He is Chef Ahn Sung Jae.
- Here, he's Whale Teacher.
-  Whale Teacher.
He's Whale Teacher because he looks like a whale.
Let's call him Whale Teacher, okay?
- Yes!
-  Yes!
It'll be lovely if you can thank Whale Teacher.
Should we say it together? One, two, three.
- Thank you, Whale Teacher.
-  Thank you, Whale Teacher.
You're welcome. Please enjoy.
- Please enjoy.
-  Thanks for the food.
- Thanks for the food.
-  We have plenty of food.
- You can have more if you want.
-  Yes.
- Let me try it.
-  Enjoy.
- Thank you for the food.
-  Thank you.
- Thank you.
-  You can have more if you want.
(Eating as soon as he was told to)
(An experienced noodle eater)
(Savoring)
(Amazed)
It's amazing.
(Going for the steak)
(Satisfied)
- It's Ahn Sung Jae.
-  What?
(Lastly, he tries the ham tangsuyuk.)
(For 3 consecutive times)
(Dipping generously in the sauce)
I love eating outside.
The classroom is...
- It tastes like a honey sauce.
-  Without that...
- Really?
-  Yes.
It's a persimmon sauce.
It tastes like honey.
- Really?
-  Does it taste like honey?
(The persimmon sauce is sold out.)
After eating this...
Don't you like it?
(They're mesmerized too.)
Gosh. The steak is so tasty. Try it.
You can sit here.
The steak tastes good.
Is the steak tasty?
Can you smell a smoky flavor?
Are you saying Kyung Mo's not skinny?
(The steak is sold out too.)
Why are your eyes so red?
(Savoring the broccolini too)
The meat?
- What are you doing?
-  I'm getting some more.
What? You're getting more?
Good.
Teacher.
Thank you.
(Teacher)
- Do you want more?
-  Yes.
- What?
-  What do you want?
- Pasta.
-  Pasta?
- Did you like the pasta?
-  Pasta...
- Give him.
-  and ham tangsuyuk.
Do you want more tangsuyuk too?
He's adorable.
You were the first to take the meal, so you get more first too.
(Getting ready for Round 2)
I'll finally eat.
- Enjoy.
-  Yes.
What is this? Whose is this?
Can I use it?
- Just use it.
-  What?
- "Just use it?" - Go for it.
(Go for it!)
(He's a cool boy who likes to eat.)
"Go for it."
- Thank you for the food.
-  Enjoy.
(North Pole Teacher finally takes a bite.)
It's good.
- It's good, right?
-  Yes.
- Is it good?
-  It's good.
-  Yes.
Is it tasty? What do you like the most?
- All of them.
-  All of them?
- What's your first pick?
-  What's your favorite?
(In charge of the steak)
First place is...
- Ham?
-  It's ham.
- This is in 2nd place.
-  Pasta is in 2nd place?
- What about the meat? The last?
-  In third place.
In third place? Okay.
(Pasta in 2nd, steak in 3rd)
(Laughing)
- Mr. Ahn.
-  Yes.
What was the tastiest dish you've ever had?
I've tried so many things.
Because my job is related to food,
I've had so many kinds of food.
I had so many dishes that I found tasty.
But what's memorable is what I ate when I was young.
- It's tasty.
-  Is this a pudding?
It would be the one my grandmother cooked.
(After eating all kinds of food around the world...)
- Potato tteok?
-  Potato tteok.
This is so tasty.
You taste food not only with your mouth but also with your heart.
It's tasty.
He said we taste the food with our hearts.
This is sweet.
If we say it's not tasty,
- Mr. Ahn will be sad.
-  That's right.
I'm used to it, though.
I'm strong on that side.
Until I've become who I am,
there were many people who told me it wasn't tasty.
But you just have to keep going with what you find right.
Do you want it?
Do you get it?
Yes.
- This is...
-  What is it?
(Stay strong and follow your own way.)
Let's try it.
- Why do I have two spoons?
-  I know.
I think so too.
- I have two spoons.
-  It happens.
Why? Why do you have two?
That's cool.
(Nodding to approve it)
The steak tastes amazing.
I was proud when we were eating together.
(How was cooking for the students?)
It was so worth it.
I'm not saying it...
because I cooked, and they liked it.
"What I had back then was unusual."
"How did they come up with that?"
If I made them curious, I'd say I was successful.
I don't expect all of them to feel that way.
If there's only one...
who goes, "There must be something more to it..."
with curiosity,
I've planted a seed in them.
(Hopefully the seeds will sprout one day.)
(Yongheung Elementary School Autumn Field Day)
(With the students' cheer,)
(they run,)
(scream with joy,)
(and show the best teamwork.)
(The whole school comes together.)
(And a cooking match with their pride at stake)
(How will Chef Ahn evaluate it?)
(It's undercooked.)
(It tastes bitter.)
(They're more serious than ever.)
(Who will Chef Ahn choose?)
(The OST of Curtain Up, Class!, "Best Scene" by DK)
(Available on all music streaming sites)
Dramaday.me