Grandma.
I’m here to express my gratitude
for the lottery you gave us the other day.
Your power is now evident to me.
Thank you, Grandma.
What’s wrong?
Why do you look so down
like an abandoned puppy?
Han.
At this shrine.
Can we make a wish for others?
Don’t you see her power
from the last time we prayed to her?
How powerful she was.
Yohan, my best friend.
You don’t need to act like a good person
and ask her to help me win the match.
Don’t get too full of yourself.
This time, I pray for myself.
Grandma, you are the most powerful spirit here.
Please send me a boyfriend.
You can send anyone.
I don’t mind as long as I get a boyfriend.
If you grant my wish,
I will perform the best Thai dance for you.
Amen.
You haven’t learned the lesson, have you?
Don’t be so picky.
If it can be useful for us, just do it.
We can perform a Thai dance for her later.
Right?
Yes.
What about you?
Why don’t you ask her to help you
with your dream match?
Grandma.
I have a very important thing
to ask for your help.
Please help Malai pass the audition.
Please help her get selected
to be an artist under the new agency.
You are acting like a hero.
For me,
being able to box again is good enough.
From now on,
I will try to do it myself.
For Malai,
I see that she’s always tried her best.
So I want her
to be blessed with good luck
and receive a good opportunity
at least once in her life.
I’m begging you, Grandma.
Please help Malai.
Just this once.
You are so cool.
I promise I will work hard with you.
Let’s start.
Tomorrow, you and I will go to Thammachak.
There will be a player tryout.
Those who are selected will appear
in the press conference with you
and take photos after the match.
Are you ready?
Ready to face Baby Shark
as your opponent in the rematch?
Bring it on.
I’m super ready.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
#JAMAREE-THAMMACHAKBOXING93
BABY SHARK LOOKS SO COOL.
I’M HERE FOR KLAIRUNG.
WILL THE MATCH BE BROADCAST LIVE?
The cheer is so loud.
Baby Shark must knock out his opponent.
I guess so.
But no need to be scared.
You have me and your dad with you.
Dad, whose side are you taking?
Of course, I’m taking your side.
My admiration for Baby Shark is over.
From now on, I only have Klairung,
my beloved son.
Fine.
I hope you mean what you said.
Of course, I mean it.
You’d better mean it.
What’s going on?
Let me see.
Is this real?
Is it possible?
Is this him?
Yes.
Okay.
I can do it.
Hit me.
Are you ready?
I’m going to take a video
to upload to our channel.
Sure. I’m ready.
I’m now the fittest and readiest
since I was born.
Baby Shark, are you okay?
What happened?
Were you not ready for the match?
Hey.
Baby Shark.
What just happened?
Surprise, mother, father.
Sunrise.
Good luck?
A lottery ticket?
Repay to the higher power?
So this is how it is.
Grandma.
If you are a powerful spirit like they said,
please help me beat Baby Shark
and become the university’s athlete.
If you grant my wish,
I will arrange a group of dancers
to perform a Thai dance for you.
I defeat the old and incompetent Baby Shark
with my punches.
It’s over, the legendary lethal left punch
and deadly right punch.
Dad.
Are you shocked?
Don’t worry.
You will be even more shocked.
There’s another disgusting phony
waiting to be crushed by me.
A real deal is not a big talker.
If you think you are a real deal,
then don’t let me beat you.
The friendly boxing match is starting soon.
What is he doing?
I found a secret weapon.
It guarantees that I will defeat you.
She is blacklisted by Biao’s agency.
Because of your troubled past,
it could cause us problems.
Grandma, how can you do this?
You’ve never been fair.
You help him take advantage
of the person who has been working hard.
What do you want?
Just tell me.