The price is still 5,000 baht.
No service charge. No VAT.
Okay.
Deal.
Han, can you grab my pants?
Wait.
How can I be sure…
that if I pay you to perform the dance,
my hands will go back to normal?
You can hire someone else.
I don’t mind.
I’m not trying the pot.
I ask because I really want to know.
Don’t worry.
Grandma is hard to please,
but she always keeps her promises.
She is so smart.
Can I ask you something?
Do you have answers for every question?
Of course.
Because…
I’m her granddaughter.
Real or fake?
Is it cake?
It’s true.
I’m willing to take a DNA test if you want.
What’s your name?
You need to tell me.
I have to say your name
when I perform the dance.
Otherwise, she won’t know
that the dance is from you.
Klairung.
Just like the meaning of your name,
you’re almost famous.
You really don’t know me?
I’m a famous influencer.
Don’t you have access to the internet?
Yes, I have.
But I don’t have time
to know everyone in the world.
Is being homeless a trend now?
Why is she living in a tent?
Maybe this is for her content.
Everyone is presenting weird content.
Unlike us.
Han.
Our content is weird, too.
Grandma.
I’m performing this dance
on behalf of Klairung.
I will do my best, like always.
I hope you will like it.
♪ Chuichai is so beautiful ♪
♪ Her dance moves are elegant ♪
Done.
Don’t forget to thank Grandma.
Thank you, Grandma.
My hands are working fine now.
Let’s go, Han.
Hey.
Can you turn on Quick Share?
I’m sorry
for calling you a con artist.
Your dance is beautiful.
I know I’m a good dancer.
Next time, let someone else say that.
I’m leaving.
KLAIRUNG
KLAIRUNG PAYAP
(So cute.)
It’s finally over.
What are you going to do next?
Will you start practicing for the next match?
We still have time for it.
We can think about it later.
Right now, we should focus on the work
for our clients.
That’s true.
Money is the most important thing.
Of course, money can knock out everything.
Thank you.
Rung, why are you so clumsy?
Shit, the curse is back.
Damn it.
But we already arranged
a dance performance for her.
I knew it.
She’s a con artist.
Why are your hands still not working?
I should be the one who asks you that.
It even got worse.
Did you promise her something else?
Not the dance?
It’s been several days.
When will you do what you’ve promised me?
I will not give in to that old Titan Grandma.
I’ll defeat her.
It’s me, Klairung.
Grandma, no!