Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
To increase our subscribers,
why don’t we pray to gods for help?
It’s really increasing.
It almost hit 100,000 subscribers.
Thank you, Goddess,
for helping us get where we are today.
Congratulations on hitting 100,000 subscribers.
I’m not your friend.
I’m the goddess!
GODDESS DALOP
Kat!
Are you here to apologize to me?
Stop talking nonsense.
No.
The goddess is possessing your friend.
How is that possible?
The person who is the most disrespectful
to the goddess is Kat.
How insolent!
I’m not being insolent.
I mean it.
Unless the goddess likes the smell of vomit.
Are you sure you didn’t do anything wrong?
What’s wrong, Ingky?
Nothing.
I’m fine.
Why don’t you tell them?
You haven’t had any matches on Tinder
for the past 3 – 4 days.
No, it’s not true.
Check it.
Give me your phone.
Look.
Her last match was three days ago.
Ingky!
Give it back, Fews.
You need to understand me.
I have more than 20 matches.
They all text me and want to talk to me.
They want to meet me.
They want…give me their love.
I don’t match with them just to fulfill
the goddess’s requirement, like you.
What?
How dare you say that?
Fews.
You said that
as if you didn’t do anything wrong.
What?
- I have new matches every day.
- OMG!
On Disco?
The gay app for dating?
Hi.
Are you a fem gay?
I’m a masc.
If I acted like a fem gay,
I wouldn’t get any matches.
You can’t do that.
What?
Why the hell are you staring at me?
I got new matches every day as a fem.
I won every battle.
What about that day?
The day that you were defeated.
P’Pat.
Oh, I’ll go.
Definitely go.
Oh, my heart.
P’Pat.
You were crying in the bathroom.
You were bawling your eyes out for an hour.
I was just crying. I wasn’t defeated.
Whatever.
Now, it’s a good chance.
The goddess is possessing Katrina.
You can apologize to her now.
Med, how can you be sure
that she is the goddess?
That’s right.
This doesn’t make sense.
She broke the conditions more often than us.
Hey!
I’m warning you.
You need to apologize to me right now.
I’m not mad at Kat.
About the vomit,
I can bear with it.
You broke my rules.
You need to apologize to me.
Sure.
But not to this face.
Asshole.
Fine.
I’ll curse you.
Your every day, every hour, every minute,
your lives will be full of misfortunes.
Wait and see the result of defying me.
What will be your punishment?
Idiots!
No, you are an idiot, bitch!
Kat!
Do you think I’m afraid of you?
Huh?
Kat!
Bitch!
They are idiots!
Amen.
Kat was talking nonsense.
A curse? What the heck?!
I think what she said might be true.
Come to think about it.
Kat is the only one
who didn’t break any rules.
Except…
the vomiting.
Nonsense.
I don’t believe it.
She just used a psychological tactic.
If we are told that we have bad luck,
we will focus on it.
Focus?
If you feel worried,
we can go to Chonburi.
Why?
I found a temple that can reverse curses.
It’s not time yet.
If we were cursed,
we wouldn’t have so many sponsors.
Girls.
Stop.
We are from AXTC.
We want to invite Air Dolls
to join a promotional activity with Crepes.
Crepes?
Crepes!
Gosh!
P’Pat’s boy group.
We’re so lucky.
We get to shoot this content
because the other YouTuber is hospitalized.
This is what you call misfortune?
We totally lucked out.
Hey.
My stomach is not feeling well.
Stop.
See?
If we had bad luck,
we would have fallen into this damn sewer.
Bad luck is a result of being reckless.
If we are cautious about everything,
there’s no way we will have bad luck.
Let’s go.
- Hello.
- So big.
Hello.
P’Pat.
Hello, P’Pat.
Hello.
I’ll introduce my members to you.
This is Hot.
He’s the main dancer of my group.
Good.
I want to talk to you.
Do you want to talk to me?
I’m introverted and not good at talking.
Will you be interested in me?
What should I do?
I don’t want to give my heart away for free.
I hope you will be kind to me.
Good job.
This is Tone, the main rapper.
Good.
Oh!
You are here, Air Dolls.
Kat!
Goddess.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were holding
a ceremony to curse us.
Why can’t I be here?
I’m also a member of Air Dolls.
The reason why I’m here,
it’s because I want to witness
your misfortune with my own eyes.
A goddess like me always keeps my word.
Kat.
Can you stop pretending
to be possessed by a spirit?
What kind of goddess
wants to go out with guys?
It would be more strange
if I went out with girls, idiot!
Is there a problem between you?
- No.
- No problem.
Not at all.
Excuse us. We need to get ready.
Sure.
See you, P’Pat.
Ing.
Can you come with me to ask for medicine?
What? Why can’t you…
Can’t you ask for me?
Do you have medication for an upset stomach?
Search in the bag.
You want us to look for it by ourselves?
Yes.
Right.
What about this?
No.
Antacids will make my condition worse.
What about this one?
Ing, use your brain.
Domperidone will make my lips feel dry.
I won’t look good.
You are so choosy.
Let’s go with this one.
What is this?
What the hell are you doing?
It’s an organic medicine.
Let’s get back to work.
Do you see my laxative?
I don’t know.
Look in the bag.
Today, Crepes and everyone
will eat spicy food.
The concept of the show is
promoting your song while enjoying a meal.
I want you guys to look like
you're having a good time while eating.
You can play jokes all you want.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask.
I have a question.
Yes.
I’m allergic to vinegar.
Have you informed your staff about my allergy?
I checked the recipes thoroughly.
They use only lime juice in every dish.
Wow!
Ingky, if you don’t want to eat, it’s okay.
It’s not that big of a deal.
I’m ready for today.
Fews.
What’s wrong?
Ingky.
My stomach is upset.
Excuse me, I need to go to the bathroom.
Okay.
If everyone is ready, let’s begin the shooting.
Hold it in.
It has to wait.
The shooting won’t take longer than an hour.
Hold it in.
P’Pat, enjoy the food.
Thank you.
I’ll get it for you.
P’Pat.
You should stay away from Air Dolls.
They have a long face
because they are down on their luck.
Yeah.
P’Pat, don’t listen to her.
I don’t know what got into her lately.
She keeps talking nonsense.
I guess her brain has stopped developing.
I’m talking about her math skills.
Don’t ask her. She can’t answer it.
Because she’s stupid.
Do you normally use harsh words
to tease each other?
That’s…
That’s right, P’Pat.
This is how we tease each other.
You’re just joking.
P’Pat, please dig in.
Are you okay, P’Fews?
Why didn’t you eat anything?
Thank you.
FEWS, ACT LIKE YOU ENJOY THE FOOD.
Do you want to try spicy pork bone soup?
I’ll try it a bit, P’Pat.
Do you know my mom always sends me
a limousine so I can go out to eat the soup?
Spicy pork bone soup
is one of my favorite foods.
I love spicy food.
Then you should eat it a lot.
That’s enough.
I’ll have a small bite.
My mouth is small.
Fews, are you okay?
For you.
For me?
Thank you.
P’Pat, do you know
that Kat used to have no friends?
Because she was too stinky.
Idiot.
Why don’t you tell him about your past, too?
P’Pat, do you know
she used to coach a cheerleading team?
She didn’t let them go home.
She acted like a dictator.
Those cheerleaders really hated her.
Bitch, you are a dictator.
Shameless.
Kat, you are a dumbass.
Nevia, you are an asshole.
Do you want to try me?
Bring it on, bitch.
Is there something rotten in here?
Did you…
…fart?
Poop.
I’m pooping.
I’m holding it in for too long.
I can’t hold it in any longer.
Fews.
What’s wrong?
Why are all the doors locked?
I’m going to poop my pants any minute.
Miss.
The water is not running.
So the cleaner locked the doors.
I’ll call the cleaner.
Hey.
The nearest bathroom is 20 minutes away.
I would have pooped when we got there.
I’ll do it here.
No.
Stop it, bitch.
Come with me. I’ll take you to the bathroom.
I’ll count to three. Then walk with me.
One.
Two.
Three. Let’s go.
Who is this?
Ingky?
I feel strange.
Have you informed your staff about my allergy?
Miss, did they put vinegar in the food?
They usually don’t use vinegar in their recipes.
But I forgot that they have a new chef today.
Where is your med?
Give it to me.
Idiot.
Why didn’t you bring your meds?
Miss, get me a car.
I need to take my friend to the hospital.
Hurry up.
Ingky, turn around.
I don’t want to see it.
You look pretty now.
Fews, go.
Go.
Fews, how are you?
Open the door.
Where is the driver?
He just left with the cleaner.
I’ll go get a taxi. I’ll be right back.
Nevia, wait.
What, bitch?
Fews, I called the cleaner.
She is hurrying back.
No need for it.
We are here to apologize to you.
You need to learn your lesson.
No, I don’t want to smell it again.
We are here to apologize to you.
Do it.
Ouch, it hurts.
The flower is beautiful.
It smells good.
You will lift the curse on us, won’t you?
No, not yet.
Because…
People like you,
you,
and you,
You need to learn your lesson.
The three of you will be serving me
until I feel satisfied.
How do you want us to serve you?
No, I don’t want to smell it again.
Idiot.
I point that way.
There.
Go.
Yes.
Stop crying. Hurry and clean it up.
Go.
Hurry up.
That’s not my style.
Idiot.
Can you press harder?
Oh, P’Pat.
P’Kat, why are you here alone?
I came to see you.
P’Pat, don’t look at them.
What?
Come with me.
What about them?
Don’t pay attention to them.
I can’t take this shit anymore.
Girls.
The penalty for a homicide
is 20 years of imprisonment.
That’s quite a long time.
I can’t take it anymore.
I want to stab her with this toothbrush.
Calm down, Fews.
You can’t let Kat hear that.
She is right outside.
She will curse us again.
I don’t want to get swollen lips again.
There’s no way she will hear it.
She turns on the music that loud.
I wouldn’t be surprised
if she lost her hearing.
See?
She didn’t hear it.
Whatever.
Let’s endure it for the meantime.
I think there will be a day
that we can avenge her.
When will that day come?
Why are you yelling, brat?
She can’t hear it anyway.
Stop yelling, both of you.
One day.
Girls.
I’m hungry.
Go buy me my usual.
Ingky.
Go buy Daifuku.
Fews, go buy a matcha drink.
I’ll buy ice cream.
Nevia, what are you doing?
Lower your voice.
I saw P’Med sneaking into Kat’s room.
She’s here.
Get up.
What?
You don’t need to whisper.
No one will hear us.
I’m telling you about the three magical items
that will help you take over her body.
Huh?
Who is there?
Meow.
Are there many stray cats around here?
No.
I only saw a mouse.
Squeak…eek…eek.
It’s a hamster.
Doo…do…doo
What kind of hamsters make that sound?
It’s probably nothing.
The thing that you were saying earlier.
What is it?
According to the Yajurveda,
we need to find three lost magical items.
They will help you
take over Kat’s body permanently.
Girls.
What should we do?
If she takes over Kat’s body permanently,
then we will be her servants forever.
We need to find a shaman to get rid of her.
How will you get rid of her?
I’m not even sure
if the goddess is a ghost or not.
She’s some kind of spirit anyway.
We can try.
But the main problem is
how we are going to take Kat with us.
I think…
I have an idea.
Who is it?
How dare you interrupt my pleasure?
So annoying.
What the hell are you wearing?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Ouch.
Don’t forget your promise.
Alright, I won’t forget it.
I’ll be your servant for three days.
What the heck is that?
Seven days.
Yeah.
Did you tie her tightly?
Yes, take a look for yourself.
Then…
Let me teach you a lesson.
Nevia.
I won’t let you get away with it.
Eat this.
Asshole.
Scumbag.
Stop it, bitch.
I will no longer be your servant.
Kat could die.
I’ll leave her body.
Asshole.
Let me go.
Stop it.
Hello, P’Pat.
Your content is always grand.
Yeah.
How did he get here?
I posted an IG story
saying I was going to see a shaman.
So he asked if he could come with me.
Hey!
Haven’t you learned your lesson?
Do you think I don’t know who kicked me?
Especially the one with short legs.
You kicked me non-stop.
Read the room, you damn goddess.
Today, what happens, happens.
I will no longer be your servant.
Make some noise.
MASTER GOK, THE ROCK SHAMAN.
Ingky, what the hell is this?
I don’t know.
But he’s the most famous shaman
on social media.
Idiot.
He looks like a joke.
Hey, is this the evil spirit
that you want me, Master Gok,
the rock shaman, to get rid of?
She’s not a spirit.
She’s a goddess.
What goddess?
Dalop.
Goddess Dalop?
Do you want me
to dump her in a river or what?
I’m fine with that.
Do you want me to trap her
in a clay pot or a stainless steel pot?
A clay pot.
What guitar effect do you want?
Anything is fine. You just pick one.
Overdrive.
When will you start?
This bitchy spirit, you’ll regret it.
What kind of shaman
plays the guitar to perform exorcism?
You are cultureless.
Music will control and subdue your spirit.
A fake goddess like you
knows nothing about it.
Fake goddess?
I have granted wishes
to thousands of thousands of my followers.
You can fight against me.
I’ve been growing my spiritual power
for 500 years.
I’ve been doing that for 1,000 years.
I’ve been doing it for 2,000 years.
I’ve been doing it for 3,000 years.
I’ve been doing it for 4,000 years.
The guitar wasn’t invented 2,000 years ago.
Why are you so dumb?
I played the hammered dulcimer back then.
Idiot.
Goddess.
Do you have the vanishing power?
I want to be your follower.
My power is only for girls, idiot.
Dang it.
Hey.
Shut up.
No.
I’m just going to ask when you will start.
Let’s get it started.
How was it?
Did it come out?
Yes.
My pee came out.
Shit.
Fine, brace yourself
for my ancient sorcery ritual.
Guys, let’s begin the ritual.
He puts the thread around her.
This rattan cane has been passed down
for several centuries.
It is used for punishment.
I think he’s going to hit her for real.
I’ll hit you with it.
I’ll give you ten seconds.
One.
Two.
Ten.
What?
Ouch.
Good.
Great.
I like it.
Ouch.
Eww.
Asshole, your mouth stinks.
Don’t do it.
Crux sacra…
…sit mihi lux. Vade retro Satana.
Bitch.
A sword?
Does he need to go this far?
Kat could die.
He won’t stab her for real.
I will.
Oh my goodness!
This time, it’s you.
No.
Stop it.
Just to get rid of the spirit,
do you really need to kill her?
It’s no longer about exorcism.
It’s about me and this brat.
You need to learn your lesson.
Guys, take them away.
Hey.
Let me go.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
I’ll leave her body.
I don’t care.
Kat!
Hey.
Give the sword to me.
No.
Give it to me.
Don’t do it.
The goddess is really powerful.
What?
You are a dumbass.
You helped me get the first magical item.
What a crazy coincidence!
I’m leaving, idiots!
I’m leaving.
What are you waiting for?
Catch them.
Catch them. Don’t let them get away.
Hey.
Where are they going?
Catch them.
Stop.
Shit.
I don’t think they are following us.
What happened to P’Kat?
Let’s go in.
At first, we prayed to a higher power for help.
Because we wanted to have better lives.
I’m…
the…
…goddess
Your lives will be full of misfortunes.
But right now,
the goddess is ruining our lives.
We shouldn’t have asked
the higher power for help.
If the goddess has all three magical items,
Kat’s soul will be gone?
You are going to help her, aren’t you?
We should, I guess.
We will.
What is the next magical item?
I think it will be a crown.
Huh?
THE SWORD OF GODDESS DALOP.
BODICE OF GODDESS DALOP.
We’re back with the 7th Miss Golden Flower.
EDITH PROOF.
As in the previous years,
this is our gorgeous crown.
It has been passed down for centuries
from our goddess.
This is Goddess Dalop’s crown.
In short, we need to get this crown, right?
Yes.
You are such a loser.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
Why are you so afraid of the pageant?
Kat is really joining the pageant.
We have to stop her.
1 YEAR AGO.
What kind of beauty pageant is this?
It’s ridiculous.
The crown looks stunning.
Quiet.
They are about to announce the winner.
The winner is…
No one.
What?
None of the contestants is good enough.
The finalists are not good.
Our crown is very picky about its owner.
See you next year.
So this crown is the goddess’s second item?
That’s why no one won the crown
in the past two years.
They need to give it to someone this year.
Otherwise, this pageant will be so bullshit.
They hold the contest for three years.
But there is no winner.
What if…
Kat gets the crown?
It’s unlikely.
Their security is super tight.
They won’t let anyone steal it easily.
I’m not saying that she will steal it.
What if she wins the contest?
Win?
Are you crazy?
Why are you laughing? I’m serious.
Win?
That’s enough.
You think she can win the contest?
If you told me she would steal it,
it would be more believable, bitch.
That’s right.
You are worried over nothing.
What are we doing here?
We are here to spy on Kat.
If she’s going to steal the crown,
she must have some kind of plan.
(Are you resisting me?)
(I don’t want to do it anymore.)
(I’m tired.)
Listen.
She’s talking to someone.
I don’t want to do it anymore.
I’m tired.
Ouch.
Goddess, why did you hit me?
Thank you for hitting me.
You are such a loser.
You are so pathetic.
Ouch.
But I don’t want to do it anymore.
Get up.
Goddess.
Don’t pull my hair.
Should we step in and help her?
Goddess.
I will never join it.
Are you challenging me?
I won’t do it.
Fine.
Then I’ll push you again.
I’ll do it.
Goddess, please don’t push my head down.
This is not enough for you.
Goddess, I can’t breathe.
Okay.
I’ll join it.
I don’t believe you.
Let me go.
Girls.
Kat is really joining the pageant.
So?
Then we need to join the pageant too.
Why?
I don’t think we need to worry about it.
Look at her.
Even if she joins the pageant,
there’s no way she will win the crown.
I’m not saying that she will win.
What if she joins the pageant
to steal the crown?
We have to stop her.
Then we need to think about our chance
to win the contest.
In the end, pageants always choose
the winner based on their beauty.
I’m the one who should join the pageant.
Ing, are you sure
you can answer their question?
The questions round of the contest are tough.
Then I’ll volunteer to do it.
It’s not the time
to compete against each other.
We need to think carefully.
What is our goal?
Think rationally.
Our goal is to stop Kat.
Then who is the best choice for this mission?
Okay.
Do you have the answer?
Yes.
Take your time to think.
I’ll count to three,
and we will say it at the same time.
Sure.
Okay?
One.
Two.
Three.
Me.
I’m joking.
That’s a test round.
A test round?
This time, let’s do it seriously.
Okay.
Alright
Come on.
Okay, do you have the answer?
Yes.
I’ve carefully thought about it.
Okay.
One.
Two.
Three.
Me.
Why are you so afraid of the pageant?
Because the person
who most deserves to win the crown is…
It’s me.
Kat.
What are you doing here?
Why can’t a goddess like me join the pageant?
We need to do everything
to help me pass into the next round.
Gosh, I’m done.
You only think about yourself.
We will no longer follow your orders.
Ingky, you will pair up with me, right?
Don’t you want to have new partners?
My friends need me.
Between the power I can give you
and your stupid friendship,
what will you choose?
The goddess was right.
They are no longer my friends.