♪The arc of time♪
♪Splits the border♪
♪The sudden parting♪
♪The missing that has no timeline♪
♪Let go of myself♪
♪Hiding in the strange♪
♪Time without you♪
♪It's just saying goodbye♪
♪It's just meeting again♪
♪The changes of leaving you♪
♪Trying to take it easy♪
♪How do I deny♪
♪The past that I honored♪
♪Repeats in my memory?♪
=Almost Lover=
=Episode 5=
(Popcorn, malatang)
I'm not that late, right?
No.
Come on. What's the mission?
What mission?
Buy some snacks.
Record the crowd.
Talk to the owner.
He Xiaoran,
you like to bear grudges.
No, I just got to know
you didn't do that
just to
prank me.
I've been following you a few days
to amend the advertisement proposal
and try out new dishes.
Looking at how you've improved Jifeng
day by day,
I really admire you.
So, when you asked me about
the night market
that I frequent,
I knew
you must be doing
some market research again.
No.
I just want to eat something with you.
Here?
Didn't you think
snacks are not healthy?
Since I want to stay in
Wusu for good,
I need to know more about this city
and be part of this life.
You
are my only friend
here.
So,
I want to be part
of your life first,
is that okay?
Be part of my life?
Let's go.
Hurry.
(Tanghulu)
Your grilled fish belly.
I can eat
20 skewers on my own, try it.
Forget it. I...
Try it.
Forget it. I can't eat this.
I can't eat this.
Try it.
No, I can't eat this.
What's wrong?
You're an adult.
How can you tear your pants?
There's a stall selling clothes there.
Go buy a new pair of pants.
No need.
This is okay.
Really?
This is Turkish style.
Do you like red-crowned crane?
I don't like red-crowned crane.
Black and white is trendy.
Xiaoran,
why do I feel like you're
teasing me?
Am I?
What about this?
I have no other choice?
No more.
There's a washroom there.
Go try.
I'll wait for you here.
Okay.
What?
It's ugly?
No.
This color
matches our
high school uniform.
It seems so.
Here. Thank you.
Xiaoran.
Hello, Sui.
You didn't bring your keys?
Hello.
Okay.
Where did he go?
You've made the call?
Here. I bought two bottles of water.
What's wrong?
Sui forgot his keys again.
I'm leaving now.
Xiaoran.
You left
Xiao Shangqi behind
alone
in his old-school uniform?
You're something else.
I don't know why.
When I saw him in that shirt,
opening up the bottle
and the soda bursting out,
I felt like
there was an explosion in my head.
It's like something
has exploded.
So dramatic?
So many years have passed.
You still can't handle him.
It shows that the problem is serious.
Right?
But he has mentioned that
I'm his only friend
in Wusu. A friend.
It's my own fault.
It's not.
Xiao Shangqi keeps asking you out
for work and personal reasons.
Frequently meeting each other
can create the illusion
of falling for each other.
Yes.
What are you talking about?
You meet Sui every day.
I don't see you
falling in love with him.
Sui is different.
He's my brother from other parents.
Coming!
Hello.
I'm the engineer from Jifeng Hotel.
Hello, please come in.
It's done.
What are you doing?
Sui Mingwei,
you can finally throw away
your house keys.
Why? The lock has been changed?
Mr. Xiao asked someone to send it here.
Exclusive from the hotel.
Besides password,
it can be monitored remotely
and it can open up the lock.
It's much better than
your keys.
Can the door lock
be changed as you like?
Is this safe?
You just agreed to that?
What if
he just moves in next?
Xiaoran,
do you think this gift is thoughtful
or it's used to express
his dissatisfaction
for being abandoned on the street?
(Yunlan Jifeng Hotel)
How do you feel about
the two new dishes?
Not bad.
Actually, I'm not a professional.
I'm not sure
if my opinions on the new dishes
are useful or not.
Well,
thank you for the new lock.
But, three of us are living together.
Sui said it's better that
we split the bill.
As for the money I've transferred,
just take it.
Sui Mingwei?
You left in a hurry that night
because of him.
You care a lot about him.
He's my friend.
You left an old friend
who is not familiar
with the place
for a new local friend.
You're so mean.
No.
It's because...
Because of what?
Look.
That's the staff dormitory.
I'll take a look.
It's Morse code.
We played this in university.
Do you remember how to decode it?
Help me out.
♪Honey honey honey♪
Dit dah dit dit,
dah,
dah, dah,
dah dit dah dah,
dah dah dah,
dit dit dah.
♪Lucky lucky lucky♪
What does it mean?
Let me see.
♪My love has you in the future♪
(Good night, I love you.)
♪Sometime in the past♪
♪I'd like to share the sweetness♪
♪It makes my heartbeat different♪
Look at there.
That's your working area, right?
Same code.
They know how to have fun.
♪The reunion scene♪
♪I'm at east every second♪
Xiaoran,
actually I...
I...
Don't you think
it's a good topic?
Love code in the city.
Xiao Shangqi,
can you...
I really want to know the truth.
Who are you looking for?
Who are you?
I'm Taiyang.
Did you use the torchlight
to send signal?
I was saying good night to father.
Father?
Don't you say "good night"
and "I love you"
to your father before you go to bed?
Look.
He's my father.
His work is busy every day.
He comes home late.
Really?
Do you stay here alone
every day waiting for him?
A lady from the hotel
is taking care of me.
She is busy today, so she didn't come.
Okay.
We're here just to make sure
you're safe.
Let's go, Xiaoran.
Please wait.
Can you stay and hang out with me?
I don't want to sleep.
Why does it sound so familiar?
Sui,
you used to be very straightforward
in pursuing girls.
Why are you so passive this time?
Let me make this clear.
My florist shop will support you fully.
You're the man.
Sui,
go to my place.
I've matched up many couples.
Yes.
The fengshui at your place is not bad.
But some people
might look okay
on the outside,
but why is she
eating for free here?
I hope you'll give up sooner.
The double arrows are so obvious,
but you didn't see them.
Stop eating if you want
to keep teasing me.
Sui,
let me give you an idea.
At work, you're colleagues,
right?
At home, you're housemates.
You see her day and night.
What are you afraid of?
Just do to her
what she did to you.
I won!
Hurry!
One point.
Two points.
Taiyang.
Father!
Mr. Xiao?
I'm leaving now.
I didn't know you're a single father.
Yes.
This is not something that
I need to report to my superior.
Also, you've been asking Miss He
to go out
for work purpose
which is not necessary.
I didn't ask about that.
(Xiao Shangqi,)
(I've loved you)
(for a long time.)
(Good night, I love you.)
He Xiaoran,
calm down.
We must have met each other
too frequently
that I'm having
this illusion.
Yes,
it's illusion.
It's illusion.
Be nice.
(Good night, I love you.)
Miss Zhou and I are thinking
to bring this to the next level.
I'm thinking that we can arrange
a trending topic
for every episode of the program
that people will discuss.
Gather the related content
for this topic
and express our attitude.
Can we invite some guests?
Sure.
Or
a lucky draw.
It can attract more audiences.
Sui Mingwei,
stop pretending.
Tell us about your ideas.
(Short video livestream
program proposal)
Oh my goodness.
Did you write this?
Short video livestream?
(After the program,)
(do you want to eat supper with me?)
(I still have some works to do.
Maybe next time.)
(Xiao Shangqi After the program,
do you want to eat supper with me?)
(He Xiaoran I still have some works to do.
Maybe next time.)
Here, Lin's buns are ready to serve.
Come and eat some buns.
The filling is beef and scallions.
Just for sake of the buns
prepared by Mr. Lin
on every Friday,
I'm willing to work in Jifeng
for my entire life.
Stop it.
Well, Lin's buns are tasty.
Well, Mr. Lin,
we're not selling our hotel, right?
I can tell our guests
are increasing.
We're not selling.
Just work diligently.
The year end bonus
will be higher than last year's.
Finish the first one first.
Look.
Isn't that Miss He?
Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Xiao, why are you here?
All the staff on night shift
are up here.
Night shifts are tiring.
We're hungry
at this hour.
Mr. Lin's buns
are really tasty.
Do you want to try it?
(Hello, everyone.)
(This is the first livestream)
(of Dajiabang.)
(We just ended our program.)
(Were you guys listening?)
(You can interact with us)
(here.)
(By my side)
(is my colleague, Wei.)
(He'll tell you)
(some of our behind-the-scenes.)
(Hello, I'm Wei.)
(Do you want to know)
(some interesting matters)
(happened in the station?)
(I'll tell you.)
- So...
- To become a host...
- To become a...
Seems like we need to
practice more,
we've interrupted each other twice
within a minute.
Is there anything else that can
create more chemistry than this?
You can't say that.
I think
we work along well.
If we didn't work together,
I wouldn't have known
I can be so in sync
with a girl.
Stop it.
Even tango takes
two to dance.
Why not we discuss
before we talk next time?
Let's raise hand before we talk.
Or a hand sign.
No, it's too troublesome.
Why not like this?
If I interrupt you again,
I'll buy you a meal.
Audiences,
do I need someone to buy me a meal?
I need a job, okay?
They're so funny.
There's no chemistry at all.
Radio station hosts
should stay mysterious.
Right, Mr. Lin?
Yes.
But, Dajiabang
should be doing livestream
as the mission for the radio station.
Why not I ask Mr. Ma tomorrow?
Why are you so free?
Go back once you're done eating.
Not bad.
Both of them
have created the chemistry.
I didn't expect so many comments.
Let me read it out.
Before sleeping tonight,
I saw this livestream.
I was attracted
by this new weird couple.
There's more.
The daily teasing between them
is too funny. I love it.
I hope you two
will share more about your daily life
online.
I wish to see
Weihe Couple's livestream tomorrow.
Weihe Couple?
Not many people talked
about our show.
Mr. He,
you don't understand.
The netizens now
like to see couples.
It's happier than actual dating.
Why?
Low risk, low cost,
and no need to get involved
in the dating.
This kind of fans
are called couple fans.
Couple fans.
Xiaoran, what do you think?
Showing off.
(A full frame of pink bubbles.)
(Looks good! Are they new partners?)
(Are they a couple?)
(There's always a new couple.)
(They're a match made in heaven.)
(A full frame of)
(pink bubbles)
(is overflowing.)
Hello, everyone.
This is the pantry
in our station.
Normally, we'll be here
to talk and bluff.
We tease our boss here, right?
I've never done that.
Actually, I'd like to
introduce the food in our station
- (Even having a meal and)
- to all of you today.
- (a milk tea is same style.)
- Today,
this is the lunch in our canteen.
(Do they really need to be)
(so in sync?)
(It's egg custard in the middle.)
(There's also egg dumpling.)
(Strongly recommend the two hosts)
(to share more on their daily lives.)
(The rice in our station)
(is the best.)
(It's sticky, sweet and fragrant.)
(If you're free,)
(you can come and try it out.)
Sui, hurry.
Why are you here?
It's not easy to meet you,
Miss He.
We've been doing livestream lately.
I'm rather busy.
I watched it.
Did you?
What do you think?
Our audiences are engaged
with our discussion.
Do you want to join us?
Let's go to another place to talk.
Today, I have...
Today, she has something on.
It's about work.
Well, it speaks the same for us.
We're going to do livestream
at the forest park.
Yes, it's requested by the audiences.
The team leader asked us to
keep the momentum
and increase the exposure.
I'll go with you.
Let's rent a bicycle.
A bicycle?
It's a huge place.
Riding a bicycle
is faster.
I'm not in a hurry.
You don't know how to cycle?
Come on.
I know how to handle any of the wheels.
Sir,
we'd like to rent three bicycles.
I'm sorry, miss.
We only have
one left.
The rest has been booked
by a company.
That's unfortunate.
I think we can just walk.
It's the same.
I'm familiar with this place.
I can find the best view.
We have other vehicles.
Why not we play rock paper scissors?
The winner will cycle alone.
I can't ride this well.
Why not you ride with me?
We can nurture
our mutual understanding.
I don't need to cycle alone.
I'm too good at it.
You might not be able
to catch up with me.
So, you both don't want to
cycle on your own, right?
Great.
I'll take it.
Bye. Let's go.
He Xiaoran!
You like her?
Surprised?
Didn't you stay here
for her?
But, you're late.
Not too late.
Enough.
I know you two were classmates
in high school.
You were together for six, seven years.
Where have you been?
No one will stay and wait for you.
I'll pursue her.
Fine.
Let's see who is more capable.
Can you ride harder?
Are you even a man?
You can't even hold the handle!
I don't need you to teach me!
Slow down!
Can you be more stable?
He Xiaoran,
don't ride so fast!
Wait for us!
Hurry up, both of you.
I'll speed up.
Wait for you there.
Come on.
Don't let her look down on us.
Hurry.
Slow down.
Slow down a little.
You can't take the speed?
Do you know I...
Watch out!
I told you to slow down.
Be gentle.
Don't you know how to cycle?
I wouldn't have fallen
if it's not for the two people.
Yes, it's all others' fault.
You'll never fall on your own.
You were shaking at the back.
That's why we fell badly.
Yes, it's my bad.
Enough.
You two fell down
and you're still arguing.
Be careful.
Don't touch water today.
Won't you help me?
Turn around.
It hurts.
It hurts?
Paste this.
It's done.
Otherwise, the wound is healed.
Quite accurately pasted.
Is that okay?
Come over a bit more.
This background is not nice.
Come to this side.
- Come.
- This side.
- Come to this side.
- Here?
Here?
Stay away from her.
Otherwise, the structure is weird.
No one is asking you to take the video.
Just putting it here will do.
Livestream is about the content.
Audiences don't care about others.
I care.
Xiaoran, come here.
I have something to tell you.
The sky is going darker.
We'll talk after the livestream, okay?
He Xiaoran,
do you know what you're doing?
Have you read
all the comments on the platform?
Is this the work matter
that you wanted to speak to me?
I know.
Many of the comments
are about us as a couple,
but there are many audiences
who like our show, too.
They're interacting with us
and they've provided a lot
of materials and topics for us.
I think it's great.
I don't care about other things.
I do.
What are you trying to say?
Okay, Xiaoran, leave him alone.
We'll start the livestream.
Sui Mingwei!
You made her think that
your livestream is popular
and that you're busy for a good reason.
Is this all you got?
What do you mean?
I've asked someone to analyze
the users.
Actually, the comments are
not that many.
The users changed their IDs
and usernames frequently
to pretend like there are many of them.
It's fake.
Why did they do that?
Ask him.
I did it.
The comments were all
made by my friends.
Xiao Shangqi,
so you've been waiting for this?
Since then,
I'll be frank.
Xiaoran.
Let's go back first.
Xiao Shangqi, I'm sorry.
This is the internal matter
of Dajiabang.
I'll get to the bottom of the matter
and get back to you.
Listen, I don't need your
explanation.
You have to
because it's related to
our show
and the audiences' reputation.
Let's go.
Xiaoran!
Give it to me.
In our recent programs,
there were 100 over comments.
How many of them were
made by your friends?
Eight or nine of them.
Each one of them
made around 10 comments.
Some were made by
their friends.
It means our program
didn't get much attention.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to wear couple shirts with you.
I'm talking nicely to you.
We have to hype things up first.
Why not we
just start dating?
After all, we're happy
going out together.
Let's stop the livestream.
We didn't get much attention after all.
It's meaningless.
You were thinking about this?
Enough, I know you're doing this
for Dajiabang.
I won't tell others about this.
I'll just say
I don't want to use this method
to increase the viewership.
(Wusu Radio & TV Group)
Have you heard of
He Xiaoran and Jifeng's
Mr. Xiao's relationship?
Of course.
Dajiabang was stopped
because Mr. Xiao was not happy about it.
Also, the livestream at the forest park
few days back
was cancelled
because Mr. Xiao went there.
No wonder they got such a huge discount
for the open tendering.
He Xiaoran is something else.
I also heard that a fan
wanted to jump off the bridge
and Mr. Xiao sent him
away from Wusu.
I've recorded
what you said.
Defamation
is a crime.
What?
You dare not admit it?
What do you mean?
Forget it.
What do you mean what I mean?
Let's go.
Did you hear that?
Or did you see that?
Why are you doing this?
Enough.
Just let her say what she wants.
I don't care.
You don't care?
Why are you avoiding Xiao Shangqi
then?
He came here twice
and you gave excuses to leave.
Everyone can tell that.
I...
I'm...
What?
I'm guilty.
If that time
the way he was wearing
the sports attire
made me feel like
I'm in love again,
after so many days,
I should be fine by now,
but why am I
still feeling the same?
He Xiaoran,
you're so not He Xiaoran.
I've told you about
what happened to us.
Actually, for us to have met again,
although it's torturing,
I really treasure
this lost and found friendship.
But, no matter how much
you treasure the friendship,
it's not an excuse for you to
deny that you love him.
I think
since you haven't met him
for many years,
this guy who made you fall in love again
is a brand new guy.
Also, before him,
you're not the same.
Why do you think
it's the same as before?
I don't know.
During that eight years' time
of loving him,
I
dared not speak or ask.
I used "friends" as an excuse
to numb and hide myself,
but I know
real friends are
like you and Sui.
There's nothing you can't say.
There's nothing you can't ask.
Do you want to live the next eight years
not knowing what to do?
(Xiao Shangqi)
(Xiaoran,)
(I'm waiting for you downstairs.)
We need to interfere.
I hate this.
It affects my work.
Yes.
It's not comfortable
for anyone.
I can understand.
Mr. Xiao, I'll go over now.
Okay.
Xiaoran.
Mr. Ma.
Don't care about the rumors.
I'll handle it.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Xiaoran!
What's going on with you?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
Xiao Shangqi,
if you hate those rumors
and hate having anything to do with me,
please mind your own
manner and
keep a distance from me.
I'm sorry to have
caused you trouble,
but your action,
your care for me,
and you said you want
to be part of my life.
Don't you think what you did
is going to
cause misunderstanding?
It's not misunderstanding.
What's it then?
I hate those rumors
because our relationship
is not complicated.
He Xiaoran,
I love you.
(Blue Friend Creative Community)
Hello, please come in.
You're back.
Today, Hao gave me
a few bottles of good beer.
We'll have hot pot tonight.
You guys go ahead.
I don't want to eat.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
You came home with that face.
Have you made it clear to him?
I didn't get to speak
and I heard him say
he hates the rumor about he and I.
No, if he hates it, don't come back.
Don't be friends with me.
I'm upset with myself.
He wanted to be his good friend,
but I fell in love with him.
I thought it's over,
but it's not.
It's still the same.
What do you plan to do now?
Stop loss and retreat.
I'll just kill the spark of love
again.
I'm experienced.
(He Xiaoran)
If you hate those rumors
and hate having anything to do with me,
please mind your own
manner and
keep a distance from me.
(I confessed but she didn't respond.)
(What's going on?)
(There is no response after confessed.)
(A few possibilities.)
(First, think twice.)
(Think about)
(her response towards you.)
(If it's cold,)
(maybe she's looking for a chance)
(to reject you in a nice way.)
You're up?
Sit down.
The apology meal.
Well,
I was wrong for
making up the couple match-up.
I'll make it up to you from now on.
Thank you.
What happened to your throat?
I'm not feeling well.
We have to go on air tonight.
I'm sincere, but you're not blessed.
Well, you...
You eat something plain.
Eat something plain.
Where's Li Hui?
She's working.
Let's leave together later.
Motorcycle makes me dizzy.
Let's take a bus.
Are you saying my speedy,
stable motorcycle is making you dizzy?
It's time to change it.
I feel that it's making me dizzy, too.
Drink more.
Drinking more will do.
(What do I do)
(if she rejects my confession?)
(Trying to test her response)
(is easy.)
(Is she interacting with you)
(on your Moment?)
(If not,)
(think about whether your content)
(is hard to be engaged with or not.)
(Instead of keeping pursing her,)
(post something interesting on
your Moment)
(and try to have a common topic.)
(Xiao Shangqi)
(Has everyone taken breakfast?)
Sui told me that
your throat is not well.
I didn't know
Baidu and my rumors
make him so happy.
A guy who never posted on Moment
posted twice in the morning.
Mo.
Did you see my Moment?
Let me check now.
You're talking about this?
I saw it in the morning.
Why didn't you click like?
(Xiao Shangqi)
(Has everyone taken breakfast?)
Are you collecting likes now?
You have to tell me.
Otherwise, we won't know.
What collecting likes?
Are you not?
You're quite smart.
Don't use your phone at work.
♪Memory suddenly stops♪
♪Did I miss you too much?♪
♪The junction in the past♪
♪The lonely man has been waiting♪
♪Afraid of hearing
that we're just friends♪
♪Many excuses after turning around♪
♪Turning around in the time♪
♪Running towards the road of memory♪
♪I've been searching for so long♪
♪Found the wait that I owed you♪
♪Wanting to be with you♪
♪No more alone and wandering♪
♪I'd like to hold your hands
if love can start again♪
♪Being with you♪
♪Not letting go of each other♪