♪The arc of time♪
♪Splits the border♪
♪The sudden parting♪
♪The missing that has no timeline♪
♪Let go of myself♪
♪Hiding in the strange♪
♪Time without you♪
♪It's just saying goodbye♪
♪It's just meeting again♪
♪The changes of leaving you♪
♪Trying to take it easy♪
♪How do I deny♪
♪The past that I honored♪
♪Repeats in my memory?♪
=Almost Lover=
=Episode 26=
If you keep eating like this,
your stomach can't take it.
Drink two glasses of wine?
I have low tolerance.
I can't even try to get drunk.
Hao.
Give me three bottles of beer.
Okay.
As long as you're happy.
I'm here for you.
(Blue Friend Creative Community)
Li Hui.
I, Sui Mingwei,
have skipped classes,
slept in the exam,
idled at work
and treated women poorly
in the past 20 years.
I didn't know that it all
came back to me today.
What comes around goes around.
Tell me.
Do you think
I'm not being serious enough this time?
Do you believe that
I can even die for her?
Yes.
I went there with her that day.
Why did I agree
to split up with her?
I'm always one step
later than Xiao Shangqi.
One step later,
and every step later.
I can never catch up with her.
I just want to keep her company,
wait for her,
and be nice to her.
End of the day,
I've only moved myself.
Just
withdraw as early as possible.
I'm not interested
in your drama anymore.
Yes,
it's time.
You need to treat her well
if you like her.
It's not about moving yourself.
Li Hui,
let me ask you
one last question.
One last question.
Hurry up.
If it was you
who grew up with Xiao Shangqi,
will you fall in love with him?
No way.
Am I that bad?
Even you won't choose me.
You're crazy.
Sui,
you've been keeping
Xiaoran company all this time
with a sincere heart.
I know you're serious.
I also know you've been hurt badly.
You've changed
so much for her.
You've even gone back to work
in the fragrance factory.
But, no matter how you change,
you can't become
another person.
You can't become the person
in her heart.
But, I think
it's great.
It's not a bad experience.
Look at the previous you.
You were not being serious.
Now, you've finally understood
how it's like...
How it's like
to really love someone.
I think I'm quite good.
Don't be surprised.
It's not going to happen
like having sex after drinking
in the drama.
We're adults.
We can't really do that.
You're quite frank.
I didn't mean that.
I was just
shocked.
The last time we were on the same bed
was during our primary school days.
Right?
You should
get me changed.
Don't try to make your way through.
Well.
Whenever I got my heart broken,
you'd just throw me in the living room.
What happened this time?
You've taken care of me the whole night
with clothes on.
Do you think I wanted
to take care of you?
You were drunk and
you went crazy last night.
I said I'll wait for you,
and then I...
I fell asleep.
To be honest, Hui,
you're the only woman
that will not be misunderstood
for sleeping with me on my bed.
Let's go. I'll buy you breakfast.
No, you should buy me breakfast.
I'm not going.
I have something on.
I wasn't drunk.
I don't care.
I remember what
you said at Hao's place.
You said you'll take care of me.
Let's go.
Look after the house, okay?
Blindfold and earplug.
(Wusu Shenghe Hospital)
Mr. Xiao,
it's quite cold lately.
The hospital is not
as good as your hotel.
You may catch a cold or a fever easily.
If it leads to coughing and pneumonia,
you'll suffer.
What's going on?
The other patients
just wipe their bodies.
He insisted on washing his hair.
He'll catch a cold.
He has to wash his hair every day.
No problem, I've brought a hairdryer.
Thank you.
Blow it dry.
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
I asked Mo
to get the things for
my hospitalisation,
but he didn't get everything.
Even the socks are not in pairs.
You had to go one more time.
Maybe he's not familiar with
where you keep your things.
Mr. Xiao, you must be starving.
I...
I was worried
no one is taking care of you.
I picked up Taiyang
and came here immediately.
I wouldn't have rushed if I knew.
Yesterday, he said he needs something
for his hospitalisation.
So, I took them
for him today.
I'm about to leave.
Help him out.
No, Xiaoran.
Well,
Mr. Xiao's hospitalised lately.
Jifeng's workload
is all on me now.
I also need to take care of Taiyang.
Well,
I'm not that young anymore.
I can hardly catch up
with my age.
Look at
my huge eye bags.
Who forced you to come?
You know Mr. Xiao well.
He's picky
and short-tempered.
He's offended
all the medical staff here.
If you're free lately,
and since I can't come here often,
can you come over
and take care of him?
His family is not here.
He got injured because of me.
I should take care of him.
That's what I wanted to hear.
I'll pass your contact to the doctor.
Mr. Xiao, if you need anything,
look for Xiaoran.
Well, the meal...
I'll put the meal here.
Hurry up.
Blow his hair dry.
I'm leaving now.
You might catch a cold
if your hair is not dry.
The ribs will hurt.
Blow his hair dry.
I'm sorry.
Blow your hair dry quickly.
Xiaoran.
Thank you.
It's all fixed.
The water pipe is old.
The connector was broken.
Thank you.
Luckily, you found out about it in time.
I've also
tidied up your washroom.
Are you still having bulimia?
Sit here and eat.
No need.
Xiaoran said she's not
coming back tonight.
She'll go to the TV station for overtime
straight from the hospital.
She goes to the hospital every day.
Can she take it?
You haven't let it go yet
or this is the concern
for a friend?
I'll never regret
the decision I made
ever since I was young.
So, I understand it
as you're planning to
befriend Xiaoran
and you don't plan to
stay away from her.
Then I don't have to
just communicate with
either of you alone,
right?
I'm not that unforgiving.
I just don't want her to feel bad.
Do you think Xiaoran
is that unforgiving?
I'll be performing with others
at Hao's place
this weekend.
Come over.
Grab the chance
and talk things out.
Romance is all about feelings
and it can't be forced.
Friends stay together forever though.
Do you want some extra flavour?
Chilli.
I don't want.
Why not?
What's going on?
Do you want to drink water?
No.
Hello, Lili.
Xiaoran,
there's a multiple vehicle collision
on the highway.
Some of the injured victims are sent to
the hospital where you are.
Go and have a look.
Do a report on that if you can.
Okay, I'll get down there now.
A multiple vehicle collision.
I'll go and have a look.
Xiaoran.
Move.
Sir,
can you tell me
how the accident happened?
I'm the journalist from Wusu TV Station.
It was horrible.
The cars knocked into each car's trunk.
Two of them were big trucks
carrying rebar.
The rebar pierced through
the rear window glass.
It was horrible.
How many people were injured?
Come on, move.
Stop taking the photo. You're disturbing us.
Are you okay?
Don't mind their attitude.
It's okay.
Didn't I get
paint poured all over my body?
This is my job.
Record all the news,
be it good or bad,
keep it real, effective and fast.
Xiaoran,
I feel like I can see
how you'll become a war correspondent.
Your faith and persistence
make your dream
closer and closer to you.
I'll continue to pursue it.
Lin Zong just informed me that
the mobile phone is fixed.
I've looked for a colleague
in the construction industry
to contact
someone he knows well
in quality control
and see if they can find anything.
Okay.
No matter what you find,
tell me about it.
He, what did it go?
Look at the photo you took.
The wall is falling off
little by little.
Based on my experience,
the concrete's not that solid anymore.
What do you mean?
It means the wall
is not hard.
Just like when you hang some heavy rack
on the wall,
it will just slide down.
You can't hang anything on it.
Also,
the leaking here
is really serious.
The rebar will rust after a long time.
The building will
go out of shape easily.
For example,
the window will damage easily
and can't be closed. It's possible.
In conclusion,
the building is not in a good shape.
It has to be demolished.
So, is this a tofu-dreg project?
I dare not say so.
I suggest you
look for our colleague
in doing a quality check
to take a look.
The building is not
fully demolished.
Get a wall
that's intact.
Test it with a rebound hammer
and we'll know.
Also,
this rebar
seems to be too small.
This kind of building
should use size 22.
This doesn't look like it.
I'm about to go back to Hupu.
I came to see you before I leave.
Those people really
gave you a hard time.
I've paid
for your medical bill.
Mr. Zhao, you came here
just to tell me this?
Guess why I'm here
today.
Are you trying to repeat what you did?
Mr. Zhao,
I don't have a heart disease.
Don't you want to know
what I said to your father
in the patient ward?
Do you still remember?
Your family and mine once
went to the sea together.
Qi was lying on the deck.
There was a wave
and he fell into the sea
as the boat was shaking.
What happened then?
Xiao Xian became crippled.
You were in the hospital
scolding Qi.
He told him that his brother's life
was ruined by him.
You said you'll never forgive him
for what he did.
If I'm not mistaken,
this is
the hospital you were in.
What are you trying to say?
I pushed him off into the sea.
What did you say?
I pushed
Xiao Shangqi off into the sea.
Shangqi
was lying on the deck
to check on the fish.
When the wave came
and the boat was shaking,
I pushed him down.
Qi!
Xian, help me!
He didn't feel it.
He thought
he fell off on his own.
Zhao Mingxuan.
Actually,
I hated Xiao Shangqi the most
since I was young.
He's so full of himself.
I remember
my father always beat my mother
when he came home.
Why are you so stupid?
Xiao Shangqi is a few years
younger than him,
but he's so much better.
Hire him a teacher tomorrow
to teach him public speaking.
You're not allowed to eat and sleep
if you can't talk well.
The reason was
that I wasn't educated
as excellent as the kids
in Xiao family.
Isn't that ridiculous?
It's ridiculous.
A great chance like this
was hard to come by.
Do you think
I'll just let it go?
What I didn't expect is that
Xiao Xian went in and saved him.
He also made it.
Qi.
Xiao Xian has become crippled.
He can never fight against me anymore.
As for Xiao Shangqi,
I have to thank you.
You're my accomplice.
You've hurt him so bad.
You don't know, right?
Xiao Shangqi had been crying to me
when he was young.
And for a long period of time,
he treated me
better than you and Xiao Xian.
He thought that
I'm the closest person to him.
Don't you think
it's more interesting than
having him dead?
You're a madman.
Yes,
I'm a madman.
So, you better don't
take a madman's word lightly.
Zhao Mingxuan,
you're shameless.
Get lost.
There's really no remorse pill
in the world.
So, I advise you
to come to your sense
and stop doing something
that can make you regret it.
Are you serious, Mr. Xiao?
You can't even stand
this bit of stimulation?
I think you should retire.
Zhao Mingxuan.
Do you think
you can have a great time
with your father?
No more.
Never ever again.
You're someone
not worthy to be loved
and win.
Also,
stop pestering me.
Otherwise, I'll also take He Xiaoran
away from you.
Don't learn from your father
and repeat the same mistake.
There is something
that once you lost,
you can never get it back anymore.
You have too many flaws.
All that you've told me now
will only motivate me
to defeat you.
I'll find the evidence.
You're too naive, Qi.
You won't be able to find anything.
You have weakness, but I don't.
So, you can never defeat me.
You can only be manipulated by me.
Go back.
How can you fight against me
as you're so weak?
Take care.
Xiao Shangqi.
I think
Qingshan Nursing Home
is a tofu-dreg project.
Maybe from the beginning itself,
I've got the direction wrong.
I said
we should go to
the construction site now.
Look at him.
I've advised him for half a day.
We'll go with some people. You...
I've met Zhao Mingxuan in the afternoon.
Let's go to the construction site.
(Employee channel)
That's fast.
When we came last time,
half of the site was not demolished.
Mr. Xiao.
I've asked around.
They have been working in
the construction site day and night.
They got complained a lot
due to this reason.
But, luckily we
have some photos as the evidence.
The photos are not comprehensive.
It can't prove that it's taken here.
Now, the entire Qingshan Nursing Home
is gone.
It's harder to find any evidence.
(You're too naive, Qi.)
(You can't find anything.)
I should've thought of it.
He came and looked for me.
It means everything has been
taken care of.
Mr. Xiao.
High fever.
39.2 degree Celsius.
He needs to be monitored closely.
He'd better not get any pneumonia.
One of you should stay back tonight.
Okay.
Thank you.
Lin Zong,
go home and take care of Taiyang.
I'll stay back.
Okay.
Call me
if you need anything.
Don't worry.
(Zhao Mingxuan)
Monitor what's going on in the hospital.
Okay, let's talk tomorrow.
Where have you been?
You didn't call me back
for days.
I keep you here
not for you
to ask me questions.
I've brewed tea for you to
dispel the effects of alcohol.
It's turned cold.
I'll heat it up.
You really look like
Xiao Xian.
You know your place.
How close you were
with Xiao Shangqi?
Why didn't you learn how to be tough
from him?
You knew that the news
was fake.
It doesn't matter.
Now, everyone will
think of the scandal
when they see you.
You're like a joke.
I'll get the tea.
If you can't even
do this,
you're not qualified to stay here.
(You're not worthy to be loved.)
(You're not worthy to be happy.)
(You'll lose)
(everything you love.)
(Once you've)
(lost something,)
(you'll never be able to regain it.)
(Yunlan Jifeng Hotel)
Lin Zong.
I'm here to get the meal.
Let me deliver it today.
Don't you need to keep Taiyang company?
Also,
Xiao Shangqi sent me a text,
asking me not to go.
How's his recovery?
You're here in time.
Talk to him.
He's not even taking his medicine.
Yesterday's medicine
is still on the table.
He also wants to be discharged.
Look at his status.
The doctor won't allow him to discharge.
I'll bear
the consequences myself.
Why are you here?
You called her here?
I...
Let me talk to him.
What are you doing?
You've been acting weird
after your fever was gone that morning.
Lin Zong said
you didn't eat or sleep
in the past two days.
You were only looking
outside the window.
How can you recover then?
You must be tired from
taking care of me.
Leave me alone.
Are you trying to take a break again?
Who are you to decide my life?
You order me around as you please.
Does that make you happy?
What did Zhao Mingxuan say to you?
I know.
You never trusted me
even when
we were together.
You think I don't deserve
to share the ups and downs
in your life.
What more now.
Fine, I'm leaving now.
Do as you please.
Maybe he's right.
I'll always be the loser.
He caused Xian to become crippled.
He pushed me off
into the sea on purpose.
My awful life
in the past 20 years
was caused by him!
I don't want to fight
against him anymore.
I don't want those whom I love
to be hurt by him anymore.
Xiaoran.
I'm scared.
Since you're not eating
or drinking here,
it's a waste of resources staying here.
Get changed and come with me.
How did it go?
Where are you
going, Xiaoran?
Don't worry.
I'll bring him back in one piece.
What he needs now
is not physical treatment.
Hello, Mr. Xiao and Mrs. Xiao.
Mr. Xiao, it's been a while.
I'm sorry
that I only came to see you now.
Although I can sense that
you looked strict,
you're the same as every father
in the world.
It turns out bad
when you show concern.
Sometimes,
you didn't know how to communicate.
You didn't know how to
express your fatherly love,
(Xiao Zhenyun, Bai Yunying)
so you acted like a strict father.
However, you loved him
from the bottom of your heart, right?
(Xiao Zhenyun)
You haven't planted any flowers
with Xiao Shangqi, have you?
In my memory,
you've never celebrated
his birthday with him.
The Xiao Shangqi I know
has distanced
himself from others
and always pulled a long face
for a long period of time.
It's like he was wearing a mask.
But as his best friend,
I know
he thirsts for love
and concern.
Now, we know the truth.
It's just that something
can't be made up anymore.
You're buried here.
What about him?
Your son.
He's not doing well.
He's not eating, drinking
or sleeping.
If this goes on,
his body can't take it.
He wants to live
a haphazard life.
He thinks he doesn't need to be loved
or to be concerned.
Mr. Xiao,
is this what you want to see?
You were managing Yunlan diligently
to take care of the family of three.
Now, you're gone.
Is this home
going to dismiss?
Are you not expecting anything
from Xiao Shangqi anymore?
Have you severed ties with him?
Does everything not matter anymore?
Did you have no regrets
when you passed away?
Xiao Shangqi.
You have the answers
to all my questions, right?
If you don't,
stand here today,
look at Mr. Xiao and think about it.
I have a feeling that
if you're willing to stay here,
Yunlan will take off.
Another thing that makes me happier
is that you and I
will have more time
to get to know
each other more.
You can tell
how happy he is
after you came home.
He also said how sorry
he was that
he has sent you overseas
in the past few years.
(It's stopped you from shining.)
(In conclusion, he really)
(expects a lot from you.)
I'll get back the things
that you protected one by one.
I'm sorry.
♪Memory suddenly stops♪
♪Did I miss you too much?♪
♪The junction in the past♪
♪The lonely man has been waiting♪
♪Afraid of hearing
that we're just friends♪
♪Many excuses after turning around♪
♪Turning around in the time♪
♪Running towards the road of memory♪
♪I've been searching for so long♪
♪Found the wait that I owed you♪
♪Wanting to be with you♪
♪No more alone and wandering♪
♪I'd like to hold your hands
if love can start again♪
♪Being with you♪
♪Not letting go of each other♪