♪Obsessions penned
into an everlasting love♪
♪Affections gently linger
around fingertips♪
♪May stars guide us through rough waves♪
♪I give all my love unreservedly♪
♪May transient frost♪
♪Persist through obstacles for love♪
♪I wait for you to look back
in this rocky life♪
♪I can stay for the promise♪
♪Despite seasons recur♪
♪The love deep within
will transcend time♪
[Secrets of the Shadow Sect]
[Episode 5]
Master.
You intrude my room
without permission.
How dare you!
He's my shadow guard
sent by the Shadow Sect.
Please calm down, Master Ling.
Shadow guards should
never leave their masters.
Just now, I saw an outsider come in.
I'm worried about Master.
So I behaved recklessly
and disturbed you.
Outsider?
Who is that outsider?
The person who came in just now
is my wife.
Do you not recognize her?
I just graduated.
I'm to blame
for not recognizing Madam Yu.
Please forgive me, Master Ling.
You!
Father.
I just took this guard in.
I'm still interested in him.
If you kill him,
I will be upset.
He protects his master.
Quite a loyal dog.
In that case,
Xuan,
take him away.
Yes.
Yingshi is rude.
I will punish him after this.
Please get rest early.
I will take my leave now.
[Tianze Hall]
Master.
How did you get hurt?
This isn't a safe place.
Get me back to my abode first.
[Cangyu Abode]
What has happened, Mother?
Why are you so anxious?
I took away
the Pipa player's son.
Just now, I was informed
that the child had disappeared.
There has been no news
about the Pipa player
for some days.
Xuan is still in one piece,
but she disappeared.
Isn't that obvious?
It's better if she has died.
The thing is,
her child disappeared.
Something must've happened.
Just now, I saw her
in your father's room.
The way she looked at me
was very strange.
The shadow guard at the door
was also staring
at me.
I fear that if the lowly woman
gave me up
after failing to assassinate her.
This would be troublesome.
A shadow guard?
Not a single shadow guard
has been seen by her side
all these years.
Why would she allow a shadow guard
to escort her today?
These are just trivial.
Please help me think about
what to do
if this assassination is exposed.
Mother, I warned you
that Xuan's residence might be a trap.
But you insist on disturbing her.
Now that this has happened,
you only have yourself to blame.
You are Master Ling's only son.
But she took advantage of her identity
as the first legitimate child
to get in your way.
But I have no desire for power.
If Xuan weren't
the eldest legitimate child,
I wouldn't have been born,
and you wouldn't have had
the current position.
I'm doing this for your sake.
I know you mean well to me.
It's getting late.
Mother, please go back and rest.
I'm leaving.
All right.
A shadow guard?
What's wrong with Young Master?
What has happened to her?
Yingshi.
Be honest with me.
Have you been in contact
with the Shadow Sect
after coming here?
I was summoned.
Why did they summon you in secret?
It's just some routine advice.
Pay no mind to that, Master.
Please get rest early.
Forget it.
You may go.
Yes.
Young Master.
What has happened in the main hall?
Why did you get hurt so badly?
Since she knows I'm in contact
with the Shadow Sect,
why did she allow me
to walk her to the main hall?
Young Master, are you saying
that Yingshi barged into
Master Ling's room
to find you?
Over the years,
I haven't heard of anyone
who could leave in one piece
after barging
into Ling Yuanzheng's place,
let alone his room.
Anyway,
thankfully, Young Master is brought
out of the main hall.
Ling Yuanzheng spared him.
It means Chiye has informed him
about this.
Ling Yuanzheng
has always been wary of us.
Your shadow guard barged into his room,
but he let it slide
and allowed him to take you out.
But if we couldn't expect this,
couldn't Yingshi?
I think he was
just too anxious.
Don't be sentimental.
It will affect our plan.
Besides,
he has been in contact with Shadow Sect
behind Young Master's back.
From what I have seen,
this is very likely
a well-planned setup to save you
from Master Ling.
That is to win your trust.
Young Master.
It's best to do something about him.
Indeed.
I'm afraid Yingshi
might have to leave.
Does it hurt?
But I'm willing to respond
to your request.
I have someone
feed her son with an Oblivion Pill
and send him back to Yongzhou
to reunite with his mother.
Perhaps
she isn't as terrible as rumored.
Sir.
I would like to test
the skills of
a First Class shadow guard.
Watch out for my sword.
You would better watch yourself.
♪If hand waves are
the prelude to farewell♪
♪If words hold no intention to stall♪
♪Goodbye♪
♪Should be reserved
for when our lives are at stake♪
♪If time rushes swiftly
like wind and dust♪
♪If tears come before words
after waking up♪
♪May you not be drowned in bitterness♪
♪I only wish your eyes♪
♪As pure as snow♪