=Sword and Fairy 1=
=Episode 4=
Ling'er.
Ling'er, what happened?
Xiaoyao, this is great.
I'm so glad you're alive.
Ling'er,
did you do something to me?
That woman just stabbed me.
How come I'm all right now?
Let me get you up.
Come on.
Ling'er,
did you use any witchcraft to save me?
I used the Resurrection Spell.
The Resurrection Spell?
A healing technique my master taught me.
Before, I failed to master it.
When I saw you pass out, I was so worried
that I tried this technique.
Thank you, Ling'er.
But I've heard
forcibly using an unmastered witchcraft
will easily make someone lose his mind.
From now on,
don't risk your life anymore.
How do you feel now?
Would you like some rest?
No need.
I just exhausted some spiritual power.
Are you sure?
Mad girl...
You'd better wish I wouldn't see you again.
Ling'er, it's getting late.
It's too dangerous to stay here.
Let's get to Suzhou City early.
All right.
What's wrong?
Snake Demon! Snake Demon!
I'm fine, Xiaoyao.
Just some numbness in my feet.
Then walk slowly. I'll help you.
It's all right, Xiaoyao.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
All right.
Where's he?
This is his blood.
Miss, there isn't too much blood.
But I'm sure
I just pierced his body.
Miss, he didn't lose too much blood
and he left safely.
It means he wasn't in great danger.
But I stabbed him...
It's all right.
Fine. He's just lucky enough.
(Suzhou City)
Where are you from?
Why do you want to get into Suzhou City?
We're from Yuhang Town
and we want to get accommodation.
In you go.
Lately, there have been snakes around.
Take care of your wife.
All right.
Thanks.
(Xiangyu Inn)
Come in, please.
Come in.
Lady and gentleman,
welcome.
What do you want, food or accommodation?
Accommodation. Two rooms, please.
Gentleman, are you here
for the combat for marriage?
- No.
- Then sorry.
Our guest rooms are full.
Full?
No way.
For the next seven days,
all the guest rooms in town have been taken.
All the guest rooms?
Who did that?
Mr. Lin of Lin Fortress.
At this time every year,
he holds a combat for marriage
and rents all the guest rooms
for participants coming from other places
free of charge.
I'm not a participant.
How about I pay for the rooms?
Landlord, if the rooms aren't full,
please give us one room.
Miss,
it's not that I don't give you a room.
But Mr. Lin has paid for the rooms.
He's taken all the rooms.
Let's go, then.
(Lin Fortress)
Wait. Stop.
Miss.
Listen.
The man is about 5.4 chi tall
and he looks poor.
He has a sword wound.
The girl is as elegant and beautiful as me.
Get them to me at whatever cost.
Yes.
Yueru.
(Lin Tiannan)
Made some trouble again?
Father.
I told you
not to make trouble out of home.
I didn't make trouble.
Confess.
The east or the west of the city?
I went out of the city.
Out of the city?
Some girls have been missing.
How dare you go out of the city?
Father, I'm no longer a kid.
I can be responsible for whatever I do.
Just leave me alone.
Don't blame me for being nagging.
Your mother died at a young age.
If I don't bother about you,
who else will?
The combat for marriage will be held tomorrow.
As long as you get a good husband,
I won't worry about you anymore.
I'm not getting married, anyway.
I made inquiries.
This time, a lot of great young men have come.
Someone will satisfy you, I believe.
Who knows
what they really want to be,
your son-in-law or my husband?
Aren't they just the same?
You just wish.
Yueru.
Chief Lin,
how about we negotiate?
On what?
If no one can defeat me just as before,
never hold this humiliating event again.
Why do you think it's humiliating?
I don't care. Either you listen to me
or I have to offend you.
Yueru, let's talk about this.
If you don't approve,
I'll shave my head and be a nun!
Fine. We'll do it your way.
All right.
Clap hands for the pledge.
If no one can't defeat me,
don't force me to get married again.
Deal.
So many sky lanterns over there.
Uphill grow trees,
- on the trees boughs grow.
- They're so high.
My heart goes to you,
but you don't know.
So high.
(Liu Jinyuan)
I can portray Yueru perfectly,
but I can't win her heart.
Come out here!
You little naughty boy!
(Yiyang Restaurant)
I got you at last.
You sneaked in for free food.
- Believe it or not, I'll kill you!
- Sir, I won't dare to steal again.
- I won't.
- What are you doing?
Mercy?
- Sir!
(Douzi)
Sir, I won't steal anymore!
I just won't!
- Why are you bullying a kid?
- You're all right now.
He stole food from my restaurant.
I guess I can beat him.
How much can a kid eat?
Are you kicking so hard to kill him?
Who are you, rube?
Mind your own business. Go away.
How can you still be so rude?
Just a little money for food. I'll pay.
Fine.
If you pay,
I'll apologize to him.
- That's what you said.
- Yes.
How much?
Fifty taels.
What?
For one month, a whole family
only spends 1.5 taels of silver on food.
And you want fifty taels?
Such strong appetites!
He has a strong appetite, actually.
His stomach is like a bottomless pit.
If I hadn't found him in time,
he would have eaten everything in my kitchen.
How could this happen?
You don't believe me?
Then ask him.
Kid,
where are your parents?
I don't know.
Why did you steal food?
I'm starving and I want more food.
Xiaoyao,
let's buy him enough food.
All right.
Landlord, give him enough food
until he gets full.
Sure. I'll go prepare the dishes.
Serve the dishes.
He almost ate up everything.
Kid, what's your name?
- Anything available, then.
- I'm Douzi.
You must be kidding.
Such a big plate of rice.
How can a kid like him finish it?
You just wait and see. You'll know.
Here. Eat.
Still starving?
Landlord, get him more food.
Ling'er,
if he keeps eating like this,
we won't be able to afford the food.
Is this kid sick or something?
Looks like he has a Demon Worm inside him.
Demon Worm?
I read about it
in the library of Water Moon Palace.
But I can't remember very clearly.
So, I'm not quite sure.
Miss, do you mean the Gluttony Demon Worm?
Just now,
I drank too much.
More than too much,
I guess.
Thanks for reminding me.
That's exactly the Gluttony Demon Worm
I read about in the book.
Miss, I'm suddenly full, I think.
Douzi, come out with me.
This is the Gluttony Demon Worm.
Have a look.
When it gets into someone's stomach,
he'll always feel starving
as if he could never be full.
Feeling any better, Douzi?
Miss, I don't feel starving anymore.
Douzi...
I thought it was just a story in a book.
But it turned out to be real.
Unexpectedly, an alcoholic like you
has read quite a lot of books.
You flatter me.
I'm just the Number One Scholar of our country.
Miss,
do you know
why this kind of demon appeared in this city?
All things reinforce and restrain each other.
The appearance of the Gluttony Demon Worm
indicates
a quite strong demon nearby.
Recently, a Snake Demon has occupied
the Dragon-hidden Cave outside Suzhou City.
It invades the city repeatedly
and many young girls
have been missing for no reason.
Everyone panics.
Snake Demon! Snake Demon!
Gentleman,
I'm from Shushan Sect,
the biggest sect in the country.
If you need any help, let me know.
That'd be great.
I'm Liu Jinyuan.
And who are you?
I'm Li Xiaoyao.
And this is my...
My...
This is Zhao Ling'er.
Mr. Li.
Miss Zhao.
I'm a mere scholar
and I usually adore strong martial artists.
We really hit it off today.
I wonder if you'd like to drink with me.
Tea, I mean.
If I knew you were Mr. Liu's friend,
I would have given you the best rooms.
Sorry about the rude welcome.
Please enjoy it.
This is my uncle's property.
You can stay without worry. Come on.
Let's drink some tea instead of wine.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Zhao looks gorgeous
and intelligent.
Li, you two make a perfect couple.
You flatter us.
We aren't a couple.
Don't be ridiculous.
Liu.
What's bothering you?
Li, I'm ashamed to say this,
but the girl I adore
happens to be the daughter of my uncle.
Then...
She's your cousin, huh?
I'm in one-sided love with her.
But she'll have a combat for marriage tomorrow.
Then ask your uncle to marry her to you.
I tried that before.
But my uncle...
He only thinks highly of martial artists.
Will you just watch
when someone else marries her?
That may not happen, though.
But...
What if...?
She must be a wonderful girl,
so you've been
this obsessed with her.
Speaking of my cousin,
she's really extraordinary.
Though she is a lady,
she has been extremely helpful.
She's straightforward.
She loves what she loves
and hates what she hates.
She tries to rid the world of injustice.
And she's as excellent as a great man.
But inwardly,
she's very gentle, too.
Such an extraordinary lady.
I'm really curious
and how I wish I could see her!
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu?
Does she like you?
I...
I don't know.
Liu,
do you want to win and marry your cousin?
Yes, of course!
- But I...
- I have a plan
to make you get what you want.
- I'm all ears.
- Come on.
(Jinyuan Inn)
Xiaoyao, you're awake.
Without my aunt's terrible morning call,
I really had some great sleep.
Ling'er.
What time is it?
It's about the Wei Hour.
[*One in the afternoon]
Xiaoyao, you slept too long.
Where's Liu?
He's gone to the combat for marriage.
Let's go and watch.
We can also ask around
and see if any businessmen
are going to Nanzhao.
Make way, please.
Ling'er, come on.
Look over there.
(Combat for Marriage)
(Gathering of Talents)
So many people are here.
So crowded.
Make way, please.
At this time of the year, Suzhou City...
Xiaoyao,
such a bustling place.
Martial artists came from all over the country
just to marry Miss Lin, huh?
I don't quite agree.
More than half of the participants
who have come here
want to take a marvelous step
with the help Lin Tiannan,
chief of his sect.
Or they just want his property.
In my opinion, no one
will win this combat just like before.
Yeah.
Miss Lin has been learning
her family's great martial arts.
Since she was 13, no men in Suzhou City
have ever defeated her.
To beat her down
can be immensely difficult.
Ling'er,
the lady of the combat
seems to be from a rich family, too.
And she can do martial arts.
Can she be the crazy woman we met yesterday?
No way.
According to Mr. Liu,
Miss Lin is very gentle.
If Miss Lin was gentle,
there wouldn't be any rude girl in the world.
Today,
you can see
the most fierce woman in Suzhou City.
Keep your voice down.
If she hears you, she'll cut your tongue.
Does Miss Lin have a tall and thin figure,
a long face,
straight eyebrows and big eyes?
Oh, she...
There she is.
She's coming up.
She's up there.
Miss Lin.
(Be Wise and Brave)
That's really her.
Nice!
(Be Wise and Brave)
Miss Lin.
What a small world!
Xiaoyao,
how about we leave now?
No hurry.
Today, I'd like to see
who will marry this fierce woman.
Master Lin.
Dear swordsmen...
This is
a combat for my daughter's marriage.
Thank you all for coming
and participating
in this event.
This year's rule remains the same.
Whoever beats my daughter off the stage
will marry into my family
and become my son-in-law.
- Nice!
- Great!
There you go.
Hurry. You go first.
Why hasn't Liu come yet?
The combat now begins!
- Nice!
- Great!
I'll go first.
Master Lin,
I'd like to call you Father-in-law now.
Come on, Miss Lin.
Next.
The pretty girl is mine.
Bravo.
Miss Lin is awesome.
Bravo!
Come on, Miss Lin.
Get lost!
Next.
- Nice!
- Bravo!
Miss Lin has such great martial arts.
Impressive.
Will anyone else try?
Anybody else?
You go there.
Go.
Me!
I...
I'd like to have a try!
Come on!
Fight! Fight!
Yueru.
Jinyuan?
Mr. Liu is there.
I have faith in you.
It's him.
Jinyuan, why are you here?
To marry you, of course.
Get down there. Don't embarrass yourself.
Yueru, there are no restrictions
for the participants of this combat.
So, right here, I'm not your cousin,
but an ordinary participant.
Well, I won't show mercy, then.
Bring it on, Yueru.
- Bravo!
- Nice!
Mr. Liu turns out to be so strong.
I can't make you win.
But I can make you not lose.
I'm all ears.
There are patterns for all martial arts.
As long as you remember all her moves,
she can hardly beat you down.
People don't kill in a combat.
When you aren't defeated,
you'll be winning another way, right?
So, you've remembered all my moves.
Yueru, you can't hit me.
I won't hurt you, either.
How about
you give in?
I never give in.
The last ten moves.
Unless I kick you off the stage,
you will win.
Bring it on.
One, two, three...
Four, five, six...
Seven, eight...
Nine... Nine...
The last move.
The very last.
Bravo!
Yueru.
Brilliant!
Fight! What are you waiting for? Fight her.
Yueru!
You'd better give in.
Fight.
Fight her.
Jinyuan.
Mr. Liu.
Liu.
Come on.
Mr. Liu.
Number One Scholar,
that was close. Why were you tempted?
Li, don't say that.
I really appreciate what you taught me.
I'm just not valiant enough
and I'm not destined to marry Yueru.
I told you you wouldn't win.
Even if you learned a dirty trick
from a wicked man,
you still failed.
This is a combat for marriage
instead of a gathering of martial artists.
If she is really unbeatable,
she won't marry anyone
and she'll be alone forever, right?
You...
- That's right!
That's not going to happen.
That's not true.
For the sake of your wound,
I won't argue with you.
Get lost now.
You think you can hurt me?
Hey, loser,
it's me who doesn't want to argue with you.
Rat, if you dare to come up,
you and I will only compete in martial arts
instead of the marriage thing.
I don't believe you.
If you break your promise
and insist on marrying me,
I'll be living a terrible life, won't I?
- Yeah.
- That's right.
You...
It won't be terrible.
Xiaoyao.
How about we leave now?
We can explain it to Miss Lin another day.
Fine.
Let's not fight.
But in my eyes,
you're just like these men down there.
Cowards.
Fight here.
Don't push it.
What?
A coward gets angry?
Fight her.
- Go.
- Fine, then!
Xiaoyao...
Ling'er, don't worry.
If I don't give this savage girl a good lesson,
she'll keep haunting us.
And we'll only do martial arts
instead of the marriage thing.
Li, don't hurt Yueru.
Be careful, Xiaoyao.
A deal, huh? Only the martial arts.
Enough talk.
Let's fight.
Bravo!
Well done, young man.
Nice!
Brilliant!
Yueru...
Impressive!
Nice!
Wonderful!
Great!
Awesome.
What a surprise! Miss Lin lost.
I knew
she couldn't fight this young man.
That's right.
What? Are you convinced or not?
Rat, just you wait!
Yueru.
- Be careful.
- Impressive, young man.
Bravo!
Nice!
Well done!
Yueru, are you all right?
- Leave me alone.
- You lost.
- Yueru.
- Rat, I'm going to kill you!
You flatter yourself. Can't stand to lose?
Young man,
you have such powerful martial arts.
May I know your name?
I'm Li Xiaoyao from Yuhang Town.
Good name.
Mr. Li,
congratulations.
Everybody,
this combat has been held for five years
and finally, we've got a winner.
From tomorrow on,
we'll hold a feast for three days.
My fellow townsmen
and martial artists,
please come.
- All right.
- We will.
Wait. What do you mean?
Father, this round doesn't count!
For martial artists,
a bet is a bet.
Master Lin, huh?
I have things to do and I should go.
Mr. Li,
I held this combat
to get my daughter a husband.
You won
and they all witnessed it.
How could you deny it?
Just now, you said
we would do martial arts
instead of the marriage thing,
and if I defeated you,
everything would be erased.
Does it still count?
Yes, of course. Fight me again!
Stop, stop.
Master Lin, you heard her, huh?
She said we only competed in martial arts.
Don't get me involved in the marriage thing.
We are
the biggest sect in the Central Plains.
How could you
do anything
the way you want?
Miss Lin, congratulations
on getting such a great husband!
You two make a perfect couple!
See, Mr. Li?
Everyone is cheering.
Father, I would rather die than marry him.
Don't be ridiculous.
You and I had a deal.
Mr. Li won the combat,
in no way
could you break your promise.
Rat, just you wait!
Yueru.
Master Lin, I'll take my leave, too.
Xiaoyao!
Mr. Li,
come to my mansion, please.
After sailing for so many days,
I'm finally seeing living people.
What's going on over there? So crowded.
A combat for marriage.
You can't go.
Come have a look.
Tang Yu, could you stop doing this?
You have to know
I'm the young master and you're the guard.
You're disqualified to restrain me.
All kinds of floral umbrellas.
I know where the beads are.
Where?
Come have a look.
Just one second.
Over there.
Come have a look.
Fragrant sachets for sale.
Cosmetics.
(Rongchang Store)
Cosmetics for sale.
Make way, please.
Fancy rouge.
They're the Spiritual Beads?
None of your business.
Miss, you have great taste.
This is the best seller in my store.
Young pretty girls love it.
This pair looks good, too.
It's so hard to pick one.
Which one do you think...?
It's a waste of time to ask you.
My Lady,
please don't waste time
on anything meaningless.
- I'll take both.
- All right.
The bill is...
She has no money.
Miss, don't try it on when you have no money.
I don't have money, but he does.
Pay for them.
He has some money.
Tang Yu!
How dare you disobey me?
Sorry, but I can't obey you
in any case irrelevant to bead-seeking.
Our budget is for bead-seeking.
We can't spend it on anything else.
In our sect,
everybody takes me as the young master
and stays away at a respectful distance.
Who really cares about what I expect
or what I want to do?
I would rather be an ordinary girl
who can do whatever she wants.
Steamed cake.
Get up.
Go away!
Sugar-coated haws.
Sour and sweet sugar-coated haws.
Sugar-coated haws for sale.
♪Rare is the quiet in the years♪
♪Autumn winds tire of wandering♪
♪The setting sun lingers, unwilling to leave♪
♪Clinging to the wall,
reluctant to part from me♪
♪Words once whispered by the beloved♪
♪Now flow eastward with the tide♪
♪Looking back♪
♪Past events fall like maple leaves♪
♪Love has reached its end♪
♪Even hatred forsakes its promises♪
♪Fate thinks itself humorous♪
♪Too many thoughts beyond my control♪
♪What reward for lofty ambitions♪
♪Few friends stay in the end♪
♪Looking back♪
♪I hear laughter in drunken dreams♪
♪Laughing at my loss for words♪
♪Ancient folly and today's madness,
all turn into void♪
♪The blade dulls, and the edge wears thin♪
♪Bonds broken, dreams shattered♪
♪The road is desolate, laments left behind♪
♪Full of footsteps no one understands♪
♪Years of longing♪
♪Still unseen through the worldly dust♪
♪Mocking myself, trapped with no way out♪
♪A thousand feelings, a million grievances,
heroes grieve♪
♪As the song ends, the crowd disperses♪
♪Hair turns gray, beauty fades to dust♪
♪The candle dwindles, unnoticed♪
♪Competing with the sun
merely leads to wasting away♪
♪When tears dry and blood fills the eyes♪
♪Falling snow turns to red♪
♪Mocking myself, trapped with no way out♪
♪A thousand feelings, a million grievances,
heroes grieve♪
♪As the song ends, the crowd disperses♪
♪Hair turns gray, beauty fades to dust♪
♪The candle dwindles, unnoticed♪
♪Competing with the sun
merely leads to wasting away♪
♪When tears dry and blood fills the eyes♪
♪Falling snow turns to red♪