=Sword and Fairy 1=
=Episode 34=
Yueru!
Blessed by Nuwa,
you have finally awakened.
Madam,
where am I?
This is the Sacred Woods in Nanzhao.
You were severely injured
and brought here for healing.
What about the two ladies?
Where are they?
They were brought here together.
That's good.
Are they all right?
You should take your medicine first.
Madam,
please answer me.
How are they?
Did they get hurt?
Mr. Li, you were severely injured.
You should take your medicine
before discussing further.
Madam,
where are they?
Your wounds have not yet healed.
It's not advisable for you
to move around.
I'm fine.
I've already recovered.
Ling'er!
Madam, how is Ling'er?
Princess Ling'er
used her spiritual power excessively.
Her body is very weak,
but her life is not in danger for now.
Madam,
what about the other lady?
Is she...
Is she seriously injured?
Where is she?
You said they were both here.
Follow me.
Madam,
savage girl...
She's not here, right?
She...
This... This is...
It can't be.
You must be mistaken.
You don't even know her.
How could you know...
Her organs
and bones
were all shattered.
When she was brought here,
she was not breathing.
Yueru!
Savage girl!
It can't be...
No, no.
It can't be her.
She must still be
in the Demon-Locking Tower.
I'm going to save her now.
Savage girl!
Li Xiaoyao.
I don't believe it. I don't believe it.
It can't be.
How could it be her?
It's impossible.
I don't believe you.
Dugu,
so many demons have escaped
from the Demon-Locking Tower.
What should we do?
Why don't you say something?
Madam.
Madam,
how are they doing?
Luckily, they were brought here in time.
The young couple's lives were saved,
but
Miss Lin...
Does Xiaoyao know?
If only you had known,
why did you bother in the first place?
If you hadn't imprisoned the Princess
in the Demon-Locking Tower
without thorough investigation,
we wouldn't have been
in this situation today.
Madam,
indeed, we were wrong.
Is it true
that Yueru is beyond cure?
It's impossible
to bring her back to life,
however,
I might
find a way to keep her from dying.
Madam,
please do everything you can.
Many demons have escaped
from the Demon-Locking Tower,
and I need to return to Mount Shu now.
Dugu, I'll go with you.
To only tell good from evil,
not humans from demons.
Situ,
you stay here to take care of them.
Consider that jade pendant
my payment for hiring you
to find my friend.
Here you are.
It's not broken.
It's not broken, not broken.
I'm here.
You go rest.
Madam,
I...
I'm already fine.
Is there anything I can do?
I'll start right now.
No need.
Or maybe I can stay here
and help you take care of Ling'er and...
And...
You being here
won't help
and might even disturb them.
Then let me help you grind the herbs.
Alright then.
Sir.
Sir, why are you here?
This gourd is good
but doesn't hold enough wine.
The wine's finished.
I should get back to work.
Xiaoyao, Xiaoyao.
You can't keep going on like this.
What's wrong with me?
I'm fine.
I got a bit hurt before,
but the Sacred Maid already healed me.
I'm fine.
She's already dead!
No one's dead.
No one.
Ling'er's also fine.
The Sacred Maid said
that Ling'er's recovering well,
and she'll wake up soon.
Yueru...
I haven't seen her yet.
Haven't seen her.
I haven't seen her.
Xiaoyao.
Xiaoyao!
Ling'er,
please wake up soon.
Nothing can happen to you.
I need you.
Yueru!
Madam, where's Yueru?
Where is she?
Calm down now.
No, I can't.
I haven't seen her yet.
Come with me.
Alright.
Yueru...
Why do you never
call me by my name?
Did you change your name?
What's your name now?
Lin Bingru, Lin Xingru, Lin Fengru...
"Lin Fengru" suits you quite well.
Yueru.
Li Xiaoyao.
This is a map of Sacred Woods.
At the deepest part of the forest,
there's a cave
called the Rakshasa Ghost Cave.
Rakshasa Ghost Cave?
There's a peculiar creature inside
called the puppet bug.
Can you help me retrieve it?
It concerns Miss Lin.
I need you to go.
I'll go.
I'll go. I can go.
Good. Remember
that the Rakshasa Ghost Cave
is dangerous,
so you must stay alert at all times.
It's okay. I can do it.
(Shuimu Residence)
No matter if you are a human or a ghost,
come out.
Yueru!
Little rat, I will never spare you.
Yueru?
It's really you.
How dare you come back?
What do you want?
Let go!
Yueru, let me explain.
Don't you dare call my name again!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
- Yueru!
- You lecher!
Why didn't you dodge?
It's my debt to you.
If taking a sword from you
clears your anger,
then
it's worth it.
I'll spare you today.
I'm telling you.
Don't let me see you again next time.
I'll remember it well.
From now on, you'll never see me again.
Yueru,
I hope you'll never see me again.
(Combat for Marriage)
Bravo!
Next one.
Why did I come here again?
It's him.
Stop right there!
You little rat.
How dare you come here?
- Yueru.
- Don't call my name!
Listen to me.
I came here by accident,
with no other intention.
I'll leave right now.
- I'm leaving now.
- Wait a moment.
You bullied me before,
and now you followed me?
Alright, I'll give you a chance.
Come up here and fight it out with me.
I'm sorry. I can't fight.
Yueru,
I truly have urgent matters.
Please let me leave.
Alright. You can leave after the fight.
I've lost.
- You did it on purpose.
- Absolutely not.
I truly am no match.
Since I lost, please let me leave.
Coward.
Madam,
this kid is still injured.
If he goes alone,
what if he encounters
that Rakshasa Ghost?
That would be very dangerous.
The Rakshasa Ghost Cave
is merely a cave
with unusual geological features.
Inside, there are exotic flowers
and sulfur springs
that emit a hallucinogenic fog,
causing people to lose their minds.
Those who stay in the cave too long,
poisoned by the fog,
will die inside.
Over time, it has turned into a legend.
Now that he's going alone,
isn't it even more dangerous?
(Shuimu Residence)
If he cannot move
past his emotional wounds,
even if his physical injuries heal,
the emotional wounds
will accompany him for life.
Then it's up to his fate.
Wait.
Li Xiaoyao!
Yueru.
Weren't we supposed
to enter the Tower together?
What does it mean
for you to run here alone?
I...
I didn't have time to tell you
that my master
ultimately couldn't bear it,
and he told me a way
to rescue Ling'er from the Tower.
That's simple then.
Just tell me the method,
and I'll go in myself.
Yueru,
for Ling'er and me,
you should go back.
Then you guys hurry out.
I'll wait for you here.
Alright.
I'll bring Ling'er out
as soon as I see her.
If you guys don't come out,
I'll enter the Tower no matter what.
I promise you.
Yueru,
just wait here for us.
When we come out,
let's
eat, play,
- and grow old together.
- Good.
Let's eat, play,
and grow old together.
Go back.
This time,
I must be able to change it completely.
Li Xiaoyao,
wake up.
Wake up.
Li Xiaoyao.
Wake up, Li Xiaoyao.
Yueru.
Yueru,
you're alright.
That's wonderful.
Silly rat,
what are you doing here?
Yueru,
I came here to find you,
and I made it.
Now, leave this place.
Ling'er is still waiting for you.
You didn't die.
Yueru.
Yueru,
wait for me.
I'll take you to see Ling'er, Yueru.
Yueru, wait for me.
I'll take you to see Ling'er.
Yueru.
It's you.
♪Empty streets stretch out♪
♪Longing for someone
to share emotions with♪
♪Making such a decision♪
Stop hitting him!
Li Xiaoyao!
♪Our love♪
♪Like the scenery you pass by♪
♪Continues on♪
♪Yet your steps never pause for me♪
♪The love I give you
has always been quiet♪
♪In exchange
for the occasional care you show♪
♪Clearly, it's a story of three♪
♪Yet I can never have a name♪
Yueru,
where are you going?
Where are you going, Yueru?
Yueru.
Yueru,
you can't leave me.
You can't go!
Yueru!
♪You say love is like clouds♪
♪Only when they float freely
are they beautiful♪
Even if you remain like this,
I won't leave you unattended.
♪The reasons for breaking up
are sometimes very touching♪
Please.
I beg you.
Don't go.
♪Clearly, it's a story of three♪
♪Yet I can never have a name♪
♪The love I give you
has always been quiet♪
♪From the start, I was determined♪
♪Thinking what I wanted was the past♪
♪But then I found out
love must be reciprocated♪
Yueru!
I have just one wish.
Once we rescue Ling'er,
let's eat,
play,
grow old together,
and be good friends forever.
♪Yet I can never have a name♪
♪The love I give you
has always been quiet♪
♪Except for the tears on my face
that say otherwise♪
♪It turns out fate is there to explain♪
♪The fact you suddenly
don't love me anymore♪
(Shuimu Residence)
Tang Yu,
you're back.
Madam.
Madam,
I'm sorry.
You don't owe an apology to me.
A'nu...
How is she?
She returned to Nanzhao.
Madam,
if there's a chance,
please tell A'nu for me
that I'm sorry.
Tang Yu,
why did you make such a choice?
Madam,
do you think I am a good person
or a bad person?
What is good?
What is bad?
Can we use these rules
to conquer Nanzhao
and rule the people?
Saving the masses
is good.
What does it mean to save the masses?
The phrase "saving the masses"
can be used for good
or for evil.
Madam,
I don't understand.
Tang Yu,
the masses
seem vast,
but in reality,
they are made up of every person
that appears in our lives.
Only by holding their lives in awe
can we truly talk about
saving the masses.
Your parents are among the masses.
A'nu is among the masses.
The Princess is among the masses.
Gai Luojiao is also among the masses.
If you can't protect their lives,
how can you save the masses?
No.
Why is it like this?
In the world,
nothing inherently is good or evil,
but people insist on dividing
everything into good and evil.
Goodness and evilness
reside in people's hearts.
I want to travel
through famous mountains and rivers,
and taste every delicacy!
I just want to complete my mission soon.
What is good?
What is bad?
If you can't protect their lives,
how can you save the masses?
We must always,
always be together.
♪In the matters of this world♪
♪If there's a sequence♪
♪You come first♪
♪The whole world comes after♪
♪Despite the passing of rumors
like a fleeting horse♪
♪My love for you remains deep♪
♪This person in my heart♪
♪If there's an order♪
♪You come second♪
♪Then there's no one else that comes first♪
♪Despite the radiant dimples,
whether near or far♪
♪I am willing to wait for you♪
♪Waiting to see you♪
♪Like longing for green in March♪
♪Loving the rain in June♪
♪Watching in September♪
♪That autumn fills the ground♪
♪Flowers fade away♪
♪Leaves feel disheartened♪
♪Thinking of painting you♪
♪Afraid of overly deliberate details♪
♪Ink and wash are hard to gather♪
♪A frown between the eyebrows♪
♪The tune of the autumn wind♪
♪Wine doesn't speak♪
♪While the qin knows the best♪
♪Startled awake from a dream♪
♪Wiping away tears♪
♪Coolness fills the cup in my hand♪
♪Stars hiding away♪
♪Moon finding its rest♪
♪A fragrance lingering by my ear♪
♪Like you♪
♪Waiting to see you♪
♪Like longing for green in March♪
♪Loving the rain in June♪
♪Watching in September♪
♪That autumn fills the ground♪
♪Flowers fade away♪
♪Leaves feel disheartened♪
♪Thinking of painting you♪
♪Afraid of overly deliberate details♪
♪Ink and wash are hard to gather♪
♪A frown between the eyebrows♪
♪The tune of the autumn wind♪
♪Wine doesn't speak♪
♪While the qin knows the best♪