♪Bright moonlight,
with lanterns still burning♪
♪Deep night's hue,
your face softly blurring♪
♪In a fleeting thought,
my heart's line is stirring♪
♪Fate entwines,
a knot forever binding♪
♪This love's riddle,
your heart cold as steel♪
♪Yet your bright smile, how it steals♪
♪Like the fireworks in the night sky♪
♪A brilliance that no words can yield♪
♪La~ la~♪
♪In this life, meeting you
is fate's best hand♪
♪La~ la~♪
♪Our love story, I'll slowly pen♪
♪In this life, I wish for your words♪
♪From black hair to white,
we'll brave time's trend♪
♪In this life, may our love forever blend♪
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
♪In this life,
may our love stand like mountains♪
♪Through seasons' change, our whispers weave♪
♪In this life, may our love never fades away♪
♪Outshining all the world's glories,
come what may♪
=Les Belles=
=Episode 14=
Lingyu,
you were always asleep when I visited you,
I didn't dare disturb you.
How are you feeling now?
The engagement
that troubled me is gone,
so I feel refreshed.
My only wish now
is to reclaim the property of my family.
However, past experiences made me realize
finding a matrilocal husband
only brings trouble.
Since this doesn't work,
I'll find another way.
Since you figured it out,
I feel relieved.
By the way, you mentioned before
that you came here disguised as a man
also to avoid marriage.
Why don't we find a solution together?
Let's call off your engagement.
Mine isn't so easy to resolve.
As long as it's not decreed
by His Majesty,
it's manageable.
I...
I'm avoiding marriage to Prince Changyi.
What?
I told you it's hard to handle.
You have an engagement
with Prince Changyi?
You dare to flee a royal marriage.
Tell me about it.
The Imperial Family values humble scholars,
so they want to
connect with my father
through this marriage.
I avoided the marriage,
but haven't been punished
probably due to my father's influence.
You've met Prince Changyi at the Lu Mansion.
Did he recognize you?
Not at all.
I hid my real identity well.
He thinks I'm just a teacher
of the Lu Clan,
Zhou Zibo.
This marriage is indeed difficult.
Didn't expect Prince Changyi,
such a gentleman,
to force a marriage like this.
Because of this marriage, I thought
he was someone
who disregarded others' feelings,
just like a selfish hypocrite.
But recently, after interacting with him,
I found he's not that kind of person.
So...
I think in the future,
if he knows my identity,
he won't treat me any differently.
Yangling,
are you...
Of course.
Prince Changyi is capable.
I want to be his advisor.
I've already decided
that I must excel as Zhou Zibo.
Miss Luo.
Why are you here?
You two...
I... I came for chives.
Yes, for chives.
Are you here for chives too?
No, no.
That's not what we came for.
We heard a lot about Mr. Zhou,
so we wanted to see him.
Yes, exactly.
Ladies, please enjoy.
Eat and drink well.
You're not just here for Mr. Zhou, right?
I just remembered
that Flower Goddess Contest is soon.
Mr. Zhou, maybe
it's time to lighten
those young men's studies.
We have no other intentions.
It's just that the contest
is an annual event.
Is it possible...
They want to invite gentlemen for an outing.
Mr. Zhou, I hope you will share with us
about their preferences.
Please tell us in detail.
- Sure.
- This...
What is Flower Goddess Contest?
Young Master,
(To Young Master Lu Yun)
the contest invites you as judge.
I won't go. Turn it down.
Young Master, about the judge...
You plan to refuse again.
I don't know how to face them.
Young Master Yun,
it was a surprise seeing you here.
This is Yuezhou's grandest event.
We've invited you every year,
yet you refused them all.
The contest is a grand annual event
that all Yuezhou's noble ladies
value the most.
Anyone who wins the title
will gain fame in Yuezhou.
Moreover,
the Flower Goddess
can receive a wish granted by His Majesty.
Will His Majesty grant any wish?
Of course.
(If I can get a wish from His Majesty,)
(I can easily reclaim
my ancestral property.)
(Gentle Breeze and Bright Moon)
I wonder
by what condition would you agree?
Aman,
you know it well,
I don't like crowds.
Please reconsider...
Your wage will be reduced...
Fine, I'm leaving.
Xuechen, why did you call me here?
What's the matter?
Previously, we struggled to find a reason
to search the Fan Family?
Since that day Fan Qingchen
acted disgracefully in public,
isn't this a perfect excuse
to search his family
for the saltpeter issue?
You want to use this chance
to eliminate them?
We've been too cautious after all,
keeping him around for so long.
And yet, trouble arises again.
It's causing innocent people to suffer.
We should act now.
I never expected this.
You used to be aloof from worldly affairs,
but now you're affected by love.
But Flower Goddess Contest spots are limited.
Only one candidate per household.
To be honest, Miss Luo,
don't hold onto false hopes.
You're a distant relative of the Lu Clan.
How could you get a spot from the Lu Clan?
Even if you could secure a spot,
since Miss Chen started participating,
she's won the Flower Goddess title
every year.
Miss Chen is exceptionally talented,
known as a gifted lady in Yuezhou City.
Moreover,
she is the legitimate daughter.
Miss Luo, we cannot compare.
You all have your own strengths.
Why belittle yourself so much?
Miss Luo is right.
Though I've just met you all,
I've noticed your exceptional qualities.
Among all the women,
some are clever and wise,
some are lively and spirited,
some are knowledgeable,
(Women's Commandments)
some are good at handwork,
some have courage and wisdom,
and some are quiet and elegant.
I am the princess of Nanyue.
But now I wish to protect someone.
As they say, "All charming beauties,
each shines in their own way."
Indeed.
You're fascinated
by the Flower Goddess Contest,
yet you fear a failure
that hasn't even arrived
and hold back.
It's a pity.
Lingyu, Mr. Zhou,
you have unique insights,
truly extraordinary.
Princess, you flatter me.
Ladies, make yourselves at home.
Have some tea and snacks.
See if you like.
(No matter what,)
(I must participate)
(in the Flower Goddess Contest.)
(Lu Mansion)
My Lady, mind your step.
Tang, thank you for bringing me back.
Lingyu.
Are you going to join
the Flower Goddess Contest?
It's a great opportunity.
Why not seize it?
I truly admire you
for your courage and action.
Unlike me.
Tang,
do you want to join the contest?
No,
I don't have any talent.
That contest is for talented,
beautiful ladies.
I'd just be laughed at.
Tang,
you always say you admire my freedom,
but the truth is, you can be free too.
Any change
starts with the first step.
Joining the contest could be your first step.
Are others' opinions
more important to you,
than your own desires?
Tang,
do what makes you happy.
Become who you want to be.
Then, you won't always have a frown.
Thank you, Lingyu.
I'll be off now.
My Lady.
You advised Princess Ningping to participate.
Aren't you giving yourself more rivals?
I didn't join the contest to beat anyone,
nor to prove who's better.
As long as I am strong enough,
why fear who the opponent is?
Don't worry. I believe in myself.
As long as I give it my all,
I will surely win the title.
Don't even mention it.
You can't even enter
the Flower Goddess Contest.
The ladies just mentioned
that this contest values lineage.
Spots are limited.
How can we participate?
Look.
(Lu Mansion)
Doesn't the Lu Clan have a spot?
Aunt Ying has just returned from her trip.
Let's go see her.
You're right.
Let's go.
The hardest task each year
is choosing a gift for Mother.
It must please her.
Aunt, although I'm not a Lu Family lady,
I still wish to join
the Flower Goddess Contest
to bring honor to the Lu Clan.
Aunt, please speak to Madam Lu for me.
Lu Clan has few direct daughters,
but you're not the only female cousin.
Why does it have to be you?
Because I'm your only niece.
Only I inherited your talent and wisdom.
I will surely excel in the contest.
You always know how to sweet-talk me.
This painting is by a renowned master.
What do you think of it?
The mountains overlap majestically.
It feels like a fairyland.
It's perfect for Madam Lu.
Wrap this up.
Yes.
(Clouds and Spring Trees)
Most women wish to marry well,
finding a good family to rely on
to have support in the future.
Why are you so different?
I just want to rely on my own ability
to make a name in Yuezhou.
If all efforts prove futile,
I will seek another path.
At such a young age,
you have such thoughts.
It's because you taught me well.
(Time Slips Away)
Miss Luo wants a spot
in the Flower Goddess Contest,
- (Does she?)
- What do you think?
Mother, over the years,
although we've sent ladies
of our Clan to the Flower Goddess Contest,
they always ended up unsuccessful.
Since Lingyu is eager,
why not let her give it a try?
She is talented,
and has a keen mind.
Perhaps,
she might actually win the title.
This must be the path she wants to take.
Lu Yun,
what are you mumbling about?
Nothing.
Yun,
what do you think of Miss Luo's matter?
Grandmother, Aunt is right.
Miss Luo performed at Zhongshan,
astonishing everyone.
All the guests were amazed.
If she could join the contest
as part of our clan,
she'll surely bring glory to us.
All these years,
I've rarely seen you praise anyone,
especially the ladies.
When Xian fell into the lake last time,
you praised Miss Luo's integrity,
kindness, and courtesy to others.
Now you commend her talent.
It's truly rare.
Grandmother, I'm just speaking the truth.
Am I right, Aunt?
Yes.
Well...
Since both of you say so,
if I don't agree,
it would seem unreasonable.
So this matter
is settled then.
- (Flower Goddess Contest)
- Okay?
(I must help her well.)
(Zichen Palace)
(The Emperor)
Your Majesty, Prince Hengyang is here.
Let him in.
Greetings, Father.
As you were.
Thank you, Father.
Hengyang,
I've heard from Changyi
that the Fan Family
is colluding with foreigners,
and allowed his only son to commit misdeeds.
You handled it well.
As a prince,
you've set an example
and have done justice.
You really have
a bit of the flair I had back in my day.
Thank you, Father.
Your Majesty,
this is the list
for the Flower Goddess Contest
by Ministry of Rites.
Bring it here.
(Flower Goddess List:
Princess Ningping, Lau Tang)
Lau Tang is participating this year.
It's rare to see her so proactive.
I'll definitely go support her.
Great.
You can meet all the ladies there.
Your brother Changyi is already engaged.
Yet, you remain unmarried as the elder.
Tell me,
how can this be justified?
Though I'm unmarried,
my heart belongs to someone.
What use is a heart's desire?
Still, I am all alone.
A lady from Lu Clan is competing.
(Lu Clan, Luo Lingyu)
Luo Lingyu?
Seems to be a rising star.
Father,
may I see the candidate list?
Alright.
Eunuch Gao.
Your Highness.
(Lu Clan, Luo Lingyu)
Miss Luo is joining the contest.
(It seems she is fine now.)
Miss Luo?
You were enraged for a beauty.
Is it her?
Your heart belongs to someone, right?
Yes. Father, you may not know
Miss Luo prepared a Fiery Dance
at the Zhongshan Banquet
to bless the soldiers at the frontier.
The entire North Army
was deeply moved by it.
Therefore, I believe
Miss Luo deserves
the title of Flower Goddess.
Since you have such faith in Miss Luo,
do you dare to make a bet with me?
What do we bet on?
Whichever lady wins the title this year,
I will grant her marriage to you
as princess consort. How about that?
Father, please don't.
Miss Luo is the only one I love.
What if I lose the bet?
Wouldn't that ruin my lifelong happiness?
You've never been afraid
on the battlefield.
It seems like
Miss Luo doesn't have real skills.
Now that I've secured the spot,
I need to get a fine outfit.
I'm afraid even 10 taels of silver
won't cover it.
I also need to hire a teacher,
which is another big expense.
- Plus...
- Miss Luo.
Third Young Master.
Wait.
I heard you're joining
the Flower Goddess Contest.
You hope to reclaim the property
by the Emperor's wish.
Yes, I mentioned to you before.
I'll handle it in my own way.
That's a good approach.
It's your first time in this contest.
If there's anything unclear,
feel free to ask me anytime.
It's no trouble at all.
I appreciate your kindness.
I can handle the contest myself.
You don't have to worry about it.
Third Young Master, you must be busy.
I shall take my leave first.
Actually, I...
We are even now.
In the future, you can follow your own path,
and I'll take mine.
(This feels a bit unfamiliar to me.)
Oh, Young Master.
Why can't you speak directly to Miss Luo?
You spoke up for her just now
before Madam Lu.
I naturally help with
what she wants to do.
What's there to say?
But now with the Flower Goddess Contest,
she doesn't need you anymore.
In the future,
what reason will you have to see her?
She doesn't need me,
but I need her.
Young Master, wait for me.
(Xuewu Courtyard)
Why is it you?
Miss Luo.
Jinchuan broke my inkstone.
May I borrow yours?
Please wait.
♪With the strength to bind a chicken, none♪
♪Yet I can seize fate's throat, alone♪
Why are you here again?
Sorry to bother you again.
Jinchuan also tore my paper.
May I borrow some of yours?
Wait.
♪It's too much for me♪
What did Jinchuan break this time?
A Chinese brush.
♪Let love not be late♪
♪Step aside, step aside, make some space♪
♪I'll choose or reject,
take my time, no haste♪
It's all his fault.
♪Without you, I'll still live my way♪
♪Step aside, step aside, let me through♪
♪Take it slow, don't be tense, it's true♪
(Xuewu Courtyard)
♪Don't waste this life, make it great♪
How do I look?
Super handsome.
Remember
that you'll say,
"I broke them all."
You'll get a raise.
(Xuewu Courtyard)
- My lady said,
- I...
"Third Young Master's items are precious.
It'd be a pity to throw them away.
Better repair them."
All tools are here.
Goodbye, Third Young Master.
Wait a moment.
Young Master, my lady also said,
"If it doesn't work, replace Jinchuan.
He's damaged so many things.
Better to find a careful person."
Is your lady at home?
She went out to learn skills today.
She's preparing for the contest,
she's awfully busy.
Young Master, no need to look for her.
See you.
(Xuewu Courtyard)
Young Master,
what about this table?
Take it back for repairs.
I wonder what skills she'll learn
to join the contest.
Jinchuan, I have an idea.
Tomorrow, get some money from the bank.
Visit all the entertainment houses
in Yuezhou.
Bribe them all.
If she goes to learn skills...
they'll refuse her,
and she will then seek your help.
Ask them to reduce the fee.
(Xuewu Courtyard)
(Zichen Palace)
Brother.
Changyi, have you just left Imperial Study,
and reported something
I shouldn't know to Father.
I've been investigating
saltpeter smugglers.
A few days ago,
I caught someone linking with Beichu.
You happen to know this person.
Just say what you want to say.
The saltpeter ends up in one place,
the Fan Family.
The Fan Family is Shuozhou's wealthiest.
They're Imperial Merchants.
Why would they betray
for such petty gain?
They colluded with the enemy.
The evidence is solid.
Father has ordered
a thorough investigation.
Brother,
the North Army
(Zichen Palace)
has had dealings with the Fans for years.
You really know nothing about this?
Regarding military supplies,
I don't needed to handle it personally.
It's all...
(Could this involve Mr. Kong?)
Changyi, if you intend to harm me,
there's no need for such a detour.
I have no such intention.
If the Fan Family is truly behind this,
I won't be lenient.
But if someone is framing us,
they won't get away with it.
I hope you investigate thoroughly.
I will uncover the truth.
Your Highness.
Weren't you going to the Ministry of Rites?
Why are you here?
I did visit the Ministry of Rites today.
Your Highness, you seem troubled.
It's nothing major,
just that more humble scholars
are joining the Imperial Examination.
The noble clans have expressed concerns.
The power of the noble clans
affects everything intricately.
I can't just ignore it,
but if we consider the noble clans,
the opportunities
for humble scholars will diminish.
Zibo, what's your opinion?
I...
I happened to make Lard and Chive Pie.
Could you help me with something first?
Of course.
Your clothes are dirty.
Thank you, Your Highness.
The dough is a bit dry.
Could you add some water?
Alright.
Your Highness, what are you doing?
I'm afraid of adding too much.
No worries, just add it.
If there's too much water, add flour.
Enough, enough.
Look,
the noble clans
are like water,
and the humble scholars like flour.
If there's too much flour, add water,
or the other way around.
But it can't be done overnight.
It must be done
according to circumstances.
I understand now.
Your Highness, you're indeed wise.
It was definitely worth visiting you.
Usually, I hear too much scholarly talk.
Watching you make a pie is better.
Zibo, you always enlighten me.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, may I become your...
become your...
advisor?
Ad...
Advisor?
Your Highness, you're unwilling, right?
No, no, that's not it.
I... I certainly am willing.
Really?
Then thank you, Your Highness.
Today
marks my first day as your advisor.
The Lard and Chive Pie must be well made.
Wait. Let's add another dish for you.
How about scrambled eggs with chives?
Scrambled eggs with chives,
Lard and Chive Pie...
I love eating chives.
That's good.
Zibo, you added so much filling.
It might spill out.
No worries.
Let me make a bigger one for you.
Alright.
Look.
Your nose...
Look at this.
(Lu Mansion)
Prince Hengyang?
What brings you here?
I'm here to deliver something to you.
You said that the jade hairpin is fragile,
so you didn't dare to wear it out.
I selected a few more items
and brought them for you.
No need to be so careful anymore.
If it breaks, it breaks.
You can replace it.
This gift
is truly precious.
I cannot accept it.
You're entering the Flower Goddess Contest.
These will surely be useful.
How did you know I'll compete?
On the list selected by my father,
I saw your name,
and brought the invitation to you
to share the good news with you.
(Flower Goddess Invitation)
(Lady Luo Lingyu has been accepted.)
You're so thoughtful.
I'm deeply grateful.
Miss Luo, regarding your participation,
is there anything I can assist with?
Do you need me to
request palace dancers to help,
a musician to accompany you,
or anything else?
I'll get it done.
If you have faith in me,
you need not do anything.
Just go back and relax.
As for the Flower Goddess Contest,
I will win on my own merits,
and earn the title of Flower Goddess.
But this gift is truly valuable.
The matter of Fan Qingchen
was resolved thanks to your help.
I should've brought a gift to thank you.
How could I accept your gift?
Resolving Fan Qingchen's matter
was a promise I made to you,
so I had to fulfill it.
As for this gift,
you can send me another one in return.
Then, we will be even.
A gift in return...
I left in a hurry,
and didn't bring anything.
I made this Tongcao Flower myself.
Hope you'll like it.
Your creations are the finest.
Are you going out
for the Flower Goddess Contest?
Indeed.
Then I won't hold you.
Thank you.
Miss Luo,
you must win the Flower Goddess Contest.
Miss Luo doesn't have real skills.
A bet is a bet.
Miss Luo will not lose.
Good.
It's a deal.
(Xunmei House)
So many dancers at Xunmei House, all popular.
Why did you specifically choose me?
Qiniang, no need to be modest.
With your remarkable talent,
I fear you'll be stolen away from me.
Even if it means waiting all night,
it's worth it.
Since you asked for me,
you must know I value money over people.
How much are you offering?
Miss Luo, it's not that
I overestimate myself,
but with such a small sum,
you can't even buy a moment of my time.
Yet you want me to teach you to dance?
Qiniang, you are mistaken.
I came here
not for myself,
but for you.
I'm all ears.
Although your Qipan Dance is famous,
it's still too refined,
hard to find an appreciative audience.
This one-time deal won't last.
If you help me
win the Flower Goddess title,
things would be different.
You're quite confident.
But becoming the Flower Goddess isn't easy.
Have you heard of Zhongshan's Fiery Dance?
It was performed at the banquet
for Prince Hengyang.
Seems like your information is up-to-date.
Do you know who performed it?
That's right.
It's me.
The Fiery Dance is from the Northern Border,
but once it passes through my hands,
it has become widely loved in Yuezhou.
The Flower Goddess Contest
is a great chance.
With a small change to the Qipan Dance,
it'll be appreciated
not just by the noble clans,
but also by common people.
As long as we combine our talents.
The Flower Goddess title is within reach.
Once this opportunity opens up,
whether it's spectators
or those coming to learn dance,
they'll flock to Xunmei House.
Earning great fortune won't be a pipe dream.
I can give you at most four hours a day.
Anything more will cost extra.
If you agree,
sign this contract.
(Sign: Luo Lingyu)
(Sign: Luo Lingyu, Mei Qiniang)
Your Highness, this is just a fake flower.
Why are you so happy?
You don't understand.
It represents
Miss Luo's deep affection for me.
But she didn't mention her affection.
How did you interpret it
as true affection?
A gentleman judges by actions.
She hosted a banquet for me,
and performed Fiery Dance.
Now she gives me
an ever-blooming Tongcao Flower.
It symbolizes our enduring affection.
On the contest day,
I will surely bring it there.
(I must win this bet with Father).
Since he has awakened,
and only minor injuries remain,
a couple more days of rest will suffice.
Thank you.
Jinchuan, see the physician out.
Sure.
This way, sir.
You're lucky.
I'm glad you're fine.
In the coming days,
rest and recover at Xunmei House.
Just focus on recovery.
Young Master.
I previously discovered
Fan Qingchen is looking for Wang Chongming.
Is there any news on this matter?
I've already had Aman
send someone to inquire.
I got the news.
I just hadn't had time to tell you.
His identity is indeed not simple.
He was the only one in the North Army
who could decipher Yin books.
Over ten days ago,
he left Xiaomei Village
in the western suburb.
His whereabouts
remains unknown.
Perhaps it was Fan Qingchen's arrival
that alerted him,
making him hide in haste.
Aman,
we must find him
before those masterminds do,
or he'll be silenced.
I have another matter to discuss with you.
In the Fan Mansion,
they indeed found
a lot of unshipped saltpeter.
Master Fan took his own life on the spot.
What?
Be careful.
There might be greater forces behind them,
which made him so terrified
that he ended his own life.
He wanted to settle the saltpeter issue.
Earlier, I met Hengyang at the palace
and tested him with this issue.
Just as you said,
he knows nothing about saltpeter.
It seems the mastermind
even set him up.
Indeed.
Prince Hengyang has the North Army.
If someone uses him,
it could end badly.
Better to clear up the misunderstandings
between us and him early.
I've already invited him to come.
Young Master, you must be tired.
Shall we take a rest?
Young Master.
Lingyu, you have such a cruel heart.
Why can't I let go of you?
I'll find another chance
to bring you back to me.
Be careful!
Who sent you here?
You know too much.
♪Clouds dream of garments,
flowers dream of grace♪
♪Love for power, beauty,
but freedom takes the place♪
♪Pearls of the night or robes of gold♪
♪All I'd trade for a cup of wine, bold♪
♪With the strength to bind a chicken, none♪
♪Yet I can seize fate's throat, alone♪
♪Wanna be my rival, you say♪
♪Sorry, you're not there yet, today♪
♪Don't speak of forever♪
♪It's too much for me♪
♪Don't stand idle♪
♪Let love not be late♪
♪Step aside, step aside, make some space♪
♪I'll choose or reject, take my time, no haste♪
♪If you're just boring, I won't stay♪
♪Without you, I'll still live my way♪
♪Step aside, step aside, let me through♪
♪Take it slow, don't be tense, it's true♪
♪Love is love, hate is hate, no debate♪
♪Don't waste this life, make it great♪
♪Clouds dream of garments,
flowers dream of grace♪
♪Love for power, beauty,
but freedom takes the place♪
♪Pearls of the night or robes of gold♪
♪All I'd trade for a cup of wine, bold♪
♪With the strength to bind a chicken, none♪
♪Yet I can seize fate's throat, alone♪
♪Wanna be my rival, you say♪
♪Sorry, you're not there yet, today♪
♪Don't speak of forever♪
♪It's too much for me♪
♪Don't stand idle♪
♪Let love not be late♪
♪Step aside, step aside, make some space♪
♪I'll choose or reject, take my time, no haste♪
♪If you're just boring, I won't stay♪
♪Without you, I'll still live my way♪
♪Step aside, step aside, let me through♪
♪Take it slow, don't be tense, it's true♪
♪Love is love, hate is hate, no debate♪
♪Don't waste this life, make it great♪