♪Bright moonlight,
with lanterns still burning♪
♪Deep night's hue,
your face softly blurring♪
♪In a fleeting thought,
my heart's line is stirring♪
♪Fate entwines,
a knot forever binding♪
♪This love's riddle,
your heart cold as steel♪
♪Yet your bright smile, how it steals♪
♪Like the fireworks in the night sky♪
♪A brilliance that no words can yield♪
♪La~ la~♪
♪In this life, meeting you
is fate's best hand♪
♪La~ la~♪
♪Our love story, I'll slowly pen♪
♪In this life, I wish for your words♪
♪From black hair to white,
we'll brave time's trend♪
♪In this life, may our love forever blend♪
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
♪In this life,
may our love stand like mountains♪
♪Through seasons' change, our whispers weave♪
♪In this life, may our love never fades away♪
♪Outshining all the world's glories,
come what may♪
=Les Belles=
=Episode 26=
Together in life, together in death.
I want us to be together forever.
Lingyu, I'll rescue you soon.
Lingyu.
He wants me dead.
He won't spare me today.
Xuechen!
To meet you and love you
is truly a blessing.
Xuechen.
Xuechen!
My Lady, you're awake.
How can he be missing?
- I'll look for him.
- Where's Xuechen?
Where's Xuechen?
There was an explosion at Mount Funiu.
He hasn't been found yet.
I will keep searching.
What?
Avalanche.
My Lady!
Please remember our agreements.
When we meet again,
we're like strangers.
Why do you say that?
I've just arrived.
How do you know my character and nature?
How can you judge me so readily?
If not for my family's property,
I wouldn't hurry to find a husband.
I was blind to choose you.
We're even now.
You do your thing,
and I'll do mine.
In dealings with others,
either I owe you something,
or you owe me a little.
It's not so easy to settle it.
Isn't that right?
You'd rather pray to the heavens
than come to find me.
Little fish, little fish.
Since you raised it,
why not give it a name?
I already did.
Little Yu.
I used your name "Yu".
If you dare to die,
I'll marry someone else.
Miss Luo.
Let's continue searching.
Miss Luo, you should head back.
Let go of me.
I will surely find Xuechen.
If you keep searching,
you'll risk your life.
Please go back.
Let me go.
He won't die.
He will survive.
Your Highness, perhaps...
There's a pouch here.
Here's a pouch.
Your Highness, I found a pouch.
It belongs to Xuechen.
It's Xuechen's pouch.
He must be nearby. Keep searching.
- Yes.
Xuechen.
(I ask for your word
that our love may stand like mountains.)
(You have my word
that our love will stand like mountains.)
You have my word
that our love will stand like mountains.
♪I sit alone amid the downpour at night♪
(You have my word
that our love will stand like mountains.)
♪A cup of wine can't drown my loneliness♪
Xuechen is here.
Xuechen.
♪I wrote down as much as I remembered♪
♪Flowers wither in the cool breeze♪
♪Yearning deep in the eyes
mottles like stars♪
♪What if I grow old all alone♪
♪Tears will be shed forever♪
Xuechen.
♪The pain of parting drifts with the wind♪
♪Picking up a brush, I just want to♪
♪Draw the fleeting time and capture youth♪
Xuechen. It's him!
Xuechen is here!
Xuechen.
Xuechen, you promised to return alive.
♪Tears will be shed forever♪
Xuechen.
Xuechen
♪Picking up a brush, I just want to♪
♪Draw the fleeting time and capture youth♪
♪At the end of time♪
Xuechen.
(One month later)
You have arrived.
Today is the day we return.
His Highness has prepared horses for us.
Drink this bowl of medicine,
and we shall depart.
Alright.
Be careful, it's hot.
Lingyu, my shoulder still aches.
Why not feed me instead?
You tried that trick yesterday.
My head aches too.
You tried that the day before.
Heartache.
I can't take it. It really hurts.
Really? In that case,
you should rest here.
I'll return to Yuezhou alone.
Wait, I'll drink it myself.
Can't I drink it myself?
Truly heartbreaking.
You said "May our love stand like mountains",
yet won't even feed me meds.
How dare you speak such words.
You clearly saw the note,
yet said nothing.
Stop pretending to be weak for sympathy.
Your little tricks,
I know them all too well.
Yes, I am overstepping,
but if I didn't see the note in the pouch,
what would you do?
Who said I cared?
If you hadn't seen it,
that's not your luck.
Someone destined will see it.
With a charming gentleman like me,
what more do you need?
You don't need it.
Alright, alright.
It's time to leave.
We should leave now.
Let's go.
Move.
(Jingyang)
She's still so strong.
Jingyang tea set,
Shuozhou jade stone,
and Wuzhou inks
are the best from cities
in the Northern Border.
I found them all for you.
Your Highness, it is too much.
Not at all. The carriage isn't full yet.
There are also some clothes
and jewelry.
We can't take so many things back.
Besides, why would I need so much jewelry?
Who said I'm giving them to you?
I'm giving them to Miss Luo.
Here he goes again.
This guy never gives up.
I'm afraid I'll miss your wedding.
So I'm giving my gift in advance.
That's more like it, right, Lingyu?
What wedding are you referring to?
Your Highness, why are you
thinking so far ahead?
Aren't you coming back to Yuezhou with us?
I still have some military matters.
I'll return a few days later.
If you wish,
we can wait a few more days for you.
No need. The longer you stay,
the more letters I'll receive
from the Lu Clan.
You should hurry back to report safety.
Alright.
See you in Yuezhou.
Let's go.
Safe travels.
Everyone, take care.
- Advisor Lu, take care.
- Take care.
We're leaving, Ajiao.
Didn't I say in the army...
- Take care!
- Take care.
(Jingyang)
(One month later)
(Lu Mansion)
(Time Slips Away)
Yun and Lingyu
have been back for a while.
Yet their marriage is undecided.
This time, we must seize the chance
to finalize the marriage.
Alright.
Let's touch their hearts.
Enlighten their minds.
At worst,
rely on age to assert authority.
They are full of ideas.
It's not easy to persuade them.
So we use their own methods
against them.
Lingyu's approach
is actually quite effective.
I can help too.
Alright, alright.
Mother, is that appropriate?
As long as it works.
Speak less, don't slip up.
Come on.
(Why does everything feel odd?)
(Did you cause trouble again?)
(I've behaved well.)
(Maybe it's you causing issues.)
You've both been back for a while.
Now everything is going well.
What are your plans next?
Grandmother,
what plans do we have next?
I'm asking about your marriage plans.
We're not in a rush for that.
- Madam Lu.
- Grandmother.
- Mother.
- Are you okay, Grandmother?
Mother.
It's okay.
I don't know
what's wrong lately.
I just feel this chest tightness.
Chest tightness.
Headache. My head.
- Anyway.
- (It's a ruse of self-injury.)
I feel terrible all over.
Mother.
Madam Lu.
You must be overwhelmed
by your beloved
dragon saliva incense.
Too much of anything
is not good.
Don't let it affect your health.
- Let me dispose of it.
- Wait.
I'm feeling much better now.
No need to trouble yourself.
These two days
are auspicious days.
If you can marry during these days,
it will surely lead to a life of prosperity.
Sister.
- A good day.
It's a good day.
(Creating something from nothing.)
That's wonderful.
Is there really such an auspicious day?
As a younger brother,
I must invite all the ladies in Yuezhou
to gather together
and have a chat with you,
so that you can find someone you like.
No need for that.
(Don't worry, I'm here.)
I'll get straight to the point.
Since you delay your marriage,
it shows your feelings aren't deep.
If that's the case,
perhaps it's best to part ways quickly.
May you each find peace.
Sister.
(Provocation tactic.)
(It's your turn.)
It's because the bond is deep
that we must consider carefully,
and plan thoughtfully.
How can we decide in haste?
Miss Luo speaks wisely.
This is also our humble wish as elders.
Don't pressure the kids.
It's just that
I won't see my dear nephew marry,
nor see the Lu Mansion decorated.
And Mother.
She won't have a great-grandchild.
(Feigning retreat to lure the enemy.)
Aunt.
Your handkerchief
needs more pepper to shed tears.
So that's how it is.
We understand your intentions.
But this matter can't be rushed.
It needs careful consideration.
Indeed, careful planning shows sincerity.
Grandmother, Uncle, Aunt,
Aunt Ying, Brother,
please rest early.
We'll take our leave now.
This...
Grandmother.
Mother.
- Grandmother.
- Mother.
You, you...
Mother, I said this wouldn't work.
You must have acted poorly.
They saw through it.
Exactly.
If they like to fuss over their lives,
let them fuss all they want.
These flowers are perfect for dew.
(I wonder what she thinks
about the marriage.)
(I've almost decided
on my wedding attire.)
(Will he propose or not?)
Lingyu,
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
I heard from Lingxi
you tried on wedding dresses
in West Market.
I just wanted to ask
if you decide on it yet.
Some ready-made clothing stores
want to use my fame as the Flower Goddess
to attract business. That's all.
I heard from Jinchuan,
that you asked Second Young Master
to calculate
all the auspicious dates for this year.
Are they choosing a good day for something?
Grandmother is eager to travel with Aunt.
I should quickly pick an auspicious day.
To plan ahead.
Alright.
(Lingxi, just you wait.)
(Jinchuan, seems like
you don't want your wage.)
Aren't you constantly thinking of me
and loving me passionately?
Why are you so calm about marriage?
Which gentleman has never forgotten me
from the first moment we met.
Who would follow me through thick and thin?
Yet there's no action taken.
It seems like mere words.
Wait.
Are you feeling anxious?
If you're not anxious,
then I'm definitely not worried.
Waiting won't bring a happy ending.
Only by taking action can one succeed.
Are you going to take action?
Proposal?
Are you going to propose?
Haven't you proposed?
You want us to help you propose?
We're all like brothers.
Let me say a few words first.
For couples, it's easy to share joys,
but hard to endure hardships together.
We must succeed on the first try.
No room for any mistakes.
You all know this well.
The Lu Clan
has deep pockets.
I plan to buy her valuable gifts
to make her cry with joy.
- Then perhaps...
- Yes.
I previously gifted Miss Luo a jade hairpin,
which she adored.
How about a place full of memories
to reminisce and express your feelings?
Good idea.
At the Zhongshan Banquet,
her Fiery Dance
truly reminded me of battles
at the Northern Border.
I must say,
under the moonlit sky,
send her a shower of cherry blossoms.
Yes, back then didn't I also...
Back then, back then, back then.
Is that all you got?
Indeed, you spared no effort.
You've tried every method.
When I take Miss Luo out,
I ensure everything's in place.
Everything is the finest.
You can speak now.
What should we do?
On an enchanting night.
You two stroll the streets.
With pedals fluttering down.
Got it.
If I could
hold an umbrella for him in the rain,
he would surely agree to my proposal.
But this summer has been dry.
How do you know when it will rain?
I... I might be able to help.
What? Can the Imperial Family
even control the rain now?
No, no.
I don't know any mystical arts.
But this is still
within our capabilities.
That's wonderful.
Come on.
We'll rely on you for the rain.
However,
there's one thing to remember.
Never share intel with friends.
Especially you.
Yes, you.
Me?
You, you, you.
It's you.
Alright.
What's your drinking capacity?
Get up and drink!
You finally arrived.
How much did you drink?
You're unconscious.
I'll take care of the princess.
What? Is this Tang?
As for these two,
you decide what to do.
Slow down, slow down.
We're leaving.
Yangling,
how much have you drunk?
Be careful.
Give it to me.
- Aman.
- Alright, alright.
- Why drink so much?
- Drink it.
- Give it to me.
- Drink.
Hiding things quietly from me.
You drink too.
Surely nothing good is planned.
Alright, I'll drink.
No sleeping.
Butterfly.
What butterfly?
No butterflies here.
Where are the butterflies?
Butterflies...
There are no butterflies.
Lingyu.
Butterflies.
Where are the butterflies?
I caught a huge butterfly.
Chasing butterflies made you drunk.
You... you're not a butterfly.
You're a fox spirit.
Fox spirit, are you here to take me home?
I'll give you another chance.
What should you call me?
Xuechen.
Be careful.
She's drunk. I'll take her back.
Alright.
Make the most of it.
What... should I make the most of?
Nonsense.
Aman,
you look really nice.
Yangling,
you usually don't like drinking.
Why drink so much today?
I'm going to...
What?
Pick chives.
Pick what?
Yangling.
- Chives.
- Yangling.
Slow down, Yangling.
Chives.
Yangling.
You... you... don't.
You've always liked gardening.
And these chives...
It's the chives we planted together.
They are still growing.
It'd be a pity to pull them out.
You're right.
Even though you haven't proposed yet,
but...
I will still protect
our little courtyard
and our little chives.
You all are great, little chives.
Yangling, wasn't our marriage
granted by Father?
Do I need to ask you again?
Are you treating me as a duty,
or as an arrangement?
Neither.
I truly admire you.
For the rest of my life, I love you alone.
I'll protect and honor you.
We'll share joys together.
In arguments, it's always my fault.
Whether matters are big or small,
let's discuss them together, alright?
♪Bright moonlight,
with lanterns still burning♪
Will you marry me?
I...
♪Fate entwines,
a knot forever binding♪
I will.
♪Yet your bright smile, how it steals♪
♪Like the fireworks in the night sky♪
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't.
♪In this life, meeting you
is fate's best hand♪
♪La~ la~♪
♪Our love story, I'll slowly pen♪
♪In this life, I wish for your words♪
♪From black hair to white,
we'll brave time's trend♪
♪In this life, may our love forever blend♪
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
♪In this life,
may our love stand like mountains♪
♪Through seasons' change, our whispers weave♪
♪In this life, may our love never fades away♪
♪Outshining all the world's glories,
come what may♪
(Lu Mansion)
We've been through so much,
yet you still won't say it.
Why is that?
Are you made of wood?
Why don't you speak?
Why won't you say anything?
Why aren't you
saying anything?
Speak up! Speak up!
Don't remain silent.
You'll be waiting for centuries
until this pillar gains wisdom.
Then it'll surely answer you.
(Who says Third Young Master is a romantic?)
(He seems utterly oblivious.)
(Why isn't he taking the bait?)
Come here.
Instead of asking Mr. Pillar,
why not
ask me directly?
(If I could ask you directly,)
(why would I pretend to be drunk?)
(I have my pride too.)
Go on, tell me.
My family wants him to marry in.
Isn't that too much for him?
Who is this person you're talking about?
Who else could it be?
It's him, of course.
Really?
Do you think if I propose to him,
he will agree?
I believe
if it's you asking,
he will definitely agree.
Let's go, time to sleep.
I need to ask Mr. Pillar 300 questions.
Go back to sleep.
(Lu Mansion)
(Time Slips Away)
(Xuewu Courtyard)
I'll prepare the bamboo tubes and water.
Let's make it rain.
I've prepared everything we need.
(Qing Courtyard)
I've read your fortune.
Tonight, it will definitely work.
Make sure nothing goes wrong.
(Lu Mansion)
Sir, come release the lantern.
Let me do it.
- It's beautiful.
- Done.
Why bring an umbrella out?
To be ready for unexpected weather.
(Today, I shall win your heart.)
(Today, under the romantic Kongming lantern,)
(I will propose to Lingyu.)
Look over there, it seems different.
Let's go have a look.
Sure, I haven't strolled around yet.
(I wonder how Yangling and the others)
(are preparing for the event.)
(Hope nothing goes wrong)
(when we release the lanterns later.)
Tang and I
worked overnight
to set up the bamboo tubes.
Once we fill them with water,
the water will flow through the tubes.
It feels just like rain.
I brought my flute.
In the melodious flute sound,
amidst the gentle drizzle,
there's a unique charm.
Who dismantled our bamboo tubes?
No worries this time.
The bamboo won't harm
our Kongming Lantern.
Qian Hexagram represents the sky.
It must mean a blessing will come today.
When the Kongming Lanterns rise,
we'll hear good news
from Yun and Miss Luo.
That would be wonderful.
Hurry, they're coming.
You handle it.
- There are fewer people. Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's make another wish.
The evening breeze is so refreshing today.
Yes, it is.
It's muggy.
They're coming.
Hurry, hurry, lights on!
Quickly, it's time!
Light it up!
(We're in position.)
(Why hasn't it rained yet?)
Can we redo it in time?
Is there still time?
This...
(Forget it. I'll do it anyway.)
(Just speak directly.)
Xuechen,
I have something to tell you.
Wait, don't speak yet.
Lingyu,
I have a surprise for you.
Oh no, it's on fire!
Wait a moment.
They are here.
Let's just splash it.
My lantern!
Hurry, light another one!
We should splash it like rain.
Bring another one over.
Who's splashing water up there?
- Why is it you?
So you dismantled the bamboo tubes.
Why would you dismantle them?
Bamboo tubes...
Lu Xian mentioned
the bamboo tubes disrupt Feng Shui.
Yes, that's right.
It blocks one's romantic encounters.
Romantic encounters?
Didn't you drench our Kongming Lanterns?
Why splash water on the street?
It is... of course,
to avoid the harsh sunlight.
The flowers are all wilted.
There are no flowers on the stone slabs.
Tang, this is just too absurd.
Who pours water
and sets up tubes at night?
And those Kongming Lanterns,
what are they even for?
We...
You don't need to be so secretive.
It's just about proposing marriage.
Why make it so complicated?
Marriage proposal?
You're also going to propose.
Indeed,
as long as the two of us
plan something at the same time,
it will inevitably be ruined.
In Shuozhou, it was like this,
and today is no different.
So, what does it matter?
As long as it's you messing up, it's fine.
♪Clouds dream of garments,
flowers dream of grace♪
♪Love for power, beauty,
but freedom takes the place♪
♪Pearls of the night or robes of gold♪
Doesn't matter anymore.
Lingyu, do you agree or not?
Wait a moment.
Tang.
♪Wanna be my rival, you say♪
What's this?
♪Sorry, you're not there yet, today♪
♪Don't speak of forever♪
This is specially made for you,
a new groom crown fit for you.
Would you marry me?
♪Let love not be late♪
♪Step aside, step aside, make some space♪
Let me think about it.
♪If you're just boring, I won't stay♪
Marry her, marry her, marry her.
Alright.
The Kongming Lanterns can't be used,
but I won't waste these petals.
Great.
Your Highness, the water is ready.
Since the water is ready,
and it doesn't need to rain,
let me cool you off.
Don't run.
Cooling off.
My Lady, fight back.
♪Bright moonlight,
with lanterns still burning♪
♪Deep night's hue, your face softly blurring♪
Look at them.
♪Fate entwines, a knot forever binding♪
How dare you splash me!
♪Yet your bright smile, how it steals♪
♪Like the fireworks in the night sky♪
♪A brilliance that no words can yield♪
Aman.
♪In this life,
meeting you is fate's best hand♪
♪La~ la~♪
Splash him.
♪In this life, I wish for your words♪
♪From black hair to white,
we'll brave time's trend♪
Ajiao, did you bring silver taels?
I brought some. Do you need it?
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
Give this to me too.
I'll return a better one in Jingyang.
Where are you going?
Don't worry about it.
Lingyu, let's go.
Where to?
Come back soon.
Where are you going?
To Jingyang.
What's in Jingyang?
To become the new husband of the Luo clan.
Do you truly want this?
♪This love's riddle,
your heart cold as steel♪
From now on,
I live as a member of the Luo clan,
and in death, a spirit of your clan.
♪A brilliance that no words can yield♪
♪La~ la~♪
Don't forget our promise.
I ask for your word
that our love may stand like mountains.
You have my word
that our love will stand like mountains.
♪From black hair to white,
we'll brave time's trend♪
Let's go.
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
♪In this life,
may our love stand like mountains♪
It's raining.
How dare you splash me!
Give it to me.
Make it a little heavier.
Come on.
It's all yours.
So beautiful.
Let's go.
♪In this life, I wish for your words♪
Wait a moment.
♪In this life, may our love forever blend♪
♪Let's make a pact with the changing seas♪
♪In this life,
may our love stand like mountains♪
♪Through seasons' change, our whispers weave♪
♪In this life, may our love never fades away♪
♪Outshining all the world's glories,
come what may♪
♪It's hard to see through fate♪
♪I sat alone amid the downpour at night♪
♪The single string broke; half a bed's cold♪
♪A cup of wine, drifting and disappearing♪
♪The waning moon sways the candlelight♪
♪Memories penned in ink♪
♪The wind is cool, flowers wither♪
♪Thoughts like stars deeply etched in eyes♪
♪If white-haired,
a solitary figure on the cold river♪
♪Tears fall for a thousand autumns♪
♪Drifting with the wind,
unending sorrow of separation♪
♪Longing only to hold the brush♪
♪Painting the fleeting years, faces unchanged♪
♪At the end of time♪
♪Suddenly turning back in the mundane world♪
♪If we grow old together,
solitary figure on the cold river♪
♪Tears fall for a thousand autumns♪
♪Drifting with the wind,
unending sorrow of separation♪
♪Longing only to hold the brush♪
♪Painting the fleeting years, faces unchanged♪
♪At the end of time♪
♪Suddenly turning back in the mundane world♪