THIS SURVIVAL GAME TAKES PLACE
IN A ZOMBIE UNIVERSE
THE CAST ACT OF THEIR OWN ACCORD
AND TURN INTO ZOMBIES ONCE BITTEN
PLEASE BE ADVISED
OF THEIR IMMERSION IN THE GAME
ONE MONTH AGO
HWANGCHON-RI
Son! Son!
-Oh, Mother, I could've gotten it.
-There you are.
Why are you carrying
heavy stuff like that?
Oh, here. Try one.
-Say, "Ah."
-Ah.
Oh, goodness. It's so tasty.
Even a pebble would taste good
if it came from you.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, you're such a good boy.
Mother, let me put on
-a fun show for you.
-All right.
Ta-da!
-What's that?
Mother. I'll be right back,
so just sit tight for a bit, okay?
Sir! Sir!
Sir!
THE 5 OF THEM ARE DEEP ASLEEP
IN COMPLETE DARKNESS
What is this?
Hey.
-Jonathan. Our hands.
-What?
Hyung, our hands are tied up.
Our legs, too.
-Noona, noona.
-Ah! I can't see anything.
-It hurts.
-Our hands are tied up.
What's going on?
Why are my hands tied?
-Hyung!
-Hm?
-Patricia!
-What's going on?
-Hong-chul!
-Patricia.
-Patricia. Is she not here?
-Hong-chul.
I wanna live.
-It's not working.
-Our hands.
Like this?
I broke my ties.
I can get my hands out. I got it,
Dex, no!
It hurts! Stop! You're killing me.
-Seriously?
-They did a terrible job.
We're all untied now.
What else can we do?
Our hands are free, though.
-Hey!
-Na-rae!
Park Na-rae!
Kkwachu!
-You in there?
-Doctor!
Kkwachu Hyung!
-Na-rae!
-Doc! Doctor!
6 HOURS AGO
HWANGCHON-RI TOWN HALL
THE 10TH TOWN CHIEF, LEE JUN-HYEOK
Man, I'm so tired. Wow.
Oh.
THEY ARRIVED AT THE PROVIDED LODGING
ROARING DRUNK
I'm so sleepy.
I'm just now wiping of the blood.
-DinDin, there…
-It's an award plaque.
I'm so happy
we get to sleep somewhere warm.
I love it.
We'll get to sleep
lying down peacefully.
-Let's sleep.
-It's so nice.
I'm going to sleep now.
There's even a chamber pot, look.
-A chamber pot?
-A chamber pot.
-Wanna torment this lot?
-Oh, no.
-Just go to the toilet here at night.
-No, thanks.
Why is your arm like that?
Huh?
Gosh, what do I do?
THE BITE WOUND IS DEFINITELY WORSE
THAN THE DAY BEFORE
-It looks so gross.
-Jeez, your arm…
It must be so painful.
-Um, I'm sorry to say this…
-Wow. Seriously.
We've all been together
up until now, right?
-Yes, we have. And we will.
-You haven't turned into zombies yet.
-We won't. It'll be fine.
-We won't.
But you don't know.
Your wound has gotten worse, right? Hyung…
What are you talking about?
It's itchy, so I just scratched it.
-No. It's fine.
-Don't do that!
It's just my skin. Look! That's it.
Seriously, that's the problem.
We'll be defenseless at night.
-What if you turn suddenly?
-That's what I'm saying.
-Then we'll all die.
-How many hours have we been together?
-Yeah, we've been together…
-We haven't changed.
-…and we haven't changed.
-But that was during the day.
-But it's about time.
-Right.
Time for what?
Oh, oppa, it's time for you to go?
No.
-Then what if…
-Oppa, it must be your time.
You spend the night outside.
And then if you're still fine,
we'll be able to trust you completely.
I think the leader
should make the decision.
Are you kidding me? It's so cold.
It's cold out. This is the only warm room.
-It's freezing.
-It's so cold outside.
Not outside. There are many rooms.
It's so cold out there.
It's freezing there!
I thought I was outside.
We'll give you some blankets.
You shouldn't have been bitten then.
Dang it, you little punk.
Noona. Hold on.
-Seriously.
-You know I'm right. You know it.
-Which one should I bite?
-You're not wrong.
-Not me.
-Eenie…
-Did you enjoy it?
-…meenie.
It's been fun, right?
-Go outside.
-Oh, come on. Don't be like that.
How would they do it in Japan?
They should sleep outside, right?
Tsuki, please.
-The Japanese hate inconveniencing others.
-Right.
-It's too cold.
-Can you sleep in the same room?
-In Japan, the culture there…
-I don't know.
So, don't take this the wrong way.
We're not asking you to go outside.
-We'll just be in different rooms.
-Right.
-It's freezing out there. Freezing!
-It's really cold.
It's not that warm in here either.
It's so cold in here.
What do you mean? It's hot.
-It's not boiling hot though.
-Hey, wait. You find the room hot?
It's not hot at all.
Maybe only zombies find it hot.
-Suddenly it feels cold.
-It feels cold.
Isn't it? Then go sleep outside.
-It's cold there too.
-Gosh, seriously.
No, I don't want to go outside!
-Then let's keep the door open.
-Should we? Let's do that.
-Keep it open.
-And sleep.
-We can communicate.
-Just put your legs inside. Okay?
Let's go outside. Come on.
-Blankets.
-Give us some blankets.
We'll give you the thicker one.
-Good night, Na-rae.
-I'll open it for you.
-Open the door.
-It's so cold.
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN TO THEM…
Good night, Na-rae.
Good night.
Na-rae.
Park Na-rae!
-Good night.
-Oppa, good night.
-Doctor!
-Kkwachu Hyung!
Kkwachu!
It's freezing. So cold.
-My entire body hurts. Wait.
-My body is stiff.
I slept so uncomfortably.
My body is so stiff
from the cold.
Na-rae, we're locked in here!
What? Wait a second. We're cold.
-Are you cold? Wake up!
-Na-rae!
-Help us!
-Wake up.
Na-rae,
someone tied us up in here!
Someone locked us up!
-Kkwachu Hyung!
-We're locked in here!
The door is locked!
-Kkwachu!
-We can't get out!
Quiet down.
What's wrong?
-What's wrong with your face?
-What happened?
What happened?
The veins on your face.
-Your veins are bulging.
-Me too?
Your eyes are bloodshot too.
What do I look like?
Yours are red too.
Na-rae's condition worsened.
I can't move my arm.
Maybe because we slept in the cold?
Hold on.
Kkwachu Hyung's condition worsened.
I can't move my left arm.
I can't move my right arm.
Na-rae, someone tied us up in here!
-I'm sure you're sleeping fine. What now?
-Kkwachu Hyung!
Please open the door. Please!
-What?
-Wait, who locked this?
Did you lock it to keep us out?
-I think the town chief did it.
-Oh, gosh.
-The drinks we had…
-He must've drugged us.
-…he must have drugged it.
-Okay.
If only Hong-chul were missing,
I'd assume he had fled.
-Yeah.
-But Patricia is missing too.
-So why did you kick us out?
-Exactly.
-Kick us out?
-So why did you kick us out?
-Exactly.
-This isn't the time to talk about that!
-Na-rae.
-My arm isn't working.
-My arm. It feels weird.
THE TABLES HAVE TURNED
FOR THE HALF-ZOMBIES AND THE HUMANS
Doctor! Na-rae!
We don't have the key.
Go look for it on your side.
In your room.
Wait a second.
"Go look for it on your side"?
-"Go look"?
-Are you ordering me around?
-He didn't mean to.
-No.
Na-rae, it's because we're desperate.
We're sorry, he misspoke. We're sorry.
I'm sorry.
Na-rae. We're friends.
Our fate depends on you and oppa.
I'm sorry, but…
"I'm sorry, but"?
-I'm truly sorry.
-Okay.
Please find the key and help us.
THEY'RE BOWING DOWN AND PLEADING!
It'd be great if you could help us.
You're not standing, are you?
You're all on your knees?
-Of course.
-Yeah.
-We believe you.
-Of course.
Try asking more sincerely.
Na-rae, Na-rae, Na-rae! Kkwachu oppa,
we've been through
so many crises together.
I told you I can take care of myself.
-Sit down here.
-What do we do?
-What's this?
-Clothes. Clothes.
Whoa!
SI-YOUNG'S PLEA CONVINCED THE ZOMBIES
There are five of us in here.
Help us just this once.
-Please save us.
-Noona.
-I do feel bad for Si-young though.
-I'm so scared.
-It's not like we can just save her.
-I know.
-Noona, Kkwachu Hyung.
-Yeah?
Listen, we stayed with you
even though you became half-zombies.
Don't call them half-zombies, yeah?
They're regular human beings.
-Watch what you say.
-I don't feel so good
after sleeping out here.
Na-rae, you're a hero.
Okay, seriously.
I'll help because Si-young
gave me this jacket.
Oh, thank you so, so much.
Thank you.
A new quest has been created.
ESCAPE THE ROOM
FIND A WAY TO OPEN THE LOCK
This is the last door left.
The only other room here.
-What's this room for?
-Oh, my. Oppa.
What's going on?
What's this?
THEY DISCOVER A CCTV MONITORING ROOM
-What's this? These are real.
-Wait.
Wait. There they are.
-Jonathan and Si-young.
-Right.
Wave your hand if you can hear me.
They can hear us.
-They can hear us.
-Then what should we do?
Let's tell them to go
to the other door, over there.
They should move toward the center.
Listen, you five!
Take three steps back.
-Wait. Left foot first.
-One, two, three.
-One, wait… Hang on.
-Left foot? Left foot!
-But your left foot is my right foot.
-It doesn't work.
Si-young's left foot.
-This is funny.
-Hey.
They're not synchronized at all.
One, two.
-One, two.
-One, two. Be careful.
-Is it working? Is it?
-No.
Jonathan, here, we need to move together.
At the same time when we say two.
HE CAN'T EVEN OPEN HIS EYES TO WALK
-Should we move forward again?
-Yeah.
-Okay. One, two.
-One, two.
-Hey, don't move forward.
-Don't move forward.
Si-young, turn counterclockwise.
-This way. One.
-One, two.
-Two.
-But why are they asking us to do this?
THEY'RE BEING TRAINED LIKE DOGS
There's a wardrobe in front of you.
Open it.
-DinDin and Si-young.
-Open this?
There's a wardrobe
by DinDin and Si-young. Open it.
-Okay, Doctor.
-That's it.
-What's wrong? What?
-What?
BOWLS: STAINLESS STEEL BOWLS
FROM THE TOWN FESTIVAL
They're rice bowls!
They're just rice bowls.
It's okay, they're harmless.
They're harmless. It's fine.
There are no zombies.
Wait a moment.
So why are you making us open this?
Well, we don't know what's what…
-Wait. DinDin.
-Did he just yell at us
-about opening the door?
-Did you yell at us?
I'm gonna kill them when I get out.
DinDin. DinDin.
-He didn't yell at you.
-No, he didn't.
HE SPEAKS IN A NEW TONE
TO MANAGE THE SITUATION
I'm sorry.
We're trying to figure it out too,
DinDin.
-He didn't.
-I didn't yell at you.
What did you do wrong, DinDin?
I raised my voice.
That's right.
THANKFULLY, NA-RAE
ISN'T AS ANGRY ANYMORE
-Yes, you did.
-Yes.
-It's all our fault. It is.
-Let's hurry.
It was a misunderstanding.
-Now…
-I'll kill them right away, really.
♪ Made a little cookie ♪
♪ Gave it to my mother this treat ♪
Save me! Help!
ABANDONED RICE MILL
A BANQUET FOR MOTHER
Oppa!
TWO MEATY PREY HAVE ARRIVED
AT THE ZOMBIE MOTHER'S DINNER TABLE
Over there! There!
-What the?
-Oppa!
SHE'S BEEN STARVING,
INSISTING ONLY ON LIVE PREY
Help! Save us!
-Wait.
-Stay calm.
Look, she's tied over there. She's tied.
Hey, she can't come closer.
Is that right?
She can't reach us.
HER MOVEMENT IS RESTRICTED
AS SHE'S TIED TO A ROPE
Did she recognize the town chief earlier?
Mother, it's me. Mother. Mother?
♪ Made a little cookie ♪
♪ Baked it for mother, this treat ♪
Mother?
No, she doesn't recognize anyone.
She doesn't.
FOOD SHOULDN'T TALK
She can't.
What if we start a fire with the candles?
Huh? What?
CANDLES: LAVENDER-SCENTED.
CAREFUL, OR YOU'LL BECOME COOKED MEAT.
Wait, she can't come over here.
The candles. That's it, yeah.
Look, the way it's tied.
It's a boating knot.
You tie it that way
so you can easily undo it.
Wow.
Like this? Like this?
If I pull at it a little,
it might come undone.
-Patricia.
-Should we pull it together?
-Where should I hold on?
-I'm sorry.
Oppa.
-I think it got tighter.
-Oppa.
IT'S TIED QUITE TIGHTLY NOW
-It's got even tighter.
-Gosh, oppa.
-It got even tighter. Oh, jeez.
-Hold on.
Let's think. Let's think.
-Like this…
-Oh?
Hey, it worked.
THE FOOD WASN'T PACKAGED PROPERLY
Hey, I think it'll work.
What if that snaps?
This one, how do you do it?
I got it.
Ma'am.
Please, ma'am. I wanna live.
-Ma'am. Almost there.
-I got it.
-Okay, great. I've got it.
-Almost.
Oppa, wait, one second.
-Oppa, were you gonna betray us?
-Hey, I…
-You were. Okay.
-No, I didn't do this. Trust me.
-She must be hungry.
-Oppa!
Hey, I got it. Almost. Wait.
SHE HAS NO CHOICE
BUT TO WATCH HER PREY GET AWAY
Let's get outside first.
It's locked from the outside.
Is it? Can we check that side over there?
-Which side?
-Can you draw her attention?
Okay. Grandmother. Ma'am.
♪ Made a little cookie ♪
♪ Cookie? I baked ♪
Na-rae!
YOU CAN'T TEACH AN OLD DOG NEW TRICKS
♪ Baked it for mother, this… ♪
Oppa, sing "Made A Little Cookie".
-Sing it now! "Made A Little Cookie."
-♪ Made a little, made a little ♪
-♪ Made a little cookie ♪
-Oppa, sing "Made A Little Cookie".
-♪ Made a little, made a little ♪
-Oppa!
-Oppa! Sing "Made A Little Cookie!"
-♪ Made a little cookie ♪
Your voice
is louder than mine. You're louder.
You're louder than me.
♪ Baked it for mother, this treat ♪
THE FOOD HAS PUT KETCHUP ON ITSELF
♪ Made a little cookie ♪
Crap.
-What do we do?
-It's blood. Blood!
THE OLD LADY CAN'T BELIEVE HER EARS
There's no way to get out of here.
There's no door either.
The window!
-What?
-It's flapping. There.
THEY DISCOVER A SMALL WINDOW
IN THE BACK
-Isn't that a window?
-But can we get over there?
Not to mention,
we have to climb all the way up there.
-We need a step. Wait. Okay.
-Let's make it fair.
It's risky
to be in front of her.
-Right. Right.
-She can reach over there.
We'll distract her, then one person
goes over there to stack something.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Then we'll switch.
And the other person distracts her.
Do you wanna go there first?
Sure. Okay, Oppa.
I mean, you normally shouldn't make
the other person go first, right?
Should I go first then? You can do it.
You go first, Oppa. Then I'll do it.
First, that basket there.
I'll draw her attention this way.
You put something there.
-Oppa.
-Yes?
-Don't worry.
-You trust me, right?
-Yeah, completely.
-Absolutely.
-I trust you too.
Ma'am. Here.
Here, here, here. Hold this, please.
Do you want to go first or should I?
Oh!
You little…
Gosh. She's abandoning me, jeez.
PATRICIA STABS HIM IN THE BACK FIRST!
Oh, come on.
Wow, Patricia. I can't believe her!
HE CAN'T JUST LET HER ABANDON HIM
Hey! Oh, gosh!
-Yah!
-Hey, wait!
EMERGENCY!
HER PANTS ARE ABOUT TO FALL DOWN
Hey!
Oppa!
Did you make it?
PATRICIA ESCAPES FIRST!
HONG-CHUL DID NOT SEE THIS COMING!
-Oppa!
-Yeah?
Wait.
I'll come back.
Oh, no. This is so scary.
HONG-CHUL GETS BETRAYED
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 31 HOURS
MEANWHILE, AT DOG TRAINING
One, two.
I think the key is inside the jewelry box.
Something weird.
Some squeaky thing. Dentures too.
It's important for someone.
Don't throw it away.
Keep the denture.
-Take four steps back.
-Four steps.
One, two.
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED
FROM THE CONTINUOUS TRAINING
One…
Look behind Tsuki and Jonathan.
Is this it? What is this fruit called?
What is it?
Aren't they ripe persimmons?
Ripe persimmons?
Ripe persimmons!
-Ripe persimmons?
-Yeah.
Are they well-ripened?
Come on. We're really suffering over here!
-I don't really know either.
-Seriously.
The key could be in them, right?
-You might find the key as you eat them.
-Gosh.
THEY GROW EXHAUSTED
AT THE HALF-ZOMBIES' JOKES
I found something.
Shoot, it's the chamber pot. Dang it!
-Are you okay?
-A chamber pot!
What's a chamber pot?
You pee in it.
Is there anything inside?
-It stinks.
-Dang it.
HALF-FULL CHAMBER POT:
A PORTABLE TOILET USED BY MAYBE 50 PEOPLE
It's partly full. Dang it.
There's a chamber pot?
-Yeah.
-Open the lid.
-Did you put your hand inside?
-Yeah!
-What's inside?
-This isn't gonna work.
THE LEADER HAS BLOWN UP
-When I get out…
-Yeah?
…I'll kill both of you immediately.
-I'm gonna kill you too.
-Fine.
-Wait. No.
-Listen. Earlier…
-Don't do this, seriously.
-No. Earlier,
I saw a wooden board earlier over there.
-I see.
-The Senior Community Center sign.
-Let's break down the door.
-Let's go to the back.
-Let's get out, first.
-To the back. One, two.
-Wait.
-They're breaking down the door?
Wait! One second! Hold on! Wait!
Wait. Stay calm. Take it easy.
-Everyone, I got the board.
-You got it?
The quest has been suspended.
-Oppa, run!
-Stop.
HONG-CHUL ALSO ATTEMPTS
TO ESCAPE USING A TOOL
Over here, here, here, here.
-No. Ma'am.
-Ma'am.
-Oh, gosh, ma'am.
-Oppa, run!
Uh, please, ma'am.
Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am. I'm sorry.
One, two, three.
Oh, jeez.
Okay, one more time.
Oppa.
SHE'S COMPLETELY DRAINED
-I'm so sorry, ma'am.
-Oppa.
Okay, one last time.
One, two, three.
-Okay! It's open.
-We did it!
OW! THE KNEECAPS!!
My shoulder hurts.
Oppa, are you okay?
-Are you okay?
-It's dislocated.
Okay!
We did it!
Hey, that worked.
Let's kill them.
-Wait. We…
-Hold on. Listen.
No.
No need to explain. Nope, it's fine.
-Jonathan.
-Who tied you up?
-You weren't lying.
-Wait. They've turned so pale.
-One.
-Come on.
It's because we slept
in the cold room without any heating.
-Your veins are bulging out.
-It was cold.
-On your right side.
-Wow, look here.
-Why it get so cold?
-This room is nice.
AS EXPECTED,
THE HALF-ZOMBIES DON'T LOOK SO GOOD
Come on. Let's go.
It's what happens
when you sleep in the cold.
-Try it.
-Watch your legs.
One, two.
-Let's go with them.
-We'll come too. Okay.
Wait. Hold on.
We'll go out first.
Fine. Man, you're so on edge.
-Why are you being like that?
-Everyone out?
-Yeah.
-One, two.
One, two. One…
This is working.
One, two.
FIVE OUT OF SEVEN ESCAPED
Slowly.
Gosh, Oppa, thank you so much, really.
No, you did it yourself.
You even let me go first.
-I let you?
-Thank you.
-I let you go first? Sure.
-You did great.
-Ouch. That stings.
TWO ESCAPED
One, two.
Wait.
Which way should we go?
Let's hide first.
They've arrived at a new place.
-Let's go.
-One, two.
-One, two, one.
They'll come if we turn
the lights on, right?
Over there.
Let's go this way. To the right.
This way?
-One, two.
-One.
They must not know
we got out, right?
I don't know.
We have to get out of here now.
Darn it.
Two… One…
Anything here? Look around.
I see something. There.
Isn't that a saw on the right?
A saw?
Yes, there is.
-Cable cutters over there.
-Cable cutters? Nice. Great.
-Let's cut it. Come on.
-Yeah.
I can't believe this happened.
That's much better.
We can hide in here.
IT'S QUIET IN THE FACTORY
AND NO ONE SEEMS TO BE AROUND
There's plenty of space up there
we can go.
Shouldn't we hide somewhere up there,
at least until the sun comes up?
It's dangerous, so…
-Everyone, put them on.
-Everyone? No, I'm good.
These must belong
to the factory employees.
We can hit our heads.
Let's go and look first.
-Okay.
-Think about what to do.
-Si-young.
-Let's go look.
I'm going that way.
Are you all right?
-I'm scared.
-Careful.
Careful. Careful.
It's the safest here, don't you think?
We can defend ourselves here
when they come up.
-We can block them here.
-Since it's steep.
What was that sound?
I heard something. Is there a zombie?
There are zombies.
THESE ARE THE WORST ZOMBIES
THEY'VE SEEN BY FAR
What the…
FACTORY FULL OF ZOMBIES
A FILIAL LOVE GONE WRONG
There's a cage.
Someone locked up the zombies
in here.
Look over there.
Someone locked them in here.
It's like a zombie prison.
-It looks awful.
-What happened? Who did this?
What do we do?
Oh, no!
Hide. Hide. Everyone, hide.
Get away from me!
What's all this, huh?
Get over there!
It's the town chief.
You little…
The town chief.
He must have done all this.
THEY'VE BEEN HANDLING AND KEEPING
THOSE WHO WERE ZOMBIFIED BY MOTHER
Those jerks.
Shoo! Away. Away!
Don't you dare.
Hey, hey! Block them.
Block them. Block them.
Hyung, what happened to your arm?
Is that… Isn't that blood?
Go bring the iodine.
Now that I've gotten hurt,
I feel braver.
I wanna get those punks
and crush them in the machine.
So what happened, hyung?
My mother…
They tied her up like a dog and ran away.
-What?
-Those punks!
Mother!
What happened?
Who did this? Get up. Get up.
Get up. Come on.
Mother!
It's me, your son!
I'm your son.
Darn it, what the heck? What the heck?
Mother, are you okay? Those punks.
Mother, just sit tight, okay?
Sit tight.
Those little…
I think they're talking about us.
I told you
not to roam around, didn't I?
Didn't I?
THEY LET OUT A STRONG REACTION
TO THE VICIOUS BLOW
Hold on.
What was that sound?
There's a rat in here. A very big one.
Isn't there?
Over there,
there,
-and there.
-There.
-Look around.
-Okay.
Hey, you guys come with me.
What do we do?
Hide all you want!
-Come on.
-Stay low.
Let's get out of here.
I'll go up this way.
You go that way. And you go that way.
I think it'll be better
to go over there.
HIDE-AND-SEEK
HIDE FROM THE TOWN CHIEF'S MEN
THE FACTORY'S SECOND FLOOR ISN'T BIG
THEY NEED TO SEPARATE
SO THEY WON'T BE FOUND
DINDIN
UNDER THE STAIRCASE, ABOVE THE PIPES
JONATHAN
THE NARROW SPACE BETWEEN STRUCTURES
THE SUBLEADER
FEARLESSLY GOES INSIDE A MACHINE
LEE SI-YOUNG
INSIDE A MACHINE ON THE 2ND FLOOR
THE LEADER IS EVEN MORE EXTREME!
DEX
THE TOP OF THE STEEL STRUCTURES
TSUKI
BETWEEN STEEL BOARDS
DEX, JONATHAN
LEE SI-YOUNG, DINDIN, TSUKI
You better hope
I don't find you.
You all are like a rat in a trap.
You don't see them?
AWARD OF APPRECIATION
LEE JUN-HYEOK
FILIAL SON AWARD
THE TOWN CHIEF'S UNDERLINGS
HAVE FINISHED THEIR SEARCH
Step aside.
Okay, hyung.
My goodness.
I got you! There you are.
What are you doing here?
No!
-What are you waiting for?
-No!
Come on. Get her!
Help! Si-young!
Stay still!
Get her.
Where do you think you're going?
Stop right there.
Stop! Where do you think you're going?
-Hold on to her tightly.
-Take her.
Hold her as you go down.
I got your back.
And clean this place up. Clean it up!
Clear the way for Jun-hyeok.
Don't try to run, just follow him.
-Hey, open the door.
-Bring her.
Hey, put her up here.
-Go up.
-Hyung, I'll do it. Yeah.
Get up. Now.
Oh, God! No!
-Stay in there, okay?
-Oh, no!
THE PRISONER NEXT DOOR WELCOMES HER
You can't do this.
You can't do this to me!
Make sure it's locked.
Yes, hyung.
We won't make the same mistake.
Look. It's locked tight this time.
-Hyung, what happened?
-I think Tsuki got caught.
What do I do?
Move aside. Move, move!
What are you doing? Stop that.
What is that?
Listen carefully.
Where are the rest of them?
I don't know.
Tell me now!
I said I don't know. I really don't.
I really don't know,
but I don't think they're in here.
-I was the only one here.
-Go.
THE YOUNGEST COMMENDABLY
DOESN'T BETRAY THEM
-Go, go.
-I'm really scared.
Listen out there!
I'll find you no matter what.
DinDin.
DinDin. Dex?
THEY EMERGE FROM THEIR HIDING SPOTS
-Jonathan.
-Yeah?
-Where is Dex?
-Come out, Jonathan.
-Where's Jonathan?
-He's coming down.
Tsuki.
Yeah?
Are you okay?
I'm… I'm not okay.
SHE'S STUTTERING DUE TO FEAR
-I'm not okay.
-Hang in there, Tsuki.
We'll rescue you.
Help me. Please.
THEY MUST RESCUE HER
WHILE THE TOWN CHIEF IS AWAY
But the problem is,
it's too dangerous for us to go ourselves.
Oh, if Na-rae and Kkwachu Hyung were here,
they could have gone and saved her.
We shouldn't have abandoned them.
We should've brought them along.
Actually, it wasn't me who abandoned them.
When I get out,
I'll kill both of you immediately.
I'm going to kill you too.
-Let's go with them.
-Wait. Hold on. We'll go out first.
Why are you being like that?
THEY HAVE NOTHING
TO SAY FOR THEMSELVES
Is it that way?
Did they really go that way? No way.
Why can't we walk properly?
I keep… I keep slowing down.
Really?
-Dang.
-Gosh, my heart. Seriously.
We can't let our guard down here either.
Oh, jeez.
IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA TO SCREAM
IN A PLACE FILLED WITH ZOMBIES
-Oh, man.
-What? What's this?
Be careful.
Oh, shoot!
What was that?
Come on.
-Jeez.
-Huh?
-I hear something.
-My brother's voice.
Si-young! I'm still here!
We need to go now.
Seriously?
-You scared me.
-Oh, hey.
-What's this? What the heck?
Oh, darn.
Oppa.
Tsuki is locked up over there.
Oh, shoot!
Hong-chul! Help me!
-What…
-Where were you?
-We were…
-Did you two leave?
-What happenen?
-We didn't.
We were dragged off by someone.
I'm over here!
Save me!
The town chief is the bad guy.
-The town chief locked up Tsuki.
-Yeah, he is the bad guy.
-Really?
-Yeah. So he took us.
The town chief's mother became a zombie,
and he tried to feed us to her.
Alive?
-Yeah.
-Yes.
Does that mean all these people here
were bitten by his mother?
Hey, he's looking at us.
YES, THAT'S CORRECT!
For us too,
when the mother tried to eat us,
she was tied to something and was limited
in where she could go, like them.
THEY REALIZE THAT
MOST ZOMBIES ARE TIED TO SOMETHING
Since she couldn't really move,
we could run away.
If you look down,
there are a few that aren't tied up.
-Gosh.
-But some of them are.
SOME ZOMBIES ARE SLOW
BUT CAN MOVE FREELY
What do we do about her?
What do we do?
Well…
-They locked the cage.
-The key is over there.
They left the key.
THEY SEE THE KEY TO THE CAGE
LEFT ON THE OFFICE TABLE
Should I… Should I…
make some noise?
Should I…
TSUKI AND THE OFFICE
ARE ON OPPOSITE SIDES OF THE ROOM
Okay, this is what we're gonna do first.
-That door over there.
-Okay.
Inside that is a safe zone.
So first, I'll go get the key.
THE STEALING STRATEGY SEEMS PLAUSIBLE
When Tsuki screams,
they still rush over to that side for now.
I'll go in and get the key.
Let's think about the next steps
after that.
Okay?
HE CHANGED AFTER BEING APPOINTED
AS COMMANDER
I got it. I'll go.
-Tsuki.
-Go.
-Yeah?
Now.
Jeez.
Look. They're going toward her.
What do I do?
Tsuki, I'm sorry. Thank you.
He got the key.
Hey, we can't…
we can't open it for her, though.
How are we gonna get there?
Some of them aren't tied up.
HE LOOKS AROUND TO SEE
IF THERE'S ANYTHING USEFUL
RC CAR: A REMOTE-CONTROLLED TOY CAR.
NOT SURE WHY IT'S IN A FACTORY.
He's bringing something.
Did you get the key?
Noona, I got the key
and this too.
Oh, my gosh.
-What's wrong?
-Look at that.
Oh, shoot.
What is that?
THERE'S A GRUESOME DEAD ZOMBIE
Look.
Huh?
We can use that?
I think we can give her the key with this.
Are you sure you can drive it well?
HE'S KNOWN AS THE SIDE MIRROR-WRECKER
I'll have to try.
IT LOOKS EASY IN MOVIES
But you can't see the path
from down there.
You can see it well from up here.
I'll crack the door open.
Will you be able to see it from there?
-Let me try it first.
-But…
And if it doesn't work,
then I'll bring it back out and go up.
I'll try it first.
-Sure.
-Okay.
THEY COULDN'T PERSUADE THE COMMANDER
We have the key and an RC car.
A remote control car?
DinDin will put the key
inside the RC car and send it over there.
THERE AREN'T MANY AT THE TOP
I think it'll work.
-Hey.
-Tsuki.
-Yeah?
-We'll send a toy car to you.
-A tiny mini car.
-A mini car?
We'll put the key inside
and send it to you.
So try to get the key.
Okay, I got it.
-Unlock the door yourself.
-Okay.
But it might be more dangerous
if she opens it.
Will she be able
to get it from there, though?
THIS ISN'T TOP GUN
Okay, DinDin is ready.
THIS IS HIS FIRST MISSION AS COMMANDER
IT'S DEFINITELY DOABLE
IF HE NAVIGATES THE EMPTY SPACES
BUT HE MUST AVOID
THE BOTTOM PATH FULL OF ZOMBIES
The quest begins.
RESCUE TSUKI!
DELIVER THE KEY WITH AN RC CAR
IT'S GOING WELL SO FAR
That's harder than it looks.
IT'LL REACH THE CAGE
IF IT CONTINUES STRAIGHT!
I think it might work.
Hey, DinDin.
He can't see it from down there.
THE RC CAR IS OUT OF HIS LINE OF SIGHT
NOW HE MUST RELY ON HIS INTUITION
Oh, yah, the noise, the noise.
IT MADE SOME NOISE
THE ZOMBIES REACT TO THE RATTLING KEYS
Oh! Yah!
Please, please, please.
THEY'RE SLOWLY REMINDED
OF THE PARKING LOT NIGHTMARE…
IT ENTERS THE DANGEROUS AREA
FULL OF ZOMBIES
-Oh, no! He dropped it.
-Oh, no.
He dropped it? The key's on the floor?
DROPPED IN THE SWARM OF ZOMBIES!
Good job, you dropped it
right where they're all gathered.
-No! What are we gonna do?
-Gosh, there, right in the middle.
They're playing soccer with it.
THAT'S A GREAT BACK AND FORTH VOLLEY
What now?
It won't be easy to pick that up.
EVEN THE CHANCE
FOR ANOTHER TRY IS GONE
The quest has been suspended.
We should've thrown it to her from here.
Seriously?
It failed completely.
That flipped over too.
We should've thrown it to her
from the edge over there.
Why didn't you drive it from here?
Why do you always insist
on doing it your own way?
We have a leader right here.
This group doesn't need a leader.
THEIR TEAMWORK CRUMBLES
But that…
I mean, I saw something.
And Si-young saw it too.
There's a dead body over there.
It's like they dissected the corpse.
Oh, man, dang!
All the intestines are out.
But if we put zombie blood on ourselves,
they wouldn't bite us.
I mean it.
That's what happened
with Na-rae and Kkwachu Hyung too.
If we put blood on us and then go,
maybe we won't get bitten.
-Put blood all over ourselves?
-Yeah.
PUTTING ON ZOMBIE BLOOD
SOUNDS TRULY AWFUL!
But do we really,
really have to rescue her?
-Tsuki?
-Oppa.
Please help me. Help.
I mean, I'm just asking.
-Oppa!
-Will we rescue her?
At any cost? What do you wanna do?
Oppa, she's the youngest among us.
That's why I was just asking.
What do we do?
Then you try it.
Me again?
Because you're the commander.
But the leader…
-You don't listen to me anyway.
-I mean, seriously, like…
what has he done as a former Navy Seal?
Any volunteers?
-Rock-paper-scissors.
-What, any volunteers?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Fine. Then, should we do
rock, paper, scissors?
-Anything is fine.
-Rock, paper, scissors, then.
-Whoever loses at the end.
-Just one person.
-We're seriously…
-Let's just do anything.
Or will you do it, Noona?
Will you be okay?
-Wanna smear yourself with blood?
-You were in Sweet Home.
Please give me the key.
If you don't play, you go.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-Scissors.
-Okay.
-We're good.
HONG-CHUL AND DINDIN WON…
-How could this be?
-I knew I'd win. Ha!
I was destined to win.
Because I was just going to
volunteer myself.
-No way.
-I was gonna go too
-because I felt bad
-Seriously.
Oh, well. Too bad.
Rock, paper, scissors!
YOU CAN TELL WHO WON
They're that happy?
Si-young, I don't think I can get it!
THEY'RE SO HAPPY
THEY CAN'T EVEN HEAR TSUKI
-Be there soon.
-Tsuki, hang in there.
Jonathan, I'll give you
a chance to go honorably.
Volunteer yourself.
If you don't play, you're it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
-If you don't play, you're it.
-Wait.
You guys really think alike.
If you don't play, you're it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
-Oppa.
-Is it me?
Oppa.
JONATHAN, IT IS
Good luck.
HE'S ENJOYING IT QUIETLY LIKE A LEADER
Jonathan, don't say you did scissors.
Say you did a heart sign
and volunteer yourself.
-Yeah, Noona. Okay. Hyung.
-Yes?
Actually, I did a heart sign,
not scissors.
Cut your crap and go.
-Come back alive. Go on then.
-Okay. I'll go then.
After you put on the blood,
I think you'll get at least one minute.
-One minute?
-One or two minutes.
-After you put on the blood.
-After the blood.
Dunk your face in the bucket like this.
-Then check.
-Hey, seriously.
If that works, let's bring that to her.
But, oppa, how can… We can't go twice.
Let's put it on him first.
You never know what will happen.
-But…
-We'll stay with you until you put it on.
-Yes, come on.
-It's fine that he puts it on, but…
Go see your brother off.
Patricia, do you wanna go?
-I'll…
-Patricia, don't come. Don't look.
-What?
-You stay over there.
Patricia, say goodbye.
No,
I'll say bye to her from here.
Oppa, you have to come back.
You have to come back.
What's wrong?
Dang.
This is bad. What happened?
THE ZOMBIE'S BODY IS MORE MANGLED
THAN WHAT THEY WERE TOLD
HE'S ALREADY GAGGING
THINKING ABOUT PUTTING ON ZOMBIE BLOOD
Put this on your body.
Then pick up the key,
hand it to Tsuki, and return right away.
Okay?
Okay. Let's do it.
Gosh.
-Is it warm?
-It's cold.
It's cold.
Why does the blood have to be cold too?
-Oh, look. Look at that.
-He touched it.
It's full of intestines.
Jeez, he's putting it on him.
He put on a lot. A whole lot.
Oh, my. Gross.
HE'LL HAVE TO GENEROUSLY PUT IT
ALL OVER HIS BODY TO RETURN SAFELY
-The blood really stinks.
-Raise your arms.
Gosh, the smell.
Wow.
It's okay.
Please look after Patricia for me.
Come on. Don't be ridiculous.
THE LEADER STERNLY SCOLDS HIM
But Patricia, you're really
something else too.
If it were my brother going,
I'd at least offer to go instead,
even if I didn't mean it.
But you seem so okay.
IN THIS SITUATION, YOUR OWN SAFETY
COMES BEFORE ANYTHING ELSE
This is enough
to make them not notice you.
You never know,
-so please look after Patricia.
-Okay.
Jonathan.
What was that?
Come back right away
if it doesn't work.
The quest begins.
RESCUE TSUKI!
DELIVER THE KEY DISGUISED AS A ZOMBIE
AFTER SOME TIME, THE SMELL OF BLOOD
WEARS OUT AND ZOMBIES MAY NOTICE HIM
We'll know the moment he gets out
if this will work or not.
HE MAKES EYE CONTACT WITH A ZOMBIE!
Oh, it's working. It's working.
-It's working.
-They're ignoring him. They are.
Jonathan,
you need to move quickly.
Jonathan, hurry.
IT'S BEST TO MOVE AS FAST AS POSSIBLE
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO AVOID CONTACT WITH ZOMBIES
HE CAN'T MOVE AS ZOMBIES BLOCK HIS PATH
He must be scared.
But look, they do approach him.
They do, but they don't seem to bite.
They're not attacking.
But they might attack him.
I feel so bad for him.
HE TRIES TO CLEAR THE PATH
Move.
Move, please.
I mean…
You said they couldn't see.
Jonathan, if you get bitten,
you'll end up like Hee-kwan.
Move.
Move, please. Come on.
I said, move.
Move, please.
HE'S WASTING TOO MUCH TIME THERE
He can't get surrounded like that.
He's surrounded! He's surrounded!
IF HE GETS SURROUNDED,
HE CAN'T COPE WITH AN EMERGENCY SITUATION!
Move, please.
I said, move.
HE PUSHES THE ZOMBIES AWAY
BY FORCE IN THE END!
Move.
Oh, he's doing great.
Behind you, Jonathan! Run!
THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME LEFT!
-What's that?
-They're attacking. Run!
THE ZOMBIES REALIZED THAT HE'S HUMAN!
What?
THEY'VE RECOGNIZED THEIR PREY
IN FRONT OF THEM!
What? What? What?
Oh, no! Go, Jonathan! Go!
-They're attacking. Run!
-Run! Go!
Jonathan!
THE ONLY WAY TO SURVIVE
IS TO RUN AT FULL SPEED!
HE STILL HAS A CHANCE
IF HE DISPLAYS HIS HERCULEAN STRENGTH
-Jonathan!
-Oppa!
Jonathan! Jonathan! Jonathan!
HE'S ALMOST AT THE EXIT!
Don't trip! Watch out!
-Oppa!
-Jonathan, no!
THE ZOMBIE WHO HAS TASTED BLOOD
TAKES DOWN JONATHAN
Patricia!
Jonathan!
-Patricia!
-Jonathan, come back in!
-Oppa!
Patricia!
-Jonathan, no!
-Oh, gosh!
-No, Jonathan!
Patricia!
Jonathan! Patricia! Patricia!
Grab Dex's hand! Take it!
Dex, be careful!
Close the door! Hurry! Hurry!
UNFORTUNATELY, HE GOT BITTEN
RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE EXIT
THE HUMAN JONATHAN
IS NO LONGER WITH THEM
Hey.
-Are you all right?
-I don't know, Hyung, I got bitten badly.
Hyung, what do we do?
-Let's go see him.
-Jonathan got bitten.
I got bitten all over.
I got bitten here too.
Jonathan got bitten.
Where did he get bitten?
Why did you get yourself bitten?
We saw them going for him.
It didn't… The blood didn't last long.
Where did you get bitten?
Hong-chul, please come check me.
Please come check.
Are you okay?
Where… where did you get bitten?
Oh, no.
Where did he get bitten?
Well, starting from his arm…
Which part?
Here?
Hyung!
-Oppa.
-Is it…
-Are you serious?
-Why would you do that?
-Is it this side?
-Yes, this side.
I think my left arm got bitten a lot.
But…
He's completely out of it now.
-What do we do?
-I don't…
Patricia, you're so…
It's your brother.
Why are you standing so far away?
Because I'm so worried.
Patricia, don't come near me.
-Stay away.
-She's been standing the furthest away.
She hasn't touched you at all.
-She hasn't touched you at all.
-I mean…
Are you sure
you guys are close?
Oh, man. Yes, we are.
-She hasn't touched you even once.
-Are you even siblings?
-All this time.
-Oh, man. Really?
I mean…
Seriously.
I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna kill you.
SHE'S IMPRESSED BY
HER BROTHER'S VENTRILOQUISM SKILLS!
You'll be dead before her.
That's possible.
EVEN THE LEADER IS MOVED
BY THEIR SIBLING LOVE
We shouldn't try
using the blood again, right?
Do it again?
Or if you're still conscious,
How about you go again?
-Oppa.
-Do you want to kill him twice?
-No, but…
-I mean…
A BOLD IDEA THAT'S DIFFICULT TO SUGGEST
Looks like…
He can't…
Wait.
Looks like he's decided
to go with this character.
-But…
-But he is right.
He's already…
-Listen.
-She seems to agree. Look at her.
Come on. Don't laugh. Stop laughing.
Objectively speaking,
Jonathan won't get bitten out there.
But the problem is that Tsuki is a human.
How are we supposed
to get her back here?
Okay. Since he's in so much pain,
let's lay him down safely.
-Let's talk up there.
-His condition is getting worse.
Oppa, stop pointing that at him.
-I'm sorry.
-That's too far.
-But…
-Or since…
-If there isn't much left--
Oh, hey, see? There.
Let's go up to somewhere safe.
Oppa, are you okay?
THEY HAVE TO PLAN
THE NEXT STRATEGY IN A SAFE ZONE
-It's so hard to rescue her.
-Come on. Here. Lie down for now.
Sit down and lean against this.
Jonathan, don't open your eyes.
Keep them closed.
-What should we do?
-Tsuki, can you open it?
-Do you have the key?
-She got it.
Good job. Good job.
But how do I get out?
I mean, there is no way
for Tsuki to get out.
Is no way you can go
one more time, Jonathan? No way?
Sorry?
If Jonathan brings her the bucket,
the problem will be solved.
Jeez. He's got
so much resentment in those eyes.
HE CAN'T HELP BUT LAUGH
AT THEIR HEARTLESSNESS
I don't know.
Come to think of it,
the town chief will return soon, right?
We have to resolve this before he returns.
-I just noticed…
-Okay.
…that there's a pulley over there.
So if Tsuki can just get to that,
I think we can
pull her up using the pulley.
How will she get
all the way over there?
The problem is
that she needs to get there.
IF SHE HOLDS THE ROPE FROM BELOW,
THEY COULD PULL HER UP
Honestly, we could save her right away
if Na-rae and Kkwachu Hyung were here.
We shouldn't have abandoned them.
There's just no way.
-Is this the right place?
-Is this it, Oppa?
My wound!
-Huh?
-Oh, jeez!
Did you hear that?
I think it's Na-rae.
The ropes. Look at the ropes.
-We've come to the right place.
-They've been freed.
-Is this it?
-Park Na-rae!
Jeez. Hey.
-Kkwachu!
-We're over here! Where are you?
We've been walking
for the past three hours.
It took us so long.
It will take us…
a day and a half at this pace.
Can we go all the way there?
This is the fastest I can walk.
We walked between the rice paddies
for three hours.
-Na-rae.
-We're glad you're here.
-Good to have you.
-We were actually thinking of you.
-Good job getting here.
-So…
-Did you get bitten?
-He doesn't look good.
Jonathan got bitten because…
Tsuki is locked up over there.
-Over there?
-Yes.
But…
-I can't go there either.
-What is this place?
IT'S A HORRIFYING SIGHT,
EVEN TO A HALF-ZOMBIE
We found the key over there.
And Jonathan got bitten
trying to get it to her.
-But we can't get over there.
-Oh, jeez!
-Here's what we're thinking.
-Okay.
Jonathan, Na-rae,
and Kkwachu Hyung go down there.
-You push the zombies back.
-Like this. Put you back together
-and push them away.
-You push them.
-And put Tsuki in the middle.
-And bring her here.
-Okay. We'll help.
-Okay. Don't worry.
THEY AGREED WITHOUT HESITATION
We have to try something now.
There is no other way.
I think the town chief
will be here soon.
Zombie Trio, you can do it.
Zombie Trio, let's go.
-Thank you for coming.
-I feel much more at ease now.
-Thank you.
-You can do it!
-I feel bad. We--
Now go save our girl.
We abandoned them.
-Noona, step here. Slowly.
-Be careful.
Tsuki, hang in there
just a little longer.
I'm coming!
My gosh. Thank you so much.
So the zombies won't bite you then, right?
I don't think they will.
-Will they not bite Jonathan either?
-Jonathan, you can do it.
Don't worry.
See? They're friends now.
They're not so bad
once you get used to them.
They're friends now.
Oh, jeez.
HE LOOKS LIKE A DRUNK FRIEND,
NOT A SCARY ZOMBIE
They're friends.
You bit me before.
FRIENDS DON'T HOLD GRUDGES
Nice to meet you. Oh, gosh. Oh.
Why are you lying on the floor?
It's not good for you.
Tsuki!
THEY ARRIVE AT THE CAGE
WITHOUT MUCH RESISTANCE
GET HER OUT AND BRING HER BACK!
Can't get it open?
Why can't you put the key in?
That's it. Hurry.
-Okay. There.
-Hurry.
-Can you put the key in?
-We got it.
-Who are those punks?
-It's open.
-What's going on?
-Don't wait. Get them!
It's the town chief.
-Who are those punks?
-Tsuki, hurry.
What the heck?
-Get them!
-No!
No, no!
Tsuki! Hey!
It's not what it looks like.
-We're not zombies.
-We're human.
Don't move, damn it!
How could you lock up
a person?
Please help me! Help me!
Please pull me up!
RESCUE TSUKI!
THE SACRIFICIAL PULLEY
Someone has to go down with this.
Someone heavier than Tsuki
has to go down to bring her up.
But if you go down…
Please pull me up!
If anyone takes the rope
in front of them,
their friend below will survive.
However, that person will fall
into the horde of zombies.
IF NO ONE DOES ANYTHING,
TSUKI WILL BECOME PREY TO ZOMBIES
What will you do?
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Shoot.
Can you do it?
When Tsuki gets up here,
grab her tight, okay?
-We'll grab her right away.
-Okay.
Hey, Tsuki!
-Tsuki, he's coming!
-Careful! Watch your feet.
Be careful.
Be careful!
Hyung, this way.
DEX ALWAYS LOOKED AFTER OTHERS
RATHER THAN HIMSELF
HE WAS A GOOD LEADER
We got her.
Oh, no. What about Dex?
Hyung!
-Hyung!
-Where do you think you're going?
-Don't move!
-Hyung! Move!
Dex, you have to live!
Hyung!
NO ONE EXPECTED THIS SCENARIO
Dex!
He's safe.
-Come on. Just a little more.
-Let's pull him up.
Come on. Let's pull the rope.
Just a little more. Just a little more.
-You can do it!
-Just a little more, Dex.
-A bit more!
-You're almost there!
Wow, you're amazing!
-Wow, incredible!
-Wow!
-You did it!
-Amazing!
-Thank you so much!
-That was great!
Thank you so much.
You made it.
HE IS A GOOD LEADER!
Wow, good job. Okay. We're next.
Please help us!
Don't move!
-Hyung!
-Doctor!
-Jonathan!
You have nowhere to escape, got that?
-Just go!
-Run now!
You jerk!
-Just go!
-Don't you move!
Town chief, you're horrible!
Hold them tightly.
-What's that?
-What?
Hey, what's that?
What's that?
A new survivor has appeared.
ZOMBIEVERSE
ALL NAMES, BUSINESSES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO ACTUAL PERSONS
OR EVENTS IS COINCIDENTAL