THIS SURVIVAL GAME TAKES PLACE
IN A ZOMBIE UNIVERSE
THE CAST ACT OF THEIR OWN ACCORD
AND TURN INTO ZOMBIES ONCE BITTEN
PLEASE BE ADVISED
OF THEIR IMMERSION IN THE GAME
52 HOURS AGO
ZOMBIE OUTBREAK OCCURS
47 HOURS AGO
5 PEOPLE JOIN THEM
43 HOURS AGO
YOO HEE-KWAN DIES
41 HOURS AGO
PARK NAE-RAE AND KKWACHU HYUNG
GET INFECTED
18 HOURS AGO
JONATHAN GETS INFECTED
AND
NOW
-This isn't good.
-Crap. What if that happens to us too?
Seriously.
18 HOURS AFTER GETTING INFECTED
Jonathan has died.
18 HOURS AFTER GETTING INFECTED,
JONATHAN DIES AND BECOMES A ZOMBIE
What do we do now?
-Come out here. We better talk.
-Right.
What do we do now?
Wow, so you really do turn.
I can't look.
-What do we do?
-So we only have eight people left now?
Oh, no.
-Eight people?
-I think we let our guard down too much.
Since Kkwachu Hyung
and Na-rae didn't change,
we were having fun training,
even in this situation.
But seeing Jonathan like this
really makes this hit home.
THE REALITY IS
THAT THEY CONTINUE TO EXIST
ON THE BORDER
BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH
-I know.
-Dang it.
Anyway, we will eventually
leave this place,
but to be perfectly honest, the issue is…
if we can take Jonathan with us or not.
Then let's hear from everyone.
If we can go together to the end--
You don't have to feel guilty.
You can say no if you want.
We won't blame you for it.
THE FIRST MEMBER TO BECOME A ZOMBIE
They're getting cereal. Yeah!
THEY DISCUSS WHAT THEY'LL DO
ABOUT ZOMNATHAN
Let's hear from Patricia first.
He's her brother.
Of course she wants to bring him.
-Of course she does.
-You never know.
What do you think?
I think your opinion is important…
-Yeah.
-…for us to make our decision too.
Honestly, I do wanna bring him.
-Of course she does.
-Yeah, it's only right.
As his family.
This isn't because I haven't been bitten,
but don't you all agree?
If I were bitten and in that situation,
I think I'd feel better
if you left me behind. I really do.
I think that's the right thing to do.
Because he died already,
if we're being honest.
I think
he'll really slow us down, you know?
-Yeah, it's bad.
-And it'd be better for Jonathan too…
to stay here.
And Mr. Gyeong-cheol,
Mr. Gyeong-cheol from before,
he'd be with him.
There's someone here who can control him.
I'm also waiting to see
if they develop a cure.
So that's why I'm protecting them.
-Because they might develop a cure later.
-Yeah.
That's why I think we wouldn't be
completely abandoning Jonathan
if we left him with Mr. Kim.
Yeah, we can leave Jonathan here.
But how do we know
that we can trust Mr. Kim?
What if he does something to Jonathan?
Like cuts off his arms.
What are you gonna do then?
Don't talk like that in front of Patricia.
Objectively speaking.
Look how rough he's treating
the zombies here right now.
You think he'll take care of Jonathan?
PERHAPS JONATHAN
MIGHT GET TREATED LIKE THIS TOO
How are we gonna take care of him?
Tie his arms and legs up?
We can't communicate with him.
Don't you think
that'll be even harder on him?
That'd be even more painful.
Then it clearly comes down to one thing.
Do we put ourselves in danger or not?
It's certain that we put ourselves
in danger if we take him.
And we don't if we leave him here.
If I'm considering how Patricia feels,
I wanna bring him.
But… it's true that leaving him
would be better for the group.
-Tsuki, what if this were your family?
-Yeah?
If this happened to your family
in Japan, would you leave them behind?
HARD TO REFUTE "YOUR FAMILY"
We don't know what happened
-to our own families.
-We don't know what happened
to our own families either.
Patricia, can you leave
your brother behind?
It's certain
that we put ourselves in danger
-if we take him.
-I think that'd be
-even more painful.
-And it'd be better
-for Jonathan too… to stay here.
-I'd leave him behind.
You can't communicate with him at all
in that state.
Patricia?
I agree.
DID I HEAR THAT RIGHT?
What on earth? Seriously.
But I, but I…
I think, I think…
You are one truly heartless woman.
I think
Jonathan's hearing is still intact.
He keeps yelling
when Patricia says
she'll leave him behind.
-Right?
-Are you two really even siblings?
BLOOD IS THINNER THAN WATER…
You're supposed to say
we should leave him behind
but you'll stay with him.
-Really?
-I mean,
-it might be a cultural difference.
-No, I…
I think it's a cultural difference.
When I think about what's best
for the group, we should leave.
Ro Hong-chul!
-Oh, dang.
-Who knows?
Maybe he wants us to leave him.
No, we can't leave him behind.
There's something left in him.
-Right.
-Okay.
Show of hands. Leave him or take him.
Who votes to leave him?
LET'S LEAVE HIM
HONG-CHUL, DEX, AND DINDIN
Who wants to take him?
LET'S BRING HIM
SI-YOUNG, PATRICIA, AND NA-RAE
ABSTAINED
KKWACHU HYUNG AND TSUKI
TIED AT 3 TO 3
THEY COULDN'T DECIDE
Let's be objective about this.
What if we take Jonathan…
and then Na-rae and Kkwachu
turn into zombies too?
It won't be easy.
Then we'd have three zombies.
If you two turn into zombies tomorrow,
our fears could become a reality.
Jonathan was sleeping too when he…
I think this is…
so… so hypocritical.
So if someone else here becomes a zombie,
you'll abandon them too?
We're not abandoning.
We'll just go our separate ways.
We'd be going separate ways, yeah.
If we can work together like we can now,
we'd take him with us.
But we can't communicate
with Jonathan like that.
You'll abandon us
if we can't communicate with you.
No, it's not abandoning.
What will you do
if you can't communicate with me?
I'd bring you with me.
How?
You can't even use your arms right now.
So if someone here becomes a zombie,
you'll abandon them too?
-How am I…
-Even if it's you?
-Even if it's me, of course.
-I'll stay with you. I will.
But I can understand
where he's coming from.
Hmm.
-Oh, oh, it's Mr. Kim.
-What? What?
I got it.
-Got what?
-I have the, uh…
coordinates for a boat
that will let you move around safely.
-What?
-There's a boat? A boat?
AN UNEXPECTED GAMECHANGER
HAS BEEN INTRODUCED
Oh, there is a boat.
He got the coordinates.
It leaves in two hours.
-Two hours from now?
-Yeah.
We have to get there
before the boat leaves
no matter what if we wanna take it.
We should get going right now.
-Yeah, I think we really have to hurry.
-So, to go…
There might be
other normal people like us
who got these coordinates.
We could team up with them too.
So we'll need to team up with them,
but if we have Jonathan with us…
I'm suddenly worried…
that with Jonathan there,
Na-rae and Kkwachu
might not be able to board either.
I'm really worried.
I just thought of that.
If it's just us,
they can pretend to be humans,
but they'd stand out with Jonathan there.
Noona, think about it.
We can't pass you two off as humans
if we take Jonathan.
We have to go now.
I say we should do as Patricia says.
Okay, Patricia.
You make the final decision.
If we go get on that boat right now,
we can go.
But if we take Jonathan,
we can't board.
We'll do as you say.
-To be really… objective.
-It's your family.
WHAT?????
Wait.
Okay, we can go. We got the answer.
THE WORD "OBJECTIVE" SAID IT ALL
-Let's go.
-Let's go then.
-His family abandoned him.
-No, that's not what this is.
What can we do?
His family is leaving him behind.
-We're not abandoning him.
-Jonathan!
His family chose a new family.
There's nothing you could do about it.
-That's the reality. Yeah.
-Oppa!
Oppa, I'm sorry.
HER EXPRESSION AND WORDS
DO NOT MATCH
-Oppa, I'm sorry.
-…for real. I tried, really.
-Let's go, we have to go.
-We'll take the coordinates.
-We only have two hours.
-Hey, let's go. It's okay.
-You can depend on me.
-Hurry up,
-it leaves in two hours. Come on.
-Oppa, I'm sorry.
-Oppa.
-Huh?
We won't be able
to get on the boat anyway.
We can't.
53 HOURS SINCE THE ZOMBIE OUTBREAK
ONE DEAD
ONE DEAD AND ABANDONED
EIGHT ESCAPED
2:10 A.M.
WOLMIDO, INCHEON
Dex, are we at the right coordinates?
-It is. It's here.
-It is!
-We made it.
-We're here!
Okay. Let's go, let's go.
-We made it!
-Hey, wait for us, humans!
-The living's got to live!
-We made it! Wait for us!
Over here. This is the location
based on the coordinates.
We made it!
-Wait.
-The boat?
Where's the boat?
It's not here.
But we made it in time, right?
-Yeah, we did. We're on time.
-We're at the right location.
-What's that?
-Huh?
Is it that boat over there?
Wait.
Did it leave already?
I think it left.
That small boat there.
-Oh, no!
-Dang it! Seriously?
Over here!
-Over here!
-There are people here!
-Wait!
-Oh, no!
-No, no!
-Seriously.
-You have to take us with you.
-What's going on?
-There are people here!
-No!
Take us with you!
This is
because we were hesitating back there!
If we were just 10 minutes earlier,
we could have boarded.
If we just made our decision
-about Jonathan--
-Back there, dang it!
Stop talking about Jonathan.
-Dang it!
-You're a jerk.
If we got here just a little faster,
we could've taken that boat.
We can see it right there! Dang it!
Are we going to die?
It would have saved the humans.
-It would have saved the humans.
-You're a horrible person!
But back at the house,
Mr. Kim said there were two boats.
-Tomorrow morning? Okay.
-There was another one
five hours later.
-Seriously.
-Then we can take the next one.
The next one.
Where can we go in and wait?
-How about over there?
-Where?
Hey, the Ferris wheel.
The Ferris wheel!
-Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-I'm going. Let's go.
Whoever's left living should live!
It's so cold. Come on!
Wow.
Let's go in here and wait,
just five hours.
THEME PARK AT THE END OF THE WORLD
5-HOUR UNLIMITED RIDE PASS
They've arrived at a new place.
Be careful. Just in case.
I think these places are actually safer.
But it's too quiet.
The Ferris wheel is up there.
So let's go up first.
Let's get to someplace high, oppa.
I really can't see a thing.
-Slow down.
-Slower.
-Okay.
-Crap.
Here, here. We're here.
-You can see everything from here.
-Whoa.
Wow.
It seems like there's really no one here.
I know. This is great.
The pods of the Ferris wheel
are up in the air.
Up there,
we'll be safe for five hours.
But nothing's running.
All the machines are off.
Even if we hide,
we can't do anything if zombies come.
Is there any way
we can turn the lights on just here?
Let's follow this wire
and see where it goes.
The light wires here.
-You're right.
This way?
I think it connects over this way.
It's a bit scary
-since it's so dark.
-I think this is it.
Is this it?
It looks like a big power box.
How do we work this?
Oh!
Wow.
-The lights are on.
-Yeah.
-So cool. Huh? It's moving!
-Cool.
We can go up that way.
The lights. It's so pretty!
Wow. We're safe now. Wow.
Wow. It's so pretty.
Are you sure this is okay? It's so bright.
It's gorgeous!
-Huh?
-Whoa!
It's a theme park!
-Wait, there are zombies!
-Huh?
There are zombies! Zombies!
There are zombies all over here too.
Oh, no.
Crap.
That's the most zombies
we've seen so far.
But there wasn't anyone here earlier.
Quiet down.
Don't make a sound.
There are too many.
That's a lot of zombies. Over here!
Hey, hey, don't call out to them.
Don't do that.
-Unni, what's wrong with you?
-What are you doing?
-There's something wrong with Na-rae.
-What, what?
-No, no, no.
-She waved at the zombies.
No, she was just teasing them.
It was a joke.
Hey, hey, get it together. Come on.
-Oppa, I feel nauseous.
-Oh, jeez.
Everyone that was here
must have been bitten.
They must have come out
because of the lights.
I mean…
We wouldn't have ever known
if we hadn't turned the lights on.
ZOMBIES POURED OUT IN RESPONSE
TO THE LIGHTS AND SOUNDS OF THE RIDES
Wait, I think there's someone there.
-Hey, there are people! Humans!
-Over there.
-Hey!
-There's someone.
How did they manage to stay there?
THERE ARE SURVIVORS
ALL THROUGHOUT THE THEME PARK
Shouldn't we help them?
We have weapons at least.
-There are too many zombies. Look.
-What do we do?
How do we get past them?
We learned how. We have guns too.
There's a kid.
We have to rescue them.
Then first, only the people who are okay…
-Huh? Us?
-…should go down
and try to figure out a route.
-What about us? We don't go?
-What about us?
You stay here and give us moral support.
-You can't abandon us.
-Just… just wait a little.
-We've always offered support.
-You can't abandon us.
-I-I mean…
-See you later.
Shoot, look at all the zombies.
All the zombies here are young.
Because they're all visitors of the park.
-Right.
-Yeah.
Let's hide here behind the guns.
-Let's hide.
-Here?
I'm scared, okay?
Ah, there are gloves here.
Okay, okay. Let's put them on.
So there are people
at the Disco Pang Pang,
the merry-go-round, and the bumper cars.
There is a little kid at tagada too.
I don't think we should move in one group.
Let's split up.
-Small groups.
-Wait. Two, four, six.
-Let's... let's pair up.
-Two, two, two. Three teams.
The ones going to the places with a lot
of zombies... should take the weapons.
Oh, gosh, they're coming,
they're coming, they're coming
But I don't think
you need weapons for the tagada.
But you can shoot at the zombies
on the merry-go-round.
THEY'RE PERFECT TARGETS
FOR SHOOTING PRACTICE
Stop it!
Someone with good aim should go
where you can use a gun.
-So Tsuki or Si-young should go.
-I can't shoot at all.
-I'll go.
-You saw it yesterday.
Then Si-young will go
to the merry-go-round.
Si-young practiced with me yesterday, so…
-Okay, I'll go with Dex.
-I'll go rescue the kid.
Dex, Dex, you're really going
to the merry-go-round?
Well, Si-young's going.
We trained together yesterday, so…
-Really?
-Yeah.
-What about you?
-I…
What are you thinking this time?
Well…
Come on. Just a little more.
A little more, a little more!
HE WANTS TO KEEP DEX FOR HIMSELF
-No, no.
-You've got this look in your eyes.
I'm just worried that if I go with him,
he'll abandon me.
-I can't trust Hong-chul.
-I can't trust him either.
-I'd rather go to the tagada.
-Then let's go together, oppa.
-Have you ever been on a tagada?
-No.
Have you ever been on a tagada?
Do you think
you're going there to ride the thing?
-But Tsuki is a good dancer.
-Yeah, that one.
What does that have to do with this?
You dance on a tagada.
A zombie's coming. Crap.
DAY 3…
EVEN THE LEADER IS LOSING HIS MIND
-What's wrong with Dex? Seriously?
-Isn't Dex kind of funny?
HE EVEN PLAYS WHACK-A-MOLE
Oh, hey. Duck, duck, duck.
Oh, jeez.
Should we not go?
THE FATE OF THE SURVIVORS
DEPENDS ON THE LIKES OF THEM
Hey then, let's do this.
Patricia and I will go to the bumper cars.
You two go to the merry-go-round.
MERRY-GO-ROUND TEAM: SI-YOUNG AND DEX
Tsuki and DinDin will go to the tagada
since they're quick on their feet.
Then let's rescue
the survivors and regroup.
-See you later.
-Let's meet again alive.
-What? What is it?
-What's wrong with him?
-He must be infected.
-Why are you coming from there?
There are so many zombies over there.
HE'S BEEN CRAWLING
FOR THE PAST 3 DAYS
Seriously.
Huh? Why aren't these guys moving?
Their heads aren't cut off though.
Are they all asleep?
THEY SEE A FRIGHTENED STUDENT
IN THE FURTHEST CORNER
-Over there.
-There she is.
IT'S A YOUNG STUDENT…
THEY NATURALLY WANT TO RESCUE HER!
Stay there.
-Hey, look.
-Are they dead?
"An electric current
flows through the floor
when the ride is going. Do not enter!"
Jeez, a current must run
through the floor.
I think we have to ride one of the cars
to get there.
They can't step on the floor,
it has an electric current.
They must ride a bumper car
and save the survivor inside.
If they want to stay alive,
they must not wake the sleeping zombies.
Hey, which one of us should go?
It's too small for the both of us to go.
You're young, you like theme parks.
So you go.
Me?
Let's make it fair.
We'll distract her, then one person
goes over there to stack something.
-Okay.
-Do you wanna go there first?
Sure. Okay, oppa.
I mean, you normally shouldn't make
the other person go first, right?
-Should I go first? You can do it.
-You go first, oppa.
THIS ISN'T DÉJÀ VU
You want me to go?
-Then let's make a plan.
-Where should I go?
-I'll take this and go there.
-Okay.
You make way
so I can get there and back in one go.
Yeah, I'm doing all the dangerous work.
I don't think so.
No, no. You make the way
and I'll take all the risk and rescue her.
-We have great teamwork.
-Oppa, I trust you.
-Oppa, I have faith in you.
-Just push that, okay?
HE HAS NO INTENTION
OF LISTENING TO HER
Careful, careful.
This is nothing.
Careful. Be careful, oppa.
Watch what you're doing!
OH, NO! HIS GROIN IS SPLITTING
Oppa, be careful!
Easy does it.
Hey, I think you should do it.
What... What?
Oh, gosh.
Me? Just try going.
The quest begins.
RESCUE THE STUDENT!
WHILE THE ZOMBIES ARE SLEEPING
HE NEEDS TO BE PARTICULARLY CAREFUL
NOT TO WAKE ANY OF THE ZOMBIES
Oh, a dead body!
THE ZOMBIES AREN'T MOVING AT ALL SO FAR
Patricia, I think it's safe.
You should come too.
They're not moving.
Wait right there.
What do I do? Oppa?
Oh, wait.
Come here.
Come this way. You can step on that.
A COLLISION OCCURS!!
Hey, hey, oppa!
-Oh, gosh.
-What's wrong with this?
-Hey, why is it doing this?
-Oppa!
What's wrong with it?
Seriously, oppa.
THE ZOMBIE, SENSITIVE TO VIBRATIONS,
SUDDENLY REACTS
-Oppa!
-Hey, here, this way!
Hold on. What's wrong with this?
Oh, no, this isn't working.
Oppa, oppa, oppa, oppa!
Kid, kid! Come here! Kid!
ALL THE ZOMBIES ARE AWAKE NOW!
Kid! Kid!
What do we do?
I don't think this will work!
HE ABANDONS THE STUDENT AND FLEES
What are you gonna do?
What am I supposed to do?
Get away!
Get away! Get back, you!
Get away! Get away!
Hang tight, I'm coming!
Be quiet.
THANKS TO PATRICIA, THE PATH IS CLEAR!
Oppa, go!
Yes, get her.
Come here, come here.
Oppa, oppa, oppa!
THEY SUCCESSFULLY GET
THE SURVIVOR
I'll lure them away. I'll lure them.
Hey! Come at me.
Come at me!
HE MUST'VE BEEN A GOOD DRIVER
WHEN HE WAS ALIVE
Come on.
Oppa!
Oh, gosh.
Oppa, follow me.
Oppa!
THIS TIME, HONG-CHUL IS IN TROUBLE
Oppa, wait.
Oppa!
Okay, wait for me.
Don't you dare. Hey!
Oppa, wait. I'll save you!
Wait!
SHE MIGHT DIE FIRST?!
Wait.
Dang it. Whatever. Let's go!
Go straight! Hey!
What? Huh?
Hey, stop it! Oh, no!
Oh, gosh.
Get away! Get away!
Oh, gosh!
Oppa, you can go now!
Oppa, go! Go!
Patricia!
Oh, gosh!
THANKS TO PATRICIA,
HONG-CHUL AND THE SURVIVOR ESCAPE
Patricia!
SHE HAD JUST BEGUN DRIVER'S ED
Oppa!
You made it.
To the right, Patricia. You made it!
Oppa!
You made it.
Good job. You did great.
THEY MADE IT OUT
OF THE HELLISH COURSE SAFELY
Patricia.
You did great!
The quest is complete.
QUEST COMPLETE
RESCUE THE STUDENT!
-Oh, zombies.
-Huh?
There. Zombies.
Shouldn't we go down there too?
Can you not see it?
Your sense of humor is back now.
No, you can't see anything like that.
TSK TSK… SHE CAN'T EVEN TELL
THE FRONT FROM THE BACK
Yeah, here. Take it, like this.
Look, there. Yeah. Look.
Wow, that's amazing!
One, two, three, four…
Five…
Let's just enjoy this.
This is our last moment.
We're too weak anyway.
If I knew this would happen,
I would have lived a naughtier life!
Naughtier?
Don't you think
it's plenty naughty already?
45 HOURS AFTER GETTING INFECTED,
THEY SENSE THE END IS NEARING
I struggled my way out of Mokpo
and came to Seoul,
and saved up all my money
while everyone said I worked too hard.
But now, I'm gonna die single.
I only told a lot of dirty stories,
I hadn't dated that many guys.
THAT'S TMI!
Jeez, this sucks.
WHILE THE HALF-ZOMBIES
CONTINUE TO GRUMBLE
DINDIN AND TSUKI APPROACH
THEIR MISSION LOCATION
We have to open that gate
and get those people out.
Okay.
What are you doing?
-Can you open the gate?
-Open it, please.
There are people in there.
Open the gate.
-Are you a zombie?
-No, no.
-I'm the DJ. The DJ.
-Neither are we.
-Open the gate. Come on.
-Open the gate.
Can you hurry?
There are people in there.
Oh, no.
Are you okay?
-We have to go. Come on.
-Let's go.
-Are you okay? Were you bitten?
-We have to go.
-We didn't get bitten.
-Go on. Go!
Thank you.
-Oh, no.
-Hurry. Let's get out of here.
-Shoot.
THE HUMANS LEFT AND ZOMBIES RUSHED IN
THE DJ COULDN'T ESCAPE IN THE END…
-Are you okay?
-Hey.
-It's gone.
-What's gone?
-What do we do?
What is it?
My sister has asthma,
so she needs her medicine.
-We must have dropped it back there.
-It's gone.
The inhaler?
-Yeah.
-Crap.
-The thing you breathe in?
-You can't go without it?
-She can't.
-How old are you?
-I'm 26. Yes.
-You're 26?
NOT A CHILD,
JUST SOMEONE WHO LOOKS VERY YOUNG
What does that have to do with this?
Jeez, why did you ride that
with your pouch open? You're 26.
NO MERCY FOR AN ADULT
It's okay. She's cute.
Let's go get Kkwachu Hyung first.
-Okay. Should I go?
-Kkwachu Hyung is a half-zombie
-and a doctor, so let's get him.
-I'll go get him then.
You shouldn't sleep like that,
it's too cold. Na-rae.
You have to keep flipping over.
-Okay.
-So you don't freeze.
Yes, flip over.
There you go.
Man, you're smart.
WE SHOULD JUST LAY HER
TO REST IN PEACE…
-Doctor, doctor!
-Wait.
We were just having fun flipping her.
What is it? What?
No, really.
-We have a favor to ask. A real one.
-What favor?
You remember
there was a kid back there, right?
The kid, okay.
She… You know, the illness
where you breathe like that.
-The illness where your heart beats.
-"Heartbeat"?
SHE'S HAVING TROUBLE
COMMUNICATING WITH THE DOCTOR
She has asthma.
-"With asthma"?
Is Asthma her friend?
There must be
someone named Asthma, right?
Miss Asthma!
So? Go on.
-She has asthma.
-She has asthma and…
-You have to come.
-Okay.
-Please.
-He has to go.
ALTHOUGH HALF-ZOMBIE,
HE STILL UPHOLDS THE HIPPOCRATIC OATH
-Okay, hurry.
-After you.
I'm freezing.
-Oh, gosh. Hi.
-Kkwachu Hyung.
-He's not a zombie.
-Hello. Hi.
-I'm still a doctor.
-I see.
To be honest,
the cold air could aggravate it.
She could be in danger
if she doesn't use the inhaler soon.
She could actually die.
There's no alternative treatment for this.
THERE'S NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO BACK AND FIND IT
Then they can stay here for now.
And since we know the ride,
you should come with us.
-Go with you? There? Oh, okay. Yeah.
-Yeah, we have to save the kid.
-Thank you.
-Let's go.
-Just hang tight.
-Good luck.
Let's do this.
-Hi. Open the gate, please.
-Yeah, open the gate.
She left her inhaler.
She has asthma.
HOW IS THE DJ STILL ALIVE
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED???
10 MINUTES AGO
THE TAGADA WAS FULL OF ZOMBIES
Just hang tight.
I'll spin you around in no time.
No, the two of you,
don't roll around together.
There you go.
All you zombies are gonna fall down.
HE DOESN'T DISCRIMINATE
AND SHOWS THEM A GOOD WOLMIDO TIME
Almost all of you are passed out now.
Now don't ever come back.
THE DJ IS ALMIGHTY
WHEN YOU'RE RIDING THE TAGADA…
They're all kind of passed out
right now, so we need to find it fast.
-Crap.
-They're alive.
We're screwed.
Oh, wait. I'm a half-zombie.
They won't bite me.
Yeah, they won't bite you. They won't.
-So I can stay here.
-Oh, no!
-I mean…
-It's Yoo Hee-kwan!
-Oppa!
If I get bitten,
I'll come get you as a zombie.
Zombie food. Total zombie food.
EVEN AFTER BECOMING A ZOMBIE
HE DIDN'T FORGET HIS PROMISE
THE PITCHER WITH 100 WINS
-Oppa!
-They won't bite you. You go.
I…
Hi. No, no, no, no.
I'm still scared. Wait. I…
-Oh, no!
-Hey, spin it.
Spin it! Spin it! Spin it! Spin it!
THEY DESPERATELY NEED
THE DJ'S HELP IN THIS QUEST
The quest begins.
FIND THE INHALER
YOO HEE-KWAN'S DISCO FEVER
-No, Yoo Hee-kwan!
-Hey.
Hey. DinDin.
Don't come this way! Not us!
-No!
-He's good.
No.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
-No!
-Oppa!
No!
I can't!
-Hey! What the heck?
-Please.
-It's not over?
-Hey, wait.
Hyung, block him!
Stop Yoo Hee-kwan!
ZOMBIE HEE-KWAN DOESN'T FALL
Why won't this zombie fall? Why? Why? Why?
ONLY THE INNOCENT HALF-ZOMBIE
ROLLS AROUND
THIS IS THE BALANCE OF A PRO ATHLETE
Is he a tagada master?
Get him! Get Yoo Hee-kwan!
HE'S ABOUT TO GET CAUGHT!
Hey!
-No!
-Let go!
Oh, no, you can't pull his pants off.
You're in big trouble.
Let go!
HIS FEEBLE LEGS ALMOST GOT EXPOSED!
-No!
-Yoo Hee-kwan!
Oppa! No!
AS PROMISED,
HE ONLY GOES AFTER DINDIN
HIS REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED
I'm sorry, but…
-No! Oppa, no!
-Are you okay?
I'll spin you around.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oh, no! Oppa!
TSK, TSK…
KKWACHU HYUNG CAN'T GET UP AT ALL
DinDin! No!
I'm a zombie.
I'm a half-zombie. Half-zombie!
AVOIDING HEE-KWAN IS ONE THING,
BUT THEY MUST NOT FORGET THE INHALER
Hurry up and find the inhaler!
That body! That one.
That one.
Hurry up and find it! Hurry!
It's not easy in there.
You're doing great.
-You two over there…
-Found it!
You're looking too comfortable.
You're coming back.
THEY JUST NEED TO ESCAPE NOW!
I found it!
By the way, why did you get on here?
Huh? I think they're all done for now.
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED AFTER 2 MINUTES…
Yeah, I think we're good.
Yeah, okay. Just a minute.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS OVER?
NO WAY!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
WITH AN IRON WILL,
HE GOES AFTER DINDIN AGAIN
-No!
-Oppa! Oppa, no!
Yoo Hee-kwan!
You're all really something, man.
-Yoo Hee-kwan!
-No!
HE'S NEARING THE END OF HIS LIMIT
There! A zombie there.
No!
-No, no, no!
I'll get rid of these zombies,
and open the gate.
IN THE END,
HEE-KWAN COULDN'T KEEP HIS PROMISE
Get out that way now! Hurry, hurry.
Come on. And rescue me too.
Don't just run away on your own.
It feels weird to be back on the ground.
-Hey, save me too. Come on.
-Run, run, run!
Jeez, Yoo Hee-kwan.
Quest complete.
QUEST COMPLETE
FIND THE INHALER
-Babe.
-Please.
Please help me.
Babe!
Oh, what's that?
Hey!
THEY FIND A SURVIVOR
ON THE MERRY-GO-ROUND
Please help us.
My girlfriend is stuck over there.
-Your girlfriend?
-Yeah.
The girl over there
-with the blonde hair?
-Yeah.
HE MADE IT OUT BUT LEFT HER BEHIND
She's Russian.
-Why did you escape by yourself?
-There are too many zombies.
HE ESCAPED WITHOUT HIS GIRLFRIEND…
DEX CAN'T COMPREHEND THIS
Please don't. Go away!
Come on. Help her.
What do you mean? You should rescue her.
-You're being ridiculous.
-Wait. No, no.
Come over here for now.
-Hey, come on. Follow us.
-Let's go as far as we can.
KOREA IS A SAFE COUNTRY!
WE CAN'T LET A FOREIGNER DIE!
Help! I need help!
There are too many on there,
so I don't think we can get on.
FIVE ZOMBIES
ARE SURROUNDING THE SURVIVOR
I think there are more than ten.
THE ZOMBIES ON THE CAROUSEL
ARE BUCKLED IN AND CAN'T SEEM TO MOVE
Can you help me?
Babe!
-Be quiet. Shush.
-Okay, okay.
You see the one next to her
in the school uniform?
-Yeah.
-Him and him.
IF THEY CAN GET RID OF THE THREE
ON THE RIGHT WITH THE POTATO GUN
-Yeah.
-If we can take out
just those zombies…
IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY CAN SECURE AN ESCAPE PATH!
How many potatoes do we have?
We only have ten potatoes.
-Let's see--
-Come on! Do something!
-Be quiet. What's wrong with you?
-Stop telling us to hurry up, man.
-You're the one who should have saved her.
-I mean…
Wait, wait.
The survivor
has been surrounded by zombies
because they turned the lights on.
They have only ten shots.
And there are three zombies to take out.
Come on! Do something!
If they fail,
the boyfriend won't let it slide.
-The quest begins.
-I've never shot at a moving target.
Aim carefully.
We don't have a lot of chances.
IT'S DIFFERENT FROM LAST NIGHT
WHEN THEY WERE HAVING FUN
AND CHEERING
Whoa!
IT'S HER FIRST TIME SHOOTING
REAL ZOMBIES INSTEAD OF MANNEQUINS!
-I'm nervous.
-Hurry!
-I know.
-This might be loud.
-Okay.
-What's your girlfriend's name?
-Tina. Yeah.
-Tina?
What's your name?
My name is I-su.
-I-su? I-su and Tina.
-Yeah.
YOU MUST MEMORIZE PEOPLE'S NAMES
TO BECOME A HERO
-I promise, I'll save Tina.
-Please.
-Is it in?
-Babe?
-Quiet. Be quiet.
-But you have to be quiet.
I'll give it a shot.
Huh?
Help me!
I said, help!
Oh, you almost hit Tina. Jeez.
-Wait.
-What are you doing?
OOPS! SHE ALMOST RUINED EVERYTHING
RIGHT FROM THE GET-GO
I'm too scared.
I didn't even think that I might hit Tina.
You have to save her no matter what!
THEY HADN'T CONSIDERED
THAT THEY COULD HIT TINA!
-Si-young, you can do this. You have to.
-Dang it.
You can do it, you can do it.
THAT WAS CLOSE!
You almost got it.
You have to concentrate. Come on!
-Are you kidding me right now?
-Seriously.
Do you wanna get beaten up with a broom?
Hurry up.
-What's with him?
-I know.
-Help me!
-What's with him?
-Babe!
-I told you to be quiet!
She keeps calling for me.
HE'S VERY ANNOYING FOR SOMEONE
WHO'S ASKING FOR A FAVOR…
Help me!
Oh!
-A headshot.
-You got him!
That was excellent.
-I got him! Wait.
-Noona,
-you got the zombie right in the face.
-Yes!
Look.
-I can't believe that worked. It worked!
-Did you see that, huh?
THE BOYFRIEND SEEMS TO HAVE
TERRIBLE MOOD SWINGS
I told you to wait. Come on.
I-su, you're too impatient. Jeez.
We got one.
So you need to get the one on the left.
Okay. Seong-jin…
-Seong-jin…
-Yeah?
-No, I-su.
-I-su.
-Right, I-su.
-I-su. Right.
Who's Seong-jin, noona?
Oh!
Did you just hit Tina?
SHE CAN'T LOOK UP
DUE TO EMBARRASSMENT
She's alive. There.
Look, she's moving around just fine.
That one did graze Tina's head a bit.
I know.
But she's not my girlfriend, so…
NOT A GOOD IDEA
TO PROVOKE THE BOYFRIEND
Oh!
IT FLEW RIGHT ABOVE HER HEAD
You nearly hit me!
You nearly hit Tina! Come on!
HONESTLY, SHE HAS NOTHING
TO SAY FOR HERSELF THIS TIME
What are you trying to pull here?
Get out of the way.
I'll fire the gun. I will.
Hurry up and put the potato in.
-Shove that potato in there.
-I don't wanna do this anymore.
Babe, just a minute! Hang tight!
I'll come save you!
-Stop laughing.
-Noona, you almost killed Tina.
-Hurry up!
-Hurry up. What are you doing?
-Hey, man, come on.
-Seriously.
THEY'D LIKE TO JUST SHOOT HIM FIRST
-Be quiet. Shush.
-Hey, do you think this is easy?
I spent so much time hitting on her
in the last two weeks.
-Where did you two meet?
-At a singles bar.
HE'S HESITATING TO HELP HIM…
Come on, shoot them!
ONLY FOUR POTATOES LEFT
Oh!
-I got a feel for it now. I got it.
-You got it? You got it?
SHE WAS ZEROING IN UNTIL NOW!
SI-YOUNG'S GOT THE HANG OF IT
-My Tina's scared.
-Get away from me.
I'm gonna hit it this time.
-Here I go.
-Okay.
You got it!
-Okay!
-You got it!
-You got it.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-You got it!
-Two down.
Hurry! Put another one in!
Get another one. Get them!
HER NEXT TARGET MIGHT BE THE BOYFRIEND
What's with him? Seriously.
You killed another one.
Did you see that?
-She never misses a shot.
-Hurry.
You got them.
PERHAPS THANKS TO THE WHINING,
SHE NEATLY TOOK DOWN THE ZOMBIES
NOW THEY CAN RESCUE TINA!
-Are you sure they're passed out?
-I think so.
Hurry! Go get her.
Babe.
-You're here.
-Babe, hurry! Come here.
Hurry, hurry.
I did it, I did it, I did it.
You're the best.
THEY DEFINITELY
SHOULD'VE JUST SHOT HIM…
You've got to be kidding me.
-Thank you.
-What's wrong with that guy?
-Huh? Wait.
-Crap! This way! Come on!
-Zombies.
-Hey.
Crap, zombies.
THEY ENCOUNTER ZOMBIES
BEFORE THEY COULD BE THANKED!
Wait for us! Wait for us!
Get off, you!
-Dang it.
-Wait, huh?
THEY FLEE TO A TRAMPOLINE
OUT OF ALL PLACES
THERE'S NO WAY OUT!
HUH? THE ZOMBIES CAN'T HANDLE IT
Bouncing zombies!
Bounce the zombies!
Dex!
-What's wrong with them?
-What do we do?
They're rolling around.
TERRIBLE BALANCE!
THEY FIGURED OUT
THE ZOMBIES' WEAKNESS
Roll around some more. Here.
Roll. Roll around.
Roll around.
I'm getting tired.
THIS ZOMBIE SEEMS A BIT DIFFERENT
Oh, come on!
Wait for me!
They're totally out of it.
THE ZOMBIE WITH GREAT BALANCE
KEEPS FOLLOWING THEM
Hey!
HE'D EVEN QUALIFY
100!
He's scaring me.
-Here. This way.
-Dex.
-Let's go, noona. Up you go.
-Jump.
LUCKY! THEY FOUND THE ONLY EXIT
Oh, come on.
Get away! Get away!
Get lost! Jeez.
Let me catch my breath. Oh.
They almost got me.
Quest complete.
Which way do we have to go? That way?
There?
-I can't even really see now.
-I can't see well either.
-Who is that?
-It's me.
-You're not a zombie, right?
-You were gonna hit me, weren't you?
What now?
I think we better do something. Anything.
-The other guys are working hard.
-Yeah.
But what can a half-zombie do?
-Then…
-Let's do something too.
-Let's clear the place for them.
-How?
How do you think?
We'll gather them up.
THE ZOMBIES GATHER AROUND
THE NOSTALGIC SOUND OF THE VUVUZELA
Zombies! What?
Stop, stop. Wait. Hold on.
This is him, right? Hee-kwan.
Poor guy. I'm sorry.
We should have moved your body at least.
-Oh, I'm so sorry. Hey…
-Whoa, Hee-kwan. I'm sorry.
…since we gathered them all here,
should we take them somewhere?
-Come this way.
-Let's go up.
The stairs are narrow.
Two at a time.
Okay, okay.
Use the right side of the stairs too.
Gosh, your joints don't bend
that much, right? I know how that feels.
You need to keep using them
to make them stronger.
Be careful.
Wow, we've gathered
a lot more than we thought, right?
-I know.
-I think we have
almost all the zombies here.
Hee-kwan, you're doing a great job
following us.
Be careful when you come up.
This way. Come on.
Sit in the back if you're a thrill-seeker.
Sit in the middle if you're a chicken.
Oh, gosh, Hee-kwan.
Oh, my goodness.
The P.E. majors are here too. Oh, really?
Let's all take a picture
since we're at a theme park.
Say "zombie" on three.
One, two, three. Zombie!
-Great. Of course they do.
-They love it.
TA-DA! THE SAFETY BARS LOWER
AND RESTRAIN THEM
NOW THEY CAN'T MOVE AT ALL
Okay, here we go.
All right. You all have fun!
Wave when you go up.
Oh, okay. Here we go. Great!
Now the other side.
They know how to enjoy the ride.
Wee! Both hands in the air.
Wave. Wave your hands!
Wave your hands.
That's great.
Wave your hands!
HE'S SLOWLY STARTING TO FEEL IT!
THEY REACH A 90-DEGREE INCLINE!
Dang it.
Crap.
Wait, I heard…
THEY'RE JUST HEARING THINGS
WOLMIDO'S SCARY VIKING SHIP
MAKES THEM WET THEIR PANTS
I'm so sorry.
-One more time.
-One more time?
They're loving it
-right now. Yeah.
-They love it, don't they?
-Okay.
-Have a fun trip. Bye.
Let's go!
It's a bye-viking. Bye-bye.
3 HOURS LEFT
UNTIL THE RESCUE BOAT ARRIVES
The Ferris wheel.
Hey, let's go.
Anywhere, let's just go.
We're done now.
I'm too tired to even blow on this now.
Kkwachu, Na-rae… What the heck?
What?
What's wrong?
-Are you okay?
-Oh, you scared me!
We're not dead yet.
-We're not dead yet.
-Are you okay?
-We were having fun.
-What?
-Na-rae,
-open your eyes. Come on.
-Why's Hee-kwan here?
We dozed off. Hey, wake up.
-Their eyes are redder.
-Their eyes are so red now.
Na-rae, are you okay?
She just dozed off.
She's okay.
Hey, who's that? He's human, right?
-What the heck?
-Who is it there, huh?
-In the control room.
-What?
-Go check it out.
-Is he a zombie?
Who is it?
-Oh!
-That startled me.
-Are you human?
-Look closer.
-Is he human?
-I'm an employee here.
-Are you okay?
-Oh, he's fine.
-Oh, no. You're shivering.
So, we can take a boat
in just three hours.
Come with us.
-Please take me with you.
-Okay, okay, I promise.
-It's so cold.
-How do you get on this thing?
Noona, what's with you?
I'm freezing.
-What are you, an electric eel?
-I'm freezing.
-Oh Dex, I'm so cold.
-You're cold?
What is this?
-It's a walkie-talkie.
-Can we borrow these
-so we can communicate?
-Set it to channel one.
Once you get on the Ferris wheel…
-Okay?
-…you can't open the door from the inside.
You can't get out
unless someone on the outside
opens the door for you. Do you understand?
Hang tight here for three hours,
then open the door for us.
-Since you have to open for us…
-Then I'll stay and hide.
-Yeah, stay hidden.
-Okay.
How many pods can we get on right now?
There are about five you can use.
Put these two in first.
They've been a little contaminated.
Don't say they're contaminated.
-No, they've been exposed. Yeah, exposed.
-"Contaminated"?
-Hong-chul.
-Get in first.
-Come on. The door is open.
-Get in, hyung.
Let's go in and look.
Get in already before the door closes.
Jeez. My goodness.
Oppa?
Huh?
I think we're gonna die soon.
No, we've held on this far.
Oh, gosh. I'm so thirsty.
Hey, why are you up there?
-We're gonna get on.
-Well, we need to get on too.
Tsuki, let's take this one.
-Go. Get on first.
-Get in. Come on. Get in.
-See you in three hours.
-Wait. Okay.
Yeah, wow. We made it.
-Hey, Patricia. Yeah!
-Wow! Wow!
We made it!
Hang in there for three hours
and we'll be safe. We can do it!
We're safe.
We're safe now.
We're safe now! Look.
-There's no way they can get us up here.
-We can do it. Look.
Look to your right. See the ocean.
In three hours, we'll be there.
-We made it.
-We just have to make it
on the water,
the zombies can't swim, right?
Tomorrow,
we'll escape to the ocean.
-It's so pretty.
-Tomorrow!
Hang in there for three hours
and we'll be safe. We can do it!
-Yeah! We can do it.
-We can do it!
The last three days have been so rough.
I used to be afraid
of confined spaces like this.
-But now, I'm so happy in here.
-There's nowhere better to be right now.
It feels like I can finally relax a bit.
I just wanna lie down
and sleep in peace.
There were a lot of scary moments.
But I think it was less scary
when we were together.
-I know.
-Yeah.
Wow.
It looks pretty from up high.
It's nice.
Get away from me! Get back!
What's going on?
Unni, back there…
Get away from me!
Oh, no.
-Who is that?
-Sounds like the guy working down there.
Crap! Zombies!
-Did he get bitten?
-Hey,
there's a whole bunch of zombies here!
-The operator got bitten.
-But we can't open the door.
He's not moving at all.
What do we do now?
Who's gonna open the door for us?
Are we going to die?
ZOMBIEVERSE