THIS SURVIVAL GAME TAKES PLACE
IN A ZOMBIE UNIVERSE
THE CAST ACT OF THEIR OWN ACCORD
AND TURN INTO ZOMBIES ONCE BITTEN
PLEASE BE ADVISED
OF THEIR IMMERSION IN THE GAME
52 HOURS AGO
ZOMBIE OUTBREAK OCCURS
(5 SURVIVORS)
47 HOURS AGO
5 PEOPLE JOIN THEM
(10 SURVIVORS)
43 HOURS AGO
YOO HEE-KWAN DIES
(9 SURVIVORS)
41 HOURS AGO
PARK NAE-RAE AND KKWACHU HYUNG
GET INFECTED
(7 SURVIVORS AND 2 INFECTED)
18 HOURS AGO
JONATHAN GETS INFECTED
(6 SURVIVORS AND 3 INFECTED)
AND
NOW
-This is bad.
-What if that happens to us too?
18 HOURS AFTER GETTING INFECTED,
JONATHAN DIES AND BECOMES A ZOMBIE
Jonathan has died.
What do we do now?
Come out. We need to talk.
What should we do now?
Wow, so you really do turn into a zombie.
What do we do?
-Now eight of us are left?
-What do we do?
-Eight?
-We didn't really think this would happen.
Because Kkwachu Hyung
and Na-rae didn't turn,
we were still having fun learning
about things in the midst of all this.
But now, it really hits home
seeing this happen to Jonathan.
THE REALITY IS THAT THEY CONTINUE TO EXIST
ON THE BORDER BETWEEN LIFE AND DEATH
-Oh, no.
-Gosh, darn it.
In any case,
we're going to leave this place.
And as for Jonathan,
to be honest,
the problem is
whether we can bring him with us.
Then let's all talk about it.
-In order to bring him…
-Don't feel guilty.
You can be honest, okay?
It's okay to say no.
No one will blame you.
THE FIRST TEAMMATE TO BECOME A ZOMBIE
THEY DISCUSS WHAT THEY'LL DO
ABOUT ZOMNATHAN
You go first, Patricia.
-It's her brother. I'm sure she wants to.
-Of course.
-You never know.
-Is that so? What do you think?
Your thoughts matter the most.
-Yes.
-For us to make a decision.
To be honest, I want to bring him.
Yes, that's only right.
-Right.
-As family.
It's not because I'm not infected,
but don't we all feel the same way?
If I get bitten and become like that,
I would rather you guys left me.
-That would be better.
-Honestly, he's already dead.
-We won't be able to move around quickly.
-I agree.
And when you think about it,
it'd be better for Jonathan to stay here.
-Rather than going around,
-You saw earlier.
-it'd be better to stay here.
-With Gyeong-cheol, the cameraman.
-He can train him.
-Mr. Kim can.
I'm also waiting
for a cure to be developed.
I'm keeping him under my protection.
-They might find a cure later.
-Yes.
Leaving Jonathan under his care
isn't the same as totally abandoning him,
so I feel a bit better.
Sure, we can leave Jonathan here.
But how can we blindly trust Mr. Kim?
What if he cuts off his limbs
and conducts experiments?
-Oh, no.
-Then what?
Gosh, don't say that in front of Patricia.
Let's be objective here.
He treats the zombies here horribly.
Do you think he'll take care of Jonathan?
PERHAPS JONATHAN
MIGHT GET TREATED LIKE THIS TOO
But how will we take him?
Tie up his hands and feet with chains?
-He's unable to communicate now.
-It'd be harder on him.
I think it'd be more painful for him.
It's really about this one thing.
Whether it puts us in danger or not.
If we bring him,
we put ourselves in danger.
If we leave him here, we don't.
Putting myself in Patricia's shoes,
I want to bring him.
But the right thing for us to do
is to leave him here.
-Tsuki, what if he was your family?
-Yes?
Would you leave them
if this happened to your family in Japan?
HARD TO REFUTE "YOUR FAMILY"
We don't know what happened
to our own families either.
Patricia, can you leave your brother here?
If we bring him,
we put ourselves in danger.
I think it'd be more painful for him.
It'd be better for Jonathan to stay here.
I would leave him.
He can't communicate with us at all
in his current state.
Patricia, what do you think?
I agree.
DID I HEAR THAT RIGHT?
"REAL FAMILY" MAKES A BOLD DECISION
I just…
The way I see it…
You're really heartless.
The way I see it, I think
Jonathan's hearing still works fine.
When Patricia said she'd leave him,
-he kept screaming.
-Right?
Are you real siblings?
BLOOD IS THINNER THAN WATER…
-You should've said,
-Are you real siblings?
"Leave him here. I'll stay here with him."
Oh, really?
-It could be a cultural difference.
-Right?
I was just saying we should leave him
to ensure our safety.
Ro Hong-chul!
HE'S COMMUNICATING BETTER NOW
THAN HE DID WHEN HE WAS HUMAN
Well, I don't think we can leave him here.
-He's not entirely gone yet.
-Yes.
-She's right.
-Okay.
Let's have a show of hands
for bringing him or not.
Who wants to leave him?
LET'S LEAVE HIM
HONG-CHUL, DEX, AND DINDIN
Who wants to bring him?
LET'S BRING HIM
SI-YOUNG, PATRICIA, AND NA-RAE
ABSTAINED
KKWACHU HYUNG AND TSUKI
TIED AT 3 TO 3
THEY COULDN'T DECIDE
Let's be objective.
Let's say we bring Jonathan.
Then all of a sudden,
Na-rae and Kkwachu turn into zombies too.
That won't be easy.
Then there will be
three zombies against us.
What if the two of you
turn into zombies tomorrow?
Our fears could become a reality.
I feel that you're being
so hypocritical right now.
If another one of us becomes a zombie,
you'll abandon that person too?
It's not abandoning.
Yes, it is.
We're just going separately.
We stay together if we can
work together like we're doing now.
But Jonathan is incapable
of communicating with us.
So you'll abandon us
if we become like that.
I wouldn't say "abandon."
What if I were to become like that?
I'd bring you along.
How would you do that?
You can't even move your arm properly.
Then if any of us turns into a zombie,
you'll abandon that person?
-How will I…
-Even if you're that person?
Yes, of course.
-Mr. Kim is here.
-What's that?
Well, I have it.
Okay.
-Have what?
-You'll be able…
-to safely travel…
-What?
I got the coordinates for a boat.
-There's a boat?
What? A boat?
AN UNEXPECTED GAMECHANGER
HAS BEEN INTRODUCED
Oh, there is one.
The coordinates are here too.
In two hours.
From now?
We must get there
before the boat's departure time.
We should go now. We ought to hurry.
Other people like us could come too
following these coordinates.
Right, we can work together.
We'll need to join forces with them,
but if we have Jonathan…
This worry suddenly came to mind.
Because of Jonathan,
Na-rae and Sung-woo might not
be able to get on the boat either.
It just occurred to me.
If it's just us,
they can just pretend to be human.
But with Jonathan,
he'll draw people's attention.
Think about it, Na-rae.
If we bring Jonathan,
you two can't pretend to be human.
We must leave now.
Let's go with what Patricia wants to do.
Okay, Patricia.
You make the call.
If we go now, we can get on the boat.
But if we bring Jonathan,
they won't let us on.
We'll do as you say.
I'll be realistic here.
WHAT?????
Wait a second.
Okay, we have an answer.
THE WORD "REALISTIC" SAID IT ALL
Let's go.
His family abandoned him. It wasn't us.
-She didn't abandon him.
-His family is leaving him here.
-Jonathan!
His family has chosen a new family.
-She has no choice.
-Right.
-But that's the reality.
-Jonathan.
Jonathan, I'm sorry.
HER EXPRESSION AND WORDS DO NOT MATCH
We need to go.
-It leaves in two hours.
-We only have two hours.
Let's go now.
Hurry, it leaves in two hours. Let's go!
Sorry, Jonathan.
-Hyung.
-Yes?
We won't be able
to get on the boat anyway.
We can't.
53 HOURS SINCE THE ZOMBIE OUTBREAK
ONE DEAD
ONE DEAD AND ABANDONED
EIGHT ESCAPED
2:10 A.M.
WOLMIDO, INCHEON
Are we at the correct coordinates?
-Yes, we are.
-It's correct.
-We're safe.
-We made it.
-We're safe!
-Let's go.
-We don't have time.
-We're safe!
Whoever's alive should survive!
-All right!
Wait for me!
This is the location
based on the coordinates.
We're safe!
-Where?
-The boat?
Where's the boat?
There is no boat.
-We got here on time.
-This is the right location.
-Are you sure it's here?
-Yes, it's correct.
What's that?
-What?
-Isn't that the boat?
Did it leave already?
It looks like it already left. There!
-Oh, no!
-Fuck!
Over here!
-Over here!
-We're over here!
-Wait!
-No!
-Hey, boat!
-You have to take us!
-What?
-There are humans here!
-No!
Please take us!
-It's because we hesitated.
-Just 15 minutes!
If we got here ten minutes earlier…
We should've hurried, but Jonathan…
-Don't blame Jonathan.
-Darn it!
You're such jerks.
-If only we got here a little sooner.
-Wait.
We can see it right over there.
Don't fight!
If only we got here a little sooner.
-Whoever's alive should survive.
-You're evil!
Listen. Mr. Kim said earlier
that there will be two boats.
-Tomorrow morning? Okay.
-There's another one five hours later.
-Okay.
-Gosh, seriously.
We can get on the next one.
Can we go in somewhere?
-How about over there?
-Where?
Yes, the Ferris wheel over there.
-Let's go.
-Let's go now.
-Whoever's alive should survive.
-Let's go!
It's so cold. Come on!
Let's hold out for five hours in here.
THEME PARK AT THE END OF THE WORLD
5-HOUR UNLIMITED RIDE PASS
They have arrived at a new location.
There might be zombies. Be careful.
Places like this could actually be safer.
But it's too quiet here.
The ferris wheel is up there.
Let's go there.
Let's go somewhere high up, Hong-chul.
But I can't see anything.
-Slow down.
-Walk slowly.
-Okay.
-Gosh.
We're here. This is it.
We can see everything from here.
I don't think anyone's here.
I know. It's so nice.
The Ferris wheel is high up in the air.
We'll be fine up there for five hours.
But it's not turning. The machine is off.
Even if we hide inside,
there will be nothing we can do
if zombies come in.
Can't we turn on the lights here?
Let's follow the cable line
and see if there's a switch.
-He's right.
-Yes, he is.
Over here?
I think it's connected over here.
-But it's a little scary since it's dark.
-I think it's this.
This?
It looks like
a very large electrical panel.
How do we…
The lights came on.
It's moving!
Over there. We can be safe up there.
It looks so pretty!
We did it!
But will it really be all right?
It's too bright.
It's so pretty!
What?
We're at a theme park!
Wait, there are zombies.
There are zombies!
They're all zombies here too.
What do we do?
Jeez.
This is the most we've seen so far.
But there weren't any earlier.
Everyone, be quiet.
There are so many of them.
There are so many zombies. Over here!
-Hey, don't yell.
-Over here!
-Na-rae, what's with you?
-What are you doing?
-Na-rae is acting strange.
-How?
-No.
-She's waving at the zombies.
She's just teasing them.
Come to your senses.
Hyung, I don't feel so good.
I think everyone who was here got bitten.
They came out
because we turned on the lights.
-Gosh.
-Darn it.
If we hadn't, they wouldn't have known.
ZOMBIES POURED OUT IN RESPONSE TO
THE LIGHTS AND SOUNDS OF THE RIDES
Wait, I think there are people over there.
-There are people!
-Over there.
-On the ride.
-Over here!
There are some kids there.
THERE ARE SURVIVORS
ALL THROUGHOUT THE THEME PARK
Shouldn't we help them?
We have weapons at least.
-But there are too many zombies.
-Oh, no.
How can we get past that?
We've been trained and have guns too.
The child… We have to save the people.
Those of us who are fine
should go down first
-What about us?
-and figure out a path.
What about us? We don't come along?
Root for us from here.
-You can't abandon us, okay?
-Hang in there.
We always helped you.
You can't abandon us.
-What are we supposed to do here?
-See you.
Jeez, look at the zombies.
The zombies here are all young.
They were visitors here.
-Right.
-Seriously.
Let's hide here behind those guns.
-Right, let's hide.
-Okay.
I'm scared. That's it.
There are some gloves.
Let's put them on.
So there are people on the tagada,
the carousel, and the bumper cars.
There is also a child on the tagada.
We can't all move at once.
-Let's split up.
Wait. Two, four… There are six of us.
Teams of two.
-Three teams.
-Okay, then.
The team going to the area
with the most zombies takes the weapons.
Damn it, they're coming.
I don't think you'll need
a lot of weapons for the tagada.
But as for the carousel,
you can shoot down the zombies.
THEY'RE PERFECT TARGETS
FOR SHOOTING PRACTICE
Then whoever's good at shooting
should take the guns.
-Tsuki or Si-young.
-I'm terrible at it.
-I'll go.
-You all saw.
Then Si-young goes to the carousel.
Since Si-young and I
were a team yesterday,
-Okay, I'll go with Dex.
-I'll go with her.
Dex, you choose the carousel?
Well, since Si-young is going there…
Since we were a team…
-Is that right?
-Yes.
-What about you?
-I…
What are you thinking?
Come on. Just a little more.
HE WANTS TO KEEP DEX FOR HIMSELF
-It's nothing.
-What's that look in your eyes?
I think he'll abandon me if I go with him.
-I don't trust Hong-chul.
-I don't trust him either.
-I'd rather go to the tagada.
-Then let's go together, DinDin.
-Have you ever been on a tagada?
-No.
-Have you?
-Yes.
You're not going there to ride it for fun.
But Tsuki is a good dancer.
So what?
You can dance on the tagada.
The zombies are coming.
DAY 3… EVEN THE LEADER IS LOSING HIS MIND
-What's up with Dex?
-Dex can be quite silly.
HE EVEN PLAYS WHACK-A-MOLE
Keep your heads down.
Darn it.
Should we not go?
THE FATE OF THE SURVIVORS DEPENDS ON THEM
Let's do this.
Patricia and I go to the bumper cars.
You two go to the carousel.
CAROUSEL TEAM
SI-YOUNG AND DEX
And the agile Tsuki and DinDin
can go to the tagada.
-Let's rescue people and gather again.
-Okay.
-See you later.
-Let's survive and meet again.
What's wrong?
Seriously, what's wrong with him?
Why did you come out this way?
There are too many over there.
HE'S BEEN CRAWLING FOR THE PAST 3 DAYS
Seriously.
How come they're not moving?
Their heads are still intact.
Are they all asleep?
THEY SEE A FRIGHTENED STUDENT
IN THE FURTHEST CORNER
-Over there.
-Hello.
IT'S A YOUNG STUDENT…
THEY NATURALLY WANT TO RESCUE HER!
-Is she alive?
-Yes.
Hey, look at this.
"When the cars are operating,
electricity runs through the floor."
"Do not enter!"
A current flows through the floor.
We'll have to ride the cars.
The floor cannot be stepped on
as a current flows through it.
They must ride the bumper cars
to rescue the survivor.
In order to survive,
they must not awaken the sleeping zombies.
Hey, who should go?
It's too narrow for both of us to go.
You're young,
so you must like theme parks.
So you should go.
Me?
Let's make it fair.
One of us distracts her,
while the other stacks stuff.
-Okay.
-Will you go first?
Sure, Hong-chul.
Doesn't the one suggesting it
usually go first?
THEY NEVER YIELD TO EACH OTHER
NOTE: THE AGE GAP IS 23 YEARS
THIS ISN'T DÉJÀ VU
I go in?
Let's come up with a plan.
-I'll ride that and go that way.
-Okay.
You just clear the path for me.
I'm taking on all the danger.
I don't think so.
If you clear the path,
I'll risk myself and go rescue her.
-We have great teamwork.
-I trust you, Hong-chul.
-Just push that, okay?
-I said I trust you.
HE HAS NO INTENTION OF LISTENING TO HER
-Gosh.
-Careful.
Jeez.
Oh, come on.
Be careful, Hong-chul.
-Oh, gosh!
-Be careful!
OH, NO! HIS GROIN IS SPLITTING
Be careful!
Be careful.
Hey, you'd better do it.
What?
Me?
THEIR ACTIONS ALREADY
MAKE HER FEEL HOPELESS…
Ride this over there.
The quest begins.
RESCUE THE STUDENT!
WHILE THE ZOMBIES ARE SLEEPING
HE NEEDS TO BE PARTICULARLY CAREFUL
NOT TO WAKE ANY OF THE ZOMBIES
Oh, this is…
The corpse.
THE ZOMBIES AREN'T MOVING AT ALL SO FAR
Hey, I think it's safe.
You come too.
They aren't moving.
Hang in there.
What do I do? Hong-chul.
What do I do?
Yes. Come here.
Just come over now. Step on the cars.
A COLLISION OCCURS!!
Oh, no.
-Oh, gosh.
-What's happening?
-What's going on?
-Hong-chul.
What's going on?
Hong-chul.
THE ZOMBIE, SENSITIVE TO VIBRATIONS,
SUDDENLY REACTS
-Hong-chul!
-It's not moving!
A CHAIN REACTION OF COLLISIONS
Wait.
Oh, no.
Gosh, this isn't working.
Hong-chul!
Hey kid, come over here!
ALL THE ZOMBIES ARE AWAKE NOW!
Hey, kid!
Hey, how do I do this?
Hey, this isn't working.
HE ABANDONS THE STUDENT AND FLEES
Hong-chul, you can't just run away!
Get away!
Get away! I said get away from me!
Wait right there. Be quiet.
THANKS TO PATRICIA, THE PATH IS CLEAR!
Hong-chul, go!
Grab her!
-Hong-chul.
-Come here.
Hong-chul!
THEY SUCCESSFULLY GET THE SURVIVOR
I'll lure them.
Come, all of you.
(BACKING UP)
Go straight.
HE MUST'VE BEEN A GOOD DRIVER
WHEN HE WAS ALIVE
Wait a minute!
Hong-chul!
Oh, no!
Come on. Hong-chul, follow me.
Hong-chul!
THIS TIME, HONG-CHUL IS IN TROUBLE
Wait, Hong-chul.
Hong-chul.
Hong-chul!
Okay, I'm coming.
Don't you dare come near me!
Wait, Hong-chul. I'll save you!
Hold on.
SHE'S MIGHT DIE FIRST?!
Wait.
I don't know. Let's just go!
What? Oh, my God!
Hey, stop it!
Oh, no!
Don't come near me!
No! Don't come near me!
-We can go now, Hong-chul!
-Patricia!
Go now, Hong-chul. Go!
Patricia!
Oh, no!
THANKS TO PATRICIA,
HONG-CHUL AND THE SURVIVOR ESCAPE
Patricia.
Patricia!
SHE HAD JUST BEGUN DRIVER'S ED
-Hong-chul!
-Yes!
That's it. You got it.
Hong-chul!
You got this.
Good job.
THEY MADE IT OUT
OF THE HELLISH COURSE SAFELY
Patricia.
GREAT WORK!
Quest complete.
QUEST COMPLETE
RESCUE THE STUDENT!
-There are zombies.
-What?
Zombies over there.
Shouldn't we go down there too?
You can't see very well?
You still haven't lost
your sense of humor.
TSK TSK… SHE CAN'T EVEN TELL
THE FRONT FROM THE BACK
Let me help you.
Check it out. Over there.
Wow, it's insane!
One, two, three, four…
Five…
Let's just enjoy it.
We don't have any strength left now.
If I had known that I'd die like this,
I would've lived a dirtier life.
Dirtier?
You're dirty enough already.
45 HOURS AFTER GETTING INFECTED,
THEY SENSE THE END IS NEARING
I struggled my way out of Mokpo
and came to Seoul,
being called a workaholic
as I hustled to save up money.
But now I'll die lonely.
I may have said a lot of racy things,
but I didn't even get to date
that many guys.
THAT'S TMI!
Shit, this sucks.
WHILE THE HALF-ZOMBIES
CONTINUE TO GRUMBLE
DINDIN AND TSUKI APPROACH
THEIR MISSION LOCATION
-We have to open the gate
-Yes.
-and get those people out.
-Okay.
-What do you want?
-Please open the gate.
-Please open it.
-There are people inside. Open the gate.
-Are you a zombie?
-No.
-I'm the DJ.
-We're not zombies either.
-Open the gate.
-Please open it.
-Hurry.
-One moment.
It's open.
Are you okay?
We have to get out of here.
Were you bitten? Are you okay?
-Shit!
-Are you okay? You go first.
Thank you.
-Oh, no.
-Hurry out.
-What do we do?
-Damn.
THE HUMANS LEFT AND ZOMBIES RUSHED IN
THE DJ COULDN'T ESCAPE IN THE END…
Are you okay?
-I lost it.
-What?
-What did you lose?
-Oh, no.
What's wrong?
My daughter has asthma,
so she needs her medicine.
I think she dropped it there.
An inhaler?
-Yes.
-Oh, no.
You can't wait?
-How could she?
-How old are you?
-I'm 26.
-You're 26?
NOT A CHILD,
JUST SOMEONE WHO LOOKS VERY YOUNG
What does that matter?
You're 26. Why did you ride that
with your bag open?
NO MERCY FOR AN ADULT
-She's cute.
-First,
let's get Kkwachu Hyung.
-Okay. I'll go get him.
-The half-zombie is a doctor.
Let's bring him.
I'll go get him then.
Your side will get cold
if you lie on the floor.
Hey, Na-rae.
Keep switching sides, okay?
-Okay.
-That way, you'll get evenly cold.
-That's it, flip over.
-Wow, you're so smart.
WE SHOULD JUST LAY HER TO REST IN PEACE…
-Doctor.
-Hold on a second.
We're having fun turning. What's wrong?
-I have a favor to ask.
-What is it?
-The child we saw earlier.
-What?
-The child?
-The child…
has this illness, you know?
-The illness that makes your heart beat.
-"Heart beat"?
HAVING TROUBLE COMMUNICATING WITH A DOCTOR
-What is it?
-Asthman.
-"Asthman"?
Who's "Asthman"?
Is that someone's name? Ms. Asthman!
So what now?
-She has asthma.
-I see, she has asthma.
-You have to come.
-Okay.
Please.
ALTHOUGH HALF-ZOMBIE,
HE STILL UPHOLDS THE HIPPOCRATIC OATH
I'm flipping over.
-My goodness.
-Kkwachu Hyung.
-He's not a zombie.
-Hello.
I'm a doctor.
The cold air can aggravate it.
It's dangerous if you don't spray it soon.
She could die.
There's no emergency care for this.
THERE'S NO CHOICE
BUT TO GO BACK AND FIND IT
Then stay here for now.
-Come with us since we know the ride.
-Come with you?
-Yes, let's save her.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Let's go.
Come back safely.
Okay, let's do our best.
-Sir, please open the door.
-Please.
She left her inhaler. She has asthma.
HOW IS THE DJ STILL ALIVE
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED???
10 MINUTES AGO
THE TAGADA WAS FULL OF ZOMBIES
Hold on. I'll spin it for you.
Two of you over there,
don't roll around together.
That's it.
You zombies might collapse.
HE DOESN'T DISCRIMINATE
AND SHOWS THEM A GOOD WOLMIDO TIME
You're finally almost all unconscious.
Please don't ever come back.
THE DJ IS ALMIGHTY
WHEN YOU'RE RIDING THE TAGADA…
They've passed out.
We have to find it quickly.
I'm a half-zombie. They wouldn't bite me.
Right, they don't bite you.
-Oh, shit! It's Yoo Hee-kwan!
-How…
-It's Yoo Hee-kwan!
-DinDin!
If I get bitten,
I'll come get you as a zombie.
I'm going to be zombie food.
EVEN AFTER BECOMING A ZOMBIE
HE DIDN'T FORGET HIS PROMISE
THE PITCHER WITH 100 WINS
-DinDin!
-He won't bite you, Hyung.
I…
Hello.
I'm still scared.
Spin it.
Spin it now!
THEY DESPERATELY NEED
THE DJ'S HELP IN THIS QUEST
The quest begins.
FIND THE INHALER
YOO HEE-KWAN'S DISCO FEVER
Don't come for us!
No!
Oh, my God!
-No!
-DinDin!
Don't do this!
When will it end?
ZOMBIE HEE-KWAN DOESN'T FALL
Why isn't that zombie falling down?
ONLY THE INNOCENT HALF-ZOMBIE ROLLS AROUND
THIS IS THE BALANCE OF A PRO ATHLETE
Is he a tagada expert?
Hold down Yoo Hee-kwan!
HE'S ABOUT TO GET CAUGHT!
You can't take off his pants. This is bad.
HIS FEEBLE LEGS ALMOST GOT EXPOSED!
AS PROMISED, HE ONLY GOES AFTER DINDIN
HIS (USELESS) REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED
You're all right.
I'll spin you.
TSK, TSK…
KKWACHU HYUNG CAN'T GET UP AT ALL
No!
I'm a zombie. I am a half-zombie.
AVOIDING HEE-KWAN IS ONE THING,
BUT THEY MUST NOT FORGET THE INHALER
Find it!
That corpse!
Hurry up and find it!
Stop!
THEY JUST NEED TO ESCAPE NOW!
I found it!
I think they got it now.
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED AFTER 2 MINUTES…
I think it's all good now.
Just hold on a second.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS OVER?
NO WAY!
WITH AN IRON WILL,
HE GOES AFTER DINDIN AGAIN
DinDin!
HE'S NEARING THE END OF HIS LIMIT
Come here!
No!
-No!
NO MORE ENERGY LEFT TO HANG ON
IN THE END,
HEE-KWAN COULDN'T KEEP HIS PROMISE
Please move now. Hurry.
And please rescue me too.
Don't run away without me.
He's so weird.
-Please rescue me too.
-Run!
Yoo Hee-kwan.
Quest complete.
QUEST COMPLETE
FIND THE INHALER
-Honey!
-Please.
Please help me.
Over here!
What's going on?
Hey!
THEY FIND A SURVIVOR ON THE CAROUSEL
Excuse me, please save her.
My girlfriend is trapped there.
-Girlfriend?
-Yes.
-The foreigner with blonde hair?
HE MADE IT OUT BUT LEFT HER BEHIND
Don't come near me.
She's from Russia.
-Why did you escape by yourself?
-There are too many.
HE ESCAPED WITHOUT HIS GIRLFRIEND…
DEX CAN'T COMPREHEND THIS
Please, do something.
Don't ask us. You do something.
-You're ridiculous.
-Wait.
Please come here first.
-Hide as much as you can.
-Follow us.
KOREA IS A SAFE COUNTRY!
WE CAN'T LET A FOREIGNER DIE!
Save me!
There are too many,
so we can't go on there.
FIVE ZOMBIES ARE SURROUNDING THE SURVIVOR
I think there are more than ten zombies.
THE ZOMBIES ON THE CAROUSEL
ARE BUCKLED IN AND CAN'T SEEM TO MOVE
Please help me.
Honey!
Be quiet.
All right.
You see the one in a school uniform?
That one and that one.
IF THEY CAN GET RID OF THE THREE
ON THE RIGHT WITH THE POTATO GUN
We need to shoot just those zombies.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY CAN
SECURE AN ESCAPE PATH!
How many potatoes do we have now?
We only have ten left.
-Hurry up and do something!
-Be quiet. What's wrong with you?
Why are you whining?
-You should've saved her yourself.
-But…
Wait.
The survivor is surrounded by zombies
because the lights were turned on.
They only have ten chances to shoot.
There are three zombies they must kill.
Hurry up and do something!
The boyfriend won't let it slide
if they fail.
-The quest begins.
-I've never hit a moving target before.
You must shoot carefully.
We don't have many chances.
IT'S DIFFERENT FROM LAST NIGHT
WHEN THEY WERE HAVING FUN AND CHEERING
IT'S HER FIRST TIME SHOOTING REAL ZOMBIES
INSTEAD OF MANNEQUINS!
I'm nervous.
It might be very loud.
What's her name?
-It's Tina.
-Tina?
What's your name?
It's I-su.
-I-su?
-Yes.
I-su and Tina.
YOU MUST MEMORIZE PEOPLE'S NAMES
TO BECOME A HERO
-I'll save Tina no matter what.
-Please.
-Is it loaded?
-Honey!
-Be quiet.
-Yes, be quiet.
Please.
Please help me!
I said, save me!
Tina almost got hit.
What the heck are you doing?
OOPS! SHE ALMOST RUINED EVERYTHING
RIGHT FROM THE GET-GO
I'm so scared.
It never occurred to me
that Tina could get hit.
We have to save her at all costs.
THEY HADN'T CONSIDERED
THAT THEY COULD HIT TINA!
-Si-young, you can do it.
-Yes.
You must do this. You can do it.
THAT WAS CLOSE!
That was so close.
Come on. You have to focus.
-Focus, my foot.
-Gosh, seriously.
Want to get smacked with this broom?
Hurry up.
-Jeez.
-What's wrong with him?
-Tell me about it.
-Hurry!
What's wrong with him?
-Honey!
-I said be quiet, damn it.
But she keeps calling for me.
HE'S VERY ANNOYING
FOR SOMEONE WHO'S ASKING FOR A FAVOR…
Let me focus. Be quiet.
-Headshot.
-He got hit.
That was impressive.
-Did you see that?
-Si-young.
It hit the zombie right in the face.
All right.
-It's actually working.
-You saw it, right?
THE BOYFRIEND SEEMS TO HAVE
TERRIBLE MOOD SWINGS
See? I told you to wait and see.
You're so impatient, I-su.
-One died, so shoot the one to his left.
-Okay.
-Hey, Seong-jin.
-Yes?
-No, it's I-su.
-It's I-su.
-Oh, I-su.
-Yes?
Who's Seong-jin, Si-young?
Was Tina hit just now?
SHE CAN'T LOOK UP DUE TO EMBARRASSMENT
Look, she's alive. She's full of energy.
It did fly right above her head, though.
I know.
But she's not my girlfriend.
NOT A GOOD IDEA TO PROVOKE THE BOYFRIEND
Be quiet, both of you.
IT FLEW RIGHT ABOVE HER HEAD
You asshole!
You almost hit Tina!
WOW! HONESTLY, SHE CAN'T ARGUE THIS TIME
What the hell are you doing?
Move aside. Should I shoot instead?
THE BOYFRIEND IS GOING CRAZY
I don't want to do it anymore.
SHE'D RATHER QUIT THAN SHOOT PEOPLE…
Honey, hang on just a little longer.
I'm coming.
Si-young, Tina almost died.
Hurry. What are you doing?
-I can't believe this guy.
-Jeez.
THEY'D LIKE TO JUST SHOOT HIM FIRST
-Quiet down.
-Man, this isn't easy, okay?
I hit on her for two weeks.
-Where did you guys meet?
-At a singles bar.
HE'S HESITATING TO HELP HIM…
Hurry up and shoot.
ONLY FOUR POTATOES LEFT
-I got the hang of it now.
-You got it?
SHE WAS ZEROING IN UNTIL NOW!
SI-YOUNG'S GOT THE HANG OF IT
Can't you see Tina is scared?
I'll definitely hit one this time.
-I'm shooting.
-Okay.
-Okay!
-She hit one.
-You got this.
Two down.
Reload now and hit another one.
Hit another one.
HER NEXT TARGET MIGHT BE THE BOYFRIEND
What's his problem?
You killed another one.
-Did you just see that?
-A top marksman who never misses!
She got him.
PERHAPS THANKS TO THE WHINING,
SHE NEATLY TOOK DOWN THE ZOMBIES
NOW THEY CAN RESCUE TINA!
-Are they unconscious?
-I think so.
Go bring her now.
Honey.
Honey, come quickly.
Hurry.
I did it. I saved you.
You're the best.
THEY DEFINITELY SHOULD'VE JUST SHOT HIM…
What the heck?
-Thank you.
-What's wrong with him?
Hold on!
Damn it. Run!
-There are zombies.
-What?
THEY ENCOUNTER ZOMBIES
BEFORE THEY COULD BE THANKED!
Wait for us, you punk!
Wait a second.
THEY FLEE TO A TRAMPOLINE
OUT OF ALL PLACES
THERE'S NO WAY OUT!
HUH? THE ZOMBIES CAN'T HANDLE IT
Bouncing zombies.
-What's wrong with them?
-What do we do?
-They're rolling around.
TERRIBLE BALANCE!
THEY FIGURED OUT THE ZOMBIES' WEAKNESS
Keep rolling around.
Roll around some more.
It's exhausting.
THIS ZOMBIE SEEMS A BIT DIFFERENT
Please!
Hold on.
They're out of it.
THE ZOMBIE WITH GREAT BALANCE
KEEPS FOLLOWING THEM
What the hell?
HE'D EVEN QUALIFY TO BE ON PHYSICAL: 100!
He's scaring me.
-This way.
-Dex.
Let's go, Si-young.
Jump.
LUCKY! THEY FOUND THE ONLY EXIT
Please.
Don't come near me.
Don't come near me!
Get lost!
We were almost caught.
Quest complete.
Which way do we go now? That way?
-Is it that way?
-Jeez.
I can't even see well anymore.
-Me neither.
-Who is this?
-It's me.
-You're not a zombie?
Were you about to hit me?
What do we do?
Shouldn't we do something?
-They're all working very hard, right?
-Yes.
What could half-zombies do?
-Then…
-Let's do whatever we can.
-Let's clean up for them.
-How?
How else? We should gather them up.
THE ZOMBIES GATHER AROUND
THE NOSTALGIC SOUND OF THE VUVUZELA
Zombies!
No way. What?
Stop. Stop right there.
It's him, isn't it? The mohawk.
I feel bad. Sorry about then.
We should've taken care of your corpse.
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry, Hee-kwan.
Since we gathered them here,
should we go somewhere together?
-Attention, please.
-Let's go.
The staircase is narrow. Two at a time.
-Great.
-The staircase to the right.
Your joints don't bend very easily, right?
I know how that feels.
You have to use them often
to strengthen your joints.
Please be careful.
We gathered so many of them, right?
-Yes, we did.
-All the zombies are here.
Hee-kwan's keeping up quite well.
Okay, come up carefully.
This way.
If you enjoy thrill rides,
sit in the back section.
If not, sit in the middle.
My goodness, Hee-kwan.
How awful.
The P.E. majors are here. My goodness.
All right, let's take a group picture.
On the count of three, say "zombie."
One, two, three. Zombie.
-Great.
-They love it.
TA-DA! THE SAFETY BARS LOWER
AND RESTRAIN THEM
NOW THEY CAN'T MOVE AT ALL
Okay, let's depart now.
Enjoy your trip.
Wave your hands as you go up.
My goodness, that's great.
-Raise your hands.
-They know how to enjoy the ride.
Put your hands up.
Wave your hands.
How great.
HE'S SLOWLY STARTING TO FEEL IT!
THEY REACH A 90-DEGREE INCLINE!
Shit!
-Someone said, "Shit."
-Wait.
THEY'RE JUST HEARING THINGS
WOLMIDO'S SCARY VIKING SHIP
MAKES THEM WET THEIR PANTS
Oh, my goodness.
One more time?
-They really love it.
-They do, right?
-Here you go.
-Have a fun trip. Bye.
Go!
Bye, Viking! Bye-bye.
3 HOURS LEFT
UNTIL THE RESCUE BOAT ARRIVES
-The Ferris wheel.
-Just go anywhere.
We're almost done.
I don't even have enough strength
to blow on this.
Kkwachu and Na-rae… What?
What?
What's wrong with them?
You're here.
That scared me!
-Oh, no.
-We're not dead yet.
-We're not dead.
-Are you okay?
-We were having fun.
-Na-rae, open your eyes.
-Yes?
-Are you okay?
-She was dozing off. Wake up.
Her eyes are bloodshot.
-Doctor, are you okay?
-We were dozing off. We're okay.
Who is that over there?
It's a person, right?
What the heck?
-In the control room.
-What?
Hey, go check.
-Isn't it a zombie?
-Who is that?
Oh, my goodness
-My God.
-Are you human?
Look carefully.
I work here.
Are you all right?
-He looks fine.
-He's trembling.
If we hold out for three hours,
we can get on a boat.
Come with us then.
-Please take me with you.
-Yes, we promise.
I'm so cold.
Na-rae, what's wrong?
-You're like an electric eel.
-I'm so cold.
-Dex, I'm so cold.
-Are you cold?
What are these?
Walkie-talkies.
-We'll borrow these for a moment.
-Channel one.
Once you get on the Ferris wheel,
-Yes?
-you can't open the door from the inside.
Someone has to open the door
from the outside.
-You get it, right?
-Please open the doors in three hours.
Since you have to open them for us,
-I'll just hide here until then.
-hide until then.
How many cars
are available for us to ride?
A total of five.
Please get them on first.
They're a little contaminated.
Don't say that they're contaminated.
-They've been exposed.
-Don't say contaminated.
Ro Hong-chul.
-Get in. The door is open.
-Go for it, Hyung.
-Yes, it's dangerous.
-Get in now.
-Before the door shuts.
-Gosh.
Kkwachu Hyung.
Yeah?
We're going to die.
No, we've been holding up well so far.
I'm so thirsty.
Why are you up there already?
-To get on.
-We need to get on too.
Tsuki, let's ride this one.
Come on. Get in. Hurry.
-See you in three hours.
-Wait.
Okay.
We made it. We're safe.
Hey, Patricia, we're alive!
We made it!
Let's hold out for three more hours.
Then we'll survive. Let's go!
We made it.
We're safe now.
We're safe now! Look.
-We can do it.
-They can't come up here.
I can see the ocean on the right.
After three hours…
-We made it.
-Once we get to the water,
-the zombies can't follow us.
-We're safe.
Tomorrow we'll be at the ocean.
-It's so beautiful.
-We'll escape to the ocean tomorrow.
Let's hold out for three more hours.
Then we'll survive. Let's go!
-Let's go! We can do it.
-Let's go!
It's been such a rough three days.
I used to be really scared
of closed spaces like this.
-But now I'm so happy.
-Now…
There's no place like it.
I feel a bit relaxed now.
I want to sleep comfortably
without any worries.
There were many scary moments.
But I felt less scared
when we were together.
It looks pretty from above.
It's not bad.
-Get away from me!
-What's going on?
Well, earlier…
Get away from me!
-Wait, who is that?
-Isn't that the employee's voice?
Hey, there are zombies.
There are so many of them.
The employee got bitten.
The door won't open.
He's not moving.
What do we do?
Who's going to open the door for us?
We're going to die!
ZOMBIEVERSE
Subtitle translation by: Ji-young Hwang