[Watch on kisskh to support admin]
♫Just a single glance, from your eyes straight to mine,♫
♫and my heart starts to melt.♫
♫As I come closer, I talk to you,♫
♫ I tremble, till I'm almost breathless.♫
♫ A restlessness overwhelms me, losing myself in the tide.♫
♫Is this what they call symptoms of love,♫
♫It happens every moment,♫
♫when I get a glimpse of you,
♫Are you feeling like me, perhaps,♫
♫A burning, restless whirl within the heart, do you feel so?♫
♫Every symptom shows, do you tremble too, just how much,♫
♫Feeling good, alike maybe?♫
♫then we can weight the chances in our hearts,♫
♫Are you feeling like me, perhaps,♫
♫As if I can't control myself,♫
♫in my dreams or wherever, it is you I meet ♫.
♫Tell me, when I meet you,♫
♫Are your thoughts the same as mine,♫
♫that we are in love?♫
Ah, it's just a mirror.
You've got like a gazillion mirrors back home.
-Just use another one.
-It's not the same, dude.
Old mirrors like this could have a past.
Don’t you dare remove it!
You can't do that.
Don't!!!
I know now.
This is Marvin, an old buddy of mine.
I forgot about him.
I'm sorry.
I bet it's been lonely for you lately
It's okay.
I'm not lonely anymore.
Then let's make life fun together.
Let's live it up together.
Want some ice cream?
Let's get the same kind, alright?
Yes, sure.
Chocolate, cookies and cream, please.
-Two cups, right?
-Yes, please.
Alright.
Everything good?
All good.
Here, two cups of ice cream.
Thank you so much.
Vin!
Smile!
-Hmm, delicious.
-You think?
I haven't been out like this in a long time.
Haven't been out at all?
How do you live, with food and stuff?"
I do go out sometimes,
but just around the block.
I don't really know how to go elsewhere.
I'm not used to it.
For food and necessities, my uncle takes care of them.
Good that you have your uncle to look after you.
In my parents' will,
he gets everything - insurance money, house - when I'm gone,
in exchange for taking care of my needs.
They planned it all, knowing what was coming.
But my uncle only does what's necessary.
He doesn't really care much about me.
Forget him.
If he doesn´t care, just let it be.
I'll be the one to look after you now.
Why are you so nice to me?
Well,
we are...
I feel so happy today.
How's it going?
What's that?
Just asking how you're feeling.
What's up, bro?
Enjoying yourself?
Yeah, having a blast.
It's my first time here.
You like it?
Absolutely, bro.
What's up!
We've done a lot of things today.
What do you like the most?
Um, just about everything.
-I feel very happy.
-Impossible...
Like what is the happiest thing in your life?
Well,
maybe...
spending time together with you.
That's touching, huh?
So, when I went to the toilet,
did anyone ask your number?
Nope,
-No one.
-Really?
I don't even have a phone.
Right.
You don't have a phone.
You've been without a phone for years,
not even on social media.
Don't you feel alone?
I'm scared to use it.
I'm afraid.
Since I got sick,
my world's shrunk a lot.
I didn't get to play outside like other kids.
Didn't go to school.
My life was just home and hospital.
When I go out,
it's always with family.
But it's not too bad, you know.
I'm happy in my little world.
But without them,
it feels even smaller.
I don't know how to live outside.
Seeing the world through social media?
I don't know how I'd feel about that.
Hey, it's alright.
I'll show you the world myself.
Alright?
But for tonight,
let's head back home.
It's getting late now.
So, want me to drop you?
No worries,
-I'll take a taxi.
-Sure?
-You've got work tomorrow, right?
-Yep.
Then...
-Shall we ask for the bill?
-Okay.
Excuse me, can we get the bill?
-I'll pay for it.
-Oh, no need.
I've got this one.
You paid me for the whole day, let me pay it.
I'll treat you.
Save your money for the cab. I've got it.
Pond, stop it! I'm not playing.
I mean it, I'll actually do it.
You're not ready for this, trust me.
How will I know if I don't really try?
Let's do it!
-Come here!
-Stoy playing.
Come!
If you wanna try, test it on your hair.
Nope!
Just bet your head on it.
-Hurry up.
-You're too into cartoons, Pond!
Oops!
Sorry!
Hello, here for a haircut?
Yes.
-Welcome.
-Right this way.
-Please follow me.
-Don't be scared.
-Take a seat here.
-Please, sit down.
Just keep your hair clipper.
Man, you're always eager to cut hair!
Sorry for the mess.
I'm practicing haircutting.
No worries.
Well, it looks fun.
No, it's not fun.
We're just kids at heart.
What haircut do you want?
Skinhead?
I have cancer.
My hair's falling out from chemo.
Thought I'd just shave it all off.
Less distracting.
Sorry to hear that.
Hope you get better soon.
My dad died of cancer too.
Still don't get why I keep treating it.
Maybe, I do it for those behind me.
Treatment just adds a little time.
But I think that little time is meaningful.
Even a little time can create a lot.
Create some good memories.
But eventually we will forget about them,
no matter how many good memories,
It´s true.
But those who remain still remember.
Sorry,
I talked too much.
No worries.
Thank you.
Sorry about that.
Got a bit hectic earlier.
What haircut would you like, sir?
Skinhead, please.
Uh...
Can he shave my head?
-Are you sure?
-You sure?
It's just shaving.
He won't cut off my head, I guess.
Let him do it, please.
Alright then.
Take care of it, okay?
I'll do my best.
Ready?
All finished, sir. How's it feel?
Great, you've got a gentle touch, bro.
Thank you so much.
How much's this?
No charge for this one.
Consider it a lesson for Pond to practice.
Thanks again.
Pond&Mac: Thank you.
Thank you.
You're lucky today.
Tomorrow, your head's my practice canvas.
You just zip it!
-You'd better do here.
-What?
Here it is.
This is your job.
Here's the broom.
Get sweeping!
-Here, here...
-Back up!
Over there, more to clean.
Pond!
Vin!
Watch out, Vin!
Vin...!
Lift your head and breathe...
Feeling better now?
Vin!
Come here!
Let's eat, so you can take your pill.
Careful, it's hot.
Blow it first.
-Let me help.
-No, I'm good.
I can handle it myself.
Not gonna blow?
Here...
I have an old phone for you.
Why give this to me?
It's weird not having a phone.
I wouldn't call anyone, though.
Then call me,
or I can call you too.
What, gonna wish me good morning and good night?
Sure, I can do that. No sweat.
But mainly, it's for when you're sick,
Like today. Imagine if I hadn't arrived on time.
Shouldn't you have gone to the afterlife?
I did want to go soon.
Life's exhausting.
Hit your mouth three thousand times.
Just joking!
Why the hurry? You've got more photos to take.
-I said I was kidding.
-Gosh!
Here, do this.
I'll set up Instagram for you.
On Instagram
you can take and store lots of photos.
Mostly, if I'm not with you, I stay at home.
What's there to photograph?
Just take them even random shots.
In fact, I will also know that you are doing well.
You can also save the best ones for framing.
Okay.
You know how it works?
Hey Vin.
What are you taking?
Handsome, huh?
-Not bad.
-Wait!
You flatter yourself?
Really? Is it really good?
What are you taking?
You look handsome too.
That looks ugly. Delete it.
-Delete it.
-No, it's my phone.
-My choice.
-These photos are too dark.
Delete that!
My decision, dude.
-Just delete it.
-Hey...
So, don't post it okay?
-Please!
-Okay.
-Promise me?
-I'll only save it.
It's awful. You're not great at this, huh?
Alright, all set, sir.
Excuse me...
-How much?
-120 baht, sir.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Hello!
Vin!
What brings you here?
Just wanted to see your workplace.
Pond, you know this guy?
That's Marvin, my ghost buddy.
Oh, this guy. Nice to meet you.
I'm Mac.
Need a haircut?
Trying to make a quick buck, eh?
-Absolutely!
- I'd love to.
But I just got trimmed.
How about a hair wash?
Just washed it before coming.
Oh!
Where to next?
Pond can take care of you.
Um...
sounds good.
-Alright!
-Pond, your turn.
-Take care of him.
-Got it.
How do you want it styled?
I don't know, bro.
Never really styled it before.
Set it how you think is handsome.
Okay, but my idea of 'handsome' might be different.
Just go for it.
-I'm the customer here.
-Okay, dude.
How's it?
Like it?
Hmm,
super handsome.
- Bro, you've made so many dreams come true,
- It's nothing.
You know, you could style it yourself at home.
No,
I dreamed that if you had a shop, I'd like to be your customer.
Then, if you like, shall we take a picture together?
-Mac!
-Sup!
-Snap a picture for us?
-Sure thing, one sec.
Just use your phone.
Alright, come on.
Okay, come on.
Ready?
1...2...3
One more.
-Just smile, man.
-Okay, smiling.
Cheese!
1, 2,  cheese!
Awesome, that's a great shot!
-Let's see.
-Check it out.
Here...
Where you would like to go next?
We're pretty lucky today.
Usually there are a lot of people in this place.
Pond, you come here often?
Yeah, but I usually skip it because of the queue.
Hey!
-What a coincidence!
-Oh, Mr. Barber.
Here for a meal?
Yeah,
-I'm here with my girlfriend.
-Got a table yet?
Still waiting in line.
Join us, won't you?
More people, more fun. And you don't have to wait.
Come on!
Yes, sure.
How often do you come here?
Sometimes...
-Long wait normally, right?
-Yeah, it's pretty long.
By the way, I still don't know your name.
I'm Pond, and this is Marvin.
Shin here and...
Meaw, my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you all.
Meaw and I met back in university.
Started like a sister,
now she's my world.
Whoa!
How envious!
It's obvious,
I envy myself too.
If not her, then who else?
You're being cheesy, huh?
Not at all.
Well, I'm off to the toilet now.
Keep the praise down a bit, okay?
Okay.
She's so cute, really.
Hey, bro!
Remember that chat we had earlier?
Yes.
At first,
I didn't quite get why you said those things so sincerely
until I heard about Marvin.
What were you guys talking about before?
Marvin,
our lives might not be long,
but having someone special
can truly make you the happiest.
So,
you guys, be my witnesses.
Witnesses?
Meaw,
I'm sorry
for the tough times ahead.
And thank you
for filling my life with meaning.
Thank you for being the joy in my life.
I don't know...
what the future holds,
but from now on,
I want to be by your side forever.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Want it?
Already?
-It's done already.
-Yeah... it's done.
-It's great, isn't it?
-Huh?
Shin must be so happy to be with someone he loves.
Hmm,
the best life is probably one filled with happiness.
Thank you so much, bro,
for making me the happiest I've been in years.
Ever since my family left,
it's been lonely and tough.
I'm scared of feeling that way again.
If I have to be alone again someday,
I'd rather die while I'm happy like this.
Have you gone mad?
I'm here with you, aren't I?
Crazy, Pond!
You have your own life.
One day...
you'll find someone you love,
get married,
and I won't be there.
Don't think like that.
I love you, man.
I'll be with you,
stay with you forever.
Really?
-You won't leave me, really?
-Really.
I won't leave.
I'll make you happy.
Wherever you want to go, eat or do,
I'll be there with you.
We'll create memories together.
you and me.
Let's make life happy together.
Um.
Then...
Can you help me set up the tent, bro?
Over there?
Yes.
-Felt like camping today.
-Really?
Thought a sudden trip elsewhere might be too much.
Hey, no need to be so considerate. Just tell me
where you want to go.
Okay,
you just said it.
But let's camp with me right here for now.
Cool, you handle the BBQ, I'll get the tent.
-Deal!
-Let's go.
I'm really happy, you know.
Even this backyard camping is so fun.
Imagine how fun it would be a mountain trip together.
Next time, let's go to Khao Yai.
Drive around,
camp out, splash in waterfalls.
Inviting others could be even more fun.
Yeah, just the thought of it is exciting.
But...
will others be keen to come?
Of course,
Last time was just a plan change, no worries.
This time, we don't have to invite everyone.
Only the well-known ones.
I'll drag Mac along too.
Yeah, that could work, bro.
Hey, bro...
thanks...
for living the dream with me.
It's okay.
I already told you, right?
I'll do my best.
Just one regret though
There's one thing you can't do for me for sure.
What's that?
Graduation photos...
I wanted to take them with everyone.
Got this huge frame at home for it.
Actually, I wanted it to hold my graduation photo.
But I know...
can't rewind time to take it.
My parents are gone too.
Some moments...
if we missed once,
we are lost them forever.
That's why we have to make every day count.
What's past may need to be let go.
But from now on,
and in days ahead...
let's fill them with happiness together.
Um...
really, thanks, bro.
I'm glad
you're here with me today.
Vin!
Oh, Vin!
Vin...!
Vin, wake up!
Somebody help...
Vin...!
Damn it!
Somebody, help!
Vin, the doctor's coming.
What's gonna happen to him?
His condition is still critical.
We need to keep a close watch.
Can't say for sure yet.
You might have to prepare for the worst.
We'll go on a trip together, remember?
Vin!
Do something, doctor!
Vin, wake up, man.
Hey!
Damn mirror!
If you're really magic,
can't you make Marvin's wish come true?
Or If you can't rewind time,
at least wake Marvin up.
Didn't you bring me here just to make Marvin happy?
If you're really powerful,
show me a miracle, please!
Don't you want Marvin to be happy?
If you really want me to help Marvin, then help me too.
Let me fulfill Marvin's dream at once.
I'm begging you, for fuck's sake.
Hey Pond,
you lost in thought?
Pond, photo time!
Come on over.
Let's take photos with us.
Come on, stand in the middle.
Look at the camera.
Look over there!
Smile big, bro!
Smile!
Where's Marvin...?
Vin's not here today.
Why?
His uncle said he's sick.
Right?
Let´s do this.
Wait up, don't go anywhere. Hold off starting without me, alright? I'll be right back.
Oh, wait!
Where are you going?
Gonna get Marvin for the picture. Don't start yet!
Oh...
Hold up, man!
Why's he stalling us?
Marvin!
Marvin...!
Pond!
Hold on, young man.
What are you doing here?
Gonna take Marvin to graduation pics.
With our tutor gang.
Um, Marvin is still sick, he can't go.
But if not now,
they'll never happen again.
It happens only once, Marvin.
I said no, he's unwell.
We can take photos later.
I want to go, uncle.
It's just a doctor's appointment.
Postponing it a day or two won't matter,
I understand you're worried,
but...
I feel like...
if I don't go,
I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
I...
don't wanna miss any more joy.
Alright,
I'll drive you.
Come on, let's come together.
-Thank you.
-Get in the car.
Hurry up, Vin...
They've all left.
Peek-a-boo!
Friends: Just kidding. We're still here!
You look disappointed, huh?
How're you doing?
Friends: We're doing well, Let's take a selfie.
Friends: Let's take pictures.
Friends: Put on the cap.
-No, use mine.
-No, mine's cooler.
Friends: Stop squabbling.
Pond: Selfie time
Friends: Come on, guys.
3...2...1...
Another one.
Change pose.
3...2...1...
Here comes the photographer.
Friends: Here he comes.
Pond: How to pose?
Come closer.
Smile. 1...2...3
Cheese.
One more 1...2..3
Looks good?
You smile too, bro.
Awesome!
Name: Hey, last night Boy and I dreamed of taking photos with Marvin.
Mymild: I had the same dream.
JK: Me too, everyone had the same dream?
JamJam: Seriously? I had the exact same dream about the graduation photos.
Boy: What's happening? Pond, are you there? Let's call.
Friends: Hey, guys...
Friends: everyone had the same dream. What's going on?
Friends: I'm really uneasy about this.
Everyone,
Friends: Did something happen?
Friends: Yeah, what's happening?
-Marvin is dying.
-Huh?
Hey there!
Hey!
Marvin's awake!
What's going on?
Friends: Easy, don't stress too much.
Friends: Look, we're all here.
Friends from other cities and abroad are also here.
One moment.
There you go...
Friends: Hey there!
Look at our friends, smile.
Hey!
We got this too.
Look what we've got.
Vin!
Time for grad photos.
Friends:  Come on, let's help him.
Oh, you're quite heavy, huh?
Friends: Put on the cap.
Friends: C'mon.
You wear the cap too.
Friends: Let me see, freaking awesome.
Friends: Super handsome.
Pond: Ready? Nurse, please come in...
-Can you take pictures of us?
-Of course.
You look so good.
Here, please.
Friends: Finally you wear it.
Smile. 1...2...3
One more time.
1..2...3
Everything okay, Pond?
Oh, yes. Almost done.
Just need to arrange things a little bit and that's all.
Good, good.
If you need help with anything, just tell me.
Your offer on the house alone means a lot,
Hey, it's not a big deal.
I should be thanking you.
This house isn’t just important to us.
For me,
it's my brother's legacy.
I should thank you, Pond,
for taking care of something I love,
as I couldn't do it myself.
No worries.
I'm happy to.
I gotta run now. Call if you need anything.
Thank you, sir.
Whoa!
What's with this quirky house? Mirrors and frames all over.
You're missing the vibe, man.
These are all memories.
And you funded all this from working at my shop?
Who are you, really?
Thought I was just loafing around?
Who am I really?  Well, my mom's money did help.
You'd better keep talking.
Just be careful not to get kicked out of the inheritance.
What’s your next move?
Wanna work with me again?
Can you give me a brake...
juts like a gap year...
-Gap year? Planning to wander again?
-Not like that.
I'll find work, but still figuring out what I really want to do
Right now, I just want to support people like Marvin.
Not letting them face things alone.
not sure what job that is.
-You're so philosophical, bro.
-Who's your brother?
Oh, come on!
Anyway, where do you need me first?
Moving, cleaning, where to start?
Toilet, start over there first.
- With all these things, why the toilet?
- Just clean it.
Should I go lift stuff?
Up to you. Go on.
[Watch the uncut version online exclusively on the IQIYI app and iQ.com website.]
♫You transform the misty air into the sweet scent of flowers.♫
♫You change the silent stars into those from my dreams,♫
♫You turn a fleeting second into eternity,♫
♫Today, my love for you is the most precious.♫
♫Because... it's you.♫
♫We orbit and meet like a dream,♫
♫illuminating each other,♫
♫in a universe filled with love.♫
♫Because it is you who transforms my heart,♫
♫making my universe whole, no longer solitary♫
♫You turn a fleeting second into eternity,♫
♫Today, my love for you is the most precious.♫
♫Because... it's you.♫
♫We orbit and meet like a dream,♫
♫illuminating each other,♫
♫in a universe filled with love.♫
♫You turn a fleeting second into eternity,♫