=Let's Go Fighting=
=Episode 19=
I know it now.
The one who has been taking care of me
is you.
I'm sorry.
You're always like this.
I won't take care of you next time.
(Mr. D: I wonder if you can come over
for the matter about the Mu Group.)
Boss,
congratulations!
You finally got Miss Mu.
What's wrong, boss?
Mr. D has asked me to meet tonight.
Will you go?
Yes.
(Berewed in badger)
You are Mr. D?
You must be Mr. Mo.
Mr. D is on his way.
(Secretary Wen: Mr. D,)
(he has arrived.)
This is a secluded place.
I wonder
if a man
who has licentious behaviour
will be favored
by Mu Li.
(Unknown number)
(Miss Mu,)
(don't you wonder)
(where Mo Chen is?)
Mr. Mo,
if you want to know,
can we
have a drink first?
(Xu Weilai, what's wrong with Mo Chen?)
I don't know, Miss Mu.
I called him
all day!
He didn't answer
or text me back!
Boss said he was going to see Mr. D.
Don't lie to me with him!
I don't believe you!
Oh,
isn't this Li?
Don't worry.
Chen
will be back soon.
Do you know where he is?
If I'm not wrong,
he must have gone to see Mr. D.
Mr. D?
He's the boss
of Starwu Investment.
The last time I saw him
was in a club.
Why don't you
take me to Chen?
(Chen,)
(I'll give you a surprise.)
OK.
Mo Feng, where is Chen?
(So, you're Mr. D.)
Chen,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Mr. Mo,
just stop it.
Chen.
Li.
I admit
I knew Mr. D was here.
But you said
I was Mr. D?
It's funny, isn't it?
I didn't expect you
to get carried away as easily as you did
when you were little.
I just dialed
Mr. D's number.
Alright, Chen,
it looks like
you found it out again.
But,
it's OK.
Then,
I can play with you
without hiding behind the scenes.
Don't be so childish.
Enough is enough.
Tell me,
how did you
manage to escape
from that female secretary?
When I thought of you,
I was invincible.
Mealy-mouthed.
Tell me!
Kiss me first.
Who
on earth are you?
Mr. Mo, if you want to know...
Then,
I took the chance to text Mr. D.
That's it?
Yes.
OK, not bad.
Here.
I am childish?
Enough is enough?
Soon,
you won't say that about me.
=Let's Go Fighting=
♪The soul falls
to the bottom of the lake♪
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪Belong to you♪