=Let's Go Fighting=
=Episode 6=
Boss,
I have already checked.
Mu Liu has no sisters.
Did she have plastic surgery?
How about
taking some more photos
for the doctor to compare?
OK.
Go for it.
Anything else?
Boss,
it's more convenient for you
to take photos.
Me?
Where's this?
Didn't you ask Mu Bingyun to meet you?
But it's at a coffee shop.
It's right around here.
What are you shooting?
Let me see.
You made me look so bad.
I think they look good.
How beautiful.
Eyes, nose,
and everything are here.
Beautiful?
Alright,
I haven't done this before.
Let me teach you.
Teach me?
Lower.
OK.
One, two, three.
Ah,
my aunt is here.
I'll go find her first.
(Aunt,)
(where are you?)
(I haven't seen her before.)
(How can I find her?)
Aunt.
Liu.
I am very worried about you.
Sit down.
OK.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you contact me so late?
It's mainly my fault.
But I didn't know
such a big thing happened suddenlly.
Take care of yourself.
OK.
Aunt,
I have something to ask you.
Do you know the Starwu International
that is against the Mu Group?
I...
I don't know.
OK.
I heard recently
that someone
was selling the Mu Group's shares
to this company.
Do you know this?
Where did you
hear that?
You also know
that I just have a few shares.
I couldn't say anything
on the board of directors.
How can I sell shares?
Maybe it's one of your uncles.
By the way,
I have finished what you asked me to do
between you and Song Yuan.
Song Yuan?
What thing?
You asked me
to transfer two million RMB to him.
I have done it for you.
When will you give me your shares?
Oh,
I'm sorry, aunt.
Since my surgery,
I have not been well.
Can you give me some time
to recover?
(Boss,)
(the doctors who saw the photos said )
(that Miss Mu
had never had plastic surgery.)
(To be 100% sure,)
(we can only do DNA identification.)
How many hairs are enough for testing?
Mr. Mo,
you have this kind of hobby?
Your room is too messy
and I just clean it for you.
(Boss,)
(Xu Weilai)
(I seem to hear Miss Mu's voice.)
(Didn't she find out
we were investigating secretly?)
(Boss?)
Boss,
the results came out.
She's really Mu Liu herself.
(Result: Sister probability is 95.99%.)
Isn't that still a 4.01% probability?
Continue to check.
Boss,
I think you are different too.
Where?
Become blind.
This is probably
the power of love.
("Pollen Shop of Dream")
Power of love?
Yes.
Spare my life, boss.
Take your cartoon
and report to the Personnel Department.
Now!
(If they're the same person,)
(does she plan to share the Mu Group
with Mu Bingyun?)
Go on a date?
No.
Go to my aunt's birthday.
Don't go.
Why?
Mu Bingyun wasn't loyal
to the Mu Group,
and the Song Yuan you loved
is using you.
I loved?
Didn't you quit your marriage with me
to be with him?
Eh.
That was all in the past.
Mr. Mo,
are you
jealous?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'm just a friendly reminder.
Lest you overestimate yourself.
You keep so many secrets from me
and don't let me investigate,
then why should I listen to you?
I didn't tell you
for a reason.
What is the reason?
You took my hair
for DNA testing secretly.
And want me to believe you?
The premise of my belief
is that you should be sincere, right?
So weird.
(When you care about her,)
(you have lost.)
=Let's Go Fighting=
♪The soul falls
to the bottom of the lake♪
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪Belong to you♪