Come here, my lord.
My lady.
My lord, I feel so empty and lonely
I need a strong chest to hug.
You're not possessed, are you?
Let me take your pulse, come.
My lord.
No pulse checking but making child.
So painful.
It's me who is in pain.
My lord.
I have prepared a gift for you.
Just endure it, it'll be fine.
You abused me on our wedding night.
My lady, are you alright.
You can avoid once but not twice.
Lin, let you taste the Peach Blossom Intoxicating Fragrance.
Are you okay.
It's so hot.
Man.
Long night, sleepless.
So empty, so lonely
I need you to be with me.
Are you being frivolous or possessed.
Frivolous and possessed.
What's that sound.
Don't bother, my lord.
What are you doing?
Put out the fire.
Put out the fire?
Come on, let's continue.
Continue?
Good.
Miss Qingdai.
You knew I didn't like Xuyuan, yet you still set me up.
What, do you want my life?
Sister, you're really hitting hard.
You deserve it.
You've been stirring my relationship
with Mr. Lin from the beginning.
You even had to make a fuss on the wedding.
Have you ever thought about my feelings?
You married him without asking me.
Have you considered my feelings?
If you have objections, go back to the mountain soon.
Annoying.
No objection.
Sister, don't leave me behind
I'm wrong.
If you don't forgive me, I won't let go.
Stop.
Miss Linglong.
It's all my fault.
Don't blame her, I will take responsibility.
Responsibility?
You you you... don't talk nonsense
I'm not talking nonsense, I will definitely marry you.
Shut up.
Demon, don't harm people.
[Tong Fusu , Valiant Demon Catcher]
Quickly take Qingdai away.
Miss Qingdai.
Are you okay?
Sister.
Sister, get out of the way. I'm going to save my sister.
You look like this now, if you
go, you will only drag her down.
Sister needs me.
Miss Linglong's skill is superb,
she will definitely be fine.
The most important thing now is to take care of yourself.
First, drink the medicine.
I don't know where this smelly Taoist
came from, she had to make a scene.
And called you demons.
You don't think we are demons?
Such a beautiful lady, even if you are demons,
I will take care of you for a lifetime.
Come.
Who are you?
The person who captures you.
Show your true form quickly.
Who is it, making so much noise so early in the morning.
Stop it.
- My lord.
- Apprentice.
What do you call him?
Master.
It's a misunderstanding.
My wife is not a demon.
Apprentice.
It's tough on you, to make such a
big sacrifice for exorcising demons.
Right? She's so lovely.
I'm going to introduce you to her now.
Rest assured,
since you sincerely ask for my help,
I will definitely help you get rid of this demon.
These two are flirting with eyes,
are they in a secret relationship?
Master, let me introduce this to you.
What are you doing, Master.
Since I'm already here, you don't
have to act with these demons anymore.
Rest assured, as your master,
I will help you get rid of her.
Manifestation spell