Demon Catcher.
I neither stole nor robbed.
All I wanted is to be with the one I love, is that wrong?
Your mistake is to be born a demon.
You've transformed into a human form.
Wouldn't it be wonderful to become an immortal?
To become an immortal, don't you think I want that?
I must admit, you successfully stirred up our relationship.
If that's the case, I've nothing to worry about.
Either you die, or I perish.
This is a demon-catching sword
made from centuries-old eagle oil.
It's mainly used against snakes.
Once it's lit, it could be burning for days and nights.
But, looking at you, I doubt you'd last a week.
My lady.
My lord.
Master.
I beg you to let her go, Master.
Stop talking nonsense and get out of the way.
Master.
My wife has no malice.
You can't tell.
Demons are very cunning.
Her kindness is just to confuse you.
Master.
I assure you.
I will absolutely keep an eye on her,
and there will be no malice.
Master.
I assure you
I promise you.
Why are you so stubborn?
Even if she is a demon.
I will protect her for the rest of my life.
You will regret this sooner or later.
[Mo Jiulang, Handsome Demonic Fox]
The Golden Core of this thousand-year-old
snake demon is really superb.
If I swallow this, I will take in
a thousand years of cultivation.
You.
Crazy woman, do you have to mess up my good deeds?
You... wait for me.
Every time I see you in the future, I will beat you.
Crazy woman.
What's wrong with my wife?
Master, this is.
My lady.
Thank you, Master.
Your feelings, your marriage, you should handle it yourself
I won't make decisions for you.
I need to take this fox demon back to the tower.
There are a few words I want to say before I go.
Master, please speak.
The rules of this world have always been,
humans have human ways, demons have demon ways.
Since you have decided to live with this snake demon.
Don't be afraid to go through hardships.
This is what I owe her.
But you know she is a snake demon,
don't you have a little bit of reluctance in your heart?
Let's go.
Crazy woman.
Can't you be gentler to me?