"In This World, I Only Love You" - Tia Ray
♫  Let the heavens release a mighty thunder tribulation  ♫
♫  Leading mountains and rivers so mighty and vast to shatter before my eyes  ♫
♫  Lifetimes of cultivation bring years of splendor   ♫
♫  Yet turn to dust between fingers in an instant  ♫
♫  When immortals and demons discern good and evil with a single thought  ♫
♫  Many souls escape into the endless wilderness  ♫
♫  I journey forward with the Spirit Fire in my veins  ♫
♫  I defy fate just to remain by your side  ♫
♫  Falling thousands of feet in love is like heavy rain  ♫
♫  Pouring down between heaven and earth  ♫
♫  Drunk in love  ♫
♫  Love and hate vanish in an instant  ♫
♫  Falling into an endless abyss of love  ♫
♫  Stirring waves upending a lifetime  ♫
♫  Even if this life leads to ruin  ♫
♫  I'd still choose to be entangled with you  ♫
♫  Through all lifetimes  ♫
Chuhui has high cultivation skills, but she still failed to get in.
Someone must have meddled with the selection.
Don't be angry, Palace Master.
One of our chosen disciples is Yu Rongrong.
Her cultivation skills are passable.
If she and the chosen disciples can steal the Blood Clot Flower,
it'll provide the Moon Palace with thousands of years of cultivation.
Why not do it?
Congratulations, Palace Master.
Based on our plan, An Xue and Tan Muying were selected.
I didn't expect that slave-born Ye Ruling would also be selected.
Although she's not as good as An Xue,
she's the most gifted captive from the Demon Realm.
She'll be our second bargaining chip.
Mu Nisheng is very talented. She can complete your task.
As expected of your sisters,
Miss Xiyue and Miss Wanqing were selected.
Once they bear Sima's children,
the Spirit Fire will fall into our hands.
By then, we will only need to kill Sima Jiao
and take his place as the masters of Gengchen Immortal Mansion.
Anyone here?
This is nice.
It's not high, and it's far from Central Pagoda.
No colleagues will drop by.
I'll lay down a thick quilt here for my own luxury suite.
There's plenty of sunshine, too.
It's much better than the place I used to rent.
This Universe Pouch may be low-grade,
but it's enough for replenishing daily supplies.
Remember not to make enemies in Three Saints Mountain.
Just keep to yourself and don't try to stand out.
Master, I won't stand out.
I almost had my own funeral.
Wow, you can really hold a lot!
Such a tiny Universe Pouch can hold so many items.
If I had known earlier, I would have packed all my belongings.
There's even someone bolder here.
Being able to survive the violent Grandmaster's wrath
is truly a blessing for me.
That person from the Demon Realm that you took so much effort to send,
apart from being ordinary and being weaker than other cultivators,
there's still no news from her.
You only need to know that
she's the only one who can kill Sima Jiao.
Young Palace Master, if you have the time to probe me,
why not think of a way to use the Bone-eroding Poison in her body
to fulfill our pact sooner.
I didn't expect that I would spend my long-awaited vacation here.
She's actually sleeping.
Did Gengchen Immortal Mansion deliberately send me this useless person to provoke me,
or can they only resort to using this ploy?
They didn't even realize she was a spy from the Demon Realm.
I didn't do anything, Grandmaster.
Stupid snake.
Why would I get a headache over a mere Demon Realm woman?
It's obvious the Spirit Fire in my body is acting up.
I want to see what she's really after.
How can she sleep so soundly?
It stinks.
Let's go.
Why didn't my alarm ring?
These flowers are rather strange.
They even glow at night.
Isn't that the girl who was blasted by the Grandmaster the other day?
This is bad.
Yu Rongrong's life flame has gone out!
Return!
Fortunately, her soul hasn't scattered yet.
- Palace Master.
- I told you to be careful in what you do.
How did you die so soon?
I'm dead?
I saw many flowers at the Grandmaster's place.
I wanted to pick one, but I ended up here after that.
Could it be the Sun-moon Shade?
Palace Master Yue, fortunately, our disciples are given a chance to be reborn.
You should quickly prepare to send her for rebirth.
Two life lamps extinguished in a single day.
The Grandmaster is still as ruthless as ever.
He must still be resentful...
and has vented his hatred onto the disciples.
Do you think he cares about these disciples?
He still remembers the old scores with the Eight Great Palaces.
Back then, our fathers...
I can't bear it!
- Grandmaster!
- It's very unbearable!
- I can't bear it!
- Grandmaster.
- Remove this fire from my body!
Bear with it, Grandmaster.
You'll feel much better when the blood is released.
The Eight Great Palaces once drank his blood
and also locked him in the Three Saints Mountain for 500 years.
His hatred grows day by day.
If he didn't show any mercy to them,
just imagine if he were to confront us directly.
He'd be even more ruthless.
Palace Master Yin is right.
He's saying that we should strike first.
But...
With the Spirit Fire in his body, his power surpasses us.
If we provoke him now,
we'll only die a miserable death.
Although he has refined a Spirit Fire avatar,
but the mountain's seal is still stable.
I urge everyone not to act recklessly.
Why do you think these disciples came here?
They're just following orders from those old fools in Gengchen Immortal Mansion.
They are here to take my blood and life.
They don't even dare to come here.
That person...
swaggered in and relaxes at my place.
Grandmaster... Wait...
Grandmaster...
You were watching me.
I didn't. I'm merely cross-eyed.
I was looking...
I was looking over there!
Tell me. What are you really here for?
To adjust my work-life balance and relax.
In short, a vacation.
What's going on?
Why did my words change?
He must be behind this.
This fantasy world has harmed me.
It even has this stuff that's effective in making one tell the truth.
- Don't you want to kill me?
- I don't.
Why don't you want to kill me?
I'm just an innocent slacker.
With my cultivation level,
why would I want to kill you?
Really?
If not, then?
Do you have a phobia of being pursued and killed?
Is your brain damaged?
I'm doomed. This effect is too harmful.
Help! Are you killing me or not?
Make it a quick death!
I wouldn't dare.
Was he in seclusion for too long that he has lost his mind?
Did Gengchen Immortal Mansion make a mistake from the start?
Why send so many disciples to serve him?
They should've sent a doctor to fix his head.
Get off. Don't lick me, you rotten mutt.
Senior Brother Snake, look at my scrawny arms and legs.
Spare my life, okay?
If you eat me, I'll only get stuck in your teeth!
You want to drink this?
You should have said so earlier.
Here you go.
Sorry. I wasn't thinking properly.
Actually, this is a specialty of Serene Vale.
This Pure Spirit Bamboo keeps producing unlimited Pure Spirit Dew.
I usually drink it like milk tea.
I didn't know you liked this, too.
Why's this snake acting like a dog?
Being able to raise a giant serpent into a loyal hound,
the Grandmaster truly lives up to his name.
I managed to survive for another day.
I can't bear it!
It's unbearable!
You dare to drink something from the Demon Realm?
Tired of living, are you?
You only went there twice to eat with her
and you're speaking up for her now?
The people in this world are greedy.
Even more so for those from the Demon Realm.
They either want the Spirit Fire...
or covet the Blood Clot Flower.
She's just better at pretending than the rest.
Martial Aunt Nisheng,
Yu Rongrong from Moon Palace vanished last night.
Her body can't be found.
You can only enter this mountain and can't leave.
You can't even go back to the palace.
No one can guess the Grandmaster's temper.
Don't panic yet.
No matter what, staying alive is more important.
If one of us can win the Grandmaster's favor
and become his wife,
Heaven Palace will rise to lead the Eight Great Palaces.
As what Palace Master said, Sima Jiao is indeed cruel and lawless.
We must find his weakness and kill him as soon as possible.
The Fengshan Spirit Fire has merged with Sima Jiao.
If Sima Jiao dies, the Spirit Fire will go out, too.
As such, the Gengchen Immortal Mansion will lose its spiritual energy.
How will we cultivate?
The Blood Clot Flower is grown by the Spirit Fire
feeding on Sima Jiao's blood.
Eating this flower and drinking his blood
will raise our cultivation level.
Have you forgotten what the Palace Master said?
Back then, he offended Sima Jiao.
If one day, Sima Jiao is unhappy and wants to settle old scores,
we'll all die a tragic death.
What's there left to cultivate?
You called me here just to discuss this impossible task?
Ye Ruling, stop acting like it's none of your business.
Don't forget that your clan is still under the Palace Master's control.
I've prepared this for Senior Brother Snake.
I hope he won't wake me tonight.
Let me have a good night's sleep.
Why does this feel so familiar?
Do cultivators get period cramps, too?
It's so painful.
Why is the pain getting worse?
Didn't Ming Li say this Companion Bell can trigger
Liao Tingyan's Bone-eroding Poison?
Why isn't she showing any reaction after being summoned by it?
Does she really think that by clinging to Sima Jiao,
she can escape our control?
Fine.
Let's see how long you can survive this Bone-eroding Poison.
Stupid snake.
What did you bring back?
She's been poisoned by a demonic poison.
Why do you want to save her?
Do you know what she's here for?
You don't know anything, but you brought her here?
Are you seeking death?
This poison is just a small trick from the Demon Realm to control puppets.
She actually fell asleep.
Among all the countless schemes sent by the Demon Realm,
they sent someone like this?
Looks like she's smarter than those other fools.
Not only did she come to seek death in front of me,
she even won over that stupid snake.
Such deep scheming...
suits this face.
Grandmaster...
Why am I in your hall?
Your acting is not bad.
You dared to use that stupid snake to bring you to my Central Pagoda.
I could have fainted last night from the stomach pain.
I guess Senior Brother Snake was worried and wanted you to save me.
I didn't mean to trouble you.
My stomach doesn't hurt anymore?
You drank my blood.
Of course, it won't hurt.
I drank your blood?
If you dare to spit it out, I'll kill you.
Your blood even works as a painkiller?
Not only does it ease pain,
it boosts cultivation, too.
Everyone in this world wants it.
Count me out.
I'm not that interested.
Looking at you now
makes me want to kill you immediately.
No... Don't... I... I will dirty your hands...
If it hurts that much,
why didn't you just kill me?
There's no reason, nor grudge.
In this world, killing doesn't need a grudge,
much less a reason.
Like right now,
there's no grudge, nor reason.
I just want to kill you.
What can you do about it?
I can't do anything.
I can't defeat you anyway.
You want me to kill you,
but I won't.
From now on,
you'll serve me.
Me?
I'm leaving now.
No grudge...
Nor reason...
So, she doesn't want to kill me?
Everyone in Gengchen Immortal Mansion is after my blood.
If not for the fact that only I can feed the Spirit Fire,
if not for the Spirit Fire nourishing the whole palace,
if not for the fact they can't defeat me,
I would have been torn apart and eaten up.
The Demon Realm has always wanted to destroy Gengchen Immortal Mansion
and extinguish the Spirit Fire.
They should want to kill me.
So, why...
doesn't she want to kill me?
After such a nerve-racking day,
I may not be able to sleep well tonight.
Ridiculous.
The answers from the Oath of Truth won't be false.
If she truly has no intention to kill,
perhaps I can use her.
500 years...
The night of the new moon.
Martial Aunt,
we've waited here every day,
but this door has never opened for us.
Will Grandmaster really see us?
Are you as shallow as those people?
If you're afraid, just leave.
No, Martial Aunt.
I just don't know how to face Grandmaster.
The Palace Master once said that, in front of this grandmaster,
it's impossible to hide anything.
We only need to show our most humble and devout posture,
and reveal our thoughts to him.
As long as I keep trying,
the Grandmaster will be moved by me.
Senior Brother Snake really meant well, but created trouble.
I haven't even rested well for a few days,
and it's back to work again.
I'm here to pay respects to you.
Please accept me, Grandmaster.
She's a brave one.
She even took the initiative to request that moody Grandmaster.
No wonder she can lead the group.
Her level of awareness is amazing.
If only I could trade places with her.
Hi.
You're still alive?
What's wrong with you people today?
You even say this when you see me.
I don't want to die.
I'm staying alive.
If you want to stay alive,
keep your distance.
I would love to.
What's wrong with the Grandmaster?
He wants me to work here and doesn't give me an access card.
How am I supposed to get in?
Martial Aunt, she probably doesn't know the Grandmaster's temper.
Should we warn her?
Is there a need to meddle?
We're the only ones here who can be safe.
I fear she will die under the pagoda today.
Grandmaster, I'm here to work!
How... How is this possible?
Just knock on the door to enter?
How did she go in just now?
I wonder what the Grandmaster wants me to do.
What's in that bag?
These are my daily essentials.
I took them out of my Universe Pouch,
but I don't really know spiritual power.
I can only take things out, not put them in.
Put down your junk and follow me.
Grandmaster, is that person outside dead?
What do you think?
Why did you kill her?
Compared to those who are greedy at a glance,
I hate those mindless puppets without souls the most.
Killing her didn't even interest me.
Why then?
She was too noisy...
and irritated me.
He kills over annoyance?
This grandmaster is really crazy.
I'm exhausted.
This is more tiring than the subway during rush hour.
Can't walk anymore?
Grandmaster, why are we climbing so high? What are we doing?
We are not doing anything.
Looks like he's just too bored
and wants to taunt me to death.
At least, I was still a human in my old job.
In this current cultivation world,
I'm just a toy of the boss.
Start by cleaning this floor.
I'll admit, the view here is pretty nice.
It's just that the Grandmaster's mood swings
ruin the work experience.
But after being confined for 500 years alone in this pagoda,
it's also not strange that his mind is twisted.
Grandmaster, look at how hardworking I am!
I'm working!
Senior Brother Snake, it's you.
I thought the boss was here to check. You scared me.
What's this about?
Are you taking me somewhere?
Or has the Grandmaster done something again?
He abandoned me here just now
and didn't tell me what my working hours are.
Are you taking me straight to him?
If he's not sealed, he'll wipe out the whole immortal mansion.
The Spirit Fire has merged with him.
As long as we keep him alive,
he can supply us with spiritual energies.
Why not add another seal on top of this restriction?
This restriction connects his meridians and suppresses him. He won't be able to kill himself.
No matter how painful it is, he can't seek death.
Grandmaster, spare my life! I didn't do anything.
Your pet brought me in here.
Grandmaster.
My spiritual power is too weak.
I can't help you.
Why don't I knock off work early?
What on earth is going on?
Grandmaster,
are you having a fever?
Let me check.
♫  Gripping tightly on the rope to the other shore  ♫
♫  Unclear, confusing, a persistent obsession is brewing  ♫
♫  And condensed into the spiritual treasure of amber  ♫
♫  Gazing at the leaves falling in front of me  ♫
♫  I borrowed a brush and black ink  ♫
Grandmaster, let me explain.
Your pet brought me in here.
I didn't mean to offend you at all.
She can actually ease
the burning pain from my Spirit Fire.
♫  To overcome the sufferings and break through  ♫
♫  The laws of Heaven, the vortex of reincarnation  ♫
♫  What does life and death matter?  ♫
♫  To save you, to save me  ♫
♫  To save all beings, I let the matter pass  ♫
♫  Be it right or wrong, rumor or legend  ♫
♫  I seize fate with my own hands  ♫
"Swimming Across the Vast Ocean" by Hu Xia
♫  The autumn winds sigh  ♫
♫  The sky is speckled with moon and stars  ♫
♫  The fingers are stained by the loneliness of past lives  ♫
♫  The candlelight flickers  ♫
♫  The shadow sways  ♫
♫  The light flashes in the night  ♫
♫  With a brush  ♫
♫  I sketch the colors of light  ♫
♫  To tenderly warm your frozen soul  ♫
♫  The memories anchor  ♫
♫  The longing is engraved  ♫
♫  Yet they can't be touched  ♫
♫  Following  ♫
♫  The veins of strands of sand  ♫
♫  I turned into Spirit Fire  ♫
♫  And burned  ♫
♫  All those karmic ties  ♫
♫  To save you  ♫
♫  To save me  ♫
♫  To overcome the sufferings and break through  ♫
♫  The laws of Heaven  ♫
♫  The vortex of reincarnation  ♫
♫  What does life and death matter?  ♫
♫  To save you  ♫
♫  To save me  ♫
♫  To save all beings, I let the matter pass  ♫
♫  Be it right or wrong  ♫
♫  Rumor or legend  ♫
♫  With fate in my hands  ♫
♫  I seize it  ♫
♫  For you  ♫
♫  For me  ♫
♫  For the healing of wounds  ♫
♫  I fight the murky sea  ♫
♫  And Heaven  ♫
♫  To complete this vastness  ♫
♫  For you  ♫
♫  For me  ♫
♫  For the first rays of morning sun to shine through  ♫
♫  To face my promises  ♫
♫  Like a moth attracted by a flame  ♫
♫  I use my body to shine even more  ♫