♫ Heavens strike with thunderous wrath ♫
♫ Mountains and rivers shatter before my eyes ♫
♫ Endless splendor
cultivated through lifetimes ♫
♫ Turns to dust between my fingers
in an instant ♫
♫ When the line
between good and evil is clear ♫
♫ Countless souls drift
into the boundless wilds ♫
♫ Carrying the spirit fire forward ♫
♫ I defy fate ♫
♫ Just to remain by your side ♫
♫ Falling into love's abyss ♫
♫ Like heavy rain pouring down ♫
♫ Drunk on romance ♫
♫ In a blink, love and hate
vanish into illusion ♫
♫ Falling into endless love ♫
♫ Stirring waves upending a lifetime ♫
♫ Even if this life leads to ruin ♫
♫ I still choose to be entangled with you ♫
♫ Through all lifetimes ♫
♫ Snow not gone, flame not out ♫
♫ Prism of three lifetimes ♫
♫ You, untouched by moon's regrets ♫
♫ No one reaches, no one hears ♫
♫ Thousands of stars in your eyes ♫
♫ Fall like fireworks ♫
♫ No fate's tangle, no parting swans ♫
♫ Memories fade ♫
♫ We wander the mortal world in search ♫
♫ Yet forget the reason why ♫
♫ Cycle back to raging flames ♫
♫ Even if my very soul were to vanish ♫
♫ Be it destiny or doom,
I light up the endless night ♫
♫ To chase the darkness away from your dreams ♫
♫ Even if heaven and earth turned to ash ♫
♫ I would never regret the day I met you ♫
Cold...
So cold...
Cold... So cold...
It isn't cold today.
Why is she so cold?
How could there be such
strong cold energy inside her?
- So cold...
- Where is this cold energy coming from?
Let me hold that for you.
It's fine.
This flower looks nice, too.
Lord Hei.
I already made it clear to you
last time, didn't I?
Yes, you did.
You said forcing a melon off the vine
never tastes sweet.
So, what are your intentions now?
What are you trying to do?
These are melons I grabbed from
the Celestial Palace disciples' herb garden.
They're very sweet.
Try some.
- It is sweet.
- Right?
But I don't care.
What are you going to do about it?
Wait. Where are you sending this?
To the Grandmistress's room.
She said the flowers and plants
from Grain Rain Vale look different
from those outside and very beautiful,
so I was assigned to deliver them.
You intend to just pick them
and send them as is?
I was careless for a moment.
How could we send them
without preparing them first?
Have you forgotten our rules
for hosting guests?
Who's there?
Watch your step.
Oh, you're among the Grandmistress's friends.
What did you mean by preparing them?
These flowers and plants need to be tidied up
before they can be presented
as a gift to the Grandmistress.
That's the proper etiquette.
Who made these silly rules?
I'm not sure, but it's always been that way.
What I mean is
I think the flowers this disciple picked
are beautiful as they are.
I believe the Grandmistress
would be pleased with them no matter what.
Yes, I'm sure Ting Yan isn't that fussy.
She might not be particular,
but we should still show our sincerity.
The rules of the Celestial Palace
are so strict.
As someone from the Demon Realm,
I just don't get it.
They look exactly the same as before to me.
Isn't this just unnecessary?
Never mind.
We won't bother you two any longer.
Excuse us.
Let's go.
Did you sleep well?
No, I feel so cold.
Did anything unusual happen
after I left yesterday?
Yesterday?
Nothing.
I just suddenly felt very cold.
Feng Qi said some strange things to me.
Something about me having been here before.
I'm going to find him.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Don't tell me you're going to
pick a fight with him?
Your cold energy has suddenly grown stronger.
I suspect this isn't a coincidence.
There's something strange going on.
I think Feng Qi is hiding something from us.
I'll use a Truth Spell to find out.
Don't do it.
You have issues with Feng Qi already.
I don't want you two to fight again.
If there's something to ask, I'll go.
By yourself?
It'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Grandmaster.
Nian Jiu.
Have you noticed anything strange here
these past few days?
Hong Luo and I saw Su Chang Qing
have someone tidy up
the flowers and plants for Ting Yan.
It seemed unnecessary,
and they worried Ting Yan might not be pleased
and blame them.
But Ting Yan isn't the picky type.
And for Su Chang Qing to be Ting Yan's senior,
he ought to know her better.
Check around there again, discreetly.
See if there's anything else unusual.
But didn't you already use
the Truth Spell on them last time
and find nothing wrong?
That's true.
Though the Truth Spell can compel someone
to speak the truth,
its effect is limited to what they know.
Understood.
These flowers look a bit odd,
but they're just ordinary flowers.
These flowers and plants need to be tidied up
before they can be presented
as a gift to the Grandmistress.
What secret are they trying to hide?
No wonder they're using spiritual power
to tend these flowers.
Something must be wrong
with the plants around here.
Has Sima Jiao grown suspicious?
Everything is proceeding smoothly
as you said, Preceptor.
That's good to hear.
Preceptor.
I trust you won't harm Yan,
so I'm following your plan.
Will Yan's memories return?
Of course.
This benefits both you and me.
Things are going well so far.
Mr. Feng, you need only find a chance
to tell Shi Yan the cost of that anklet.
Then she'll remove it herself.
I understand.
Someone's coming.
Yan!
Grandmaster.
Good. Everyone's here.
Ting Yan and I plan to stay a while longer
and open a few more spirit veins
for Grain Rain Vale as a reward.
Grandmaster, you're too courteous.
That...
That reward is too generous for us to accept.
Not at all.
Back at the Celestial Palace,
I once allocated you a spirit vein as well.
Of course.
You took good care of me back then.
I will never forget that kindness.
We will always remember your favor.
I'm sure Dongyang Zhenren
remembers this well.
Indeed.
The air here is so fresh.
It's been a long time
since I last smelled anything like this.
Even the stones in Grain Rain Vale
seem to give off a faint fragrance.
Did... Did I crush the stones too hard
and break them?
That's impossible.
This waterfall holds the bond
you've had since childhood.
Over the years,
while you were away,
it slowly infused itself into the stones.
Now that you're back, it has returned as well.
I've lived here before?
This lake is where you grew up.
But I'm not a fish.
There's no way I lived in the water.
Did you remember something?
Remember what?
Yan.
You were once a Frost Fish.
That's why you have the extreme-cold nature.
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
I'm not.
Back then, You Chi feared my father's power
and plotted against him,
wiping out my entire clan.
Preceptor Ming Li,
seeing I still had a breath of life,
secretly cast me into this lake,
leaving me a chance to survive.
It was then
that you appeared.
I wonder how things are on Ting Yan's side.
But I have no memories of what you said.
But I remember it all.
You were once a Frost Fish,
but Demon Lord You Chi
forged you into a human form.
By chance, you saved me here.
You even tore off
a scale from your chest to save me.
How could I ever forget such a bond?
You say I saved you?
Do you think I'm the woman
you've been searching for?
It's not what I think.
It's that you are indeed her.
I'm sorry.
I'm not the one you're looking for.
It's all right.
Maybe you just haven't remembered yet.
If you stay here a few more days,
you'll recover your past memories soon.
You mean this place
can help me regain my memories?
That's right.
That has been my wish all along.
So, Feng Qi intentionally brought me here
to help me recover my memories
when I was a Frost Fish?
If you can remember Sima Jiao,
you can surely remember me.
That's a different matter.
The person you seek likely vanished long ago,
their soul scattered to the winds.
That's why I am what I am now.
Those memories won't be mine.
Do you understand
what I mean?
Yan.
Yan!
Grandmaster, there's definitely something odd
with the flowers and plants here.
Look.
It's like they've been
corrupted by demonic energy.
Then what about the cold energy inside me?
Feng Qi told me I'm a Frost Fish raised here.
Could the recent surge in my cold energy
be due to this place's influence?
Did he really say
you were raised here as a Frost Fish?
Yes.
Cold energy and demonic energy.
Grain Rain Vale is supposed to be
a blessed sanctuary within the Demon Realm.
How could it be more complicated
than the outside world?
Dongyang Zhenren and the disciples
from the Immortal Realm all live here.
Surely they wouldn't settle
in a place filled with strife.
Unless my master and those here lied to us.
But Grandmaster,
you already used the Truth Spell on them.
As I've said, the Truth Spell
can compel someone to speak the truth,
but it isn't flawless.
What do you mean?
Just now, I questioned them
about the Celestial Palace.
There were discrepancies in the details
compared to what
the real Dongyang Zhenren would say.
Do you remember
Shi Qian Du's death?
The Soul Cleanse?
Could Shi Qian Lv be behind all this?
Did he cleanse the souls of the people here?
The cold energy Ting Yan suddenly emitted
mostly came from the food at the banquet.
That was when I started suspecting
something strange about this place.
This duck meat is delicious
and seems very nourishing.
It feels like it's restoring my energy.
Ever since I entered Grain Rain Vale,
my body has grown increasingly uncomfortable.
It must be the cold energy
from Ting Yan's anklet affecting me.
To manipulate
your cold constitution so strongly,
while simultaneously
spreading demonic corruption
to all the plants and creatures here,
there's only one place
in the entire Demon Realm capable of that.
What is all of this?
Where are we?
Who are you?
Alas, we've been found out.
Shi Qian Lv's Soul Cleanse is truly formidable.
You've even forgotten your own master.
Mr. Ghost.
We never came to Grain Rain Vale.
This is actually the Demon Realm's core,
White Bone Abyss.
So, everything here has been a lie.
Who could have plotted so meticulously
to trick us here?
No one else but the Demon Lord and Ming Li
could wield such power in White Bone Abyss.
Preceptor, Sima Jiao
is not to be underestimated.
This Grain Rain Vale is a flawless illusion
we created together
using Shi Qian Lv's Soul Cleanse.
- Even so, he has seen through it now.
- No matter.
Since we've lured Sima Jiao and Liao Ting Yan
into White Bone Abyss,
everything is under our control.
Precisely.
That Frost Fish
still wears the defensive anklet
made from his heart-protecting bone.
They certainly wouldn't expect
your two-birds-one-stone strategy.
The Frost Fish's defensive anklet
channels cold energy
that backlashes onto Sima Jiao,
severely restricting his cultivation.
If the Frost Fish removes the anklet
to save Sima Jiao,
it will give us an opening to capture her.
Right now, the priority is to bring
Liao Ting Yan here to refine the frost stone.
Then we can kill Sima Jiao
and take his blood in one strike.
- What's wrong?
- Grandmaster, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Ming Li's people will be here soon.
You should leave with Nian Jiu first.
The Demon Realm will unleash
their full strength against you.
You can't take on all of them alone.
I'll go get Hong Luo.
Nian Jiu will go with you.
I'm stronger than before.
Don't underestimate me.
Besides, I still have the anklet you gave me.
I'll be fine.
All right.
Wait for me.
Sima Jiao, how have you
been recovering at Grain Rain Vale?
Cut the chatter.
Hong Luo!
Grandmaster.
Ting Yan's cold energy can,
through the defensive anklet
made from your heart-protecting bone,
retaliate against your cultivation
and limit your powers.
Hong Luo!
- Hong Luo!
- Yan!
Yan.
Something's wrong here. Are you all right?
Was all of this part of your plan?
What do you mean? I'm just worried about you.
Did you collude
with the Demon Realm and Shi Qian Lv
to lure me into this Grain Rain Vale illusion?
What's your goal?
I have no intention to harm you.
I only want to awaken the memories between us.
I told you, I'm not your Frost Fish.
Yan, I can explain!
This concerns Sima Jiao's safety.
Don't you want to know?
What's wrong with Sima Jiao?
Perhaps you noticed.
Sima Jiao's cultivation weakening
and his body acting strangely
since arriving here.
It's related to the artifact on your foot.
Impossible.
He forged this defensive artifact for me.
It can block all harm.
You should know this artifact is made
from his heart-protecting bone.
It shields you from damage,
which doesn't hurt him,
but your cold energy clashes with his.
The White Bone Abyss triggers your cold energy.
It makes you uncomfortable,
but since you're a Frost Fish,
it won't actually harm you.
Yet your accumulating cold energy
backlashes onto his body through your anklet.
What's wrong?
Grandmaster, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Yan, you'd risk yourself for him?
Who's there?
Grandmaster. Nian Jiu.
Hong Luo, what are you doing here?
Where's Ting Yan?
Wasn't she with you?
This isn't good.
This is bad.
She removed the defensive anklet.
Nian Jiu, get Hong Luo out of here first.
Hong Luo, I'll get you out
and return to help him.
All right.
Yan.
Father.
Your leg...
So, even your injury was a lie.
You manipulated my guilt
to make me your tool for revenge.
You've disappointed me.
Qian Du was right.
Raising you was a waste of time.
If I meant anything to you as your daughter,
you wouldn't have done this to me.
You were behind
the Grain Rain Vale illusion too,
weren't you?
Yan, I devoted my life's learning to you.
But it still couldn't match Sima Jiao's skill
in swaying hearts.
So be it.
Feng Qi.
Yan, please believe me.
I would never harm you.
Are you really going to choose his side?
I don't care about your past.
I just want her memories restored.
Do not hurt her.
Leave her to me.
Preceptor and I still need her
to fight Sima Jiao.
Rest assured, Mr. Feng.
The best way to recover her memories
is to send her to the Guiyuan Chamber
deep within White Bone Abyss.
That's where the cold energy is strongest.
It will awaken her cold constitution.
When she returns, you'll have the Frost Fish
who's recovered everything.
But Sima Jiao
is incredibly difficult to deal with.
He watches Yan every moment
without letting her out of his sight.
What if Sima Jiao is actually willing
to bring her here?
What do you mean?
Shi Yan's father told me
she's always dreamed of Grain Rain Vale,
a sanctuary revered in the Demon Realm.
Why don't we embellish it
and create a Grain Rain Vale illusion for her?
How could that be possible?
You don't need to worry about that.
Just bring your Frost Fish there.
Yan, I'm sorry. I lied to you.
You're not truly yourself right now.
When you regain your Frost Fish memories,
you'll understand why I did what I did.
Is that General Chang Zhi
standing next to the Preceptor?
No, that's Feng Qi,
the orphaned son of General Chang Zhi.
Ming Li.
You, as Preceptor, dare to betray your lord?
I'm loyal to the former Demon Lord.
I don't consider this a betrayal.
You want to use my blood
to resurrect that old beast?
Insolence!
Subjects of the Demon Realm,
welcome the return of the former Demon Lord.
Welcome the return of the former Demon Lord.
What a joke.
You think
your words alone make it true?
Is this how the descendants
of the You family behave? Arrogant and useless?
Old fool! I'm still
the Lord of the Demon Realm!
How dare you disrespect me...
Not willing to surrender
your demonic body to me?
But as a descendant of the You family,
this is your fate.
Your demonic soul
has been in this body long enough.
Too long to matter anymore.
How's the progress on the Xingtian Chain?
My Lord.
Speak.
The frost stone is still
undergoing intensive refinement.
Soon, it will let us
kill Sima Jiao in one strike.
We can't afford any mistakes
with the Xingtian Chain.
Yes, I shall head to supervise now.
The Frost Fish assassin,
once devoted to the Demon Lord,
has now become rebellious because of Sima Jiao.
Sect Master Shi, thanks to your help,
we've succeeded.
I had asked you to rest earlier,
but you insisted
on guarding the Guiyuan Chamber.
Preceptor, the success of the Xingtian Chain
is crucial for our revenge plan.
There mustn't be a single slip-up.
Are you driven by revenge,
or are you reluctant
to see your fake daughter suffer?
You're overthinking.
I excel at marrow cleansing
and can use theG uiyuan Chamber's
cold energy here
to aid the froststone's refining.
In that case, I thank you for your assistance.
Preceptor, Sima Jiao is charging in.
He's rushing to his death.
Sect Master Shi, I'll handle Sima Jiao.
I leave this to you.
Understood.
Revenge is within reach.
Don't blame me for being ruthless.
Sima Jiao, the former Demon Lord's
blood sacrifice
and return are inevitable for the Demon Race.
You alone can't stop it.
You Yan's true vessel has been shattered
by the Sima clan's Spirit Fire.
Yet you still dream of resurrection.
Return Liao Ting Yan,
and I'll grant you an honorable death.
You're too late.
By now, she's probably
been refined into frost stone.
I'll use it to kill you soon.
It will be complete any moment now!
I won't let that happen!
Ting Yan!
Sect Master Shi!
How much longer
until the Xingtian Chain is ready?
It's been a while, Grandmaster.
I've let you live too long.
I'm glad I raised a good daughter.
Given your current relationship,
shouldn't you be addressing me as Father?
The frost stone isn't fully refined yet.
Coming here armed with that pathetic relic,
you're asking for your own demise!
Grandmaster, I'll take care of Ming Li!
♫ Dye the moon and sky in crimson light ♫
♫ We'll shatter destined paths ♫
♫ Through illusion's trials ♫
♫ Awaken silent souls to tremble ♫
♫ Transform our parting's elegy ♫
♫ Strength bows to nature's law alone ♫
60% of the cold energy already clings
to the Xingtian Chain.
With this, I can severely injure you.
♫ Rewrite the starry tides of time ♫
♫ Dye the moon and sky in crimson light ♫
♫ We'll shatter destined paths ♫
♫ Through illusion's trials ♫
♫ Awaken silent souls to tremble ♫
♫ Transform our parting's elegy ♫
♫ Strength bows to nature's law alone ♫
♫ So what if we perish? ♫
Do you really think
your petty tricks can kill me?
Do you think I'm ignorant enough
to survive over a thousand years
without realizing this?
Sima Jiao, I know you're stalling here
to buy time for Liao Ting Yan's escape.
But even if she escapes the Guiyuan Chamber,
can she escape her fate?
Her destiny ceased to be yours to control
the moment she met me.
Ceased to be ours to control?
If it's not ours to decide,
then is it yours?
Her destiny
is hers alone to decide.
Nian Jiu!
Wake up!
Sima Jiao, don't you see?
Anyone close to you
can't control their own fate.
Your birth and the existence
of the Fengshan Clan
are all but a joke.
You're only fit to be locked away,
turned into blood slaves and puppets!
You're unworthy
to rule the Immortal-Demon world!
The extreme cold energy has awakened
her Frost Fish instincts.
Her body betrays her will.
Sima Jiao, do you think
her nature can overcome her feelings for you?
Ting Yan.
♫ In the world of madness,
love burdened with greed ♫
It's done.
♫ Branded with scars too raw to hide ♫
♫ Helpless to resist,
partings always catch us off guard ♫
♫ This budding love is then severed ♫
♫ The tale of fate keeps winding on ♫
♫ I'm unafraid though memories are gone ♫
♫ Through karma's journey,
all lifetimes share one gaze ♫
Look! The blood core
is merging into the blood pool!
It's the blood of Fengshan!
Congratulations, Demon Lord!
The Xingtian Chain is indeed working wonders.
Once the blood pool fills,
the blood sacrifice can begin.
Sima Jiao!
Sima Jiao...
♫ The tale of fate keeps winding on ♫
I'm sorry... I...
I couldn't control myself...
I'm sorry...
I...
I didn't mean to hurt you...
I know.
I don't know what happened... I...
♫ Through every trial we've endured ♫
♫ No matter who has sought the cure ♫
Sima Jiao...
♫ Then wish upon the stars ♫
No...
♫ Reborn beyond souls ♫
Sima Jiao, wake up!
No!
♫ Autumn winds sigh ♫
♫ Moon and stars dapple the sky ♫
♫ Brushing the loneliness of bygone days ♫
♫ Candlelight flickers low ♫
♫ Shadows sway ♫
♫ Shimmering in the night ♫
♫ With a brush I draw ♫
♫ The color of light ♫
♫ To warm your frozen soul ♫
♫ Memories anchor here ♫
♫ Longing is engraved ♫
♫ Yet cannot be touched ♫
♫ Following ♫
♫ The veins of gravel ♫
♫ I turn into spirit fire ♫
♫ Burning away ♫
♫ All these karmic ties ♫
♫ To save you ♫
♫ To save me ♫
♫ To cross over all suffering,
I'll break through ♫
♫ The laws of heaven ♫
♫ The vortex of reincarnation ♫
♫ What of life and death? ♫
♫ To save you ♫
♫ To save me ♫
♫ To redeem all beings, I'll let pass ♫
♫ Right and wrong ♫
♫ Rumors and tales ♫
♫ To seize fate ♫
♫ With my own hands ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ For me ♫
♫ For the healing of wounds ♫
♫ I'll stir the murky seas ♫
♫ And strive against the heavens ♫
♫ To protect the vastness ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ For me ♫
♫ For the light of dawn ♫
♫ I'll face promises ♫
♫ Like a moth to a flame ♫
♫ And use my body to shine ♫
♫ On even more ♫