The King's Avatar
Episode 15
You miss love every day.
No wonder your people have no progress in cultivation.
Yes.
I'm now able to coax the Shi clan.
I can finally clear the fire.
Since you have great cultivation,
can I also be a water-slinging sparring partner?
Why did you apply the water-slinging sparring partner on your face?
I'm making a mask.
When I had weak cultivation, the mask would easily fall off.
Now that I have improved my cultivation,
the mask can also be put on my face.
What's the use of this?
It keeps the skin moist.
It seems that my spiritual power is still enough to make up.
Senior Brother said that this is to treat the injury of falling down.
It's not necessarily a correct answer.
But it's definitely fine to use it as a bandage.
While the Shi clan is not awake, let's go out and play.
I can't go out of Bai Lu Cliff, can I?
It's been 500 years.
This is the first time
I've had a moment of sleep.
Is it because of him?
He has a headache again.
It really hurts.
It's because his head hurts too much
that he doesn't care about the injury on his hand.
Maybe compared to the injury on his hand,
the pain on his hand is nothing.
It's nothing.
Father.
I...
For the sake of your service,
I can give you a vacation.
Or do you want
to go to the temple to see the spirits?
I'm not that kind of person.
I want to see the spirits.
Why?
I can't wait to see them.
I have to go to see them.
Senior Brother,
what's up?
Ning Yan, here.
This is the letter Ru Ling told me to bring you.
You went to see Ru Ling behind my back.
Did Ru Ling say anything?
and the beautiful scenery.
What about me?
Did Ru Ling ask me out?
I don't think so.
It said I can go alone.
It's almost 6 o'clock.
Am I leaving?
Snake, what's wrong?
Ting Yan.
Since Ru Ling gave me my snake heart,
I don't know why
I always...
I always miss Ru Ling's breath.
Ru Ling didn't do anything to your snake heart.
She always wears it
and at most, it's her scent.
Then why did I become a human?
I know.
It's your heart that fell in love with her breath.
That's why you became a human.
Then, Ting Yan, what should I do?
How can I make Ru Ling fall in love with me?
I don't know.
Snake, you just became a human.
You don't know
that the relationship between people
needs to be cultivated slowly.
Why don't you become a teacher in Ru Ling?
Then you can stay with your master
and be with him.
But I already have a master.
How can I become a teacher in Ru Ling?
My master will definitely disagree.
You're like a brother to him.
He won't say no to such a small thing.
I'm just a snake.
How can I be with my master?
Don't worry.
My master is just not good at expressing himself.
You're still very important to him.
I'm leaving.
I...
Master.
I wasuku Shrine
You asked Ting Yan away?
Yes.
What did she comes out for?
Master.
Ting Yan asked me to tell you
that she went to search for Ru Ling.
She learnt to منage something first and then leave.
Who reported to Ye Ru Ling?
A disciple.
What should you do?
I don't think he has any problem.
He should be fine.
But he has a son called Yuan Shang.
I don't know if he's his weakness.
What else?
I have a favor to ask.
I want to...
Go ahead.
I want to be a teacher in the forest.
I hope you can approve of it.
You think too highly of someone.
Don't get more annoyed at me
if you take this little thing on your own in the future.
Thank you, participated in the act of private role.
Thank you, agreed.
So it's just the right balance.
Not even a little difference between the balance and something,
This is the sky of wisdom?
It's so beautiful.
It's like the aurora.
The colorful light in the eyes of the common people
is a proof that I can't get away with it.
Mother,
are we really going to stay here forever?
After the battle of Xiemo,
we were enslaved by the Eagle King
from the son of the Demon King Fulu
to be punished.
I thought that the new princess
was a good person
and gave her to me.
I never thought that after you were born,
you would still live with me
in this dirty place.
Now,
the Sima Clan is left alone.
But if she suffers again,
the barrier between the Demon and the Sword will disappear.
We can return to the ancient map.
Mother,
is there no other way to return to the ancient map?
Are we going to our hometown?
The place of the cold.
It's said that the cold place of the Demon Kingdom
can also take us through the barrier.
In fact,
if we can cross the barrier
and go to the Demon Realm,
we can see the scene of the aurora.
It's more beautiful than now.
That's the best place to watch the view.
Can we go there?
Ting Yan, you...
Anshu Zhu Ling, be careful.
It's as painful as a book store.
You're still thinking about me at this time.
Ting Yan,
how did you get hurt by this barrier?
Didn't you say that
you have the special system of the cold?
Did you lose your mind?
No.
Why do you ask?
Nothing.
It's my fault. I forgot to remind you.
After the two wars between the Demon and the Sword,
the Sima clan set up this barrier with fire
to stop the two wars between the Demon and the Sword.
So,
no one from the Xian Mansion and the Demon Kingdom
can cross this barrier.
No wonder it's so powerful.
It hurts.
You're not hurt, are you?
Let me see.
Why does the cold body of Ting Yan
have no reaction to the barrier?
Father,
I found out that Yuan Shang has been
often acting in the area near Bai Lu Cliff.
Bai Lu Cliff?
What is he doing there?
He seems to be waiting for someone.
He dared to make a poem
under the eyes of Sima Jiao.
He thinks that his life is too long.
How about this?
If he can die in Bai Lu Cliff,
he can just give this matter
to Sima Jiao.
Xun,
you're really smart.
You're really something.
Keep watching.
Find a chance
to let Sima Jiao do it first,
and then we'll do it.
Okay.
What's so good about him?
Oh my god.
You Lan.
If he didn't do it last time,
there wouldn't be a case like this.
It's
right to be bad.
By McCaskill,
he should be grabbed by him.
He's still here.
Why bother to do it Tay guys,
You even placed the
one
think
you
I'm sorry.
You really made me wait.
I finally sent a letter to you.
I contacted you twice.
But you didn't come.
You didn't even send me back
half a year's message.
It seems that you are really a high-ranking officer.
You're going to break up with me, right?
What kind of emotional speech is this?
It's like the man found out that the woman changed his mind.
He didn't answer the phone and didn't reply to the message.
Finally, after meeting, the woman knew that the man had complained.
She was going to fight.
What's wrong?
You dare not talk?
Si Ma Jiao may come to watch the show with me.
I have to be careful.
It's over between us.
Don't come to me again.
Good.
You really broke up.
But don't forget that
your life is still in my hands.
How is it?
Did you feel better
when you were poisoned by the stone bone yesterday?
I... I...
Why did you come again?
It hurts.
I was so jealous of you.
You are so hateful.
How can you have a girlfriend
with a strange drug-controlling man?
You are worse than that stupid Si Ma Jiao.
You are so arrogant.
Come on.
I will break up the love for you today.
You...
You dare to talk to me like this?
Aren't you afraid of death?
Okay.
I will help you.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
Did Si Ma Jiao
detoxify you?
Impossible.
If she detoxifies you,
she will know your identity.
She will kill you if she knows your identity.
What identity?
An innocent girl who was cheated by her ex-boyfriend?
Who is the ex-girlfriend?
You are still pretending to be confused with me.
You forgot the task I told you before?
Why didn't you kill her?
You don't want to kill me?
No.
Why don't you want to kill me?
Since it's so painful,
why don't you kill me?
I am already badly injured.
This is a good chance
for you.
Your cultivation has reached the化神机 stage.
So,
do you want to kill me?
No wonder.
It's not Si Ma Jiao who is suspicious.
It's the original owner of this body.
He really took the three holy mountains
with him to kill himself.
Since he knew it,
why didn't he kill me?
Si Ma Jiao is wise and wise.
He is broad-minded.
How could he be angry with me
for such a small thing?
Okay.
Si Ma Jiao doesn't care about your identity.
What about the others in the Chen's Mansion?
If the chief comes,
or other princesses find out your identity,
do you think Si Ma Jiao will protect you?
Are you threatening me?
What identity?
Don't talk nonsense.
I won't kill Si Ma Jiao because of you.
Wait.
I still have your soul.
Although I can't control you now,
as long as I have him...
I just thought about it.
Why did he come to me?
Go on.
What if he comes?
I'll kill you.
You can't even defeat Yuan Ying.
I did nothing.
I...
I'm so powerful?
You're just a little trainee.
Why are you so strong today?
I'm a god now.
A god?
A man is not a smart thing
to arrange such a spy.
Si Ma Jiao.
I've done so much for you.
Don't think that you can't reveal your identity
if you kill me.
Who's the first one to do it?
Can you stop acting?
I didn't want to kill you.
Stop.
You betrayed me
because you fell in love with Si Ma Jiao?
I'm not useless.
Don't talk nonsense.
What if Si Ma Jiao is listening to the wall?
What if I think I like him?
Ridiculous.
Even if you fall in love with him...
Shut up.
Don't talk nonsense.
You're so delusional every day.
You'll get sick easily.
I advise you to go to the hospital.
Just find a place to rest.
Don't think about the world.
You'll get sick easily.
That's all.
You...
Who are you?
I'm Yuan Shang.
You're the weakling of Yuan's family.
You came to the door yourself.
That man said
the magic weapon can control me.
It's useless.
Senior, you're still sleeping?
I'm sleepy.
You're already a magical weapon.
Do you need to sleep?
There's no need to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
But I want to sleep.
It's like eating.
There's no need to eat.
But I want to eat.
You're so strange.
Did he
come with me just now?
Senior, you heard it?
Do you know who I am?
No one can hide anything from me.
But I don't know it myself.
Then what do you think
I am?
You're here to kill me.
Tell me if I should kill you.
If he wants to kill me, he should have done it long ago.
Besides, he killed me now.
Didn't he bleed so much yesterday?
He's not that boring, right?
What are you thinking about?
Your hand just rubbed the flower.
It didn't wash.
It just stuck to my mouth.
It just won't wash.
We've got about 70% left.
I can finish the task at one try.
Or we can just skip it today.
But this time,
you must take off the mask
and all the things on these lands.
Did you tell him to remove it first?
I haven't.
He has to take it to the orange tree.
When did you get it?
Didn't I managing your investment at that time.
It will always be yours.
You were the one who hit the ex-boyfriend.
What's an ex-boyfriend?
It's someone who shouldn't have appeared
and should be considered dead.
He deserves to die.
You're so nice to me.
You fed me blood and taught me how to be an ex-boyfriend.
He's nice to people,
but he's still being sneaky.
He's so arrogant.
Since you think he deserves to die,
you should follow his order
and kill him.
I just became a God of War.
I can't kill anyone
as you're so kind.
You'll get used to it if you kill more people.
Where are we going?
I'll take you to kill someone.
I'm not going.
Get up.
I don't want to kill anyone.
If I insist on killing someone,
then kill me first.
Do you really think I won't kill you?
I think you won't kill me.
Are you angry?
Grand Master.
Actually, this is not my home
and I'm not familiar with this place.
I often make some
murderous crimes.
Fortunately, you're here.
So I can be a good girl
in such a cruel place.
So my words are true.
The seven-name case is also true.
As long as you don't force me to kill,
everything will be fine.
Don't be angry, okay?
If you don't believe me,
try me.
Try me.
Shut up.
Okay.
Father.
You're the disciple of the sect, right?
Save me.
Father.
Is everything ready?
Yes.
Yuan Shang is dead.
Before his death,
Sima Jiao did a soul-searching technique to him.
There must be a trace of Sima Jiao's magic in the body.
We can call Yuan Shang weak.
He can't stand the torture.
He died with a fragile heart.
Then Sima Jiao
won't suspect us
and will also be the murderer.
Okay.
I told you to keep an eye on the young princess.
Why don't you know where she is now?
Please calm down, Your Highness.
I'll go to the young princess right away.
Who are you?
You're the personal guard of the teacher.
I wonder what you're doing here at night.
o
He who wanted to save Her Highness
didn't allow his sister to show up.
To me
He's only a slave who has night sheriffs' functions.
I'll show you around.
Check it out yourself.
I'm not afraid of you.
You...
You're not hungry.
You dare not let me go?
Your brain
is more stupid than my tongue.
If you weren't a teacher,
you wouldn't be alive today.
This is a bad omen.
Did the family kill me?
What do you think?
When you were searching for the soul for me,
you left me a spell.
It turned out to save me.
Useless.
Wasted my spiritual power.
You already know
I was the one who colluded with Mo Yu
and sent Liu Ting Yan to you
to find a chance to kill you.
Why did you save me?
What's your purpose?
And
why did
the teacher kill me?
How did Yuan Che give birth to such a stupid son?
You can scold me,
but you can't insult my father.
Wasted my76 a little 아니라
Guo Zi
Take her to find Yuan Che.
If she's Geez News heavy,
just let her son live.
Or
let's go and kill her.
Wasted Germs
Shang'er.
The teacher
UNE OVER Kevin
did this to my son
and even tried to frame my master.
It's not a good idea.
Thank you for your kindness.
I wonder how you will deal with Shi Qianlv.
You don't need to know what I'm doing.
You just need to do what I tell you.
Okay.
I'll be your guard in the future.
I don't know what you did to Yuan Shang.
I want you to follow Shi Qianlv
to gain his trust.
Okay.
I'll be your spy.
I'll send you the message when I know something.
Master said
you don't need to contact him.
You just need to do what Shi Qianlv wants.
Remember,
you must gain his trust
so that you can use him in the future.
As for Yuan Shang,
you can forgive him.
But he can't see anyone since then.
If you can't hide him,
he'll kill him for you
to solve the problem.
I'll follow your instructions.
Thank you for saving my son.
Shang.
Sister.
Cang Lan.
You're finally back.
It's good that you're back.
You suffered.
I'm not suffering.
Congratulations on taking the princess' heart.
Now you can live here.
You don't need to be forced anymore.
Come on.
Sister.
When you were in the mountain,
didn't you find a chance to kill Sima Jiao?
Sima Jiao is too powerful
and very cautious.
He only asked Ting Yan to serve him.
I couldn't get close to him.
But Cang Lan,
I found that
Ting Yan might be the body of the cold that Mother mentioned.
The body of the cold?
Only the cold fish of the Demon Citadel can have the body of the cold.
Is Ting Yan the body of the cold fish?
Great.
The barrier set by the fire
can only be passed by the body of the cold
if Sima Jiao is eliminated.
But I tried.
He seems to have forgotten his identity
and doesn't remember how to transfer the body of the cold.
Then we can just take his internal energy.
How can we do that?
He won't live if we take his internal energy.
Ting Yan doesn't know his identity.
Cang Lan,
we can't ask others to sacrifice themselves
to help us.
If he is found to be a person of the Demon Citadel,
he will die in the Immortal Manor.
It's better to ask him to help us
to return to the Demon Citadel with our fellow demons
and complete Mother's last wish.
No.
Ting Yan is sincere to me.
I can't be suspicious of him.
As long as Ting Yan is alive,
we still have hope for our plan to go home.
But, Cang Lan,
it's easier to take Ting Yan's internal energy
than to kill Sima Jiao.
Enough.
Don't worry about it.
I will find a way.
Good.
Tell Yuan Che
that you sent the news
that Liao Ting Yan is a person of the Demon Citadel.
Then he will think
that Sima Jiao heard the story
of the ancient cave of the person of the Demon Citadel
and killed his son.
In this way,
Sima Jiao will be convinced.
Yes.
An Xue,
you will be able to complete
the task of the Three God Mountains
in the future.
You have done it very well.
What kind of reward do you want?
Now that Ying Liu Nian is dead,
the new princess is not in good health.
An Xue only wants to go back to the sect leader.
There is nothing else I can ask for.
Good.
Thank you, sect leader.
You may leave.
Yes.
Zhen Xu,
when are you going to
show An Xue
the magic of soul-willing?
Father,
the magic of soul-willing is very painful.
An Xue doesn't know our great plan
and is always loyal to us.
Look at the magic of soul-willing.
Zhen Xu,
you have to remember
that in this world,
except me,
no one can be loyal.
In our great plan,
there must be no flaws.
I understand.
Where is Liao Ting Yan?
Ting Yan is still sleeping.
She is awake
and eating and sleeping all day.
I will wake her up.
Do as you wish.
Liao Ting Yan's evil identity
has been found out by the teacher.
Patriarch,
Shi Qian Lv actually found
Ting Yan's evil identity.
What should we do?
This is a secret.
How did the old man know?
Did Shi Qian Lv have collusion with the evil?
That's why he knew Ting Yan's identity.
Go and find out
where the news came from.
Yes.
But Patriarch,
how should we deal with Ting Yan?
Since Bada wants her dead,
we will do as they say.
Patriarch,
are you going to kill Ting Yan?
What's wrong?
You can't bear to?
I can't bear to.
I believe
you can't bear to either.
I will ask Yuan Che
to find Shi Qian Lv's alliance
and kill Liao Ting Yan
to gain Shi Qian Lv's trust.
Patriarch.
Princess Yuan.
Please
help me to make the decision.
What's wrong with you, Princess Yuan?
Today,
I found
Shang Er's body under the White Deer Cliff.
There is a silk rubber
on her body.
How could this happen?
Princess Yuan,
I'm sorry.
But
why would the Patriarch
do that?
I just found out.
Liao Ting Yan
is a spy of the Demon Citadel.
I'm afraid my son knows about this.
He wants to kill someone
and he will mobilize the silk rubber
to kill my son.
Now,
the Patriarch is so fond of
the Demon Citadel.
If this continues,
the Gangchen's Mansion
will be in danger.
I will never
let him do this.
I was
a little bit respectful of him before.
I didn't expect
he would take our lives
so lightly.
He is a good man
and he is not a thief.
I must avenge him.
Patriarch,
you are here.
You are reading too.
Since I entered the Magic Realm,
I have a strong sense of the world around me.
I'm also curious about
the structure of the world around me.
I'm bored,
so I'm here to see
if there are any good books.
What did you read?
I read...
I just read whatever I want.
Read it.
Let it go.
Can you promise me
not to get angry if I read it?
No.
Look.
I knew you would be angry.
It's just that those people from the Immortal Gengchen's Mansion
came out.
Master, please tell me the truth.
It says that
the Immortal Gengchen's Mansion
is not only where we see now.
There are some outside families around it.
Except for the place where the cultivators live,
there are also places where the demons live.
Is it true?
It's true.
Many years ago,
the owner of the Demon Citadel was in chaos.
The Sima clan killed the demons.
They set up the Demon Citadel.
Since then,
the people who were possessed
could no longer use the spirit weapons of the Gengchen's Mansion
to cultivate.
The Sima clan is so powerful.
It is said that the battle
was a perfect match.
The battlefield became a thousand miles away.
The original Qiu Ling Mountain
also became a minefield.
It also said that
you were raised by the Taoist Army.
It said that you were arrogant and didn't listen to it.
So it found a immortal
to suppress the demons for you.
It said that the name of your Taoist Army
is...
It's so fake.
Let me tell you.
This book is nonsense.
Boss,
this book is too much.
I don't believe it.
I'm not lying.
Master Shi.
Please restart the seal formation.
I will be the leader of the Taoist Sect
and guard the formation.
Princess Yuan is too serious.
Master Shi is so stubborn.
We should
persuade him
to take the right path.
Now,
the new princess of the Heavenly Palace has been appointed.
It seems that
it's not a problem
for us to re-seal her.
However,
Princess Yuan,
you are right.
Once we restart the seal formation,
we will have a dead man.
What...
What should we do?
You suggested that Liao Tingye's demon identity
be sealed by the seal.
It must be a good thing.
Since Sima Jiao
favors the demon and the spy so much,
we should use her
to lure Sima Jiao into the formation.
Even if we fail to seal her,
we can capture Liao Tingye
and control her in the future.
At the banquet a few days ago,
I think she seems to have a lot of feelings
for Master Shi.
We can also take advantage of it.
Princess Yuan,
this is a good opportunity.
Okay.
It's not too late.
I will call
all the princesses
to discuss this matter together.
Thank you, Master Shi.
Attic of The Great Ning
policy wasze to the priest's aunt,
No.
Can I go there by myself?
Of course.
This is a party
for you.
To kill you.
Go.
I'm afraid that I can't protect you.