[A Love Never Lost]
[Episode 22]
Commander Zhang,
now that you're
the Southern Army's commander,
you sure know how to impress us.
One question from you,
and even our chief judge
is stumped.
Sir,
the track gauge in Wuhan
is 4.85 feet.
Same
as in Beijing.
I just got off the train,
and I sent someone to measure the tracks.
The gauge in Zhangde
is also 4.85 feet.
This proves one thing:
corruption's the same everywhere!
Commander Zhang,
our railway gauge standard
comes from Europe.
It was set by Europeans.
Is that so?
Then
why did they set it
at 4.85?
Why not 4.86
or 3.86?
Why exactly 4.85?
Exactly.
Good question.
The European railway gauge
came from
the wheelbase of European carriages.
The wheelbase of European carriages
is exactly 4.85 feet.
And why is the wheelbase
that wide?
You really know how to argue.
Because that's the width
of two horses side by side—
their rumps set the standard:
4.85 feet.
So that's how it is.
Kaizhi,
you really are a man of knowledge!
Cheers.
Chief Judge,
your man is really something.
Now I'm relieved.
If he were any weaker,
he really couldn't
handle certain people out there.
Look at that.
The drill hasn't even started yet,
and someone's already
buttering up the brass!
If you're to suck up,
don't just do it to one person.
Make sure both men in power
feel flattered.
Am I right?
That's right.
Duan,
why are you leaving?
I was just kidding. Come on.
The Western food
is awful.
Who came up with it?
Come on, brothers,
drink as you please.
Cheers.
Let's drink.
Don't take it the wrong way, Chief Judge.
Before the drill,
I wouldn't dare offend you.
It's totally fine.
General Zhang, you have a sharp eye.
I should be learning from you.
Commander Zhang,
you must've come from the artillery corps.
How did you know?
Artillerymen
are always obsessed with measurements,
and
they always use feet.
Kaizhi,
I have high hopes for you.
Our border hero,
come.
See?
The two armies haven't even faced off yet,
and the tension
is already thick in the air.
That's why it's even more important
for us judges
to stay fair and impartial.
If Manchu generals
want to lead Han soldiers,
they should study
Han culture more.
Han culture values flexibility,
not rigid rules.
My friend.
The Commander-in-Chief
has changed his stance.
I told you long ago.
Don't take it too seriously.
It's all about mutual favors—
you help me, or I help you.
Come on,
don't look so upset.
Come with me over there
and greet those
brigade commanders.
Let's go.
[Imperial Bank of China]
Miss,
are these the correct amounts?
Yes.
Shuhong.
Alright, wait a moment.
It's really you.
Yeah, it's me.
I could tell from afar.
What?
You're back in Shanghai?
Yihua.
The carriage is about to leave.
I've got business.
Coming, coming!
You go ahead. We'll catch up later.
Sure. Come visit when you're free.
You're still so beautiful.
Who was that?
Your third son's wife.
Still as pretty as ever.
Brother-in-law.
Had another fight?
You bet.
A big one.
Since you came back this time,
you two have always been arguing.
What's really going on?
Your brother-in-law…
Forgive me for being blunt.
He's just not cut out to be a leader.
To be honest with you,
I've already teamed up
with comrades in Shanghai
to take him down.
In my opinion,
he's only good for writing his theories.
The most important thing right now
is the Zhejiang-Anhui uprising.
Success or failure doesn't matter.
We just have to make it happen.
We need
those donors to see exactly
where
their money went,
how we spent it,
and whether it was worth it.
Whether we succeed doesn't matter.
But look at him—
keeping saying we're not ready.
He's just being unreasonable!
Did the money for Qiu Jin and Xu Xilin
get delivered?
It's all been handed over.
Well,
keep Zhangde's money separate.
We might need it anytime.
Didn't Wang Han take some money?
That was for operational expenses.
I'm talking about the pension
for Wang Han's family.
A pension for Wang Han's family?
Why so surprised?
He's alive today,
but who knows about tomorrow?
You're really cold-blooded.
If one gives
one's life for the revolution,
it's worth it.
But their families
still have to live on.
Attention!
Salute!
Giddy-up!
Stop!
What are you doing?
Enjoying yourself, Kaizhi?
This rain is perfect.
You're my superior.
I have to join you
in this romantic moment.
But if I catch a cold when we arrive,
I'll have to blame you.
You, come here!
What's going on?
The assassin ran that way!
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Don't run!
The assassin is in the hotel.
Surround the entire building.
Open the door!
Coming. Coming.
Open up! Open up!
Fool!
Dying for you people
really isn't worth it!
Out of the way!
Search the place!
Yes.
You, go that way.
Sir.
[Northern Army Camp]
What is it, Chief Judge?
The confrontation time has passed.
Why hasn't anything started yet?
Can't be helped.
The Southern Army hasn't arrived.
Everyone, stand up!
Salute!
Renjun,
I heard that
some battalions in the Northern Army
have canceled the military salute
and changed it to bowing.
Is that true?
The Ninth Battalion
just got a new Manchu commander.
He said the Commander-in-Chief, Feng Shan,
approved the change.
Really?
The Commander-in-Chief approved it?
What can we do?
I can't control others,
but my men won't change.
Whoever dares to change,
I'll kick their ass.
An army is an army!
Looks like Mr. Yuan
really picked the right man back then.
Of course.
A man's gotta know gratitude—
always stay proper,
righteous, grounded,
and clean.
Qianli,
why do Northern soldiers
hang their shoes around their necks?
Chief Judge,
you shouldn't ask me that.
You should ask the new quartermaster.
The new quartermaster?
He was just transferred here
two weeks ago.
He's the Commander-in-Chief's
brother-in-law.
You'd better ask him.
The joint drill is about to start,
and they're all barefoot?
Tell them to put their shoes on. Now!
Put them on!
Quickly!
Tell me.
What's going on here?
For this autumn military drill,
because of the parade,
all officers and soldiers
are required to wear leather shoes.
The shoes were all custom-ordered
by the new quartermaster in Tianjin.
Who knows
how much money he pocketed from this?
The shoes all came out
too small.
In a whole company, only 11 or 12 men
can actually wear them.
As for the rest...
Is the entire Northern Army
in this situation?
Yes.
All the shoes
were ordered by that quartermaster.
The Commander-in-Chief's brother-in-law,
what's his name?
Qide, with Qi meaning inspiration
and De meaning
virtue.
Inspiration and virtue?
More like lack of virtue!
If they don't fit,
we can just go barefoot.
Without shoes, we can still defeat them,
can't we?
Yes!
However,
if we go barefoot in the parade,
our steps won't sound crisp and loud.
So just bear with it.
No matter how small
the shoes are, put them on.
We'll throw them away after the parade.
For the Northern Army,
for our honor,
can you grit your teeth and tough it out?
Yes!
[The Qing government holds an autumn military drill
between the Northern and Southern Armies in Zhangde.]
It's been three full hours.
Sir,
the Southern Army still hasn't arrived.
That's right.
The actors aren't tired,
but the audience's backs are aching.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
I'm really sorry.
We hit a snag in the last kilometer.
Zhang,
we're all on the Emperor's payroll.
I'm showing you respect,
and you've got to show me some too.
We all need to show
His Majesty and Her Highness
some respect, right?
Of course.
Commander Zhang,
now you know
how long a kilometer is, right?
Is it 4.85 feet?
Sir,
both armies'
artillery units are in position.
The artillery duel
is ready to begin.
Shall we start?
Start.
Start!
Commander Zhang,
from here on,
I really don't dare beat you anymore.
To be honest with you,
Mr. Yuan is having bad luck.
I don't want to cause him more trouble.
The show's about to start!
Southern Army, get ready!
Fire!
Great! Great!
Northern Army, get ready!
Fire!
Awful.
That was awful.
Second round.
Southern Army, get ready!
Fire!
Good, good, good!
Excellent!
Northern Army, get ready.
Fire!
Third round. Southern Army, get ready!
In the third round, the Southern Army
hit all the targets!
Great! Great!
Zhang is indeed
from an artillery background.
He took the wrong road,
but his artillery skills are good.
The Northern Army is upset.
Losing two rounds like that
seems a bit suspicious.
Upset about what?
When two flowers blossom,
each has its own charm.
If you ask me,
they both
have their strengths and weaknesses.
Northern Army, third round,
get ready!
Fire!
They're not firing cannons
but practicing calligraphy.
The impact points are perfectly aligned,
forming the character "one,"
implying number one in the world.
We're indeed not good enough.
The Southern and Northern Armies
have completed
three rounds of artillery competition.
The Southern Army
has won all three rounds.
Great! Great!
Sirs,
the parade of both armies
will begin in one hour.
Please wait a moment.
The Northern Army is upset.
They missed every shot in three rounds.
As the Chief Judge,
how should I handle this?
Sir.
Just pretend you didn't see it.
No.
I can't tolerate the Northern Army's
nonchalant attitude towards
the court's autumn military drill.
As a leader,
I should approach this with authority
and knock the Beiyang Army
down a peg or two.
Tufang.
Yesterday in Zhangde,
an assassin dropped a bomb.
Two guards were killed.
Is that so?
The assassin's target
was none other
than you.
It's been confirmed.
The assassin was carrying a photo
clipped from the Shanghai Times
on the 10th of this month.
In his luggage,
we also found
a luggage claim ticket
from a Shanghai hotel.
The Police Department
has already notified the Shanghai Circuit
to assist in the investigation.
From Shanghai?
Who wants to kill me?
No matter who it is,
for our part,
we'd best keep a low profile
and stay cautious.
Sir.
This is the hotel registry.
Please take a look.
[Nanyang Hotel]
Tianbai.
Wang Han is in trouble.
The police in the Settlement
have traced it to the Nanyang Hotel.
The hotel staff all know me.
I'm afraid…
The autumn military drill
in Zhangde wrapped up peacefully.
[The autumn military drill
in Zhangde wrapped up smoothly.]
The papers are full of praise,
but no breaking news.
That means Wang Han failed.
His target is still alive.
Who was Wang Han's target?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Oh, right. Go to the bank immediately
and cash out all our savings.
I'm afraid we can't
stay in Shanghai any longer.
Leave the child with Xueqing.
You and I will head straight for Hangzhou.
Hangzhou?
Qiu Jin in Shaoxing
really needs my help.
We'll go there directly
and lay low for a while
so they can't trace us here
from the Nanyang Hotel.
What a pity, Miss.
If you cash out everything now,
you'll lose quite a bit of interest.
I know,
but you can't have it both ways, can you?
I want to convert them all into stocks.
I've heard stocks
are more profitable than savings.
That depends on which stock you pick.
Hello, Mr. Song.
Considering seniority
and the past relationship
between our two families,
calling me Mr. Song
feels a bit too formal, doesn't it?
It does.
Uncle.
You're buying stocks?
Yes.
I can recommend two for you.
No, I don't want to trouble you.
How's that trouble?
I know the financial world
like the back of my hand.
This is what I do.
With the amount you have,
if you trust me…
I ran into Song Chen when I was in Tokyo.
He sent me the photos.
He also told me
that you took the photos.
When I was in Tokyo,
I ran a photography studio.
See?
The branches of our Song family
are a bit too low
to accommodate a phoenix like you.
Buy stocks 056 and 017
for this lady immediately.
Okay, Mr. Song. I'll buy them right away.
You're not
in urgent need of cash, are you?
I do need some cash as well.
Give 200 silver dollars to this lady.
Come up to my office later to complete
the paperwork.
Okay, Mr. Song.
Well…
Song Chen
complained to me about being broke.
He said you took photos for him,
but he hadn't paid you yet.
I'm paying on his behalf.
I have other matters
to attend to. I must go now.
[The West Lake in Hangzhou]
Tianbai,
how did Wang Han fail
to kill Liang Xiang in Zhangde?
Bad luck, I guess.
The West Lake is still the West Lake.
Still as beautiful as ever.
Hongming,
I want to ask you about someone.
Six years ago in Hangzhou,
I met a remarkable man
named Sun Jingchao.
Sun Jingchao?
Sun Jingchao,
leader of the White Cloth Party,
knows some medicine.
At the peak of the White Cloth Party,
it had up to 20,000 members,
spread across
the seven counties of Fuyang.
Unfortunately,
he was captured by the court
two years ago
and is still imprisoned in Hangzhou.
This time,
Qiu Jin gathered various party leaders
for a meeting at Datong Academy.
Sun Jingchao was the only one missing.
I see.
I need to see him.
Help me get into the prison.
No way, Tianbai. That's too dangerous.
Shuhong, let me explain.
I don't want to hear it.
How could you?
No matter what,
Liang Xiang is my child's father.
Whether you're enemies or not,
you shouldn't have
asked a mother
to kill her child's father.
To hell with that father!
I'm telling you,
I, Wu Tianbai, and that bastard
are mortal enemies!
I will kill him.
What?
Feeling sorry for him?
I'm talking about my son.
I'm speaking for my son.
What are you on about?
You are feeling sorry for him!
Just admit it.
If you didn't care,
why are you arguing with me?
How many times have I told you?
That wasn't my choice.
It went completely against my will.
Not your choice?
Listen, Shuhong.
That day, you two weren't alone
when you did those filthy things.
There were three people there.
I was there too!
You're finally telling the truth.
You never trusted me.
You've treated me
like nothing but a tool.
Tell me,
how long have you
wanted him dead?
Since the very first day!
For what he did to the country
and to me myself,
any real man would never forget!
Don't expect me to!
I was a fool.
Such a fool.
All these years,
whatever you told me to do,
I did it.
I never questioned right or wrong.
I completely lost myself.
What did I get in return?
Just those words from you.
Wu Tianbai,
you're too heartless.
If you ask me,
you care about no one
but yourself!
Look at me.
My body is covered in scars.
I can't even walk.
I have to lie down just to pee!
Do I still have myself?
If I'd lived for myself,
would I have
ended up like this?
I'm telling you, Shuhong.
A hero battered and broken
is still a hero!
Given Sun Jingchao's
enormous influence
in the seven counties of Fuyang,
the prison gives him special treatment.
They even
allow him
to run a clinic behind bars.
Even some officials
go to him for treatment.
The White Cloth Party
is the largest
of all the parties in Zhejiang.
Seven counties, over 20,000 members.
If we can
bring these people to our side,
it would be of great help
to Qiu Jin and Xu Xilin's
Zhejiang-Anhui uprising.
Exactly.
It would be such a waste otherwise.
I must see him. I must.
I'll see him in person
to discuss this matter.
You go make contact
with the prison officials.
Even if it costs a lot, it's worth it.
Alright, but the money…
My woman is still mad at me.
Wait until she comes back.
Again?
How long have you two been together now?
Still acting like you just met.
Another 3-3 invasion?
Why do you always like
playing on the third line?
You love flashy moves.
I just focus on securing territory.
By the way,
I heard from Referee Jiang Fangzhen
that you submitted a memorial
about the autumn military drill.
Is that true?
Baili sure can't keep his mouth shut.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You've barely got your footing,
and you're already poking the bear?
If the army continues like this,
what future does it have?
Back in the Banner Battalion,
I was always a troublemaker.
Old habits die hard.
Kaizhi,
let me introduce you.
This is my wife.
What do you think?
Even better than your Miss Li, right?
A beauty. A beauty.
A real beauty.
In what way is she beautiful?
A true beauty is one
with the appearance of a flower,
the voice of a bird,
the spirit of the moon,
the grace of a willow,
bones like jade, skin like ice and snow,
the poise of autumn waters,
and a heart of poetry.
Hear that?
This is the man
I've been telling you about…
Yang Kaizhi, right?
Who else but him
could praise a woman like that,
chirping away like a thrush?
This way, he's here.
You are…
[Tuoteke Duanfang, Viceroy of Liangjiang]
I'm Tuoteke Duanfang,
courtesy name Wuqiao.
Nice to meet you, madam.
No need for formalities.
Mr. Duanfang,
Viceroy of Liangjiang.
By seniority,
you should just call me Duanfang.
It feels more familiar that way.
Go tell Xiang that
Viceroy Duanfang is here.
Yes.
My house isn't far from here.
I thought I'd stop by.
I heard your son just returned
from the autumn military drill.
Forgive me for not welcoming you properly.
Viceroy Duanfang.
Tufang, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Viceroy Duanfang,
I'll leave you two to chat.
Okay.
You sure have some high-ranking guests.
He's a big shot?
Looks like a mediocre,
withered old man to me.
This man is far from mediocre.
Among the Bannermen,
those who earned their positions
through the Imperial Exam are rare.
He's one of the few.
Tufang,
it's a bit plain here.
Later, I'll have someone send over a pot
of bird plum blossoms.
My mother arranged everything here.
She likes it simple.
I just came from Jiangning
the day before yesterday.
Xiangcheng sang your praises,
saying you're a rare new military talent
among us Bannermen.
Yuan Xiangcheng, Mr. Yuan?
What, you two haven't met yet?
That's not right.
You work on military affairs,
yet you haven't gotten
acquainted with Yuan Xiangcheng.
That's just making things
harder for yourself.
I'll arrange it in a few days.
People need to interact.
How can you
become close without interaction?
If you're not close,
how can you work together?
I'm just a junior.
Getting close with
a high-ranking official
feels improper.
It might look like
I'm trying to climb the ladder.
Yuan Xiangcheng
isn't as bad as some people say.
In and out of the court nowadays,
officials
with vision, capability, and ambition
like him
are not too many, but too few.
Just look at
how he's governed Tianjin.
It's improving day by day.
We Bannermen
need to let go of our old prejudices.
I didn't bring much for this first visit,
just a calligraphy piece I wrote.
It's a couplet from Emperor Yongzheng.
"To judge people wisely,
one must learn broadly and listen widely."
He's truly a refined gentleman.
Duanfang's calligraphy
is really quite good.
But what's his intention?
Is he acting
as a go-between for Yuan Shikai?
He and Yuan Shikai
have become in-laws.
What else could he mean?
So that's actually true?
One is the Viceroy of Liangjiang,
the other of Zhili.
So Jiangning and Tianjin
are family now.
A man of his rank
visiting me personally…
I really don't know what to make of it.
So, my son,
in this world,
there's no absolute right or wrong.
Five years ago,
the rules set by our ancestors
forbade intermarriage between Manchu and Han.
Back then, that was considered wrong.
But five years later,
intermarriage
between Manchu and Han became right.
No right or wrong?
If that's really the case,
I'm stuck in a tight spot.
Yuan Shikai
has been transferred to Beijing
and appointed as a grand councilor.
Zaifeng has also joined
the Grand Council.
These two are at odds again.
Today, Duanfang came,
and yesterday, Zaixun came.
They both came to recruit me.
I really don't know whose side to take.
Do your own thing.
Don't worry about others' opinions,
not even Kaizhi's.
In my opinion,
he's not the type
to be content playing a supporting role.
You really
don't need me to go with you?
I was a bit impulsive that day.
Don't take it to heart.
This sounds like a farewell speech.
You stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
If anything happens to me,
go straight back to Shanghai.
The child always needs
someone to take care of him.
I got it.
Be careful.
If I walk back,
don't be too shocked.
[Hangzhou Prison]
Mr. Sun.
The guy from Shanghai is here.
Are you feeling up to it today?
If so, I'll let him in.
If not, I'll send him away.
[Sun Jingchao, head of the White Cloth Party]
Let him in, Kuan.
Okay.
Come in.
You guys
are lucky
to catch Mr. Sun
in good spirits today.
Normally,
Mr. Sun wouldn't treat you
for any amount of money.
Thank you, sir.
Are you alright?
Mr. Sun, I'll leave you to it.
When you're done,
just call me, okay?