[A Love Never Lost]
[Episode 1]
[Tang Caichang united with the Revolutionaries, but the uprising launched by the Independent army was brutally suppressed.]
[In 1900 AD, when modern China was in peril, the Eight-Nation Alliance invaded Beijing, and Empress Dowager Cixi fled with the Guangxu Emperor.]
[Various ideologies emerged, deeply influencing the youths of the land.]
["40,000 people shed tears, where in this vast land is our divine land?" Communist ideology had yet to enter China.]
[Some upheld feudal residential autocracy, some advocated constitutional monarchy, and some yearned for more radical revolutions.]
[struggling to carve a new direction for China's future in this turbulent stage of history.]
[Several factions emerged and confronted each other, while the youths began their searches amidst the clash of currents,]
[The 27th year of Guangxu of Qing Dynasty] [1901 AD]
Hurry up.
[Revolutionary Party] [The organization in Jingzhou, Hubei was captured]
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Keep up.
Hurry up!
They are all the remnants
of Tang Caichang's accomplices in Jingzhou.
May I ask
to hold a public trial for them?
No.
[Yang Kaizhi, Revolutionary]
Currently, the Empress Dowager and the Emperor have gone to survey Xi'an.
The situation is turbulent.
We'd better not hold a public trial.
What should we do?
Extreme times call for extreme measures.
Shall we kill them all?
Don't kill them all.
But don't free them all either.
Let them bet on their own luck.
[Youth of Banner Battalion, Liang Xiang]
[Courtesy name: Tufang]
What's this?
Are you
beheading people today?
Go away.
Kid,
why are you here?
Why aren't you in class?
The teacher canceled our class today.
He said something was happening here.
I borrowed my third cousin's horse.
It was fast, so I got here first.
This is such a sinister thing.
A kid like you shouldn't spectate it.
You just might get possessed by a ghost.
If you're not afraid,
what am I afraid of?
Beheading people is a sinister and unlucky matter.
Normally,
you should choose to do it
when the sun is the strongest.
At the very least,
the sun should be right above our heads.
Look at the weather today.
It's ominous.
Three-quarters past noon is here.
Double round.
Behead him!
Kneel!
Next.
Move.
What's your name?
Yang Aiguo.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
You're rebelling at the age of seventeen?
What a pity.
Kneel!
It's just a gamble.
The bet is your life.
Don't panic.
You have two-thirds of the chance.
If you get one flat and one round,
you'll be released.
If you get double flat, you'll also be released.
Only if you get a double round
will you be beheaded.
Your toss determines your life.
Throw it well.
One flat and one round.
Released.
What are you waiting for?
Go!
Drag him away.
Next.
Hurry up, go home.
You are so lucky.
I'm afraid others won't have such good luck.
Get up.
Let me send you back.
I'm familiar with the soldiers of the Banner Battalion.
If anyone catches you again,
I will speak up for you.
Let's go.
[Hubei, Jingzhou]
Slow down.
You're going too fast. It's scary.
This land belongs to the Qing Dynasty.
You dared to rebel
at such a young age.
But you're scared
of a fast horse ride?
I feel dizzy if I ride too fast.
Okay, I'll ride slowly.
I'll be honest with you.
I skipped class today
to spectate the beheading.
My master will scold me if I go back late.
You're not a soldier yourself?
Us Bannermen
are reservists as soon as we're born.
But you have to be 18 to be a soldier.
I'm one year too young.
You're also 17?
That's right. We're the same age.
Liang, why are you here?
Uncle, I have a class to attend.
I'm leaving.
Be careful. Don't fall down.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
When order is lost, benevolence and righteousness arise.
When wisdom and intelligence emerge, so does deception.
When family ties are broken, there arises filial piety and compassion.
In times of national crisis, there emerge loyal ministers.
Abandoning sacredness and cleverness will benefit the people a hundredfold.
Abandoning benevolence and righteousness will restore the people's filial nature.
Abandoning deceit and profit will eliminate thieves and robbers.
Where did you go?
The rebels were being executed outside the city. So I...
Kneel!
Didn't the rest of you say that
he went home to get brush and ink?
All of you, kneel down!
Kneel!
When family ties are broken, there arises filial piety and compassion.
In times of national crisis, there emerge loyal ministers.
But what about all of you?
Don't you have any sense of
filial piety and loyalty?
The horses are back.
[Jingzhou Banner Battalion]
Don't touch me!
Slow down. Don't touch me.
If my mother sees me
with this bowl of water,
she'll beat me for sure.
It’s Liang Xiang's fault.
You are the culprit, Liang Xiang.
Want to bet
if I dare to
carry this bowl of water back on my head?
No way. I think you can't.
Master won't forgive you
if you spill the water.
That's right, he won't forgive you.
There you go again.
Look at all of you.
What should we do
with you lot in the future?
If I go back with this bowl of water on my head,
what will you give me for losing the bet?
If you can do that,
we'll treat you
to 20 fried fritters.
Your words, not mine.
Don't regret it.
If you spill
even a single drop,
you'll have to treat us
to 20 fried fritters instead.
Yes, that's right.
Twenty fried fritters.
We'll report
your failure to Master too.
Let's make a bet then.
Let's bet.
Bet!
Yes.
It's really on his head now.
Don't spill it.
Let's go home.
Liang.
You are really something.
You brat.
Look at all of you.
Twenty fried fritters.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
What did I tell you?
Your father passed away early.
You are my only hope.
Why can't you study hard
and make me proud?
I was wrong.
Really?
You're 17, going 18 soon.
You're an adult.
You should learn to work hard.
Are you going somewhere?
Have dinner by yourself. It's on the stove.
The magistrate's family has invited
the Salt Transport Commissioner of Huguang's wife for dinner.
[Descendant of Dorgon, Prince Rui, Mother of Liang]
Somehow, they found me
and asked me to accompany her.
I wonder what they are thinking.
What am I supposed to do with you?
Of all the things you could have done,
why did you have to be a rebel?
So beautiful.
Your Liangbatou hairstyle is beautiful.
What is this lousy official doing?
It's so noisy.
How do you Bannermen
kowtow with so many
accessories on your head?
[Manistrate's Mansion of Jingzhou]
The women in the old ancestral residence
only kneel when they have to kowtow.
We use our right hand
to touch the tip of our Liangbatou.
When we touch it,
we tilt our head slightly to the right.
One touch equals one kowtow.
For each kneel, we touch it 3 times.
If we kneel again, we touch it 3 more times.
Could you demonstrate it for us to see?
Just like this.
It's so neat.
It's so elegant.
So beautiful.
We have made the right call to invite you.
The Salt Transport Commissioner's wife is also a Bannerman.
I don't understand your rules.
When she arrives later,
you have to help me out.
Make sure I don't make a mistake
and make a fool of myself.
Got it, Madam.
This is my daughter, Duo Mei.
[Duo Mei]
Duo Mei, greet your aunt.
Aunt.
We Bannermen
use "auntie" instead.
For example, the sixth auntie or
the seventh auntie.
We add their ranks in front of the address.
Would you look at that?
I almost made another mistake.
Later,
when the wife of the Salt Transport Commissioner is here,
you can call her third auntie.
Does a junior need to perform formal greetings too?
Of course.
Does she kneel on both knees
or just one knee for the greeting?
Men kneel on both knees.
When ladies meet each other,
they can just bend their knees instead.
Just like this, Madam.
Like this.
It's such a neat greeting.
I've never seen it before.
This gesture.
Mei, did you get a good look?
Yes.
Keep your head straight.
Keep it. You can use it on the way.
Where is my case?
The one I asked you to hide.
My Commander-in-chief entrusted this to me before he died.
I must get it done.
I have to go to Shanghai.
You still plan to run around?
Do you want to die?
Miss.
Is the distinguished guest here?
She'll be here soon.
Mother asks you to hold back on the chili when you cook.
The wife of the Salt Transport Commissioner can't eat spicy food.
Got it.
Here comes the wife of the Salt Transport Commissioner of Huguang.
Go.
Go right now.
Immediately.
This way, please.
Here comes the wife of the Salt Transport Commissioner of Huguang.
My daughter, Duo Mei.
Greetings, Third Auntie.
Here.
What a beautiful girl.
How old are you?
Auntie, I'm 17.
So beautiful.
Greetings, Master.
Are you Lady Bi?
Yes, Master.
Lady Bi.
Where have you been making money?
Master,
20 years ago,
I married Liangmu of the Zhengnan family.
Liangmu works for the court.
He transferred
to Jingzhou from Nanjing 2 days ago.
I see.
You must be wealthy now.
I dare not call myself wealthy
in front of you, Master.
Get up.
Today, the host is giving us food.
You don't need to be too polite.
Yes.
Master.
Come on. Have a seat.
Go.
This way, please.
This is the seat of honor.
So...
I'm here today.
It's not convenient for her to take this seat.
I'll sit here on her behalf.
Have a seat, everyone.
You wanted me to show you the Bannerman etiquette.
Well, this is it.
Your Ladyship.
Have a seat.
You don't have to go against
the host's kindness.
Sit down and eat with us.
Thank you, Master.
Your Ladyship, please.
I really didn't know.
You really didn't know?
I only knew she was the widow
of a soldier of the Banner Battalion.
As for the rest...
You must know Dorgon, Prince Rui, right?
The ancestor of the Plain White Banner,
the Regent Prince, Father of the Emperor.
Dorgon? Prince Rui?
Yes.
Her maiden family is a descendant of Dorgon.
You asked her to accompany me?
You...
That's deliberately making things difficult for me.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, I really didn't know.
Mother.
What should we do?
She's so drunk.
What do we do now?
Mother.
My son.
How dignified.
Be careful.
Slow down.
Very dignified.
There is a guest room in the mansion. How about…
Liang Xiang.
I'm here.
It seems that
I can't teach you anymore.
Go to the administrative ministry.
They want to see you.
Master,
please forgive me this time.
I love studying, Master.
Master.
Please forgive him.
Liang Xiang won’t do it again.
Go.
Liang Xiang.
It's not that I don't want to teach you,
but...
What's wrong, Liang?
Why do you look so listless?
How should I tell you?
We didn't expect
your ancestral family in the capital
to suddenly think of you either.
The document arrived yesterday.
They want you to reach Shanghai in three days.
Shanghai?
Why?
I also want to know why.
Why are they only reminded of
the ancestors of the Qing Dynasty
at a time like this?
The world is
in terrible turbulence.
On one hand, the internal strife of the party.
On the other hand, the threat of foreign powers.
In the battle of the Boxer Rebellion last year,
the Eight-Nation Alliance
seized Beijing city with less than 20,000 people.
They're still in there right now.
They still have our imperial capital hostage.
There have been several rounds of negotiations.
Tell me.
If a negotiation can't be reached,
what can you do
if they make themselves at home
and take advantage of us?
Nothing.
The Empress Dowager and the Emperor have gone to survey Xi'an.
In Xi'an,
they finally thought of reorganizing the army
and rebuilding the troops.
Look.
The official document
stated some facts.
Compared to their glorious ancestors,
princes of current times have become increasingly incompetent.
Some may be well-educated but fail to grasp the big picture.
They feed on tax funds but know nothing about civil affairs.
They indulge in arts and entertainment, treating knives and acrobatics
as mere amusement.
Do you understand, child?
It means,
members of the royal families in the capital
are rotten to the core.
They couldn't find a suitable candidate anymore.
That's why they found you.
Me?
They want to
send you to Japan to study military affairs
and expand your knowledge.
Study in Japan?
Me?
The Deputy General
told you in person?
Yes.
An official document from Beijing?
You're going to Japan to study?
I have to
sail to Shanghai in three days.
The cold pot is steaming.
The cold pot is steaming!
Mother.
Where are the herbs, Mother?
The cold pot is steaming.
My son.
[Anhui, Anqing]
Paste it on. Hurry.
Paste it on!
Stop!
Paste it on.
Eyebrows.
Don't take them off until we walk past the drum tower.
[Second daughter of Anqing Kaiwentang Stationery Shop, Xie Shuhong]
Do you hear me?
Bye.
Come here.
Who is it?
You.
Me?
Come here.
Are you Song Chen, the third son of the Song family?
[Son of the vice president of Shanghai Business Association, Song Chen]
Who are you?
Guess.
I don't have the time.
Wait.
I know who you are.
The second daughter of Kaiwentang Stationery Shop.
You remember me now?
You sure are bold.
Am I?
Why are you adding to my trouble?
See you, Mr. Song.
I...
Who is that beauty?
I'm asking you.
How would I know?
Are you fobbing me off again?
Do you want a beating?
You...
[Kaiwentang Stationery Shop]
Second Young Miss.
Father is so biased.
[First daughter of Kaiwentang Stationery Shop, Xueqing]
He got you such a good man
but got such a bad one for me.
You went to see him?
You guys decided on everything.
Of course I had to
see him for myself.
This has nothing to do with me.
Just blame our father if you want to.
He has his eyes on the Song family's money.
The president of the Shanghai Business Association
is too good to miss.
Our father is not that vulgar.
Then why didn't he get me a scholar too?
What's so good about a scholar?
Your sister just married
an empty title.
At the end of the day,
I'm still here handling everything
myself.
Don't be stubborn.
I just don't understand.
Tell me.
Is copulation
like reading a book?
You do it once
and it's no longer a big deal, right?
Watch your words.
Don't talk such nonsense.
You're a girl
and you're not married yet. How can you say such things?
I mean, just look at the state of you.
Brother-in-law
hasn't come back to visit you at all.
He didn't even send a letter.
That's not true.
See? He just asked someone to deliver this here.
Your brother-in-law is busy in Shanghai.
He asked me to go there too.
That's all he wrote?
He just had to
deliver his message.
What more did he have to write?
Will you go there?
If I go there like this,
I'll add to his worries.
So I want to discuss it with you.
Discuss with me?
The supplies mentioned in the letter
are urgently needed.
He needs someone to send them to him.
I thought about it.
I need you to help me
with this.
Me?
Your in-laws...
My in-laws?
The Song family has a head office in Shanghai.
Each month, they hire a private ship to travel to and fro.
Your brother-in-law asked to buy
so much stationery from our father.
I thought,
wouldn't it be more convenient to deliver them
with the Song family's ship?
It's convenient for you.
You can take the opportunity
and tie me to the Song family.
What are you talking about?
Am I that kind of person?
Don't you want to go to Shanghai?
[Shanghai]
[On the 5th month of the 27th year of Guangxu (July 1901), under the diplomatic coercion and military threats of imperialism,]
[The Qing government sent Emperor Guangxu's younger brother, Aisin Gioro Zaifeng, to Germany from Beijing to submit an apology letter.]
The Eight-Nation Alliance has occupied Beijing
and the North is at war.
We alone can enjoy prosperity.
[Shanghai Qinghe Qinlou Villa]
Prince Chun
[Vice President of Shanghai Business Association, Song Baoquan]
is visiting Germany.
He will pass by here
and board the ship here.
This is the time
to show our loyalty.
We should be respectful
and welcome them with all our hearts.
Right?
Yes!
Mr. Song.
This is the latest car model of 1900.
There is only one such car in Shanghai.
It was transported from London three days ago.
It's very fashionable.
Charlie, drive it away.
My lifestyle
is not so luxurious.
Drive this to the Chamber of Foreign Affairs.
Have it ready for Prince Chun's use only.
Who are you?
These are the independent army wealth coupons
you bought last year.
I brought them here for you.
It's 20,000 yuan in total.
Please have a look.
You worked for Tang Caichang.
Boping was my brother.
Last year, I did buy
20,000 yuan worth of his army wealth coupons.
But the right of the past is wrong in the present.
What a pity, young man.
Zhang Zhidong mercilessly killed the revolutionaries
and beheaded my brother.
Do you think I would still invest
in this pile of waste paper?
But the Commander-in-chief told me that
no matter the result of the revolution,
I must hand these coupons
to you personally.
As people,
we should keep our promises.
What do you think?
I won't make things difficult for you.
Chairman Song,
you can deal with these coupons
however you want.
But...
Can you do me a favor?
Go ahead.
I heard that
you just sponsored the Viceroy of Liangjiang
to send military students to study in Japan.
Yes, I did.
Then...
Can I be one of the students?
Hello.
Is Yang Yifan here?
[Shanghai Girls' School]
Mr. Yang. Mr. Yang.
Finding you was difficult.
I heard that
the emperor's younger brother is in Shanghai.
The main road was
completely jam-packed.
It was quite a grand setup.
Brother-in-law.
Why is His Majesty's brother making a scene?
It's nothing to be proud of.
It's shameful.
Shameful? Why?
They failed to win the battle.
Careful.
They couldn't sign the peace agreement in Beijing either.
So, the Eight-Nation Alliance stated that
the imperial court must send a first-tier prince
to Germany
and submit a letter of apology.
Isn't it shameful?
Hanhua.
You managed to recruit a student?
Not at all.
This is my sister-in-law.
We've been in the newspaper for seven days.
We haven't got a single student.
We'll take our time, there's no rush.
I was wondering why they were
so excited to see me.
Another day,
another sum of rent to pay.
Who organized this school?
I did.
[Principal of Shanghai Girls' School, Yang Yifan]
[Courtesy name: Hanhua]
You did?
Surprising, isn't it?
That's how things are in the Settlement.
You can do any business
and anything.
On your own,
you can own a big bank,
a big store, a big factory,
and even a school.
No one will stop you.
You can teach whatever you want.
There's only one type of rent tax called the Police Patrol Contribution.
The rest is up to you,
be it the school's rules
or the curriculum.
But why do you want to start a school?
Good question.
The cost is so high.
Can you make money out of this?
My sister would be worried if she knew.
You are more like your father than your sister.
All right, you can stay here.
It's empty anyway.
I need to discuss things
with my colleagues.
There are so many troublesome things to handle.
Wait, Brother-in-law.
Why didn't you take a look?
My sister brought you a bunch of
food and necessities.
We'll talk about it later.
By the way,
before you leave Shanghai,
I'll show you around,
okay?
No rush, Brother-in-law.
Can't we take our time?
I can even stay and help you.
Help me?
How?
I can't be a teacher.
But I can be a student, right?
All deals
are the same.
You have to first make yourself known.
We've been doing that.
We have been advertising our place for a week now.
You can start your class first.
If there are no students,
invite all the ladies and maids here.
The more,
the merrier.
They'll be your temporary students.
Once you start offering classes, you'll gain popularity.
Then, you can build a reputation
and attract actual students.
Good idea.
You're just like your father,
so much more than your sister.
[Shenghe Hotel]
[Reception for military students in Japan]