[A Love Never Lost]
[Episode 4]
Dr. Wu Tianbai
and Mrs. Wu are here.
Please.
Welcome, Dr. Wu.
Mrs. Wu.
The French consul, Mr. Morion,
and Miss Lucy are here.
What's wrong?
You're all shaking.
I'm fine.
Yihua.
Miss Lucy is greeting you.
Don't be afraid. Stay close to me.
Don't talk to anyone.
Make yourselves at home.
Don't mind us.
Who's the one you're so concerned about?
Who else could it be?
Your third son's
wife in Anqing.
My son's wife?
Which one is she?
The doctor's wife just now.
The doctor's wife?
My son's wife?
Where is she?
Forget it, My Lord.
Don't wash your dirty laundry in public.
Look around
for Prince Chun,
the man of the hour.
Is he here?
I don't know him.
He's a young man around 17 years old.
Is he at the head table?
There are only foreigners there.
The prince is so young?
Oh no.
I saw an acquaintance.
That fat guy?
Is he looking at me?
He's the Governor of Jiangsu.
I used to work under him.
Is he coming this way?
Listen.
Go back to the carriage now.
No matter what happens,
stay in the carriage.
How about you?
Don't worry about me. You leave first.
Tianbai, come here.
How have you been, Governor?
The pretty girl with you,
who is she?
My wife.
Get her here.
I'd like to meet her.
She left a piece of jewelry in the carriage.
By the way,
where is His Highness?
His Highness
wouldn't come somewhere like this.
So many people in Shanghai
want to curry favor with His Highness.
Is Song Baoquan worth His Highness' attention?
I see.
Tianbai.
You've wised up, right?
Good.
Later, you and your wife
should sit next to me.
I'll
give you some pointers.
Tianbai.
What's in your hand?
This
was meant for His Highness.
But since His Highness didn't come,
I might as well
give it to you,
you bloody traitor.
Tianbai!
Rebel!
Help!
Help! Rebel!
Tianbai.
Go!
Move! Move!
My Lord.
T-There's smoke.
Help!
My Lord!
Go after him!
Go! Go!
Don't let the rebel escape!
This is…
Why are you looking at me?
Your wife in Anqing chose her.
She…
She's quite something.
Where are we going?
Say something!
I told you.
We're destined
to be together.
Like it or not, you have to stay with me.
No. I'll leave you.
I'm done with you!
Are you scared?
This will implicate your whole family, won't it?
But it's too late now.
We'll go to Japan
and start all over.
You and I
are bound together.
We've made
headlines.
Therefore,
leaving with me
is the only way forward.
You have no other options.
[Shiliupu Pier, Shanghai]
One at a time.
Keep up.
Get out.
Let's go.
Tianbai.
I knew you hadn't left.
Hanhua.
Stop.
Don't say anything.
I'll clean up the mess you left.
But you have to promise me
to be nice to her.
I promise you.
Take good care of yourself in Japan.
If you get in trouble,
write to me at this address.
The ship is leaving.
Get aboard.
Hurry up.
Get aboard now.
Don't sit on that bunk.
Do you hear me?
Who are you talking to?
I'm talking to you.
Liang Xiang.
This bunk is mine.
Yours is the upper one.
Who are you to tell me
which bunk is mine?
Bannermen like you
love to look down
your noses at others.
You're the rule makers.
Am I wrong?
Kaizhi.
I've had enough of this.
Do you have to be so snarky?
We're both military students.
Don't be so mean.
Just because you know my secret
doesn't mean you can patronize me.
Listen.
I died once.
I fear nothing.
Both of you are here.
Which bunk is mine?
You'll sleep above Kaizhi.
He's rich and needs a bodyguard.
No problem.
Kaizhi.
I'll be your bodyguard.
Wuwei Corps Right Division
serves
wherever the money is.
This is the meal ticket.
The Japanese ship is great.
They offer
three meals a day.
You haven't answered my question.
What question?
Why did you do that?
Stop asking why.
You almost became a murderer, didn't you?
If that bomb
had really exploded,
how many people would've been injured?
How could you do that?
You're a teacher
at an all-girls school.
Yes.
I'm a teacher,
a scholar,
and a modern-day Jing Ke.
I was exercising my right.
This country is doomed.
The people are numb.
Someone has to stand up
to change everything,
to fire the people up,
even if it's a futile attempt.
This is fate.
We sink or swim together.
Sit here. Sit here.
Good morning.
I want…
Toilet.
This way, sir.
I'm going to the toilet.
I…
I want…
Water.
Okay.
I want…
This one.
Okay.
Wait.
All…
All of them.
I want the same.
Okay. I got it.
A Chinese girl.
My friend is seasick
and feeling very uncomfortable.
Can I bring some food and drinks
back to my room?
Of course.
Is your friend feeling dizzy
and nauseous?
Yes.
He vomited all night.
He's better now
but still very weak.
Is that guy Chinese
or Japanese?
This guy is from Japan.
Born and raised.
Miss,
I'll ask the kitchen
to prepare miso soup for you.
Please wait a moment.
Excuse me.
I'd like to order
the same breakfast
for my friend who's gone to the toilet.
Okay, sir.
Whoa, you're already eating.
It's funny that you really went to the toilet.
I had to keep up the act.
By the way,
the bathroom is very clean.
It smells good,
and the floor looks like a mirror.
If you spit on it,
guess what?
What?
You can slide from one end to the other.
It's true.
I swear.
Thank you.
They're making it now. It'll be ready soon.
He can actually speak Chinese?
So, you need to be careful with what you say.
One day,
I was walking on the street in Shanghai.
The old white woman walking in front of me
was very fat.
I said to Maichen,
"I wonder what she eats
to become so fat."
That old white woman
turned around and answered in Shanghai dialect,
"Food."
Also,
when Wuwei Corps Right Division
trained at Xiaozhan,
Mr. Yuan found several
German consultants for us.
They all had beards.
Like this.
Did they speak Chinese?
Only one sentence.
They knew it by heart.
Mr. Yuan said to the Germans,
"My soldiers are perfect,
except that
they don't aim when they shoot.
They shoot like this."
Mr. Yuan added,
"You need to teach them to aim."
The Germans replied,
"Leave it to us."
It was the only sentence
those Germans knew.
No matter what Mr. Yuan
asked them to do,
they replied with conviction,
"Leave it to us."
Your miso soup.
What's going on?
Eat. Stop staring.
Among the three of us,
Tufang has the best table manners.
Do I?
Do all the nobles
care about table manners?
My mother does.
We have a set of fine porcelain dinnerware.
She only takes it out when we have
distinguished guests.
She eats soup
with a spoon,
holds a teacup with both hands,
and never makes noise when she eats.
You hear that?
A real nobleman
can trace his noble lineage
at least three generations back.
By the way,
is your mother's ancestor
really Emperor's Father and Prince-Regent
Dorgon?
The family book says so.
You're of noble lineage.
You, Yang Kaizhi,
are from a family of scholars.
Only I, Li Renjun,
am from a line of shepherds.
Who told you
I'm from a family of scholars?
You studied at Ziqiang Institute in Wuchang,
didn't you?
You told him about me?
You studied at Ziqiang Institute in Wuchang?
The officials
of Shanghai Circuit have dug into the background
of every military student heading to Japan this year.
They know everything
about everyone.
The miso soup
is authentic.
It's appetizing.
Very appetizing.
By the way, can you get me some bread?
The freshly baked kind
with a delicious smell.
Hello.
Can I help you?
Are you taking the bread in your hand
back to your room?
Yes, it's freshly baked and still hot.
Yeah. It smells delicious.
Do you want it?
Take it if you do.
I can get some more from the dining room.
Can I?
Thank you very much.
Could you please
send it
to that cabin for me?
That one, 206.
You're welcome.
I'm glad to help.
206, right?
Does he like it?
Yes.
I think your husband
has a good appetite.
Excuse me.
Can I hang the laundry here?
Are you
asking me?
Is there a third person here?
Shall I ask about it for you?
I asked the chief steward.
First, there's a laundry room on board.
They offer laundry service for free.
These are all undergarments.
Why would I let strangers wash them?
You have a point.
What's the second?
If you want to wash clothes yourself,
the staff can dry them for you.
Dry them?
How?
I don't know.
Maybe they have a machine for it.
The chief steward also said
you can't hang your laundry
anywhere on the ship.
It's the rule here.
I got it.
The Japanese have so many rules.
Are you and your friends all military students?
Yes.
We're all
government-sponsored military students who will study in Japan.
You did your own laundry at home?
Yes.
You're better at it than me. I barely know how to do it.
I can see that.
Wash it like this.
Then this.
Let me wash them for you.
This is improper.
They reek of alcohol.
He drank a lot before going aboard
and puked all over himself.
Who is he to you?
No one.
Just an acquaintance.
Let me wash them for you.
You need
to soak the clothes in water for a while
before soaping them up.
I have soap.
Thank you.
I'm afraid he's feeling unwell again.
I need to go check on him.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Who's it, Shuhong?
I mentioned him.
A military student.
Let him in.
I'd better leave.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Nice to meet you.
I know Takagi Sakuzo.
What?
The principal
of the Imperial Japanese Army Academy.
I-I don't know him.
This is the only good thing about the Japanese.
No matter how high-ranking a general is,
you can go to his house to visit him.
Two years ago, I had tea with him.
One can't do the same
with Chinese dignitaries.
Hand me the scissors.
I need to trim my toenails.
Do you know
why Japan is willing
to nurture
new talent for our army?
Please
enlighten me.
The Japanese think
they must work with China
to fight against
Russia
and Western powers.
Yes.
Of course.
You don't need to care about
what the Japanese think.
Learn as much from them as you can
while they're willing to teach.
I think so too.
Was Xiang Yu brilliant?
X-Xiang Yu?
Who is Xiang Yu?
Do you know Xiang Yu?
Xiang Yu, the Hegemon-King of Chu?
See?
She knows more than you.
I know the Hegemon-King of Chu.
Xiang Yu only lost
one battle in his whole life.
Do you know who he lost to?
He lost to Han Xin at Gaixia.
Han Xin was even more brilliant than Xiang Yu.
But how did Han Xin
become so brilliant?
Do you know it?
What about you? Do you know it?
Just say it.
Don't keep us in suspense.
Look at you.
Not humble at all.
Don't learn from her.
You're ridiculous.
Why would he learn from me?
How many people
would be a big fool like me who believed your lies?
When did I lie to you?
What did I lie about?
Why would I lie to you?
The weak should humbly learn
from the strong.
Why was Han Xin so brilliant?
Because Han Xin
was once Xiang Yu's spear-bearing warrior,
which was a bodyguard.
Throughout the Battle of Julu,
when Xiang Yu ate, slept, fought,
and even when he pooped,
Han Xin was with him.
Han Xin
was trained by Xiang Yu.
Understand?
I understand.
Han Xin was brilliant
because he learned from
his enemy Xiang Yu.
Understand?
Yes.
Truly understanding that is not easy.
You can't get it.
Young man,
if you want to achieve something,
you have to be as humble as Han Xin.
You need to use your enemy's combat experience
to improve yourself.
By the way,
you…
I forgot to ask your name.
My name is Liang Xiang.
You're a Bannerman?
I'm a Bannerman.
If you want…
I shall take my leave.
See you.
He…
He's actually a Bannerman.
Qianli.
Why do you think
my noble birth
is a concern for so many people?
Who are you talking about?
Is it a concern for you?
Me?
It is,
isn't it?
Don't say that.
You're different from them.
From whom?
The princes
and young nobles.
You want honesty?
Everyone in Wuwei Corps Right Division
hates people from the Eight Banners.
They're full of themselves.
Are they?
Our country is in hot water now.
Those people
played a big part in it.
Does that include
His Majesty?
His Majesty is a good and talented emperor.
But…
But what?
He doesn't get to call the shots.
Someone's reigning behind a curtain.
What are you two doing here?
Just for some fresh air.
By the way,
the officer in charge just told me
after we arrive in Japan,
we can't
go straight to the Army Academy.
Really?
Then where will we be going?
We need to go to prep school first
and then intern in the Japanese Army Regiment.
Only after we're qualified
can we go to the Army Academy.
I'll be a private again?
How's that different from serving in Wuwei Corps Right Division?
I was already a squad leader.
Just go with the flow.
I've lived in military camps all my life.
I was born a reservist.
It's not that scary.
Yang Aiguo,
you've experienced death.
Whatever the future holds
can't daunt you,
right?
You know what?
Liang Xiang, in your veins,
there's courage running.
You're composed
whatever happens.
I'm different from you guys.
In my mother's words,
it's a miracle
that I get to study abroad in Japan.
You two must have met before.
He left?
He left just like that?
Yes.
His Highness boarded a ship at Shiliupu Pier
this morning at 6:15.
He'll take the ship Guangji to Wusong first
and then transfer
to the German cruise Baian.
It's a huge ship that weighs 12,000 tons.
You did quite a bit of research this time.
Mr. Song.
We should thank God
His Highness didn't come.
Otherwise…
What do the police say?
They've opened a case
but haven't caught the criminals.
I see.
I heard the criminals are a man and a woman.
The Governor of Jiangsu knows that man.
But no one knows…
who that woman is.
I'm not interested in that.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll take my leave.
Baoquan.
Is it about your third son's wife?
Don't speak of her again.
Never again.
That woman had nothing to do
with the Song family
and will have nothing to do
with us in the future.
Understand?
Why are you yelling at me?
Your wife in Anqing is the one to blame.
My goodness.
We're arriving in Japan soon.
Are you scared?
What I did will soon
track back to your parents
in Anqing.
Someone at the banquet knows me.
So…
Look at what you've done!
You have a doctorate in chemistry.
You're all about scientific rigor
and act like you know it all,
but in fact, you know nothing!
You were just messing around.
You acted on a whim.
No smart people
would do what you did.
You call this a revolution?
Obviously, we're
on different wavelengths.
Yeah.
How can a young girl from a small town
understand
the romantic dream of a revolutionary?
It's beyond you.
It is beyond me!
But however romantic your dream is,
you need to use your brain to make it come true.
Your bomb
didn't explode when it should have
and went off
when it shouldn't have.
Now you're in a tight spot
and escaping to Japan.
You don't understand.
What is romance?
Romance
is attempting the impossible.
It's Sisyphus'
constant endeavor to push
the boulder uphill.
It's all about that kind of spirit and courage.
Don't give me that!
I…
From the first day we met,
this is all you got.
You're a big talker.
Fine. I'm casting pearls before swine.
I'm casting pearls before swine.
Let me ask you.
After we go ashore,
how are we going to make a living?
Do you have a house in Japan?
Do you have enough money?
Will the police come after us again?
How do we get food and clothes? How do we live our lives?
Do you even have a plan?
I don't have a plan.
Shuhong.
It seems you still don't understand
the situation
you're in right now.
Situation?
What situation?
You're a fugitive on the run.
I'm a fugitive. So are you.
What kind of life should a fugitive expect?
With food on your plate,
a roof above your head,
and no one
coming after you,
you should be grateful.
Will they really go to Anqing?
Your whole family will be implicated.
In other words,
my father, mother, and sister
will all be implicated by us?
All my neighbors will know
the second lady of Kaiwen Hall
fooled around
with a punk
and caused an explosion in Shanghai.
Basically, yeah.
Shuhong.
Here, wipe your face.
Go away!
Stay away from me.
Stop crying.
Do you hear that?
That pretty girl is crying.
I hear it.
It's strange.
They don't look like a couple.
It's indeed strange.
Strange?
I don't think so.
Beautiful girls
usually have bad taste in men.
Attention, military students.
The ship will dock soon.
Take your belongings.
Later, line up on the deck
and get ready for the handover ceremony.
Everybody clear?
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
Take your belongings.
[Tokyo, Japan]
[The Roster of Chinese Students]
Newspaper. Newspaper.
Why are there so many Chinese people here?
Don't look so surprised.
Tens of
thousands of Chinese students
study in Tokyo.
Most of them
stay in Kanda.
Really?
Therefore,
it's fine that you don't speak
Japanese.
There are all sorts
of Chinese people here.
Educated people like me
and ignorant people like you
both can thrive here.
Wait. Wait.
This is it. Let's get settled.
[Bamboo]
Take off your shoes.