Episode 12
What is she doing back here?
Ha Eun Ju, you didn't end up getting fired?
You are hanging on as the President's connection. Why ask me?
She's so crazy, really.
Next time I will kill you with my own hands.
Are you alright?
Why don't you mind your own business?
Anyway, you're really amazing.
I didn't expect you'd accept to move to that place for rehearsal.
Stop right there.  It only feels bad when I hear a compliment from you.
Hong Yi Yeong, when you were a junior, did you take a class with me at Gyeongsang National University?
Something like Social Media Marketing...
Did that happen?
I think it's possible. But where are you asking, all of a sudden?
You can work on the test until noon.
If you are finished, leave the test answer sheet on the desk and leave.
Do you, by chance, remember that class' graduate assistant?
Graduate assistant?
I don't remember. Was there an assistant?
Never mind.  I don't have anything to talk to you about. Go.
What are you saying out of the blue?
Artists are also employees.
Rescind the wrongful dismissal.
Conductor Nam must apologize.
Sinyeong Philharmonic, reflect upon yourself.
Artists are also employees.
Rescind the wrongful dismissal.
As I live and breathe I never expected to see the Ministry of Labor come to do an audit.
Has the Chairwoman returned?
She comes back on the weekend.
Is President Go still in on a rampage?
Don't even mention it. He calls several times daily.
I think he's going to pass all the blame to me.
Yes.  That's why you should have told the Board your side of the story first.
As I think about it, she joined the orchestra the same time as we did.
Gong Seong Min entered our orchestra during a dark period and suffered a lot.
Artists are also employees.
Rescind the wrongful dismissal.
Conductor Nam must apologize.
If I am not reinstated, I'm going to city hall. I'll file a protest there.
Our orchestra has been running at a deficit for five years.
Don't lie.
The whole world knows that Sinyeong Group supports our orchestra.
Our funding was reduced a while ago.
If things are left as they are now, we will all be unemployed.
They are supporting Maestro Nam. Our orchestra is begging to be saved.
I am sorry but I can't take your side.
Unni, please save us. Save us.  We are your colleagues.
Before that, let me ask you just one thing.
Did you also think my performance was worth only 40 points?
I sent your résumé to Professor Kang at Sinyeong Music College.
You could teach a few hours there.
I gave you a letter of recommendation.
I quit singing because of vocal chord nodules.
I can still do music even if I can't perform.
I thought I was going to die, but dying isn't easy.
I've also been through it.
It's something even our juniors will have to suffer.  Someday.
Conductor, did you perhaps know that the dead Kim Ian had an older brother?
What are you talking about?
When I was at Gyeongsang University I took a liberal arts class with Hong Yi Yeong.
There was a graduate assistant.  He came once to proctor a test.
He also collected our homework on behalf of the professor.
What did that person have to do with Kim Ian?
I think he was Kim Ian's hyung.
Now, he is a member of our orchestra.
Come in.
Welcome. Coffee? I just made it.
No, I'm fine. What did you need?
It's nothing important. I wanted to ask you a quick question.
I heard something strange yesterday. Jang Yun is not Jang Yun.
I looked up the résumé you submitted to the Sinyeong Philharmonic.
Besides your name is all the rest here phony?
No.
You know that falsifying documents like this is a crime, don't you?
I know.
Then, may I ask why you used a phony name when you joined the orchestra?
No matter how much I think about it, I can't tell whether this is advantageous to you or not.
It's not as though you stole someone else's résumé. So why the hell did you do it?
I don't want to say anything. It's a very personal reason.
If you inform the orchestra and they fire me, I'll leave, no problem. You can go ahead and report it.
Is it possibly because you don't want someone to find out your true identity?
Just exactly who? For what reason?
You don't need to know.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
I understand you don't want the Sinyeong Philharmonic to know.
I'll take my time considering whether to report it or not.
That's all for today. Leave.
You scared me!
Why did the Conductor call you? You haven't done something wrong, have you?
Just... We were talking about the performance.
I was worried for nothing.
One isn't usually called out for a good reason.
Do you remember the percussion practice room with the Colberg?
I was going to visit with you before but we didn't because you passed out.
Yes, I remember. Why?
Would you like to go with me tomorrow?  We are taking a break from rehearsals.
Tomorrow?
Why tomorrow?
Do you have plans?
It's not an important appointment, however I cannot cancel it.
If you decline to see a Colberg, it must be an important appointment. Well, just—
Never mind. There won't be a next time.
How can you be so heartless?
Hello?
Ms. Hong Yi Yeong. Is six pm, by chance, a good time?
Let's have a lesson a little earlier.
This seems like the right place.
Hong Yi Yeong. Over here.
Is the practice room nearby?
Did you get lost on the way?
Yes, not really.
Are we not going to the practice room?
You're still a long way from entering the practice room.
Hold the mallet and stand there on tiptoe.
I'm sorry?
Don't make me repeat myself.  Stand firmly on your toes, keeping your heels up.
Oh. Yes.
Up to your chin, down to your belly button. Hit a 120 bpm four-beat tempo equally with both arms. Start.
Excuse me?
A tempo of 120 bpm and a 4/4 beat.
Yes.
Loosen your shoulders. Don't bring your arms lower than your belly button.
8/8 beat.
16/16.
Increase the tempo. 130 beats per minute.
140.
150.
160.
170.
I'm sorry. I nearly died.
Repeat everything from the beginning to now ten times.
What?
120 bpm 4/4 beat.
Yes sir.
I'm sorry I'm late.
How could you let the CEO wait like this?
The Chairwoman isn't present. It's my first time meeting you too.
I'm sorry. The meeting ended very late.
I'm sorry.  I've been very rude when we are meeting for the first time.
Don't worry.
It was a last-minute meeting scheduled to suit me, so I should be flexible.
- Please bring another menu here.
- Yes.
- Have some wine.
We were talking and CEO Jang said that he is very interested in our art foundation.
And he has a deep interest in classical music.
I've heard it often from the Chairwoman.
She said you're even a patron for many organizations.
You're embarassing me.
Professor Kang told me you were very aggressive so I expected someone very scary.
You aren't at all.
What I said is correct.
She looks like a flower, but our General Manager Yun is very scary. We must be careful.
Especially when it comes to donations, you must be very careful.
I had hoped Maestro Nam would come with me today.  He suddenly had a flu fever.
Next time we will greet you together.
Don't worry about it. I'm here to meet you two today.
Cheers.
Ah, it hurts.
I'm sorry.
No, I just don't have strength in my arms.
Thank you.
It's no problem.
He's not home yet.
Yeah, Unni?
I had a lesson today, so I'm home late.
Yesterday I was acting a bit sensitive. You aren't mad at me, right?
If I got angry about something like that, I would die of stress.
Then, it's all good.
However... I really don't want you to be talking about the accident.
Mom and Dad too. They said they were heartbroken after you left.
We have forgotten nearly everything and are getting over it.  Let's not dig out more details of that day.
That would be good for you too.
Okay.
Are you prepared for your blind date?
Prepare what?
It's all because of you. Why did you have to hurt your leg?
This is the first time I've been grateful for crutches.
You should try it out. It'd be good if he was a good person.
Forget it. I'm hanging up.
What is this?
Did that jerk Jae Hyeong break in again?
This fool!
Noona Yi Yeong
Why aren't you picking up? It keeps ringing, so it must be important.
Forget it.
So, you had something you wanted to tell me?
What's this?
Are you perhaps afraid that your beloved cousin murdered someone?
When did you take this?
Have you been following me?
Why would I be following you?
I took it coincidentally while I was waiting for Yi Yeong.
So what about that picture did you want me to see?
I heard that day.
- Noona Su Yeong told you to keep away from Yi Yeong.
- And?
- Isn't there a reason that Noona Su Yeong was so angry?
- So what if there is?
This photo... can I show it to Yi Yeong?
Are you threatening me right now?
It's not a threat. I'm making a reasonable request.
From now on, keep away from Noona Yi Yeong!
You keep away! You, you—
Don't you recall what you did to her?
- A person can make a mistake at least once in their life.
- A mistake?
You don't make any mistakes, Hyung?
You get out of here. Don't look for me.
Noona Yi Yeong really is a good person.
So what?
Even if I am young, I am good at reading people.
But in my eyes, you don't seem like a good guy.
You seem like you would hurt her.
Because of my mistake, I also hurt her, but her getting hurt again, because of you...
I don't want to see it, even on my death bed.
Then you tell her yourself that I seem  like a bad guy.
And you show her this pic directly, alright?
This little kid.
Insomnia
You don't seem like a good guy in my eyes.
You seem like you would hurt her.
Show some concern about how you dress.
Good luck. Don't be rude like your unni.
Don't worry.
I dressed myself up nice and will mind my manners too.
I won't swear.
You said you had plans but...
you were going on a blind date?
Well, about that...
I ended having to go after fighting with my sister.
You worked at getting ready.  You dressed in pretty clothing.
Can you walk down the stairs?
Of course.
What are you doing to do if you get hurt?
Since you are going on a blind date and all.
Don't make fun of me, okay?
Are you in a teasing mood? I'm going to the blind date.
So what?
You really don't care that I'm going on a blind date?
The fact that I'm going on a blind date.
You know that I'm not going to tell you to not go.
If that is so, who is being calm? You're in a foul mood.
So disappointing.
So should you just not go and spend some time with me?
There's is not even one drop of sincerity in your voice.
Go exercise or something.
I'm being serious though...
♫ Darling you mean the whole wide world to me ♫
♫ Darling you are sweeter than an evergreen ♫
Yi Yeong, is there something wrong today?
Give me that photo.
Photo? What photo?
Give me the photo that you took from my house. You went there yesterday.
What are you talking about? I never went to your house yesterday.
Am I a moron? To do something a second time?
Are you going to keep lying?
It really wasn't you?
You didn't come to our house yesterday?
I said I didn't go.
I told you twice that I didn't go.
I really am disappointed in you.
Then if it's not you...?
Who is it then?
If it's not Jang Yun, then who is it?
Who... took my photo?
I'm sure it was  the same footprint.
If the second footprint is not Jae Hyeong's, and the first one is also not Jae Hyeong's, ...
Then is there another person other than Jang Yun who came into my house?
Are you cold?
Yes?
It seems like the air conditioner is on pretty strong right here.
If it's okay, can I give you my jacket?
No, no, it's okay.
If you are hot, you can take off your jacket.
No, no.
- Then... shall I?
- Sure.
Thank you.
Seems so much cooler now.
You look so pretty when you smile.
Huh? Oh, no no.
Are you possibly... hungry? Shall we go and get something to eat together?
I don't know good restaurants so I searched on the internet.
I sort of have plans... today.
So today is not good.
Then what about next weekend?
I think that also will be a bit hard to arrange.
You are busy, I see.
Then what about the next next weekend?
I'm sorry.
It's not that I don't like you.
Actually... I have someone that I like.
Seeing your face, I guess it didn't go well, huh?
It was awful I'll never go on a blind date again.
What do you want to do?
What do you think? Eat something delicious and go shopping.
And go see some busking too.
What's up with that?
What do you mean? It's a date.
A normal date.
Give us two orders of tteokbokki (rice cakes in spicy sauce
And kimbab
(Korean rolled sushi)
4 orders of odeng (fishcake)
Some soondae (blood sausage)
And next...
♫ Even though my body which is still floating as though I'm still living in a dream ♫
♫ goes to the place which it has gone to again I feel something's different too ♫
♫ Because it makes me think a lot again, saying without thinking much ♫
Impressive.
Yeah, well, let's get over that problem. Next
♫Stay with me ♫
How is it? Is it okay?
Wait a minute
♫Even if I were nervous, now it's all disappeared. ♫
Very comfy.
♫ It's not the dream of a moment ♫
How about this?
♫ I'm in love. I'm in love. ♫
What's it about?
A cat who was reincarnated 1 million times...
It meets a cat and falls in love one million times
and dies forever.
That story is so sad.
It's a beautiful story.   I'm feeling good so I'll buy it for you.
What's up with you?
♫ Stay by my side ♫
Go on in. Sleep well.
Didn't you turn off the music in the morning?
No. I don't own that album.
What?
Yesterday, I also thought  someone came into my house.
Then you should have told me!
I looked everywhere yesterday  but how come only that photo is missing?
The sneaker prints in the living room  are exactly the same as the last time, so I thought it was Jae Hyeong.
But he said it wasn't him.
How can we believe that?
I can know just by looking at him. It's obvious when he's lying.
I took a photo yesterday.
This is the time that Jae Hyeong came in.
And this is the print which I photographed yesterday.
What is the probability that the exactly same sneakers were worn by two other people?
If the footprint that I took a picture is not Jae Hyeong's, then...
that means it wasn't him yesterday  either.
We must change the lock tomorrow.
I will also check with the security guard.
First wash up and pack a bag.
What?
You can't sleep here tonight.
I can sleep on the sofa.
For someone who has insomnia, how could you sleep there?
I never imagined I would be sleeping in your bed.
I didn't know either.
I know it's hard to sleep in an unfamiliar bed, but give it your best shot.
I will.
- You still haven't located Yun Yeong Gil?
- Yes.
We can't find a trace of him.
He's like in a motel somewhere. He's like hiding too and...
That's that. The police officer who took Hong Yi Yeong's statement at the time of the incident.
We have to find out where he is.
Did you say he quit the police force?
He was emigrating to Canada.  I barely started asking around, and I was going to meet him.
He knew some things which weren't noted in the accident report.
That's not in the documents.
It's from when Hong Yi Yeong gave her statement for the first time.
Yun Yeong Gil was in a state of shock
and turned himself in immediately.  it was not in the official report, but
she said she thought she might have killed someone.
That she may have stabbed someone with a knife.
Where are you going?!
To the cable car!
Huh? Cable car?
Are you trying to ride that right now?
Have you ever seen a lunar eclipse?
There's a real shadow on the moon.
Why suddenly play a duet?
You're not playing the piano, right?
Now, look,
do it like that.
It looks as if you're holding your hyung's hand.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with me?
Last night, did you fall asleep?
Don't even kid around.
I fell asleep so fast like a baby.
Without both taking a sleeping pill and listening to your singing. It's amazing.
There are many amazing things.
That's normal. Let's go.
What?
Shall we just start dating?
I mean, I am a bit embarrassed to be the first one to say this.
I think I like you, Yun.
I thought about it today and I thought about it when I opened my eyes too
but I really like you.
That's a little... complicated though.
Complicated?
For you and me...
It will be difficult for us to have a relationship.
Difficult?
Why?
Because when Ian died,
there was another injury on his body
which wasn't from the car crash.
A stab wound.
The person who killed Ian could've been you.
What are you... now talking about?
You may not remember, but the person Ian loved
was you.
Timing and Subtitles by the Sing To Me Team @ viki
♫ It's okay even once in a while if your voice is soft ♫
♫ Please let me hear your song ♫
♫ So that I can love you more ♫
♫ I will treasure it alone for a long time ♫
I Wanna Hear Your Song
♫ Before thie feeling wanes ♫
Have you come here to me thinking that I stabbed your sibling?
What if I really did kill him?
How am I supposed to live then?
As things are, why are you sitting here?
I have somewhere I need to go but I just don't have the courage to go by myself.
You were with Yi Yeong yesterday, weren't you?
Do you remember someone named Jang Do Hun?
Yi Yeong!
I think what they are telling the truth.
I'm not going to run away. I will show you.
♫ It's okay even once in a while if your voice is soft ♫