Episode 28
Is there a reason you wanted to see me so suddenly?
I thought you would have serious heartache lately, because of your son, so I contacted you immediately.
Although  I am embarrassed because my son may have tainted the orchestra's image,
he didn't murder anyone.  He was framed.
Framed?  Are you saying he has been blamed for someone else's crime?
Is it alright if I let you in on one of my secrets?
Of course. Let it out, I like these things.
It's been said that Yun Yeong Gil, who fell in the Sinyeong building not long ago,
was the hit-and-run driver in the accident which killed pianist Kim Ian a year ago.
Yes, that's what the news said, but what does that have to do with your secret?
The pianist Kim Ian, who was killed in that accident,
was actually  my son.
- Your son?
- Yes.
We were separated when he was young so I rarely saw his face.
How ... in the world ...
That's why I said it is a secret. But you know what?
Recently I visited my oldest son,  who told me something very interesting.
What did he say?
He said Conductor Nam Ju Wan, Professor Kang Myeong Seok and the dead Yun Yeong Gil
are all involved in my son's case.
What is meant by that?
Well, I'm just saying that is what I heard. How will you deal with the consequences
if the conductor and the son-in-law of Sinyeong Group are involved in a murder?
It's a bit worrisome.
- Did CEO Jang really say that?
- That's what he said.
But, as I think about it, it's strange.
Why would the culprit of the Kim Ian hit-and-run die in our building?
Are you positive you have nothing to do with the accident?
Really. Why are you dragging me in? No way.
And, even if I did. Both Kim Ian and the hit-and-run driver are dead and buried.
What benefit do we gain in raking over the ashes of those incidents?
It would be nice if everything were covered up soon by public disclosure of Jang Yun's charges.
Is everything going well, Conductor?
Thanks to you.
The court released  the suspect in this case, so I kind of lost my enthusiasm for it.
So I thought a second round of interrogation was unnecessary.
However, there's something I need to verify.
Please go ahead.
According to our investigation, you and Sinyeong Music College Professor Kang Myeong Suk are very close.
He sent you to study abroad, paid for your tuition and recommended you for the conductor post.
He has helped me a lot, since I was a student.
So, are you still on good terms?
What do you mean?
I mean, are you two getting along?
Sometimes we argue.
Did you ever argue because of the late Yun Yeong Gil?
Yes, we did.
When?
The night of the day that Yun Yeong Gil's body was discovered.
He asked me I killed him and I said some nasty things.
I got so emotional that I spoke without thinking.
But why did he ask you if you killed Yun Yeong Gil?
I don't know. Call him and ask him.
Actually, a tip-off video arrived this morning.
You've been suspecting me for a year. But do you have evidence that I killed Kim Ian?
If you do, let's see it. Say it after you show it.
Isn't that what Yun Yeong Gil had, evidence of who killed Kim Ian?
So I killed Yun Yeong Gil in order to hide that evidence?
I can't hear it clearly, but if you watch the middle of the video,
you said to Professor Kang that he killed Yun Yeong Gil because he had evidence that Professor Kang killed Kim Ian.
Well, that is what you are saying.
Is that so?
- Didn't you say that?
- I don't remember.
From my perspective, you, Professor Kang, Yun Yeong Gil, and Kim Ian are all connected.
Was Yun Yeong Gil just a fan of yours?
Yes.  He was my fan.
Do you know the stairs where Yun Yeong Gil died?
Were you ever near the exit to that stairway that day?
No, I ...  I didn't go in that direction.
Ms. Assistant.
- Why are you running away?
- When did I?
- You just did as soon as you saw me.
- You know that's not so.
Are you denying you keep running away, Miss Judas?
I am not Ju Da. Get out of my way.
Okay. Okay.  Let's say you are not Ju Da.
- Have you eaten?
- What did you say?
- Want to have a meal together?
- I don't.
If not rice, what do you like to eat?
(Eating bap, "rice", in Korea is synonymous with having a meal)
Where did you go to search for the conductor on the day of the concert?
I don't remember.
Don't do that.  Try to remember.
You remembered precisely before that you had not gone to the exit to the stairway where Yun Yeong Gil was found.
I don't know.
Did you go to the rooftop?  If you went, I'm sure you would recall.
If you continue to question me that way, I'm leaving.
Excuse me.  I'm sorry.  I'm sorry.  Is there anything else you want to eat?
Is there anything else you want to eat? Order something.
Can I have whatever I want?
Eat up.
- Do you like the conductor?
- Who said so?
Ju Da kept attacking Hong Yi Yeong.
Calling her a poodle, stuck-up, whatever.
So it was quite obvious.
Actually, it's correct that she is a poodle. She was picked on because she deserved it...
You saw the conductor that day.  Where did you see him?
If you're trying to protect the conductor because you like him, that's wrong.  That's a crime.
Protect, who's protecting whom?  That's not so.
Then, what is it?
That is ... I was so frightened.
What exactly did you see that day? It's okay. Take your time and tell me.
That day. I went to look for the conductor in the hallway.
I wondered if he had gone outside because he was nervous,
so I went outside.
I searched for him all over the rooftop,
but I didn't find him anywhere.
And then I happened to ...
because I thought I saw someone through a window...
I'm leaving now.
Hey there!  Wait!
Wait!
This is driving me crazy.
So Jang Yun really made a recording that day?
Then did you think it was a joke?
The police have the video.  I saw it.
Damn. My face was filmed so the police will summon me.
- Are you afraid?
- Why would I be afraid? It's just a bother.
Yun Yeong Gil was your doing. Why do I have to be involved?
You don't have any proof.
If you continue to do that, I'll say you killed Kim Ian last year.
If not, would you like to turn yourself in with me?
Why should I? A culprit should turn himself in.
Fine.  Let's say I'm the criminal.   There are no witnesses and Hong Yi Yeong can't remember anything.
The only people who know what happened that day are you and I, so why would I turn myself in?
Ju Wan, you and I just have to play dumb and close our eyes.
Don't you think of your family? Don't you feel sorry for the grandmother who raised you?
What are you going to do about conducting? Can you live without music?
For you, that's your whole life, your everything.
- Are you certain Hong Yi Yeong won't ever regain her memory?
- What?
She already recalls that I was in the warehouse.
It's only a matter of time.
Wait a moment.  Wait.
What's wrong with you?  I'm going to report you.
I'm not trying to harass you.  I was waiting for you to ask a favor of you.
The reason I'm like this ...
is my brother died a year ago.
Yes. It was on the news.
I'm looking for the man who killed my brother
and you are a witness to him committing a crime. That is what I believe.
It's not proof that he killed my brother, but it could be the key to getting him to talk.
If you saw something that day,  I beg you to  tell me.
I promise I won't tell anyone about you.
I beg of you.
I arrived a little early and came in.
After I get the item, I'll leave. When you come, if I'm not outside, come in.
Oh, you're here.
Hello.  I'm sorry I left yesterday.
You're here to pick up what the late customer left.  Just a moment.
I took care to put it aside yesterday.
Here.
Cathedrale d'Auxerre
Bach Fugue in G Minor
Is this it? What the ahjussi left?
Yes.  It's a requiem isn't it?
Yes.
He used to listen to old pop music.  Why, of all things, is this a requiem?
Is this everything?  Did he leave anything else?
No.  That's the only thing.
Thank you. Next time, I will come  back to really listen to music.
We see each other again, Hong Yi Yeong.
Yi Yeong!  Hey, Yi Yeong!  Hong Yi Yeong, wait!
Hey, Hong Yi Yeong! Stop.  Let's talk.
Hello.
Professor Kang came to the café.
I ran away but he's following me.
I'm here near the café ...
Stop there. Hey!
Yi Yeong.
Yoon.  Behind me ...
Hello.
Yi Yeong!
1 year before
Track 01
I'll let you meet him.
You want to meet him. I said I will let you meet him.
Satisfied?
Sorry.
Please don't say that. But I have a request.
Just until we arrive at Professor Song's house, let's smile.
I don't want to be in a gloomy mood with you.
Yeah.
That car's a little weird.
Which car?
The black car behind us.
I think it has been following us since earlier.
Us, why us?
What's the matter with that car?
Are you okay?
Hold onto the handlebar!
Just what is he doing?  This is not going to do.  I'm going to report him.
Calm down.  It's okay.
It's just thunder.
Take a big breath. Take a big breath.  Let it out.
Big breath.  Let it out.
Do you want me to make you laugh within ten seconds?
How?
Wait.  Wait and see.
♪ There is a man
("One Man" by Kim Jong Gook)
♪ He loves you so much
♪ There is a man
♪ He couldn't say he loved you
♪ If I reach my hand out to you
♪ I could touch you
♪ I'm the one who cares for you more than myself
See.   You laughed.
You really are an awful singer.
You know, Hong Yi Yeong?
Yeah?
There is one thing I didn't tell you.
I should tell you now.
To me?
What is it?
Who is it?
Who are you?
You, who are you?
Who is doing this to us?
Who is it? Please don't come close.
Yi Yeong!
Who are you? Who are you?
Please help us, please help us, please...
Hong Yi Yeong!
Please spare us, please...
Don't come close! I will stab you if you come close!
Yi Yeong! Hong Yi Yeong! Don't touch that woman!
Get out of here.
Who are you?
There isn't much time, they will come for you soon. Use the knife to free yourself. Quickly.
Sunbae Ju Wan?
Don't waste time. Quickly get out of here!
Are you okay?
Danger ahead!
No. No. No!
Stay here, please.
Emergency Room
Why are you still here?
I asked why are you here.
Why are you with Yi Yeong?
Go! Go!
Stay away from Yi Yeong! Please!
Please go away! Please!
Mom, calm down.
- I'm sorry. Mom.
- Please stay away from us!
Why are you with Yi Yeong?
Please stay away...
I am sorry but even if you stay, you can't see her.
So please leave.
When I see her wake up, I'll leave.
At this point, don't you think you've done enough?
Please leave Yi Yeong alone.
The EMTs told me what happened. Although I know no one is at fault, I resent you.
Think about what you've done to her all of this time.
Because of the guilt of having stabbed your brother,  she's lived having erased all of her memories.
Then you showed up in front of her. Opening old wounds, digging around her life,
suspecting her and treating her as a murderer,
you hurt her and made her cry. In the end, you made her like that!
You made this happen!
I'm sorry.
Please let me see her face just once more.
I beg you. I'll just look once and go.
You don't deserve to see her. Since she met you,
I don't recall ever seeing Yi Yeong smile happily. She always looked pained.
How could you do this to someone you like?
If she doesn't wake up, you are responsible for it all.
♫ Because I can't forget.  I cry. ♫
♫ I cry. ♫
♫ Even if it is a lie. I  try ♫
♫ Why am I still looking for you here? ♫
♫ While I'm looking for you who won't come ♫
♫ So I try ♫
♫ You and I ♫
♫ On a day without you, I also am not there ♫
♫ I know also that this is a person I can't forget ♫
♫ Tell me what should doin’ it now ♫
♫ Even If it is a lie, tell me ♫
♫ Saying everything can be taken back ♫
♫ Even it is a brief moment ♫
♫ When  I call you thousands of times ♫
♫ I found myself but I’m still losing myself ♫
♫ Can you come back to me? ♫
♫ Because I can't forget I cry ♫
♫ Even if it is a lie, I try ♫
Instead of me,
I think it's right that you have this.
I'm so frightened that this is the only thing I can do.
I'm sorry.
Timing and Subtitles by the Sing To Me Team @ viki
♫ On the days I long and long again for you ♫
♫ I regret ♫
♫ that I couldn't hold on to you ♫
♫ On the days I long and long again for you ♫