Episode 10
Timing and Subtitles by the Sing To Me Team @ viki
This place is really in the middle of nowhere.
To think that this was where he spent his last moments.
It was a hit and run.
It was raining hard that day.
It was a truck that was making deliveries near that area.
Four hours after the accident, the driver turned himself in.
Because the streams of rain were so heavy,
he testified to the police that he didn't know he had hit Ian.
When he woke up from sleeping at a rest stop, he found blood on his vehicle, so he went to the police station.
After getting the call, I rushed to the hospital morgue.
It was the last time I saw him, dead and covered in blood.
Do you know what I regret the most right now?
There is something you regret?
Ian! What do I do?
I'm sorry.  I'm sorry, Ian.
While he was alive, not once did I...
I never held his hand even once, except for when he was little.
I see.
I didn't know that it was a hit and run.
Ian was hit by a truck on this road,
And Ian's car was found on a vacant lot nearby.
Why did he leave his car and walk down this road?
Last time, you said that the person he loved killed him.
So I thought that he was riding in the car that his girlfriend was driving,
and that's how the accident happened.
His girlfriend was found in another location the next day.  In a confused state.
What?
Does that mean they were in this location together?
Yes.
I don't really understand.
Then were they together and then fought and separated?
I wonder what happened that day?
You should have looked into it.
Do you think that I didn't look into it?
That's not what I'm saying.
I want to know more than anyone what happened that day.
To you, he may be just another person you can't remember,
But to me, he's the most important person.
Do you know what Ian was like when he was discovered?
He was practically in two pieces.
Eight of his ribs were broken.
They punctured his intestine, splintered his spleen, and ruptured his liver.
That's enough!
Please stop.
I'm not blaming you.
You said that the girlfriend is alive and well, so you can go ask her.
About what happened that day.
Is there a special reason why you can't ask?
A special reason why I can't ask?
She had no memory?  She can't remember anything that happened that day?
Are you serious?
What are you going to accomplish by meeting someone who doesn't remember?
We don't even know for sure if that woman was at the scene.
Her bag was in the car!
Hyung, you don't know how Ian died?  He died because of his abdominal organs ruptured.
His liver was stabbed by a knife!  But you still think it's a simple hit and run?
So you think now that the woman killed Ian?
I can't say that's not true.  Since she could be pretending not to remember.
What?
I'll find out what the truth is.
Isn't Hong Yi Yeong the only person who witnessed the events of that day?
Ian is dead, but that woman is still alive.
I don't know who his girlfriend is or where she lives.
The police won't tell me her identity.
I didn't know he was dating anyone in the first place.
I see.
You're not mad, are you?
Earlier, my emotions got the better  of me. I'm sorry.
It's fine.  I'm more sorry.
I don't even know anything, yet I asked an unnecessary question.
Where is the location of your accident?
Excuse me?
You said that you had an accident in a taxi.
I heard I was on the way to Professor Song's place,
so probably on the road from Seoul to Yongin?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.  Please stop the car for a minute.
Who are you? Who are you?
Is this place familiar?
It somehow felt familiar.
When were you in this warehouse?
A dream? I feels as if I saw it in a dream.
Let's go in. If you go in, you might remember something.
Calm down!
What is it?  What?
No! No!
Please open the door.  There's a person in here, please open the door!
Please open the door!
Help! Save me, please!
Please open the door.
Calm down, it's okay.
Save me!
Please help me!
I'm back.
Oh, you're back early, even though you had a work dinner.
I didn't want to go, so I just came here.
Father isn't here?
He went on a delivery.
Hey, call Yi Yeong.  She hasn't been answering her phone since earlier.
Why, Yi Yeong?  Is there something wrong?
What do you mean, is there something wrong?  I was going to tell her that I wanted to set her up on a blind date.
Do you think she already figured that out?
That blind date. Don't you see my crutches?
Do you know how much I'm suffering because of your blind dates?
This girl, who do you think you're screaming at?
Hurry up and call Yi Yeong.
When I can't get in touch with her, I can't even eat because I get worried.
I understand.
Unni
I reported it to 911 and the local police station, so someone should be here soon.
Are you better?
No.
Why were you so scared?  Did you really have a memory of being here before?
I'm not sure.
I kept seeing the scary images from my dreams.
What kinds of scenes?
I'm not sure.
I can't tell what.
Calm down.
It's okay.
Nothing will happen. It's okay.
Should I make you laugh in just ten seconds?
How?
Wait and see.
♫ Following a long shadow
♫ I'm walking with you in the darkness of twilight
♫ Holding hands, even if it forever,
♫ just being together makes me cry.
♫  Winter is approaching
♫ I'm not the only one weak.
♫ I love you like this and
♫ It's the only thing my heart can do.
♫ The only thing it can do.
You laughed, right?
Its so funny that I'm tearing up.
- I've been wanting to tell you for awhile...
- Yes?
You're really bad at singing.
You know, right?
That's so unexpected.
I told you that my specialty is singing badly.
But wasn't I kind of good today?
I'm doing all sorts of things after meeting you.
♫ Being with you is like walking through a green forest ♫
♫ I can't never get tired ♫
♫ It's okay even once in a while if your voice is soft ♫
What's the reason?
That you are able to sleep when you hear out-of-tune singing?
♫ So that I can love you more ♫
♫ For a long time ♫
I'm not sure why.
When I listen to it, for some strange reason, I feel at peace.
Especially your singing.
To me, it's a magical voice, like an angel.
The person who made the report, are you inside?
Yes, we're inside, here!
Quickly.
Are you alright? You're not hurt anywhere?
Yes, we're alright.
The warehouse custodian didn't know that anyone was inside and locked the door.
He's elderly, so he must not have heard you asking him to open the door.
Here, please come out.
Come in.
What are you doing here at this time?  Did you drink?
I drank.
I can't even play my instrument, so I was just going to drink myself to death.
Wait here. I'll take you home.
Are you drunk?
Do you know how many security cameras there are here?
I don't know, and I don't care.
It would be better if someone saw us.
You're not even a child.
Wait here. I'll be back quickly.
Is it alright if I don't get out?
I wonder why you're acting so child-like today.
Come on, quickly.
Don't drink so much.  Alcohol is not good when there's an infection.
Do I need to tell you that?
Leave some time free tomorrow.  I'll take you to a hospital that I go to.
I don't want to go home.  Can't you stay with me tonight?
Of course not.
Sleep well, and don't wake up.
I saw you that day, Conductor.
What are you suddenly talking about?
That day. One year ago, when we performed with Kim Ian.
What did you see that day?
You didn't go to the afterparty, you turned off your cellphone, and I saw you go somewhere.
By chance, did you meet Kim Ian that night?
Why would I meet Kim Ian?
Then, is it a coincidence that Kim Ian died that night in an accident?
If it's not a coincidence, are you saying that I killed him?
What kind of person do you think I am?
You're going to say anything just because I didn't let you play?
I'm just worried about you.
Worried about what?
I told you that I saw Hong Yi Yeong riding in Kim Ian's car.
As soon as you heard that, you disappeared somewhere.
Kim Ian died, and Hong Yi Yeong can't remember anything.
You keep paying attention to her. How could I not be worried?
I keep thinking you were swept into something bad—
Get rid of those useless worries. I went home and slept that night.
Don't you remember how hard I worked for three months for that performance?
I don't know why I have to explain myself to you like this.
Thanks.
Hong Yi Yeong!
Unni?
My mom and I must have called you more than ten times between us. Do you know how dangerous this world is?
Am I a kid?
You came to my house just because I didn't pick up?
With that leg.
How long have you known my mother?
If I hadn't said I'd come she would've called the cops.
Check your phone every once in a while!
Okay.
Here, tea.
Where did you go with Jang Yun? You used to talk about him being a stalker.
I said he's not a stalker.
Unni, do you remember a pianist who was in an accident last summer?
His name was Kim Ian.
Kim Ian? I think I heard of him before.
What about him?
Jang Yun is his older brother.
What?
I think it was because of my accident last year. I have no memory of Kim Ian at all.
I said I wanted to find my memories, and Jang Yun said he woul help me.
So we went to a place where I might remember him.
Ah, it's cold!
Unknown Caller
Who could it be?
Hello?
♫ Goodbye yellow brick road ♫
♫ Where the dogs of society howl ♫
Hello? Who is it?
♫ You can't plant me in your penthouse ♫
Did something happen? What about your cousin?
She gave me medicine and left.
Is it okay if I come in? It's a bit scary to be at home alone.
Sure.
I'm sorry.
Want something to drink?
Thank you.
Has something like this happened before?
No, this is the first time.
Call me immediately if it happens again.
I will.
What is it?
No, just...
I just haven't sat here and admired your home before.
When you first moved next door, I thought you were a weird person.
I heard you thought I was a stalker.
That happened, too.
A lot of stuff happened. I got really mad yesterday.
To be honest, it's not that I have nothing to be anxious about.
Looking back, I think it was a relief.
That you came here, so close to me.
Can you please play piano a bit for me?
It's not common to see such an expensive piano in this neighborhood.
Oh, you're here? Come in.
It's been a while, our star conductor.
No matter how popular as you are, what can I do to see you when it's so difficult?
The performance date is so close.
First, accept my glass.
Last week, I went with Father-in-law to a golf meeting, and he asked about you.
You should meet with him no matter how busy you are, don't you think so?
He's the bemefactor who put a young guy still wet behind the ears,
having nothing but a body, in such a position.
I'll make some time.
What is all this?
I thought you were a prodigy, but I guess you worked hard.
You must have practiced so much. The pages are in tatters.
Don't just touch it like that.
Hey, are you getting shy?
Saint Saëns Second Concerto in G Minor for Two Pianos
Oh!
Beethoven!
I played this so much when I was young.
Can you please play for me just this once?
Why should I?
Don't be like that. I want to hear it, after a long time.
I don't want to.
Come on, come on, sit down.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
Alright! For the music,
I will choose one I like.
Für Elise
I heard you have Hong Yi Yeong as your assistant.
Yes, well.
Hey. You're also someone who's hard to figure out.
I feel disgusted whenever I see her, because she reminds me of a dead person.
Just what do you intend?
You're Ha Eun Ju, right?
For starters, the man in the picture whom you wanted me to investigate
is, like you said, not Jang Yun.
I followed him around to find out his identity and he works part-time at an Italian restaurant.
Just in case, I looked into the restaurant and I found something.
What kind of information?
Have you perhaps heard of Nano Semi-conductor?  It's a semi-conductor company.
- It invested there, in the restaurant.
- Nano Semi-conductor?
Yes. They said the CEO is Jang Seok Hyeon.
By chance, do you know Kim Ian?
That man is Jang Yun's younger brother.
Kim Ian is?
Are you watching her or something?
Oh, you're here?
By the way, you knew each other before, didn't you?
It's been a while.
You had a younger brother?  What did he do?
He was a pianist. Kim Ian.
He died a year ago. He was murdered.
- Who killed him?
- Someone he loved.
- How is his girlfriend doing?
- She is alive and well.
Then you can go ask her.
Is there a reason why you can't?
Don't you want to know what's in your lost memory?
One year ago
- What's your name?
- Why my name?
Why are you being that way? When two people first meet, they usually start with their name.
So what's yours?
It's Hong Yi Yeong.
Hong Yi Yeong. That's a pretty name.
Should I tell you my name too, or not?
I already know yours.
I called your name more than a hundred times today.
Kim Ian. Ian Kim.
Not that name, my real name!
My real name is Jang Yun.
In Dong Jang, Yun Taek Hal, Yun,  Jang Yun.
Timing and Subtitles by the Sing To Me Team @ viki
♫ My memories that I loved changed ♫
♫ Until I shed all my tears ♫
♫ Even I beg you on my knees, even on my knees, don't hug me ♫
I Wanna Hear Your Song
♫ Even if I have a lot of scars, I'm okay. ♫
Are you afraid that Hong Yi Yeong might remember that day soon?
Are you afraid that your beloved cousin might be a murderer?
I want to have some fun.
What do you want to do?
Date.
An ordinary date.
I heard something weird.
I heard that you are not Jang Yun.
When you were a junior, did you take a class with me at Gyeongsang National University?
Do you happen to remember the assistant for that class?
We're meeting frequently.
I'm thinking of moving into this neighborhood.
I think I like you.
Do you want to date?
♫  I call you who has lost your way beyond the sunset ♫