Episode 30
- One more photo?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I found this in your dressing room. This belongs to Professor Song, doesn't it?
I think it is his. I'll return it to him.
We should take some photos, too.
Principal, please take a photo of us.
One, two, three.
- Thank you.
It came out well, it looks good.
Only you look good, what is this?
Yi Yeong.
I don't have any coins right now, so can you get me a drink from the vending machine?
I'm suddenly so thirsty, I think I'll die.
Suddenly so thirsty?
- Sure, what do you want?
- Anything, the cheapest one.
You always say "Anything, the cheapest one."
He usually did that when he was lying.
Really?
I was there too, that day, in the lobby after the performance.
Were you?
Then we could have met that day.
To be honest, I couldn't watch Ian's performance until the end.
Why not?
I got a bit jealous.
Have I told you why I quit piano?
No.
It was because of Ian.
When I hear him play, it felt meaningless
for me to continue playing piano.
I had a hard time with that, back then.
Thinking about it now, I don't know why I ever had such thoughts.
In any case, I was in the car,
and went to the lobby  right after the performance ended.
Sure, what do you want?
Anything, the cheapest one.
You always say "Anything, the cheapest one."
- Thanks.
- Sure.
Oh, Hyung.
Why are you still here, not going to the after party?
I wanted to take some photos.
Sorry, I'm just so warm right now.
Can you please take this and my performance jacket and put it in your car?
Right now?
- Yes, right now.-
Sure.
Thanks.
So that's why you had his clothes.
I didn't go to the after party that day and went right home.
On my way to my car, I saw our mom.
I wasn't feeling very good and I didn't want to go to the after party.
And Ian kept calling me,
but I didn't answer his calls.
I wonder what he wanted to tell me.
If I only answered his call,
would he still have died that way?
I thought about that hundreds of times.
Don't blame yourself anymore.
You didn't do anything wrong that day.
Ah, about Conductor,
on the day of the incident, I thought he was there to kill us,
but I don't think that was the case.
He was there to rescue us.
Rescue you?
Please spare us, please spare us...
I thought I removed the rope that was tying my wrists, but it wasn't me.
The Conductor cut the rope with the knife that he had.
And he told us to run away quickly.
Run away from here.
Who are you?
Sunbae Ju Wan?
Don't waste time and get out quickly!
I reproached him so much, calling him Ian's murderer.
But that wasn't true.
Whether he killed Ian or not, he is a murderer.
What does that mean?
Nam Ju Wan killed Yun Yeong Gil. There is a witness.
Is that true?
I have the video.
This... who sent this to you? Do the police know, too?
They will, soon. The witness even uploaded a message on a bulletin board.
The police will investigate soon.
I told him to turn himself in.
But if you really killed someone, Conductor,
I wish you will turn yourself in, even now.
Turn yourself in, I will give you an opportunity. Please tell them who really killed Ian.
Do you want to see someone else get hurt or killed?
Is it Hong Yi Yeong's turn next?
Please stop lying.
You are someone I looked up to for seven years.
Where is the Conductor that I liked and respected so much?
Hong Yi Yeong
Conductor?
Oh, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I called because I have something I really wanted to tell you.
What is it?
I finally remembered everything.
You didn't come to that warehouse that night to kill Kim Ian and me,
you came to rescue us, didn't you?
Yun showed me a video of you today.
The video with Yun Yeong Gil.
I don't know what other people think,
but I am sure you did not kill Kim Ian.
So why did such bad things happen between you and Yun Yeong Gil?
Thinking about that makes my heart hurt so much.
You know everything about what happened that day, don't you?
Before more bad things happen,
can't you help us find who killed Kim Ian?
I request your help.
I would really like
that no more people were to be hurt or killed because of what happened that day.
Yang Su Jeong?
- We have met once before, haven't we?
- Yes.
We did some investigating.
You are the one who uploaded a message on the Sinyeong Philharmonic bulletin board
with the nickname "Yu Da," aren't you?
Saying that you are a witness to what happened that night?
Shall we talk? And you have your cell phone with you, don't you?
What about it?
We have a confiscation warrant for your cell phone, Yang Su Jeong.
We will confirm something and return it to you. Show her the warrant.
Yang Su Jeong! Yang Su Jeong!
Yang Su Jeong!
Just listen to us, please.
Out of the way, please!
Sorry, we are sorry.
Yang Su Jeong?
Calm down, please.
Why do large conglomerates need cultural foundations? Hotbeds of corruption. Who is Ms. Yun of Sinyeong Philharmonic?
Corruption in a cultural foundation, and how an employee is involved.
Has Ms. Yun embezzled foundation funds? Rumors that a music foundation
for rural youth never existed. Sinyeong Philharmonic reputation ruined.
This is my notebook computer. Don't ever open it.
It's full of all the bad things I've done here.
If you look at it, you will come to hate me.
Keep it for me, and throw it in the Han River when you get a chance.
Are you really alright?
Do I look alright? I may go to prison.
Whatever happens to me, or whether Sinyeong Philharmonic disappears or not,
you can just go back to the U.S. You have family there.
But not me. I have to survive somehow.
I request this favor.
Why are you so calm?
There is a witness, what will you do?
Are you thinking about turning yourself in?
Who knows? I'm thinking about it.
How about going abroad for a while? I can send you for about three years.
I'll probably get arrested at the airport.
So why did you let things come to this point?
You should have given me some room to move, at the very least.
What are you so anxious about?
Are you afraid that if I'm arrested, you will be dragged along, too?
Don't worry too much about that.
Yun Yeong Gil was stalking me, he demanded money,
we fought and he fell by accident. That's how I will take care of it.
For the time being, don't come to see me.
I won't be able to, even if I want to.
There is something that I am curious about, regarding that day a year ago.
A year ago? What now?
You arrived in your car to the accident site on the highway, then rode in Yun Yeong Gil's car, didn't you?
Why are you talking about this again, now?
I was just curious.
When Yun Yeong Gil got out of his car and chased Yi Yeong,
weren't you riding in the back seat of his car?
While just watching Ian after he was stabbed?
He didn't even see your face, so why did you kill him?
So you're really making me into a murderer, aren't you?
Because you don't want to go down alone? Sorry,
but the person who hit Kim Ian with the car was Yun Yeong Gil.
No.
Yun Yeong Gil was chasing Hong Yi Yeong. I saw it.
And the person in the car was you, Professor.
No! What do you know?
There were five people at the site that night, weren't there?
Yun Yeong Gil was chasing Hong Yi Yeong,
and Ian was lying in the road, after he was stabbed.
And I was going there. Since I didn't kill Kim Ian, it was you.
But you killed him.
Because you appeared and he saw your face. Isn't that right?
Then why are you looking for the evidence that Yun Yeong Gil hid?
You are afraid that your face is recorded on that.
Because you ran over a living person with a car.
Why did you kill him? He didn't know anything.
Even if he saw your face, he wouldn't have done anything.
Don't act big, when you're the one who doesn't know anything.
That day, he threatened me first, got it?
Why it was me getting out of the car? Was it me who was doing this to them?
He asked if other people knew
that I'm going around doing such things.
He asked me that while smirking!
Is that why you killed him?
Yes. I killed him.
Why? Going to throw me in prison or something?
I'm regretting to death that I can't see that for myself.
Conductor Nam Ju Wan.
Why are you doing this now, after being quiet for a year?
You were insisting that you didn't kill Yun Yeong Gil, but are you now scared because there is a witness?
You just don't want to go down alone? Are you going to drag me in and confess to our crimes together?
And if you do, does that somehow mitigate your committing murder?
If you confess or not, that is your choice.
But I will never become Kim Ian's murderer like you want.
Why not?
Because there is a witness for your crime, but there is no evidence for mine.
Is that unfair?
The world is unfair.
So don't exert yourself needlessly, just go home and wait for the police.
Before I accuse of you of killing Kim Ian a year ago, too.
Hold on, hold on.
Conductor, did you really ...
kill Yun Yeong Gil?
Yes.
How?
He came right before the performance to demand money.
We fought physically and I pushed him, which caused him to fall down the stairs.
You even killed someone. What do you have to say to me?
I wanted to tell you what happened that day.
That day?
A year ago, the day Ian died.
Why are you telling me that now? What use is it now?
You killed someone.
Are you about to tell me that you killed Kim Ian, too, perhaps?
No. Can't you just hear me out?
I feel you are the only one who will believe me. I request this of you.
After the performance that day, I saw Kang Myeong Seok meeting with Yun Yeong Gil.
Professor Kang told him to find the ballpoint pen he had lost,
and that Hong Yi Yeong and Kim Ian had taken it.
I already knew Yun Yeong Gil was dangerous, so I followed him,
and saw him come out of a warehouse.
And you went inside?
Yes. I thought I should help free those two kids.
That was when things began to get twisted.
Twisted?
From this point on, I just heard about it, because I didn't see it.
Yi Yeong ran away with the knife that I had dropped.
It's dangerous!
And Ian was stabbed with it.
When I finally got to the scene,
Ian's dead body was there.
Who killed him?
I don't know, because I didn't see it.
Until now, all I had was a suspicion.
But now? You know who it was?
I have a request of you.
What is it?
This is a key for the last locker in our waiting room.
If something happens to me, please give what's in that locker to Jang Yun.
What will happen?
I don't know when we will meet again. But on that day,
let's see each other with a smile.
It's sweet.
Yes, it's yummy.
Is Uncle alright?
Don't worry about him.
Oh, look at that, you will get a scar.
Here, let me see.
No, no.
Just leave it.
Conductor?
Conductor Nam Ju Wan
What's going on?
I heard Hong Yi Yeong got hurt while rescuing someone?
Yes.
She is as nosy as ever. Is she badly hurt?
A bit.
If she had broken a leg or something, I would have felt refreshed.
How can you say such a thing?
What do you want?
Conductor asked me to give this to you.
What is this?
It's the key to the last locker in the waiting room at Sinyeong Philharmonic.
That day, a year ago, what Conductor saw
was Kim Ian's dead body.
He did not see who killed Kim Ian.
How about trusting him, just this once?
Nam Ju Wan?
You will have to come with us. You are a suspect for Yun Yeong Gil's murder.
You have the right to be silent, and you have a right to an attorney.
Breaking news.
At around 2 p.m. today, Mr. Nam, a man in his 30s, who was appointed to the permanent post of Conductor,
was arrested without a warrant as a suspect for the murder of Mr. Yun,
who died in Sinyeong Philharmonic's building.
Two men are involved in a fierce physical fight.
And one of them pushes the other forcefully.
The police used this video as evidence
and, after investigation, applied for an arrest warrant.
Then why are you looking for the evidence that Yun Yeong Gil hid?
You are afraid that your face is recorded on that.
Because you ran over a living person with a car.
Why did you kill him?
He didn't know anything.
Even if he saw your face, he wouldn't have done anything.
Don't act big, when you're the one who doesn't know anything.
Why it was me getting out of the car? Was it me who was doing this to them?
He asked if other people knew that I'm going around doing such things.
He asked me while smirking!
Is that why you killed him?
Yes. I killed him. Why?
Going to throw me in prison or something?
What is in that ballpoint pen, anyway?
The money that Professor Kang has embezzled from the college,
small and large, everything.
8/19/2018
Kim Ian, 2/28/1991 - 8/19/2018
2018.08.19
Are you alright?
It's dangerous!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Run away.
I won't leave you.
You have to run away.
I will not leave you alone!
I can't. I can't.
Please, please...
Think straight, Hong Yi Yeong!
Keep your mind focused and look at me.
Listen to me well.
From now on, just run towards wherever you see light.
And when you see anyone, report this right away.
Got it?
I don't want to.
I'm sorry for dragging you here when you didn't want to come.
I told you there was something I couldn't tell you before.
It would be great to see you again, but I'm not sure I can do that.
I don't know how you feel, but I liked you so much.
No, no.
Don't say such things.
I'm alright, so you go now.
Hurry.
Hurry and go!
Timing and Subtitles by the Sing To Me Team @ viki