Episode 10
It's Yu Dong Man.
You asked me that question last time.
Are you going to be a professor or a detective?
You said I had to choose.
To be honest, I thought it wouldn't be that bad to become a professor.
But I was actually learning from the students,
embarrassingly.
I thought it would be better to catch people
who were less than me than to teach those who are better than me.
So, I'm going back to being a detective, instead of being a professor.
Professor Yu Dong Man
Professor's Office
It can't be.
Professor ...
Seon Ho.
Is Professor Yu really not there?
He left this behind.
If you see him, please tell him this,
it takes one week to process a resignation.
Professor Seo Sang Hak,
please take care of our losers.
Like a 20-year old, go fall in love, travel, and fight a little bit.
I'm telling you to live your life while having some fun, punk.
Life isn't only about investigating.
Professor Yu Dong Man
The call cannot be answered.
I didn't call to stop a professor who ran away, so just listen to this.
The burner phone that was contacting Park Cheol Jin
turned on. The location came up as well.
If it's now, we can catch those illegal gambling bastards,
so please call me.
Or answer your phone!
That burner phone
is the one who put this all on my mom, right?
I knew it ... I kept thinking it was weird.
I mean, Seon Ho was going out every night.
We've been saying over and over that we don't have secrets among us!
You liar!
Let's go for now. I heard the GPS is on.
Okay.
- Let's go to Beom Tae's house first.
- What?
The KIT (Kang Investigation Team) has standards. We can't take a taxi.
KIT?
An investigation team led by Kang Seon Ho.
Kang - Investigation - Team! Don't you remember?
The heroes of the leaked final exam incident, they're us!
Hero!
- Okay. Let's go!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
Get up.
- Kang Hui.
- You'll get sick if you hold it in.
I can't bear to see that.
I know you're very angry inside and upset.
So go meet the professor and say whatever you want to say.
"How can you do this without saying anything to me?"
"Leaving like this isn't right!" "Are you that great?" "Is being a professor everything?"
And where do you think the professor would have gone after writing his resignation?
He probably went to catch the criminal.
The professor must be where the criminal is, right?
Let's go.
Why don't you stop?
Why do you keep calling someone who won't answer?
So that Professor Yu can call back whenever he wants to.
It wouldn't be easy for someone who ran away without saying goodbye to call.
He would be embarassed.
So that's why I'm giving him the chance first.
He can decide to come back since I left a trace,
or at least call.
Where the hell did he go?
Who is that?
He's an old customer.
But what kind of fishing is he going to do
when he stays inside all day?
- Isn't he like a wanted criminal?
- Come on.
No way.
Ay, no way!
Professor Gwon Hyeok Pil missed call
Kang Seon Ho 18 missed calls
Professor Choi Hui Su 12 missed calls
Professor Seo Sang Hak 2 missed calls
Police University
21st, noon
20th, travels to Police University
The main route of Go Deok Bae
I watched you for 48 hours,
but suddenly I can't even find you?
Go Deok Bae, that fat bastard.
Where the hell are you hiding?
Yes, go ahead.
Sunbae!
Money Exchange
Yes, I'm here.
That is ...
The last location where the burner phone was turned off was in Changrim-dong.
- If it's Changrim-dong, isn't that where a lot of foreigners are?
- Yes.
Professor Yu is probably there.
This is definitely the GPS's last location.
There are more alleyways than I thought.
Hey, then, let's split up in pairs and look for him.
No, Beom Tae and I will go this way.
Wait, but still, it's a bit—
It's okay. It's daytime and there are a lot of people.
You two look on the main road.
I'll call you if we find Professor Yu Dong Man.
- Let's go.
- We'll see you later.
Later.
But do you think the real culprit is here?
We did follow him here, but I don't even know what to do.
What would the professor have done?
Honestly, I really hate the professor.
He turned himself in, he left the school,
and he doesn't care about the promise he made to me. I really hate him for doing things his way.
Still, I wish he were here.
Should we go for now?
Republic of Korea
Passport
Oh! It's you, Professor Go!
Gossi Beer was closed during vacation. Didn't you go on a trip?
A-Are you all right?
I-I-I was surprised. Seeing you guys here.
I know! How could we meet right here?
But what are you doing here?
H-Here?
Oh, there's a special sauce here I came to buy.
But what are you guys doing in this neighborhood?
- Oh, we—
- My colleague
Mi No lives in this neighborhood.
We came here to eat with him and then head back.
Oh, is that so?
If you go there, in that corner, there are many good restaurants.
All right! Thank you! See you after school starts!
- All right. Eat and head home, all right?
- Bye.
What's wrong? I was going to ask if he saw Professor Yu Dong Man.
I mean... he seemed a little strange.
Even his clothes and his bag.
Give me your phone.
Sunbae! Professor Go's car was spotted in the foreigner neighborhood of Changlim-dong.
Did this jerk already leave?
Damn it. Why would he come to the foreigner neighborhood?
I know, why did it he have to come here out of all places?
That's what I'm saying. It's not like he came here to sightsee.
What's in this area?
Well ... they have tacos, pho, curry,
I wasn't talking about that.
Then what else?
Well, there must be a lot of foreigners, so there are banks or
currency exchange places, you punk.
What is that... that... that place that specializes in exchanging foreign currency.
Exchanging currency?
Oh, currency exchange store! That's right, a currency exchange store!
Because you're lonely, you're doing all the talking.
Huh?
Now I'm seeing things, I'm going crazy.
Oh!
Professor Go ... the culprit?
No, he's not. He can't be.
- He's not, right?
- I don't know.
He could really be here for groceries.
Groceries? Gossi Beer was closed because of the school vacation.
This is a homemade listening device, and it has a maximum transmission range of 3 kilometers.
Is there any other punk other than that Mr. Go jerk, who could have been eavesdropping within that range?
You don't know that!
Professor Yu Dong Man was right.
What do you mean?
Which way did Professor Go disappear?
That alleyway.
Let's go there for now, quickly.
What are you guys doing here?
Professor!
Is it okay if we stay in here?
Hey, didn't you see the professor's fierce eyes?
- You're right. It's better if we just wait here.
- Yes.
Aren't you going to answer me? What are you doing here?!
Then what are you doing here?
What, you punk?!
Professor Go is the culprit, right?
How... How do you know that?
The burner phone that was used to communicate with Ahjussi Cheol Jin turned on.
I followed that phone's GPS and ran into Professor Go here.
What?!
H-How can you say that so... simply?
No, no, no. So, you ran into him?
Who did? You?
No, not me but Beom Tae and Jun Wuk.
You punk! Did you completely forget how Cheol Jin got hurt?
You dared to come here and you even brought your friends?
If you were worried about that, then you shouldn't have left!
If you hadn't left, we wouldn't have come all the way here
looking for you.
You trusted Ahjussi Cheol Jin and waited for him.
Now I can be by your side.
How can I trust you when you're like this?
Hey, today, because you didn't know whether it was real or crap,
you lost that jerk, Professor Go.
Do you think I've just been watching him because I couldn't catch him?
Do you know how many days and nights, I spent trying to get the right evidence
and arrest him, you frustrating punk?!
Just take your friends and go home.
Was I even your partner?
Answer me. Don't run away.
This punk!
Answer me, Ahjussi.
What?! Ahju—
What? You're not a professor at the National Police University anymore.
Hey, Kang Seon Ho!
The Investigation exam. Last answer. The most important thing in an investigation!
I put 'partner' as my answer! Because that's what I learned!
Partner
I've only learned that for half a year.
Now, that's useless too.
Hey ... Hey, punk!
Whoa.
Professor Seo Sang Hak said he will accept your resignation in one week.
I'm really going to mind my own business now, so do what you want.
Wait a minute.
My back ...
My back went out. My back ...
Your back?
Are you all right?
- Should we go to the hospital?
- I really wasn't expecting that.
I think I have a herniated disc.
I-I'm sorry, Professor.
Am I not an ahjussi now, but back to a professor?
I mean, it's because I was so mad earlier.
So why are you resigning and investigating without telling me
when you're the one that called me your partner?
Oh, my back, my back.
Even now, shouldn't we go to the hospital?
Forget it, punk. Just follow the navigation.
If you got here this fast, what does that make me?
It must be embarrassing.
But what was that? Why?
Can't you be a little embarrassed?
I've been embarrassed countless times.
I've been embarrassed because I am young. I've been embarrassed because I don't know anything.
Whenever you do things like this, as if you don't care about me,
I think to myself, "Was I the only one who thought we were partners?"
I was really embarrassed.
So this is my last time, too.
If you do this again, then I really ...
won't see you again.
Wow, you're really scary.
I'm serious.
I'm serious too, punk.
Seriously...
After I heard something about a wanted criminal, I felt very nervous.
So I looked at him secretly, and after seeing his face, I realized it was that man.
The professor from the National Police University, who came here a couple of times.
I'm glad you called us. Where is he?
He's on the second floor here.
He went out and hasn't come back yet, but you can go up there.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
He really came here when he felt lonely.
Illegal gambling site opening and closing log.
What is all this?
Professor Go?
Welcome.
What about Park Cheol Jin's things?
I already received them.
But Detective Bae, that jerk loves money so much, I'm tired of him.
It doesn't matter. We can just cut him off.
There are no problems with the preparations for the event, right?
It's not my first time. If you want to take a sabbatical, we have to go big one more time.
Why did you follow us when I told you to go home?
I need to investigate this too.
It's not like it's a stranger. It involves my mom. And now that I know who the culprit is
I can't turn back.
I have to catch that culprit myself.
My head hurts.
Jun Wuk and I ran into Professor Go.
Yes! We're in danger
now that he knows about us.
We can't go home like this and put our family in danger.
This is driving me crazy.
Why the hell are you guys doing this to me?
What are all of you talking about?
Let's talk, Professor Yu.
What were all those findings in your room?
Why would you go into someone else's room and look through it?
Is the owner of Gossi Beer really part of the illegal gambling team?
Yes, well...
So, the students followed him and met Professor Go?
What the hell were you thinking?
Why are you yelling?
Didn't I resign to prevent this from happening?
Are you saying you did nothing wrong right now?
I'm not saying that, but it's because you suddenly started yelling.
- That's enough from both of you.
- If you decided to become a professor, you shouldn't have been investigating!
What are you going to do now with those students running around trying to catch him?
That's why I resigned to just be a detective! I did everything I could too!
- I said that's enough.
- Forget that.
- What are you going to do now about those students?!
- I can just take responsibility for them!
How are you going to take responsibility for them?! What if they get hurt too?!
I said that's enough!
Is this the time to be like this?!
I just heard that the person who runs a business right in front of the National Police University is an illegal gambling operator!
Even the students are in danger. Do you really want to fight right now?!
- What about the police?
- We can't call the police.
Cheol Jin was even connected to this. There might be others we don't know about.
I told you I'm just going to take care of everything!
What are you going to take care of on your own? What? Are you going to work with the students?
We'll do it.
- What?
- Let's catch him.
Our students are in danger now.
Does that make sense?!
All right! I love you, Dad!
I told my family that I'm attending a seasonal class.
Okay.
But that isn't a lie.
To be honest, an investigation is a seasonal class.
Seon Ho, what about you? Did you call your family?
Yes, earlier.
But did the illegal gambling site start in front of the National Police University or before that?
I wonder.
He would have made a lot of money,
but why did he run Gossi Beer?
It's not in a place like Gangnam but in Asan of all places.
Who cares about a criminal's history?
He probably lost it from gambling.
Why aren't the professors coming?
I know some Hoobae police officers that I can trust—
I told you, you can't call the police!
We'll only get rid of the bottom player.
Then how are the three of us going to arrest him?!
Why is it just the three of us? Including the students, there are seven of us.
They're freshmen. They just barely got started!
Exactly, so we'll investigate with them and then the three of us can make the arrest.
What?
If it's difficult, you don't have to get involved.
I don't want to force you.
Professor Choi and I, I'm sure the two of us are enough to do it.
Professor Gwon.
I don't think this is right.
This never happened according to me.
We can catch him.
Our students are in danger.
Professor Gwon is right.
It doesn't make sense to do this with the students.
You're right. It's not protecting them,
but it could be putting them in more danger.
But isn't it better if you know about it?
I am going crazy because I couldn't see it.
Anyway, I'm saying I'm going to help. I think that is the right thing to do.
For both Professor Gwon and you,
tonight will be a long night.
♫ I who was unable to to hug ♫
♫ you who smiled at me when you saw me like that ♫
♫ From behind me getting farther away whether I keep reaching for you or not ♫
♫ To keep me warm and from getting hurt ♫
♫ So I wouldn’t see ♫
♫ Even the image of you hugging me who was crying ♫
♫  remains ♫
The most important thing in an investigation!
I put 'partner' as my answer!
Whenever you do things like this, as if you don't care about me,
I think to myself, "Was I the only one who thought we were partners?"
I was really embarrassed.
♫ Even the image of you hugging me who was crying ♫
♫ remains ♫
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes, what about you?
Yes, I slept really well. The weather's really nice.
Hey!
Why are you lying there like that?
Such crap.
Ridiculous.
You shouldn't eat green colored food, bro.
But it's tasty.
Professor Choi Hui Su has decided to help you.
This is the plan for the investigation.
The investigation will always take place in teams of two.
Kang Seon Ho and I will start searching from Gossi Beer where Go Deok Bae was.
Professor Choi Hui Su and Oh Kang Hui.
Professor Choi Hui Su and Oh Kang Hui will—
We will look into the online gambling website.
Okay, fine.
What should Jun Wuk and I do?
We'll do anything, leader Yu.
Yes, leader.
Beom Tae and Jun Wuk will— Aish.
Those two will go with me.
Professor Gwon Hyeok Pil, Beom Tae, and Jun Wuk will
question people in Changrim-dong where Professor Go was seen
to find out why that jerk went there and what he did.
Right now, we only have a specific suspect but no leads or proof.
We need to find evidence that will enable us to arrest the suspect as soon as possible.
I hope you all show good teamwork and get the best results.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Changrim-dong.
So the real estate registry shows that there's a basement here, right?
That's right. It's a pub but its electricity use is at an industrial level.
That means he definitely did something here.
How do we check it?
Why? Are you going to prevent me from breaking in like last time?
No.
We have to put each and every one behind bars who insist on breaking the law.
Punk.
Was it around here where we ran into Professor Go?
There's only a currency exchange shop, so that must be it.
Then should we find out by pretending to be customers
what Professor Go bought in this neighborhood?
Sting operations are illegal.
What we have to do is an investigation through interrogation.
What do you think sting operations are?
- Student No Beom Tae.
- Pardon?
That is...
So sting operations are when you use a trap
to catch master criminals who are difficult to catch.
Then in what instances are sting operations allowed, Student Jo Jun Wuk?
Pardon?
To someone who intends to commit a crime,
providing an opportunity and environment is legal.
If you cause an innocent person to commit a crime
on purpose, that's illegal.
Yes. That's right.
We are now going to figure out what Professor Go bought from here.
Then the type of investigation we're going to carry out, is it a sting operation or interrogation?
Sting operation?
- Sting operation!
- Interrogation!
When I come back here, you both should give me the same answer.
And there should be proper reasoning for your reason. Wait here.
Yes, sir.
Which one is it? Is it interrogation?
Shall we go in together?
No. I'll go in by myself.
But do you really think your mom would know?
They change the site address dozens of times a day!
They open another one and then blow it up!
Do you think that is possible with my brain?
Yes. A thief knows another thief well.
And my mom knows them well.
I'll be back.
Reasons For ID Check
Hey! Would there be a basement there?
They are usually made very secretively.
Behind mirrors or...
Yes. Under carpets.
If you look right here, the floor...
So it's just a floor.
Hey! What is that?
What?
Hey! Sheesh!
Wow...
Wow! Look at these jerks.
They really did do it here.
How did they do it right in front of Police University?
Since it's the darkest under the lamp.
They would have moved their headquarters to a different place, right?
Of course.
Hey, do you think it's easy for people to stop gambling?
It's the first time you've seen me in a uniform. How come you're not saying anything?
What do you mean the first time? I already saw it during the trial.
- You saw?
- Of course.
You were glaring at me. How could I not see?
Forget that. I have something to ask you.
Do you remember what you said last time when I visited you?
The guys who did the illegal gambling website.
That they reopen sites and then close them down effortlessly.
Why, you b*tch? Why are you annoyingly asking me about that again?
I really have to know.
How do you know it is the same website if they reopen it?
You go. Go, you b*tch.
I'm in danger because I chased those guys from the illegal gambling website to solve your case.
So, you have to help me.
Which brainless jerk messed with my daughter?
Did they do that because they want me to be the end of their lives?
Even if Jesus or Buddha comes, no one can mess with Oh Jeong Ja's daughter!
I won't let that happen.
Why would you fight with God?
What's so great about them?
I will go against anyone who messes with you, whoever it is.
So, you too get your head together.
You are Oh Kang Hui, daughter of the vicious Oh Jeong Ja.
You are much smarter than me,
and much better than me!
What should I do for you?
Let's go.
It's me.
Don't you recognize my voice? I am Madam Oh.
Search and find out where that wench, Gumbler is within the hour.
These are things that took place at the Changrim-dong currency exchange shop.
Korean?
Money Exchange?
Got you.
Money laundering? Illegal foreign exchange transactions?
What's that?
According to Article 16 of the Foreign Exchange Control Act—
I feel sleepy.
Tell us what happened next quickly.
What do you want? Grab a loan?
I heard you guys provide other services.
Other services?
Yes, don't worry about the money.
Just name the price.
What does this jerk look like he wants?
A fake passport or a burner phone?
This jerk wouldn't be the police, right?
Hey, from which angle does he look like police?
With just a look I can say he's on our side.
Do you make fake passports and burner phones?
Are you Japanese?
A fake passport and burner phone?
Is that bastard trying to leave the country?
Yes. After making a killing first.
I spoke to my mom.
That Gumbler is a lady who stabbed my mom in the back.
Anyway, this ahjumma is a VIP of the illegal gambling website we are investigating.
And so?
They gave away invitations to the VIPs for the opening of the website.
They are hosting that opening event tomorrow night.
The chance of hitting the jackpot is twice as high.
Let's go and meet Gumbler.
Be careful.
Professor, just a moment.
I can trace the IP if I can just get access to the site.
If we can catch them in the act and figure out their address,
we can even arrest Professor Go on the spot.
Just spread rumors everywhere that you are a hacker.
Then what am I supposed to do?
There's that backtracking program Yoon made.
There is.
But that's an old program for backtracking accounts, so we'll have to recode it to backtrack an old IP address.
Then, it will take time.
How much?
About two days.
Do it by tomorrow.
Tomorrow? I said two days.
Do it as if it's a matter of life or death, then it will all work.
Even if we do it as if it's a matter of life or death it doesn't work like that here.
There will be a message with a link on that phone.
Check it and toss the phone safely.
Then what about you, Ahjumma?
It's just a phone, I can buy a new one.
You testified against my mom in the trial, right?
Then why are you helping us this much suddenly?
Your mom cried.
Children are the enemies.
You pay for the coffee.
It's fastest to do it here since I can use the LAN.
Okay.
Then, let's start.
Recipient : Seon Ho
Jackpot Chance VIP Link
Grand Open
That website hasn't opened yet.
But I can track them with this window, so I'll code the program and get their IP before they go live.
Then we will get the IP address and get their location,
and when they open the website, we go there immediately.
Yes.
Those jerks.
Professor Yu Dong Man and Seon Ho went to confirm something saying they'll come tomorrow.
So instead of waiting, go to sleep now.
Okay.
Ah, and that ahjumma is wrong.
- What?
- You aren't an enemy to your mom.
You're that one daughter in the saying, "One good daughter is better than ten sons."
So sleep confidently. Straighten your shoulders and smile to sleep.
You were very cool today and did very well.
Good night.
Living life is a worry.
We are sitting here to catch the guys who did illegal things right in this place.
I couldn't even imagine being in Police University with you
when you caught me and dragged me to the police station.
You will come back to the school when the investigation ends, right?
Depends on how you behave.
Why are you playing hard to get?
I won't even play hard to get if I don't like it.
What?
I'm not sleeping.
So don't slack off.
Data generation complete
Let's start everything.
Run the program?
Now, we just have to start?
Yes.
Would you like to run the program?
GRAND OPEN 6/24/ 21:00
North Korea
South Korea
There are two escape routes, this place and that one.
Then I can go to one place and Professor Choi can go to the other.
The time the website will be open is tonight at 21:00 hours (11 pm).
As soon as they go live, we're going to raid them.
- You four will monitor everything from here.
- What?
We don't go with you?
Information and speed are vital in cybercrime cases.
If the server or database goes offline or gets lost,
then the evidence will disappear and we can't catch the culprit.
Therefore, until the moment we apprehend him
you guys will keep monitoring from here and will let us know if there are any emergencies.
Okay.
But do we actually need four people to monitor?
Yes. I think we will need four people.
Yes.
Let's not make mistakes. Let's not be sloppy. Let's not let go of the culprit.
Tonight, we will definitely catch those guys.
Yes, sir.
Is it done?
The setting is over now.
The website will open six hours from now.
GRAND OPEN
But who got you the IP address?
There is someone.
I have been getting help from him since I was a police officer.
What about Professor Gwon?
He went outside to buy some dinner for the kids.
It must be hard for Professor Gwon, right?
Well, he is a person who follows the rules.
But he is taking all sorts of actions that break his rules and principles.
But do you think the person who did all that right in front of Police University
has something like rules?
Honestly, we came here in a hurry.
I feel like I'll be flustered when I see
Professor Go later tonight.
I do understand a little bit
how you felt seeing Cheol Jin.
After this work is over, let's go on the drive we were supposed to go on earlier.
Then make sure you don't even sprain your ankle
or get a scratch on your face.
Let's keep ourselves intact for the date.
Professor,
I called because I had something to tell you.
It looks like the rain is going to pour down.
And they said that the weather would be nice today.
GRAND OPEN
Right now, there is only
one hour left before the website goes live.
Okay. Let's go.
Hey. Call me immediately if anything happens.
Professor. Be careful.
Don't you know that I'm a judo athlete from the national team?
They should be the ones to be careful of me.
Excuse me, Professor.
Forget it.
Be ready to give me whatever your answer is when I return.
I'll be back later, kid.
Stay out of it when we make the arrest since only Professor Yu and I are authorized to investigate.
What is there to worry about when there are two veterans here?
Let's get this done quickly.
Error
What's going on?
The data is being erased.
What?
Why?
That's not the right place.
First, let's make sure they can't escape.
I'll go take a look.
I can't get through to Professor Choi.
Professor Gwon isn't picking up either.
Try Professor Yu.
I'll try again.
I'm sure they're safe.
Yes. I'll have to wrap it up before then.
Yes. I understand.
Hurry up!
How much time to complete?
There are only 10 minutes left. We'll leave after we clean up.
Okay, Professor.
Finish up and come.
I'll see you in Thailand.
I'm on my way so get a boat ready.
Okay.
Caught you.
Are you surprised, asshole?
Kang Seon Ho
What's up?
You're in the wrong place, Professor.
They didn't go live with the site but instead are running a self-destruct program.
I input the IP address when the firewall went down, but...
Self-destruct program?
I think they know we are hacking them.
There's no way it would have leaked.
It could put the others in danger, so I'll leave now, alone.
Hey! Hey ki—
Professor. Please come quickly.
Professor!
Professor. Are you all right?
This bastard, do you know who you're messing with?
Hurry! Block them!
To the back!
Go Deok Bae, you are under arrest on charges of opening a gambling operation, violating the Game Industry Promotion Act,
violating the Electronic Financial Transactions Act, violating the Crime Proceeds Concealment Control Act,
violating the Telecommunications Business Act,
and for violating the Information and Communication Network Act.
You have the right to consult an attorney and the right to remain silent.
You have the right to defend yourself,
and the right to request the court to review the legality of your arrest without a warrant.
But don't do it, jerk.
Because you're dead meat now.
♬ When things don't go your way, tell me.  ♬
♬ When it feels like I'm about to fall, hold me ♬
♬ When everyone leaves you, tell me. ♬
♬ And I'll be by your side, hold me ♬
♬ What about it? Can you tell me everything? ♬
♬ I'm saying I'll always be by your side. ♬
♬ How about it? All of the heavy worries ♬
♬ can you and I ♬
Seon Ho finished his first investigation well.
♬ carry them together? ♬
We're hanging out at the beach!
Have a good time.
There aren't any buses going to Seoul.
That crazy asshole!
What's that?
A gift from my boyfriend. I really love it.
Keep your head up! Just because we don't have money doesn't mean we don't have strength.
What are you talking about?
What do you think I'm talking about? Do a good job!
I'm here to meet with Han Jeong Sik, the head of the criminal investigation department.
It'll be your last time taking the students along to do something so dangerous.
How did you know I went with the students?
It's finally here.
But how did you get into Police Univerity?
♬ And I'll be by your side, hold me ♬