The final exam papers
[Episode 9]
were leaked at the Police University.
The cradle of justice, the National Police University.
KCS News focused on the corruption that took place at the school,
which mars that ideal.
It has been less than a year since Professor Yu began at the Police University.
He gave out the answers for his own class exam.
According to the Asan police station, Mr. Yu initially denied all charges,
but eventually confessed during the investigation.
What are you saying suddenly?
I leaked the final exam.
You bastard, what are you doing?
You should have been the one to handcuff me.
Hey! Park Cheol Jin!
I wanted to make some money and ... here I am.
Hey, you punk!
You should have quit when you found the listening device!
Even though I acted like I lost my memory,
you wouldn't put on the brakes.
You bastard! Shut your mouth.
Senior Inspector Yu Dong Man. Mentor.
You can stop watching my back now.
You crazy bastard.
Wait, what's going on right now?
Professor Yu Dong Man was crying.
How could Professor Yu Dong Man cry?
Isn't he also a human?
If your heart hurts and you're upset, you could cry.
Yeah, Kang Hui. It's almost time to go back.
Don't wait and go ahead.
I'll take Professor Yu— Oh.
Prof—
You did it on purpose, didn't you, so that I could write the article.
I'm Lim Byun Seok, reporter for KCS.
You're Professor Yu Dong Man, right?
A student from the Police University sent me a tip
that the answer key for a test was leaked, but the school was covering it up.
- Go away.
- Is it an illegal solicitation or something like that?
You trash reporter, can't you hear me?
- I said get lost.
- Come on, would you feel good if I called you jjapsae (like calling a police officer "pig")?
We're just checking facts from a position of providing the citizens with the truth.
The truth? Yeah right.
Do you guys even care about that?
A scolding from the cop who committed an act of corruption.
I can see the headline.
Corrupt police officer revealed. The current state of police officer training and corruption.
I will broadcast it very provocatively for you.
You know well that our country gets angry easily over an issue like this.
- Is that it?
- What?
A jjapsae that was like a gangster, casually committed false statements,
concealment, corruption, and abuse of power.
Is he the only one responsible for this corruption? What was covered up?
How much of what he said was false?
If you're going to start something,
make sure you do it thoroughly and get it right
if you're not a trash reporter
but a real reporter, punk.
Have you gone crazy because you want to be buried by the public?
Even if I did and in the end, if he doesn't come,
I should be buried too.
Hey, Reporter Im!
- Hurry up and leave.
- Ay—
- Stop!
We're not done with our investigation.
There's a ban on news reports. Leave.
- I'll just have some coffee before I go.
- What coffee? Just go!
We only have two.
So go home.
The report.
Let's write it.
Are you sure?
Admitting to the crime, right then when I was present.
After hearing that, would I write an article or not?
Of course, I would write it.
- What is it that you want to say?
- You knew, didn't you,
that if the news went out, Park Cheol Jin, the real criminal, would come forward.
I did hear that you two were partners.
Is that why?
Write an article, not a script, you punk.
You definitely said that!
"If that guy doesn't come, then I will be buried instead."
I should suffer. A police officer
couldn't catch his subordinate, who was standing right next to him making a mess.
That's why I waited for him to come and confess by himself.
And he did! So that's it.
So, you punk, keep your eye on this case.
Keep track of who is in charge of the investigation, how everything is going,
and what the hidden truth behind this case is.
Keep your eyes open and use your pen well.
If you're a real reporter,
and not a trash reporter, then I'll be a detective and not a jjapsae.
- But why do you keep speaking informally?
- You can do it too, you punk!
Yeah, Reporter Oh, it's me. Who's in charge of the investigation on the Police University answer key case?
Professor!
Let's go to school now.
Yes, Professor.
- Goodbye.
- Good work.
Deposit complete.
Park Cheol Jin's address. #301 Gyeongam Officetel,
21 Haengyeong-ro, Yangjin-myeon, Asan-si, is this correct?
Uhm, beyond the answer key...
I wanted to make a statement about the illegal gambling case as well.
I'd be thankful if you could reach out to the Seoul Metropolitan Team—
Your mother, Kim Yeong Su. Your younger sister, Park Na Hyeon.
It's correct?
- What the hell are you do—
- Shut your mouth.
It's an order from the higher ups.
You have to protect your family first.
Park Cheol Jin's address / Apartment 301 Kyungyam Officetel, Hengyoung-ro 21,Yangjinmyeon, Asan City
One. Two. Three.
Then, the exams are restarting from today, right?
Honestly, I was hoping the Investigation exam would be canceled.
I didn't study this weekend.
- You never study.
- You're right.
But do you think Professor Yu Dong Man is all right?
No sleep in days,
and not eating properly at all.
I'm all right.
And a face like dry firewood!
I'm so upset.
Will Professor Yu be all right?
The administration office is a mess too. Professor Yu is probably worse.
Here. There was an unsavory incident a little while ago,
but the final exams should be completed as scheduled, right?
Professor Yu, is the Investigation exam today?
Yes. I'm planning on giving the exam today.
Also, the professors who finished their exams can finish grading them by this week.
It seems like some reporters are still holding out,
so please refrain from contacting the media as much as possible.
All right, then let's wrap up today's meeting.
I have been waiting for you to apologize,
but you're leaving today as well.
What? Did I say something wrong?
I mean, look at what happened to our school's status because we brought in the wrong person.
Oh, was it two people?
You're right. We don't even have the basics and came in causing trouble.
I apologize.
He looks fine after all.
Look at him, what did you do so well?
I don't think Professor Yu did anything wrong.
You don't know, do you? I heard the two of them were partners.
All right, all right. Why are the professors even acting like this?
To be honest, the professors need to take an exam before getting hired.
I didn't study this hard so that
I could learn from someone like Yu Dong Man.
- Doesn't that piss you off?
- Of course it pisses me off.
But who the hell reported it to the news?
Exactly, who was it?
Hey, does that matter?
What matters is that a human being like that gangster is still a professor.
I can't even write a petition for this.
I know.
Today is the final exam, and at the same time,
it's the last day of the first semester of Investigation.
I ...
Aren't you going to hand out the exam papers?
What, are you telling me, the professor who cheated, to shut up and hand over the exam papers?
Even if it sucks and you don't want to hear it, be patient.
If you don't like that, it's all right, you can leave the classroom right now.
Because I'll be petty and give you an F.
I'm sorry for the delay in the exam.
I'm also sorry for the reporters that are lined up in front of the school.
I'm sorry that I canceled class on you so many times during the semester.
I was thinking about saying something like that but forget it.
I'll just say one thing.
Don't hate your Investigation class because you hate your professor
because it'll be your loss. Got it?
The exam time is 70 minutes. Let's start.
11:02 am
First semester final exam for the 2021 first years.
Investigation exam questions
11:30 am
40. What is the most important thing in an investigation?
Perseverance
Passion
Fact
Evidence
40. What is the most important thing in an investigation?
Did you solve the questions?
But what he said earlier, he meant don't hate the person even if you hate the crime, right?
He meant you can hate the person,
but don't hate Investigations class.
Hey, Professor Yu.
I'm going to go first.
I guess that Professor Yu's confession was really false.
Of course, it was false.
Who reported it to the news?
I'm sure it was one of the students.
I think why they did it is more important.
I'll head out first.
National Police University
It was you.
That's right. I reported it.
- Why?
- I think it's wrong.
An insider commits a crime in the presence of police and reserve officers,
and the elders are trying to keep it quiet.
Someone was not righteous, and the school wasn't fair.
I didn't learn to turn a blind eye to those things.
Is that so?
But what does it have to do with fairness or justice,
if the investigation of the case wasn't even finished?
If it was for me, don't do this again.
Why?
Because whatever I do, you won't change your mind?
No, because you're a good person.
As you said, you made the choice because it was fair and just,
so don't ever make a foolish choice again because of me.
And you're right. It won't change my mind.
If nothing I do will change your mind, then I'll just do what I want.
I can't give up even if you die.
From now, because of you, I think I'll keep making that foolish choice.
- Hey, Park Min Gyu.
- I'm not going to hide it anymore either.
Cheol Jin, that punk, said he won't meet anyone,
so don't waste your time either.
Who does he think he is?
Is the investigation still ongoing?
Hey, it's a case caused by a guy from our station, so they aren't even sharing it with us.
They aren't even showing us a single statement.
All right, I'm hanging up.
Professor, play a judo match with me.
Ah!
What the hell did you learn?
Talk to me, punk. Talk to me. Talk to me.
You're the one who should talk.
What happened? What's going to happen?
Are you not going to say anything?
I'm also by your side.
- Are you comforting me?
- I'm telling you because I don't think you know.
- What are you going to do now?
- Why do you keep asking?!
We have to catch the criminal because it doesn't end with Ahjussi Cheol Jin.
The burner phone that was used to contact Ahjussi Cheol Jin.
Why are you doing this?
I mean, why the hell did this investigation become so important to you?
If I hadn't hacked you back then,
you'd have caught all those illegal gamblers.
Then Kang Hui's mom wouldn't have been on trial for something she didn't do.
Whether you hacked it or not,
it is my fault as a police officer for letting go of the culprit.
It's Oh Kang Hui's mother's fault that she was deceived while trying to relieve her gambling debt
by selling her account.
You knew?
- Kang Hui's mom's trial?
- Would I have kept saying I would catch the culprit
without even knowing that?
The trial isn't over yet.
We just have to find the crucial evidence before that.
This punk thinks I'm some kind of idiot.
Then from when do we start investigating again?
Professor.
Yu Dong Man
Police University
Kang Seon Ho
Police use this technique the most on site.
Learn this properly first and come.
You can't even flip me over. Who do you think you can catch?
Yu Dong Man
Police University
We have to catch the criminal because it doesn't end with Ahjussi Cheol Jin.
Put it down there.
Evidence No. 4
Evidence No. 7
We conducted a search warrant on your apartment,
All the burner phones and the fake bank accounts that you confessed to using for the crime
were confiscated as evidence.
Your accomplice, the taxi driver, also confessed that he did everything
as per your orders. You, Park Cheol Jin, will
be transferred to the detention center soon.
From now on, you'll continue ...
to not talk
or hear anything.
You know, right?
All the evidence of Cheol Jin's illegal gambling operation came out
and he will be transferred to the detention center soon.
If you kill someone,
how many years is the prison sentence?
It depends,
but I also don't know when it's accidental murder
out of jealously. Hey! Why is he touching her there?!
Hey! Would a gun be better or a knife?
I think
a gun would be better.
Shoot!
If you're an accomplice, we'll share the jail time, right?
Yesterday enemies and today accomplices?
Let's make it a win-win situation to defeat a bigger enemy.
She— She smiled!
Sunbae, don't smile for him.
Why is she smiling for him?!
Sunbae Myeong Jung is screwed now.
He became a public enemy number one
since Beom Tae and Jun Wuk are working together now.
- What about the work between you and the professor?
- What?
Didn't you call me out to tell me about that?
Right.
Shall we sit down for a while?
Park Cheol Jin won't be transferred today.
You can't meet him anyway, so just leave.
Then...
convey my words.
- Kang Hui—
- So
when did you find out that the case you are investigating with the professor is my mom's case?
Just recently.
I found out when we went to your mom's trial.
Seems like Professor already knew.
He said that since the trial isn't over yet,
we can just catch the culprit before then.
Professor was already doing the investigation so well.
But what about you?
Why are you doing this investigation with him?
I...
messed up once.
That is why Professor couldn't catch them.
At first, it was because of that.
But now I learned while doing this investigation that
I shouldn't give up even if I'm afraid
and that I shouldn't run away even if it's scary.
Even if the person close to me is the criminal,
I have to relentlessly identify the crime.
That's how you protect the person you care about
as a police officer.
I also want to become such a police officer.
I really want to become like that.
That is why I decided to
do this investigation till the end.
And that police officer is
Professor Yu Dong Man?
Yes, Lawyer.
I want to meet my mom.
It's been a long time since the brakes broke,
so take care of yourself, you criminal loser.
That's from your crazy mentor.
But what the hell does that mean?
It means he's going to see this through to the end.
The starting was with the illegal gambling site.
And then Kang Seon Ho hacked their accounts.
The site and the accounts are all gone.
Now we have no chance to get these guys.
- Everything we worked on for a whole year is gone!
- What is this?
You're suspended, jerk! Get out!
Then Cheol Jin was attacked while he was giving me information.
The ones that you are after from the gambling site,
they're at the National Police University—
There were two suspects when
Cheol Jin got hurt.
Go Deok Bae, Professor Gwon.
The alibi of professor Gwon was proven.
Park Cheol Jin getting caught at that time.
It means the unregistered phone called him, and Cheol Jin came here.
His phone and movements
are the same base station.
The same pattern keeps recurring.
A burner phone that gave instructions to Park Cheol Jin
and...
the wiretapping device in my office.
Within three kilometers.
There is one person who I couldn't confirm till now.
Go Deok Bae
Gwon Hyeok Pil
Go Deok Bae.
Go Deok Bae
National Police University
We will be open when the semester starts. Gossi Beer is on vacation.
Damn it, why now?
Customer Go Deok Bae
This month's meter rate - 1,517,530 ₩
What?
Why is the electricity bill so expensive?
Driver's license preparation guide
National Police Unversity students are commissioned as inspectors immediately after graduation and put to work right away.
With that said, a driver's license is essential because you have to start driving right away.
- Understood?
- Yes!
Once I get my driver's license, vacation really starts, right?
Getting a driver's license, why did Sunbae Myeong Jung have to put this up?
I'm swamped to death.
What are you doing? Are you looking for me once again?
- Did you have a hard time sleeping?
- No.
Wait a moment, I'll go to the store and get you some necessities.
I'm said I'm fine. I slept well.
I'll go in first.
Contents of registration certificate for buildings
Owner : Go Deok Bae
Building Details
Cement block structure, cement tile roof, slab roof two-story building, B1, ground floor, and 2nd floor.
The first basement level?
Where on earth is this first basement?
It doesn't even seem to have any stairs or doors.
What are you doing?
You didn't see my text?
Gossi Beer is closed on vacation so today's work dinner party is at the jokbal (pig's feet/trotters) restaurant.
First, let's raise our glasses.
Well, there was an unpleasant incident,
but thanks to the professors,
who have ended the semester well.
Drink as much as you want.
I hope you have a relaxing time.
You worked hard!
You worked hard too!
Wow, their portions are big.
Please eat.
Although I haven't even eaten yet, I feel like I'm getting younger already.
Is this the strength of collagen?
Seeing that it's very chewy, I think the collagen is very strong.
What are you doing?
Can't you see Professor Yu here?
Drink up.
Ah! Why is he so petty and eating it all so quickly?
Mind your own business and eat up the collagen.
Can I say something?
Of course!
Thank you for your hard work in dealing with the incident caused by the new professor.
On behalf of Park Cheol Jin,
I will apologize.
I apologize.
So you know.
Why are you apologizing instead of him?
If your brother causes trouble,
you have to apologize for him.
Drink this.
Plus, there isn't such a way in Korea.
It's not your fault.
The legs...
You can't even flip me over. Whom do you think you can catch?
So that b*tch asked me to wash her underwear.
She said she was the leader or something.
Do you know what happened to her underwear because I didn't get down on my knees?
I ripped it up into pieces, didn't I?
Mom, I asked you if you really didn't do it.
Hey, do you know how much she complained? You only get two pairs of underwear here.
Mom!
Anyway, so she tried to steal another pair of underwear.
Why are you yelling at me b*tch?
What are you so serious about regarding me suddenly?
Do you believe me if I say that I didn't do it?
You don't believe what I say either, just like the attorney.
What are you saying! I'm your daughter.
You really don't run a gambling business or anything like that, do you?
No, I didn't. I said I didn't!
I said I didn't do it!
Hey, think about it. They change their website a dozen times a day.
Then they reopen it and then get rid of it again.
Do you think that is possible with my brain?
It's not you, right?
If it happens to be you,
then I really won't see you again.
Why? To do what?
Hey! Oh Kang Hui!
Even if you didn't see my welcoming ceremony, I will let you see my graduation ceremony.
Hey, Kang Seon Ho!
Why don't you answer the phone?
I was busy training here.
Why? What's going on?
- I have to do this investigation too.
- Huh?
I'll do it too. This investigation with you and Professor Yu.
Even if they say that my mom is a criminal,
I have to get to know it myself.
Kang Hui, I couldn't explain it to you but...
this investigation is really more dangerous than you think.
From the age of five when my mom first went to prison until now, my life has been in danger.
I'm not even afraid of that.
There is only one thing I am afraid of in my life.
It's me running away.
I won't run away so I will catch all those bastards,
and save my mom.
I'll talk to Professor Yu.
And, I like you too Kang Seon Ho.
I told you that I won't run away now.
♫ When I see you, time stops ♫
♫  I am helpless  ♫
Say something at least—
♫  Everything in the world just stops  ♫
♫  Love is a moving thing going to you.  ♫
♫  If a person whom I don't even know ♫
♫ asks how I feel ♫
I won't...
run away anymore either.
♫  I like everything, I just like it  ♫
♫  We begin a beginning ♫
♫  which has no end  ♫
OPEN
Go on with the talk you had earlier.
You said that you had been in a relationship even though you
aren't married even at this age.
Just tell me, alright?
Who was it? Was she pretty?
She was the ugliest in our station.
I wondered who would date her.
It was right in front of me.
I would have been pissed if she was pretty.
Why did she have to be ugly?
Why did you break up?
Did it change like in movies?
- An accident.
- Accident?
- Eun Ju!
- Calm down.
Eun Ju! Eun Ju!
She was chasing the culprits behind the illegal gambling website.
At the intersection, she slammed into a car that violated the traffic signal.
The ending is similar to mine.
It must have been hard. How did you hang in there?
Just with the
resolution that I would finish the work that she couldn't.
How did you hang in there?
Me?
I changed because the world wouldn't change.
So? Are you trying to become a police officer again
instead of being a professor to finish what Eun Ju couldn't?
At first, it was because of that, and then it was because Cheol Jin got hurt.
Now,
I am also by your side now.
I'm doing it because I don't want another guy to get hurt.
Just be a professor.
- You scared me!
- You're just one of many cops in this world.
Just be a professor.
I also want to do so.
But wherever I go
people always get hurt or die if they are around me.
So, I want to be just a detective.
Professor Yu Dong Man
New Message
Kang Seon Ho – Sleep tight.
I sent it by mistake.
Good night.
I'll practice really hard and will definitely be helpful in your investigation.
Case Outline
Case Overview
Yu Dong Man
My eyes...
What's that?
I got the driver's license.
Stop it now.
Among us, only Seon Ho and Beom Tae didn't make it.
Who cares? You get three chances in life. Isn't that so, Beom Tae?
That's right. I took my college entrance exam three times too. Of course, I have to take the driver's license test three times as well.
Also, my dad said he would lend me his car if I get my license.
What? Daebak! Are you serious?
What is it? Made in Korea? Grey color?
Oh, that's right. Beom Tae, your family is a known rich family in Asan, right?
Wait a moment.
Is there any other Beom Tae in this school?
- No.
- It's not true.
What is this?
Kang Hui, did you wear perfume?
No.
It must be the smell of her shampoo.
Pathetic guy. You couldn't get even a driver's license.
I passed the technical and written exams, I just failed driving on the road.
Shut up and follow me.
Hey! This jerk! This is not a joke.
Driver training
Won't you go faster?
I am going. Why are you yelling?
We are on the shoulder of the road.
Turn on your signal, change lanes, and step on the accelerator, punk.
Don't you know it's illegal to go slower than the speed limit?
You're frustrating me.
♫ and let's run All Ready Go farther than anyone else ♫
What is that b*stard?!
Eh? What?
Yes, Hello. I'm on Dangjin-ro 12-gil right now.
I can see a vehicle that looks like they are drunk driving.
The car's plate number is...
Take the left side already!
♫ We're going to challenge ourselves every day. We're going to be burning. ♫
8773.
60 Ru. That Ru for license plates. 8773.
Since we'll arrive later,
send me the numbers surrounding you quickly.
Yes, I understand. Thank you.
You heard, right?
But could it be a drunk driver in the middle of the day?
- It looks like they are driving in the lane properly.
- You punk!
After seeing that person cause an accident ...
will you realize only after seeing an article about
the death of a family member from a drunk driver?
♫ Fly away high until the end ♫
♫ The hot sun isn't in that sky there ♫
♫ I found it (I found it) in my heart (in my heart) ♫
Do we keep going?
Focus on the car. Keep focused.
Good, good. You're doing fine.
Don't get nervous.
You are doing well.
What would you have done if we got into an accident?
Ah there is no way that would happen. I am there with you.
Ah this jerk. Look at your crooked eyes.
Thanks to you I think I will drive very well hereafter.
Ah that's good to hear.
There's at least one thing you can use that you learned from me.
It's just that everything you saw and learned while investigating with me is
backward and not the standard. I want you to forget about all that.
From now on, as a police university student,
just remember what you learn from your professors. Got it?
Ah, I don't want to.
I learned it through so much hard work. Why would I forget it!
I will remember everything and use it all.
Listen to me, you jerk.
Like a 20-year-old, go fall in love, travel, and fight a little bit.
Live your youth with some fun.
Life isn't all about investigating.
Ah, and practice judo really hard.
I am already doing it well.
And it's not just the investigation.
It's an investigation that I am doing with you.
You also taught me judo and driving so that I can follow you well, Professor.
I will work hard this vacation.
So, call me if you get any information. I'll come immediately.
Okay?
Okay. I got it.
You also spend your vacation well, with fun.
What is it?
- What's going on?
- What?
You've been smirking to yourself since earlier.
Bro, what's going on?
I'm just looking forward to the vacation.
It makes you happy just thinking about it, right?
It makes me so happy, right?
So, do you have plans?
Yeah.
- Studying investigations.
- St—
Studying...?
You should go to the hospital first during vacation.
Did you find out anything?
Yes. It's about the photo of the bill you sent to me.
There's something different about the electricity bill.
Well, it could be nothing, but something about it makes me a little uncomfortable.
What is it?
It would be much better to use contract power for general use if it was about the size of Gossi Beer,
but it was registered for a more expensive industrial purpose.
Why would he do that?
PC cafes or Bitcoin mining kids.
These guys, who have to pay outrageous electricity bills,
know how to use this trick well.
They want to reduce their electricity bill compared to the amount of electricity they really use.
Why?
The burner cell phone tower was captured, but the location keeps changing.
There is a program that figures out call patterns and frequency.
If we investigate using that, I think we'll be able to figure out the actual phone call locations.
Are you filming a James Bond movie?
It is used by the FBI, so we can code it too.
It will take a while though.
About two weeks.
It was you?
You were right under my nose!
Professor Go, you son of a b*tch.
Dormitory
You'll be forwarded to voicemail.
Why isn't he answering the phone?
Where are you? You should see my license in person.
Seon Ho! Before we leave, they want everyone to return the laptops.
Oh, that's right. Okay.
I need to transfer a file first.
Communication log
Program running
What program is running?
GPS tracking
06-22-2021 >> [+82-10-0548-1648]
The cell phone is turned on.
06-22-2021 >> Exploit sent, enjoy your reverse shell
Mobile phone 1 (010-0548-1648)
Number tracking
+82.10.0548.1648
GPS tracking
Number tracking ..... GPS Tracking 2021.06.22 The cell phone is turned on.
The burner phone is on.
Searching ...
GPS tracking +82.10.0548.1648
Seon Ho.
What are you talking about?
I just came back from the club room,
and Professor Seo Sang Hak said that.
Letter of resignation
It's Yu Dong Man.
You asked me that question last time.
Are you going to be a professor or a detective?
You said I had to choose.
To be honest, I thought it wouldn't
be that bad to become a professor.
But I was actually learning from the students,
embarrassingly.
I thought it would be better to catch people
who were less than me than to teach those who are
better than me.
So, I'm going back to being a detective, instead of being a professor.
It can't be. It can't be.
You rude jerk.
Don't you know how to knock?
What? Now what? Why is your face like that?
Professor Seo Sang Hak, please take care
of our losers.
Professor ...
♫ I guess you see a different me ♫
♫ The one person who resembles me, that’s you ♫
♫ When you look at me, when you touch me ♫
♫ I feel the reason for opening my eyes every day
That reason is you ♫
♫ Even when I was pushed around and fell down ♫
♫ You helped me get back up ♫
♫ Not just for one moment
But you make me live for a long time ♫
Police University
I was trying to help solve your case, chasing after the ones involved in the illegal gambling site.
It got a little dangerous.
What kind of crazy bastard messed with my daughter?
Please tell him if you see him, that it will take a week to process a resignation.
Where else would he have gone? I'm sure he is wherever the culprit is.
- Okay. Let's go!
- Let's go!
Who is it? Isn't he from that room?
I saw his face, and it was him.
As soon as it's cleaned up, I'll go overseas.
I called because I have something to tell you.
The last location where it turned off was in Changrin-dong.
If we do it now, we can catch those illegal gambling jerks,
I'll head out there first.