ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL DEEP AFFECTION EYES
BY ER DONG TU ZI ON JJWXC.NET
Thanks for today.
Sis.
Sis, are you okay?
He left?
Yes. I've checked it.
Thank you. Sorry to trouble you.
No need to thank me.
If this happens again,
just come to me.
My brother already told me
that you're loaded,
so you'll treat us right anyway.
How did you know?
Don't think we don't know.
- Just that--
- You go ahead first.
Wasn't it you who said--
Alright then.
Sis, I'm just a call away.
Thanks.
- So handsome!
- That guy in the bathroom just now…
That was him, right?
That's him.
You sent Maimai to distract Cheng Kairan.
What makes you so sure she can fool him?
It's simply that I'm quite familiar
with Mr. Cheng's character.
This kid's not just a good actor,
he understands people.
Smart kid.
What do you want from me?
I came to apologize
about what happened with Jiang Luzhi. I--
Got it. Anything else?
Add my WeChat.
You tanked your rep for me today.
I'll make it worth your while.
I'll transfer the money soon. Scan me.
Just ignore my sister's nonsense.
Not necessary.
Meng,
Dr. Gao's appointment is set.
No more no-shows.
Then, let's try
a different kind of compensation.
Date me instead.
I'm way more reliable than Jiang Luzhi.
What happened to you ladies?
This eager to get married?
Are you really younger than me?
Two years younger.
How do you know?
I accidentally saw your ID
when paying at the hospital today.
YE MENG
Are you following me?
You're overthinking.
I'm not that bored.
Alright then.
How do you feel about age gaps?
I only like them younger.
Preferably
the sweet, gullible type.
Get me?
You really do love playing the hero.
You risked your reputation today for me,
all to make Jiang Luzhi jealous.
Was it worth it?
None of your business.
Hurry. Off you go.
Can I add you on WeChat?
This kid needs to learn
to protect himself too.
Guard your reputation carefully.
- One more skewer of this.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- What else?
- And I'll take
another tofu skewer too.
- And meatballs.
- Meatballs.
- This one. Okay.
- How much is it?
Twenty yuan.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I was still hungry all afternoon.
Here, you eat.
Ms. Mei, how much is it in total?
Ten yuan.
- Thank you, Ms. Mei.
- Sure.
Thank you for tutoring with me.
Aren't you just making up for it
by buying me food?
Don't run away!
Don't chase me!
Is it Kai?
- What trouble is he in this time?
- Don't chase me!
- Can he win?
- Stop right there!
Don't run away!
No way he can win.
Help me, Ya'en Ye, Ye Meng!
- Stop!
- Help me!
Don't run away!
Hurry up!
- Don't run away!
FANG YA'EN
YE MENG
NO BULLYING KAI
Meng, who would've thought?
Even after all those years in Jiangbei,
you've kept your habit of early mornings.
Good.
From now on, you'll join your old grandma
at the morning market every day.
Grandma,
I'm into running.
That's why I'm up early.
You stick to your grocery shopping.
Morning runs are perfect.
Dr. Gao's early shifts start around then.
You two could squeeze in a date.
Do you know how many girls
are lining up for him?
Listen here.
Even if your legs break tomorrow,
you'll crawl there dressed to impress.
You listening?
And don't pretend
you didn't hear me this time!
Alright, I know. Let's go.
- Everyone's waiting at home.
- Are you going?
Yeah, I'll go tomorrow.
Hello.
What has Cheng Kairan been up to lately?
Cheng Kairan?
Well, he's made something of himself now.
But his whole situation…
I can't really explain it over the phone.
After I married, Chen Jian forbade me
from keeping in touch with him.
So, we haven't seen each other in years.
That scar on his face…
Is that from back then?
Exactly.
He was a handsome kid once.
Now that scar's ruined his face.
And he's been hunting for you.
For years,
he stalked your old house
by Nantang Temple.
Only when your grandma
moved in with Big Aunt
did he back off.
But he swore you'd pay.
Every last bit.
Then I'll go talk to him myself.
No, wait for me.
Wait until I get out of the hospital,
then I'll help you find him.
You're supposed to be
the "perfect wife and mother."
Why are you meddling in this?
Don't worry.
I'll handle it myself.
CONQUER THE NEW SEMESTER
What a coincidence.
You show up at my bar
with some "what a coincidence" act?
Why aren't you dodging anymore?
Do you have time?
Let's talk about the past.
Sure.
I know you've been haunted
by what happened back then.
Today, I came to tell you the truth.
I did call the police,
but they couldn't find any of you.
Because none of you wanted
to set foot in a police station,
those guys fled, and you ran too.
Hello. 110?
I need to report a crime.
Call the police?
We were so close back then.
You watched them drag me away.
Didn't lift a finger to save me.
I didn't realize how serious it was.
You were constantly
picking fights every other day.
- So, I didn't know--
- Cut the act!
What's the point of all this now?
Fine.
You're determined to pin
everything on me. Is that it?
Yes!
Then just stab me too.
Will that finally satisfy you?
You think I don't dare?
Kai.
No matter what happened,
a real man doesn't lay hands on a woman.
That's just not right.
Release it.
Brother, Jinyu,
what are you doing?
- Why are you here?
- How did you hurt your hand?
What are you doing here?
Jinyu has a performance tonight.
Since I finally have a day off,
I came to watch
and maybe get some extra tutoring
from him after.
Kai,
I truly want you to live well.
If that scar bothers you so much,
I know a doctor who could remove it.
Jinyu, are you okay?
Jingjing, let's go.
I'm coming.
- Show me your hand.
- It's okay.
How long exactly
are you planning to follow me?
Not following you.
My place is this way too.
Thanks for today.
Though that girl back there,
sweet and innocent,
totally your type, right?
I won't cross Cheng Kairan,
nor do I have the interest or energy
for your little dating games.
What about Jiang Luzhi?
Why did you date her then?
Because she is prettier than you.
You're the kid I've ever met
with the most terrible taste.
But you are the one with good taste to me.
I'm home now.
Guess our paths don't align anymore?
Super on your way.
I forgot my keys today.
Mind if I borrow
your place to get to mine?
Thanks.
Wanna come over to my place?
Nah, I'm good.
I'm leaving then.
Are you still alive?
Still alive.
I'll make sure to include
your injury compensation when I pay you.
What, are you made of money?
You're always paying for everyone.
Don't forget to treat that wound.
All these years.
Only you're still here.
NINGSUI BEER, EDGE-LESS TOAST BREAD
What are you doing up here?
OCEAN BLUE BAY PHASE III NOW LEASING
Baby,
are your eyes tired?
Mom, I'm so tired.
Here, have some milk first.
Let's just finish this last one,
then it's straight to bed, okay?
Mom, I don't wanna do this anymore.
Why giving up now?
If you quit, you'll repeat the year.
Listen to Mom. Drink your milk first.
It'll give you energy.
Come on. Just a few sips.
Look how well you're doing!
My clever girl!
AUDIO MESSAGE
You asleep?
Seems like you've been doing well lately.
I'm good.
Just checking in. How's life over there?
I'll be traveling for work soon,
so maybe I can swing by and see you.
Dr. Gao,
I've already shipped you the first batch.
This is their newest product.
Check it out.
The results are unreal.
One day post-op, next day walking.
- You're the doc, you know--
- You're back.
Finally decided to show up?
Dr. Gao's been waiting forever.
Were you too busy keeping company
for your lady friend at the hospital?
Meng's got a heart of gold.
Nah.
Hit the club last night.
Danced till sunrise.
- Was too wrecked to come back.
- Classic you. So damn cool.
Miss Ye.
We meet again.
You two know each other?
Meng, come sit over here.
- Scoot! Make room!
- No…
Come here.
Didn't sell, did it?
Sit here.
Dr. Gao,
last time you visited,
Meng was swamped with work,
but she's free today.
You youngsters should talk.
Really talk.
Grandma, where are you off to?
It's so much nicer when we chat together.
Come on. Sit down.
Right here!
Dr. Gao,
since we've already met
and you know all my information,
let's go through my humble requirements.
Sure.
After marriage,
we'll live at my parents' home.
On weekdays,
you'll wake up before 6:30 a.m. daily.
I value family-oriented partners,
so you'll need
to cancel all work-related
social engagements, okay?
With so many at home,
breakfast needs separate prep.
Grandma's teeth need extra attention.
Her congee must be extra soft.
Big Aunt loves
South Street's oily sugar cakes.
Use paper towels to blot all that grease.
Middle Aunt prefers
West Street's soup dumplings. Right?
That shop's always packed.
Go queue 30 minutes early
- or we'll miss out.
- None for me. I'm on a diet.
Aren't those your fave?
Then there's Little Aunt.
She's back from abroad,
so she's all about Western food.
Bagels, toast, all that needs to be ready.
And the coffee has to be
freshly-ground, obviously.
How'd I do?
Anything to add, everyone?
Why did you hit me?
Grandma needs soft food.
Big Aunt prefers low-grease sugar cakes.
Middle Aunt craves
South Street's soup dumplings.
Gotta queue early.
Little Aunt's all about bagels.
Don't forget freshly-ground coffee.
Okay.
Got it. Every detail locked in.
Good thing
I'm an early riser anyway.
Future kids will take my surname,
Ye. No objections, right?
I'm the last heir in this family,
so I've decided to follow
the nation's initiative
to have two kids, both Ye's.
You'll raise them.
That works for you?
Childbearing's hard on women.
I get why you'd ask.
And the surname doesn't matter to me.
We're family either way.
Dr. Gao, out with it.
How much did my grandma
pay you to marry me?
Grandma says after marriage,
I won't need to buy a house or car.
The old family home at Nantang Temple
gets put in my name…
Only after I turn 50.
By 50, that place
will be a condemned wreck.
Fine.
If Dr. Gao doesn't agree,
then we're done here.
I was joking about the house thing.
I already have a place and a car.
What I mean is,
I agree.
That's wonderful.
Let's chat some more--
- You, sit down.
- What are you doing?
Dr. Gao,
- shall we exchange contacts?
- What are you doing?
- Sure.
- Alright.
- Why is that?
- You youngsters chat away.
- Like you're the only one allowed to?
- Here, scan my code.
- Take it back.
- Okay.
- You try it first.
- You like drinking coffee too.
- Dr. Gao.
- Nourish yin, boost kidneys.
Dr. Gao!
You like drinking coffee too.
You're so annoying.
I've been to this shop too.
What coffee?
Since when do Chinese people
drink coffee every single day?
Come on. Better than
- the health products you sell.
- Take nutritional supplements.
Li Jinyu.
Li Jinyu, are you at home?
Li Jinyu!
Morning.
Good morning!
Did you sleep well?
327-3 XINGYI ROAD
Climb over my wall
to get to your place again?
No need today.
I've got my keys this time.
What do you want then?
Since our power is out,
could I borrow a toolbox?
Is that your puppy?
So adorable. What's their name?
Ping'an.
Hi, Ping'an.
I just moved in next door.
That makes me your new neighbor sister.
What's it doing up there? Not coming down?
It's obsessed with getting to the rooftop
but can never make it.
Stubborn little thing.
Sounds just like you. Good luck!
- How's your hand doing?
- No big deal.
Glad it's okay.
If anything happened to your hands
that put you off your piano,
I could never repay the loss.
Thank you!
Goodbye.
Li Jinyu.
Anything else?
I just realized
I'm not great with toolkits.
So, I'd like to hire an electrician
by the hour instead.
Thank you.
Meng.
"I've moved in with Fang Ya'en."
This kid!
I found the circuit diagram. Take a look.
Got it?
When I was at the hospital that day,
I noticed you have a crazy good memory.
Didn't memorize it.
How are you supposed to fix it?
I already know how.
You're just full of skills.
- Fixed.
- So fast.
Thanks.
But the lights still aren't on.
You sure you fixed it?
Turns out nothing needs fixing.
You just forgot to pay the electric bill.
Don't forget to clock my hourly rate.
What's wrong?
Give me your contact.
I'll transfer the money to you.
Payment QR code.
Paying by the hour.
I'll send you for one hour.
Fifty yuan enough?
What are you drinking?
My water dispenser's still broken,
and I'm parched too.
There's water in the fridge.
Help yourself.
MEMORY PALACE
Memory Palace.
I've seen that book before.
From what I hear,
it teaches you
to use familiar mental spaces
to memorize new, unfamiliar information,
like having rooms
in your mind
where each one
stores massive amounts of data.
Right?
Pretty much.
But it doesn't have to be a house.
It can be simplified.
It could be a person,
- even a single phrase.
- You bastard,
- Mom!
- get out of here!
- Get lost!
- Just close your eyes
- Mom!
- and picture any familiar object.
When you need the memory,
use your association skills to link
new information to these mental anchors.
It will be a bit easier
to remember things this way.
That's impressive. What's your alma mater?
No college degree.
Just a high school diploma.
High school diploma.
What?
Your fancy college degree
make you look down
on us high school grads?
How could I?
I didn't go to a prestigious university.
Jiang Luzhi did,
but she never looked down on you.
Why would I?
I've already broken up with her.
Yeah, ex-girlfriend.
But seriously, this Memory Palace
looks legit impressive.
A razor-sharp memory
isn't always a blessing.
What's the downside?
If I'd learned this back then,
maybe I could've outscored Jiang Luzhi.
You have no idea.
I memorized until
my hair literally thinned
and still failed.
Why do you always
compare yourself to Jiang Luzhi?
Not necessarily.
But didn't you say she's prettier than me?
There's always someone prettier.
That'd be endless competitions.
Who are they? Tell me.
Anything else?
Nothing really.
I mostly came by to ask,
are you free tomorrow?
I'd like to take you out to eat.
INCOMING CALL FROM JIANG LUZHI
Hello. Anything?
My high school friend's
getting married next week.
I'm a bridesmaid.
I'll be in Ningsui for two days.
MESSAGE FROM CLASS PRESIDENT
CAN YOU BE MY MAID OF HONOR?
Let's meet up then,
so we can talk.
Tomorrow's packed.
Then we can't eat together?
Got plans tomorrow.
Alright, let's plan for another day then.
I'll head out now.
Thanks for the water.
Pull the door shut.
No problem.
LUCK
IN MEMORY OF BELOVED HUSBAND LI MU
BY WIFE LI LINGBAI IN 2016
Jinyu!
Jinyu, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Dad, Mom doesn't want me anymore.
How could she ever not want you?
Mom's just upset right now.
It'll pass, I promise.
Please take me abroad with you.
- Don't leave me behind.
- Okay.
Dad will talk to Mom
when we get back. Come on.
Li Jinyu!
327-3 XINGYI ROAD
INCOMING CALL FROM LI LINGBAI
Why?
Why didn't you die instead?
Li Jinyu!
Li Jinyu.
I saw him in.
Want to try some double-skin milk pudding?
Made with love by your best neighbor.
Just for you.
ZHOU'S DOUBLE-SKIN MILK PUDDING
You made Zhou's Double-Skin Milk Pudding?
I went all the way to get this myself.
Just for you.
Why so glum?
You look like a kicked puppy.
If I cheer you up,
will you rank up with me?
Did something happen?
Does best neighbors like you
concern a little too much?
Has anyone ever told you
you're impossible?
No desserts for difficult people!
What?
You asked Li Jinyu
if he wants to date you.
A little louder and I'll be deaf.
I haven't even scolded you
for dropping big news while I was eating.
Now I get why
you were being so kind today,
specially delivering this milk pudding.
Do I really seem like the type
to ditch friends for a pretty face?
- Aren't you?
- Then don't eat it anymore.
Give it to me.
Wow, talk about a face-slap.
Just days ago,
you swore you'd never
date Jiang Luzhi's ex.
And now? Full-on simp mode?
Me? A simp?
Please, he just happens to be my type,
and my family
won't stop nagging me to marry.
- I need a boyfriend as a cover.
- Cut the crap.
You're only after him
because Jiang Luzhi has been
outshining you for years.
This is your petty revenge plot.
Well, this backfired,
and now the kid's being difficult too.
Well, well, if it isn't the kid himself.
What's he doing here?
We just got new inventory in,
and I need muscle.
Granny Tou mentioned he's free
for part-time work.
Might as well keep it in the family.
Ya'en.
Ye Meng bought me this
double-skin milk pudding.
Try some. It's incredibly sweet.
No, thank you.
Well,
your main tasks today.
Hang up these new arrivals.
Pack some items for warehouse storage.
And sort the rest for today's shipments.
- No problem.
- Sure.
For specifics, ask Ye Meng.
She knows the details.
I'll sort out the shipping orders.
- I'll help you up.
- No need.
Do your stuff.
Oh, now you can speak properly?
You can greet her in good manners.
But treat me with such an icy poker face?
If you want smiley service,
that's gonna cost you extra.
What are you doing here?
Boss,
you don't mind if I pick up
some part-time work, right?
Go ahead with your work.
Here for Ya'en?
- Let me call her for you.
- No.
I'm here for you.
Let's talk outside.
What's the matter?
I…
I came to apologize.
I know
you were provoking me on purpose that day.
You knew
I'd never actually hurt you.
But I also can't
pretend we can just stay strangers.
Alright, I understand.
Was there anything else?
What's your relationship with this guy?
You're younger than him.
Stop calling him "this guy."
He has a name.
Listen, you need to stay away from him.
Don't be fooled by how nice
he is to the old lady now.
That filial piety is all fake.
When he first got here,
he got into a fight
and sent someone to the ICU.
If she hadn't spent her life savings
to pay over the compensation,
he'd be finished by now.
Cheng Kairan, don't tell me
you never fought as a kid?
We've all been young and reckless.
Who hasn't made mistakes?
Honestly,
I could expose this bastard's scandals
for three days straight!
He's a total scumbag.
At my bar,
he's always swimming in women.
Has every auntie in town
wrapped under his tricks.
Remember Granny Zhang from town?
The one with all-white hair?
Well, two days ago,
in my shop's women's restroom,
she and another woman were…
- I know.
- I can't even say it out loud.
I know.
You know?
So, it was you in the booth that day.
When did you two meet?
- We just met.
- Just met?
Just met, and he's already
helping you lie to me?
That little brat must've
forgotten who's paying his salary.
Wait.
Don't tell me he likes you?
Cheng Kairan,
don't try anything funny.
When I lose control,
even I can't predict what I'll do.
Listen carefully.
if anyone messes with him in the future,
I'm holding you accountable.
Why are you still here?
- No, Ye Meng, I…
- Oh?
To what do I owe the honor, Kai?
Marching into my place
looking ready to throw hands.
Here to pick up fights?
You're crippled, Ya'en.
Don't worry about it.
I've been cursed.
Next time
you need help with anything,
just tell me directly.
I'll send someone from my bar.
Oh, please, with your people
standing guard, who'd dare come in?
I'll be out of business in days.
No big deal.
- I'm okay.
- Bit busy right now.
What are you here for?
Heard you hurt your leg.
Just came by to check on you.
Stop the act, alright?
I've told you.
Once this waiting period's over,
we shall get the paperwork done.
I want to take my son back for a few days.
Grandma's missing her grandson.
Now you want to be a good dad?
Ye Meng.
Rumor has it
you're barely scraping by in Jiangbei.
Pathetic.
All those retakes
just to flunk into some third-rate college
and still a nobody.
Just move back home already.
Get a stable job.
Maybe even land yourself
a respectable husband.
Who are you?
- Looking to get smacked in the mouth?
- Who are you?
Allow me to grandly introduce
Chen Jian,
our dear Ya'en's
wonderfully proper ex-husband.
A truly upstanding decent man.
Watch your mouth!
And what do you mean "ex-husband"?
We're not even fully divorced yet.
Soon, very soon.
If you want
to skip the waiting period, fine.
Ya'en can file for divorce immediately.
She's showing you mercy
only because you're
the father of her child.
Just leave already.
As for your request, noted.
I will ask Jiayu when he returns.
Fine.
But watch who you associate with.
I won't have you corrupting the child.
Ye Meng, this is the guy you vouched for?
Won't even stand up for you
when you're being bullied.
Do you need it?
Do I need it?
Perfect!
Then you don't need to go to my bar,
since you've already
found a side gig, right?
If anything else comes up,
go find your Lady Ye.
Kai, take some fruits with you.
You two keep these for yourselves.
Subtitle translation by: Wanjiao Song