♫ I still remember ♫
♫ Your flickering gaze ♫
♫ With a sense of excitement ♫
♫ You vowed eternal love ♫
♫ But over time, you've forgotten ♫
♫ Promises drowned in life's twists ♫
♫ Only memories remain like scattered fireworks ♫
♫ When I turned to walk away ♫
♫ If I could go back to the day we parted ♫
♫ I'd never let go of your hand ♫
♫ I cannot hide my feelings ♫
♫ I'm about to be out of control ♫
♫ As breathing turns weightless ♫
♫ All I possess is drowned ♫
♫ The me who still loves you deeply ♫
♫ Has never changed ♫
♫ If miracles could exist ♫
♫ Promises would be kept ♫
♫ Please remember ♫
♫ The dream where you see me ♫
I've done everything you asked.
Where's the surveillance footage?
Assign me the Hailan Bay project
and I'll delete the footage right away.
Don't push your luck.
Don't be so harsh.
I just want to share your burdens, Mom.
Is that wrong?
Stop pretending to be obedient.
You came back for revenge, didn't you?
True. Actually, you know me well.
So why would you make things hard for me?
This petty project means nothing to you.
Let me take over
and I'll delete the footage right away.
And I'll keep my mouth shut
about Wang Xing Sheng's disappearance.
Fine. Deal.
But I don't want to
hear about Wang Xing Sheng again.
You know how I do business. Don't ask for trouble.
Rest assured. I just want what's rightfully mine.
I hate to make things ugly
unless it's my last resort.
We're family after all. You're my beloved mother.
I'll take my leave now, Ms. Li. See you tonight.
Mr. Wang, forget about the mess of Hailan Bay.
It's someone else's problem now.
Welcome.
- You'll see her soon.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Everyone's inside.
Jin Yu! I've missed you so much.
You're finally back.
How could you be so cold? You never visited us.
Enough. People might think I wronged you.
Come on, let's drink.
What's wrong? Why aren't you
drinking with our buddy?
Stop calling him "buddy".
Has he ever texted you all these years?
Nonsense. We're the Three Musketeers in Jiangbei.
That's still a thing? I thought you'd replaced me.
We did. Long ago.
Ye Meng, come meet everyone.
This is Ye Meng, our company's beauty.
She's not just pretty
but also exceptionally skilled.
Ye Meng, this is Li Jin Yu I've mentioned,
Gou Kai's innocent childhood friend.
He owns 15% of Hanhai Group's shares.
It may sound insignificant, but it's a lot.
We've met before.
My mistake for not recognizing
Mr. Li's wealth earlier.
Lucky by birth. I'm jealous.
Hi, everyone.
- Ms. Li.
Jin Yu has finally grown up and become mature.
He volunteered to share my burdens.
Now we can work together as a family.
Sometimes I regret sending him abroad so young.
I felt guilty, worried he'd go astray.
But he excelled academically
and remained a perfect son.
As your mom, I'm truly proud of you.
Now, he has the support of his best friends.
It makes me so happy. Let's drink.
Yeah. Brothers forever. Ye Meng.
Come on.
To our success.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Alright, keep chatting. I'll greet others.
Okay.
Don't drink too much.
Mr. Li is such a talented young man
and a great son. How rare.
Stop flattering me. But we can talk over drinks
if you're interested.
Ye Meng can't drink. I'll drink on her behalf.
Who are you to drink on her behalf?
Isn't she married?
That's just a rumor. I know my employees.
I'm going to the restroom.
Gou Kai's relentless.
He even follows her to the bathroom.
Can't you tell? He's pursuing Ye Meng.
Are you mad at me?
Gou Kai, isn't it obvious?
Didn't I tell you I'm married? Learn boundaries.
You keep saying you're married. To whom?
Let me see the guy.
Aren't you dating someone, too? Where is she from?
Ningsui.
Ye Meng's husband is also from Ningsui.
Do you know who he is?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you obsessing over my husband?
Are you having a crush on him?
What are you talking about?
I'm just concerned about you.
Yes, I do.
Who is it?
It's me.
Fine. May I use the restroom now, Mr. Gou?
Sure.
Thank you. Where are you going?
To the men's room. Okay?
This is ridiculous. Stop messing around.
What's wrong with everyone?
What are you doing? Let me go.
Back to Gou Kai?
You pretended not to know me. What's going on now?
Are you scared that Gou Kai might be upset?
Yeah, I'm terrified. But you're
even more scared than me, aren't you?
They have decent wine here.
Want to get a bottle for your mom, Mr. Li?
It's hard to get a cab here.
Let me give you a ride.
No need.
My lawyer friend dug up something
on Wang Xing Sheng. I'll tell you on the way.
Let me give Miss Ye a ride.
We've all been drinking.
My driver has arrived. Safety first.
No need. You're the client.
I couldn't possibly trouble you.
I'll ride back with Mr. Gou.
My driver's been waiting.
Who doesn't have a driver these days? Let's go.
I could use a ride.
Go home by yourself.
You...
How are you getting back?
Want a ride?
Great, give me a ride then. Thanks.
I live kind of far, though.
No problem.
Don't take it personally.
Li Jin Yu's always like this.
Tai Ming Xiao said Li Jin Yu's girlfriend
is also from Ningsui. Do you know each other?
No, we don't.
Good, you'd better keep your distance from him.
That guy was trouble overseas,
hanging out with hooligans,
smoking, fighting, and drinking.
Completely wild.
You saw it earlier. He put on
that innocent act in front of Li Ling Bai.
So pretentious.
Mr. Li had an eventful time overseas.
You're interested in him?
Could you stop being crazy?
Tell me about Wang Xing Sheng.
Tell me who your husband is,
and I'll tell you about Wang Xing Sheng.
I just don't get it. Why are you so curious?
He's just a guy from the town, nothing special.
Then what do you see in him?
Tell me about Wang Xing Sheng, or I'm getting out.
Someone's following us.
Lose them.
Wang Xing Sheng has been convicted of
something like illegal fundraising.
He acquired a land plot in Ningsui.
The project failed due to broken capital chains.
Later, the Hanhai Group acquired the land.
That's the history of Hailan Bay.
When did it happen?
In August 2016.
August 2016?
You know how I do business. Don't ask for trouble.
I can't shake them off.
In July 2016, my mother committed suicide.
Then Wang Xing Sheng went to prison.
Six months later, Hanhai Group took over.
This is too much of a coincidence.
You suspect your mom's suicide
is connected to Wang Xing Sheng's fraud?
Yeah, that's right.
Change of plans. Head back.
You were following me in case
Gou Kai came to the hotel with me?
I'm here to see my wife.
I'll call the police.
I'm your husband. It's not trespassing.
Fine.
Let's get divorced.
What do you mean?
What do you think?
I went back to Li Ling Bai
to investigate your mom's case.
You don't know Li Ling Bai.
She's not as easy to handle as you think.
She's always been ruthless.
I suspect she's already making moves.
So let me look into Wang Xing Sheng, okay?
Or you'll be in danger.
Listen, I'll get to the bottom of it
no matter how dangerous it is.
Why do I feel I don't know you anymore?
Li Jin Yu, I'm exhausted.
I'm done guessing whether you're lying.
Just sign the papers.
Ye Meng.
♫ You ♫
♫ The moment I see you ♫
♫ The moment I think of you ♫
♫ The moment I hear any news of you ♫
♫ My heart is touched ♫
♫ My mind is occupied ♫
♫ Where to go ♫
♫ How to escape ♫
♫ Those memories of you ♫
♫ Have drowned me ♫
♫ I can't let go ♫
♫ I remain silent ♫
♫ My words stuck in my throat ♫
♫ Maybe this'll end the sorrow ♫
♫ Pretending to be determined ♫
♫ I'm still trapped at the starting point ♫
♫ The most perfect lie ♫
♫ I even deceive myself ♫
♫ If love means letting go ♫
♫ Let's sever all connections ♫
♫ But why ♫
♫ The moment tears fall ♫
♫ I don't want you to leave ♫
He was a witness in my mom's suicide case.
But he still hasn't confessed to me.
I suspect Li Ling Bai has something to do
with my mom's death.
Oh my god. Are you saying
Li Jin Yu is a secret rich heir?
His mom might be related to your mom's death?
And you've gone from spouses to enemies.
I didn't realize how dramatic it would sound.
I don't know this version of Li Jin Yu.
I even suspect that
the one in Ningsui is his twin.
So what's your plan?
I'll divorce him when the time comes.
Listen, getting divorced
isn't as simple as you think.
I've been sorting through transfer records
and financial statements recently.
It's been driving me crazy.
Forget it. Enough complaining. Get some sleep.
I need to open the store early.
Goodnight.
Ya En.
Hello, Mai.
My friend's birthday is coming up.
Could you help me pick a dress as a gift?
Sure. How old is she?
About my age.
What style does she usually wear?
Something lively and colorful.
She loves vibrant patterns.
How about pairing these together?
That works.
That's it, then?
- Okay.
- Alright.
How much is it? I'll pay via WeChat.
No need. I'll put it on Mr. Cheng's account.
That's not right. Kai will scold me.
I just won't tell him.
Alright, you're so good to me.
Don't mention it.
What brings you here today?
Did your boss give you time off?
We've been slow lately.
Kai's too overwhelmed to keep an eye on me.
What happened?
It's infuriating.
Someone's targeting our bar,
flooding us with fake bad reviews.
Our business... keeps declining because of this.
Did Kai offend someone?
I-I don't really know.
Ya En, don't tell anyone I told you.
I won't. I promise.
- Alright, I have to leave.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye.
Who could he have offended?
Oh no.
Why are you here during business hours?
Don't you have work today?
Are you hiding something?
How could I hide anything from you?
Unless I want an early death.
What's this?
Business is slow.
I'm just boosting sales with promotions.
Business has its ups and downs.
It's normal.
It's because of Chen Jian, isn't it?
Who's the snitch?
You think I can't read reviews?
It's not really because of his bad reviews.
That jerk! He deserves worse
than just a bucket of paint.
You threw paint at him?
You're not in trouble, right?
I'm fine. I just paid some compensation.
Let me handle this next time.
Don't worry about me.
Business will go back to normal.
Kai.
I think we should keep our distance.
My problems with Chen Jian shouldn't involve you.
I don't mind being involved.
But gossip spreads fast.
No one listens to explanations.
People might misunderstand us.
I-I'm not scared of gossip.
I visit you because...
I-I really like Jia Yu. We get along well.
You can't stop me from visiting
just because people might gossip.
M-My bar is already struggling.
Now you won't let me see my best friend?
Wait, why are you crying
all of a sudden? Stop crying.
Anyway, let's meet less often.
But you can text me. Okay?
No! If you stop me from visiting...
What should I do now?
Seriously.
Mai, Kai is crying. Talk to him.
It's not that I'm weak. I'm heartbroken.
Let me check again.
Alright, hurry.
Why did you come?
Mr. Gou doesn't seem happy to see me, huh?
Nonsense. But shouldn't you be heading
to the new project? Why are you back?
How else could I confront you, Mr. Gou?
Why did you suddenly transfer me away
and bring Ye Meng back?
Didn't you promise to bring me back
after Hailan Bay's opening?
Something came up.
We'll transfer you back after the new project.
You're still lying. What am I to you?
Obviously, a star employee.
I apologize if I led you
to misunderstand something.
But we're strictly professional. Nothing more.
So you've been using me from the start.
You approached me and gave me the project
just to undermine Ye Meng.
Now that Ye Meng's back, I'm useless to you.
So you're kicking me aside now?
I approached you? You approached me first.
The project was Ye Meng's to begin with.
I assigned it to you temporarily.
Now that she's back,
she'll get the project back, right?
You're shameless.
Don't you know Ye Meng is married?
Yeah, I do.
Listen. I'm done playing your games.
I quit.
Don't you adore Ye Meng?
Then I'll pray you keep loving her forever.
I'll be waiting for your downfall.
Thank you. Please wait.
I'm sorry for leaving abruptly.
There's a lot of work to hand over to you.
It's okay. Don't blame yourself.
It's sudden, but Gou Kai
wronged you in the first place.
I'd quit too. What's your next move?
- Haven't decided yet.
- Here's your coffee.
I may take a break in my hometown.
Thanks.
Sounds alright.
The Hailan Bay project has a new manager?
Will they replace the whole team?
No, don't worry. The new manager is our friend.
He is Ms. Li's son and Gou Kai's childhood friend.
I thought Ms. Li's son was in elementary school.
Not Li Zhuo Feng, but Li Jin Yu.
Which Li Jin Yu?
It's a difficult name.
J-I-N. Y-U. He was my college roommate.
He's also from Ningsui.
Do you know him?
No, but the name rings a bell.
I knew it.
Can I ask you something?
You've been in Ningsui for so long.
Have you ever seen Ye Meng's husband?
What does he do?
What does he look like? So mysterious.
No, I haven't met him. I'm busy.
I have to go. Let's talk next time.
Where are you going?
Who is her husband?
Mr. Gou.
Meng.
The new manager
of the Hailan Bay project is my acquaintance.
Relax. Don't be nervous.
Okay.
Li Jin Yu.
Hi, everyone. I have an announcement to make.
From now on, I'll be in charge
of the Hailan Bay project.
We know each other well, so I'll be direct.
I won't outsource PR anymore.
I've built my own team.
As for the project...
I'll be in charge.
Mr. Gou, long time no see.
Mr. Li, our team passed rigorous evaluations
and signed the contract with you.
You can't just cancel our collaboration.
Are you joking?
This is no joke.
As the project manager,
I have every right to make changes.
Really?
The contract clearly states
that unless the service provider
makes major errors,
the client can't terminate the contract at will.
I've reviewed your new trial operation plan.
Our evaluation says it's subpar.
Does that sound like a solid reason?
Of course, you can
end our cooperation for any reason.
But we can choose not to accept it.
Contracts legally bind both parties.
If you disrespect contract terms,
we'll file a lawsuit.
Go ahead. Think you can win the lawsuit?
The result doesn't matter.
Hailan Bay's trial opening is starting soon.
If we sue now, negative publicity would likely
delay the trial opening.
I hear Hanhai Group values this project.
Is this what you want?
The team can stay, but redo the plan.
Mr. Li.
Sure.
Submit the new plan by Monday.
Don't force it if you can't do it.
Just pack up and leave.
Meng, one week...
No problem.
Don't worry about the shops at Hailan Bay.
New operations officer
Cheng Kai Ran will handle it.
With the opening approaching, everyone is pressed
for time and can't afford to run around.
Please stay here for now. Alright?
Mr. Gou.
Is there anything else? We have work to do.
Mr. Li, please don't interfere with my work.
Don't forget our agreement.
Clothes really make the man.
You've hidden yourself well.
What do you want?
Let's talk about Ye Meng.
People don't know that you're married.
Including your best friends Gou Kai,
Tai Ming Xiao, and even your mom.
Don't try anything. Ye Meng and I
are already processing our divorce.
Out of nowhere?
I just joined the company.
I need a marriage alliance to secure my position.
Ye Meng is not my choice.
Well done. Such a good actor.
Do you have to fake a divorce to protect Ye Meng?
I know what she's investigating.
What do you want?
Replace Gou Kai's team and make me
the PR head of the Hailan Bay project.
Otherwise,
I wonder how Li Ling Bai would react
to the news of your marriage.
Mr. Cheng, this way please.
Mr. Li, Mr. Cheng is here.
Here. Bring me that contract.
Yes, Mr. Li.
Why did you ask me to meet
at Ye Meng's company? Where is she?
She went out for lunch.
Then what are you doing, sitting in her chair?
This is my company.
It's only been a few...
Mr. Li, here you are.
Wait, what did you call him?
- Mr. Li.
- Mr. Li?
Is she an actress? How much is your daily wage?
Mr. Li, what does your friend mean?
Go back to work.
Yes, sir.
So devoted. Great actress, my friend.
Come on. Take a look.
I want you to manage the shops at Hailan Bay.
Li Jin Yu, Legal Representative of Hailan Bay...
Nice prop work. "General Manager".
It really is you.
How did you become
the general manager of Hailan Bay
after just a few days in Jiangbei?
My mom owns Hanhai Group.
So you're giving me the shop management rights...
Since you have experience managing Jubaoshi,
it's better to entrust this job to you.
How convenient. I don't buy it. Tell me the truth.
Or I won't help, no matter how much you pay.
Ye Meng is divorcing me.
Why? What happened?
My mom might be related to her mom's suicide.
I want her to stop investigating.
It's not that I won't help...
But why not just tell Ye Meng directly?
Don't let this ruin your marriage.
I'm afraid my mom might target Ye Meng
if she finds out about the investigation.
You know, Wang Xing Sheng
may be gone because of my mom.
The company's full of her informants.
I need your help.
But no one can know.
If Fang Ya En finds out
that I helped you instead of Ye Meng,
we're both doomed.
We're different.
How are we different?
Even at your worst, you're only staying in place.
You're so mean...
Mr. Li, coming back to this,
you really need to make it up to Ye Meng.
This is serious.
Meanwhile, I'll do as you say.
See you around. Mr. Li.
This counts, right?
Of course.
I knew you had potential when I interviewed you.
My buddy, love you. Text me if anything comes up.
What?
As soon as Li Jin Yu took over
the Hailan Bay project,
he kicked you out
and brought back his ex, Jiang Lu Zhi?
Yeah, I never expected him to go this far.
But that makes no sense. Why would he do that?
The strangest part is that Jiang Lu Zhi
didn't expose my relationship with Li Jin Yu.
I suspect she made some deal with him.
Also, Li Jin Yu put Kai in charge of
the Hailan Bay's shops.
Kai? What's Li Jin Yu trying to do?
He's hindering my investigation.
Right. Look into Kai. Find out what they're up to.
Alright. Kai can't keep secrets. Leave it to me.
Let's stay in touch.
Okay.
Bye.
Mom, what happened to Kai?
Nothing. He's fine. Go to sleep.
The food was great today. I think I gained weight.
Get back to revising the proposal.
Meng, it's the tenth revised version.
See if it needs further improvements.
Ye Meng.
This is my home. Yours is over there.
Wait.
Do you need anything?
Why aren't you going in?
Hello, what's up?
Nothing much.
It's just that I fought with Ye Meng.
What?
But you can't tell Grandma.
Make sure they don't come to my place tonight.
Rest assured, my lips are sealed.
I won't breathe a word.
Hi, Granny. Jin Yu and Ye Meng had a huge fight.
- What?
- He just called me crying.
He was sobbing... So heartbroken.
What should we do, Granny?
Enough.
Hello. Why are you calling?
Meng and Jin Yu fought.
Meng even mentioned divorce.
What? They can't get divorced.
Did you fight?
Of course not. We're perfectly fine.
I'm new to the company, so I want to
discuss work strategies with Manager Ye.
Grandmas, why are you both here?
We brought chicken soup.
Let's go in.
Get in. Open the door.
Come on.
Be careful.
♫ You ♫
♫ The moment I see you ♫
♫ The moment I think of you ♫
♫ The moment I hear any news of you ♫
♫ My heart is touched ♫
♫ My mind is occupied ♫
♫ Go ♫
♫ Where to go ♫
♫ How to escape ♫
♫ Those memories of you ♫
♫ Have drowned me ♫
♫ I can't let go ♫
♫ I remain silent ♫
♫ My words stuck in my throat ♫
♫ Maybe this'll end the sorrow ♫
♫ Pretending to be determined ♫
♫ I'm still trapped at the starting point ♫
♫ The most perfect lie ♫
♫ I even deceive myself ♫
♫ If love means letting go ♫
♫ Let's sever all connections ♫
♫ But why ♫
♫ The moment tears fall ♫
♫ I don't want you to leave ♫