ADAPTED FROM THE NOVEL DEEP AFFECTION EYES
BY ER DONG TU ZI ON JJWXC.NET
Come in.
Hold on. Let me turn on the lights.
Yes, turn them on.
Get inside.
Juhua, give me a hand.
Coming. I'll help.
What's all this?
I told the grandmas
I found a new job at Hailan Port.
Didn't say my exact position.
And I figured you wouldn't want them
to know we've been fighting.
Food's here.
Soup's ready.
- Quick, quick.
- Right.
Quick, sit down.
Go on, both of you, sit.
Come on.
Hurry up.
You, sit down.
Meng, sit here.
Sit.
Here.
Meng.
Have some soup.
Meng,
you've lost weight these last few days.
Just gone to Jiangbei for work
and look at you, pale as paper.
I'm fine.
That's makeup.
She's always been fair.
Here, Jinyu, have some soup.
Drink this.
Thanks, Granny.
Your big aunt
made this especially for you.
It's nourishing.
- Drink up.
- Yes, drink up.
- Grandmas.
- Sure.
I already ate too much at dinner.
I can't finish this now.
I still have some work,
but once I'm done, I'll drink it all.
Work at this hour?
It's after office hours.
What kind of terrible boss
makes you work overtime after dark?
Tell me. What's more important?
Your health or your job?
- Family comes first.
- Exactly, family first.
Next time,
- I'll give your boss a good talking-to.
- Do it.
- Fire him if you have to.
- Fire him.
- Granny's right.
- Exactly.
Some people do need to be taught a lesson.
What a lousy boss. Drink up.
Drink, Meng.
Drink it.
There. Good.
- Refill her bowl.
- No, really, that's enough.
Do you ladies have other things to do?
Maybe get some rest.
Of course we do.
- Yes.
- Mahjong.
Yes, we're playing mahjong.
You drink.
Get the table out.
- Come.
- Quick.
- Over there.
- Come on.
Bring it here.
Careful.
More soup?
No, thanks.
Should we just go in?
Wait a bit longer.
Okay.
What exactly did Grandma Ye tell you?
She said to wait for her instructions.
Instructions? What instructions?
She didn't say.
- Maybe she'll call.
- Well…
Did she say when?
No. I don't know anything.
Useless.
Maybe we should sneak in and listen.
You go.
I don't dare. What if we get caught?
- Then hug me. It's freezing.
- Fine, hug.
I'm the dealer.
Three.
- Your turn.
- It's your turn.
Grandma, I really need to work.
We've already played eight rounds.
Can we stop now?
Two more.
- Yes, two more.
- Just two.
And since everyone's here tonight,
let's talk about the wedding.
- Yes, let's do it.
- Right.
Right.
You're both working
- at Hailan Port now.
- Yes.
- That makes things easier.
- Exactly.
So, what about the house?
We're not in a rush for that.
How can you not be in a rush,
Meng?
Don't worry.
Badou's dowry is safe with me.
If it comes to it, I'll sell the garden.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
No point waiting.
We'll go look at houses tomorrow.
First thing in the morning.
Grandmas, I'm really tired.
I'd like to rest early.
You should too, okay?
Fine, fine. I'll call your middle aunt
- and Maimai.
- Yes, call them.
I'll do it now.
They live far. Don't bother them.
- It's fine.
- Mom.
- Grandma.
Next time, call me earlier.
I had a pile of things to do.
- What are you doing here?
Didn't you call me over
to play mahjong?
She hadn't called yet.
Just passing by.
- Passing by.
- What a coincidence.
- Exactly.
- I just happened to be nearby too.
Fate, right?
Enough standing around.
Come on. Sit down.
- Hurry up.
- Come on.
- You have fun. We're going to our room.
- Off you go.
Go sleep.
Sleep with your wife.
- Okay, go.
- Hold her tight.
You idiot.
No sense at all.
You nearly gave us away.
It's freezing out there.
We almost caught a cold.
Serves you right.
That's not important.
What matters
is that we settle the wedding tonight.
We'll play mahjong till dawn
if that's what it takes.
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
Honey,
maybe skip working
on the proposal tonight.
You're exhausted. Get some rest.
Are you going to help?
You're so eager to push me out.
Li Jinyu.
You and the grandmas really think
this little act will work?
I didn't bring them here.
- It's them--
- I'm being serious.
They've just seen how hard
you've been working.
They came to check in,
- bring you some soup.
- Save it.
No, honey, I swear it wasn't me.
But yeah, it was.
Meilan, hurry and play.
Nine Bamboo.
I can't keep my eyes open.
Maimai,
find me some heart pills. Hurry.
Grandma, I can't either.
Middle Aunt, you go.
Bring me a coffee.
Pung!
Three Bamboo.
- Three Bamboo?
- Yes.
My turn?
Four Character… Don't want it.
What? Discard.
No, I'll dry it myself.
Let me.
Careful. You almost hit your head.
What are you doing?
I'm tired. Going to sleep.
Then sleep properly.
Move your hand.
Li Jinyu!
Not moving.
Since when did you start being shameless?
Since right now.
You're impossible.
THE RISING SUN ILLUMINATES
Ye Meng.
Ye--
Ms. Ye, someone's posted
about formaldehyde
under the promo video.
It's getting pushed to the top.
Mr. Li, the revisions are ready.
If there are no issues, please sign off.
LUSH GREEN LIVING
- I just reviewed it.
- Mr. Li.
Some of the data still isn't clear.
I'll fix it and bring it back.
One moment.
Mr. Li,
- I have something to report.
- Go ahead.
HAILAN PORT
For Phase Three,
I'll use the data from the first
two phases to refine our strategy
and build a model
we can duplicate for future campaigns.
Take a look.
THE FORMALDEHYDE LEVELS
ARE THROUGH THE ROOF!
We have a problem.
Check out our Weibo page.
HOW DARE THEY CALL THIS HEALTHY LIVING?
Formaldehyde over the limit?
What's going on?
Your team's in charge.
You owe us an explanation.
Our Weibo page
is flooded with posts about this.
If it keeps spreading,
the first thing people will think of
when they hear Hailan Port
is formaldehyde.
That would be a disaster.
And since your team
manages all the accounts,
if this blows up,
the blame falls squarely on you.
Mr. Li, you said you wanted results
that looked good without overspending.
Then take a look at my plan.
TESTING REPORT
Ningsui Environmental Bureau
just reposted our video.
They publicly confirmed everything.
I saw that negative comment
the day I took over this account.
Ms. Ye,
someone's posted about formaldehyde
under the promo video.
It's getting pushed to the top.
Keep an eye on it.
- If it gets worse, alert me right away.
- Got it.
If someone wants
to stir things up, we'll flip it
and make it work for us.
TESTING REPORT
The narrative's already shifting.
Yeah.
The backlash is fading fast.
With an official endorsement behind us,
the negative buzz will die down,
and we've gained
more visibility in the process.
Mr. Li, this is my cost-cutting,
results-driven approach.
It saves half the budget you set.
Looks like this seat
really does belong to me.
A bet's a bet.
Mrs. Ye,
you're even sharper than I imagined.
Thanks.
Problem solved.
Impressive.
Did you check that IP address?
Yeah. Sending it now.
SAFETY FIRST
Zhou Yu.
Take a look.
You know what to do. Don't forget.
This is definitely the IP address
that posted the comment.
Is that Jiang Luzhi?
Ye Meng's here too.
Tail Jiang Luzhi. I'll follow Ye Meng.
Got it.
Why are you following me?
I…
Calm down.
It's fake?
Are you hurt?
Drop the act.
He works for you, right?
- What?
- Jiang Luzhi was behind it.
You only brought her in
to push me out.
You're overthinking.
I just thought with the way things are
- between us now--
- Quit the excuses.
If you're that afraid
of anyone finding out,
sign the divorce papers.
Never. Don't even dream about it.
- Ye Meng…
- Let go.
Let go, Li Jinyu!
Li Jinyu!
What the hell are you doing? Let her go!
Let go!
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Ye Meng's part of my team.
You're just the client.
You don't get to boss us.
This is between us. None of your business.
There's nothing between us.
Ye Meng.
- Ms. Wang.
- Luzhi.
Long time no see. What brings you here?
- Visiting my mom.
- Good.
Drop by the school sometime.
Take care.
Whoa.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
This is Jiang Luzhi's house.
What?
- Luzhi who?
- Don't play dumb.
You're not here to tip off
your little buddy, are you?
No, no. I was just walking past
and thought of him.
Have you been tailing me?
Didn't you say the other day
we should cut down on contact?
Exactly.
And I didn't contact you.
I just happened to pass by
and ran into you.
I was saying hello.
Since when is that stalking?
Right…
Well, you've said hello. I'll get going.
Hold on.
Why do you look so guilty?
Guilty?
Me? Not at all.
You look exactly like a man
with something to hide.
Tell me the truth.
Li Jinyu still can't let go
of his ex, can he?
And you've been helping him sneak around.
What… What are you even talking about?
I'll call Ye Meng right now.
No, no, wait! Don't.
I just… I noticed
Jiang Luzhi switched jobs.
I thought she was up to something,
so I came to check it out.
That's your excuse?
Let's see if Ye Meng buys it.
Please, don't call her.
Can you stop dragging
Ye Meng into everything?
I'm just following orders, okay?
Don't make this harder for me.
Cheng Kairan, answer me.
Whose side are you on,
mine and Ye Meng's or Li Jinyu's?
I… Of course, I'm on your side.
But don't you remember…
this alley?
Stop trying to change the subject.
Listen.
Whatever Li Jinyu does,
you tell me immediately. No hiding it.
So, wait… Am I supposed
to contact you or not?
Well, on this,
yes, you should absolutely contact me.
And you'd better not delay.
I'm leaving.
Ya'en!
You don't remember this alley?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm home already.
Why are you still following me?
What's going on between you and Li Jinyu?
I told you. Strictly business.
Client and contractor.
Wait.
I've known him for years.
His face is always stone cold.
Never seen him look at someone like that.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
What you saw was tension.
A hostile client-vendor relationship.
I'm not joking. I'm serious.
- Nothing to talk about. Go home.
- Hold on.
327-4 XINGYI ROAD
Uh…
It's still early.
I've never been to your place before.
- Can I come in?
- Not happening.
Cousin-in-law!
Maimai.
Here to feed the dog?
What dog?
- And this is…
- My boss.
Nice to meet you, boss.
I'm Qiao Maimai,
her cousin-in-law.
My cousin is her husband.
What's up?
Oh, right.
My cousin's at Gem tonight.
Want to come with me?
Gem?
The bar in town.
I've got things to do. You go ahead.
Alright. Call me when you're free.
Bye!
Why are you still standing here? Go.
Just let me come in for a bit.
Did you not hear her?
My husband runs a bar.
He's deep in that life.
Still want to come in?
Ye Meng.
What now?
You've really let me down.
How did you become like this?
What is wrong with him?
GEM MUSIC BAR
MUSIC BAR FESTIVAL, SPRING WAVE IGNITES
In a bit…
Li Jinyu
is coming to see me.
I swear I didn't
mean
to contact
you.
Oops.
Don't look at me like that.
You're creeping me out.
Uh, that photo… I already sent it.
See for yourself.
After Jiang Luzhi met with that guy,
she went back to her parents'.
No surprises.
Nothing unusual.
- Relax.
- You got spotted, didn't you?
No way.
I'm great at staying invisible.
But if you're worried,
I'll tail her again tomorrow morning.
Li Jinyu, have you lost your mind?
Okay, fine. I'll tell you.
When I was shadowing Jiang Luzhi,
I ran into Fang Ya'en.
And I'm pretty sure
Ye Meng sent her to keep tabs on me.
Please, don't put me
in the middle of this.
It's tearing me apart.
And this knife…
It's a toy?
Take this!
Nearly gave me a heart attack.
Ye Meng was attacked by the guy
who met with Jiang Luzhi.
He had this on him.
And Ye Meng? Is she okay?
She's fine.
The attacker was Zhou Yu,
an intern brought in
for the Hailan Port project.
I think he's also tied
to that negative comment.
I've had someone
pull his HR file.
Look into his background for me.
Jinyu.
What are you doing here?
Talking business with him.
Mr. Gou!
And you are…
Let me give myself
a proper introduction. Cheng Kairan,
owner of this bar.
So, you run this bar.
Pleasure to finally meet you.
I've heard plenty about you.
Always wanted to see for myself.
See what exactly?
Your charm.
Specifically, what makes
Ye Meng choose you.
I wanted to know
what's so special about you
that she'd marry you so willingly.
Charm's obvious,
isn't it?
But marriage…
- That's…
- Kai.
You and Ye Meng grew up together.
Nobody on the outside
can really understand what you two share.
And Gou Kai,
always jealous,
always after someone else's girl.
If she doesn't like you,
it is your problem.
Yeah, maybe ask yourself why.
Ye Meng's standards have always been high.
Average guys don't even register.
She's not into your type,
all appearance and no depth.
She likes men like me,
real businessmen.
No offense.
Mr. Cheng, right?
Yeah.
I'll get straight to the point.
You and Ye Meng are not a match.
And word is you two are already divorcing.
So, let's make a deal.
Even the divorce news is out.
That hurts, man.
Alright…
Five million.
Wire me five million
and I'll walk away
from Ye Meng forever.
How much?
Five million.
You really dare ask that?
Yeah. Isn't that how it works in dramas?
You hand me a blank check,
I write in the number?
But if you don't have that kind of money,
stop pretending you're loaded.
Since this is our first meeting,
I'll give you a discount.
Two hundred and fifty.
Two hundred and fifty what?
Two hundred and fifty yuan.
Come on, Mr. Gou. With all your money,
you can't even put down that much?
That's not true love.
Jinyu, what's that supposed to mean?
Whose side are you on?
On the side of true love.
Fine.
- I'll transfer it.
- Wait, you're serious?
I was joking.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Do I look like I need your pocket change?
True love is priceless.
Good.
Then I'll show you
just how much love is really worth.
Hailan Port's going smoothly.
Nice work.
Come to Ningsui for a team retreat.
Guy's out of his mind.
He really thinks
Ye Meng and I are a thing?
What if he actually hands me five million?
You're out of your mind.
Ye Meng is worth more than money.
Says the guy who once
couldn't scrape together 500
and now acts all high and mighty.
You're a textbook case
of a nouveau riche mentality.
Pathetic.
How long are you planning
to keep this marriage under wraps?
Until the Hailan Port project
is wrapped up
and Li Lingbai's people leave Ningsui.
You owe me five million.
But hey, if you don't pay, that's fine.
We're buddies, right?
You bought those
smear accounts, didn't you?
You think work
is just some game where you get
to scheme against Ye Meng?
So, she ran crying to you?
I'm only doing what I want.
How I do it is none of your business.
I agreed to a deal with you.
That didn't mean you could gamble
with the company's reputation.
If I catch you pulling stunts
like this again, especially
if they hurt Ye Meng,
our deal is done.
Airhead.
Why's she still here?
None of your concern.
What are you doing here?
Company retreat.
Dropped in to check on you.
And guess what?
Ye Meng and her small-town husband
are finally splitting.
Who told you that?
Gou Kai.
Why else would he
suddenly throw a retreat
and ask me to set up
a love confession scene?
Love confession?
- Where?
- Aurora Racetrack.
You should come.
He's footing the bill anyway.
Only problem is,
I have no idea
how to set up a confession stage.
Still here this late?
Shouldn't you be at home
playing the rich wife?
Why act like a wage mule here?
Or did that hidden marriage of yours
blow up in your face?
If I'm stuck working overtime,
isn't it because of you?
No clue what you're talking about.
Check your WeChat.
That blurry back shot?
Even my mom couldn't tell it's me.
This is your idea of framing me?
Framing you?
If I wanted to,
the second Zhou pulled a knife on me,
I'd have handed this to the cops.
Would've been cleaner.
Zhou Yu attacked you?
Impossible.
I only said his last name was Zhou.
Never said it was Zhou Yu.
You set me up.
He really did come after me.
But let's be honest.
With your nerve,
the most you'd dare
is hiring him to spam bad reviews.
You'd never risk more.
What are you doing?
Giving you one chance to apologize.
Come on. Drink.
I really can't drink anymore.
Alright, fine. I'll drink.
I'm sorry. Is that enough?
You've baffled me since we were kids.
In third grade, you were
already ratting me out.
When you get nervous,
you pinch your fingers the same way.
Never changed.
You really do know me.
And you know me just as well.
You think I wanted this?
Growing up, your grades
were worse than mine,
but you never cared.
Teachers and classmates praised me,
but you didn't bat an eye.
But with that face of yours,
you lived louder than anyone.
If I really didn't care,
would I have quit
Gou Kai's company just to save face?
You really envy my face?
Truth is, I envy you more.
At least you've got the brains for it.
But tell me, Jiang Luzhi,
don't you have your own life?
Why do you spend every day watching mine?
Be honest. It's not Gou Kai
you're obsessed with.
It's me, isn't it?
You're out of your mind.
Though I'll admit,
the reason I joined Gou Kai's company
was because I thought you liked him.
I wanted to get under your skin.
Exactly.
I'm the one you've been obsessed with.
You just won't admit it.
Who would've thought…
the joke's on me.
So?
You awake now?
I still remember
when you came back for graduation
and gave that speech.
You stood on that stage, shining,
talking about your dreams.
You said you'd study harder than anyone,
make it to the big city,
to be somebody,
to know yourself,
to love yourself,
and to surpass yourself.
That cringe speech?
I forgot it years ago.
Can't believe you still remember.
Jiang Luzhi,
you should start living for yourself.
Maybe. But I still hate you.
Right back at you.
I'm leaving.
A headhunter's been calling.
The offer's way better
than what I get at Hailan Port.
At least I won't be stuck
working for you and your husband.
And for the record…
The only reason Li Jinyu let me stay
was because
I threatened to expose your marriage.
He wanted to protect you.
But tell him not to worry.
Even if I quit now,
I'll still hold up my end of the deal.
I won't blow your cover.
Ye Meng.
I hope you're happy.
Today's all about freedom.
If you want food and drinks, come with me.
If you want to lie down and chill,
head over there.
And hey, Gou Kai's picking up the bill.
- Nice!
- Let's go!
Let's go!
This is one of the projects
our company's about to launch.
Let me take you for a lap.
I'll pass.
You're going to be in charge
of the racetrack proposal.
At least get a sense of the place.
What are you doing here?
Tai Mingxiao asked me to come.
Haven't raced in a long time.
Want to try me?
When's the last time you raced?
Your skills must be rusty.
Afraid you'll lose?
Get in.
Wait.
About the proposal…
I've got a few ideas
I want to discuss with Mrs. Ye.
Why don't we talk them over in my car?
Li Jinyu, what exactly are you playing at?
And what's with the matching outfit?
You did that on purpose?
Mr. Gou, you're the contractor.
I'm sure you don't mind.
CARVOLUTION MOTOR
Ye Meng, watch yourself.
About my mother's death…
You were the witness, weren't you?
Subtitle translation by: Jiaxin Wang