♪ Out of the blue, the rhythm has started ♪
♪ Pulling all strings of emotions ♪
♪ Tear off the strikingly long hemline ♪
♪ The best arrangement has been set ♪
♪ So don't mess up on purpose ♪
♪ Who's always standing behind the tide of smiles ♪
♪ Suffering under the dark clouds ♪
♪ Luckily, still standing strong ♪
♪ Who is always in the winter of sadness ♪
♪ But is visited by the sunlight ♪
♪ Even icebergs would warm up and smile ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refused to throw away the words "so sad"? ♪
♪ The best arrangement ♪
♪ Bye, goodnight sunset ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refuse to look forward to a better future? ♪
♪ Baby, tell me why, why, why? ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refuse to look forward to a better future? ♪
♪ Baby, tell me why, why, why? ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
[Love Designer]
[Episode 37]
Look at this.
It's so cute.
Is it cute?
It's cute.
And this. You...
Ms Tian.
Mom.
Lin Lin.
Do you want to
make Mom sad so badly?
I...
Wu San.
I have
some work to do at my shop.
Qin Qing.
Mom!
What are you doing?
Do you want to die?
Have you asked Song Lin
what's going on?
Qin Qing has just opened up
to Song Lin.
If I tell her,
she'll definitely misunderstand him more.
Actually, nothing happened between us.
He's been very busy
with the new project.
I didn't have the time to ask him either.
Qin Qing.
Am I being contradictory?
Before this, I even told you
that Wu San was so busy,
that you'd better not cling onto him every day,
And don't contact him every day.
Why do our roles
swap now?
It's not your first time
being this way.
Do you believe him then?
Yes.
I believe him.
Tell me. Why can't the two people
who are in love
be together
smoothly and peacefully?
Maybe a relationship
needs to work on.
Otherwise, how else can I put it?
I just need to stop
thinking that it's something bad.
How is this not bad?
It sucks.
Do you know that
even in front of his mom, Wu San
has never
let go of my hand?
I'm always the one letting go of his hand.
Since love
involves two people,
whether or not
to let go shouldn't
be decided by one person.
I've been thinking
although love is important,
kinship and family are more important.
To let him choose between
love and kinship,
it's too cruel.
I don't want him to make
this kind of choices.
Why has everything been so hard recently?
It's too hard.
[Message from Zuo Yu Lin]
Miss Fang, don't worry.
Lin and the others will be fine.
Xiao Fei sent me a photo.
It shouldn't be long
before they come back.
Miss Fang.
Please check
if the content for
the invitation okay.
It's okay.
We've received the information
of all guests, right?
Yes, we have.
I'm so careless.
I'll check with Tang Jie
again later.
Sure.
Once you're done with the invitation,
don't send them out.
Leave the time blank for me.
Why?
I want to postpone the opening time.
Isn't the time
that we set before alright?
I have some other plans.
Give me an unfilled invitation.
I'll get it.
Miss Fang.
Is there
a story behind this?
Hello, who are you looking for?
I'd like to customize a few sets of clothes.
Sure. This way, please.
Hello. How may I address you?
My name is Lin Zhen Zhen.
Su Yu Shan's wife.
You're Mrs Su.
I haven't met you before.
Nice to meet you.
Aside from water,
would you like a drink?
We have
coffee, tea and juice.
It's alright.
Water is fine.
Sure.
Mrs Su, are you here today
to customize
a suit or a dress?
Both.
These are some design sketches.
You can have a look.
Is it for yourself?
For me and my husband.
Make a few.
We wear them often anyway.
They'll be worn.
No problem.
These are some design sketches.
Please have a look.
There are some samples inside.
If they're not to your satisfaction,
we can also
customize based on your request.
I heard you are moving soon.
Yes.
Maybe when the clothes are done,
you'll go to the new shop to try them on.
It's at Qingpu district.
I know.
When you took part
in the design competition,
I noticed you.
I'm not sure
what is
so noticeable about me?
My husband thinks very highly of you.
Shouldn't that
be noticeable to me?
I see.
Mrs Su didn't come today
just to customize clothes.
I get it now.
To be honest to Mrs Su,
President Su has helped me a lot,
he recognized my talent.
I'm very thankful that
he gave me the chance
to put my thoughts in action.
That's it?
That's it.
I heard that
you are Song Lin's girlfriend.
Yes.
A girl with your personality
should be
pretty popular among boys.
Actually,
as long as my boyfriend likes me,
that's enough.
You don't believe me?
I believe you.
I've never doubted you.
I came here today to see
what kind of person he gave
Si Yue's building to.
Mrs Su, I think
President Su definitely
cares about you a lot.
Even other people like us
can tell obviously.
A few days ago in Milan,
he purposely went to the jewelry exhibition
to select jewelry for you.
Have you received it?
I received it.
Every festival and anniversary,
he would buy jewelry for me.
Mr Su really loves me a lot.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
Are there other designs?
Let me have a look.
Here are some fabrics.
You can have a look.
Okay.
They are seasonal.
This trip to the United States
went pretty smoothly.
Go back and have a good rest.
The investment fund
will come in within these two days.
This time,
thanks to you.
I really have to thank you.
Let's not say
such empty words.
They're not edible or usable.
Look at you.
If there's anything you want to eat or use,
tell me.
Not a problem.
As if I don't eat out enough
all year round.
If you really want to thank me,
cook a good homemade meal
by yourself to reward
your hero, me.
What? I cook?
Why? You're not willing to?
You're so smart.
You should master it very fast.
Moreover,
the things I want to eat are very simple.
Braised pork, pickled bamboo shoots,
and sweet and sour fish.
Tell me. You quit
for my small company.
Do you regret it?
Don't flatter yourself, okay?
The reason I left
the previous company
is because
their decision panel
had doubts about
my business judgement.
This is something
I can never tolerate.
Plus, my collaboration with you
has its financial return.
Only hard cash feels real.
But the only thing
I can do is the investing section.
The rest
depends on your team.
Don't worry about this.
I'll send you back first.
Send President Ling back home first.
It's okay, Mister.
My house is too far.
Send him back first.
I'll feel sorry about that.
Don't.
I'll take a nap first.
You've worked hard for the past two days.
You've worked hard too.
Have some rest.
Thank you for this time.
How did you know I came back?
I'll get going.
Bye.
You came to pick me up?
I heard from others.
This time, I left in a hurry.
I didn't get to tell you.
But let me tell you
good news.
I've sold the shares.
All of the shares.
The problem is solved,
so the company is saved.
Song Lin.
I know you don't want to share with me
about your work,
but you should at least talk to me
about private matters.
For example, where you're going?
Who you're going with?
For how many days? When are you coming back?
As your girlfriend,
I have the right to know about these.
You know that day,
I went to your company for you.
Zuo Yu Lin told me,
you went to the United States with her.
Do you know how I felt?
And for the past three days,
aside from that message,
you didn't contact me at all.
It's too cold.
Let's go back and talk. Okay?
Let's go.
Song Lin.
If you continue to
ignore my feelings,
I think our relationship
can't last any longer.
Grandma.
Ya Ya.
I miss you.
This weekend, come back to visit Grandma
if you have time, okay?
Okay. Then I...
I'll go back today. Okay?
Okay, okay.
I'll hang up now.
That's the story.
I think I get what you said.
About this...
If it was back then,
I'd definitely be angrier than you.
You know my personality.
You don't even have to say,
I would've found Song Lin
to teach him a lesson.
But recently,
after experiencing
the matter with Ms Tian,
I realized that
for two people who love each other
to get together,
it's really not easy.
So,
when we face problems,
we have to be calmer.
Actually, I'm not angry about
who he went with
or where he went.
What I'm angry about is
why he never told me anything
before all this happened.
If I didn't go to the company that day
and bump into Zuo Yu Lin,
I wouldn't even know
that he went to the United States.
He has been doing this recently.
Whether it's about work
or his daily life,
he doesn't tell me anything.
If we continue
not to communicate,
I'm really worried that
the distance between us
will get farther.
Tell me. If this
happened to you,
wouldn't you be angry?
I would be angry.
Of course, I would be angry.
But I think this situation
is a bit different.
I think Song Lin didn't tell you
because
he didn't want to get you involved
in the competition
between him and Su Yu Shan.
He didn't want you
to be stuck in between.
Actually, I know.
He wanted to protect me.
He didn't want my work
to get affected.
But I also want him to know that
as his girlfriend,
I can help share his burden.
Even if it's to listen to his worries,
it's fine.
I also want him to know that
I need him.
I can be by his side.
He is protected.
He can feel safe.
I understand.
What I said to him just now
might have been too harsh.
What should I do?
Look for him. Send him a message.
It's him?
He said he's at his grandmother's house.
At his grandmother's house...
Go and meet him.
Director Wang.
Sister-in-law!
Why are you here?
Song Lin's not here today.
It's okay. I'm looking for you.
Sure. Have a seat.
Okay.
Why did you look for me?
Any questions?
I promise to tell you about all I know
without reserve.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you know where is Song Lin's
grandmother's house?
What do you want to do? Go to see him?
I'll send you the address.
Okay.
My buddy
has been outstanding since young.
He's used to being proud and arrogant.
But this time,
his pride was
really hurt.
His pride was hurt?
I've sent you the address.
Okay.
Let's put it this way.
He...
feels that you don't
need him,
as if he's not needed,
he can be replaced at any time.
He's always not needed.
Maybe he's not used to that.
Is that how he thinks?
He must have
done something wrong.
As for you, please be forgiving.
Don't get annoyed.
Please bear with him.
Honestly
he's the only buddy I have.
Please and thank you.
Grandma.
Don't keep working
in the field.
You're old now. Don't injure yourself.
If you really want to eat
your own vegetables,
I'll hire two workers
to work for you, okay?
Hire two workers?
Grandma enjoys
working on my own.
There's no point buying vegetables.
What happened?
Did you sprain your back?
Look, I said it just now.
Hurry and go back.
Leave this to me.
There are still so many leaves
to tidy up.
Don't worry, I'll do it.
Okay. I'll go back first.
Go back. Go back.
I'll go and cook for you.
Okay.
If you're tired,
go back home and rest.
I'll go back if I'm tired.
Okay.
Go down slowly.
No problem.
Hurry and go back.
Okay.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello.
Do you know
the person living here?
Yes.
Is there someone
called Song Lin here?
Song Lin?
That boy is in the vegetable field.
Where is the vegetable field?
You
walk along this path towards that side
and you'll see it.
Okay. Thank you, Grandma.
Song Lin.
Are you still angry?
Seeing you,
I can't get angry.
Then I guess it's useful
to be good-looking.
♪ Patches of colors, dancing fingertips ♪
♪ Everything is craving for the side of your face ♪
♪ The wind stopped, the insects quieted down
But my breath is getting faster ♪
When I was young, I really liked to
play at Grandma's house.
I'd rushed to come here during the holidays.
What did you normally
play here?
There are lots to play with.
Climbing trees, climbing walls.
Going out and picking
the apples of the neighbors.
You were so naughty when you were young.
Were you been beaten before?
Back then, there were
a lot of kids here.
Every time I was here, I would
ask them out to play.
Going to the water reservoir together.
Climbing the sand piles together.
Poking ant nests.
When we came back after getting into trouble,
they'd get beaten at home.
I would go back home
and Grandma would cook something good.
Your grandmother surely loves you.
She loves me a lot.
How old is your grandmother?
Does she live here alone
normally?
There are relatives here
taking care of her.
She's old now.
She can't do a lot of things
on her own.
I wanted to bring her
to live in the city.
But she doesn't want to.
She said the air is better here.
It's quieter.
And she has her own vegetable field.
She can plant vegetables
and eat whatever she planted.
Old people are like that.
They prefer
natural places.
Maybe she's used to
being here.
Grandma went back to cook.
I'll bring you back to
meet her later.
She probably wants to meet
my girlfriend too.
Song Lin.
I neglected your feelings
because of my work before.
I'm sorry.
Don't say
sorry to me.
Everyone would be
in a bad mood.
Arguing with you
was also because I took things personally,
and got myself into a dead end.
What do you think
we keep arguing about?
Isn't it because I care about you?
♪ Would you like to indulge at the moment.
Embrace everything? ♪
♪ I have a question. Why? Suddenly, I feel dizzy♪
Is it comfortable sitting here?
♪ Is that the taste of the passion of midsummer? ♪
Grandma probably has prepared the meal.
Do you want to go back and eat?
Or do you want to sit here
with me for a while more?
Either is good.
♪ Your beauty is unparalleled ♪
Let's go. Go back and eat.
♪ Back to back, I miss you every single day ♪
♪ Two hearts beating as one ♪
Is your butt dirty?
Your butt is so dirty.
You hit me.
Walk slower.
I'll walk from this side.
♪ Patches of colors, dancing fingertips ♪
♪ The beat of my heart is so obvious ♪
Grandma, I'm back.
Let me introduce her to you.
Grandma.
This is Grandma.
This is...
Just now, you...
Just now what?
Just now, Grandma showed me
the direction.
You're not going to introduce formally?
Of course, I will. Aren't I'm doing it now?
This is Zhou Fang,
my girlfriend.
Hello, Grandma.
Good, good.
Hurry and sit.
I'm not sure whether the dishes
suit your taste.
Yes, they do. I'm not picky with food.
What a good girl.
Here. The soup is here.
Auntie Zhao.
Grandma Song.
Who is this? So pretty.
Our granddaughter-in-law.
Really?
Let me introduce.
This is Auntie Zhao.
This is Zhou Fang.
Hello, Auntie Zhao. I'm Zhou Fang.
Grandma, you're so blessed.
Ya Ya is the one who is blessed.
He found such a good wife.
Ya Ya?
Yes.
Pet name.
When he was young, he didn't grow teeth.
So, we gave him a pet name.
So, you're Song Ya Ya?
Hurry and eat.
That's so cute.
Here, here.
Oh, right, little girl.
It's your first time here,
I didn't have the time
to prepare a gift for you.
This one is for you.
No, Grandma. It's okay.
I didn't bring anything
for you either.
Really, it's okay.
You don't like it?
No, that's not what I mean.
Then...
Come.
Come, good girl.
Put it on.
It looks better on you.
Hurry and eat.
Just wear it.
Grandma gave you that.
But let me tell you,
this bangle
has a story.
It's precious.
It's a gift from Grandpa.
Then I can't accept this.
Grandma, please take it back.
No, no.
Keep it, keep it.
It's okay.
Grandma, it's okay. Don't worry.
If she doesn't like me anymore,
I'll get it back for you.
You brat.
Look at this kid.
Hurry and eat.
Here. Hurry and eat.
What are you doing?
Why did you come over?
Grandma hasn't slept yet.
Don't let her know
that I am in your room.
Why are you here, Song Ya Ya?
Can you not call me Ya Ya?
I came to chat with you.
Communicate.
Chat about what?
Confession session.
Answer all questions.
No fallout.
No getting angry.
Sure. Who's going first?
You go first.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Do you have
an ex-girlfriend that you can't forget
even until now?
I don't even have an ex-girlfriend.
What's there to be unforgettable?
Don't brush it off. Tell me seriously.
I'm not brushing it off.
I don't have an ex-girlfriend.
I'll pinch you.
This...
Once broken up, a girlfriend
is just another stranger.
I don't miss or think about her.
There won't be
any trace left in my life.
That's cold.
It's either I'm cold
or I do you wrong.
Choose one.
Fine. You win.
Your turn to ask.
I'm going to ask now.
Then...
What?
I'll ask something
that I don't really
want to know
but I'm curious about.
Please go through your
relationship history.
That's a big question.
How big is that?
How rich is your history?
Fine. I'll confess.
When I was in my first year
of university, I had a crush on
Huo Chen Dong.
Who? Who did you have a crush on?
Face towards me.
Didn't you say there was nothing between you two?
There was nothing between us.
How is this nothing?
I only had a crush on him
for a short time in university.
A few months.
I even let you have a meal with him.
How big-hearted can I be?
I came clean to him
when we ate together.
We are just bros now.
You two still talk
about this until now?
Can you cut it out?
We've cut it out.
What?
We've gone over the matter
with your ex-girlfriend.
We can't go over
the matter with my crush?
Yes, we can.
Then I'll continue.
After that?
After that,
there was too much coursework in university,
so I wasn't in a relationship.
After I graduated and
came back from overseas,
I met Wang Ze Yang.
Your life has been
pretty rough.
You can skip Wang Ze Yang.
I know everything.
After that...
It's me.
Now that you said it,
my relationship history
isn't that rich.
It's alright. You have three.
That's the standard answer.
Fine. My turn to ask.
Ask then.
How expensive is this bangle?
If I break it,
can I afford to pay for it?
You definitely can't afford it.
You can only pay me back
with the rest of your life.
Then I have to be careful.
Be careful of what? You don't want to pay me back?
You said
it'll cost the rest of my life.
Of course, I have to be careful.
I need to keep it when I get back.
The rest of your life
has nothing to do with it.
Okay?
You can't leave me anyway.
We'll have to be together no matter what.
It's you who can't leave me.
It doesn't matter who can't leave the other.
The point is we will be together.
Right?
Right.
You know...
It's almost time now.
Uhm...
Grandma has seen you as well.
Don't you think
it's time to take me in?
Your words
do make sense.
Let me think.
Indeed, we should
go by the book...
And get a certificate, right?
I knew it.
Get a certificate for Ya Ya.
Get what certificate for Ya Ya?
In my residential area,
there was a white puppy
with the name Ya Ya.
What certificate do you think?
Were you bitten by it before?
No...
Little girl, have you kept Luo Luo's drawing?
I kept it. Don't worry.
I've put it in the box.
Okay.
What secret are you talking about?
The secret that
you can't know about.
Grandma, you two have
secrets now?
Of course, there are secrets
between girls.
It's good that you have.
Okay, okay.
You two should make a move.
It's going to be
another three to four hours on the road.
Okay.
Grandma,
I'll come back every month
to visit you.
Okay.
Do your things first,
and come when you have time.
Grandma always welcomes you.
Don't worry, go. Go.
Go and stay with me
in Shanghai.
Grandma likes here, that it's quiet.
Grandma, we'll go back then.
We will come back
to visit you.
If you miss us,
just call us.
We'll come and pick you up.
Don't worry.
As long as you two are fine,
Grandma is happy.
Go, go.
Take care of yourself.
Call me if anything.
Okay.
Treat her well.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Go. Hurry and go.
Hurry and go back in.
Okay.
We'll go back now, Grandma.
Take care.
Hello, Lin?
Hello, Zuo.
There's something
I need to talk to you.
What? Tell me.
Ask Qin Qing out for me.
I want to meet her.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
What's the matter?
A serious matter.
I want to give Zhou Fang a surprise.
So I need to look for
her bestie,
her best friend
to seek advice and help.
Surprise?
You're putting some effort.
But let me tell you.
I know your relationship
is doing pretty good now
and you do treat her pretty well.
When my dad was sick,
you also helped out quite a bit.
I know you're
a loyal friend.
But that's not the same thing.
You hurt Zhou Fang before.
That's a fact.
Don't ever forget it.
If in the future,
there's any sign of disturbance
or cheating,
I'll have you know,
I will make a fuss.
Stop making a fuss.
There won't be any cheating.
As for disturbance,
we can use
a bit of that.
What do you want to do?
I want to marry her.
So, the surprise you mentioned is
you want to propose to her?
I want to marry her.
Will you be good to her forever?
Of course.
Say it. What do you want me to do?
[TKY Shop]
[Congratulations on TKY Shop's Opening]
[Open Ceremony of TKY Shop
for Haute Couture Experience]
Fu,
have you tidied up the workbench?
Customers will come in a bit.
Not yet.
It looks more realistic if messy.
It doesn't need to be realistic today.
Hurry and tidy it up.
Tang Jie, they've arrived.
Pick them at the entrance.
Okay. Don't worry.
Shao Kai.
Where's Miss Fang?
Miss Fang? Miss Fang is outside.
Okay, okay.
Yes, yes.
And uhm...
After the development of the new releases,
we will be here all the time.
Please go in to have a look.
Okay.
Okay. We'll go in first.
Sure.
Miss Fang,
it's ready inside.
Okay. Go in and take care of the others.
Okay.
Go.
You came just in time.
Your place is pretty good.
Not bad, right?
You have a good eye for location.
Mom, if you want to praise me,
praise me straightly.
Why are you so reserved?
If I praise you straight,
you might get arrogant.
I won't.
Are Song Lin and Wu San here?
They're inside.
What's up? Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
I'll bring Auntie
in then.
I'll bring your mom to meet
my Wu San.
Okay. Hurry and go.
-We'll go first.
-Have some wine.
Come over later.
Okay.
Welcome. Please go in.
President Su, Mrs Su.
Welcome.
Zhou Fang, congratulations.
Thank you, Mrs Su.
You look so beautiful today.
Thank you.
Let's go in.
Sure. Here. Please go in.
A lot of customers came today.
Everyone, welcome to
TKY Shop Experience Store.
We would like to invite
our beautiful President Zhou to give a speech.
I'm a bit nervous.
Thank you
for coming to our
experience store today.
As you can see,
this isn't a formal
opening ceremony.
It's just a small party.
I've invited the people that
I love the most,
that I'm closest to here
to take this opportunity
to tell everyone,
thank you so much
for supporting
and inspiring me
in my career and my life
for all this while.
Setting up an haute couture experience store
has always been my dream.
I am very honored
to witness it happening
with everyone here.
Now, I'd like to announce that
our experience store
is officially open.
Thank you, everyone.
This is my new office.
How is it? Not bad, right?
Pretty good.
You put the wardrobe I gifted you here.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
It must have cost quite a lot.
Your works are important.
The cost of it doesn't matter.
Thank you on behalf of
my works then.
You're drinking? Still drinking?
I'm in a bad mood.
What happened?
How is it going with your boyfriend?
My boyfriend and I
are doing good.
It's just that Ms Tian,
she still doesn't agree
that Wu San and I are together.
She still doesn't accept me.
Why?
I think maybe it's because
Ms Tian raised her son up
all on her own.
So, the love she has
towards her son
would be much stronger
compared with other mothers.
Much more special.
And Wu San
has been an obedient kid
ever since he was small.
Throughout this period,
being together with Wu San,
I know it well that
I want to be with him
forever.
I will never give up.
Of course, you can't give up.
You finally found someone
you're in love with.
Why should you give up?
Uhm...
Get your parents
to talk to her.
My mom
couldn't really accept Wu San either.
She felt that
he was younger than me.
Would he be reliable?
Would he be dependable?
But during this period,
she slowly accepted
Wu San.
As for my dad,
he just had surgery, just got out of the hospital.
A lot of things
happened at home.
At this timing,
I don't want to
make them worry.
So...
Don't be sad. Don't be sad.
Let's not give up.
It's hard to find someone
whom you like.
Both of you are in love.
Why should you give up?
Don't give up.
The thing is...
You know sometimes
I see Wu San
getting stuck between me and Ms Tian.
It's hard for him.
I feel sorry for him,
but I don't know
what to do.
I...
You...The Ms Tian that
you mentioned.
Which school is she from? No.1 Middle School?
No.1 Middle School?
Okay.
I'll go and find out.
You have a solution?
What solution can I have?
But
you have to trust me.
Trust Auntie.
You two are doing good.
Let's not give up.
Don't worry about this.
Let me... Let me think of a solution.
I'll think of a solution.
You saw Wu San just now.
What do you think?
Is he good?
Lin Lin, what time is it now?
Why are you still working?
Go to bed.
Mom.
I want to move back there tomorrow.
No.
Didn't I tell you?
I've been feeling unwell recently.
Leaving me alone
at home,
won't you be worried?
Mom, you haven't taken your medicine yet.
I'll get medicine for you.
[Message from Qin Qing]
Mom, are you feeling unwell?
It's okay.
How about we go and check
at the hospital?
It's okay.
It may get better after I take some medicine.
♪ The maple leaves are slowly falling
outside the window ♪
♪ But your smell still fills the air even now ♪
♪ Our faces were blushed in all of our photos ♪
♪ How many memories are behind that? ♪
♪ Gentle and tender times ♪
♪ If all the plots about love ♪
♪ Were not missed out ♪
♪ Washing out ♪
♪ All the passion that we had when we were young ♪
♪ If we had learned ♪
♪ Not to say 'I don't know' easily ♪
♪ If we are still in love, what's next? ♪
♪ The rain moistened the tree branches ♪
♪ Silently decorating the quiet streets ♪
♪ The night is filled with warm air
It's time to bid goodbye to the past ♪
♪ Sadness still fills the heart ♪
♪ Unable to make a final decision ♪
♪ I still remember the perfect painting
we had in mind ♪
♪ Included you and me ♪
♪ Unfulfilled ♪
♪ promises ended up in regrets ♪
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ The problem we were trying to solve ♪
♪ If we are still in love, what's next? ♪
♪ If you still love me ♪
♪ Please remember all the moments
we had together ♪
♪ There is no need to be envious of
the happiness of the others♪
♪ If you are reluctant as well ♪
♪ You don't have to be alone like me ♪
♪ You have loved with all your heart and soul ♪
♪ Just remember that true love was here before ♪
♪ If you still remember that
we were once deep in love ♪