♪ Out of the blue, the rhythm has started ♪
♪ Pulling all strings of emotions ♪
♪ Tear off the strikingly long hemline ♪
♪ The best arrangement has been set ♪
♪ So don't mess up on purpose ♪
♪ Who's always standing behind the tide of smiles ♪
♪ Suffering under the dark clouds ♪
♪ Luckily, still standing strong ♪
♪ Who is always in the winter of sadness ♪
♪ But is visited by the sunlight ♪
♪ Even icebergs would warm up and smile ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refused to throw away the words "so sad"? ♪
♪ The best arrangement ♪
♪ Bye, goodnight sunset ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refuse to look forward to a better future? ♪
♪ Baby, tell me why, why, why? ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪ The best arrangement, why... ♪
♪ Do you refuse to look forward to a better future? ♪
♪ Baby, tell me why, why, why? ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
[Love Designer]
[Episode 38]
I'm so tired.
Sit for a while.
I'll get you something.
This is Luo Luo's drawing book.
Don't forget to take it
when you go back later.
Okay.
I'm going to wash up.
What's wrong?
You called me to come here
in such a hurry.
Wu San.
I asked him out several times.
But he didn't come.
I have not seen him
for several days.
Have you asked him what happened?
He said he is busy at work.
He said his mother is sick.
Anyway, he has a lot of reasons.
Isn't because that
his mother is sick?
Stop bothering.
His mother is sick.
But he shouldn't
ignore my messages.
Furthermore,
I sent many gifts
to his mother.
All the gifts have been returned.
I have a feeling.
If this condition continues,
we're done.
Maybe Ms Tian
always keeps an eye on him.
So he can't find a chance
to see you.
No.
He is not a mummy's boy.
This is really my first time
to see you
becoming so restless and lost
because of a man.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I used to think that
he wouldn't leave me.
Because he loves me so much.
He will appear when I miss him.
When I feel annoyed after seeing him,
he will disappear obediently.
Now I'm really scared.
I'm scared that he will disappear
from my life.
Do not worry.
Wu San is not that kind of person.
He is very responsible.
I know that
he is not that kind of person.
But
I liked
Jiang Yan so much before.
I didn't act like this.
Do you think that
I am hopeless already?
Hopeless.
What to do?
Don't you just want to see Wu San?
That's very easy.
It's really not easy.
I really can't handle Ms Tian.
You can't do it alone.
Let me help you.
Tonight, I'll cook
your favourite
bean stew noodles for you.
Mom, let me do it.
Have a taste and see if
my cooking skill is better or Dad's.
Hello, President Song.
Hello, Zuo.
I'm going to deal with
an investment project now.
Come with me.
Please send me the address.
I'll go and meet you.
No need.
Send me your address.
I'll pick you up.
Ok, no problem.
What's wrong?
Mom.
The company suddenly
has an urgent matter
that I need to go to meet a client.
I can't accompany you
tonight for dinner.
Okay.
Go ahead, I'm fine.
Company matters are more important.
Okay, mom, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving, mom.
Lin.
Who are we going to meet today?
I need to get ready.
You need to get ready indeed.
Today, we are meeting
President Zhou and President Qin.
What do you mean?
I didn't expect it, Lin.
You will do this kind of thing?
Do you think I wish to do so?
Nice watch.
Looks good, right?
Previously, Qin Qing
went to Italy
with Miss Fang.
She bought it for me.
Did Miss Fang buy any gift
for you?
Yes, she did.
What did she buy for you?
It's none of your business.
So much nonsense.
I want to compare.
Compare?
Buy me a house. Compare then.
Sweetheart, sorry.
I should explain this matter
to you clearly.
Sorry for making you worried.
I'm fine.
It's not your fault.
You are not angry?
Why do I have to be angry?
I am the one being inconsiderate.
I am responsible to tell you
about this matter.
But don't worry.
I have figured out a good way
to talk to my mom.
But it takes time.
During this period,
I also did a self-reflection.
Why my mom is so against
towards our relationship?
Actually, I am
the main reason.
Because in my mom's eyes,
I must be
a child without judgement.
So she was so anxious
to decide for me.
I will prove to her
that I am not a child.
We did not act on impulse
about our relationship.
I will do my best
in my career
and be responsible for my relationship.
So that I can tell her
in an independent and equal position
as soon as possible...
that I want to be together with you.
It's a notice, not a request.
Was it fun in Italy?
Did you go out
for shopping?
Yes.
Did you buy anything
that you like?
Of course, I did.
What did you buy?
Clothes, bags,
shoes, jewelers, make-ups...
You bought so many things.
Did you have a look at
menswear or something else?
I didn't go shopping for menswear.
I only look for womenswear.
That's true.
Why did you look for menswear?
What's wrong with you?
What does your facial expression mean?
What facial expression?
Nothing, just chatting.
During this time, I have been thinking
how to prove myself
to my mom.
But I didn't provide you
with a sense of security.
I'm sorry.
Wu San.
Qin Qing.
You don't need to say anything.
I just want to tell you
regardless
of the situation now,
in my heart,
I, Zuo Yu Lin
have realized that
my life would not be complete
without Qin Qing.
Do not worry.
I will definitely work hard.
Blame on me.
I was so naughty when I was young
that makes you feel difficult now.
I blame myself for being so obedient
when I was young
that makes you feel so wronged.
Let me look at you.
I haven't seen you for these few days.
You are not eating well again.
You became thinner again.
Let me cook some good food for you.
Wu San.
Hug me again.
Okay.
Sweetheart.
Promise me to take good care of yourself.
I will.
Eat on time.
Sleep well, okay?
You too, eat well.
Enough.
I'm leaving now.
Be good.
After you go back,
listen to your mom.
Don't talk back to her.
If
she asks you to go on a blind date,
just go.
I know you keep me in your heart.
That's enough.
Do not worry about me.
Zuo.
What time is it?
9:30.
This watch is nice,
where can I buy it?
Italy.
Qin Qing bought it for you?
That's nice.
Aren't you going back?
I'm not going back.
I'll stay here tonight.
Okay.
You must...
I can't do it.
I'm leaving.
Then I'm leaving too.
Wu San.
Be good.
Goodbye.
Drive carefully.
Okay.
I've told you he cares
about that watch.
Yes, he is.
Lin.
Can you...
If you are going to let me
see you both being lovey-dovey again,
don't talk about it anymore.
Next time,
I will be only in charge of making phone calls.
Let Chen Chen save you.
Got it, Lin.
Young man.
So happy?
Of course, I'm happy.
I'm happy
to see my dear Wu San.
Song Lin asked me why
I didn't prepare a gift for him.
Why?
Didn't you buy him a gift?
You haven't given it to him?
I haven't done it yet.
What are you doing so hard?
I don't want to tell you.
I don't want to listen.
I want to find my dear Wu San.
Coming to the mall early in the morning,
what do you want to buy?
Are you going to
cook for me?
Recently I have been so busy every day,
working overtime every day.
It's been a long time
since I cooked for you.
Didn't last time you say
you want to eat crayfish?
I've learnt it online.
I'll cook for you tonight.
So good?
Okay.
Tonight, let's invite Ling Xi
to come over and eat together?
Why invite her
to come over for dinner?
Didn't you keep on saying that
you want to invite her for a meal?
But you still haven't invited her.
So this crayfish meal
is not just
for me.
No.
Back then, my company
was having a hard time,
we lost our capital fund and
the equity couldn't sell out,
But later Ling Xi
helped us
sell them out.
At that time, you said you wanted to
invite her for a meal.
But you haven't invited her until now.
I'm thinking that it will show our sincerity
if we have a meal together at home?
It's fine if you are unhappy about it.
Let's eat by ourselves, don't invite her.
Call her.
Or else I look stingy.
You're nice.
Hurry, give me the plate.
Coming.
Here.
Give you a piece.
Smells good.
Put on the plate.
Is it hot?
So hot.
Hot.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
Not bad.
What else do you wanna eat?
Let me cook it for you.
Big plate chicken.
I'll open the door.
You came.
It's my first time coming to your house,
I don't know what to bring.
I bought two bottles of red wine.
You are being too courteous.
It must taste good.
Come in.
Smells good.
Almost all dishes are ready.
Ling Xi is here.
Sit down, sit down, the dishes are ready.
Okay.
We prepared these for the whole morning.
Looks really sumptuous.
You see.
You rarely come for a visit.
How can I not prepare more dishes?
All the dishes are served?
All done.
Quickly have a bite.
Not bad.
Try it.
It's really delicious.
Let me tell you.
Today, Zhou Fang and I
have done nothing except cooking.
Thank you both for preparing these.
Come.
Come, welcome to my house.
I actually want
to thank Ling Xi.
If she didn't help me
sell ​​the shares
to gain some capital fund,
this house would be gone.
I didn't agree to
live with you.
When are you
going to agree then?
See how's your performance.
My performance?
I will do well.
It's really awkward for me
to watch you both being romantic.
It's okay, you have soup too.
How delicious.
Nice cooking skills.
Come.
Thank you both for your kind hospitality.
Then,
we all must
keep on working hard.
Cheers.
Work hard.
Come on.
Zhou Fang.
President Su.
Here is the thing.
We are preparing to launch
the application online in advance.
Can you give me
more designs?
Yes, I can.
But will this matter
affect Song Lin?
To be frank,
yes.
I know you are
Song Lin's girlfriend.
But since the day
you chose Wan Feng,
you're destined
to be his competitor.
In our field,
if you want to succeed, you must take the first place.
Otherwise, you will fail.
I will support you
and be confident to you
as always.
Su Yu Shan came to me today.
It's okay, don't worry.
Now
it is the important stage
where we both sides are competing.
We both should
avoid each other to some extent.
Is there anything I can help you?
You want to help me?
Let me think about it.
Work hard then.
Work hard to be
my most powerful opponent.
After all, I'll become
stronger when I meet a strong opponent.
I can't do anything about it.
But...
Don't say it anymore.
I'm so tired lately.
After some time,
It'll be more tiring when the new product launches.
But I feel better when I hug you.
Why?
Let's go home.
I don't dare to be absent from work now.
Go to your house or mine?
My house?
Let's go.
President Song.
Welcome home.
President Song, how is it?
Are you surprised?
Most of the Wan Feng's former employees
are back.
Thank you all for choosing me again
and willing to work with me.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Let me introduce her
to you all.
She is the new shareholder of our company
and the foreign agent
of our company.
Ling Xi, President Ling.
This time, thanks to President Ling's help.
Our company managed to
operate until today.
Hello, President Ling.
Hello, everyone.
I have been in the industry
for so many years.
I rarely make mistakes
on my insight.
I believe this time,
you all
won't disappoint me.
Don't worry, President Ling.
Our company
is just getting started
on the virtual haute-couture field,
but technically,
Zuo And Fei
has achieved a lot
before this.
So now,
you all just need to
work together with me in the future.
Are you confident?
Yes!
Let's work hard.
President Song.
Wan Feng's
application has been launched online today.
[Wan Feng Group 's online try-on
application is launched]
Su Yu Shan
has chosen a good day
to surprise us.
It's okay, do your work first.
You are drawing again.
Aren't you particularly busy?
Why are you still have time to come here?
I am here to send you a meal
upon someone's request.
Stop working, Miss Workaholic.
Eat something first.
Thanks for sending the food every day.
Did you receive a good order?
Apparently this diamond
is at least ten carats, right?
Five carats.
Can I open it and see?
Okay, be careful.
Okay.
It's very expensive.
You... It's very expensive, okay?
Looks good.
A tasteless rich man
wants to use it for a marriage proposal.
I guess he is very sincere.
He is very sincere indeed.
He has a good taste
that he knows to ask me to do design.
How could he be tasteless to
ask you to design?
He has very good taste.
If one day you get married,
will you ask me
to design your diamond ring?
Of course, I will.
Have you ever thought of
how your diamond ring
would look like?
I guess it would be something like this.
Do you think
this design needs
any modification?
I think it's perfect.
No need to modify.
If one day,
someone is holding this ring
and proposes to me,
I would say yes immediately.
What are you smiling?
I didn't.
You did.
What were you smiling at just now?
I'm hungry, let's eat.
Tell me, what were you smiling at?
I didn't.
The security system
must be monitored closely.
Understand.
Take a look over here.
Is everything okay?
It's fine, President Song.
After
the security system
has been upgraded,
there are no more loopholes.
Now the pressure is also the motivation,
understand?
We need to hold this breath.
We can't be sloppy
on the customer's privacy.
Okay.
After the internal test
within these two days,
we can launch it online for the beta test.
Continue your work.
Thank you all
for your hard work during this time.
I will reward you all
after some time.
Okay, thank you, President Song.
Hurry up.
[Chairman's office]
Don't worry.
Our application
will be launched online as soon as possible.
Okay, bye.
The investors are giving you pressure again?
I can handle them.
You
just need to focus
on your software now.
Leave everything else.
We have
lost the opportunity now.
Did you know
the key to our negotiation
in the U.S.?
Wasn't it because
you invested all the assets
in the project?
So
they agreed in the end.
The success of this company
does not depend
on you alone,
it depends on me too.
Why are you always
full of fighting spirit.
Have you ever...
had the moment...
the moment that you feel
really desperate?
Actually,
I have things that I wanted to achieve
but I couldn't make it.
But I understand that
I may not get it
forever.
By the way,
tonight, Su Yu Shan
invited us for dinner.
What does he want?
My gut tells me that
we have to attend tonight.
Anyway,
we must not show any weakness.
Zhou Fang.
President Su.
This time, you contributed a lot,
so we managed
to launch the application successfully in time
I would like to invite you for dinner tonight
as a celebration.
I have something to do tonight.
It's time to relax.
It's decided.
I will ask my assistant
to send you the restaurant address.
President Ling, President Song.
Come here, please come in.
Sorry, President Su,
for keeping you waiting.
We are brothers.
No worry.
We still need to be courteous.
What's the matter?
Just thought of
inviting you both for a meal
as a token of gratitude.
Today,
our application was launched online.
Thanks to
the solid foundation of Wan Feng
that had been built by President Song.
Of course.
Thanks to President Ling.
Your past evaluation
managed to provide us
with a large amount of funds.
You are too humble.
Wan Feng
can perform so well
under the leadership of President Su
who is such a capable person,
I'm actually very happy about it.
Wan Feng is a company
that I started by myself.
It's like my own son.
Here, have a drink.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Come, sit down.
You didn't tell me that
you have invited my girlfriend as well?
I didn't know you are coming either.
Hello, Ling Xi.
President Su
brought us all together
without notifying.
Is there anything you want to say?
I want to say that today
our Wan Feng application
managed to launch successfully,
all thanks to Zhou Fang's designs.
Because of her designs,
the number of registered users
is constantly soaring.
But at the same time,
your application
has turned into a counterfeit.
This is the point
that I would like to apologize for.
I don't need an apology.
In this industry,
we should be clear that
who launches it online first
can grab more opportunities in the market.
I can understand.
It's okay.
I know it too.
Your intention today is not just
to invite us for a meal.
The main purpose of President Su is
for me to congratulate you, right?
Then, congratulate you
for a successful launch.
I also hope that
your application can perform better
in the future.
Let's work hard.
Soorry,
I need to use the washroom.
I also want to go to the washroom.
Is this necessary?
Yes.
Are you okay?
What are you planning to do later?
Of course, we will not
give up so easily.
Song Lin and I
will do our best
to keep the company unaffected
and continue to operate.
Initially, I just wanted
do my job well.
I didn't expect to bring
any burden and pressure to you all.
I'm very sorry.
Of course, it is right for you
to do your job well.
But have you ever considered
Song Lin's feelings?
Yes, I am interested in Song Lin.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm going back first.
If there is nothing else,
I'm going to accompany my girlfriend.
I'm leaving now.
President Su.
You keep on fighting against us.
It's quite boring.
You launched the application online in advance
in order to seize the market.
But I think
the loopholes
in your application
have not been solved yet,
right?
This is not an appropriate attitude
that a smart manager
should have.
President Ling.
Thank you very much
for your reminder.
Today I also want to remind you that
it takes courage
for one to accept the reality
and acknowledge failure.
Maybe you will lose fewer,
if you stop fighting earlier.
Time can prove everything.
But I believe that
there is not much time left for you
to feel triumphant.
Of course, it is right
for you to do your job well.
But have you ever considered
Song Lin's feelings?
Yes.
I am interested in Song Rin.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you leave
without asking me?
What do you mean?
I felt uncomfortable.
About what?
Just now,
I actually understand
what Su Yu Shan said
just now.
But I couldn't help you.
As your girlfriend,
I have no way
to stand with you
and fight on the same battlefield
as Ling Xi does.
So I feel upset.
Why you feel upset?
What happened today?
What's wrong?
Because his software
launched online?
Actually I knew earlier that
the software
was going to be launched online.
But due to the ethical trading policy,
I couldn't tell you.
I sometimes feel myself
like an outsider.
I even have to
confront you.
Will you hate me?
Why would I hate you?
Although you are now
working for Su Yu Shan's company,
isn't that just your job?
You are still
my girlfriend.
Your job there
won't affect us
to fight together.
I used to think that
we can fight together side by side.
I thought we can
work hard and
gain success.
But now the business industry
is so competitive.
I did not expect
it would become a situation like this today.
Song Lin.
I'm really scared that
one day our distance
will get further and further.
I'm afraid we will
have nothing to say.
I'm afraid I can't catch you.
Don't think about it anymore, okay?
I have told you long ago,
no matter what happens
between us,
we will walk to the end together.
Right?
Didn't you agree too?
What do you mean now?
I can't be so sensible
like you.
I don't have the same
capability as Ling Xi's
to help you again and again
and provide you with capital funds.
I can't give you
any professional advice either.
Is she
more suitable for you than me?
Zhou Fang, let me tell you.
You are the best for me.
No one is more suitable for me
than you.
And I won't give
any chance to anyone either.
Okay?
Do you remember?
Don't cry.
Qing, you are here.
Yes, I am.
You are here.
I know you need me.
So I'm here.
I know you are in a bad mood.
Talk to me.
I think
I feel sorry for him
on this software incident.
You feel sorry for him?
What did you do wrong?
You are just working hard
for your career.
What did you do wrong?
I just don't want to be
his competitor.
I don't want to be like this.
What's wrong
if you are his competitor?
Comrade Zhou Fang.
Can I beg you
to separate your love relationship
from your career?
Can you not always think
for other people?
Why it is so tough
to be in a relationship?
It is too difficult.
Why is it
so difficult?
I'm still comforting you,
while I haven't settled
my own problem yet.
Ms Tian
doesn't accept me at all.
Where are you going?
This is the dress I made for Ms Tian
according to her body shape
in the photo.
I don't know if the size fits her.
You send this to her.
Bring it back
if there is any problem after trying on.
I will modify it for you.
When the time comes,
you send her
one of your accessories.
So that she can see
your capability.
Let her know
you are no longer the rebellious girl
during your high school,
but a capable and reliable
jewelry designer.
Here.
Dear.
Why do you always
treat me so well?
Feel like a mother.
Qin Qing.
The gifts are already prepared for you.
Can't you just come over by yourself?
Why bring me over?
I'm so busy.
Zhou Fang.
I feel more secure
if you are here.
Besides, you are already here.
Why are you still nagging?
Where is it?
Right there.
Please come in.
Ms Tian.
Why are you here?
I...
Hello.
Ms Tian,
it's been a long time
since my graduation.
I'm just here to visit you.
Just be frank.
Don't beat around the bush.
Ms Tian.
Hello.
I am Zhou Fang,
a friend of Zuo Yu Lin and
Qin Qing.
Qin Qing wanted to visit you
since a long time ago.
She is not sure what gift
we should give to you.
This is a dress
that is designed by me.
This is a fine jewelry
that is designed by Qin Qing.
We hope you will like it.
They are too expensive.
I can't accept them.
They are not expensive.
This is a small token of gratitude from us.
Thank you.
But I can never accept
these.
It's better for you to bring back
and give it to your elders.
You are my elder.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to see me.
You graduated almost ten years ago.
As a teacher,
I have more
anticipation and blessings for you.
I hope you can have a better life,
and you can find
your happiness as soon as possible.
However,
our Lin Lin
is definitely not your destiny.
I'm sorry.
Drink slowly.
What problem
can alcohol solve?
Then tell me
how I can solve it.
I want to get drunk now.
I want to forget
how shameful I was just now.
Were you ashamed just now?
I don't think so.
It was not shameful at all, okay?
I
always feel
quite confident in myself.
But today,
just now,
I feel like I am
worthless.
Like a fly,
I was disgusted by others.
Can you stop thinking
so much?
I don't even
think it
so embarrassing.
Maybe she has already
forgotten about it.
You are the one who is thinking about it.
It's okay if she despises me.
But she treated you
in a rude way too.
I don't think
she was being rude to me.
Let me tell you.
This is the first time
we have made efforts.
At least, Ms Tian
had a new perspective about you.
And she also saw
your work already, right?
That doesn't count.
She wouldn't
look at it properly.
In her eyes,
I used to be a bad student,
and now I'm a bad woman.
Forget about it.
Forget about what?
What do you mean?
I want to give up.
What are you giving up?
Let me ask you.
If now
Wu San is the one sitting opposite to you,
what do you think he will do?
He will work on it
without hesitation.
You taught me before
about men
and women.
Today, it is my turn
to give you a lecture.
Drink this first.
Before this, you always said that
you always had
bad luck in your relationships,
and met some unreliable men.
Why was it so?
Because when you meet a problem,
you never try to solve it.
The problem will always be there
once you don't solve it.
I even said that others are not reliable.
I think I am pretty
unreliable too.
Who said you are not reliable?
You tell me, I'll go beat him up.
I think you are reliable.
And you are becoming more and more reliable.
Tell me.
Before you met Ms Tian,
you and Wu San
quarreled every day,
always had a fight for nothing.
Now,
you both are so overwhelmed
by love.
What does this mean?
This means that
impediment leads to motivation.
Only when there is a challenge,
there is a breakthrough.
Right?
You should thank
Ms Tian.
You both are so in love with each other.
I can't even believe it
if I didn't witness the situation that day.
You can become like that,
Qin Qing?
You are quite persuasive.
Don't just give up so easily.
She hasn't really given you a challenge.
You are going to give up already.
This is unfair to Wu San.
I believe we will
find the breakthrough of Ms Tian.
Do you believe it?
I believe it if you are with me.
I am always with you.
♪ The maple leaves are slowly falling
outside the window ♪
♪ But your smell still fills the air even now ♪
♪ Our faces were blushed in all of our photos ♪
♪ How many memories are behind that? ♪
♪ Gentle and tender times ♪
♪ If all the plots about love ♪
♪ Were not missed out ♪
♪ Washing out ♪
♪ All the passion that we had when we were young ♪
♪ If we had learned ♪
♪ Not to say 'I don't know' easily ♪
♪ If we are still in love, what's next? ♪
♪ The rain moistened the tree branches ♪
♪ Silently decorating the quiet streets ♪
♪ The night is filled with warm air
It's time to bid goodbye to the past ♪
♪ Sadness still fills the heart ♪
♪ Unable to make a final decision ♪
♪ I still remember the perfect painting
we had in mind ♪
♪ Included you and me ♪
♪ Unfulfilled ♪
♪ promises ended up in regrets ♪
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ The problem we were trying to solve ♪
♪ If we are still in love, what's next? ♪
♪ If you still love me ♪
♪ Please remember all the moments
we had together ♪
♪ There is no need to be envious of
the happiness of the others♪
♪ If you are reluctant as well ♪
♪ You don't have to be alone like me ♪
♪ You have loved with
all your heart and soul ♪
♪ Just remember that true love was here before ♪
♪ If you still remember that
we were once deep in love ♪