It's him.
Yes, it's him.
He's the one who poisoned Princess Liuyun.
Wenwen.
Lu Yiwen.
Lu Yiwen, stop right there!
You're still not well. Go back quickly.
I can't let you go.
I'm the one who hurt you.
I don't deserve to see you.
No.
I don't believe you poisoned her.
Brother, please help.
Thank you, please help.
Tell me.
What exactly happened?
My original intention was to poison Princess Liuyun.
I don't know why you were the one poisoned.
Jinjin.
Don't trust anyone.
The symptoms of Princess Liuyun's poisoning
are not caused by Night Camellia at all.
But...
Her medical report
shows all signs
that she was poisoned by Night Camellia.
Night Camellia dissolves in wine, colorless and tasteless.
Those poisoned by it
seem normal for the first few days.
But gradually, symptoms of weakness appear.
Like suddenly falling unconscious.
If there's no antidote,
they'll die from the poison in just a few days.
The dangerous thing about this poison is
that on the victim's body
there's no way to find any trace of poisoning.
I only put the poison in Princess Liuyun's wine flask.
That's where I used the poison.
This is also why, after the incident, the royal physician confirmed that Princess Liuyun
was poisoned with Night Camellia.
But
after Princess Liuyun was poisoned,
she has been in a coma ever since.
But instead, it was me
who seemed to match
all the symptoms of Night Camellia poisoning.
So you mean
I suspect someone switched the wine cups.
Switched the cups?
Then who poisoned Princess Liuyun?
What kind of poison was she given?
Are you done talking?
Hurry up, let's go.
Wenwen
Jinjin
Actually,
you've always known how I feel.
Ever since we were young,
as long as it's something you want to do,
I'm always willing to be by your side.
But all you ever wanted was to become the City Lord's wife.
If you're happy,
then I'm happy too.
Wenwen
Take care of yourself.
Wenwen, don't go! Wenwen!
Are you okay?
I just didn't expect things to turn out like this.
Liking someone
does it really mean you have to do something like this?
There's nothing wrong with liking someone.
But you have to take responsibility for your actions.
I really can't bear to let him go.
This isn't like you at all.
I want to tell you,
since it's all over now,
you should look forward.
No, it's not over yet.
There are still doubts about how Liuyun was poisoned.
I have to figure it out.
How did Liuyun get poisoned?
First of all,
I have to stay at the City Lord's residence.
and look for opportunities to investigate clues about Liuyun's poisoning.
Let's talk as we walk.
Let's go.
City Lord
Now I can finally prove I'm not the real culprit, right?
You misunderstood me all this time.
You realize you were wrong, don't you?
Since you know you were wrong,
shouldn't you do something to make it up to me?
I was wrong.
I should even reward you.
Yes, yes, yes.
I really should reward you properly.
For us,
make a pot of tea.
This is the highest honor.
Me, make tea?
Aren't you supposed to invite me to the City Lord's mansion to have fun?
Shouldn't you let me stay for a few days?
Why are you making me make tea?
No way.
Weren't you the one insisting
on becoming the City Lord's wife?
Being the City Lord's wife means doing these things.
Why is this Murong Chengfeng acting so weird?
Fine.
For the sake of the investigation, I'll put up with it.
It's too hot.
Let's see what excuse you have now.
Make another pot.
It's too cold.
You blockhead, help me!
Good tea.
I want to eat fruit.
Feed me.
Feed Li Sijun.
City Lord.
I remember you love bananas the most.
Eat.
Massage
Lord
I think
Why don't we go paint instead?
But I heard
Miss Lin
music, chess, calligraphy, and painting
can't do any of them
Who says I can't?
I—I can
anime-style ink painting
Showcase
How is it?
Interesting, right?
Very interesting, very interesting
I think
It's missing a stroke here
Lord
I think
We should play chess instead
Sure, sure
Do you know how, Miss?
I do
I can
Gomoku
Lian'er
Did you deliver the letter to my father?
Don't worry, Miss. Master already knows.
Now I finally understand
Being the Lord's wife is really not easy
You have to know music, chess, calligraphy, and painting
And you have to take good care of the Lord
It's even harder than being a housewife
Isn't that Yingxue?
Why is she sneaking around?
Lian'er, you go back to the other courtyard first
I still have important things to do
Yes, Miss
This Miss Lin is quite interesting.
She’s given us brothers something new to enjoy.
Interesting, yes,
but she’s a crazy girl.
Look at that smile of yours.
Don’t tell me you’re interested in her.
Me, interested in her?
Nonsense.
You’d better be honest.
Any woman I set my sights on
I won’t let anyone else have her.
You—
You like her?
Her?
How could that be?
She’s malicious and has a terrible reputation,
not to mention she’s uneducated.
She’s disrespectful to her elders.
Aside from being interesting, she has no redeeming qualities.
Looks like her dream of becoming the lord’s wife
is as good as shattered.
But,
she’s been behaving quite well lately.
But the position of the lord’s wife is a serious matter.
I’ll consider it carefully.
Think it over.
Xiao Li,
look,
you can’t beat me.
Go call Miss Lin over here.
I want to have a proper match with her.
When did you get four?
What are you doing?
You scared me to death.
Look at Yingxue over there.
Why is she being so sneaky just dumping out some medicine dregs?
You suspect her?
Yes, I suspect her.
Let’s go.
As expected.
Isn't this the antidote, Qianjinzi, used to treat Ye Haitang?
Qianjin, Qianjin.
Come here, come here.
This game of Gomoku you taught me
is simply fascinating.
What other fun things do you know?
Show them all to me.
If I’m pleased, I’ll reward you handsomely.
What I’m best at is making incense.
Making incense?
City Lord,
lately, for the sachets I’m making,
I’m missing a special ingredient.
But this ingredient
can only be bought at Shibali Shop.
So,
I’d like to go out for a bit.
Don’t worry, City Lord.
The sachet I make
definitely won’t disappoint you.
It’s even more interesting than the ink wash paintings of the second dimension school.
That’s much more interesting.
Alright.
However,
I'm still a bit worried.
I'm sure Minister Lin
also wouldn't feel comfortable letting you go out alone.
After all, our relationship with Northern Yue
is still a bit tense right now.
How about I send a few
guards to accompany you?
They can ensure your safety.
Why go to so much trouble?
I think it would be better
to just have Li Yan go with me.
Why does it have to be Li Yan who goes with you?
Who else could go
that would be safer than the commander by the city lord's side?
Isn't that right?
Besides, hasn't the city lord always assigned him
to protect me during investigations?
I think he's done a good job protecting me.
Alright, then let Li Yan go with you.
Yes, city lord.
How strange.
Of all the medicines seen by the city's doctors,
I doubt any have seen more than I have.
But these medicine dregs
I can't tell what kind of medicine they are by the smell.
May I ask, this medicine
what illness was it originally meant to treat?
Well,
I have an older brother who is infertile.
I don't know where to find a remedy for this.
As for me,
I'm worried he might upset his stomach.
So I wanted to ask someone knowledgeable.
So, you see,
Last time,
your husband came here
and got you some Danggui Yimuwan.
That means
your periods are irregular.
When it comes to fertility,
there must be some issues.
I know, madam,
you must be embarrassed.
About these matters,
it's hard to talk about them.
But let me tell you,
this is for your infertility.
I
Your brother, your brother
For your brother's infertility
it doesn't help at all.
If that's the case,
let's find someone more capable.
Let's go.
Why look for someone else?
Why not ask me instead?
Please wait, both of you, wait!
Wait!
Last time,
the fertility medicine I recommended to you
you didn't take it.
You two seem like a loving couple.
This time,
I'll give you a couple's incense pill for free.
Here, take it.
Take it.
At night,
put it in your tent as incense.
The effect is immediate.
It will let you
have a child right away.
Who said we want a child?