If you really think
Miss Lin is innocent,
then hurry up and show the evidence.
Give everyone an explanation, understand?
Come.
Alright.
I will do my utmost
to find the real culprit
and give everyone an explanation.
Also, to clear Miss Lin's name
and prove her innocence.
After our investigation,
the mastermind behind poisoning Princess Liuyun
is Miss Lin.
The city lord has already ordered
that Miss Lin
be executed immediately.
It wasn't me!
I'm glad you're alright.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
You...
You, you should take good care of your health.
You shouldn't have come so late.
I have something urgent.
What is it?
I really can't do this without you.
If you're not here,
the case can't go on.
So I need you.
All the evidence now
points to Changle.
Back at Shibali Inn that day,
she was already acting suspicious.
Later, at the lantern festival,
her reactions were strange as well.
Especially when I asked about Ye Haitang,
she refused to say anything.
And she reacted very strongly.
Tell me,
do you think she's deliberately avoiding
our questions?
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
I...
Lately,
have you had any more fainting spells like last time?
No.
It only happened twice.
Then...
Have you
eaten anything unusual recently?
Any strange food?
Or maybe caught a chill
because of the cold weather?
No.
None at all.
Look,
it's not hot at all.
What's really wrong with you?
I...
You're dressed too lightly.
You've just recovered from a serious illness.
It's quite cold outside.
Take my cloak.
You care about me.
If you really care about me,
then do me a favor.
What favor?
I need to go to the City Lord's residence.
To investigate Ye Haitang.
You want to investigate Ye Haitang at the place where Changle lives?
Then I have no other choice.
You were lucky last time.
But it won't be like that every time.
I won't let you go.
You care about me.
No matter what,
I still won't let you go.
If you care about me,
then you should help me clear my name even more.
That's twisting words.
I have to get to the bottom of this quickly.
Otherwise,
the City Lord will keep misunderstanding me.
I...
I can stall for you for at most half an hour.
Great!
I knew you wouldn't just stand by and do nothing.
Good brother, I'm off then.
Wait a second.
Go ahead.
Xiang'er.
Help me think about it, will you?
How can I arrange to meet Brother Li Yan again?
Xiang'er thinks
Why doesn't the Princess have the City Lord give the order
Would Li Sijun dare to disobey then
What do you know
I want Brother Li Yan to fall in love with me on his own
Not because of some order
When it comes down to it
Isn't it all because at the Lantern Festival
Miss Lin interrupted halfway
If she hadn't tried to seduce
Brother Li Yan
Maybe he would have already fallen deeply for me
I knew Brother Li Yan had feelings for me
Brother Li Yan
Princess
Xiang'er just washed some fresh grapes
They're sweet and juicy, perfect for cooling off
Come sit and try some
Princess, this...
Sit down
Princess
The City Lord has been busy with official duties lately
He specially ordered me to bring
the luminous pearl from Northern Yue's tribute
as a gift for the Princess to enjoy
On such a sunny day
Of course, it should be accompanied by flowers and music
Brother Li Yan
Would you like to enjoy a song with Changle
To enjoy it with the Princess
is my honor
Where exactly is the night-blooming begonia hidden
Brother Li Yan, do you think it sounds nice?
Brother Li Yan.
This music is beautiful.
It brings back many wonderful memories.
I recently bought a lot of fresh spices.
I’d like to invite you to take a look with me, Brother Li Yan.
Princess.
This...
The whole garden is filled with fragrance.
Of course,
the natural scent is even richer.
I will accompany the Princess myself.
Alright.
Then...
Let’s enjoy this natural fragrance together.
Who’s in there?
Brother Li Yan.
Can you come and enjoy the flowers with me more often from now on?
Look at that lotus.
Stop!
Reporting to the Princess.
This assassin broke into your bedchamber.
Seize the audacious assassin!
Yes!
Brother Li Yan
Are you alright?
You're bleeding.
It's nothing.
You audacious thief!
How dare you trespass into the princess's bedroom!
Princess
I must take her to the Inspectorate now.
Xiang'er
Take good care of the princess.
Brother Li Yan, be careful.
Princess
Come with me.
Is your hand alright?
I'm fine.
What about Ye Haitang?
Staying alive is the priority now.
Hurry, go!
Wait!
Miss Lin
Why is it you?
You really are unbelievably bold.
You actually dared to barge into my bedchamber.
Do you think the City Lord's residence is your own home?
Sister-in-law,
don't be angry.
It will be my home in the future.
And right now, it's basically my home too.
Sister-in-law, don't you consider me family?
You really are shameless.
My brother hasn't even looked at you properly.
And you still dare to call yourself his wife.
Guards, seize her!
The City Lord has arrived!
Greetings, City Lord.
City Lord.
What is going on here?
What has happened?
Brother,
Miss Lin entered the City Lord's residence without being summoned.
She even sneaked into my bedroom—an unforgivable offense.
Miss Lin,
it's you again.
City Lord,
um,
here's what happened.
Lately, I've been obsessed with making incense.
And I heard that Princess Changle here
has a very special spice.
So I came over out of curiosity to take a look.
I can vouch for that.
Miss Lin is quite knowledgeable
when it comes to making incense.
So I—
Did I give you permission to speak?
I deserve punishment.
Brother,
weren't you going to punish Miss Lin?
Why are you blaming Brother Li Yan instead?
Miss Lin
You have no respect for rules and act recklessly.
You are to copy "Lessons for Women" as punishment.
One hundred times.
You can't go home until you've finished copying.
Li Yan will supervise.
Why am I so unlucky?
It was strange enough to end up inside an ancient book,
and now I have to copy this "Lessons for Women"?
I'm so hungry.
I really want to go home.
And eat my mom's braised chicken drumsticks.
Are you hungry?
It's delicious.
Those two siblings from the Murong family,
they're really too much.
They must know
I hate these wordy, old-fashioned things the most.
That's why they made me copy "Lessons for Women".
So many times, too.
Give me your hand.
I mean, give me your hand.
You want to...
You want to eat my hand?