If I'm not mistaken,
that day at Shenlong Temple,
and the assassins sent from Lover's Valley,
were arranged by you, weren't they?
That's even more baseless.
I've never harmed Miss Lin.
Nor have I ever sent anyone to kill you.
I was unconscious for a while recently.
The court physicians can all testify to that.
Besides,
when I woke up later,
I heard that Miss Lin had suffered so much.
I was heartbroken too.
Oh?
Is that so?
Princess Liuyun,
when you lie,
your tears just won't stop.
And you don't even blush or flinch.
Fine, I admire you.
Guards!
Bring the person in.
Yes.
Yingxue!
You...
Commander Li,
what crime has Yingxue committed?
Why are you treating her like this?
Princess Liuyun,
what crime has Yingxue committed?
I'm afraid you know better than I do.
Li Sijun
Li Yan
You usually seem so dull.
I didn't expect
you to be so cunning.
Yes, you're right.
Poisoning,
the Lovers' Valley assassination,
Shenlong Temple—
I arranged all of it.
But so what?
Lin Qianjin has already been beheaded.
As long as you die too,
no one will know I did all this.
Princess Liuyun
What is this?
Do you think your tricks are clever?
Li Yan
Already revealed the truth
to me.
Back at Lovers' Valley,
I had already sent a message to the Lord
that you were the mastermind behind all of this.
We did this
just to make you lower your guard,
to make you think Miss Lin was sure to die,
so you would feel safe hiding the poison,
and finally reveal your true colors.
Lord
I was momentarily blinded by greed, my Lord.
Seeing how well you treated Miss Lin,
I was afraid,
I was afraid she would really take you away from me.
That's why I did this, my Lord.
This is not an excuse for you to stir up trouble
or frame others for murder.
Lord of Northern Yue
wants an explanation from us, doesn't he?
Go back and give him a proper explanation.
Guards!
Take Liuyun
and escort her back to Northern Yue.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, with Miss Lin buried with me,
it's worth it for me.
Weren't you dead?
Oh, right.
I forgot to tell you.
Chief Lin
and the evidence of colluding with Northern Yue
as well as the prison break by the man in black
were all orchestrated by the city lord.
Miss Lin and Chief Lin
were acquitted and released long ago.
Fine.
You all set me up.
Do you think this means you've beaten me?
Just wait and see.
Who is it?
Miss.
It's me.
Go away.
I don't want to see you.
Aren't you annoying?
I said I don't want to see you.
Even if you break down the door,
I still won't see you.
Li Yan.
You really left.
Who told you to leave?
Miss.
I didn't leave.
I was just afraid you'd be angry.
And it would harm your health.
I'll always be here with you.
Miss.
You saw it in the main hall too.
If Liu Yun hadn't walked right into our trap,
we really wouldn't have been able to do anything to her.
We set up this plan
just to let you and your father
suffer grievances for Liu Yun to see.
But I couldn't tell you.
You know, every time I see you suffer,
my heart
feels like it's being cut by knives.
Take off her shoes.
Hit her! Beat her to death!
Beat her to death!
Commander Li.
As you ordered,
all the eggs and vegetables on the street
have been bought and brought back.
But what should we do with all these eggs and vegetables?
I smashed several times and still don't feel better.
Exactly, it doesn't help.
If anything happens to Miss Lin,
I'll hold you all responsible.
Yes.
But you came here,
yet you still didn't save me.
You even locked me in that
room full of rats.
I...
I was so scared, so hopeless.
Do you know that?
I couldn't even get enough to eat.
I've gotten so thin from hunger.
I'm telling you,
the most hateful thing is,
you even came to the cell
to say those hurtful things to me.
Do you know how heartbroken I was, crying by myself?
Tell me clearly,
did you see me getting hit by others,
and you didn't feel sorry for me at all?
Those eggs and vegetables, I...
Don't talk about that.
It would have been better if you hadn't brought this up.
Now that you mention it, I'm even angrier.
See for yourself.
Other guys
all do romantic things
for the people they like.
But you,
you just bought eggs and vegetables.
When they ran out of things to throw,
they all started throwing shoes at me.
Do you know how much that hurt?
I know.
You weren't the one getting hit.
Of course you don't understand.
Don't be upset—
Don't be upset, right?
That's easy for you to say.
Let me tell you,
don't think that just because you cleared my name
you can make up for everything.
All those hurtful things you said,
I remember them perfectly.
I didn't.
You didn't?
I'm telling you,
it's over between us.
I never want to see you again.
From now on,
we're cutting all ties.
We're done for good.
Since Liu Yun was escorted back to Northern Yue,
Northern Yue has assembled an army of one hundred thousand.
They have invaded our borders.
What are your thoughts on this?
These Northern Yue scoundrels...
I originally planned to have the Grand General
lead two hundred thousand elite soldiers
to resist them.
But I hope the city lord will reconsider.
As the saying goes, "Before the troops move, provisions must come first."
But this year, there is a plague in the city.
The state treasury is lacking funds.
If we want to ensure supplies for the front lines,
we will inevitably have to increase taxes.
But with the plague this year,
how can we
ask the people to pay these taxes?
What you mentioned
is exactly what troubles me.
Actually, I have an idea.
In Lover's Valley,
the great physician once mentioned
the little yellow flower from the story
can dispel wind-heat and clear toxins.
If we combine it with other medicines into a powder,
and put it into the wells, it can quickly cure the plague.
Have you heard?
The young lady of the Lin family solved this plague.
Who would have thought this little poison girl
would do such a good deed?
We really should thank her.
The plague is over!
It's over!
Miss, you are truly amazing.
The plague that affected everyone in the city
was cured by you.
It was nothing.
Today is truly, since the plague began,
the most lively day in Nanling City.
I heard the city lord praised the event you organized,
the charity sale to raise funds and donate provisions to the army,
and couldn't stop complimenting it.
Fresh juice! Come and try some!
It's been so long since we've seen
such a lively scene.
It's already dark,
but everyone in the city
is still out setting up stalls and selling goods.
All to raise provisions for Nanling.
Miss, you really are incredible.
When I step in,
success is only natural.
But Miss,
we're currently at the bottom
of the rankings.
What?
Hurry, hurry, get the goods to them quickly!
The top salesperson is about to start selling.
Everyone, come and take a look!
These are sachets I made myself.
And scented balm and powder.
If you take these home,
you'll give off a charming fragrance.
Most importantly,
every penny you spend
will go to support the front lines.
To the soldiers fighting bravely.
If you're interested, take action!
That's right.
These sachets,
they must be poisoned.
I think we shouldn't buy them.
Boss.
I'd like to buy a scented lip rouge.
Why are you here?
I want to buy a gift for someone I love.
Which one do you think would suit her?
Then may I ask, sir,
your beloved,
what color does she like?
I think...
it should be red.
Red.
We have three kinds of red here.
They are classic peach red, rose red,
and death Barbie pink.
May I ask,
your beloved,
which shade of red does she like?
If you get it wrong,
you're doomed.
You...
What's the difference between them?
This is true peach pink.
This is rose red.
No, I mean this one.
This is death Barbie pink.
Then, that must be the last one.
You blockhead.
You're dead today.
Isn't this Li Sijun?
Why are you buying things for girls too?
Why don't we look around some more?
Li Sijun is really gentle and considerate.
Everyone,
Qianjin Shop mainly sells spices and sachets.
And all kinds of fragrant items.
Come and have a look, everyone.
They're very suitable.
Recommended by Li Sijun.
Then there’s definitely no problem.
I want one of these. I want one. Me too!
We have them all, we have them all.
Don't push.
Don't rush, don't rush.
We have everything, we have everything.
Don't push me.
Give me two of these.
I want this one too.
Thank you.
This is yours.
Alright.
So there were influencers selling products even in ancient times.
Fan economy.
Miss, what did you say?
I mean,
maybe
we should change our marketing strategy.
Oh my god
This fragrance is just so enchanting
The magical violet
blended with the aroma of Feizixiao lychee
makes you feel as if you are
standing on the Bai Causeway by West Lake
encountering
a romantic and mysterious love
All the ladies
you absolutely have to buy this
Buy it
Wear it
Your special someone
will fall in love with you instantly
If you don't believe me
we can ask Lord Sijun
Lord Sijun
after smelling this scent
how do you feel
I have a kind of
feeling of being in love
A feeling of being in love, did you hear that
Li Sijun said he feels like he's in love
So what are you waiting for
This product
is limited to 300 pieces today
Ladies
you must get it
Only 300 available
Raise your hand to show interest
First come, first served
Come on, are you ready
Three
Two
One