- What's that, San Andres?
- Brian Ricafort sells porn!
Hello, gorgeous!
Fuck you!
Brian! Stop it!
Paco? Why are you going
to the Guidance office?
Hello?
Excuse me?
Oh, Erica. Do you need me?
I was just looking for Paco.
I think he's in your office.
Ahh, I see.
It's probably an anxiety attack.
Did he tell you anything about me?
I'm worried I'm being too clingy with him.
I can't say anything, sorry.
But I think it might be the
pressure from the parade?
Maybe he doesn’t like my samgyupsal idea?
You know what,
let me check on him.
Paco: I miss you, Mrs. H. Quickie
before the parade, please.
Mr. Ragos, Mrs. Holly, please come
to the grounds. Brian started a fist fight.
Erica, attend to Paco first, okay?
There's some commotion at the parade.
Commotion?
Brian's caught in a fist fight.
I have to go.
Okay Mrs. Holly!
Erica!
What are you doing here?
Paco? Are you okay?
Why are you getting naked?
Are you sick? This isn't the clinic.
Ah, uhm…
It's just so hot!
Are you having an anxiety attack?
Mrs. Holly said--
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Is it because of me, Paco?
- Sorry, Paco…
- No! No, it's because of the…
- ….universe!
- Huh?
Because of all the wars.
Wars?
Yes.
What's up with all that,
you know, world peace?
We're busy with this
parade like everything's fine
while there are wars out there.
I have no idea what the
hell you're talking about
sometimes but since I like you…
Yes! Yes to world peace.
Amen!
Sorry for walking out
on you like that before.
- It's nothing! Come on, it's okay.
- Let's get back to the parade.
No, we can stay.
It's cancelled 'cause Brian
punched somebody.
Oh, shit.
Is there kimchi on my face?
What was that for?
Uhm, sorry for leaving you.
I hope that makes up for it.
Wow, since when?
What do you mean 'since when'?
I mean, what are you?
Lesbian? Bisexual?
Bicurious? Gender-fluid?
I don't know.
I just follow what I like?
Am I your first?
Oh, shit!
Why?
I've never heard that one before.
Interesting!
Thanks, I guess.
I didn't know you were into these things.
I just got carried away by
the moment and costumes.
Uhm, but can we keep
this a secret for now?
Sure. I don't kiss and tell.
Okay. Deal.
Tell him!
What do you want me to tell him?
Confess to what you did! You fucker!
Mr. Ricafort,
watch your language.
- That's right!
- Sorry, sir.
I'm the one who leaked your videos.
Besides, sir, I'm an
advocate of the pride org.
I support all gay men.
Especially the bisexual haters like you.
What did you say?
Sir!
Get away from her.
Get away.
Do you see how violent he can get, sir?
Okay, okay.
You know what, this is a case
of a 'she said, he said' situation.
Amber claims to be innocent.
And you, Ricafort, why do
you keep pinning this on her?
Because he's the only one
who's got a beef with me!
Wow! With that attitude? I'm pretty
sure you've pissed off quite a few people.
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
I'll give both of you…
disciplinary action!
You'll provide community service.
Sir, why do I have to do it?
I'm the one who got
punched! It freaking hurts!
Sir, aren't I the victim here?
Those were my nudes that got leaked.
I mean I look good but still!
Whoa! "I look good."
You're not gonna quit?
My decision is final.
That was a quick decision, sir!
Naturally! I am the principal.
Besides, you should
be jerking each other off!
- Huh?
I meant you should support each other
because you belong to the same community.
Ah, wait, sir.
- I'm gay.
- I know!
But I don't wanna associate with them!
I don't like those kinds of gays!
You think we like you? Hello!
We just didn't have a choice.
Hold your horses.
I'm not referring to the rainbow community.
I'm referring to the Vanguard community.
What you two should be doing, you
should love and respect each other.
You should try it once!
Love and respect each other.
Try it!
Brian?
Brian!
Ma.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Is it true?
You're selling your nudes online?
Mom, please.
I mean, it's a job option for some people.
They're earning a pretty penny from that.
But son, I don't think I'm
ready to let you do that.
Especially at your age.
Are you doing this for the volleyball camp?
I just didn't wanna bother you or Dad.
You have your own problems.
I don't wanna add to your worries.
Stop this, Brian. Okay?
If you're really set on
joining that camp, then okay.
I'll figure something out.
I don't know how yet,
but I'll think of something, okay?
One more.
I don't want to.
I'm done!
- No more!
- One more round, Bullet!
- One more, Bullet!
Bullet, come on! Let's do it again!
Where the hell are you going?
Father God, according to
John 1 Chapter 1 Verse 9,
You are just and forgiving
as long as we admit to our sins, right?
Lord, here I am, confessing my sins.
I sinned, Father.
Father God, I gave in to temptation.
But Lord, is it really wrong?
because it feels so good!
Joanna, come back to us!
Lord Almighty!
Forgive me, Lord.
Honey, can you check
these flyers I made?
We're gonna give them out tomorrow.
Okay, Mom.
Oh, wait, did I disturb you?
No, I was just praying.
Are you done then?
Yes, I'm done.
All right then goodnight.
Good night, mom.
Mom, here's fine! You don't need to
take me to class, it's embarrassing!
Yeah, yeah, okay. Don't forget,
I'll only be gone two weeks.
It's just in Cebu.
Behave well at Granny's, okay?
Yes, mom.
Want me to bring home anything for you?
How about some rabbitfish?
They sell them fresh over there.
I don't want any.
I'm really sorry, honey.
What can we do, your
dad's as ugly as his manners.
It's supposed to be his
turn to look after you!
But he's got somewhere else to be!
Sorry!
It's okay, mom. Granny and I
will spend some quality time.
I have such a good girl.
Be a good girl, okay?
I love you! I love you so much!
It's just 2 weeks. Just 2 weeks.
I should go.
Don't wanna be late to my flight.
Bye! Bye.
It should look nice.
Here are the flyers we
talked about last night.
You should be able to
invite at least one person!
One soul is enough!
- Got it?
- Yes, mom.
Wait, that reminds me of Paco…
Is he all better?
Can he control his disgusting urges now?
Is he still courting you?
Chasing you around?
We don't talk that much anymore, mom.
He's busy with his classes.
So glad to hear it!
But we should still invite him, okay?
We have to pray over him.
- Okay, sure, mom.
- I'll be going then.
Be safe!
Okay, mom. Bye!
- I love you!
- I love you, Ma!
What happened to you?
Did you run away?
Mom's leaving for work.
So I have to stay at my granny's.
I was supposed to be
with dad but he left, too.
They're separated, you see.
Oh, sorry, I didn't know.
It's weird, actually.
They don't seem that bothered about it.
They're still friends.
As for me, I still can't accept it.
I don't think it's weird.
What would be weird is if you feel nothing
about what happened.
You're not made of stone, are you?
What's that?
Ah. Here, have one.
If you're not doing anything later,
come to our church's anniversary dinner.
There's free buffet.
Sweet!
Will you be served at the buffet?
- Let me help you with that.
- Okay! G!
- Take this one, it's heavier.
Hey, bestie, are you okay?
Fine, fine.
You don't look it.
You look like you have a worm up your ass.
Spit it out. What is it?
I know you've got tea.
More like a confession, actually.
About yesterday…
Hold it, Milo.
Hey! Where were you yesterday?
You missed all the gay action!
True that, bestie!
Slugfest of the century.
Bisexual versus femme!
It was nuts!
Nah, I was busy with
something more important.
Like what?
Well, sorry, but I don't kiss and tell.
That's stupid.
So you admit there was kissing involved!
Yeah!
But I didn't say who, did I?
Who could it be?
Is it Paco?
I think with just a little more push,
he's gonna be mine!
Oh my God, hey!
Hey! Don't be delusional.
Babe, you know how famous people are!
Get a grip!
Kate, tell her. Back me up!
Since when did they become friends?
So what if they're friends? You jealous?
You're totally jealous.
Change topic.
What were you gonna tell us?
Nothing.
My ass!
Enough with the suspense.
Just spill it!
- Come on!
- Hurry up!
Fine!
But be quiet.
I'm the one who leaked Brian's scandal.
I feel guilty.
- Yo!
- Huh?
Why did you do that?
Because I was annoyed with him!
He was acting all high and mighty!
But now, I feel bad.
You know what?
It'll eat at you until you own up to it!
Bestie, I can't confess to Brian!
Did you see him punch Amber in the face?
Right, Kate?
I'm not ready for that!
Okay, hear me out.
What if you tell Mrs. Holly
and ask for her advice?
We can go with you if you like.
We're here for you. Aren't we, Kate?
I'm scared!
Don't be scared. We've got your back.
- It's gonna be fine, bestie.
- You can do it.
We're here.
Hi, Paco.
- How are you?
- Uhm, fine.
Are you done being angry with me?
Angry? For what?
Probably because I'm dating Erica now.
No! What do I care?
Wait. Something's different about you.
I can't put my finger on it.
Well, I'm just happy.
- I feel good.
- That's good.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
Sit down beside me. Tell me what's up.
I don't get it.
Psst, Allaine.
What's different about Gee?
What's up with her?
Madame Zeny! Good day!
Good day, principal!
How have you been?
I've been well.
This is for you.
Oh, thanks.
Ah, I've brought you another surprise.
This is Brian and Amber.
What kind of bullshit
did these two cook up?
He punched him.
There was a parade at school,
and they had a disagreement.
You know how kids are.
The last pair you brought
here punched each other, too!
You remember?
Is it a school you're
running or a boxing gym?
A boxing gym.
No, I'm kidding.
Not that I'm complaining.
My house was built almost
solely with your students' help.
I noticed.
But that just means
your school's crawling with brutes!
They're just kids.
Let's give them a break.
Anyway, I've introduced them to you.
We'll be on our way.
Let me just repeat that:
Brian, Amber. Amber, Brian.
Both of you behave. Please?
All you have to do is follow Madame.
That's it.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Yes, sir.
I will see you in the office.
- Let's go, Joyce.
- Behave.
I don't want any stress.
And I don't like softies and weaklings!
You're not gay, are you?
Why do you ask?
I don't like gays.
- Like we wanna be here?
- What was that?
Nothing, madame. Neither of us are gay.
I'm a dude.
I just like makeup. Hashtag vain!
What do you need us for?
Clean up the garden.
And paint the vases over there.
This is your fault!
Fuck you.
You'd better be doing that right.
Can you mind your own business?
I'm just saying, I never wanna be stuck
doing community service
again because of you!
This isn't so hard.
It's just up, down, top
to bottom, top to bottom.
That's all you gotta do.
Let me try that.
Top to bottom, top to bottom!
Is that correct? Did I get it right?
Not like that! Like this!
Top to bottom, top to bottom,
top to bottom, top to bottom!
Mm, yes!
Is that it.
Hey! You fucking idiots!
He started it, not me!
- Mind your own business!
- That's enough!
You're just giving me more work to do!
Clean this mess up!
Good God, what have you done?
That's how I imagined you
when I got on that videocall.
What?
Imagine if you weren't wearing makeup
and acting like a girl.
I'd have boned you!
We'd have been at it like rabbits.
Then what?
You're gonna collab with
me and sell my nudes, too?
Fuck you!
That's what's wrong with you, Brian.
I'm not going to change myself
just so you or anyone
else, finds me palatable!
I worked too hard to build myself up
to get to this level of
confidence and be out.
Blah, blah, blah. Shut up!
You don't wanna hear people out.
You're so full of yourself.
You can't even wrap
your head around the fact
that I wasn't the one
who leaked your nudes.
Then who?
How the hell should I know?
You know, I accepted you into the pride org
because I believe that
you're nice deep inside!
Besides, I have nothing against you
even if you ruined me and
stomped on my whole being.
I'm used to it!
I don't hurt that easily!
Get changed.
Thank you, madame.
Why dresses?
Don't be fussy.
You're enough trouble as it is.
That's all I have, dusters.
They're pretty, actually. Floral.
I don't wear these things.
Wait, Bullet!
You wanna hang out?
Maybe tomorrow. I gotta do something.
After then?
Will it take long?
I can wait.
You wanna go get milk tea or… you know.
Stop asking.
I said tomorrow.
Are you mad?
Listen, Gee. I've got shit to deal with
outside school, okay?
So stop being a pest.
The fuck, am I your grandma
or something? Want presents?
Are we close?
Yeah, we're almost there.
- Your bag's kinda heavy, huh?
- I'm hungry.
Is there a lot of food?
This is our house.
- Isn't it nice?
- Can we go in?
Where's you mom?
She's inside.
With love, the power of joy,
and the blessing of light,
we manifest that we will forever
have happiness in our hearts!
Now and then, amen!
Amen!
- Amen!
Let's give the Lord a round of applause!
Praise the Lord!
Forever!
Mom.
Thank you.
Please excuse me.
Good evening.
Mom, this is Allaine.
Allaine, my mom.
She's the pastor of our church.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hello, Allaine.
I didn't know my daughter
had such a beautiful classmate.
Thank you, ma'am.
- Are you here to get baptized?
- Sorry?
Because the tub's ready.
We just need to fill it up.
Mom…
I think I wanna
experience the service first.
May you have the enlightenment
that you want in our service!
Take care of your guest, darling, okay?
- Okay, mom.
- I'm almost done here.
Moving on, brothers and sisters.
- As it says in Jeremiah Chapter 17--
- Don't you wanna get baptized?
Why? You wanna see my hard
nipples through a wet blouse?
Maybe.
I just made you cry in my arms.
Hey, Allaine.
I didn't know you were part of the church.
Joanna just invited me today.
You guys dating?
Don't tell me you brought
her to meet the parents?
Have you decided to get tied down, Joanna?
No, we're just friends.
And I'm here for the Lord.
Lighting strike you.
Where's Brian? He's not here?
Why? Why did you let him get into trouble?
I'm glad he's getting into brawls,
not into hair salons.
This is your fault for
tolerating his homosexuality.
That's his decision.
And I'm just here to support my son.
Let me take care of him.
For one or two months.
I'll make him straight.
I've got cousins from
the military in Tacloban!
Huh?
That's never gonna happen!
Your role here
is to help him with his needs.
Like that volleyball camp in Thailand.
Why are you making it hard for him?
You're the one who's
making things hard for him
making him think there's
a future in him being gay.
He's just gonna get laughed at.
Hello? It's 2023!
Where do you live? In the 1960s?
My goodness!
The LGBT movement has already
accomplished so much in the world
without asking for help from anyone!
Then let Brian figure it out!
He doesn't need anyone's help anyway!
So you're fine with him
selling nudes on the internet?
Like you said, it's his decision!
You're evil.
Just leave, you useless piece of shit.
Madame, can I ask you a question?
I'm just curious.
Why are you angry at gay people?
Do you see my husband anywhere?
You have a husband?
He left me!
He ran off with his gay bestfriend!
They'll both burn in hell!
Madame, I'm gay.
I know.
You know?
It's obvious!
What about him?
Hey!
Aren't you a couple?
Ew! No!
You know,
not every gay person is like your husband.
Sure, there are assholes
but we're not all the same.
And isn't that for the better?
If you had known much later that your
husband's hiding something from you,
that would hurt you more in the long run.
At least he was honest with you.
So what?
He still left me.
I just wanna be angry, what's it to you?
Okay!
I was just asking.
Okay.
Finish your plate.
After that, you can leave.
I still have things to do outside.
Why did you have to pry about her husband?
I just wanted to know why
she's angry at gay people!
At least now, I got the answer I wanted.
A gay man betrayed her.
And I respect that! It's understandable!
She should sit with her
anger for as long as she likes!
At least now, we know.
That she's not angry just
for the sake of being angry.
You mean like me?
I didn't say that.
Madame!
Madame? Madame?
Shit, did she fall asleep?
Is she still breathing? Check her pulse!
Oh my God!
Madame?
Are you okay, Mrs. H?
Was that Brian's dad?
What did he do?
Nothing. I'm fine.
He's just an asshole.
You can tell me anything, all right?
Thanks for being here, Paco.
Somehow, I'm glad I
have someone to lean on.
Where's the money?
You'll have it next week!
That's what you told us last week.
You're fooling us every week.
You're losing sleep over 20k?
You're cheaping out on 20k?
I blew all the money playing odds.
And I'm still waiting for my allowance.
I'll give you the first 10k
by installment, I promise.
Installment? Fuck that.
Don't! Don't hurt Bullet!
Who's this? Your sugar mommy?
For fuck's sake, Gee.
Stay out of this.
Wait, how much does he owe you?
20,000.00
No big deal.
Here.
For the payment.
Make sure it's not fake.
This will do.
Next time, pay your debts on time.
What did I tell you? Just trust me.
I can't do this! I'm really
scared of Mrs. Holly!
I'm not ready to do this.
I thought you felt guilty?
You should face your problems!
Okay, here's what we'll do.
I'll check if Mrs. Holly is in.
If she's there, follow after me.
- Okay, stay here.
- Okay.
Stay here. I'll be right back.
Okay.
Erica?
Hey.
- Come on.
- She's not there?
She's not there. Come on!
How are you guys?
You know,
don't let it get to you too much.
You had nothing to do with it.
And Madame's in her advanced age.
That's to be expected.
For all you know, all those remaining
years she's had are just a bonus.
Besides, the school will
take care of all the expenses.
The wake, the burial, the wake.. Amber,
you're great at doing make-up, right?
You can do Madame's makeup if you like.
She'd have loved that for sure.
And if you wanna send her flowers, yeah!
Nice!
Am I the first person you brought in here?
Of course.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
No, seriously.
I've had multiple sexual partners, Joanna.
One little wince and I
know something's off.
Tell me.
Okay.
You don't seem like the same person
I did it with in the restroom.
Like I don't feel the same way.
What do you mean?
I'm attracted to these things.
Anime characters and monsters.
So… should I just go home?
No. Wait.
Wear this.
Okay…
You like this?
Are you okay?