=Your Trap=
= 11. Can I Trust You=
Long time no see, Mr. Feng.
Mr. Ji.
I'm afraid President Feng
needs to change his title.
You didn't expect this, did you?
The shares I hold
have surpassed yours long ago.
Plus this stamped appointment letter.
(Appointment Letter)
Listen to me, everyone.
From today on,
I'll be the president of Wanli.
This is really great.
I feel my burden is lightened.
Come on.
Let's raise our glasses together.
Congratulations to Mr. Ji,
the new president of Wanli Group.
But I'm curious,
who appointed you?
Where did you get the official seal?
What are you doing?
I am Wanli's president.
Let me go!
President?
Do you know that stealing seals is illegal?
Take him away.
You...
What are you guys doing? Let him go!
Darling, save me!
Han Qing, how dare you trick me!
Did you all conspire to deceive me?
Liars!
Don't say anything.
Yin Yi.
How dare you fool me like this?
Dad, I'm leaving first.
What's going on?
Mr. Yin.
Ji Weijun is not happy
that you promoted Mr. Feng,
so he stole the seal
and faked the appointment letter,
hoping to become Wanli's president.
I'm asking him. Why did you speak?
Mr. Yin.
She is my assistant.
She is your assistant?
Yes.
All the physical evidence is here.
How are you going to explain?
Under the guise of an assistant,
you got involved in the affairs
of our Yin family.
Where did you get the ball?
Miss Han.
You should have some self-awareness.
Don't seduce the wrong person.
Mr. Feng had an agreement
with Peidong at that time
to take over Huajing.
The first thing is to marry Yin Yi.
Second,
never get a divorce in the future.
Miss Han.
You are in the prime of your life.
Do not interfere in other people's marriage.
We can't do this.
I underestimated your rationality.
I overestimated your rationality.
Cooperate with me
to expose the mole.
Then I can set you free.
So you mean
you have already seen through their plan
and want to go along with it?
Han Qing.
I can only trust you now.
Because you are like me,
helpless.
Yes.
I am helpless.
So I've fallen to this point.
Can you let me go?
I don't want to fall deeper into error.
Han Qing.
I hope you can be smarter.
Whether it's you
or me,
we are just a pawn to the Yin family.
As for your dad's matter,
I will help you deal with it.
You don't need to sacrifice yourself anymore.
You can try to trust me.
Ji Weijun will relieve you of your office
at the shareholders' meeting a month later.
He wants to sell Wanli.
Starting from today,
act with me in this play.
I will accompany you to the end.
(Are you playing me, Feng Siqian?)
(Believe me.)
(Han Qing.)
(Can I trust you?)
♪Always dreaming of fireworks filling the sky♪
♪Waking up in my dim world♪
♪Always owing just a small thing♪
♪Only for meeting you♪
♪Tomorrow♪
♪Always missing your goodbye♪
♪The spring of forgotten roses♪
♪Always yearning for♪
♪Your unintentional glance♪
♪Never forgetting♪
♪Those old days♪
♪You always appeared in my dreams♪
♪It's too beautiful a plot♪
♪Always sleepless♪
♪I am trapped in sin♪
♪Trying to fill it♪
♪But no one is spared♪
♪Always teasing around, for my sincerity♪
♪Imminent random wildfires♪
♪Always puzzled♪
♪How can I quit♪
♪Forgetting the history♪
♪But lost again in the lips and eyes♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)