=Your Trap=
=21. Selection=
How is it going?
Ji Weijun has been arrested.
He said he had discussed it with Lin Zongyi
to take Ms. Yin to the factory,
intending to use her and the baby
to threaten you.
He didn't know
that was his own child.
This scum.
Cooperate with the police investigation
to catch the real culprit.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
My baby.
Take a seat.
Did you put a tracking device on me?
You always manage to find me accurately.
♪Lean towards the color that lies within♪
How serious is your car accident?
You're injured.
I'm fine now.
Luckily, I noticed the problem
with the car in advance.
So I stopped the car early,
and it didn't lead to a major accident.
I thought I would never see you again.
I'm a lucky man.
Let's go back now.
Siqian.
Yin Yi is still lying inside.
It's not appropriate
for you to flirt here.
It's you who did that
to Ji Weijun and Yin Yi.
What are you talking about, honey?
Wasn't it planned by you and me together?
You said you wanted to
retaliate against Feng Siqian and Yin Yi.
They both played you like a fool.
Now you're turning against me?
Lin Zongyi, you are so shameless.
Thank you for your compliment.
Lin Zongyi.
I warned you before
not to stretch your hand too far.
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Now Yin Yi is on my side.
With my shares and Yin Peidong's,
I can secure my position in Huajing.
What can you do to me?
Do you really think you have obtained
Mr. Yin's shares?
What do you mean?
Hello.
Mr. Lin, bad news.
Yin Peidong has been transferred long ago.
We found no one there.
Stop.
She is my fiancée.
Don't even think about going anywhere.
Lin Zongyi, when will you ever stop?
Do you know that you colluded with Ji Weijun
and almost killed Han Qing?
It was you who informed Ji Weijun?
I warned him
not to harm you.
It was his own decision.
It has nothing to do with me.
The damage has been done.
I will settle accounts with you
for everything you did one by one.
But my dad is still in his hands.
Don't worry.
You've got me.
Hello.
Get the shares straight for me.
President Feng.
Lin Zongyi has been
meeting with the major shareholders
of Huajing in private
to collect shares everywhere.
So he still hasn't given up.
By the way,
what about Mr. Yin?
How is he doing over there?
Mr. Yin was frightened
but it's nothing serious.
There is a doctor taking care of him now.
He should wake up soon.
However...
Speak.
Before he had the accident,
he transferred all his shares to Ms. Yin Yi.
It seems that he still doesn't trust me.
That's right.
Now, Lin Zongyi's shares
are almost the same as yours.
In the end,
it depends on Ms. Yin Yi's attitude.
Okay, I got it.
Go back to work.
Okay.
(Yin Yi)
Feng Siqian is in big trouble.
Only you can help him.
Time flies so fast.
You asked me to come
just to catch up?
Your dad is safe abroad now.
You will reunite with him soon.
You wouldn't easily help me.
What is your condition?
During this time,
there is chaos within Huajing.
Lin Zongyi took advantage of the chaos
and bought a large amount of shares.
Now his shares
are equal to Feng Siqian's.
The shareholders' meeting will be held
next week.
By then, whoever gets my shares
will become the largest shareholder of Huajing.
What do you want me to do?
Leave Feng Siqian.
Then
I will transfer all my shares
to him.
Han Qing.
You should know better than me
what does Huajing mean to him.
You don't want to
ruin Feng Siqian's career and life, right?
I don't think I can influence
Feng Siqian's decisions.
Miss Han,
you've underestimated
your importance in Feng Siqian's heart.
Before, you were willing to destroy Feng Siqian
for Ji Weijun.
It seems that people change.
My dad was right.
Love
is the most unreliable thing in the world.
Only the interests in hand
are the most important.
I promised my father
to marry Feng Siqian
because only he
could bring continuous wealth to the Yin family
and help us keep Huajing.
Miss Han, don't blame me.
Ji Weijun is now in prison,
and I've lost my child.
Now I can only maintain
my identity as Mrs. Feng.
What if I refuse?
Then I will expose all your scandals
and insider information.
The acquisition will fail
and Huajing's stock price will plummet.
Everything Feng Siqian owns
will also vanish into thin air.
I know you love him.
You won't refuse.
Does my fiancee have time tomorrow?
Let's meet.
♪Always dreaming of fireworks filling the sky♪
♪Waking up in my dim world♪
♪Always owing just a small thing♪
♪Only for meeting you♪
♪Tomorrow♪
♪Always missing your goodbye♪
♪The spring of forgotten roses♪
♪Always yearning for♪
♪Your unintentional glance♪
♪Never forgetting♪
♪Those old days♪
♪You always appeared in my dreams♪
♪It's too beautiful a plot♪
♪Always sleepless♪
♪I am trapped in sin♪
♪Trying to fill it♪
♪But no one is spared♪
♪Always teasing around, for my sincerity♪
♪Imminent random wildfires♪
♪Always puzzled♪
♪How can I quit♪
♪Forgetting the history♪
♪But lost again in the lips and eyes♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)