=Your Trap=
(There is always a dividing line
in the treatment of women by God.)
(What separates him and me)
(is fate that I can't escape from.)
(If)
(there's a line drawn)
(in the definition of angel and devil...)
Assistant Han.
Am I your bait
or your fish?
(then cross that line,)
(will I become an angel)
(or)
(a devil?)
I fell for it.
Is this what you want?
Mr. Feng.
What I want
is all of you.
(Feng Siqian.)
(You are the devil.)
(The devil who imprisons my soul)
(and makes me unable to resist.)
=1. Battle with the Devil=
(Three months ago)
Han Qing,
a professional mistress dispeller,
traveling frequently between
Jiangcheng and Huaicheng,
helping lawful wives
save their failed marriage
or gain the greatest benefit.
I heard cases handled by you
are practically certain to win.
More accurately,
I've never failed
for three years.
Very good.
I have heard of your methods.
You spend more time
investigating the evidence
of my husband's affair.
The more we have on him,
the greater our chances of winning.
Ms. Yin.
Are you trying to reconcile or divorce?
Divorce.
I want at least half of his wealth.
The chairman of Huajing Group
has a net worth of nearly 10 billion.
With a man like him and your requirements,
this case is not easy.
I understand your concerns.
He wants me to move out
and he'll take everything from me.
Not to mention...
Okay.
I will never let any scumbag off the hook.
But I want the money I asked for,
not a penny less.
The duration of the contract is three months.
(Letter of attorney)
You and I each take what we need.
(Signature of Party B)
Don't come again tomorrow.
Why have you just arrived?
Sorry.
I got stuck in traffic.
Alright.
HR told you everything you need to know, right?
Be cautious and careful in your actions.
President Feng hates scheming people the most.
Don't ask what you shouldn't ask.
Don't look at what you shouldn't look at.
Not everyone can enter Huajing Group,
especially as an assistant
to the president.
Working for President Feng, it's better to...
To be a smart mute.
Seems like you've got the hang of it.
Go.
This is the president's office.
President Feng.
- President Feng.
Get back to work.
President Feng.
She's the personal assistant
arranged for you by the company.
I don't need one.
Let her go.
It is reported that
Mr. Feng is humble and modest.
I didn't expect you to be so arrogant.
Arrogant?
Isn't that right, Mr. Feng?
We've got
plenty of people like you in Huajing.
Why should I keep you?
Let's go.
I'm different from them.
As long as the goal is legitimate,
I can use any means,
just like Mr. Feng.
So
you will definitely need me.
A woman with a temper and personality.
I like it.
A boss with strength and challenges.
I like it too.
Zhao Lu.
Help her handle the admission procedure.
Okay.
Please come with me.
By the way,
your lipstick color is too tacky.
Remember to change the color next time.
President Feng, this document is ready,
just waiting for your confirmation.
Here.
(The supreme hunter)
(often disguises himself as the prey.)
(And curiosity)
(makes a man)
(start to explore a woman.)
(Not to mention)
(no matter how well men disguise themselves,)
(they can't resist)
(an unsolicited prey.)
Feng Siqian is a very scheming man.
He is very guarded against women.
I only need three months.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
♪Always dreaming of fireworks filling the sky♪
♪Waking up in my dim world♪
♪Always owing just a small thing♪
♪Only for meeting you♪
♪Tomorrow♪
♪Always missing your goodbye♪
♪The spring of forgotten roses♪
♪Always yearning for♪
♪Your unintentional glance♪
♪Never forgetting♪
♪Those old days♪
♪You always appeared in my dreams♪
♪It's too beautiful a plot♪
♪Always sleepless♪
♪I am trapped in sin♪
♪Trying to fill it♪
♪But no one is spared♪
♪Always teasing around, for my sincerity♪
♪Imminent random wildfires♪
♪Always puzzled♪
♪How can I quit♪
♪Forgetting the history♪
♪But lost again in the lips and eyes♪
(The right of communication
through information network)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)