The city is expected to experience winds
exceeding level seven
in the next twenty-four hours,
with gusts reaching level nine.
All residents are advised
to take precautions
and plan your travel reasonably.
Relevant departments should
implement protective measures.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
[Not for public parking]
Director Zhao.
Let's go upstairs.
It's so windy.
It's been a rough trip, Zhao.
Li, how are you doing in the dorms?
Is there anything you need?
Monitor Gao.
Don't give me that crap.
You promised me to solve the case
in three months.
It's been almost six months.
The circumstances are special.
It's a complicated case.
Everyone's doing their best.
Also,
we're on a big mission.
How could you drink?
You reek of alcohol.
What will the other comrades
think of you?
How can you command?
It's a long story.
I swear, I didn't drink a drop.
It all spilled into my shoes. See?
No time to change.
Li, take note of this.
Okay.
What happened?
We staged a birthday party
to avoid suspicion
from the suspects.
That's why I...
Are you really drunk?
I need the current status report.
Suspected drug traffickers Jiang Yingzi,
Liang Jiaju, Lin Zhida, and others,
along with the drug-related locations,
have been identified
and are under our control.
Our forces are in position,
awaiting orders.
Maintain strict surveillance
while gathering evidence.
Yes.
Also, change your shoes.
[Harland Underground Facilities Map]
Director Zhao, Director Gao.
Give Director Zhao an update.
Yes.
Here, Director Zhao.
The trucks responsible for
transporting the towels
have now entered
the drug processing factory.
[Drug Processing Factory]
Officer Zheng will lead armed forces
to infiltrate from
a nearby abandoned factory.
The clock's ticking. Move!
- Hurry up!
- Quickly!
Move faster!
Chop chop!
- Hurry up!
This is the drug manufacturing factory.
[Drug Manufacturing Factory]
Xueyao will lead her team through
Gate One on the ground.
Xiaoguang will wait on standby
with the convoy
and break in through
Gate Two in the tunnel.
As for Wanhuang Hotel,
Xiong's team
has the surrounding area
under surveillance,
ready to strike when the time comes.
Welcome to Wanhuang Hotel.
All locations are surrounded and ready.
This is the other suspect
we've been tracking, Bai Ling.
All suspects have been identified.
How's the evidence collection going?
We've got all the key evidence
including photos and videos.
We just need their statements.
Are the suspects armed?
Yes, but not well armed.
Remind the team to be careful.
Don't worry, Director Zhao.
We will eliminate this drug ring.
[Producer Zhang Yimou]
[The First Shot]
[Episode 29]
Where the hell have you been?
Jiaju, the deal got exposed.
[Drug Manufacturing Factory]
I'm trapped.
Don't come back.
This round's over.
Find a new place and start over.
Jiaju! Jiaju!
Here.
We're running low on ammo.
Use them sparingly.
Got it.
Let's go.
Hurry up. Come on.
Okay.
Hurry up. You hear me?
It's on.
Qiang!
Yeah.
Dump all the goods and ingredients
into the tank. Wash it all away.
You know what to do with these.
Be careful.
The goods are freshly made.
We're about to deliver them.
Dump them.
We've made 100 kilograms.
Doesn't matter.
Put on a respirator. Do it.
Okay.
Scarry,
stay back with some of the guys to help.
Okay.
Once it's done,
burn this place down.
The rest, come with me!
Follow me!
Are you insane?
You're going to poison everyone!
This is the blue drum!
Get it out of here!
Now! Move that blue drum, quick!
Keep dumping it in!
Madam.
Phone's for you.
[Mr. Ma]
Hello, Mr. Ma.
Zheng Bei,
we've got all the evidence.
Attention, everyone.
We're closing in.
Long!
Cops are here!
Run! Get out of here!
Police! Freeze!
Don't move!
[Public Security]
Freeze!
One step and we shoot!
Don't move!
Police. Freeze!
Drop your guns.
Let's go.
Come here.
Don't go any further.
It's dangerous inside.
Stay here.
Take photos for evidence.
I'm going.
Police. Freeze!
Don't move!
Don't move! Stay still!
Watch out.
Don't move!
- Long!
- Move!
Zheng Bei!
Don't move!
Don't you want to know
where your dad is?
You took him.
Your dad doesn't seem
to be moving anymore.
He's not breathing either.
Where's my dad?
Li Wenlong is right downstairs.
Let me go ask him myself,
see where my dad's body is!
Li Wenlong!
Li Wenlong, open the door!
When I was a kid,
visiting my mom's grave,
my dad used to say that when he died,
he wanted to be buried next to her.
"Leaf returns to its roots."
I laughed at him.
I said he shouldn't be
into superstition as a scientist.
But later, he explained,
it's not superstition.
No matter how fast and far
you go,
you always end up coming home.
Li Wenlong escaped over the wall!
Hurry!
Over here!
Where is he?
He got away.
What are you doing holding a gun?
Can't shoot?
You let him run away!
It's my fault.
He mentioned my dad.
Don't make me regret
bringing you onto this task force.
Snap out of it!
Mr. Lin.
- Mr. Lin.
Dad,
I've got some guys
who know good cooks.
We could do this ourselves.
Every time we barely get a slice.
How's that enough?
Of course, I know.
You think I don't?
But the thing is,
we don't control this territory yet.
We need to be patient.
Can't we just
switch territories?
Freeze!
You shoot.
I shoot.
Stop messing around.
Or you'll ruin it.
Dad,
isn't it crazy how the Russians
invented this game?
Russian roulette...
I don't have enough lives to play this.
Alright, enough.
Bring me those two cases.
[Chairman Office]
Come in.
Police. Don't move!
- Freeze! We're police!
- Freeze!
Give me the gun!
Freeze!
Drop the gun! Don't move!
Don't move! Cuff him!
Easy.
Captain Wang,
are you alright?
Xiaoguang, what's the situation?
Bei,
we've secured the factory.
Most of the goods are here.
Have you caught anyone?
No sign of Liang Jiaju,
but we've got the place surrounded.
He won't get away.
Have you seen Jiang Xiaohai?
No.
Okay. Be careful.
Are you injured?
Just minor stuff here.
You?
Nothing serious, just some scrapes.
Get Wang
to update HQ right away.
Captain Wang, report to HQ
with the status update.
Okay.
Found them.
Their hideout is tough to break into.
Xueyao's team is holding the perimeter.
But they won't be able to
slip out easily.
Everyone,
check your gear!
Let's go!
Move!
Ammo!
Are you alright?
Yeah.
They're holed up deep inside.
Too many barriers. Can't get through.
Look around
and see if there's another entry point.
We've already checked.
It's a dead end.
Wu!
There's still one inside.
Everyone, stay sharp!
Okay.
Go.
Liang Jiaju's definitely inside.
It's a thick door.
We can't pry it open.
Xiaoguang, do you have any explosives?
Blow it open.
Hello.
Director Gao.
What's the update?
Director Zhao.
The suspect, Jiang Yingzi,
has been captured.
But during the arrest,
she got shot twice in the right leg
and is currently in a coma.
She's being rushed to
the People's Hospital now.
Send extra men to guard the ward.
Yes.
Li Wenlong managed to escape,
but no one outside
saw him leave.
We're expanding the search area
to find him.
The suspects, Bai Ling,
Lin Zhida, and Lin Jiang,
have been captured.
We're escorting them over.
- Dispatch the team...
- Director Gao.
Liang Jiaju is hiding
in a secret room in the factory.
The door's jammed.
They need explosives to break it down.
They've requested a batch to be sent.
Guozhu,
- take a team and send those explosives.
- Okay.
Hold on.
Director Gao, I'll go.
These rookies barely know
how to handle explosives.
Better if I go.
Be careful.
You're not young anymore.
You're retiring at the end of the month.
Director Gao,
I haven't said this to you in 20 years.
Captain Gao, do you trust me?
I do!
Get out of here.
Yes!
I'm going.
Be careful, Uncle.
[Drug Processing Factory]
I've finally figured out
why we couldn't find out
how they got the drugs in.
There's another tunnel.
Gu Yiran,
if you're going to
keep spacing out like this,
sit this one out.
Don't come along.
It's a coal truck.
It's probably used for moving the drugs.
This tunnel leads directly
to the drug manufacturing factory.
Look.
There's crystal residue.
We can take the tunnel
and get there faster
than driving around.
[Drug Manufacturing Factory]
Uncle?
What are you doing here?
Brought you guys some fireworks.
Seriously,
you didn't need to bring this yourself.
We could've handled it.
You?
The guy who burned his hand
with sparklers?
No chance.
This place is dangerous!
You should stay in the station.
You're almost retired.
Why did you come here?
You're talking too much.
There's nothing dangerous.
You've caught all the bad guys.
Tell me where to bomb.
Here.
Hurry up.
Be careful, Uncle.
Don't talk.
Stay back.
Keep your distance.
These two factories had nothing to do
with each other before,
but they dug out
a whole tunnel between them.
What was that?
What just blew up?
Xiaoguang,
what was that explosion?
Bei, we're blowing the door.
Liang Jiaju's behind the door.
What? I can't hear you!
We're blasting the door open.
Uncle's here with us.
What?
Just blowing the door.
It's all good, Bei.
We've got it under control.
Let's go now.
Let's go!
Uncle,
you missed this one.
Piss off.
My skills are getting rusty.
I didn't use enough.
Stop staring.
Go get the boxes.
Yes.
There's a door.
Why is the door rattling?
Xiaoguang.
Don't blow this door.
It's packed with explosives here!
Quick, disarm the bomb!
Don't open the door!
Everyone, stay put!
Back up!
It's opening.
Don't push the door, Bei!
♪Memories fade, hidden in snow♪
♪Unclear paths, where do they go?♪
♪Voices speak, nothing to show♪
♪I can't hear my heart's flow♪
♪Time chases, past and future blend♪
♪Ambition and doubt contend♪
♪Facing the game♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Who sheds their blood with such pain?♪
♪Who writes a story
of endless ruins in vain?♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Whose blood and sweat♪
♪Is painting the vivid pictures
in this tale?♪