[Science and Technology
Drive Productivity]
[Producer Zhang Yimou]
[The First Shot]
[Episode 8]
Dad,
you're making food for yourself.
Go away.
You've eaten.
Your mother and I are still hungry.
Where is the owner?
What's up with your cooking?
Ignore him.
I'll go take a look.
Just another drunk.
Ignore him.
Take your parents.
Get out through the back door.
Call the police.
Run!
Go, go.
Smash the restaurant.
Got it.
Burn it.
Where is the gun?
Gun.
Liuzi, where is the gun?
Don't move.
Listen, Shen Li.
Just come at me.
Leave my parents out of it.
Shen Li.
You remember me.
I don't just remember you.
I also remember your partner Zhang Xuan.
You two killed a cop.
Kill him.
Police. Don't move!
Don't move!
Are you okay?
Take it easy.
Get up!
Cuff them.
Cuff them all.
Bei, are you alright?
Bei,
check on Mr. Gu.
I heard his neck was blistered.
He's fine.
It's just a scratch.
Fine?
- Just a scratch?
- Without him,
this place would be a wreck.
You're ungrateful.
I'm ungrateful?
Don't use Red Flower Oil.
It will make the swelling worse.
Who said that?
I've used it since childhood.
Trust me,
I get injuries all the time.
Mom, where is my ice water?
Here it is.
Here you are.
Here.
What are you doing?
Use this to ice it down.
It'll help with the swelling.
It feels good, right?
It's cold.
You'll be fine once the swelling's down.
Let me take care of you first.
Mr. Gu is a tough guy.
If I fuss over him,
he might get embarrassed.
Sounds like you'd be embarrassed.
I'm tough too.
But I don't mind a little pampering.
Alright, after I
take care of you,
I'll go check on him.
Son,
you're in your thirties.
Why are you still acting like a kid?
I'm only thirty,
for crying out loud.
Mom,
close the restaurant
for a few days.
I'll get a decoration team tomorrow
to repair it.
Fu and the others are
going to Tieling for a trip.
You two should join them.
Your mom and I met in Tieling.
Take a trip somewhere,
maybe Shenyang.
Come on.
Go rest.
I'll handle it.
I've got it.
Hold on.
It's too cold,
frozen solid.
Give it a second.
It's okay, son.
We can take care of ourselves.
This was just bad luck,
not your fault.
Mom,
that guy was someone I locked up.
He's out for revenge now.
And there are plenty more like him
in No. 5 Prison.
What if they're all like him?
How can I not worry?
I'm a cop,
arresting bad guys all day,
but I can't even protect my own family.
Come on.
What about the people
who've turned their lives around
because of you?
They still come by to support us.
Right, Dad?
And all those banners we've got.
The garage is almost full.
Yes.
You're
the youngest detective captain.
You catch so many bad guys every year.
I go dance in the park
with my head held high.
The other old guys are jealous.
Aren't you doing Tai Chi?
It's a mix of Tai Chi
and square dancing.
It's a new style.
Alright, go inside.
All this talking
is stressing me out.
Go back to your room.
So it's a new dance.
Tai Chi dance.
Fine, I'm going.
I'll take care of Gu.
Eat it while it's hot.
Gu loves it.
Make sure he gets plenty.
Keep icing Dad's dad's hand, okay?
Don't worry, I got it.
Mom,
don't worry.
What are you doing?
Mr. Gu's hurt pretty bad.
I'm going to help him bandage up.
Bandage?
Get out of here.
You can't even wrap dumplings.
Well, I've got a mirror over there
I need to get.
You want to get a mirror at this hour?
Can't you do it tomorrow?
What are you up to?
What is that in your hand?
Bei.
Is everything fine?
You finally came.
Where were you earlier?
I went to check the cabs.
I just came back.
Are your parents okay?
They're fine.
How about...?
She's fine too.
Don't worry. Go to bed.
Alright.
Bei.
Who is that guy?
He's pretty wild.
Three years ago, we busted him
for running drugs on a motorcycle.
He wasn't the main guy,
so they let him out.
Officer Liang was killed by them.
Eat it and go home.
Those punks.
We'll deal with them soon enough.
Go ahead.
You too, get some rest.
What are you doing?
It's not even in the right place.
Who did this for you?
Let me fix it.
No, really, it's fine.
Let me help you.
No need.
Seriously, you missed the wound.
Let me fix it. Come on.
Not embarrassed now, huh?
You got sharp ears.
I can hear everything
your sister listens to
through the walls.
I keep telling her to wear headphones,
but she won't listen.
Have some sweets to calm your nerves.
Thank you so much, Ran.
Aren't you a bit old
for White Rabbit candy?
My sister gave me this.
She said you're clever.
Apparently, it can be used
as a secret code.
See? Class actually paid off.
It did, it did.
You still skipping tomorrow?
Eat something
before it gets cold.
Come on.
Son,
you're in your thirties.
Time to grow up.
I beg you pardon?
What did you just call me?
Are you eating or not?
Try some
fried dumplings.
Come on.
Let me take a look.
Morning, Uncle.
Gu.
Why did you
run to work?
Feeling better?
Almost back to normal.
Morning, Uncle.
Morning.
Had to run,
or I'd still be half-asleep.
Your Halan accent is getting better.
Alright, I'm heading inside.
Go ahead.
Wang.
Take care. Rest up.
Healing takes time.
Okay.
Officer Zheng.
What's with you?
Spending money like it's nothing?
Everyone earns their money
through hard work.
You know that.
Look at Gu.
He hasn't recovered yet,
but he ran to work.
You know that.
Enjoying
a cozy taxi ride?
I'm investigating taxis, Uncle.
- I'm leaving.
- Hold on.
What now?
What are you doing?
You're acting like
one of them now, huh?
Not calling me Master anymore?
Come on. Let go.
We were just talking.
Why are you getting physical?
You're investigating taxis
so you had one pulled over
right at the police station.
Are you informing the criminals?
Who's the fool here,
you or them?
Well...
It's to scare them off.
We...
I have a meeting.
You're too careless.
So many taxi fare receipts.
When will I be reimbursed?
Stop it.
Do you want to run to work?
- Director Gao.
Sit down.
Director Gao, I'll start.
Go ahead.
We've looked into
all the taxi companies in Halan.
[Yifeng Taxi Company]
The focus is this company.
We were right.
These drug dealers
are indeed using cabs to run drugs.
This person
is the manager at Rattlesnake Cabaret
and is also
the second-in-command of Yifeng.
Erjin.
We've got the whole structure
of Yifeng figured out now.
Their drivers
caused a scene at the Wanhuang Hotel,
and I happened to be there.
I noticed something.
Only Yifeng's cabs
have in-car radios.
Those radios aren't cheap.
I checked.
If they're just using them for dispatch,
the cost is too high.
Mr. Gu.
Over the past couple of weeks,
we've confirmed one more thing.
Only this taxi company's cars
have traces of drugs.
Traces of drugs?
Yes.
Mr. Gu
summarized the scents of all the drugs.
He has taught us
to identify the scents
of different drugs.
We've even had several classes on it.
That's a useful technique.
We use it for investigation.
It helps us keep our investigation
under the radar.
Drug dealers are cunning,
and they usually hide well.
But no matter how careful they are,
once they're around drugs,
they leave behind a scent.
So it comes down to
"observe, smell, question, and pulse."
Have we tracked down their supply point?
Not yet.
But we suspect
of an abandoned factory
called Sanlianer Factory.
We've been waiting,
worried about tipping them off.
We're still in the surveillance stage.
They're only dealing ecstasy?
Yes.
You've investigated for so long.
Any progress on the meth front?
Not yet.
Even though Halan is far from the south,
the long northern
and eastern borders
make the situation complicated.
Drug activity has become more complex
in recent years.
Now, we've found new drugs.
The provincial authorities
are taking it very seriously
and have ordered us
to crack the case of new drugs
within three months,
before it spreads.
You guys have to be thorough
and precise.
Understood!
[Qin Yi]
Business is not about money
when it grows to a point.
Mr. Hu.
How many goods did Blue Aurora
steal from me?
I... I gave you all your money back.
Do me a favor.
Even your own dog
might bite you.
Your place is now mine.
Take it, take it.
I told you
not to be a thief.
Did you forget, or just not listen?
Boss.
Why's the goods
been moving so slowly lately?
Lately,
some of our guys
have noticed suspicious people
tailing our cars
and hanging around the warehouse.
We've had to
stop unloading a few times.
Shut him up.
The cops are onto us?
And this time,
they're targeting us specifically.
Who's running the task force?
They set it up after
what happened in White Building.
The leader
is Zheng Bei from Major Crimes.
Don't stress
about the taxis.
Just keep tabs
on Zheng Bei.
Boss,
if we can't move the product,
shouldn't we be more worried
about the taxis?
Alright.
Boss, go enjoy a bath.
This mess is filthy.
I'll clean it up.
After that,
head over to Blue Aurora.
You'll be in charge there from now on.
Boss,
Xiaohai's getting out today.
Should we send someone to pick him up?
No need.
What should we do with this?
Grab a saw.
[Halan Detention Center]
Bei.
Mao.
Officer Zheng.
Are you here to pick up Xiaohai?
Yes, yes.
I didn't want to leave Mao alone,
so I brought her along.
You... You here to see Xiaohai too?
Yeah, just checking on him.
Did he get into trouble again?
No, just visiting.
That's good.
I was worried he might've
caused trouble again.
He used to get into a lot of it?
No, not really.
He's just got a temper.
Was a bit impulsive as a kid,
but he's much better now.
What happened to him
as a kid?
Before he came to our house,
he went through a lot.
Before your house?
Isn't he your brother?
Xiaohai probably didn't tell you.
He's not my biological brother.
My real brother was also
named Jiang Xiaohai.
My dad didn't like girls much,
so he never treated me well.
Later,
my mom gave birth to a boy.
However, my brother
got sick and died in elementary school.
After that, my dad adopted a boy,
who you now know as Jiang Xiaohai,
and gave him my brother's name.
It was his way of coping.
I didn't know that.
But you two seem really close.
To my dad,
he might've just been a replacement.
But to me,
he's like my real brother.
I can see that.
We have
been through a lot together.
The first couple of years
after he came to our house,
things were good,
especially with my mom around.
But after she died,
my dad started drinking
and beating us both.
Eventually, I left for work down south.
I heard he nearly
got beaten to death by my dad
and ran away from home.
He has
had a tough life.
He's gone through a lot
and made many wrong choices.
I've always felt guilty.
I've been thinking
that if I hadn't left,
maybe he wouldn't be like this.
Bei's here.
Mao, go wait in the car.
I'll be right there.
Let's not hang around here.
How about coming to my place for dinner?
Yeah.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
I just need to talk to Xiaohai.
I have to head back to work.
OK. You guys chat.
How was it in there?
It was... alright.
I've had time to think.
I talked to your sister.
She's been through a lot.
Stop getting into trouble.
If you can turn things around,
you'll be doing the right thing.
And don't feel like
you're less than anyone else
because you're not.
Stay on the right path.
But if you mess up again,
I'll bring you in myself.
Can you promise?
Yes, Bei.
Uncle, I'm hungry.
Can we go home and eat?
Hungry already?
Quiet, Mao.
Alright.
Since your sister is here,
go back now.
We will
catch up later.
Go ahead.
Okay.
I'm going back, Bei.
OK, I'm leaving.
Thank you, Officer Zheng.
Swing by anytime.
Okay.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
Xiaoguang.
Bei.
What's the update?
Last night,
these two foreigners were doing meth
at Blue Aurora.
Around 3 AM,
they hit up Xiangbali Bathhouse.
High out of their minds,
they started a fight with the staff.
One of them
stabbed his buddy to death.
The guy's totally out of his mind.
He's cooked his brain with drugs.
Where is he?
Tiedong precinct.
We've got his urine sample
and statement.
Then we...
The results are out.
The meth matches what we found
at White Building.
Really?
Are you sure?
Positive.
We finally found our link.
It's at Blue Aurora.
They were on drugs,
but we can't
pin it on Blue Aurora just yet.
Let's go check it out.
When do they open?
Around 4 PM.
It gets busy around 9 or 10.
Alright.
We'll hit them early morning.
Yao and Guozhu,
you two cover the lobby,
and handle the outside.
Dress sharp,
got it?
Xiaoguang and Mr. Gu,
you two head inside,
and scope out the dance floor.
I'll handle the rest.
Any issues?
None.
Get some rest.
I know.
No trouble.
Try to sleep.
Too wired
to sleep.
Make yourself.
Got it.
Boss.
Over here.
That table up front.
Check, please.
Right here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Lin Jiang,
the owner of Wanhuang.
This is the boss I mentioned.
Good to meet you, Mr. Lin.
We're all family here.
I'm Lin too.
Just call me Linzi.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Let's go to my hotel.
What's wrong, Mr. Lin?
Not fancy enough for you here?
Come on, buddy.
You're running a big operation,
but you're still down to earth.
Let's chat here.
Alright then,
the first round's on me.
Good to meet you, Mr. Lin.
Where are you from, Mr. Lin?
Local.
I've been in Halan for a while,
but I've never heard of you.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I'm just blunt.
I'm all over the country.
Born and raised here.
A hustler.
What?
Never mind.
Let's talk business.
You really got a hundred cars?
Yep,
as many as you need.
Jettas?
ou sure you can do 15% off?
No doubt.
But what do you need so many cars for?
What for?
For taxis, of course.
Alright. I can get the plates too.
Mr. Lin.
You're running a business like this
all over the country.
Aren't you worried about getting caught?
The frames are all modified.
If they find out,
I'll get you a new one.
You're the man.
Mr. Lin.
Meeting you today
made my day.
Lately,
it's been nothing but bad luck.
What happened?
Ran into a real pain.
Let's not get into that.
All healed up, Mr. Lin?
Why are you everywhere?
Are you haunting me?
Halan is small.
We're bound to cross paths.
Right?
Jiang,
I'm in the middle of something.
If you want to eat,
do it somewhere else.
Talking car deals?
Talk to me.
Mr. Lin, I swear.
I didn't tell anyone.
Linzi, done eating?
Yes.
Then get back to work.
Okay, Hai.
You played me.
Mr. Lin,
no discord, no concord.
Let's settle this with a drink.
Screw that!
You still haven't answered me.
Can we cooperate?
You really want to work together?
Fine.
I'll show you
what real cooperation looks like.
You played me.
Get my gear!
Fight!
Hello.
I'll be right there.
I didn't fight.
Really.
I was the one who got hit, sir.
City police.
That's all I know.
Sun.
Mind if I ask a few questions?
Sure.
Why are you here, Bei?
What did I tell you this afternoon?
You've only been out a few hours.
Already looking for trouble?
I didn't fight.
You didn't fight?
Then why is Lin Jiang
all messed up?
It wasn't me.
I just came to eat.
What a coincidence.
So you just
happened to see Lin Jiang get beat up?
Right?
I... I didn't touch him.
Jun.
Did he start it?
No.
He was just quietly eating his noodles.
How do you know each other?
[Mr. Zheng Great Chicken Ribs]
Sorry, Uncle, Auntie.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry, Miss Zheng.
No need to apologize to me.
Just know you were wrong.
Right, Dad?
Alright.
I heard
you didn't get into the fight.
But it's still my fault.
I shouldn't have gone there.
And I should've shut it down
when they were fighting.
Uncle Zheng,
have a smoke.
Bei.
Xiaohai.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
If you light up in here,
Mom's going to call the cops.
Didn't you see the sign there?
No smoking inside.
Nobody gets a pass,
not even my director.
Sorry, Auntie Zheng.
I'll step outside and smoke.
Auntie, Uncle,
don't worry.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll get the place fixed up.
It'll look just like before.
Don't worry about it.
For two months,
it's been nothing
but fixing the main store,
then the branch.
I'm worn out.
Here's just been done?
Don't worry about it.
Go on with your work.
I'll chat with him.
Let's go.
Eat something.
I just ate.
Come on.
It's my treat.
What do you want to talk about?
Nothing heavy.
Just chit-chat.
I want to talk
about Qin Yi.
You know what business
Qin Yi runs, right?
Yeah, a taxi company
and a glass factory.
You know this.
Nothing more?
More?
At most some scuffles over business.
Nothing more.
Someone died at his glass factory.
That's serious.
And that taxi company
isn't exactly clean either.
Besides passengers,
what else are they hauling?
Bei,
I'm just a security guard.
Whatever they haul
has nothing to do with me.
Maybe.
But that doesn't mean you don't know.
Right?
So, tell me,
how much do you know?
Bei, please don't ask.
I don't know anything.
Xiaohai.
I've seen a lot of guys
like you.
Young,
been through some stuff,
made mistakes,
but deep down, not bad.
When I see that,
I try to help.
Bei,
I know you care
and want to help.
I care because I'm a cop.
I don't want to see you go astray.
But that doesn't mean
you can fool the police.
I'm not trying to fool anyone.
Those guys who jumped Lin Jiang,
they're from White Building, right?
I remember their faces.
You're playing the word game.
You didn't throw a punch.
But can you really say
you had nothing to do with it?
Are you here to arrest me?
I'm here to help you.
Since you know what Qin Yi's into,
you must realize
he's breaking the law.
I need your help
to take him down.
You want me to be your informant?
Betray my godfather?
That's the wrong word.
It's not betrayal.
It's doing the right thing.
I can't help you.
I've never touched
the stuff you're after.
Maybe not yet.
But can you guarantee
you won't in the future?
Can you be sure
Qin Yi won't force you into it?
Bei,
do you know how I met Qin Yi?
Tough boy.
Have another sip.
You're awake.
Where are your parents?
You're an orphan too.
Come with me.
I'll buy you new boots,
a hat,
a coat, and pants.
Okay?
You'll freeze if you stay here.
Can you get up?
If you can, come with me.
This winter is cold.
Much colder than the one I remember.
Meeting you under this bridge
must be fate.
Five years now.
I don't want to lie to you.
But I can tell you
that Qin Yi never involved me
in his dirty work.
I really don't know what he's up to.
If you've got evidence,
go arrest him.
That's all I can say.
I've given you a chance.
Just kidding.
I get it.
You're close to him.
Let's eat.
Godfather.
You're here.
You startled me.
Where were you?
Went by my sister's,
then took care of Lin Jiang.
Take a seat.
Godfather.
The cops are really watching your fleet.
You should be careful.
It's fine.
Let them check all they want.
You mean that officer, Zheng Bei?
Did you go get information for me,
Xiaohai.
Are you looking out for me,
or are you getting too close to him?
You think I don't notice?
Check equipment.
Confirm teams.
Get ready to move.
Roger that.
[Blue Aurora]
♪Memories fade, hidden in snow♪
♪Unclear paths, where do they go?♪
♪Voices speak, nothing to show♪
♪I can't hear my heart's flow♪
♪Time chases, past and future blend♪
♪Ambition and doubt contend♪
♪Facing the game♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Who sheds their blood with such pain?♪
♪Who writes a story
of endless ruins in vain?♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Whose blood and sweat♪
♪Is painting the vivid pictures
in this tale?♪