[1997]
Buddy, it's too noisy outside.
Let's go inside.
I'll show you something cool.
Trust me. It'll be worth your while.
Get out of here.
- Go.
- Get moving.
Get up.
- Come on, get up.
- Get up.
Buddy.
Get lost
with your friend!
I know you.
You're Jie.
Stop trying to butter me up.
I said get lost. Are you deaf?
Get lost!
You hit me?
Because there's a cop
standing by you?
Jie!
Kid, messing with my boss, huh?
What's going on?
Mouse recognized me.
What? Just your luck.
Move!
Make way!
Move aside!
Out of the way!
Get up.
Who is it?
How dare you touch me?
Bei?
Stay crouched.
Get up.
It's been just a few days.
Back to drugs again?
Hurry up.
Haven't you had enough of the rehab?
Get up.
- Move fast.
- I have.
Cuff him.
Is that so?
Get up!
Do you think I can't see
how high you are?
You know this Jie guy?
Where's the stuff?
I don't know.
Let me ask you again.
Where is the stuff?
I really don't know.
Xiaoguang, cuff him.
Not telling truth, huh?
Please don't.
I lied.
It's behind the sofa.
Behind the sofa?
These.
Just ecstasy.
Just these?
Right?
Yes.
Put them away.
Head down!
Don't move.
Stay crouched.
Take them away.
Get up!
Need another person here.
[Producer Zhang Yimou]
[The First Shot]
[Episode 1]
[Halan, Northeast, 1997]
♪Folks, wake up♪
Are we too early?
Just to be safe.
What's the rush for something big?
Let me show you something interesting.
Where did you get this?
I'll share some with you tonight.
Great.
Is that the guy?
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
Hands on your head.
- Hurry up.
- Keep up.
- Hands on your head.
Move fast.
Faster.
Stand still.
What's your name?
Captain, let's do this.
We'll take the statement.
You and Xiaoguang must be tired.
You should head back and rest.
Alright, you guys do it.
Sure.
Get up. Don't sleep here.
Go home and sleep.
Hello?
Major Crimes First Unit.
Zheng Bei speaking.
Where?
Got it.
Grab the keys. Come with me.
What's up?
There's a homicide case.
[Halan Dongtie Glass Factory]
Officer Zheng.
Officer Zheng, you're here already.
Where's the reporter?
He's being questioned.
It's the security guard on duty.
He's terrified.
What time did you hear the noise?
At 11:40 PM.
This building? Is there a power failure?
Yes. Because of the snow
and outdated wiring.
The whole area is out of power.
This building is the staff dormitory.
The reporter said
it's room 505 on the fifth floor.
Where's the body?
Behind the building.
He has multiple stab wounds.
Pretty scary.
There's more than one victim.
Don't stand on the blood.
Take a look around here.
Bei,
he must have run down this fire escape
and jumped over the wall.
What?
Is this your first time
at a murder scene?
Throw up.
You'll do it sooner or later.
Get used to it.
Just throw up.
Get them here when you're done.
Stop rubber-necking.
You're not allowed to go in.
Everyone, stop gathering here.
Leave.
Just leave.
Go back.
Stop rubber-necking.
Let's go back and tell Boss.
[Huazhou to Halan]
[Huazhou, Yuedong Province]
[Huazhou People's Police Academy]
He's the first again.
It's only been half an hour.
[Huazhou People's Police Academy
Criminalistics Volume A]
Gu Yiran.
Mr. Chen.
Have you given any thought
to what we discussed?
Do you want to stay at the academy
after graduation?
I haven't decided yet.
You've only got half a year.
Discuss it with your father.
It'd be great for you two
to be colleagues.
I'll think about it.
I'm not worried
about your grades at all.
But you're too reserved.
Make more friends.
Alright?
I understand.
Thank you, Mr. Chen.
Go ahead.
Auntie, calm down.
Take your time.
It's been days.
I can't reach her on the phone.
I don't know
where her rented apartment is.
I'm afraid those scoundrels
will lead Xiao astray.
Ran, you're close to her.
Can you help me find her
and tell her to come home?
Please.
Xiao!
Xiao, it's Ran.
Xiao.
Ran.
Dad.
I know you're more upset
about Xiao's passing
than I am.
Your mother's been gone for years.
I've been busy with work.
Auntie Zhou has always been
taking care of you.
You treated Xiao as your sister.
I should've noticed sooner.
It's not your fault.
Since Xiao started
dating that gangster,
she hasn't come home.
It must be that guy
who got her into drugs.
Dad,
I have to go.
Auntie.
Ran.
Auntie,
what's the name of that guy?
Huang Jiahui.
Who is it?
Hurry up.
Police. Don't move!
What's the matter?
Don't move!
What's up?
What's happening?
You've got the wrong person.
Officer.
I told you it's not...
It's not me.
Hurry up.
Sir.
You've got the wrong person.
Get in.
Slow down.
You're breaking my arm.
Get going.
This was later found at the scene.
The murderer is likely from out of town,
arriving by train on the 2nd.
[Suspect:? Huazhou]
Has the coroner's report come in yet?
The report has been sent here.
The man who fell was Song Wen.
The one upstairs was Song Wu.
They're brothers.
Both were security guards
at the Dongtie Glass Factory.
Song Wu had multiple stab wounds
and died from excessive blood loss.
Song Wen also had knife injuries.
But the cause of death
is still under analysis.
We're not sure if he was alive
when he fell.
What about the one who got away?
We haven't found him.
The tech department
is currently comparing
the third person's fingerprints
with those of all the factory workers.
Oh, right,
take a look at this.
This.
These shoes are
part of the standard issue
from that factory.
At the scene,
apart from the murderer's shoe prints,
only these shoe prints were found.
Both are size 42.
They match those brothers' sizes.
Besides that,
the tech department
hasn't found anything new.
We can only wait.
Is the reporter here?
What's his name again?
Jiang Xiaohai.
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
We just want to ask you some questions.
Have some water.
In the statement,
you said you saw a stranger
that day, right?
Yes.
A new face.
Not from our factory.
Then why did you let him in?
They came by car.
"They"?
Song Wen was driving.
Hai, open the gate.
Wu, why are you here so late?
A guest was visiting us.
Don't worry.
What did the guy look like?
Did you get a good look?
It was too dark.
I could only tell he was young.
In early twenties.
What about his build?
Build...
He looked about my size.
Was there
anything odd?
They didn't talk much.
They seemed pretty serious.
They got out of the car
and went up to the White Building.
You saw them get out of the car?
Yes, I did.
How tall was he?
You mean the stranger?
He was a bit shorter
than the two brothers.
About 1.6 to 1.7 meters.
Oh,
when they drove in,
I saw the person in the backseat
holding a bag
really tightly.
What kind of bag?
About this size.
Bigger than a typical bag.
How did you know
something happened upstairs?
I was almost asleep.
Around midnight,
I heard an argument upstairs.
Couldn't make out
what they were arguing about.
It sounded like a fight.
I didn't want to get involved initially.
I was too tired.
Then shortly after,
there was an even louder noise
from the back of the building.
So I got up, put on my clothes,
and went to check.
Chill out.
We're at the public security bureau.
Don't be afraid.
Alright, that's about it.
Thank you for your cooperation.
You can go back now.
If you remember any more details,
feel free to contact us.
Yes, sir.
Take it easy.
Help!
Help me!
We had a new discovery.
When the medical examiner
cut open Song Wen's clothes,
he found a small pocket inside.
The substance in the pocket
seemed to be drugs.
It has been sent for analysis.
When they drove in,
I saw the person in the backseat
holding a bag
really tightly.
[Drug Dealing]
[Drug Dealing, Profit Splitting?]
A black backpack was missing
from the scene,
likely taken by the murderer.
It probably contains drugs.
That makes sense.
The cash at the scene
must be drug money.
Another drug trafficking case?
What's been going on lately?
These drug dealers
are getting out of control.
Negative?
Negative.
We busted them right at the deal.
Huang Jiahui was obviously
high as a kite.
But we couldn't find anything.
Is the urinalysis only for heroin?
Maybe he
used other drugs?
We suspect
he used a new drug
that's not within our
current testing range.
A synthetic drug.
Meth?
Exactly.
We do suspect it's meth.
But this type of meth is new.
Our current testing technology
is outdated.
If we had sent all the evidence
for testing elsewhere,
by the time
we got the results,
Huang Jiahui might have already fled.
What can we do?
My back hurts.
Li,
thanks for your hard work.
Bye.
Officer,
I told you it was a misunderstanding.
Are you the guy
from downstairs that day?
You reported me, didn't you?
What do you want?
Go away.
We know each other.
It's okay.
Wastrel.
What did you say?
I said you're a wastrel.
I've done my research.
Your name is Huang Jiahui.
Middle school dropout,
no skills,
lazy all day,
no job,
just living off women's money, right?
Hey, don't be so cocky.
How can I compare with you?
I'm studying at the police academy.
You're in the underworld.
Besides taking drugs and fighting,
what else can you do?
You...
What?
If I were your parents,
I'd regret having a son like you
for life.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Stop him!
What did you say?
Stop him.
Take him back!
Arrest him.
Say that again!
Shut up!
Wait till I get out.
Wait till I get out, brat.
What are you doing?
Are you alright?
Hey,
how long would someone
be locked up if they started a fight
at the police station?
You did it on purpose?
Aren't you worried he might run away?
No way he can get away here.
But it might not last
until the test results come back.
The lab where my dad works
is a qualified testing organization.
And I have the expertise
to assist
in improving efficiency.
You can have someone oversee
the entire process.
Could you help me get an opportunity?
What do you say, Professor Gu?
I've worked with the police a lot.
But meth is different
from traditional drugs.
And different types of meth
have variations
in their production processes.
Our current technology
and equipment are limited.
So, we can't detect it
in such a short time.
Our lab technician said the same thing.
Indeed.
So we can only wait
for the report from elsewhere.
Thank you for your help, Professor Gu.
It's okay.
I'll bring my colleague back.
Get some rest.
Let my son try.
He's more persistent than me.
He also wants to seek justice
for his sister.
Let him try.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
Bei, do you think they might have
made a mistake?
With so many people on the train
and meth being a new type of drug,
it's normal if someone missed it.
Not likely.
Those guys are veterans.
They are experienced.
Even if they haven't seen meth,
they've seen plenty of
heroin and ecstasy.
He was carrying a large bag.
They couldn't have missed that.
Then what's the problem?
We have our guys at the train station.
Technically, they wouldn't
let him pass easily.
I'm thinking
the guy from Huazhou
might not have come alone.
He had accomplices.
But that security guard,
Jiang Xiaohai,
said that apart
from Song Wen and Song Wu,
the murderer was the only stranger
entering the factory.
Just because he entered
the factory alone that night,
doesn't mean he didn't have
accomplices outside.
Besides, we can't fully
trust Jiang Xiaohai.
You think he's lying?
His recollection seemed too clear.
What did the person following him say?
Sun has been following him these days.
Nothing unusual so far.
Give it to me.
Let me keep it for you.
Who wants this stuff?
Hey.
What time is it now?
It's past six in the morning.
I'll go get you breakfast.
What would you like?
Don't bother.
You should contact the bureau.
Why?
The test results are out.
Let me take a look.
Absolutely not.
It has to be handed over
to Officer Zheng.
It's fine. Let me take a look.
What are you talking about?
Bei, you're back.
This is our captain.
Officer Zheng,
I'm from the Testing Center.
Director Gao asked me
to deliver this report.
Where's Director Gao?
He's in a meeting
with municipal officials.
[Identification Report]
He wanted you to look at this first.
Alright.
This is the test report of the drug
found on Song Wen's body.
The main component of the evidence is
methamphetamine hydrochloride,
also known as solid meth.
You cracked it?
The main component is
methamphetamine hydrochloride.
Here's the complete test report.
Also, based on the
various component levels,
I've drafted a formula
for your reference.
And the purity is extremely high.
I'm heading back to the bureau
to get a search and arrest warrant.
Is that what Director Gao
went to the meeting for?
Exactly.
Alright, I understand.
Then I'll be leaving.
Wait.
Amine? Hydrochloride?
What... What is this?
You look so serious.
Is there a problem?
This is meth.
- What?
It's in Halan?
Meth?
I've only seen it
on the news and reports.
It's a new type of drug, right?
Similar to ecstasy?
It's indeed a new synthetic drug.
But its harm is much greater
than that of ecstasy.
We've only found
this small package so far.
No one knows how much of it
is circulating throughout Halan.
The murderer carried such a large bag
when he escaped from the White Building.
If it was full of this stuff,
how much would there be?
That'd be a lot.
Bei,
you've arrested
the most drug dealers and users.
How is this made?
I catch drug dealers.
I don't make drugs.
How would I know how it's made?
Ask something helpful.
When I
went to
the provincial bureau for training,
they mentioned
that opium,
marijuana,
and heroin
are all
plant-based drugs.
Their yield depends on the weather,
like crops.
So, what about drugs
like meth
and ecstasy?
They are chemically synthesized drugs.
You can make them
in any lab.
The yield can be enormous.
Highly profitable.
My goodness.
Meth's been around
in the south since 1991,
so it's not shocking
it's here now.
Not shocking?
There's nothing normal about it.
No drugs is what's normal.
You're a cop. Quit that mindset.
I'm telling you,
I can't control what happens elsewhere.
But in Halan,
if there's drug dealing,
we shut it down.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
That night,
the police found a large amount
of unsold meth at Huang's residence.
Huang and his accomplices were arrested.
Based on Huang's statement,
the Huayun District police
followed the lead
and finally took down
a major drug ring
with a severe impact.
New drug crimes
have been on the rise
in the last two years.
It's all over now.
It's not.
Every time I close my eyes,
I see her lifeless face.
Son,
you've done everything
you could.
When I was young,
I couldn't protect Mom.
Now I couldn't protect my sister.
In the end, I'm the useless one.
Have you read the report?
Director Gao,
I've been a detective for years.
And you've seen it,
no criminal I've got my eyes on
ever gets away unscathed.
Right?
No matter what drugs
they're trafficking,
we just need to catch them.
Cheer up.
I'll resolutely
follow your instructions.
I really admire your attitude, kid.
What else can I do?
The bureau has already
reported the situation to higher-ups.
Due to the severity of this case,
they've decided to
form an investigation team
and appoint you as the leader
to specifically handle this case.
It's not just about solving
this murder case.
The bigger concern
is the drug trafficking ring behind it.
In short,
drugs
cannot exist in Halan.
Absolutely.
But we
still have
other cases pending in our team.
If I leave,
what about those kids?
You're acting like a kid.
They're all in their
thirties and forties.
What?
Can't they function without you?
Isn't it just the ecstasy case?
I've got Xiong and the team
keeping an eye on it.
If needed,
you can lend a hand.
Director Gao,
I was just discussing
with Xiong and the team
that we don't have
a dedicated anti-drug unit.
Meanwhile,
in the Major Crimes Unit,
I'm the one who's caught
the most drug dealers.
Xiaoguang has learned something from me.
If we're putting together
an investigation team,
we need the best people.
You're quick on the uptake.
Who do you have in mind?
Tell me.
First, we need
a forensic expert.
The fingerprint comparison result
for the murderer
at the White Building
still hasn't come out.
It's holding us back.
We need to improve efficiency.
So we definitely
need a forensic expert.
Also,
we need someone tough.
This murder case shows
dealing with these drug dealers
involves confrontations.
We need someone who can take charge,
fight,
and has good physical abilities.
Right?
What do you think of this lineup?
So we're bringing in two new colleagues.
A forensic expert
and a good fighter?
You got it.
Where are they?
In the conference room.
Look at his build.
It's impressive.
Truly a good fighter.
Look at his muscles.
Ding Guozhu!
Criminal Tech Department. Ding Guozhu,
reporting in.
I'm Zheng Bei.
Hello, Captain Zheng.
Welcome to the investigation team.
Thank you.
Hello, I'm Zhao Xiaoguang.
Hello, Xiaoguang.
Nice to meet you.
You're from the tech department?
With your build,
I thought you were a boxer.
Boxing, wrestling, Sanda,
I can't do any of that.
But I'm decent at calisthenics.
You're wasting your talents.
Well...
What do you know?
He graduated
from a criminal police academy.
He's a forensic expert.
My apologies.
So
where is the fighter?
She should be here soon.
Are you sure you want her?
Yes.
In the past two years, she arrested
about half of the criminals
for the Jiangtie bureau.
She's a good fighter.
Yes, she is.
But her personality...
Don't worry.
I'm her senior.
I can handle her.
A female officer?
I didn't see that coming.
I'm quite excited.
Well, don't be.
Why?
Haven't you heard of Zhang Xueyao?
Who is she?
Do I know of her?
"Mad Dog Yao"
from Jiangtie bureau.
Mad Dog Yao?
Bei.
I know you're skilled.
But try to be serious.
Forget it.
I still lose to you every year.
What were you talking about?
Let me in on it.
Nothing much.
But I did hear "mad dog".
We were praising you.
Now, let me formally introduce you.
This is my junior.
Zhang Xueyao, the city's Sanda champion.
Alright, that's enough.
If there's any major arrest operation,
I'll apply to the bureau
for reinforcements.
Bei, is it just us
in the investigation team?
When do we start the investigation?
There's one more person.
Let me recommend someone.
Mr. Gu from the Investigation Department
at Huazhou Police Academy.
He's also a seasoned drug expert.
I asked him to join
the investigation team.
But
he's not very interested.
And his colleagues there
don't want him to go.
That's fine.
We shouldn't
trouble that old man
to come all the way here.
Right?
He's not that old.
It's not about age.
Capturing drug dealers
doesn't require
a teacher, does it?
It doesn't?
Can you tell
which of these two bags
contains crystal sugar
and which contains meth?
I can't.
Neither can I.
Both contain crystal sugar.
People often think
all we do as cops is make arrests.
Some of the younger officers,
full of adrenaline,
can be a bit impulsive.
But you're different, Zheng Bei.
You're not a hothead.
I've watched you grow.
Ever since you graduated
from the police academy,
it took you a year to make detective,
five years to reach the first rank,
and now you're already
a Chief Inspector.
You've faced countless challenges,
earning countless merits.
You're probably
the youngest detective captain in Halan.
You know better than I do
that solving cases relies
on intelligence and knowledge.
Director,
I'm not saying that
drug knowledge isn't important.
But our job
is too dangerous.
To put it bluntly,
we could die at any moment.
You want a chemistry expert
who's never made an arrest
or been to a crime scene
to capture drug dealers?
Isn't it just asking for trouble?
He may not have been on a mission,
but you have.
Will you just stand by
when danger arises?
What? Am I his bodyguard?
Don't give me that nonsense.
Let me put it this way,
our country is determined
to eradicate drug crimes
and is planning to establish
specialized anti-drug units.
Soon,
Halan
will form its own anti-drug detachment,
and you're on the first list
of candidates.
These are Professor Gu's records
of helping the Yuedong police
with drug cases over the years.
Take a look.
Alright.
I don't need to read them.
You're determined.
So I'll follow your lead.
You said
he wasn't very interested.
You need to put in some effort.
You go invite him.
Me?
Yes.
I've informed the higher management.
You need to go to Huazhou.
I... You...
Get your ticket now. I'll reimburse you.
Fine, thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
[Huazhou People's Police Academy]
Excuse me,
is this the teaching building?
Yes.
Thank you.
Come in.
Hello.
I'm looking for Mr. Gu
from the Investigation Department.
That's me.
You are
Mr. Gu?
Yes, I am.
That's fine.
We shouldn't trouble
that old man to come all the way here.
He's not that old.
You're Mr. Gu, the chemistry expert?
He played a crucial role
in successfully cracking
the coastal meth case back in 1993.
[Gu Yiran, Date: 3rd April, 1993]
Son,
Mr. Chen told me
you've applied to the academy
to establish a lab.
Yes, for specialized research
on new types of drugs.
Dad,
I want to stay on as a teacher.
Hello, I'm Gu Yiran.
Nice to meet you.
♪Memories fade, hidden in snow♪
♪Unclear paths, where do they go?♪
♪Voices speak, nothing to show♪
♪I can't hear my heart's flow♪
♪Time chases, past and future blend♪
♪Ambition and doubt contend♪
♪Facing the game♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Who sheds their blood with such pain?♪
♪Who writes a story
of endless ruins in vain?♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Whose blood and sweat♪
♪Is painting the vivid pictures
in this tale?♪