Get out.
Stand here.
Get moving.
[Producer Zhang Yimou]
[The First Shot]
[Episode 4]
Lele.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
Am I late?
No,
I got here early.
I thought I'd tidy things up a bit.
Where did you
get this gigantic blackboard?
I applied to Mr. Gao for it.
Now that you're here,
help me move away this small one.
We'll use it
in class.
Will do.
Alright, push it over here.
Okay.
Push it back.
Keep going.
Okay, thanks.
You're a persistent guy.
My dad just fried these.
Give them a try. They taste great.
Thanks.
There you are.
I can barely recognize this place!
What happened?
Who did all this?
What a transformation,
right?
Good morning.
Mr. Gu.
Zheng Bei,
your desk is over there.
Which one's yours?
I'll be in the lab.
Guozhu,
the food serving area
looks good for research,
so I moved your stuff there.
Wait a second, Mr. Gu.
I've put
your microscope here.
Mr. Gu,
you really put in the effort.
It was just a quick tidy-up.
Thank you so much.
Look,
although he's also wearing a white coat,
he doesn't look like a food server.
And who does?
Uncle.
If Uncle hears you,
he won't give you any food.
[Drug trafficking & profit splitting]
Here's what we know so far.
[Suspect]
[Huazhou]
The killer got on the train
from Huazhou on the 31st.
He somehow avoided
the railway police
and made it to Halan on the 2nd.
Then he got into the car
of the victims, Song Wen and Song Wu.
The killer brought drugs for a deal,
but something went wrong
during their transaction,
leading to a conflict.
As a result, Song Wen
was pushed off the building and died,
and Song Wu was stabbed to death.
Therefore,
Song Wen and Song Wu
were probably
the local drug distributors
or drug dealers here.
What do you call drug dealers
in your hometown?
Pushers.
So, pushers.
They were two pushers, got it?
So Song Wen and Song Wu
weren't just two security guards
at the glass factory.
The factory was just a cover?
Since they dared to deal in the factory,
maybe the other employees knew about it.
Where's the roster we asked for?
Show it to me.
Where is it?
Here it is.
Not bad. Very organized.
I didn't have anything to do here,
so I tidied up a bit.
[Duty Roster]
This doesn't add up.
According to the duty roster,
Song Wu was on duty
on the night of 2nd April.
So?
Wasn't Jiang Xiaohai the reporter?
Yes,
the case file says
he claimed he was on duty that night.
So Jiang Xiaohai lied.
He wasn't on duty that night,
and he shouldn't have been
at the glass factory.
So
these two brothers,
Song Wen and Song Wu,
purposely chose the night
Song Wu was on duty
to do the deal at the factory.
That way,
no one would find out.
They might have thought that way.
So what was Jiang Xiaohai up to?
He seems very suspicious.
What are you reading?
Detailed records
on the factory's security guards,
including their history
before joining the factory.
I got them here yesterday afternoon.
Is there anything on Jiang Xiaohai?
One moment.
Here it is.
He has a criminal record.
Assault inflicting serious injury.
He spent five years in Zhanzhou in 1990.
Bei.
Yes?
I found something.
I think there was a fourth person
at the crime scene.
What?
The blood on this shoe print
belongs to Song Wu.
The pattern
matches the factory-issued boots.
Based on the curvature
of this half print,
I reconstructed the outline
of the entire print.
According to my reconstruction,
the shoe size isn't 42.
It's 40.5 or 41.
So besides the brothers and the killer,
there was a fourth person
at the scene that night?
So
this person in factory-issued boots
wasn't Song Wen or Song Wu.
Exactly.
That doesn't make sense.
We've looked into all the employees
of the glass factory.
They all have solid alibis.
Besides the victims
and the killer,
no one else had been
to the white building that night.
One person did.
[Criminal Profile: Jiang Xiaohai]
I didn't mean to keep this from you.
But you did keep it from us.
Why did you lie?
Because I panicked.
I was afraid you'd think
I was the killer.
You thought we'd think
you were the killer?
If you didn't do it,
why would we think that?
You were at the crime scene,
and you lied to us.
I suspect you were
directly involved in this case.
What were you doing at the factory
on the night of 2nd April?
During the day,
I overheard Song Wen and Song Wu talking
about a big deal
that could earn them tens of thousands.
What kind of deal?
They didn't say.
They just said that Song Wu should
be ready to open the door at night.
So you sneaked in at night?
I didn't.
I hid in the factory after work
to see what they were up to.
Jiang Xiaohai,
think carefully
before you answer me.
Song Wen drove
that Yuedong guy to your factory,
and Song Wu opened the door for them,
right?
Right.
Did you see it?
Yes.
When did they arrive at the factory?
At 11:40 PM.
That's very specific.
I checked my watch.
Then what happened?
They got out of the car
and went straight
into the white building.
All three of them got out
and went into the white building?
Yes.
And then?
Then they went into Room 505.
What did they do afterward?
I was hiding in the corridor,
and I heard them arguing inside.
After a while, it sounded
like a fight broke out.
Jiang Xiaohai.
The room had gone quiet by then.
Help me.
Help.
Then I heard...
Song Wen's voice.
I failed to hold on to him
even though I used all my strength.
Why didn't you tell us
about this last time?
If I had,
you...
you would've thought
I was one of the killers.
Look,
here's a new file.
I'm so thirsty.
But there isn't any water.
So this guy witnessed the whole thing.
Why didn't he call the police?
He said he was scared
and didn't want any trouble.
You should've seen him.
I couldn't stand him.
This family we visited
lives on the north side
of the staff residential compound,
on the fourth floor,
so they had a clear view
of the back of the white building.
Did both he and his wife
see what happened?
Yes.
Guess what?
The guy got up to pee at midnight
and saw Song Wen
hanging outside the window,
about to lose his grip.
Then he saw Jiang Xiaohai rush over
and grab Song Wen.
And then?
Then
comes the crazy part.
The guy watched the whole thing,
and instead of calling the police,
he brought his wife over
to "enjoy the show."
Looks like Jiang Xiaohai
didn't lie this time.
He held on to Song Wen for a while.
Then the power went out,
and then Song Wen fell off.
Did they witness the entire fight?
How can we be sure
that Jiang Xiaohai
wasn't involved in the fight?
I've got all the forensic evidence.
The murder weapon wasn't cleaned.
Only the killer's,
Song Wen's, and Song Wu's
fingerprints are on it.
Back at the Major Crimes Unit's office,
I had Sun tail Jiang Xiaohai
for a few days.
We also checked
his household registration records.
Nothing unusual came up.
So how do we categorize what he did?
A failed attempt at heroism?
That,
and withholding information
from the police.
Let him go.
Report this to Mr. Gao,
and see if a lecture is needed.
Either way, it's no longer our concern.
Something's off here, Bei.
What we initially hypothesized
at the crime scene
was that the murderer
pushed Song Wen off the building,
killing him,
and then stabbed Song Wu to death
before escaping down the fire escape.
But now it seems
that when Jiang Xiaohai arrived,
Song Wen was still alive.
Would the killer really run off
without making sure he was dead?
I just reviewed the footprint analysis.
The killer's steps were uneven,
and the strides were irregular.
This suggests he was either exhausted
or already injured.
So even if he saw Song Wen hanging there
when he reached the ground,
he probably wouldn't have gone back.
That makes sense.
[Jianpeng General Store]
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
The murderer
must be on the run now.
I've already sent people
to the major intersections
to check everyone passing by.
Now, we wait.
All the drug money was left
at the white building.
If he wants to find a place to hide,
the quickest way
is to sell the drugs he has for money.
Being new to this place,
he's unlikely to sell them in bulk.
Instead, he'll probably
split them into small packs
and cash them out quickly.
Guozhu,
Guozhu!
What are you doing?
Are you even listening?
We're having a meeting here.
Why are you staring at that sausage?
Is that Yuedong guy
in there or something?
Maybe he really is.
Just eat it! What nonsense.
Gosh.
Listen.
The local police station received
a call from a store owner.
The tech team went there
and lifted two fingerprints,
but they didn't take them seriously.
They thought it was from someone
who had a nosebleed
and accidentally smeared the surface.
But these two fingerprints look
increasingly familiar to me.
I think they belong to the Yuedong guy.
That would be too much of a coincidence.
You're trying too hard
to crack the case.
The odds are...
The Yuedong guy has a distinctive whorl
on his middle finger
and unique loops on his thumb.
I paid special attention to them.
I have a habit of using
objects around me
to remember fingerprint patterns.
To me, the folds of this rye bread
and this sausage
look just like his fingerprints.
Let me see.
Look,
the curves go upward to the right.
Rye bread and a sausage?
You technicians
have such a unique way of thinking.
Do they really resemble fingerprints?
They do! Look closer!
See the curvature?
Hey, don't eat my evidence!
What evidence?
Bei, she ate my evidence!
Can you two stop bickering
like kids?
Why do you have to eat his sausage?
This is meat,
and I'm hungry.
Where is that store located?
Near Boiler Plant
No. 2 Elementary School.
Near that school, huh?
That's indeed
not far from the glass factory.
Not far at all.
If he left
the glass factory and headed north,
he'd reach the lumberyard, right?
Then he might have passed by that store
on his way downtown.
Go compare the fingerprints.
Very impressive, Ding Guozhu.
You've got sharp eyes.
These really are
the killer's fingerprints.
See?
The match is crystal clear.
These fingerprints
have helped us narrow down
the search area,
saving us a lot of time.
Our team is really
full of talent.
Bei, you've got
to buy us dinner tonight.
I've treated you to dinner
eight times this month,
and you still want more?
I only have 30 yuan left.
Tell me what I can buy you guys.
Just joking.
I just wanted to express
how thrilled I was.
Give some to Mr. Gu.
I'm good. Thanks.
My dad made this himself.
It's super tasty. Have a try.
It's great.
Try some.
The coating on popcorn machines
contains lead.
Eating too much popcorn
can lead to chronic lead poisoning,
which damages
the nervous and digestive systems.
I suggest you cut back on it too.
I've been eating it since I was a kid,
and I'm just fine!
Stop making stuff up!
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Gu is just concerned
about your health.
Why are you getting so upset?
Mr. Gu, don't worry about it.
He won't be here for long.
Just ignore him.
Alright.
Don't listen to him. Let's eat.
Come on. Eat up.
Alright, enough with the digression.
Aren't things serious enough already?
Is this the time to snack?
Let's make
the store
the center,
and start a search
within a five-kilometer radius.
[Arcade]
Drug dealers prefer
to sell drugs in places
where all sorts of people gather,
such as arcades, pool halls,
skating rinks, karaoke bars,
and dance halls.
Check those places.
Not only does he need to sell drugs,
but he also needs to eat and sleep,
so check
small inns,
bathhouses,
[Longyun Inn Check-in Records]
and hair salons too.
So what's the plan?
Are you joining us
for the on-site investigation?
My paperwork just went through.
I'm officially part
of the special investigation team now.
It went through?
Great.
Then let me give you
your first lesson
in on-site investigation today.
Lesson one:
Stop acting like this.
You're too tense.
Move around.
Dance a bit.
Dance, see?
What should I do?
Drink and dance.
See how they dance?
Feel the vibe.
Fine, I'll drink. You dance.
Lesson two:
Never drink on the job.
What's in the bottle?
I just filled it
with tap water in the restroom.
Sedimentation and filtration alone
can't purify tap water.
Chlorine dioxide is required too.
Yeah, yeah.
Just make do with it for now.
Learn the ropes and blend in.
I'll go chat with someone.
Is he the guy from the Pattaya Hotel?
He's got a lot of info.
Bei, I've asked around,
but no one's heard
of anyone selling small packs of meth.
Then why are you here?
Didn't you say
to keep an ear out for other news?
What is it?
A stranger has been selling
Red Dragon on the down-low.
Is he from the south?
I'm not sure.
I haven't met him.
Find out where this guy
has been.
Keep an eye on him,
and report back to me with anything new.
I'll definitely keep an eye out
to help with the investigation!
Alright, go have some fun.
Bei, how about a dance with me?
Biao,
do you know anyone who sells this?
Bro, that chain of yours is dope.
Do you think I'd look cool wearing it,
like one of those gangsters?
This is a genuine piece
of Hong Kong merchandise.
It's 24k gold.
You can't buy this quality
around here.
No wonder it's so nice.
So it's from Hong Kong!
I'm sure we can work something out.
[Halan Yifeng Taxi Company]
Where to?
Shujing Road Department Store.
That's not close.
I can give you a receipt
for reimbursement.
Just tell me how much you want on it.
Just run the meter.
Feeling warmer now?
Much better.
Judging from your accent,
you're from Yuedong, right?
So many cops are over there.
Monkey, what do we do now?
Come on.
Let's go back and tell the boss.
What brings you to Halan
in this freezing cold?
For a big deal?
No, just some small business.
You Southerners are so modest.
That bag of yours looks pretty full.
Is it packed with cash?
Don't worry.
There are no bad guys around here.
[Yifeng Taxi Company]
Catch him!
Don't let him get away!
Stop!
You won't be able to escape!
Useless.
You messed up a sure thing!
Erjin,
I was already being cautious.
I thought nothing could go wrong
with him in our garage
and the three of us could handle him.
But that guy, Liang,
was really tough.
He's definitely been trained.
I was no match.
Even Laosi might not have been able
to handle him.
If he were easy to deal with,
Song Wen and Song Wu wouldn't have
been killed by him.
Erjin, have a drink to calm down.
I've already sent people out
to look for him.
We lost him near our garage.
Our men are everywhere.
We'll find him for sure.
I've got people watching
the Shujing Department Store.
They'll let me know immediately
if there's any news.
How could you lose him on our own turf?
You may not care about your reputation,
but I care about mine.
Find him and shut him up
before the cops catch him.
Hong Kong will soon
return to the motherland...
I advance the pawn.
Hong Kong is returning to China soon.
Will we be able to travel there?
Why not?
Why? Do you want to go?
You'll need to get
a permit from the police.
A permit?
Hey, Bei.
What's up, sir?
I want to go to Hong Kong.
Hong Kong? That's so far away.
You should go to Tieling first.
Tieling?
You little brat.
Bei,
my TV's gone wrong again.
Could you come by later to check it?
Sure,
I'll come over after work.
Take this.
What is it?
Black fungus
from the mountains in my hometown.
They're very nutritious.
Have your parents try them.
Okay. Thanks, Ma'am.
Hello?
Hello, Zheng Bei.
Near Zhenxing Road,
someone reported
he had spotted
a suspicious out-of-towner.
Okay, got it.
Got it.
I'm on my way.
How much do you sell it for?
I don't sell it. It's for myself.
You finished those two packs
from yesterday already?
Give me one more pack, man.
No money, no goods.
I think it's this building.
Are you sure he's from Yuedong?
He sounded like it.
He bought breakfast from me yesterday.
Anyway, I'm sure he's from the south.
Do you know which entrance he uses?
Yeah.
Come on, I'll show you.
Great.
My friends and I are members
of the residents' committee.
We always patrol the area
after packing up at night
and keep an eye out
for strangers.
That's so selfless of you.
It's nothing,
just part of our duties.
You're the ones who handle
the real troublemakers.
Right.
Is it this way?
I think so.
It's the second entrance.
That one?
I saw him go in there.
Okay, got it.
Thank you so much.
Let me give you a hand.
It's alright.
I got this.
There you go.
Go ahead and do your job.
Thank you.
No problem.
Give it to me!
- Give it to me!
- It's mine!
Give it to me!
What's going on here?
Stop fighting!
Don't move!
Drop the knife!
Drop it!
Let go!
Stop running!
Are you insane?
What's going on?
Stay back!
Uncle!
Drop the knife.
Drop the knife!
Stay back!
Come any closer, and I'll kill her!
Uncle!
Step back!
If you don't, I'll kill her!
Let her go. I won't go after you.
Back off!
Uncle.
♪Memories fade, hidden in snow♪
♪Unclear paths, where do they go?♪
♪Voices speak, nothing to show♪
♪I can't hear my heart's flow♪
♪Time chases, past and future blend♪
♪Ambition and doubt contend♪
♪Facing the game♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Who sheds their blood with such pain?♪
♪Who writes a story
of endless ruins in vain?♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Whose blood and sweat♪
♪Is painting the vivid pictures
in this tale?♪