Boss, there are cops ahead.
Just traffic cops. Don't be afraid.
Just drive normally,
like you always do.
Boss,
we got a message from Vladivostok.
They said if we pay enough money,
they can get us out anytime.
But their price is a bit steep.
The cops raided our place.
Where are we supposed to get money now?
When I started hustling in my teens,
all I had was
the protective amulet
my mom gave me.
Everything I've got today
is earned with my fists.
Money?
As long as you're ruthless enough,
you can get as much as you want.
[Producer Zhang Yimou]
[The First Shot]
[Episode 14]
You can go now.
Okay.
The dishes are good today.
You chat with him first.
I'll start eating. I'm starving.
I'm hungry too.
Let's talk quickly
so we can all eat.
Talk about what?
About Qin Yi.
There's nothing to say.
Just say what you know.
I don't know anything.
What do you want me to say?
Do you know
what kind of sentence you could face
for smuggling, transporting,
selling drugs,
violently resisting inspection,
and arrest
if the case is serious?
You could get 15 years,
life imprisonment,
or even the death penalty.
So you know that.
You seem pretty familiar
with criminal law.
If you're in this line of work,
you've got to know a bit.
Do you realize
you still have a choice
rather than these sentences?
If you provide us
with useful information,
it could be considered a contribution.
Dude,
are you seriously
using lines from TV dramas?
No worries.
I think the food here isn't bad,
right?
It's pretty comfortable here.
I'm in no rush
to leave.
It can be even more comfortable.
We even brought you some food.
Look.
The kitchen made this just for you.
How is it?
Smells good, right?
The food here isn't bad, is it?
I was afraid you wouldn't talk.
So I prepared it in advance.
Have some?
Sure smells good.
But I really don't know
what you want to hear.
This trick doesn't work on me, dude.
It's fine if it doesn't work.
It's up to you.
I'll leave it here.
Nothing.
I just think
it's a pity.
You've reached this level,
and now you have to take the fall
for your boss.
What's in it for you?
Wouldn't you wonder
why you're the one in here
but not Qin Yi?
I'm fine with it.
What?
You're fine with it?
No problem then.
That's fine.
I have nothing to say about that.
But does Qin Yi
appreciate your sacrifice?
Stop with the useless talk.
Whether he appreciates it or not
is his business.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Look at his determination.
This is what true brotherhood
and loyalty are like.
You're really devoted.
If you're willing, stay here.
I'm tired today anyway.
There's plenty of time ahead.
I'll come check on you when I can.
We'll talk more tomorrow. Let's go.
What are you worried about?
You're
so invested in our case in Halan.
As the team leader, I'm very reassured.
We haven't been able
to extract anything yet.
All the knowledge I learned from books
hasn't been useful.
It's just not used enough.
You've only been
in the interrogation room a few times.
It's already pretty good.
When I first started
interrogating suspects,
every time I came out,
I doubted if I was the one
being interrogated.
Don't try to comfort me.
I mean it.
As you do it more
and get used to it,
you don't have
as many emotions about it.
Sometimes,
experience
can turn into intuition.
So, how should you handle
someone like Erjin,
who's tough to crack?
Understand him more.
Learn about his personality
and preferences
and then ponder slowly.
We have plenty of time.
He won't be able to run away.
Why rush?
You're quite optimistic.
What else can we do?
If all the bad people in this world
were easy to catch and deal with,
we wouldn't be needed.
Let me tell you.
That Erjin guy
is determined,
so he'll keep quiet.
In the interrogation room,
there are all kinds of people.
Some want to confess but hesitate.
Some know
their partners are next door
and will compete to earn merit.
Some are long-time couples
who want to reunite soon
and cooperate actively.
These criminals are also human.
As long as they have dignity
and emotions...
They must have weaknesses
and vulnerabilities.
We can find the breakthrough.
Yes.
Take it slow.
There's no rush.
Even though I've interrogated
so many suspects,
dealing with these big drug dealers
is like crossing a river
by feeling the stones.
Right?
If it doesn't work today,
we'll continue tomorrow.
If not tomorrow, then the day after.
We have plenty of time.
Keep at it.
Right?
That's the spirit.
Don't frown.
This is good.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
I'm going to interrogate Erjin now.
I don't believe it.
Today, even if I have to pry it out,
I'll get the lead
on Qin Yi from Erjin.
Sit down.
I can't, Bei.
Erjin has a fake Qin Yi.
How could he not know
where the real one is?
These people are too cunning.
Because they're so cunning,
we need to use our brains
to handle things.
What can you achieve
with just this approach?
Erjin's using a fake Qin Yi
to mislead us.
He'd rather get caught himself
than let Qin Yi be exposed.
Do you think Erjin will tell you
where Qin Yi is?
What kind of spell
has Qin Yi cast on these people?
They're all risking their lives for him.
Winning people's hearts is their skill.
Qin Yi wouldn't be
in his current position
if he wasn't capable.
That's true.
Decades of smuggling and amassing wealth
have resulted in a room full of gold.
He can't spend it or move it.
Isn't that a pity?
Yes.
Our colleagues who handled the evidence
were exhausted from moving all that gold
to the evidence room.
A person would need
several lifetimes
to earn that much.
Drug trafficking makes a lot of money.
That's why we need to
root out all these cancerous elements.
- Director Gao.
Director Gao.
What's up?
You all look depressed.
Although Qin Yi has escaped,
we have set up roadblocks
across the city.
He can't get out of town.
As long as he's in Halan,
we'll definitely catch him.
On the bright side,
since we started the operation,
we've uprooted
the entire ecstasy chain.
All the Blue Aurora's Lucifer
have been confiscated.
You shouldn't only focus on the failures
and ignore the results.
The case is not closed yet.
Everyone, cheer up.
- Yes, sir!
I have requested
the maximum reinforcement for you.
Zheng Bei, arrange it.
Got it.
From now on...
From now on,
go home and sleep.
Have a good rest.
There will be tough battles ahead.
- Yes, sir!
Listen to the Director.
Awake?
Get up if you're awake.
What for?
Weren't you complaining
about the hard bed?
My sister has aired out
the mattress for you.
Let me replace it for you.
Get up.
I'm good.
What do you mean you're good?
Let me tell you.
The service in the Zheng family
must be up to standard.
So that you have no complaints.
What are you doing today?
Speak up if you have something to say.
Come with me to Yao's house.
What happened to her?
She's fine.
But she is sick in bed.
She visits her parents every week.
I'm going this week on her behalf.
It's understandable to report good news
but not bad news.
Isn't it more convenient
to make a phone call?
No.
Why not?
Just come with me.
This is also a police inspection.
We have to go.
We shouldn't go empty-handed, right?
I've already bought the gifts.
Mr. Zhang.
Mrs. Zhang.
These are gifts for you.
I'll leave them here.
Mr. and Mrs. Zhang.
This is our new colleague
from the bureau.
He's a young man from the south.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Zhang Xueyao's colleague.
My name is Gu Yiran.
Nice to meet you.
Now, let's get to the point.
Go ahead.
They can read lips.
It's a good opportunity for you
to practice your undercover skills.
Express yourself clearly. Now.
Mr. and Mrs. Zhang,
here's the situation.
During our recent operation,
Zhang Xueyao...
She performed exceptionally well.
Yao did an outstanding job this time.
So our bureau
has rewarded her
with a trip to Changbai Mountain.
For seven days.
That's why she won't
be coming back this week.
We're here to check on you.
If you need any help, just let me know.
We'll leave you here.
I'll take him to get something to eat.
Goodbye.
We're leaving.
What were you talking about?
I told you to report good news,
not bad news.
What were you saying there?
I didn't catch on.
Let me explain.
I brought you here to understand
the real situation of everyone.
It's to help you
integrate with everyone.
It's because we consider you
part of our team.
Stop talking inappropriately.
Okay.
Got it.
Why is this candied hawthorn so sour?
Darn it.
It's making my teeth hurt.
What kind of
crappy candied hawthorn is this?
You've ruined my boss's teeth.
Pay up.
This is just the right time.
Where did you little brats come from?
You're here to bully us?
You two young ones,
why don't you learn to behave?
- Beat him.
Get lost.
She has good social connections.
Yao is not simple.
Of course.
I only choose the best people.
I don't count.
I was invited by Director Gao.
How come you don't count?
I tried several times
to get you here.
How can you say that?
Okay.
If you say so.
What do you mean, "if you say so"?
It's the truth.
Let me tell you.
In the eyes of these neighbors,
Yao is like
a heroine.
Look, when there is an issue,
everyone is willing to help.
It shows that Yao
usually protects them a lot.
Kindness is not given for free.
Yes.
It's really not easy
to live in such an environment.
No wonder she has
that kind of personality.
People used to think
she was just a tough
and fierce character.
They kept their distance from her.
But over time,
as they got to know her,
they realized she was actually
a very righteous girl.
She's always known
to protect her own people.
Having people to protect
makes her push herself
to become stronger.
This is quite similar to you.
Mr. Gu,
you also have people
you want to protect, right?
I'm full.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll help her parents pack up.
It's hard to know your true feelings.
Mrs. Zhang,
I'll help you pack up.
Okay.
Turn around and get in the tricycle.
Come on.
Gu, think about
what you want to eat tonight.
After we send them back,
I'll treat you to a meal.
Okay.
Get in the tricycle.
Get in.
You push, I'll ride.
You follow and run.
Let's go.
Go on. Push a bit.
The tricycle
needs some repair.
It's too heavy to ride.
Push slowly.
No. There's no brake.
I've eaten at all the places
around here.
This stall
has been here since we were in school.
I've been eating here since then.
This is our special Halan dish.
This is grilled gluten.
Look over there.
Take this.
It's hot.
Are you going to eat that?
Just give me all of it.
Throw this away for me.
Kebabs.
I want to eat that. Is it okay?
Drooling, huh?
Thanks.
How is it?
Not bad, right?
Do you want anything else?
No, that's enough.
Play a round of shooting.
No need. I just want to watch.
Just a round.
Come on.
Finish eating and give me the skewers.
I'll throw them away.
Sir, two guns.
Okay.
Five yuan each.
Sir.
I want two rounds.
Alright.
Let's see your shooting skills.
Pretty accurate.
Not bad.
That's three shots.
This shouldn't be just luck, right?
Not being able to fight
doesn't mean I can't shoot.
I also graduated
from the police academy.
I didn't hear you say that before.
It's nothing special.
Listen to your words.
Let me tell you,
aiming is disrespectful.
What's the point of aiming?
Don't you just hit the target
when you shoot?
See?
After the case is closed,
will you return to Huazhou?
Why?
Are you trying to drive me away?
Maybe I want you to stay?
You're interrupting me.
Really not.
Anyone who graduates
from the police academy
can hit the target anyway.
[Halan Public Security Bureau]
Over in Huazhou,
more than ten people in total
have been arrested.
That's quite a blow
to the Red Dragon.
The police beauty
hasn't been around for a few days.
The atmosphere here seems off.
Yao, why are you back?
You recovered?
Why didn't you call me to pick you up?
I wanted to give you a surprise.
Wait. Your leg's healed?
What's the big deal?
- It's just a scratch.
- Just a scratch.
Always like this.
What's up, Bei?
Did you get scratched?
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm looking for a gift for Yao.
Catch a break.
This is your discharge gift.
Wishing you good health in the future.
From the Zheng family.
Here.
The smell is quite strong.
Aren't you the Sausage Princess?
Hanging all around.
Sit here.
You wouldn't know.
I was so bored in the hospital.
I almost turned that hospital bed
into a training ground.
Isn't that right?
I had that feeling before.
I'm different from you.
By the way,
how's the investigation going, Bei?
I apply for an immediate return to duty.
Please instruct, Bei.
Return, yes.
This time,
the police in Huazhou have had
a very successful arrest operation.
They sent a briefing.
Including Hao,
a total of 12 crime gang leaders
have been taken down.
They have seized
over 23,000 tablets of Red Dragon
and 1,500 grams of meth.
A large amount of meth
was also seized from Blue Aurora.
The source of Red Dragon
has been completely cut off this time.
Guozhu, how about you?
I review the evidence every day.
No new discoveries yet.
Xiaoguang, what about you?
I was leading a few officers
assigned by Director Gao.
We're canvassing
within a five-kilometer radius
centered around Qin Yi's house.
Indeed, someone saw Qin Yi
getting into a car.
But we don't know where he went.
The license plate was fake.
All major exit points from the city
are also under strict inspection
of all vehicles.
But we haven't found any trace
of Qin Yi yet.
He should still be in Halan.
Qin Yi has earned a house
full of gold bars
but didn't spend any.
Now that trouble has come,
he didn't take the money with him.
He must be unwilling to accept this.
Keep a close watch on him these days.
Yes.
Qin Yi has been hiding for four days.
Erjin must be anxious.
That's exactly what we want.
Mrs. Zheng.
Come on.
Help yourself to the dumplings.
If you need more,
I'll cook more for you.
Would you like some garlic?
Mom, don't bother him.
He's from the south
and isn't used to it.
No, thanks.
Right, Mr. Gu?
Where is your brother?
I'll go get him.
No, don't bother.
Just eat.
I'll take a stroll outside.
What's going on?
Today is a bit special for our family.
Especially for my brother.
Zheng Bei.
Are you standing in the rain like this?
Come with me.
[Happy Little Lucky Star, Summer Gala]
♪Two little tigers, two little tigers♪
♪Running fast, running fast♪
♪One has no ears♪
♪One has no tail♪
♪It's so strange♪
- Three, two, one. Bow.
- Gu, you're all here.
Alright.
Let's go.
Their teacher said
this year's programs are amazing.
They may be young.
But they can perform small plays now.
Next show.
[Happy Little Lucky Star]
The play,
"Little Hero Fights Off
Human Traffickers."
When I was ten years old,
I was a naughty boy.
I often played a game with friends.
"Police and Robbers."
I knew that police officers were brave.
I often greeted them on the street.
But I didn't know
how scary robbers could be.
Until that day...
Next one.
Be quiet.
Not shouting anymore?
Are you going to eat it or not?
Little brat.
Dare to be stubborn with me?
Let me show you how I deal with you.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Open the door!
Let go!
Sit down.
Behave yourself.
Sleep!
Here.
Eat it.
I hid it.
No poison.
It's delicious.
Just eat.
So you can have strength.
Drink it.
But don't wake them up.
They usually can only drink water.
Then why do you have this?
If you pretend to be obedient,
you can get it.
Drink it.
It's very sweet.
Okay, don't drink too much.
It's really sweet.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
You look really cold.
Come over here with me.
It's really warm here.
My name is Lele.
I'm 12 years old.
What about you?
I'm Zheng Bei.
I'm 12 too.
You're 12 too?
You're so tall.
When is your birthday?
January.
Mine's in September.
So I should call you Brother Zheng Bei.
Brother Zheng Bei.
You're so brave.
You actually dared
to resist Big Pockmark.
Can I be your friend?
Here.
At dawn, you all go out and beg.
Whoever gets the most money
will get this lollipop.
Ladies and Gentlemen, please be kind.
Please be kind.
Alright.
You.
Go.
Ladies and Gentlemen, please be kind.
Please be kind.
I haven't eaten for two days.
Please give me some money to buy food.
Good people live long and safe lives.
Helping others brings lifelong joy.
I know you're the cleverest.
Good.
Really good.
Next one.
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Watch them for a while.
You're tough.
You even got chubbier.
Give it a try.
I can't do it.
I'm very dumb. I can't memorize it.
Can't memorize it?
You've been here for two months, right?
Still so stubborn?
Are you asking for a beating?
Are you going to recite it or not?
I just can't.
Fine.
I'll cut out your tongue.
Mutes don't have to speak.
People will pity you
just by looking at you.
Let go.
[Happy Little Lucky Star]
What are you doing?
Go!
Don't look back.
Run as hard as you can.
We just need to run to that forest.
Let's go.
Bei.
I can't run anymore.
It's too far.
Too far.
Do you see that brightest star?
That's the North Star.
As long as we keep heading towards it,
we'll be home soon.
Do you believe me?
But I can't walk anymore.
Lele.
You hold on to this.
I'll pull you, okay?
I will definitely get you to the city.
I'll sing you a song.
It's from a TV show.
♪I'll sing a song♪
♪That old song♪
♪I'll sing softly♪
♪You hum along slowly♪
♪Do you still remember♪
♪Your past dreams?♪
♪Those bright days♪
♪Filled with hope♪
Look.
There's a chimney and lights ahead.
Where?
I don't see it.
You're too short to see it.
If we walk a little further,
you'll see it.
Come on.
We have to hang on.
If we make it, we'll have everything.
Mom and Dad,
popcorn, candied hawthorns,
and hot dumplings.
Hang in there.
Don't move!
Kids, you're safe now.
Welcome home.
[Happy Little Lucky Star, Summer Gala]
It's better if you don't
follow along right now.
This story is about him.
It's just a pity that in reality,
there aren't always happy endings.
We'll soon be eating warm dumplings.
Warm dumplings.
Is anyone there?
Is anyone there? Open the door.
Little brat.
Where is he?
Probably over there.
He must be nearby. Find him quickly.
Lele.
Lele, get up.
They're coming after us.
Get up.
Don't run around.
Wait for me.
Wait for me to come back.
Bei, I'm scared.
Where are you going?
Listen to me, Lele.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
We've already made it through
so many days.
We'll definitely make it home.
Remember.
Don't make a sound.
Wait for me to come back.
I'll definitely come back to get you.
You human traffickers,
I'm right here.
Wait and see.
You little brat.
Run!
Stop right there.
You...
I...
Kid.
When I found him,
he was covered in wounds.
The injuries were festering.
He was cold and hungry.
Making it out from such a distant place
was nothing short of a miracle.
He was in a feverish coma for two days.
The moment he woke up,
he told me there was
another missing child.
He was talking about Lele.
We immediately went to
search near the garbage dump.
But there wasn't a trace of him.
Later, after some inquiries,
an old man said
he'd seen a kid like that.
He felt sorry for him
and gave him something warm to eat
and invited him inside to warm up.
But the kid refused.
He insisted on going back
to the garbage dump.
He said he had to wait for his brother.
He was afraid that if Bei came back
and couldn't find him, he'd be worried.
Can you imagine
how much that kid trusted Zheng Bei?
What happened afterward?
You never found that kid?
At the time, we mobilized
almost the entire police force.
For about half a year.
In the end, all the human traffickers
were caught.
We rescued over ten children.
But Lele wasn't among them.
Later, we found the body
of a 12-year-old boy
in a field
behind the criminals' hideout.
So he probably believes
it's his fault that Lele died.
[Assorted Soda]
The soda is still just as sweet.
But you're always wearing a sad face.
Yeah.
This soda is really sweet.
You always got beaten up.
You were covered in bruises.
But every time you took a sip of soda,
you felt better right away.
You used to tell me
that soda was a painkiller.
Were you just fooling a kid?
You were just a kid yourself.
Let me tell you.
Out of all the kids,
you were the most resourceful.
Even though Big Pockmark was so fierce,
you always managed to trick him
into giving you soda.
That was easy.
All you had to do
was pretend to be obedient
and act like you were on his side.
Being genuinely good to someone
is what's really hard.
I know you were truly good to me.
So, were you really good to me?
The snow was so heavy.
I was so cold.
My hands and feet
were numb with cold.
Why did you leave me?
Why?
Zheng Bei.
Why did you leave me?
Why?
Zheng Bei.
Why did you leave me?
Why?
I'm sorry.
Zheng Bei.
Let's go home.
Still not sleepy?
I'm alright.
I heard from Uncle
that you've been going to
that garbage dump every year
for the past few years.
Yeah.
I can't get over it.
I can't let it go.
I understand.
But, Zheng Bei,
you can't blame yourself like this.
Lele's death was the fault
of those human traffickers.
It wasn't your fault.
The traffickers deserved to die.
But I'm the one who left Lele there.
I told him to wait for me there.
In the end, I ran out
and got found by Uncle.
Now I've grown up,
but Lele is gone.
If I hadn't tried to escape
with him that day...
Forget it.
I'm rambling.
If you keep blaming yourself,
you'll just create
a thousand more "what ifs".
Life is long.
Don't carry all the pain of the past
on your shoulders.
Everyone
has their own fate.
What I need to carry,
I'll carry.
I still dream about him at night.
He just looks at me,
waiting for me.
A life was lost.
How can I just forget about it?
Yeah.
How can you just forget
about a life?
So mysterious.
Is this the good place you mentioned?
We don't have a VCR at home.
We might as well go to a video hall.
Leave it to me.
Look.
This one, and this one
are pretty good.
Zhao Xiaoguang!
Are you an idiot?
Don't you know
using horror movies
to impress girls is outdated?
How about something thrilling?
I've got everything.
Don't brag.
Show me something thrilling.
Take a look.
Let's go for the top-tier stuff.
I'm not short on cash.
Come on.
Check this out.
Three Monks?
Flaming Mountain.
Donald Duck?
That's it?
Boring.
Who watches cartoons?
We're not three-year-olds.
Dance with Ducks.
Fire-Spitting Lady.
The Carnal Sutra.
All starring the most popular actresses.
These three are the hottest right now,
and it's hard to get.
Would you take them?
We definitely would.
Alright.
Police!
You're suspected of
being involved in pornography.
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
In a split second,
I gave Zheng Nan a look.
In a flash, I had an idea.
We played along with the situation.
In no time,
the boss revealed his true colors.
You should've seen it.
Bei's sister
was instantly impressed by me.
Bei.
Aren't you afraid
that Zheng Nan's brother
will knock you out instead?
Yes, I am.
But tell me,
didn't I manage to score
a small win this time?
You did.
I have to say, you're pretty impressive.
Renting a video tape
and you ended up taking
on an anti-pornography case.
I might as well send you to that team.
I think that works.
Absolutely not.
I was born to be part
of the Special Investigation Team,
and I'll die as one
of the Special Investigation Team's
men.
A ghost.
Do you have any sense?
That ghost is behind you.
Stop doing that.
Holy crap.
When did you get here?
You scared the heck out of me.
Could I be more frightening
than a ghost?
Could a ghost be more terrifying
than a drug dealer?
Meeting time.
As of now,
all the people we've caught
have been interrogated one or two times.
But these small-time thugs
know nothing.
That's normal.
They just follow orders
and manage their little area.
The lower-level guys don't have access
to central information.
And knowing nothing
is actually the safest.
What about Erjin?
Still playing mute?
He's definitely a big shot.
He's willing to harm himself.
Now he's lost his teeth
and can't talk.
All we can do
is watch him in frustration.
No need to worry.
Let's see how long he can hold out.
The current situation,
in summary,
is that we have a lot of people
but no useful leads.
I'll report.
Director Gao has sent us
quite a bit of reinforcement.
We've also expanded
our search within the city.
We traced Qin Yi's
previous movements.
We even checked the recently
demolished houses
in the city center.
So far, no new findings.
If Boss Qin is hiding in plain sight,
he's really hard to find.
Qin Yi is cautious.
He handles things meticulously.
He looks approachable,
but he's actually very distant.
Once a person like him
gets close to someone,
it usually means they've established
a very strong trust.
We can start investigating
from this angle.
But doesn't that mean
we still have to interrogate Erjin?
Qin Yi is an old bachelor.
No family, no relatives.
No one else.
He has Jiang Xiaohai.
Isn't he his adopted son?
He wasn't among those
we arrested earlier.
This kid likes to fight,
but he definitely wasn't involved
in drug trafficking.
We even specifically checked
among the security guards
at the glass factory's White Building.
He quit a long time ago
and started working on his own.
Yes.
He's clean.
But that doesn't mean
he's severed ties with Qin Yi.
It all depends
on how strong
their father-son relationship is.
It's hard to say.
If their bond is weak,
they might not be in contact at all.
But if their bond is strong,
he definitely won't cooperate with us.
He'll just say he doesn't know anything.
What can we do then?
Exactly.
And Xiong even arrested him before
for inciting a disturbance.
What if he holds a grudge?
We'll just have to try.
I'll go talk to him.
That's right.
The fact that he could leave Qin Yi
and get a proper job on his own
probably means he took your advice.
It shows
he understands right from wrong.
Keep investigating.
We need to
quickly track down Qin Yi's whereabouts.
♪Memories fade, hidden in snow♪
♪Unclear paths, where do they go?♪
♪Voices speak, nothing to show♪
♪I can't hear my heart's flow♪
♪Time chases, past and future blend♪
♪Ambition and doubt contend♪
♪Facing the game♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Who sheds their blood with such pain?♪
♪Who writes a story
of endless ruins in vain?♪
♪Truth hides, waiting to mend♪
♪Whose blood and sweat♪
♪Is painting the vivid pictures
in this tale?♪