[DRIFTING AWAY]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.]
[Episode 3]
My name is Zhen Zhen.
My story starts
from the year when my mom
pulled some strings to get me
into the top high school in Xuecheng.
A new school
and new classmates
made me think
that would be a new beginning.
However,
it was, in fact, the beginning of my nightmare.
When should I go to your home for tutoring?
It's best on Saturday and Sunday.
Okay, I got it.
I'm leaving.
Be careful on your ride back.
Okay.
What's wrong?
you haven't told me
where you live.
Oh, right.
No. 201, Unit 2.
Okay, I got it.
Bye.
Mom.
Why didn't you knock before entering my room?
It's my own home.
Why should I knock?
How's your schoolwork?
Not bad.
What do you mean by "not bad"?
Not bad means not bad.
I mean it literally.
Don't talk back to me.
Can't you talk to me properly?
People say
there are two types of children.
One type is here to repay the parents' kindness.
The other
is here to collect debts.
You're here to collect debts from us.
When your grandma died,
just because I didn't let you go to her funeral
in the countryside,
you just put on a long face
and ignored me for half a month.
Your grandma's funeral
and your exam clashed.
-What's more important?
-Mom.
I dreamed of Grandma
last night.
That old lady!
Why couldn't she be quiet?
What did she want?
What did she say?
She said she wanted to go home.
I told her it was impossible
because you've removed her from the household registry.
How could she come back?
Then, she cried.
She said she'd come back to you.
Let me think about it.
Today is...
The day after tomorrow…
The 15th.
The day after tomorrow is the 15th.
Go burn some joss paper for your grandma.
Burn more.
Manager, you...
It's late.
Why are you calling me?
Eat the walnuts.
I wasn't talking to you.
What is it?
Tell me.
Zhen Zhen.
This is for you.
No, it's not appropriate.
It's okay. It's fine.
Take it.
But this is…
It can ward off evil spirits.
Why did Zhou Yue give her
his favorite pendant?
Shameless!
She seduced our campus Beau as soon as she transferred here.
I'll teach her a lesson.
Shameless!
What's wrong with you?
What?
What are you doing?
Let go!
Let...
Don't move!
Let me go.
Let go…
Shout out loud.
You have to shout loudly.
Shout!
"Help!" Shout it! Shout it!
She stopped shouting.
What do you want?
Nothing.
You think you're pretty?
You feel so good about yourself.
A country bumpkin like you,
do you really think
you're a match for Zhou Yue?
Do you think Zhou Yue
really likes you?
He doesn't like you anyway.
If I am to
mess up your face,
will Zhou Yue still talk to you?
You hit me?
Beat her!
Don't come over!
Don't come near me!
You're bleeding.
Really.
Let's go.
Let's go to the hospital.
Just you wait!
Let's go.
Kneel.
Kneel!
You're really something now, huh?
You can never make
something of yourself.
You've learned to hit a bottle on people's heads now?
Do you know how much
it cost me?
5,800 yuan!
They surrounded me by the wall,
trying to hit me.
Why didn't they hit others?
You are my mother.
Why are you siding with others?
I'm being reasonable.
You're not being reasonable.
You just care about the money you've spent.
Why am I not being reasonable?
Did you hit someone's head with a bottle
and crack it open or not?
Blood flew on her head.
Is there blood on your head?
They just drew a few lines
on your face with the lipstick.
Listen.
Kneel here.
Think about
what you did wrong.
Try to learn a lesson.
Our money
is not a windfall.
How much did I spend
to get you into this school?
Hello?
Oh my.
Mr. Li!
Why are you
calling me all of a sudden?
Is the test passed so quickly?
Ma'am, I'm Zhen Zhen's classmate.
I'm here to tutor her.
Come in.
Mr. Li, please continue.
Zhen Zhen.
That's great.
Thank you.
This is a good thing.
I'm happy.
Okay.
How about I come…
come back another day?
Okay.
Sure.
Goodbye, Mr. Li.
Hello.
He...
Get up.
What?
You're still in the mood?
Get up.
Before I was ten,
I lived with my grandparents.
I only came to live with you
after I turned ten.
It's barely seven years.
But the seven years
feels longer than a lifetime.
I was beaten up by others today.
You didn't defend me when you came back.
Instead, you punished me.
Every time you get mistreated outside,
you come home and take it out on me.
I'm your daughter,
not your punching bag.
I'm not
the reason why your life failed, either.
What...
My life…
failed?
You kept talking.
Why are you so eloquent?
Use these skills of yours
on your studies.
Make your grades
go up, okay?
Did you do well
in high school?
Did you get 100 on every test?
If you can't do it yourself,
why do you require me to?
I'll have a popsicle.
Okay, 50 cents.
Okay, thank you.
Here.
Here's your change.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Why aren't you at school?
It's none of your business.
You have a bad temper.
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you go to school?
I'm sick.
There's a blood vessel in my brain
that's a bit malformed.
I get spasms when I'm nervous.
By the way,
you haven't told me
why you skipped school.
My mom is sick, too.
I'm doing it to treat her.
What's wrong with your mom?
When I was a top student at school,
she didn't praise me.
Now I'm a bad student,
she scolds me to no end.
It's her who is sick,
but she forced me to take medicine.
Do you think
it is fair?
You're right.
Those people
can't climb the mountain themselves,
but they force their children
to reach the peak.
Aren't they just crazy?
That's right.
That's how
she turned me rebellious.
So, the more she wants to
show off to others,
the more I want to ruin it.
You do have a personality.
It's cold,
and you sit here.
You might get sick.
Go sit in my shop
and warm yourself up.
How about this?
Let me take you to eat something.
These are for you.
What? Walnuts?
Take a look.
Why are you giving me walnuts?
These are the work of my apprentice.
A gift for you.
Well,
you carved really well.
It's nothing.
Are you really giving them to me?
Thank you.
Are you full?
You should go home.
I'm not full yet.
I want to have another burger.
You just don't want to go home.
I'll order one more for you.
You'll have to go back after you eat it.
No wonder she skipped school today.
Turns out she came out
to date another man.
She's so good at flirting.
She really doesn't rest for a single day.
Dad!
You haven't been back for half a month.
I was busy at the construction site.
Wait,
why are you home so late?
Do you realize what time it is?
Why are you back so late?
Why are you coming back later and later?
Stop!
I was talking to you. Didn't you hear me?
When do you want me to come back?
It's always wrong in your eyes whether I come back early or late.
Why don't you set a time?
I'll come back at that time.
I can't even criticize you now?
The kid of one of my colleagues
is of the same age as you.
He can even cook for his mother.
Look at you.
You can't help in anything.
I even have to feed you
after I cook.
Wash your hands first.
Hurry up. Time to eat.
Wash your hands and eat.
Did they pay the remaining balance?
Not yet.
The project has been completed for over half a year.
It's just a small amount of money.
If you were capable,
you would have got it long ago.
Zhen Zhen's cram school costs money, right?
We have to pay the mortgage, right?
You also have to support your father, don't you?
Tell me.
Which one is the priority?
Which can be put off?
I'm not going to the cram school.
Don't waste your money.
Just eat.
I'm really not going.
I won't go even if you sign up.
What?
I spend money on you,
yet I'm the one who is wrong?
Mom,
I sincerely beg you.
Don't spend that money on me.
If I'm in debt,
I can't even walk tall.
Why are you in debt?
Everything you invest in me—
I have to prove they're worth it
by doing well.
I really can't do it.
Did I give birth to you and raise you
just for you to
go against me?
You...
Do you think I want to
waste money on you like this?
If you don't go to cram school,
can you make it to a good university?
My colleague's kid
only went to
cram school for a semester,
and he went from being 20th in class
to 9th place.
If you like other people's kids,
you can take them home
and raise them.
If I knew
what you would be like today,
I wouldn't have given birth to you!
Alright, let's eat.
How did I give birth to
such an ungrateful person?
I transferred you
from a school ranked 20th
to one ranked 4th.
Do you know
how much it cost?
I didn't ask you to transfer schools for me.
In my previous school,
I ranked No. 1 in my grade.
I was fine.
It's you who insisted on transferring me
to this school.
So it's not my fault
that I can't keep up
and my grades dropped.
I'm just stupid.
Half of my stupid genes
are from you.
If I'm a fish
and you insist that I walk on land,
whose fault would that be?
You're asking for it!
Do you dare say it again?
You can't defeat others,
so you use other kids as weapons
to go against your own kid.
Come back.
Come back!
Alright, let's eat.
Here, the food is cold.
What sins did I commit
in my previous life?
How unlucky am I to have ended up
marrying you
and giving birth to her?
The one who just ran into her room
isn't just my daughter,
is she?
Didn't you hear how she insulted me?
Was your mouth glued shut?
Why didn't you dare to say anything?
Why are you blaming me now?
Zhen Yuliang.
Everyone in the world
can blame me,
but you can't.
Why?
Because I've worked hard without complaint
and poured my heart and soul
into our relationship.
And that can't even make you
defend me?
Why am I
the bad guy here?
Let's try to make do, yeah?
If not, let's just divorce!
That man is quite tall.
He seemed to have monolids.
I like monolids.
What did you eat for breakfast?
Hamburger?
Fries?
Or a family combo?
With chicken wings?
Where are you going?
You guys can talk in front of me.
Don't gossip behind my back.
Don't you know your place?
You were just dumped by Zhou Yue,
and you're already
rushing to jump into a rebound relationship…
What nonsense are you talking about?
You're a good student,
yet you skipped class every day
and sneaked out of school.
It turns out you went to
sponge off a man for food.
How was it?
Was it yummy?
I should've done more than hit you with a bottle that day.
Let go of me.
Let go!
-What are you doing?
-Let go of me!
What are you doing?
Nothing, Ms. Chang.
We were just playing.
Go back to your seats.
Okay.
Do you know what the self-study class means?
Let me tell you.
Whether I'm here or not,
you should act in the same way.
Zhen Zhen.
Come to my office.
Why did you quarrel with the property owner again?
You don't know how arrogant she was.
She was so annoying.
She deserves it.
What?
She was practically bullying me.
Should I have praised her for it?
Is she God
and us workers her slaves?
You just passed the test.
Are you trying to ruin your future
just to fight with her?
W-Where are you going?
I haven't finished yet.
I'll go apologize to her.
Okay?
Hello?
Ms. Chang!
It's me.
Well...
What's wrong with Zhen Zhen again?
Ms. Chang.
Mrs. Zhen, you're here.
Have a seat.
Please have a seat.
You, too.
Okay.
I invited you here today
to tell you
something.
When Zhen Zhen was just transferred here,
she was a good student,
but her grades have recently
plummeted dramatically.
Someone even saw her
dating a boy in Qingtan Street.
The school prohibits
students from having relationships.
It's an absolute no-no.
I admit my grades have dropped.
I also admit that I skipped school.
But I won't admit to having a relationship.
You skipped school the day before yesterday
and went on a date with a boy
at a fast-food restaurant on Qingtan Street.
Is that true?
I didn't go on a date.
No?
Other students
have told me!
And you're still denying it?
Who is that guy?
May I ask
what the definition of having a relationship is?
I just had a burger in a fast-food restaurant.
Can that be counted as a relationship?
You adults
were all once my age.
Why are you getting more and more narrow-minded?
I'm asking you!
Who is that guy?
I don't know!
Who are you talking about?
I have no idea!
Stop!
C-Calm down.
Where are you going?
Zhen Zhen.
Where...
Ma'am.
It's you, isn't it?
Don't think I don't know
it's you!
How dare you!
You even dare
go to our home to seduce my daughter!
Huh?
What are you doing?
Do you think we, the parents, are blind
and fools?
Stop it.
We're at school!
Are you a dating tutor?
Mom!
Listen.
Stay away from my daughter!
You...
Otherwise, I won't spare you!
I won't!
I won't spare you!
You loser!
Where are my books?
Novels, painting albums…
Why are they all gone?
I sold them.
You sold them?
I bought those by saving money
for years.
I paid for them.
I can sell them if I want.
You are so unreasonable.
It's useless to reason with you.
How can you be so self-righteous?
Why didn't they hit others?
They just drew a few lines
on your face with the lipstick.
Kneel.
You are my mother.
Why are you siding with others?
I'm being reasonable.
I don't care if you eat.
Open the door!
Come out!
What are you doing?
I'll burn down everything that has a word on it
in your house.
Say it again.
Do you dare say it again?
I'm too ashamed to go to school.
It's useless to keep those things.
I gave birth to you.
Is this how you repay me?
Huh?
You gave birth to me
not because you like me.
It's just because you got pregnant.
You raised me
because it's convenient
to vent your anger on me.
A mother beats her child.
As long as she doesn't kill it, the law won't interfere,
nor will outsiders.
Say it.
Say it!
Say it properly!
I'll allow you to let it all out today.
Go ahead. Let it all out!
Every time you compare
my ungratefulness
to your hard work,
it can drive me crazy.
I just want to settle the scores
with you.
After we settle it,
I can have some peace of mind.
I gave my life to you!
Ungrateful.
You know?
I gave my life to you!
What else do you want from me?
It's just a C-section.
Your tummy was cut open.
You also said that
you shouldn't have given birth to me
and that it was a mistake to give birth to me.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't meet your requirements.
Every time you beat me and scolded me,
my dad would say
you're just sharp-tongued, but you're tender inside.
But you know what?
your sharp tongue
has hurt the feelings of everyone in the family.
Everyone.
The slap you gave me
at school today
is the turning point in our mother-daughter relationship.
From now on,
just let me be.
Leave me alone!
Get lost.
Get out!
Go as far as you can!
I don't want to see you again!
Get lost!
Okay.
Is the house ready?
Yes.
What about the car?
It's done.
Since everything is ready,
let's…
open again.
[Luan Cheng]
Feng.
Where did Feng go?
Don't hide.
Where are you going?
The whole room
waiting for you.
I can't walk anymore.
I'll carry you.
Let me carry you.
Go away!
I can't drink anymore!
You have to.
You just had a few drinks, right?
Morbid.
What? Mortal?
I am a mortal.
Do you want to be an immortal?
Huh?
How is it?
How many orders did you get today?
Business is not good now.
Those male guests
always get drunk.
Ignore them.
I'll take a rest.
Bye.
Who is it?
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for Ding Yachun.
She's not here.
Where did she go?
She went to college in Shanghai.
Who are you?
I'm a tenant.