[DRIFTING AWAY]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental]
[Episode 13]
Let go.
I will,
but not now.
Just return the money to them!
Don't move!
What are you doing?
Let's go!
Why are you handcuffing me?
Is there a mistake?
My name's Sun Xuequan!
I'm not from Xuecheng.
I-I was born in Suilu.
Is there a mistake?
Get up!
Let me ask you again.
What's your name?
S-Sun Xuequan.
I've really never been to Xuecheng!
My home...
My home is in Suilu.
Suilu...
Your name is Shi Bi!
Don't move!
Director Chen,
don't bother to see us out.
Thank you so much.
When you come to Xuecheng,
I'll receive you properly.
Alright, I won't keep you any longer.
-Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
Sit still.
Shuanghuan.
I've committed a capital offense.
Thank you for taking care of me all these years.
Our time together has come to an end.
Go...
Go home
and raise the child.
In this life, we...
Don't ever come to me again!
Sit properly.
Keep grinning.
You won't be grinning for long.
Officer, I...
No talking.
I just want to ask
where my child is.
His grandfather took him away.
All these years,
you've been thinking about me.
It must've been hard on you.
How have you been over these years?
Just so-so.
Neither good nor bad.
What about you?
I thought about you every day.
I also dreamed of you.
It was roughly the same for me.
I dreamed a lot.
It's just that
I couldn't let you
appear in my dreams.
It doesn't matter.
Our dreams
have all ended.
Do you regret it now?
Is there any way back?
Captain Peng,
we've arrived in Xuecheng.
Has it changed much?
Not really.
Actually, it's the same for everyone.
This day
will come sooner or later.
But the processes
are completely different.
0213, you sleep here.
Hello?
We
have caught them.
Hello.
Wait a minute.
You're on speaker.
My daughter
and my wife
are both next to me.
Raise your voice
and say that again.
Everyone in the criminal gang that killed Liu Xinyuan
has been apprehended.
Daughter!
Xinyuan.
Xinyuan, did you hear that?
Did you hear that?
You've seen all the photos.
Do you know what crimes you've committed?
You're suspected of kidnapping,
intentional assault,
and premeditated murder.
Song Hongyu,
denying it is useless.
There are traces of your involvement
in the Bishui Garden case,
the Yanhui City case,
and the kidnapping case
in Luancheng.
On November 1, 2002,
you and Deng Ligang
took Liu Xinyuan and Huang Ying
away from the Green Island Hotel.
After that, the two of them
disappeared.
In the drain of room 402,
Bishui Garden, where you lived,
we found Liu Xinyuan's
DNA.
Do you remember this bracelet?
You don't need to use the photos
to intimidate me bit by bit.
The law values evidence.
I did
all the killings.
They just came into the room
to help me dispose of the bodies.
With all the lives
lost at your hands,
getting involved in any of the cases
leads to the same result.
Does your loyalty
make any sense?
May I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
I hid my driver's license
in the cabinet crack in Bishui Garden.
Did you find me
because you got that license?
That was the first clue we found.
Why did you put the license
back there?
It was hard for me to get my driver's license.
I didn't want to throw it away.
If I could
be a normal person someday,
I could
continue
delivering beer.
You're an optimistic man.
Do you remember us?
The two police officers
who were almost killed by your car
in the winter nine years ago.
The assault on police officers alone
is enough to convict you.
Let me jog your memory.
Over these years,
your criminal activities
spread across nine provinces in the country.
You only kidnapped
women in special professions.
You usually kidnapped
two women
who were beautiful
and had many customers
to increase efficiency
and make quick money.
When you coerced them
into asking their friends
for money,
you used fake addresses.
Am I right?
Does that ring any bells?
It seems you're saying
that all cases in China
were committed by me alone.
Then tell us about
the Bishui Garden case.
How did you commit the crime?
How did you divide the work?
How did you split the loot?
Deng Ligang said
they didn't kill that person.
They let that person go after getting the money.
How's that possible?
When have they ever spared a victim's life?
Calm down.
No suspect
confesses everything right at the beginning.
Among the four of them,
Shi Bi was the first to crack.
We should find a breakthrough from him.
Focus on him.
Within 48 hours,
we must get them to talk.
Are you in charge here?
Can you do me a favor?
What's that?
I have a wife
named Feng Shuanghuan in Suilu.
When I was brought in,
I had some valuable items with me.
Can you give them to her for me?
No.
Feng Shuanghuan is a good person.
Do me a favor.
Pass on a message for me.
First of all,
the items you had with you
are all exhibits.
No one can take them out
just because they want to.
But we can assure you
that after your sentence is pronounced
and we make sure there's nothing wrong with these items,
we can give them to her for you.
Tell us
how you teamed up with Deng Ligang.
My wife
was the first person I killed.
After killing my wife,
at the time,
I didn't want to live anymore.
But
I couldn't really bring myself
to commit suicide.
After killing her,
I didn't know what to do.
So, I called
my only friend at the time,
Deng Ligang.
Love isn't worth much,
but this
is worth something.
Next time, kill more efficiently.
It's best to use a rope
to strangle her.
Look at the mess you've made.
She's already dead.
How can there be a next time?
Everyone's like this when they kill for the first time.
You'll get used to it.
Come on.
College graduate who delivers beer.
Have some hard liquor
to calm your nerves.
What can you do?
You still have to live.
The two of us
were both fired from the factory.
From now on,
we'll set up our own factory.
Do you hear me?
What?
We'll set up our own factory.
What factory?
A meat processing factory.
Deng Ligang helped me.
So, I thought
I might be tied to him
for the rest of my life.
Actually, I was quite afraid of him.
Take a break.
When I first did it,
I was just like you.
Five...
There's 100,000 yuan in total.
Let's split it evenly between us.
Congratulations on finishing your first job.
Here.
Come on.
Open your mouth.
Open it wide.
Wider.
When you killed,
did you feel guilty?
Yes.
When I killed the first person,
I was quite scared.
I also had nightmares at night.
But after killing many people,
I became numb to it.
How many people did you kill?
10...
18.
Or maybe 19.
I don't remember.
Do you regret it?
It's fate.
I'm sorry!
Can you forgive me?
How I feel about you
can be summed up in one word:
hatred!
You did what I wanted you to do,
and I'll do what you want me to do.
I'll tell you everything.
♫The first lunar month brings the Chinese New Year♫
♫On the first day of the month♫
♫The young wish the old a happy New Year♫
Why are you sitting here?
Don't be afraid.
Do you know
which part of the human body
bleeds the fastest?
Right here.
I won't bully you.
I just want to sit beside you every night
and look at the moon.
I can see
the same moon as my son.
How many times have you been arraigned?
When will you be sentenced?
You've never mentioned it.
What crime did you commit?
Do you have children?
Yes.
My son...
has never been away from me
even for a day
ever since he was born.
I don't know
how he's been doing these days.
The correctional officer told us to watch you
in case you try to kill yourself.
I won't commit suicide.
I'll be out soon.
After I get out,
I need to take my son
to and from
school.
When we get home,
I need to prepare an extra meal for him.
In a couple of years,
I'll enroll him in a painting class
and have him learn to play an instrument.
I need to be there for him
as he grows up.
What took you so long?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've been waiting for so long.
Did you
find hope again
when my brother
returned to Xuecheng
for medical treatment?
Yes.
Now it's my turn to ask you.
When you changed your mother's household registration information,
you changed everything
except her name.
That wasn't an oversight, was it?
Suppose
I had changed her name.
She's lucid one moment and confused the next.
What if she got lost?
You have a sense of filial duty
and treat your mother so well.
Have you ever thought
about those kidnapped girls?
Those women?
They didn't give birth to me.
You think
this is cool,
don't you?
How should I put this?
When I was a kid,
my father was a boiler operator.
Every day, he drank counterfeit alcohol
and talked nonsense when drunk.
When he got drunk,
he would beat my mom,
me,
and my brother.
So, I secretly went to Mount Jingliang
to learn martial arts.
I didn't expect he'd be so lucky.
He got liver cancer early
and died.
I couldn't take revenge on him,
so I could only take it out on society.
Let me tell you something.
I've interrogated many criminals.
Almost every one of them
mentioned
their family of origin issues
at the critical moment.
They had either a bad father
or a bad mother.
There was something wrong
with their wife,
husband,
and children.
There was always someone else to blame.
They shifted responsibility
to gain sympathy.
You don't have to do this.
Don't you enjoy being cool?
Be a man.
In this world,
there are so many alcoholic fathers
who come home and beat their family.
But many of their children
succeed despite the adversity.
Have you ever thought about this?
Through learning,
knowledge,
diligence, and hard work,
we can change many things,
including our fate.
You chose this path
because you thought it was
a shortcut.
Fundamentally,
this proves
your laziness
and stupidity.
Do you understand?
I understand.
It's fate.
Alright.
Let's
stop arguing.
In the taxi murder case
in 1993,
you killed for the first time, right?
[Available]
You see?
I told you they were doing roadwork.
[Roadwork ahead. Please detour]
You didn't believe me
and thought I was making a detour.
I've at least driven seven or eight kilometers
for you.
You should give me at least
an extra eight or 10 yuan.
Right after I got in your car, you told me
your meter wasn't working.
Then, you made a detour.
Now, you want to charge me extra.
What's your game?
Isn't this an illegal taxi?
My meter wasn't working.
I told you
my meter wasn't working!
You agreed to it!
Let me tell you.
I have 10 yuan,
but today,
I'm not giving it to you.
What can you do to me?
Get out. Get out.
What? Are you refusing to take me?
Listen.
Today, you must
take me to my destination.
Otherwise, I'll make a complaint about you.
What are you doing?
Get out of the car.
No!
Get out!
What can you do to me?
I don't believe this.
You scumbag!
I've never seen anyone like you!
I've never seen anyone like you either!
Shame on you! Scumbag!
You refused to take me.
Listen.
I've got your license plate number!
Shut up!
Rogue!
Scumbag!
Just go!
I'm telling you.
You can't get away with this even if you drive away!
She's not going to stop.
How dare you curse me?
How dare you curse me!
You've got a dirty mouth.
Help.
Are you alright?
Get up and walk. Hurry.
Get up.
Come on.
Get up and walk.
Get up.
Come on. Get up and walk.
I'm letting go.
H-Help me.
I-I'll give you
money.
Come on! Get up.
Walk on your own.
Try walking on your own.
Have a try.
Madam?
Wake up.
I think it was an accident.
I had never thought
about killing someone before that.
But what could I do?
I didn't dare to call the police.
I couldn't dump the body
into the river
because it was frozen.
Nor could I bury the body under the ground
because it was frozen, too.
So,
I chopped her up
and dropped her body parts
along the way
as I drove on
until dawn.
That was
my 1993.
Then how did you all
get together?
And tell us how you committed your crimes.
It was fate.
We were all skilled workers.
I was a fitter.
Ji Dashun was an electrician.
Shi Bi
was a blacksmith.
Every day, we were dressed
like big shots,
wearing gold rings
and gold necklaces
and carrying briefcases.
Now that I think about it,
we were quite stupid.
However,
there were people who believed us.
Then, we
found a target,
demanded money,
killed them,
and dismembered the body.
That was the whole process.
Pretty meticulous, right?
If you
had caught me in 1993,
I'd probably have been sentenced to death then.
But you didn't.
Now, you've caught me.
I've lived for another 18 years.
I've gained.
People always want
another chance.
If I could go back in time,
I think
I would do a better job of covering my tracks.
You probably wouldn't even
be able to catch my shadow.
I'm not afraid of death.
Lying in a grave
is fine.
There's no need to be afraid of getting old
or having no money.
There's no need to be afraid
of the miserable life every day.
There's also no need
to be afraid
of counting the letters
in the word "afraid."
I'm afraid
you'll be counting
the letters in "afraid" in that place.
Besides,
do you think you'll have a grave?
82...
32...
19.
Remember this badge number.
It's my honor.
See you in court.