=Success Rate=
Miss,
=Episode 4=
is this your dog?
Thanks for helping me catch Oreo.
It just chewed through the leash.
No worries.
Come down first. It hurts.
Did it bite you?
Wait, don't touch me.
No, come down first.
Come down first.
I'm Che Xiaoxiao.
Thank you so much!
Otherwise, Oreo would've been lost.
I'm Bai Wu.
Don't mention it.
Bai Wu,
how should I thank you?
No need to thank me.
Just keep an eye on your dog.
Hmm.
Sensing energy.
Energy is being collected.
Collection complete.
The System can be upgraded.
Upgrade now?
Of course.
Upgrading...
(A blessing in disguise.)
Come on, take a look.
Take a look.
This is a great thing.
Take a look, take a look.
Good things!
How about
going to the stall of Fatty first?
Chance Fatty agrees to trade: 7%.
(It seems he still holds a grudge)
(about the last time I found a bargain.)
Hold on.
System,
you've become smarter.
Current version
can offer analysis to assist with problems.
Nice!
Today I will definitely harvest a lot.
What treasures do you have?
Qianlong-era items.
They are fake, huh?
Fatty,
how's the business?
Why are you here again?
I obviously support your business.
Pfft.
No need.
I feel unlucky.
(As expected,)
(he really doesn't want my business.)
Hey, young man,
come over here.
Last time, weren't you worried
I might dirty your antiques?
My apologies.
Last time, it was my mistake.
You're kind enough to let it go.
Come, come.
Li,
you're actually trading with a jinx?
Not afraid of jinxing yourself?
Quiet down!
Here, take a look, young man.
What's the authenticity rate
for these stalls?
2%.
26%.
What a shame.
Fatty's stall has a much higher rate.
Ming-era teapot,
valued at 25,000-30,000 yuan.
How much is this?
5,000.
Today's chance of finding a bargain: 0%.
(What does that mean?)
(Not a single steal today?)
3,000.
Deal.
(Isn't this a steal?)
5,000. I'll take it.
5,000.
Surprised?
Caught off guard?
Jin Youlong.
Pang Kun?
You've offended me
and my friend too.
If you don't want to stay in Jiang City,
then you can leave.
Unexpected, right?
I'm very close with Mr. Jin.
If I knew you were his friend,
I wouldn't have let you off that day.
People might think you're rich.
What do you want?
You cut off my road for gaining money.
Of course, I'll cut off your road too.
(So they're the distractions.)
Sir, 8,000.
8...
10,000.
Young man, 10,000?
You're determined to compete with me today?
Stop wasting time. Yes or no?
(This teapot is worth at most 30,000.)
30,000.
- Mr. Jin.
- Raise the bid.
Got it.
50,000.
50,000?
How much?
You're ruthless.
Hey.
Giving up already?
Sir, here you go.
Oh no.
Got it wrong, didn't you?
Who's the jinx?
This is a walking fortune!
20,000.
40,000.
30,000.
60,000.
100,000.
You're really going all in against me?
Highest bidder wins.
It's fair.
Everyone, everyone!
Come and take a look.
This guy is good for nothing.
Just a penniless nobody.
Isn't that Young Master Jin
of the Wanbao Chamber of Commerce?
How'd this guy
get tangled with someone like that?
Well said.
I can't compare to you,
rich but stupid.
What do you mean by that?
That teapot is worth at most 30,000.
The jade, artifact and the vase
are worth no more than 60,000.
You're already lost over 160,000.
Trying to outplay me?
My finances aren't running dry.
You'll bleed money before you know it.
Dare to trick me?
That's a lot of money.
Not cheap, huh?
160,000.
For someone like you, it's astronomical.
But for me,
it's just pocket change.
Everyone, everyone,
(What's going on here?)
Come on, remember this face.
Bai Wu.
The watchdog of my family's branch store.
He got lucky and found a bargain.
Really think you can turn your life around?
I'll walk you to the end of the road today.
You just love collecting junk, right?
Fine, I'll sell it to you.
1,000.
Sorry.
I forgot.
You don't even have 1,000 yuan.
He did guard my family's gate for years.
He's loyal
and obedient.
Let me give him a discount.
250.
Pay me 250.
This guy really doesn't know his place.
How dare he offend Mr. Jin!
Yeah, that's right.
Offending Mr. Jin
means he'll be done in the antique industry.
Probably he can't even stay in Jiang City.
Bai Wu!
Bai Wu,
what are you doing here?
Alright, Bai Wu, I won't disturb you.
Take your time.
Pack all of these up.
Pack these up.
Mr. Jin,
he's going...
Stay close.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks.
Pack these up.
I want all of them.
Got it.
He's focused on quantity
and hides what he truly wants.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wrap it all up.
I'll take it.
Double the price.
Jin Youlong,
are you raising the prices of antiques here?
Oh dear.
You wouldn't understand
the pains of the wealthy.
Fine.
You're so extravagant.
Buy it.
Go ahead, buy it.
Get the goods.
Mr. Jin, shouldn't we check the price first?
Alright.
I'll definitely cut off
your financial path.
Come on.
Bai, it's a 50-50 split.
Thanks for the hard work.
Let's work more later.
- Mr. Jin.
- Thanks a lot!
Let's exchange WeChat.
- Thanks.
- Bai Wu.
I'm in trouble right now.
Could you lend me a hand?
You go over there
and tell the stall owners...
You want to spend money.
I have to step in
and help clear out the stock for everyone.
Thanks a lot, Mr. Jin.
It's just more than 2 million.
Pocket change.
Oh, I remember something.
Feel free
to smash these things.
None of them are worth much.
Don't feel bad about it.
Everyone,
add me on WeChat, add me!
- Thanks!
- Thank you.
Add me on WeChat so we can connect.
Mr. Jin, are we really letting him go?
Why are you still holding it?
Get a few blank handprints ready.
A 100,000 loan
will make your life unbearable.
Let's do something for him.
(Loan Agreement)
(I've already swapped his loan)
(High-interest loan, daily rate 5.5%)
(for a high-interest loan.)
(Now that 100,000 he owes me)
(Lender: Shadow Loan Co.; Borrower: Bai Wu)
(has already snowballed)
(into millions with interest.)
(Better to give away ten years of life)
(than owe Shadow Loan even a cent.)
(He's doomed.)
I can kiss anyone,
except you.
You can kiss anyone?
I'm telling you, Mu Yi'er,
your parents agreed to our marriage.
Sooner or later, you'll be my wife.
I'm warning you,
you can't kiss anyone.
Mu Yi'er, what are you doing here?
Are you trying to provoke me?
Mu Yi'er, don't...
This isn't right.
Don't...
You...
You!
Just you wait.
He has left.
What are you doing?
(Qingqing's been brainwashed)
(by this fortune teller.)
(She believes everything he says.)
(There isn't a good man.)
(Today, I'll help Qingqing)
(expose this con artist.)
Miss Mu...
Miss,
you've seen it yourself.
Our relationship is unique.
So what if you kissed?
Exactly.
We have kissed.
So, he's coming with me.
Wait, when did I kiss you?
Now, we're on equal footing.
Bai Wu,
you promised to have dinner with me.
He's coming with me.
Come with me.
- Come with me.
- My arms are broken!
- It's broken!
- Come with me.
My arms are about to break.
Hey,
your dog ran off.
Oreo!
Bai Wu, wait here for me.
Don't go with her.
Xiaoxiao! Xiaoxiao!
Oreo!
Miss Mu, you...
Master Bai,
today,
can you help me one more time?
What do you need?
Be
my boyfriend.
♪Who is mocking me for being too young?♪
♪Taking shortcuts avoids some collisions♪
♪But the price is abandoning kindness within♪
♪Losing my most precious collection♪
♪He's at the pinnacle of the pyramid♪
♪Being frivolous, arrogant, like a disguise♪
♪Destiny requires me to boldly venture♪
♪Appraise treasures,
whether priceless or not♪
♪The dragon is not a thing in the pond.
Don't underestimate a young man in poverty♪
♪When I can see the success rate♪
♪I choose loyalty, courage, and brotherhood♪
♪Go through hardships
for a pair of wise eyes♪
♪Search for the truth amid ups and downs♪
♪The vanity fair is the arena of beasts♪
♪The auction house is where I shine♪
♪Appraise the purity or filth of hearts♪
♪Who understands my unyielding resilience♪
♪Who admires my bold defiance♪
♪The river washes away towering waves♪
♪The youth is strong, and China is strong♪
♪Go through hardships
for a pair of wise eyes♪
♪Search for the truth amid ups and downs♪
♪The vanity fair is the arena of beasts♪
♪The auction house is where I shine♪
♪Appraise the purity or filth of hearts♪
♪Who understands my unyielding resilience♪
♪Who admires my bold defiance♪
♪The river washes away towering waves♪
♪The youth is strong, and China is strong♪