It's the child she wants to kidnap
(I am a kidnapper) My name is Masamune Shinjo
Became a kidnapper for some reason
Who are you
The Nanase Rin I kidnapped is a genius girl who has lost her memory.
(Amnesiac genius girl) "Besides English, I can also speak other foreign languages"
"Do you understand what I'm saying?"
Is this some kind of spell?
Later I was involved in a shocking case
(The girl's parents were brutally murdered) The police are investigating the murder...
Xiao Lin's parents were actually killed
(Who is the real murderer) Is the murderer from the police?
suspect found
(Mysterious man targeting girls) Xiaolin and I are investigating the truth of the murder case
But was attacked by a mysterious man
Then my missing wife suddenly appeared
(The missing wife appears) She is the one who suggested the kidnapping, Shiori
Meeting Nanase Rin’s sister for the first time
(date of kidnapping)
It turns out you live nearby
It’s more convenient to take care of buds here
I recently rented this weekly apartment
Yeah
Fortunately you are okay
What happened
suddenly a man appeared
I want to take Xiao Lin away
Who is he?
Have you seen Xiao Lin?
There is no such auntie
Don't you have any clues?
You were the one who planned this kidnapping, right?
Did you tell her?
I've always wanted to ask
Why did you choose my house?
Did you kill my parents?
Order to carry pistols
On the premise of giving priority to the safety of the hostages
Just in case of emergencies
yes
Pistol?
This means that the headquarters thinks Xinzhuang is cruel, right?
A suspect in kidnapping and murder
In short, if you catch Xinzhuang, you will know all the truth.
yes
OK, I'll tell you
I picked your parents
It's because they dare not call the police
I heard that Director Nanase of Eishin Memorial Hospital
Abuse daughter in private
Hello
Right
Don’t you remember? But your body should know
Yes indeed there is
You pull me up to show her. Hurry up.
If this kind of thing is exposed
The hospital's reputation will plummet.
So I judged that he did not dare to call the police
Do you think I would believe this?
That's your freedom
But I want to declare one thing
I didn't kill your parents
Not to mention the parents who killed Meupiao
I can't get the ransom.
This is...wait a minute
So you didn’t get the ransom either?
Of course
What about Yasheng’s medical expenses?
Didn't you pay for it?
Medical expenses?
Otherwise, who paid... strange...
Right
Did you go take care of Meisheng?
I didn't see you yesterday
Didn’t I ask you to accompany her?
-I have a lot to do. -What are you busy with?
There's nothing more important than children
don't yell
Neighbors will call the police
Use this money to stay in a hotel temporarily
Okay Masamune
we want to live here
Have you seen the news?
This guy is wanted now
It's dangerous wherever you go
Right Masamune?
yes
I have accepted this. Please take care of me during this period.
accomplice aunt
I will leave temporarily starting tomorrow
Research continues
Yes I understand
Long time no see, Dr. Mizuhara
This is a souvenir from Singapore for you
You still have time to hang out here
The child hasn't been found yet
Don't worry, you will definitely find her
You don't seem to understand the seriousness of the matter
You are the one
Do you understand how many interests and people are involved behind this matter?
In case of failure
You've lost more than just your Ph.D. status
What is status?
I bet my life
Stop talking nonsense and go find that kid
Don't be preempted by the police
I didn't mean to argue
Let's live in peace with each other
get up...
Get up, get up, get up quickly
-Get up, get up... -It hurts
what are you doing
What's your attitude? I woke you up out of kindness.
-Won't you be gentler? -It's time to eat
Please eat first
Well, little Rin, let’s eat it too
You eat first
I started
-How's it going? - It's so hot and delicious.
No
Will your tongue be numb or make you feel dizzy?
ah? what are you talking about
It's okay, eat quickly
What are you doing again?
I started
Wow, this seasoning is too salty.
Auntie, do you still have a sense of taste?
How about it
I really miss the miso soup you cooked
Do you like this taste?
Relaxed physically and mentally
delicious
I'm going out to work later
During this time, please stay at home.
Yeah I will
Did you hear Xiaolin?
Auntie, I want to ask you a favor
give me a mobile phone
cell phone?
Hello...
Didn’t you say you should stay at home?
I didn't agree
It's dangerous to go outside
of course i know
But something more dangerous may happen if this continues
Judging from your current income and expenditure...
Efficient application and risk management are very important
What is more dangerous to feed?
You shouldn't be doubting Xi Li, right?
Reasons to doubt her
More than not doubting her
What do you want a cell phone for?
The day of the kidnapping was July 8th
Contemporaneous with the kidnapping
Nanase and his wife were also killed
The murder weapon that killed the dean was the samurai sword decorated in the house
The wife is a letter opener
Katana and letter opener...
Do you see what they have in common?
Completely different murder weapon
Neither of these murder weapons were brought in from outside.
I see
so what
Xiaolin, does your head hurt?
Did you remember something?
Xiao Lin, this is...
Monitor?
Don't you think it's strange?
Just call this monitor
You should know what happened on the day of the murder, right?
I see
You are right
Do you really understand?
please wait
Sunouchi-senpai, this is Mr. Matsuda from the security company.
-Ito-senpai-What's going on?
There seemed to be some public quarrel yesterday
This is the guard's body video, can you see it?
Why don't you watch it yourself?
Because you sit in my seat
- Can you take a look? - What's going on?
I have been a guard at Rongjin Memorial Hospital for a long time
about a year ago
Dean Nanase Mamoru asked me to serve as his residential security guard as well.
How long is it?
Plus one makes it thirty years faster
Thirty years is really very senior.
The dean must trust you very much
Even ask you to be the security guard at the residence
Don't dare to take it
I personally rarely talk to the dean
It should be based on my performance in the company.
That's it, that's it
I want to ask
Why were the monitors in the dean’s house removed?
Yes, that was not long ago
The dean asked me to dismantle it
tear down?
When was that?
July 5th
He said he wanted to switch to a monitor from another company.
Ask me to dismantle the one I'm using now
What about the previous images?
The dean asked me to delete them all
all?
So nothing is left?
Sorry I can't help
It doesn't matter
Can I go then?
Okay, thank you for your cooperation
I'll take you out
Right
Where were you on July 8th?
No. 8?
This is a routine inquiry
I patrol the hospital as usual from morning to six o'clock in the evening
Go see your high school classmates after get off work
The two drank until morning
Can you give us the name and contact information of that friend?
OK
so unlucky
Maybe we can know the truth if we have surveillance video.
Do you think it's a coincidence?
Murders and kidnappings occurred immediately after the monitors were removed
And none of the previous files have been left behind.
It is indeed too beneficial for the murderer
Sunouchi-senpai, please take a look.
There seemed to be a fight in the West District yesterday
I don’t know if this is a body-worn video.
Could this person be...
It's him
Hello, is that okay?
It's time for us to go back
By the way, what is your relationship?
You and aunt
Your personalities are completely different
How do we know each other?
So what if we know each other?
Where did you first meet? Who spoke to you first?
Is it you or her?
-Who confesses first? -You are the gossip reporter.
haven't seen you for a long time
i have been waiting for you
- Come over there - OK
Who is he smiling so happily?
So when and where did you meet?
When I was a child, I was in a kindergarten
Neither Xili nor I have parents
I used to be a crybaby and a clumsy person
Xiori is very reliable and smart.
She often teaches me how to read
Will also play with me
- It seems - It seems?
I don't remember much about that time.
I get a headache every time I think about it
Definitely not a good memory
Our fate has been with us since then
Do you want to eat?
If you don’t want it, don’t want it.
How about it
I got the eyewitness testimony
It seems to be Xinzhuang and a child who looks like Xiaolin
And there was a woman in her thirties or forties next to her.
woman?
An accomplice of Xinzhuang?
she's gone
Follow up quickly
It's a university hospital
hurry up
It doesn't look like a date
Needless to say
Shiori wouldn't do that...
who knows
We are nominally husband and wife, but you have been living apart.
Xiao Lin, please stop making trouble.
Hello
You still doubt me
No, you misunderstood
Of course I still doubt it
Your whole person is suspicious
They might betray us to the police.
Hello
Who was that person just now?
why go to hospital
besides
The medicine you took in the morning
Is this a traditional Chinese medicine that improves the body’s self-healing ability?
What
Why take this medicine
Can't answer?
Then let me change the question
Where were you and what were you doing on July 8th?
8 days?
It was the day of the kidnapping
This person has something he didn't say
yes
do you really want to know
I...
The police at that time
Was it you who called me here?
Sorry for the unexpected visit because you are not in the office and had to come here.
What's the matter
Can we come inside to talk?
Just say it here
Ms. Xinzhuang
You should know that your husband is involved in the kidnapping case, right?
To prevent neighbors from gossiping
Let's go inside
Sunouchi-senpai
what do you want to ask
There was a fight in the street yesterday
A man who witnessed the scene said
That person is suspected to be Mr. Xinzhuang who is on the run
And that person also brought a girl with him
We suspect she is Nanase Rin
Then what
Then...
In fact, besides them, I also saw
another woman
I would like to ask out of necessity
Where were you last night?
Yesterday...I was at home
Is there anything to prove?
I live alone
There are no monitors in this apartment either.
There seems to be nothing to prove
Yeah
By the way, let me ask you where person No. 8 is.
No. 8?
I can't remember it for a moment
It doesn't matter if you think about it slowly
We're willing to wait until you remember
This room is so beautiful
The environment is very quiet
It seems very comfortable to live in
What's wrong, senior?
Have any guests been here?
Feel sorry
I went to the hospital
I remembered
July 8th
I was in the hospital all day because I felt unwell
Hospital?
I am infected with HIV
HIV？
human immunodeficiency virus
After infection, the body’s immunity will be reduced
However, with proper treatment
It’s not contagious everywhere
Can live like ordinary people
You don't have to be afraid
Just because of this disease
I feel uncomfortable when exposed to the sun
Doing housework is also very tiring, so you accumulate dishes
Have you finished asking?
If you want to continue the investigation, please bring out a writ.
Okay, I'm very sorry.
err on the side of caution
We will check your hospital records
please
Oh, I never thought she had such a hidden secret
senior?
Let's go
yes
Xi Li is talking
It's okay
I take medicine and there's nothing wrong with it
Why don't you say when it happened?
Have had it since childhood
It seems to be a vertical infection from mother to child
mother and son...
I discovered it three years ago
Because the cold has never been cured
I only found out after doing a blood test.
If you say that, wouldn't it be okay for Yasheng to...
Yasheng is fine
She has had a test and it was negative
Yeah
But why
Why didn't you tell me
If I said
Can you still abandon me?
you won't abandon me
Definitely not
Even if I say I'm fine
You will also worry about staying with me all the time, right?
Would rather stay awake
Sacrifice yourself to accompany me
You are too gentle Masamune
I don't want to see you become like that
and
I don’t want Yasheng to be with you either
See how sick I am
This is...
I never forget my family
Sorry for hiding this from you
Sorry for ruining our happiness
But at the time I thought
This is the best approach
I didn’t expect that I would end up involving you in the end.
I'm really sorry
It's not too late now
I will surrender
It all started because of me
I have to end it
no...
you did nothing
This kidnapping was planned by me alone
I did it myself
Masamune
Xi Li... you go and accompany Mei Sheng.
You must accompany her this time, okay?
Do you want to leave here?
That's right
Gone, gone
Go faster. Go faster.
Xiaolin, we should go
Don't cause any more trouble to Xi Li
hurry up...
Get up and walk well
Masamune
hope one day
We can still live together as three of us
And you
Actually, I also want to have a good chat with you.
last question
Was I really being abused?
I don’t know the details either.
only
Dean Nanase seems to be doing some kind of research
Research...
Maybe you are also related to that research
Let's go, let's go
hurry up...
Gone...
No one knows what kind of research Dean Nanase is doing.
He is simply a research maniac
mad Men?
Sometimes research is more important than internal affairs
- right - yes
By the way, the dean suddenly took a long leave recently.
I was scheduled to go to Singapore next month
Singapore?
Are you going to attend a society or a family trip?
I didn’t know that the dean hated attending the society.
It doesn’t feel like a family trip either.
Tell you secretly
I heard that the relationship between the dean and his wife is not good.
physician
Oh, it’s Matsuda
Would you like a cup of coffee after the examination?
Is he Mr. Matsuda who also serves as the security guard at the dean's residence?
The performance must be excellent
Only the dean would entrust him to be the security guard of the residence.
That's because Matsuda worked hard to recommend himself
You even came here to ask me a favor
Help him connect with the dean?
I also suddenly wanted to drink coffee. Would you like another cup, doctor?
- Matsuda? - It’s different from what he said
I confirmed with the travel agency
He did have three tickets booked to fly to Singapore
Singapore?
So are we going as a family of three?
Not by name, it’s Dean Nanase and Xiao Rin
The other person is Dr. Mizuhara
Going abroad not with your wife but with Dr. Mizuhara?
Going to Singapore?
Go and ask about it
Dr. Mizuhara seems to have lost contact.
Even the employees of the consortium don’t know where she is.
Hiding your whereabouts?
There is another strange thing
The person who ordered the air tickets was not the dean himself.
But Mr. Yamazaki, the legal adviser
Yamazaki?
ok thank you
-thank you-walk slowly
Boss, I want a Suwa special sandwich.
-One of Suwa's special sandwiches is good-Next news
It has been five days since the kidnapping case of Nanase Rin occurred
-The police have disclosed the appearance of the male suspect... -This matter has not been resolved yet.
The world is so chaotic now
-Seriously, this murderer is really hateful... -Yeah
Your Suwa Special Sandwich is ready
-Add 50 yuan and you will get a cup of coffee - no need
- I charge you one thousand yuan - no need to look for it
Thank you for visiting
long wait
If you're hungry, take it.
Eat quickly
Am I a bad boy?
Being beaten like this
Is it because I'm not good?
How is it possible
Children are irreplaceable treasures of their parents
How could it hurt you?
I never believe it
those bruises
Maybe you were injured because you had too much fun with your father
Don't be afraid, it will be fine
Xiao Lin
You still want to go home
Go back quickly
go to school
Playing with good friends like that
Why are you talking about this?
Although you are doubting the police
But they're not all bad guys, right?
There will also be people in the police who are trustworthy.
You can ask him for help
Masamune, do you want to surrender?
Did I hit the mark?
Acting cool in front of aunt and running out
Are you going to turn yourself in as a result?
We can't escape anymore
Now there are eyes and ears everywhere
Do you want to sleep outdoors and eat instant noodles every day?
So you have to surrender?
Are you in pain too?
Why not ask the police for help
Go to the doctor to get your memory back...
Stop pretending to care about me
If it's for my own good, help me
I?
what can i do
Then surrender yourself
Even if it's just me, I have to find the murderer
Revenge for parents
Wait wait a minute
Want to find the murderer?
Even the police are having trouble
How can we do it with just the two of us?
- I can - impossible
Can't escape anymore
I really want to be good for you
If I really want to be good to you, I should stop here.
See this for yourself
Look, everyone is looking for this face everywhere now
Find this face
I have a history of murder
He is a major criminal who is regarded as a thorn in the side of the country.
So what, I have nothing
Mom and Dad were killed and terrible things happened all the time.
Can't rely on the police to remember anything
i have nothing
nothing but you
I can only believe you
But you said it was for my own good?
That's why it's for your daughter's sake
you don't care about me at all
You never worried about me after you took me away
I see...
it's all my fault
sorry
but i swear to you
I'll take you with me from now on
There's never a time when I don't worry about you
Even now
But I'm scared
Because I can't do anything
Just say you'll protect me
I will protect you
I will protect Xiaolin for sure
Really
I promise
OK, then I'll leave it to you
Let's go
That's right
The dean asked me to book those air tickets.
Why did Dean Nanase go to Singapore?
have no idea
I just do what he says
That's really strange
Dean Nanase Mamoru is a research madman and a secretist
Keep a distance from people around you and hate coming into contact with people
Such a dean actually trusts you so much
Indeed compared to others
We are relatively close
Have you known the dean for a long time?
I used to be the eldest lady's tutor
Have you ever taught Xiaolin how to read?
She doesn't need anyone else's guidance
I'm just helping
She was taught by experts in various fields
-Various fields? -She's no ordinary eight-year-old
Proficient in more than 20 languages
Others like mathematical physics
Medical quantum mechanics and more
Comparable to top research scholars in various subjects
He is the youngest child in the country to join Mensa
Who is Xiao Lin?
At least
It's not an existence we can imagine
Mamoru has always regarded you as an errand boy.
Bossing you around
I can only sigh from the side
I don't care
Thanks to this, I learned a lot
yes
you are indeed strong
is a smart man
Then again
Who killed Mamoru?
do you have any clues
It doesn't matter
I don't care about this kind of thing at all
Xiao Lin?
He seems to be a very special child
Maybe it has something to do with Dean Nanase’s research
Once we find out, Lesson 1 will take over the investigation.
another injury
The investigators were very dissatisfied
Said you were handling the case without permission
I obviously shared information
The information is very useful and I thank you very much.
But you also need to think about organizational norms
Just upholding justice does not mean you can act arbitrarily
Qin
Have you forgotten why you were transferred?
Senior has obtained the witness information of the suspect.
In Nagisa Water Park
Hello...
This costs 50,000
Xiaolin...
Do you think it is meat?
It’s only half price. Half price.
I’ll use this to cook the ingredients today.
How much is this
300,000
Give him 300,000
300,000?
300,000 here
Why does it hurt so much?
Maybe you can use it for self-defense
I've confirmed it with witnesses.
It seems that it is indeed Xinzhuang and Xiaolin
They went that way
I'd better go look for any clues.
yes
(1,500 yen per night if available today)
I'll go in first
See if it is suitable for two people to live in
Do you hear me if you stay here?
I want to accommodate two people
-Three thousand yuan -Three thousand?
Tomio Nanase
Vice Chairman of Rongjin Memorial Hospital
Three thousand yuan
This person...
Lawyer Yamazaki...
Isn’t it just a child that can’t be counted as two thousand?
Do you want to live in Sanqian?
Three thousand?
The room was surprisingly good
Hey Xiaolin?
Xiao Lin
Xiaolin...
Hello
It's you again, you want to treat Xiao Lin...
Xiaolin...
Professor Masamune Shinjo
please leave
how do you know my name
I just promised Xiaolin today
Will definitely protect her
It’s not even a day yet
I said it
I will protect...this child
protective rind
Sunouchi-senpai
I almost lost him
Hey what is this
Don't touch
Masamune
Xiao Lin
sorry
And I frightened you again
I will definitely protect you
Hello
where is xiaolin
Mr. Xinzhuang, don't worry
Xiaolin is here
what is that
If you dare to hurt Xiao Lin...
How could I hurt her?
She is our...
light of hope
©ASTORY & KT Studiogenie/tv asahi
(The genius girl who recovered her memory) I knew she was not an ordinary person, but I didn’t expect her to be so powerful.
I wanted to find the murderer before but now I have no motivation.
(Partner is in danger of breaking up?) Please don’t have anything to do with Xiao Lin anymore
(Amazing progress) Found it
i might be killed
Masamune