Commander.
The Emperor's orders cannot be disobeyed.
It's an assassination mission.
Dead or alive.
Helan Ci.
You transferred the troops from Anding Gate to stop me.
Do you know that
before Yu Henian died,
he gave the capital's defense map to the barbarians?
Fire the arrows!
Fire the arrows for me!
He is just bluffing.
Kill this traitor!
Ying Wujiu.
You really didn't disappoint me.
Even my imperial guards couldn't stop you.
You brought your troops back.
Do you want to see me beg for mercy on my knees,
or do you want me to give you the dragon robe?
Your Majesty, the flank of Anding Gate is unguarded.
The scouts reported that
the barbarians have breached the pass.
I brought the troops back
not for treason,
but to enter the city and fight the enemy.
Fight the enemy.
I will defend my own empire.
If you want to take Jingzhi away,
it will be over my dead body.
Otherwise, even if you flatten this Meridian Gate,
you can only take away my Imperial Noble Consort.
Jingzhi.
I thought I could win against him once.
But I forgot that
the Emperor of Dazheng shouldn't gamble with Dazheng's gates.
Ying Wujiu, catch the sword and enter the city!
Kill!
Jingzhi.
This last time,
I have chosen a way of survival for you.
Kill!
Dazheng's empire
is not a place for you animals to run wild.
Ying Wujiu!
I have said it.
What is mine,
I will personally protect.
Since Your Majesty wants to be crazy,
I will accompany you.
For this last time.
Your Majesty!
Ying Wujiu.
Don't mind me.
Kill them all.
Jingzhi is watching from the city tower.
Don't embarrass me.
Hyah!
Kill!
Helan Ci.
Jingzhi.
Don't cry.
I have always forced you my whole life.
For this last time...
For this last time,
I allow you to live the life you want.
Ying Wujiu.
I have defended the empire,
and I have returned her
to you.
Commander.
Now the royal bloodline is withering.
Only if you ascend the throne
can you stabilize the world
and suppress this mess.
This chair is stained with too many people's blood
and has trapped too many souls.
I
do not care for it.
This empire
was defended by Helan Ci with his life.
Protect it well.
If you ever become a tyrant,
even if I am no longer in the martial world,
the blades of this world
will return at any time.
Ying Wujiu,
do you regret it?
That is the supreme position of the world.
Jingzhi.
Living this life again
was never about the world.
All my fighting and scheming
was just for this moment,
to watch this sunset with you.
Dedicated to all those who look up at the light from the abyss.