He sent you,
Ying Wujiu.
He made you personally send me to his bed.
And you actually accepted this decree.
Helan Ci wants to use this extremely twisted way
to completely crush Ying Wujiu's dignity
and warn me at the same time.
Thunder or rain,
are all the Emperor's grace.
This dancing dress,
the Emperor ordered you to wear it to serve him tonight.
My hands are injured.
I can't untie my clothes.
I'll have to trouble the Chief to undress me personally.
Ying Wujiu, aren't you a eunuch?
You personally put this torn dress on me.
Qu Jingzhi.
Will you only be satisfied when you drive me to death?
Ying Wujiu,
you finally can't pretend anymore.
That night, Helan Ci fell asleep due to a headache,
and didn't actually call me to serve him.
Jingzhi.
Look at the birds in this pavilion.
I spent a fortune to find each of them.
But none of them
is like you, a canary that can heal,
who pleases me.
Your Majesty is the true dragon.
I'm just a lowly life in the mud.
If I say you are a rare treasure, you are.
Jingzhi.
I will issue a decree tomorrow
to make you a Noble Lady
and grant you the main hall of Yanxi Palace.
From now on,
you don't need to return to the Yeting Bureau.
Your life and your body,
will be locked by my side for eternity.
He's watching.
I can't be exposed,
otherwise Helan Ci will immediately have him shot to death.
Helan Ci,
you don't just want to kill me,
you also want to break her spine
and turn her into a plaything in a cage.
Since this cannibalistic imperial power wants to lock her up,
then I
will personally smash this palace cage
and take you away.
Congratulations.
You'll be a Noble Lady tomorrow.
The Prime Minister ordered me to deliver the final death order.
The Prime Minister wants to assassinate the Emperor
and frame the Eastern Depot.
The castrated dog blocked the Prime Minister's way,
so he naturally must die.
If you obey obediently,
the Prime Minister will leave your corpse intact.
If you dare to have second thoughts,
you should know what those three years in the water dungeon felt like.
You...
Yu Henian,
you shouldn't have,
you absolutely shouldn't have threatened me with his life.
Yu Henian's secret letter of treason and private army deployment.
With this,
I can expose Yu Henian's plot,
break free from his control,
and never be controlled again.
I must go find Wujiu immediately.
Wearing Helan Ci's golden lock,
where do you want to escape?
Ying Wujiu!
I got Yu Henian's secret letter of treason
and the private army deployment.
Take me away.
Are you okay, Jingzhi?
Hold me tight.
Even if the King of Hell comes for you today,
I will get you out.
Ying Wujiu, wake up.
You liar.
Didn't you say you could retreat unscathed?
You.
You are still here.
You are not crippled.
Besides the deadly poison, the Yu family's arrows
were also coated with
a strong aphrodisiac meant for martial arts masters.
Jingzhi, don't touch me.
Don't you know I'm a normal man?
If you light the fire now,
I will burn you to ashes.
Jingzhi.
My little empress.
I finally hold you in my arms.
What did you call me?
Ying Wujiu.
You remember the past life too,
don't you?
You were reborn too.
Ying Wujiu.
Listen well.
In the past life, you died for me.
In this life, you fell into hell for me.
From now on,
don't even think about pushing me away.
Today,
I will give myself to you completely.
My Jingzhi.
Even if tomorrow brings a bottomless abyss,
I will never let go.
What's going on?
The secret guards who went to Yanxi Palace
and the assassins who ambushed Ying Wujiu outside Shenwu Gate,
why hasn't a single one returned to report?