♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet with the best one ♫
♫ The bird makes a promise to the forest ♫
♫ A brave response ♫
♫ makes my world clear up ♫
♫ The voices in my heart ♫
♫ are all about you at the moment ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
♫ are as splendid as dreams ♫
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
[A Romance of the Little Forest]
[Episode 20]
[Falling down at the same place twice
could only be my own reason.]
They didn't come with a spoon!
Thanks.
If Lv Jian hasn't told me about that,
I didn't know you finished your essay.
It's good news. We need to celebrate.
And he said it's admitted
by many top overseas labs.
By the way, which publication?
No, thanks.
Unfortunately, Zhuang Hui is not here.
If he were here, he would like the cake.
So sweet.
Have a seat.
I want to tell you something.
Just go ahead. It's fine.
Both my experiment and paper succeeded.
And I've been eager for the lab for long.
Maybe I could find a solution there.
Nice. It's good for you.
Let me drink a toast to you.
So I'm afraid I need
to go studying there for at least a year.
But actually,
I don't know when I can come back.
I won't come back until I find the solution.
It's fine.
Then we can live in
a land of idyllic beauty together.
What are you doing? Give it to me.
It's sweet.
Just like you.
You're drunk. I'll send you back.
No. Here's my home.
I won't leave. My home is right here!
Where are we going?
Let me off...
♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet the fine weather ♫
♫ Meet someone ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
Fortunately.
Professor Zhuang!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Where's my wine?
You can't drink anymore.
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
♫ are as splendid as dreams ♫
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
Pretty nice.
I can even become rich with my skills.
Tiantian.
Bubble tea is ready. Come and have a try!
I'm sure you'll fall in love with it.
No other bubble tea can compare with it!
I'm here.
What's wrong with your leg?
Where's broken?
Where is it?
You were fine when we just came in.
What's going on?
Let me try.
Unbelievable.
I've become fatter
since I ate and played with you.
So less sugar next time.
You're still that slender.
Wait. Why are you in a wheelchair?
Still refuse to answer me.
Does she want to satirize me by it?
Calm down, Tiantian. Listen to me first.
I'm sorry.
I was too reckless yesterday.
I shouldn't mention your sadness.
It doesn't matter.
You can do whatever you want.
Stop. Listen to me first.
Okay.
Do you know that?
I really feel relaxed since I'm with you.
Because I think I can be myself.
Just say or do whatever I want
without thinking of the results.
I know you'll tolerate me
no matter what I say and do.
Your love gives me power and confidence.
People always say others can't really
feel their own experiences.
But I really hope
I can try my best to get your feelings.
You see.
I'm as same as you now.
I can't forget your expression
of suffering a lot.
I treated your pain as a chip of our love.
I didn't mean that.
You've done nothing wrong
to me so there's no injury.
I don't deserve your apology.
Once again.
Why?
Don't indulge me anymore.
Do I?
Fine. Just take it as connivance this time.
Do you remember what I've told you before?
"Gifts of roses have a lingering fragrance."
I've indulged you today...
Well...
If I make something wrong in the
future, can you indulge me once?
Yes. Of course.
- Really?
- How can I deceive you?
Then you should sign me a note.
Okay. It's not a big deal.
Let me get a pen and a note.
Stay here and wait for me.
Stop there.
If you go, how can I experience it?
Fine. This way, please.
How am I?
Awesome.
Faster than I.
What to write?
Turn around.
Okay.
Just write "Li Tiantian will indulge
Jin Xi's fault once without preconditions."
Then sign your name.
So simple.
It's a solemn promise. Not simple.
Indulge... Jin Xi's fault...
once...
without preconditions.
It's done.
Let me see.
Why are you so happy?
It's like you've really
made a significant mistake.
What's the matter?
Keep it.
If you'd like to "indulge" me,
then let me see it.
If not,
you can cremate or throw it as you wish.
Then I won't tangle with you anymore.
I see.
Keep it well.
I'm done.
By the way, how did you make that bubble tea?
Tell me the recipe.
It's my secret recipe,
which is concluded
by drinking bubble tea for a month.
So how can I tell you so easily?
Oh, dear. I'm your girlfriend, okay?
So flexible. You still can kick me.
Come on. Try again.
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
Yu Meiren.
You're really something.
You wouldn't need to leave in a hurry
if the forum wasn't held in advance.
Can you catch the plane?
You're not in good condition.
Are you too tired?
If so, we can be absent this time.
Anyway, you've delivered the paper.
It's the achievement of the whole group.
I'll let the world see it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
To ensure you a good rest,
now we'll dim the cab lights.
We advise you to keep your seat belt fastened,
as a precaution against sudden turbulence.
Sorry. I left in a hurry
because of sudden work.
I'm now at... You can turn on
the reading light above your head.
[Low battery. Auto power off.]
♫ I want to stand beside you ♫
♫ adjoining your shoulder ♫
♫ I want to guard our memories ♫
♫ If I can pretend ♫
♫ In fact, my happiest moment ♫
It's quite like the one sold in the store.
Boss Tian, you really know a lot.
It's my secret recipe.
Have you contacted Professor Zhuang after that?
No.
It's been a long time.
Why aren't worried about it?
How can a girl express her mind first?
Besides, I've gained insight into his mind.
He can't escape from my control.
Fate has determined everything.
Maybe it's suitable for others.
But I think you need to be active with him.
Really?
You can choke when you're drinking
so what else can you do?
Just listen to me. Be proactive.
Fine. I'll have a try.
Do you remember the story of being stood up?
I've organized my words.
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Let's meet at the botanic garden at 10.
He doesn't like mosquito repellent.
If he waits for me here,
he must be bitten everywhere.
Lady.
It's in strong ultraviolet and
has many mosquitoes here.
Why don't you stay in the shadow?
Life needs to be gilded,
which means we need to bask.
Besides, I have an anti-mosquito bracelet.
Aunt.
Do you still work here?
Do you know me?
I've been here before.
I don't want to discourage you
but I've seen it so many times before.
The boys who let girls wait for them for so long
won't come to meet them.
Just see around.
Look at me, aunt.
I am pretty, right?
I have a good figure, right?
Just like a star.
So is he willing to stand me up?
No... He's unwilling to do so.
Uncle, how much is the bubble machine?
30 for one. 40 for two.
Too expensive.
Sorry, the number you dialed is powered off.
Please try again later.
Open the door.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
So weird.
Is he immersing himself in the experiments?
Lv Jian!
Miss Meiren.
Where's your Professor Zhuang?
Prof. Zhuang... He's left... Hasn't he told you?
Left?
He's not at home.
Did we miss each other?
He's gone abroad.
Abroad?
He's gone there for academic purposes.
He can't come back for a short time.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Excuse me, what would like to drink?
- Water.
- Okay.
Local time is 6:10 pm.
It's a sunny day.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen.
We'll arrive at our destination in one hour.
Excuse me, sir. What would you like to drink?
Water, please.
Okay.
What's going on? I...
I must wash it today.
- I can't...
- Why?
- I refuse.
- You're disgusting!
Why do you walk in a hurry?
The shoes are hard to walk in.
Could you have tenderness toward me?
So are you a tender girl?
- Don't want to wash...
- Young lady!
You can't have a result with a man
who needs you to chase.
The range of girls chasing men
is thin like paper.
If he likes you, it's a paper.
If not, it's a stainless steel window screen!
He won't accept you! You should give up!
Well... What do you mean?
We're talking about who washes dishes today.
What do you mean?
Weren't you chasing him?
He washes every time.
Can't I wash once?
Because you can't make them clear.
- Hit me again?
- Bye.
- You can't catch me.
- If so, I'll keep it short!
If so, you still can't get the final happiness.
Watch out.
Are you okay?
Miss Meiren, are you fine?
Why are you here?
I... My friend asked me to
dance nearby... Fine. Move on.
Otherwise, it'll close. I have to leave now.
Let me send you back.
No thanks. I'll soon arrive.
Miss Meiren.
It seems your home is over there.
I want to buy something first.
Miss Meiren.
If you're unhappy, you can tell me.
Why am I unhappy? I'm so good.
I'm really worried about you.
Why?
Is it because of Professor Zhuang?
No. Unfaithful lover Zhuang!
Be at ease.
I have many ways to ruin him.
Stop!
He and I...
Professor Zhuang Yu and I are not lovers.
Nothing unfaithful.
Don't treat me as a victim.
I'm not that fragile.
Forget it.
Are you hungry? Let's have something tasty.
I'm losing weight.
Then we can go dancing.
Exercising is the best way to lose weight.
Wait a second. I'll arrange it.
Do you think I look sad?
Go to play yourself.
I want to stay alone.
I've seemly met this expression before.
I have to tell Miss Tiantian first.
Are you tired? I can move myself.
I'm fine. We haven't walked long.
Don't move. I can do it.
I see.
Thank you.
- Let's sit here.
- Okay.
It's fine.
The urban market is quite busy.
Just like our rural festivals.
That's it.
I really like our lovers' phone cases.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Please enjoy it.
So many toppings?
Just like a mixed congee. Can it be tasty?
Bubble tea should be drunk in this way.
People always say "all toppings, entire joys."
Let me have a try.
Hello?
Handsome boy?
What?
I see. Okay.
I have something urgent to do now.
Shall I go with you?
My bestie was fooled.
I have to console her.
What's going on?
In short, whoever
cheat others' feelings need to die.
Is that too serious?
Could it be a white lie?
How can you defend an unfaithful man?
No! I have no relations with an unfaithful man!
I have to leave now.
Uncle Fang will come to pick you up.
I don't know her alarm level now.
Hold on! Alarm level? Tell me about it.
According to the dramas and our experiment,
I find that there are levels
for sadness and anger.
Tell me some details.
A blue warning signal means she's out of wits.
So weird.
Why is there a pheasant?
It sounds quite serious.
Serious, right?
Anyway, it's the lowest level.
Severer?
A yellow warning signal means she's moody.
[Zhuang Yu]
[Delete contact "Zhuang Yu".]
Oh, please. Don't leave me alone...
Good-for-nothing!
Why are you crying for a trivial?
The kitchen knife is extremely sharp.
It can cut almost everything.
Let's demonstrate it to you.
It can cut both vegetables and meats.
Nice cut!
I've never thought she's so dramatic.
What did you say?
Nothing. Any color else?
Yes. Of course.
Close to me.
All in all, don't tease girls.
I have to go now. Tell you next time.
Wait a moment.
- Take care.
- I see.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Why don't they relapse?
If my legs relapse,
it doesn't mean I cheat on her, right?
Hello.
I'm leaving.
If you want to clean the room,
you can place an order on the mini apps.
We'll be here at once.
I see. Take care.
Goodbye.
Meiren, how are you?
So nice.
Close your eyes.
Why are you here? Aren't you dating?
Breathe naturally.
Slacken yourself.
Oh, my! So tidy!
It's messy so I asked her to clean it.
Orange warning signal.
What would you like to drink?
I've made some vegetable juice.
You can make juice.
As my knife is blunt, chunks are a little big.
But luckily, the juicer is awesome.
Your finger!
Where's Band-Aid?
Old place, right?
I don't need it. It's not painful.
I bought a new knife from TV shopping.
Let's try when it arrives.
There are three glasses here.
Broccoli, celery and coriander.
Which one do you want?
Until your whole body is comfortable.
Then move your head and neck
gently toward left and right.
How is it?
Is it fresh?
What happened to you two?
Zhuang Yu...
How can I think about this kind of man?
Professor Zhuang.
You've finally arrived.
Come in, please.
It's hard for you to travel for so long.
The signal here is poor.
I hope you haven't missed
any important messages.
How should I call you?
Forget to introduce ourselves.
Professor Giannandrea is our teacher.
We're asked to bring you some furniture.
- You can call me Li Lei.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Professor Zhuang. I'm Lucy.
Good to meet you both.
- Sorry.
- Fine.
Let's help him put things in his room.
Do you remember the story of being stood up?
I've organized my words.
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Let's meet at the botanic garden at 10.
Sorry.
I just got off the plane.
I thought to say goodbye to you face to face.
Anyhow, you were out.
Then I decide to tell you when I arrive.
Have you waited for a long time?
[You're not friends.]
Delete contact?
Deep breath.
Relax.
That's a resolute decision.
Don't you give him a chance to explain?
Explain?
Do I lack an explanation?
"My phone was robbed."
"The signal tower is down."
"My luggage was stolen."
"The plane crashed."
I can fabricate 100 different explanations.
But are they useful?
Is it his reason to leave without telling me?
Is there any misunderstanding?
Such as a white lie?
It's right.
Maybe it's a white lie
which makes me think
that I'm important to him.
Anyhow, it's just self-deception.
I don't think your love is a lie.
We all know how he treats you.
Does he have no idea how to tell you?
It doesn't matter. I don't mind anymore.
Falling down once may be
because of the shoes or the road.
Falling down at the same place twice
could only be my own reason.
Essentially, it's my own business.
Not a matter of someone else.
Don't worry.
I've reconciled myself.
I feel so good.
Are you sure?
Take a rest first.
I need to go out now.
Where are you going?
Collect bird droppings.
Oh, my goodness. Red warning signal.
Wait for me.
So many sparrows here.
We can always see their droppings.
Sparrow.
Parus major.
What?
It's a parus major.
Parus major is also your relative?
Yes.
I've told you I'm familiar with the mountain.
It seems it isn't familiar with you.
I haven't come back for a long time
so it needs time to know me again.
People always think they
outclass the creatures
close to them in zoology.
Anyhow, everyone will look up at birds.
You can recognize a fleeting bird?
If my memory serves me,
last time Professor Giannandrea told me that
he was a professor in botany.
Obviously, Professor Zhuang's
memory is retentive.
Some memories are just tough to be forgotten.
[The animal in this scene is made by CG.]
Don't you enjoy sleeping?
What's wrong with you?
Gathering them all night?
Energy of Universe
only can be absorbed in the morning.
Forget the energy.
You haven't had breakfast, right?
I've brought it for you. Try some.
I'm really hungry.
Thank you.
Not this.
Here you are.
Have some soya milk. Don't choke.
As an old saying goes, "Tomorrow is another day".
It's getting late.
Go to a date with your president.
Oh, come on.
Not date. It's my job.
Job is a good thing.
Better than the bullshit love.
Tiantian.
You need to get them both.
Your president sounds like a good man.
Cherish him.
The time is up. I have to go to work now.
Go ahead.
Don't forget to eat them all.
Have some soya milk if you choke.
Don't eat the wrong one.
Be at ease. I'm not a child.
Kids have few vexations.
Here are the work that BD team have got.
As Xiaofang is not
here... I'll check them.
Yu Meiren is in poor condition recently.
Don't forget to find
some alternates in advance.
Okay.
Come in.
Then I'll go out to work.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Sorry for being late.
I went to see my bestie first.
Don't say so.
How is she? Which level?
Red warning signal. A great calamity.
A great calamity? How great?
It's a long story.
Just tell me.
[A fish head]
Why don't answer it?
It's the fish head seller. Just ignore her.
She must have something
to talk to you. Answer it.
Then I'll answer it.
Aunt Wang!
The fish you sent was quite nice!
Two more fish just like that!
Money... Right...
What's wrong?
Water.
You... Water...
Go ahead.
President Jin, you're so unreasonable.
Aunt? Fish?
Are you drunk in the daytime?
No. I got it wrong.
By the way, how are you these days?
Why do you all ask that?
I'm so nice.
My zeal for work
is higher than your imagination.
You're quite right.
I have a great plan.
Move on.
Innocent or charming make-up
is popular, right?
They're all trying to please men.
I think they're all obsolete.
- Sounds reasonable.
- I know it's right.
Besides, many festivals are coming
so all relatives will take turns to ask girls
whether they have a boyfriend or not.
If not, they'll arrange blind dates for you.
It's possible.
It's a certainty.
Are you bothered and agitated by the blind dates?
I haven't had it before so I don't know.
It's not bad if the girl is pretty.
No.
In fact, many girls don't like it
but they have to cope with their families.
What do they want to get from the date?
Love? No!
They want to get out of it after it's finished.
What is love?
You know it best
for you have so many love affairs.
It lapses so fast.
Hold on.
How many love affairs do I have?
I've just had my first love.
Stop nonsense. Get to the point.
Forget it. You're not an independent lady
so you can't understand it.
Based on the new demand of independent women,
I invent an anti-blind-date make-up for them.
Forbid them to fall in love with you.
Staying away from men
will bring you a brilliant future!
Oh, yes. Exactly right.
Fine, I see.
Okay, then wait for it.
Okay. Thank you, Sister Wang.
Sister or aunt?
Forget it. Sit down.
Hello, everyone.
I'm your favorite blogger,
Mermaid With Long Legs.
I'll bring you a special make-up today.
We all hate to have a blind-date at festivals.
Are you getting tired
of laughing hypocritically?
Have you had enough of
being remarked without dignity?
As long as you learn
this anti-blind-date make-up,
it's like you're armed.
Drive your dread of blind-date away.
Smoky eyes show your eagerness for freedom.
From now on, you don't need to be a mild wife.
Taupe and plum are obsolete.
Only puce can match your make-up.
Puce brings us a sense of never returning.
It should be the attitude of independent ladies.
Quite special.
Compared with men,
we should gain safety from the make-up.
Look at her.
She really knows
to grasp independent women's hearts.
Puce!
Puce brings us a sense of termination.
No update for three days?
Isn't she a daily-update blogger?
It shouldn't be like this.
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
Why does the leading actor
appear so little in this episode?
♫ How did you make my heart flip ♫
Don't look at him.
Look at me.
[The real love expressed by universal language]
[won't stop a man to pursue his fate.]
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ You make all the stars in the sky shine for me ♫
♫ I can sail a boat in the starry river ♫
♫ Love is like sweet honey in our hearts ♫
♫ Even the air is filled with the scent of flowers ♫