♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet with the best one ♫
♫ The bird makes a promise to the forest ♫
♫ A brave response ♫
♫ makes my world clear up ♫
♫ The voices in my heart ♫
♫ are all about you at the moment ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
♫ are as splendid as dreams ♫
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
[A Romance of the Little Forest]
[Episode 14]
[A lie needs to be covered up with a thousand lies]
Hold on.
Act after five minutes.
Copy that.
What's wrong, President Jin?
Nothing.
How's the soap I gave you?
Not bad, it's fragrant.
But the bubble is not much.
The clothes can't be well cleaned.
The clothes?
Yes.
Since it's given by the brand,
I can't ask too much.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
I'll give you the report soon.
That soap... was
used to wash face.
You don't know that?
People use facial cleanser to wash face now.
No one will use soap to wash face now.
President Jin.
Are you still using soap to wash your face?
No.
Time has changed.
Who will use soap to wash face now?
I use a facial cleanser.
Facial cleanser.
Three minutes left.
Okay.
What are you watching?
Classic romance a few years ago.
Reviewing the past to know the present.
You won't like it.
President Jin, thank you
for letting me watch TV series while waiting.
It's no big deal.
Can I watch it?
I've never seen a romance.
Here.
Fireworks?
Romantic, right?
I'm sorry to say so,
but this is out of fashion now.
Out of fashion?
Yes, it was romantic back then.
But it's out of date now.
President Jin, why hasn't the person
you're waiting for arrived yet?
It's okay.
Cancel it! Cancel it!
This...
Well, what happened?
Time has changed.
Someone is still lighting fireworks?
It's out of date now.
It's out of fashion.
Failure is nothing.
Life is experiencing.
Soap bubbles, fireworks,
these are ephemeral.
It's okay if you don't like it.
This gift will accompany you
to the end of the world.
You want to give me lipsticks?
Yes, the company sent it to me yesterday,
and said it's essential for the company's image.
I'm just helping to push the wheelchair.
Why am I related to the image?
A single one or a box of lipsticks?
A box of them, about a dozen lipsticks.
There are many colors.
I can't even recognize them.
How can I use it?
That should be expensive.
Is your boss interested in you?
Impossible.
Let me tell you,
the essence of a capitalist is exploitation.
He gave me a soap last time,
so I stayed up late to write a 1000-word report.
He gave me lipsticks this time.
Obviously, he wants to remind me
of making up before going to work.
Really? Tell me what brand it is.
I'll help you to judge what he wants to do.
Let me have a look.
It's like a "Zheng" without a crossing.
Have you heard of it?
"Zheng" without a crossing?
No.
I guess it's a small brand.
What company is it?
Why do they accept promotions from all brands?
I guess so.
If it's expensive,
the company won't give it to me.
But I don't know how to make up.
I thought you are a makeup blogger,
so you can use them.
Cheap lipsticks for me?
Well done, Boss Tian.
You're so generous.
Okay, tell me,
what do you want me to do?
How did you know that?
I didn't say anything yet.
Of course, or you won't get up so early.
And I just told you about the lipsticks.
But you called me directly.
I guess even a famous brand lipstick
is not so attractive.
Boss Tian, you're so smart.
Okay, enough.
Come on, or the capitalist
will force me to work later.
Okay, to be brief.
Two things.
First, I think Zhuang Yu is not bad.
Not bad? He's perfect, right?
So my three-step verification method worked?
Kind of.
I'm magnanimous, right?
I've even forgiven him
for mocking me
and standing me up when I confessed my love.
It's not because you're magnanimous.
It's because Straight-A Zhuang
is like a leading actor in TV series.
Since he has fallen for you,
can you tell him you're his schoolmate?
Let me see the romance
of a Straight-A couple.
No, he stood me up back then.
I can also make a fool of him now.
I'll let him taste the same feeling.
Okay, about this,
find a good time to tell him about it.
Tell me what the second thing is.
I need to work now.
The second thing is complicated.
If someone can tell your mom about it,
he must know you well,
and know people in Qingshui Village.
Which aunt sent this picture?
I didn't notice this.
I'll ask my mom about it.
Mei, I've prepared today's necessaries.
It's at the reception desk.
Bring it to Zhuang later.
Okay, where is Meinan?
He went out.
He won't tell me where he went.
Just let him be.
Mom, you told me...
Hello, everyone.
I'm Mermaid With Long Legs.
What are you watching?
Isn't this you?
What is this?
Mermaid With Long Legs?
What is it?
I'm not good-looking, stop watching.
Why?
What is this?
I got bored recently,
so I recorded my life.
Record your life?
Why did you say "everyone"?
I'm saying hello
to the customers that will buy grapes.
What customers?
Tiantian's grapes are unsalable, right?
I want to make a video,
and introduce the grapes in Qingshui Village
to my colleagues in the school.
Tiantian's family did harvest many grapes.
Your colleagues can buy
all the grapes her family harvested?
There are not only my colleagues of course.
I'll ask them to send the video.
More people will know about it,
so more people will buy it.
So it's you that made the grapes
in Qingshui Village sell so well?
Yes.
Look at them.
How annoying they are!
Slandering you behind your back.
They said you became a blogger,
fooling around all day long,
and you also made Tiantian do that.
Why can't being a blogger be called a job?
I don't know about bloggers.
They told me,
it's an unstable job.
Mom, don't listen to what they said.
First, blogger is a serious job.
Second,
why is being a blogger unstable?
A blogger is paying
more effort than any of them, okay?
You really know this industry well.
Not exactly.
This is commonsense.
Give me that.
I want to watch it.
No need.
I'm not good-looking.
Why not?
You are the one with long legs.
I'll see how long your legs are. Give it to me.
Is there something I can't watch in it?
Just watch it.
There is nothing you can't watch.
Mom, where did Aunt Guilan get this video?
I was so furious in the group chat,
so they didn't dare to send it to the group.
Wang Xiumei sent it to her own group.
When Aunt Guilan saw it,
she sent it to me and asked me about it.
They're annoying, right?
Why do they make rumors about a teacher?
It's so evil.
Okay, don't be angry.
It's not worthwhile to be angry at it.
How could I not be angry?
They made rumors about you.
What do they want?
I really hate those dishonest people.
What a pity.
What is a pity?
Mom, what's your name
in Qingshui Village's chat group?
Half Boss in Qingshui Village.
What's wrong?
I guess you're
a Quarter Boss in Qingshui Village now.
Why?
Did half of your group members
add Aunt Xiumei's group?
Yes.
Well done, Wang Xiumei.
She created a small group secretly.
Yes.
She really didn't pay any respect to you.
Mom, tell me if you get any clue.
Don't forget about the necessaries.
[Zhuang Yu, Date of birth: 1993-09-16]
The fan club has investigated
his birthday and constellation for long.
And I got it so easily.
Luckily, Ms. Feng has a homestay hotel.
Thank you.
Is this okay?
Yes, yes.
Enjoy your lunch.
Call me after you finish it.
What's wrong?
Don't leave.
There will be a buffet later.
How about eating together?
Then I'll push you there.
- I'll leave after you finished.
- I didn't mean that.
Lunchtime is short.
How about you eating here as well?
Oh no.
What about my rice noodles?
Eating here?
Forget it.
I'll pick you up after I finished eating.
See you later.
Well...
Housekeeping.
So tidy.
His constellation is indeed Virgo.
He even didn't take his bag.
He shouldn't be far away.
♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet with the bright weather ♫
♫ Meet someone ♫
It's so hot, what is he looking at?
♫ A casual response ♫
♫ And my lonely world brightened ♫
♫ The voice in my mind ♫
♫ I was cured even if I ignored it ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
What does it feel to fall
in love with someone?
Whether I'm with him or not,
I'll be happy,
when I think of him.
I don't want him to be with someone else.
He can only be with me.
[Wang Xiumei, why did you
create a group chat secretly?]
I want to do something for him.
And do more.
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
Here.
See? The long queue.
An old saying goes,
there must be something good
if there is a queue.
I noticed this food stand the
first day I came to work here.
Because I eat here every day,
the boss saved me a seat.
Here, the rice noodles you always order.
Thank you.
Not bad.
The soup is clear.
It's delicious and not too salty.
The rice noodles are not sticky.
It's fresh, sour and delicious.
But it's not spicy enough.
Maybe it wants to cater to local tastes.
Boss, give me some chili oil.
Okay.
Come on, eat.
It's delicious when the rice noodles are hot.
Chili oil, add it yourself.
I didn't imagine you look like an ass...
you dress in a suit,
and don't match with this little food stand.
You seemed like an expert
when you were commenting on it.
I understand a little.
See? Much better now?
Yes.
I didn't imagine you're so nice, President Jin.
You came to this little food stand with me.
It's no big deal.
When I was starting my business,
I had no money to eat.
I ate two bowls of instant noodles every day.
Really?
You're such an ass...
You're such a person
who emphasizes the quality of life,
but you ate instant noodles?
The quality of life is just a habit.
I don't think what I eat matters.
If I'm rich, I can eat something good.
If I'm poor, I'll eat instant noodles.
Besides,
instant noodles have so many flavors.
I may taste something fresh if I eat more.
I didn't imagine you're not born rich
with a silver spoon, President Jin.
Silver spoon.
It's more reliable to use my spoon.
And others won't take it away from you.
He is pompous and competitive.
Interesting.
What are you talking about? Just eat.
I didn't imagine
you're so sincere and hardworking, President Jin.
According to your physical condition,
you must have suffered more than you said
to gain your achievements now.
I think my understanding
of you is a little too superficial.
Okay, this lunch is on me.
Boss.
Add a dish of stinky tofu.
Thank you, President Jin.
Do you need to make up after lunch?
Make up?
You mean the lipstick?
Silly me.
I left it in the company.
Sorry, President Jin.
I'll care about my image,
and won't lose your face.
This is almost done, right?
Well, Professor Zhuang,
you're sunbathing with them together?
By getting along with them all the time,
I can sense every tiny change in them.
Getting along with? You mean with the plants?
I heard of this word for the first time.
Thank you for your water.
What water? I just came here.
Nothing.
He may feel comfortable with a little stool.
Why do people studying botany look like wood?
Aren't they afraid of rain or wind?
People don't need photosynthesis.
Too much sun exposure
will increase the risk of skin cancer.
Pay more attention
to sun protection during field investigation.
Why does this sound like a makeup blogger?
No, I need to be straightforward.
Hello, bro.
I haven't contacted you for long.
I wonder if everything goes well.
The sun is hot in summer.
Remember to have some sun protection.
Why do I feel it's strange?
Perfect.
I didn't imagine
you're so sincere and hardworking, President Jin.
According to your physical condition,
you must have suffered more than you said
to gain your achievements now.
I can't hide it anymore.
Come in.
President Jin.
It's Qin Ya's activity.
They want to give Meiren a chance
to interview their spokesperson alone,
and are asking about our opinion.
Qin Ya's spokesperson
is the new star in the TV series.
It seems Qin Ya values Yu Meiren.
Meiren's countryside VLOG matches well
with the concept
of organic healthy life Qin Ya advocated.
Well, say yes first,
and thank Qin Ya for the chance they offered us.
We'll draft an interview outline soon.
I'll contact Yu Meiren.
Ask about the preferences
of Qin Ya's spokesperson in China,
and arrange a meeting for us.
Okay.
Go ahead.
President Jin.
How's the coffee machine?
Not bad, thank you.
What's wrong, President Jin?
It's just a Qin Ya's activity.
Why do you urge me so many times?
Will I waste time saying craps?
No, you won't. Just say it.
The exclusive interview of a new star?
Well done, you can even find this chance for me.
Of course, I'm almighty.
But,
Qin Ya gave you this chance themselves.
The atmosphere you're creating
matches with the character
the new star wants to build.
Am I sincere?
Yes.
Right? I also think so.
Even if there is something I didn't tell you,
I did it out of good will.
You can understand, right?
Yes.
Compared with your hard work,
this is not worth mentioning.
You really think so?
Tell me more about it.
Okay.
I've been friends with you for so many years.
I know you well.
You're just a gentle sheep
covered in a wolf coat.
But I feel you're strange today.
Well, nothing.
Can you give me the interview outline tomorrow?
The interview will last for ten minutes.
The brand and the star will check it.
Tomorrow? That's too hurried.
Dear President Jin.
Considering that
I flattered you so much just now,
can you give me one more day?
No, I asked you to be sincere.
Who asked you to flatter me?
Okay, it's my fault.
Then can you feel my sincerity again?
There is only one day,
you're asking too much from me.
Okay, okay.
I can give you half a day more at most.
When do you want to come back?
I'll ask Xiaofang to order you a ticket.
It's okay, I can do it myself.
I'll tell you after I order it.
Okay, I'll hang up.
I need to prepare the interview outline.
After you went to the village,
you can take care of yourself well.
Well done, Yu Meiren.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Oh no, I came in without knocking at the door.
He'll blame me.
How did you come in?
The door is open.
I knocked and there was no response,
so I came in directly.
Oh no, did I call Yu Meiren's name just now?
But don't worry.
I didn't hear a word
about the beauty you're talking with.
It's your privacy.
I won't ask,
or tell anyone about it.
I shall leave if you don't need me.
Call me if you need me.
Well...
It's not what you think.
What do you mean by it's not what I think?
I didn't say anything yet.
Then, what do you want to know?
Tell me, interviewing that new star,
what does that mean?
Let me explain it to you.
Mom, are you thirsty?
Do you want some water?
I'm not thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I'll get a cup of water.
Wait.
Drink this.
Mom, it feels like
you're interrogating a criminal.
Why are you nervous?
I'm not nervous.
Here's the thing.
The new term is going to begin.
There will be an evening party.
The school invited a new star,
and I'm the anchor.
So I need to prepare an interview outline.
You mean, the new star will go to your school?
Really?
Mom, why don't you trust me?
Professor Zhuang.
The evening party
in your school will invite stars?
Please, please.
Mom, look at you.
You don't trust me,
and you listened to the rumors about me.
Zhuang may laugh at us.
Of course I trust you.
I'm just caring about you.
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not nervous.
Mom, you heard about it.
I'll leave soon.
Or, I'll be late for the party.
Zhuang's work is almost finished.
We'll leave together.
You'll leave so soon?
But there is one more thing.
You didn't forget about it, right?
[This animal was made by CG]
Have you heard of it?
People always feel that they
are higher than those creatures
only one step away from themselves
in the sense of zoology.
But people will look up at the birds.
Their world
is something beyond
those constrained human beings.
You also sometimes feel constrained,
Professor Zhuang?
It's getting dark, let's go.
It's still so bright.
Is your old watch reliable?
You've collected Artemisia annua.
I said you'll leave this week.
It's not too fake, right?
I bought the ticket on Friday.
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't ask me.
We're still in Qingshui Village,
so you're still my boyfriend.
If you didn't tell me,
what if people found out the truth about us?
Let me tell you,
if you leave without telling me,
I'll be angry.
I told you about it now.
But I asked about it first.
Take this.
Remember to apply it before going out.
Be careful of skin cancer.
This...
Reef Safe, you can even use it in the sea.
I've checked it for you.
Just take it as a reward
for helping me to keep this secret from my mom.
You told a lie,
then you need
to make it up with a thousand lies.
You think I don't want to tell the truth?
My parents' idea is conservative.
In their eyes,
what I'm doing now is not a serious job.
Not to mention my parents,
think of yourself.
The first time you saw me,
you didn't give me a good face.
I stayed in the mountain for two weeks.
I didn't eat or sleep well.
My face must be pretty bad.
You earn money with your ability.
There is nothing to be misunderstood.
Your rising constellation is Capricorn, right?
Seriously,
tell me your exact birth time.
I'll check it for you.
No, thanks.
Tell me about it.
Don't call this pseudoscience.
It has statistical support.
Okay, fine.
Even if there is no statistical support,
it's interesting to analyze it.
If you tell me,
you can know more about yourself.
And I can know more...
It's Capricorn.
My rising constellation is Capricorn.
You know it?
Someone told me about it.
You said you don't believe it,
but you remember it so clearly.
And I can see it even if you don't tell me.
It's not a total pseudoscience, right?
Mom, what are these?
It's too much.
It's not much.
Walnut, to make you smarter.
This is black sesame,
to make your hair darker.
And this is black wolfberry.
It's good for your eyes.
I can buy these on the Internet.
Those are not as good as mine.
These are natural and pollution-free.
Take it.
I can't eat them all myself.
Who said it's only for you?
It's also for Zhuang.
Zhuang has so much hair.
He doesn't need walnut or black sesame.
Just take it.
It's so heavy.
Let me help you, Miss Meiren.
Thank you.
Come on, give it to me.
It's okay, uncle. Have some rest.
I'll do it as exercise.
Okay, thank you, Lv.
It's okay.
You'll leave today?
Yes, I'll leave with you.
Didn't you arrange a luxury car for yourself?
Where is your car?
Here is it. I wonder if I can get a seat.
Of course.
But I can only send you to the town.
Get in.
Mei, listen to me,
you can work in the daytime.
Don't stay up late.
It's bad for your health.
Learn from Zhuang.
Catch up with his position soon.
Don't worry.
The leaders all like me.
Besides, I need time
to write essays and do analyses.
Yes, you're right.
Strange,
you barely mention your leader.
My leaders are the old professors in the school.
What? You want to call them, mom?
No need.
I have nothing in common
with those old scholars.
You're still interrogating and doubting me.
I'm not.
I found it out yesterday.
Wang Xiumei's relatives heard about it.
Actually, they are jealous of you.
I blocked them.
And I told Guilan,
don't tell me about these anymore.
Then why did you ask so much?
I'm worried about you
since you're working outside.
I want to call your leader
and ask him to care about you.
But I don't need to do that now.
You have Zhuang.
Zhuang, take care of her for me.
Okay, aunt.
He agreed so quickly?
But what's his face?
Zhuang, you're colleagues.
Take care of each other in work and life.
Don't worry, uncle.
What does this mean?
Afraid that I'll stick to you?
Don't worry.
I've been living alone for all these years.
Okay, well,
put that black sesame
in the fridge when you arrived.
It can be kept for a year.
Remember to eat it.
- Okay.
- Okay,
you've said that black sesame so many times.
Time is limited.
Just go, or it will be late.
Just go.
Don't forget to call me when you arrive.
Mom, why did you cry suddenly?
It's okay.
I just can't bear to part with you.
Okay, time is limited.
Don't be sad, I'll be back soon, mom.
Just go.
Okay, okay.
Goodbye, uncle and aunt.
Be careful.
Take care of yourself.
They're leaving, don't be sad.
Thank you.
Sister, Shanghai is not far from our hometown.
Come back if you have time.
I haven't talked much with you this time.
Where have you been recently?
Why didn't I see you?
Nothing.
What? You like other girls in the village?
Nonsense, it's not like that.
Then why did you stammer?
I went to Li Tiantian's home.
Tiantian is not there,
why did you go there?
Because she is not there,
Grandma Li can't
take care of the grape yard herself,
so I went to help her.
Well done, boy.
Give it to me.
Thanks.
[Internship Report]
Don't thank me.
I won't sign on a specious internship report.
Miss Meiren.
I can help you to take it back home.
It's okay, Professor Zhuang is here.
I'm sure he would do this little favor for me.
Goodbye.
Then goodbye, Miss Meiren.
See you the day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
Professor Zhuang, wait for me.
He becomes an iceberg man again.
Zhuang, take care of her for me.
Okay, aunt.
Why is he like this?
Not to mention other things,
at least we are friends now.
Why does he feel so reluctant
to say something nice?
Afraid that I'll stick to you?
No.
I've been trying hard for so long,
how can I quit at the last moment?
What is wrong with him?
He didn't go to sleep late at night?
The alarm is over.
You don't need to act so hard in the future.
And thank you for posting our photo.
There is no group in your WeChat,
so everyone can see our photo.
If you mind,
just delete the photo.
Is he still in bed?
Morning.
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
Hello, bro, besides watching birds,
I also know something about astronomy.
I observed the sky at night,
and found your forehead is dark recently.
Only with sun lotion,
can you escape a disaster.
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ You make all the stars in the sky shine for me ♫
♫ I can sail a boat in the starry river ♫
♫ Love is like sweet honey in our hearts ♫
♫ Even the air is filled with the scent of flowers ♫