♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet with the best one ♫
♫ The bird makes a promise to the forest ♫
♫ A brave response ♫
♫ makes my world clear up ♫
♫ The voices in my heart ♫
♫ are all about you at the moment ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
♫ are as splendid as dreams ♫
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
[A Romance of the Little Forest]
[Episode 26]
[When you truly desire something,
the entire universe will help you]
Tiantian,
there is no way to make western desserts
in this kitchen.
But on the rice cakes,
I added a lot of brown sugar
to make them sweet.
Why haven't you left yet?
Thanks to Jin today.
I didn't know your tastes changed so much.
When did you love meat so much?
Grandma, Jin Xi is just my colleague.
How does he know what I like to eat?
I don't think colleagues
will use this pair of phone cases.
Don't overthink it.
I can't be bothered changing it.
Come on, let's eat.
Thank you.
Jin.
I'll cut it for you.
No, thank you.
Come on, eat.
Do you have to anatomize them?
Could they die of illness?
These Common Teal bodies
were found in the same depression.
Died of illness?
Not so coincidental.
No blood around the eyes or mouth.
Does not meet the characteristics
of the death.
An autopsy is required
to determine the true cause of death.
This is?
Carbofuran. Pesticide.
Carbofuran is very toxic.
A packet can poison twenty.
It's on the list of wildlife with important
ecological, scientific and social value.
Illegal hunting of over twenty wild animals
can be filed in a case.
Call the police.
The situation you mentioned,
in fact, we have already recorded it.
The birds are dense in the wetlands here.
Poachers were more rampant in earlier years.
The common method of poaching
is to set up nets.
One is called a flipping net.
To find a piece of water in advance.
Set up the net.
Put a few domestic ducks in as matchmakers.
What matchmakers?
The decoys that lure the Common Teal.
Ducks are herd animals.
When they see their own kind, they will go over.
That's right.
You can catch dozens of them in one net.
There is another kind, called sticky net.
It's to set up nets in the reeds and forests.
When the bird flies,
once hit it, they can't get down.
All these years,
we've pitted our wits against the poachers.
They have a strong sense of
anti-reconnaissance.
Seeing us and volunteers,
they won't go over to pick them up.
Even if we catch the poisoners,
they will say they're spraying pesticides.
Caught picking up bird carcasses,
they won't admit that they poisoned.
Wetland reeds are so obscured from view.
It's difficult to enforce.
Since poachers are repeat offenders,
do you know who it is?
Jia San?
Do you all know him?
Xue and I met Jia San before.
I felt that he was particularly suspicious.
So I went after to check it.
He scolded us badly.
When we solve a case,
we need to form a complete chain of evidence.
From suspects buying drugs, spilling drugs,
catching, killing, processing to selling,
we all need to collect evidence.
The terrain here is complex.
Our police force is also not enough.
Unless...
we can capture Jia San with the stolen birds.
Otherwise,
it's difficult to take further action.
Now that we know who the poisoner is,
we can catch him.
I heard that Jia San is like a ghost.
It's not that easy to catch him.
Since he has poisoned,
he'll definitely pick up the body today.
I just need to wait in the depression.
At least I can confirm
if the poacher is Jia San.
No, Miss Meiren, it's too dangerous.
How about we go together?
Too many people and he knows you.
In case Jia San finds out,
he'll be more alert.
Next time it'll be harder to capture him.
But...
Think about the dissected Common Teal.
There is no food in his stomach.
Only gravel and poison.
The waterland is shrinking.
It is not easy for them to find food.
They were hungry,
and were just looking for water to drink.
Who knew they would lose their life?
It shouldn't be like this.
This is supposed to be their home.
So don't argue with me on this matter.
Catching poachers one day early,
one less bird to die.
Dusk is the first peak of bird activity.
Jia San is still not coming.
Could he wait for
the second peak of bird activity?
He is too greedy.
[The animals in this scene are made by CG.]
It's you.
Just two!
Mr. Wang, I'm checking the goods.
I know it's a big deal for you.
I should prepare enough goods for you, right?
How can it be compared with first class
and second class national protected animals?
First class and second class? Is there a team?
Tomorrow, no, Mr. Wang,
give me two more days, okay?
I've been watched these days.
I really can't do anything.
Who else can it be?
Just those people.
The volunteers.
They'll get themselves killed.
They dare to get in my way.
If I meet them, I'll
teach them a lesson.
Who is it?
You want to die, do you?
Dare to get in my way!
Come out! Who is there?
Don't shout. It's me.
Come out.
Hug me.
Come on.
Who?
What's going on here?
What the...
Stay close to me.
Rotten luck.
I didn't find the ducks but illicit lovers.
Is he gone?
Not yet.
Still not gone? Did he find us?
You lied to me.
Liar.
Why are you so close to me?
No, I just want to thank you
for walking with me all the way back.
Don't flatter yourself.
If Grandma hadn't given you so many things,
I don't want to make such a trip.
Yes.
Want to take a break?
I heard that the stars in the countryside
are particularly bright at night.
Look at this view. It's so good.
Do you remember
last time we watched fireworks in the park?
Do you think
fireworks or stars, which look better?
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
Which time? I don't remember.
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
Wait for me.
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
Leave it to me.
Don't be afraid.
You mean Jia San?
Why would I be afraid of him?
If you hadn't come,
he has been locked up by the police, okay?
Then your plan will be ruined.
How did you know about our plan?
And why are you here?
Because I want to see you.
This is your style.
Meet when you want to meet,
go when you want to go.
Meiren.
Tell me.
Who told you I was here?
What...
Director Li.
I promised Miss Meiren to keep it a secret.
Don't do this to me.
Professor Zhuang.
You can't force me in public.
Birds Records in Baiyuan.
This is what I'm reading.
Don't overthink it.
Are you interested in birds too?
Or because someone went to Baiyuan?
Why did you take off for two days？
You're going to Baiyuan, why?
I signed up for bird volunteers
at the Baiyuan wildlife station.
Will the university stop me from this?
Baiyuan wildlife station.
I got it.
Thank you.
Hello, excuse me?
How to get to the wildlife station?
The station is about a kilometer away.
Thank you.
Will Miss Meiren be in danger?
Should we go to the depression to help her?
No, in case we are discovered by Jia San,
she will be more dangerous.
I'm still worried.
Jia San is a repeat offender.
He has poisoned the birds in the water
for so many times.
He must be ruthless.
She said she'll call the police immediately
if something goes wrong.
It takes only five minutes to run up there.
We'll be right here,
waiting for her to come back.
Depression.
Run up for five minutes.
Poison in the water.
The junction of rice fields and depression.
Law of Attraction.
What?
When you truly desire something,
the entire universe will help you.
Don't bluff me by the things in the book.
I don't want to see you again.
How come I still see you all the time?
Maybe the universe knows its own mind
better than you do.
Aren't you a scientist?
Why don't you do experiments in the lab
but say a bunch of idealistic theories to me?
I happen to be sampling over here.
Just stop by.
Stop by?
Stop by.
It only has reeds but no Artemisia annua.
Or did you study reeds instead?
Same species, it can be inspired.
You said you want to see me.
It's funny that your head is
still full of grass.
Then take your time?
Why are you following me?
I happen to live here too.
Are you sure?
Is your department so short of funds?
Mr. Li can't get sponsored without you.
[Baiyuan Little Inn]
What's going on? Why is the power out again?
The fuse is broken.
Thanks.
Thank you.
You can go.
Well, I'm going to take a break.
Then tomorrow...
Of course, you do your job, I do mine.
[Meiren Homestay]
Meinan.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
I knew you were coming.
I have prepared green bean soup for you.
You can have some.
Thank you.
It's sweet, thanks.
What are you doing?
I... I want a sip too.
Go ahead.
I'll leave now.
Don't forget about tomorrow!
Don't worry, I can't forget.
What is it?
You have an appointment tomorrow?
I'll help you carry them back to your room.
No.
Where are you going tomorrow?
Who is it?
It's me.
Here you are.
That's the sound of the door.
Don't be afraid.
This room is too small.
Two people will be very crowded here.
Better?
Thank you.
I live right next door.
Call me anytime if you need anything.
Good night.
Wait.
Can you...
please...
Okay.
I'll stay.
When did I ask you to stay?
I'm talking about the fan.
It also needs this.
I'm right here.
Don't be afraid.
Want to hear any story?
The Little Girl Selling Matches again?
I don't want to hear it anymore.
Not a girl this time.
It's a boy.
Will the matches sell the little boy?
Not bad.
Not selling anything this time.
It's about a boy chasing the stars.
A star chaser? That's rare.
The boy
lives in a small mountain village
where it is always rainy.
It's hard to see the sun in this village.
Not to mention the stars.
But the boy couldn't forget
late one fine night,
he saw a star once.
The stars shine so brightly.
The boy was captivated.
After dawn,
the boy decided to leave the village
to find the star.
It can't be true.
How can the stars shine brightly?
The boy's family said the same thing.
They said the boy must have been dazzled.
The boy was anxious.
He told his family
the stars he saw are like
the Pentas lanceolata (Forsk.) K. Schum.
In front of the house.
The Pentas lanceolata (Forsk.) K. Schum.
Has been growing on the doorstep
for as long as the boy can remember.
Hearing the boy's words,
the flowers seem to understand,
swaying in the wind.
But it doesn't talk.
It can't testify to the boy.
So the boy made up his mind.
Since there are no stars in the village,
go to a place where the stars can be seen.
The boy wants to walk along
the edge of the dark clouds.
This always comes to an end.
But the boy doesn't know.
To find the end of the clouds,
he tramps over hill and dale.
But no matter how he goes,
that dark cloud is always over his head.
Whenever the boy is tired,
the flowers on the mountain
remind him of the flowers in front of his home,
the night when he saw the stars.
So he can't give up.
And then?
No matter how much the boy goes,
he never reaches the border
of the dark clouds.
But then one night,
he closes his eyes,
those flowers suddenly appear
right in front of his eyes.
That flowers glowing with light,
is exactly the same
as the stars he saw that day.
What flowers?
After wasting a year of time and emotion,
you just came and told me a story?
Look at you.
You get annoyed when he is around.
You're not happy when he leaves.
What should he do?
My sister? What's wrong?
Did she and her boyfriend quarrel again?
Watch the road. I'm discussing the plot.
Why does she touch him?
Why bother caring about his appearance?
He is here.
If he is not for you, then for whom?
He saved you and helped you.
How romantic!
That is why I need to be calm, okay?
I think this is the Drawbridging Effect.
In the most dangerous times,
I happen to run into an acquaintance
who offered a helping hand.
It's easy to get confused about the heartbeat.
Aren't you flipped?
Can't you tell the difference?
What's more,
it takes some time for you to forgive him.
I'm so looking...
forward to it. I've got some things to do.
Talk to you later.
What is it? Why not say it?
Drive slower.
Don't worry about it.
It's still very slow.
It's time to turn the corner.
She didn't find us, did she?
I don't think so.
This happens to be a blind spot.
She can't see.
Look.
If a girl puts her hands on you,
what's the relationship between you two?
Nothing?
Impossible.
Her hand, your head, like this.
Think again.
It must be the girl dislikes the boy,
so she pushes him away.
Impossible, they are familiar with each other.
Really?
Then that must be a joke.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Do you have a crush?
No wonder you don't understand.
If you ask me,
I think Miss Li treats Meinan as her brother.
Don't overthink it.
President Jin,
My huckleberry friend.
Isn't it the plot of the love drama
Tiantian is watching?
Go!
There is some distance.
Go, let's catch up!
Don't worry, President Jin.
- Come on.
- In my speed.
There won't be a problem. Don't worry.
Go!
Don't worry, President Jin.
Please wait a minute.
Don't worry. Let me check it.
It won't take long.
Drop the ball at the last minute.
[Jail for bird hunting]
Hello, what are you talking about?
I said to buy you watermelon.
Thank you, Miss Meiren.
What's going on?
Let me introduce him.
This is a famous botanist,
Professor Zhuang Yu.
He has just returned from
an exchange visit abroad.
He comes here for field research.
Director Li of Huaguang Unversity Botany
recommends our station.
We were just discussing
the plan and ideas for the preserve.
Associate...
What?
Associate Professor.
And an associate professor of botany.
What do you know about bird conservation?
What ideas can you have?
Right.
Miss Meiren, you're from the same university.
Do you know each other?
- No.
- Yes.
Save it.
It's just a matter of fact.
Why do you come to the wildlife station
for field research?
Don't hold me back.
We'll know later.
These two teachers...
Something must be wrong.
Come, sit.
Officer Wang,
let me first report to you
about last night's situation.
Professor Zhuang has just called the police.
We have some preliminary information
about the situation.
Now we're here to record the whole case.
That's why he disappeared this morning.
He came here to take credit.
Yesterday when I saw
Jia San, he took a call.
The call seems to be from his accomplice.
He called his partner Mr. Wang.
I suspect
they have a number of first-class
and second-class animals.
Mr. Wang?
This person Jia San said
might be the guy the villagers mentioned.
I heard that this person is very cunning.
Now in this season,
they have the potential to poach again
in large numbers.
However,
thank you for the valuable clues.
That's all for today.
About the fight against crime,
it's the duty of our police.
If there is a need for you
to cooperate with the investigation,
we will inform you.
That's it. We'll leave now.
Miss Tiantian,
President Jin has come to our village
to purchase.
Is this still necessary?
He does his job, I do mine.
Besides, my Taobao
store is still open.
I have a sales promotion.
It sells like hot cakes. Let me show you.
Look.
Your sister took this photo for me last time.
- How is it?
- It's beautiful. If I'm the buyer,
I'm sure I'll place an order too.
Right? Look at the grapes.
How fresh and juicy those grapes are!
Miss Tiantian, it's so hot.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Meinan, after the delivery,
do you have any arrangements?
No.
Great.
Are you interested in going to
the market in town tonight
for Chinese Valentine's Day?
What will you do with a girl?
You ask me about it?
I haven't been in love. I don't know.
Who said they were in love?
I didn't mean that.
Definitely not in love.
When people fall in love, they're romantic.
Look at these two people.
They left early this morning.
They can't be in a relationship.
I also remember.
What day is it today?
It's not suitable for going out.
Wait a moment, I'll check it for you.
Look.
Well...
President Jin...
Have more watermelon.
I'll eat it.
Stop.
Meinan,
thank you for bringing me to
such a beautiful place.
Tiantian, for you, I'm
willing to do anything.
The flowers you sent me are also beautiful.
No, Tiantian.
No matter how beautiful the flowers are,
they're not as beautiful as you.
You're the most beautiful person in my heart.
Any flower in the world
can't be compared with you.
Meinan, you're so sweet.
Am I?
Maybe it's because I had this.
Then I want to taste it too.
- Go.
- What are you going to do?
Hello? Can I borrow an electric tricycle?
The car was driven away by Meinan
to deliver grapes for Tiantian.
Do you need me to ask someone else?
No, thanks.
President Jin, is your source accurate?
This is absolutely reliable.
I heard you said you quit this day last time,
I thought that...
I did. But others haven't.
I was worried the grapes would be damaged
on the way.
I brought several extra boxes of grapes,
let's sell them on the night market.
I don't want to bring them back.
Come on.
If we finish early, I'll invite you to lunch.
Come.
Okay.
Come on, hurry up.
This one.
If pretending to be the buyers,
at the time of delivery,
we can capture them and the goods.
No.
Why?
I also saw Jia San yesterday.
He carried a knife with him.
It's too dangerous for you to go.
A knife? I didn't see it.
It seems that your attention
was drawn to other things.
What are you talking about?
I was too busy watching the moon.
The moon was full yesterday.
What?
Miss Meiren, it's impossible to see
the bright moon last night.
So you have met yesterday.
- No.
- Yes.
I'm not holding you back.
But if there is no foolproof solution,
we can't act rashly.
But it's breeding season.
If poaching is rampant,
it'll have an incalculable
and serious consequence
on the wild bird populations of Baiyuan.
Not to mention,
Mr. Wang has a batch of first
and second class animals,
even more endangered wild birds.
Have you ever thought about these?
Although I can't save the world,
to protect your well-being alone,
I'm willing to give it my best shot.
Professor Zhuang,
what's your brilliant plan?
Can you share it with us?
Can I be your WeChat friend?
Yes, for follow-up contact.
Please accept my request.
Good, you've learned this trick.
I will appreciate your help.
Well, me too.
Wait a minute.
What?
You're scared?
Let me confirm.
Don't you forget something?
What?
Your character setting.
Boring.
Where to sit?
Welcome. Please have a seat.
Yes.
What can I help you with?
Thank you, sir.
Ask my wife, please.
What are your special cuisines?
These on the menu.
These are our specialties.
Please.
Do you have any game here?
Like that table.
No.
We're a restaurant.
We don't have any game.
That gentleman is eating chicken.
Sir, drop the act.
We understand.
I want to eat chicken,
wild.
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are my future ♫
A foolproof plan, you?
Are you Iron Man or Superman?
Although I can't save the world,
to protect your well-being alone,
I'm willing to give it my best shot.
What danger can there be in broad daylight?
It's just doing business.
What about the delivery?
In broad daylight?
Professor Zhuang,
what's your brilliant plan?
Can you share it with us?
Cutting the watermelon?
Professor Zhuang is really considerate.
But...
You can eat without affecting the lipstick,
can't you?
How come you get overwhelmed
by a mere piece of watermelon?
Sometimes I also need to keep it classy.
Professor, you look so handsome.
You're a perfect match with Miss Meiren.
You're like a real couple.
Thank you.
Obviously, I'm the one who helped first.
Professor Zhuang, when I look at your eyes,
I know immediately
your idea of pretending to be a couple.
Is it to protect Miss Meiren?
I told you.
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ You make all the stars
in the sky shine for me ♫
♫ I can sail a boat in the starry river ♫
♫ Love is like sweet honey in our hearts ♫
♫ Even the air is filled
with the scent of flowers ♫