♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ Passing through beams of light ♫
♫ Meet with the best one ♫
♫ The bird makes a promise to the forest ♫
♫ A brave response ♫
♫ makes my world clear up ♫
♫ The voices in my heart ♫
♫ are all about you at the moment ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
♫ are as splendid as dreams ♫
♫ Migrant birds follow the light ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
[A Romance of the Little Forest]
[Episode 12]
[The flowers are blooming.]
Date.
Maybe she is with her friend.
No.
Yu Meiren is not back,
which friend is she with?
Linda, there's a file
for Qin Ya on my table.
Let Tiantian send it to me.
Let me send it to you.
No, let Tiantian do it.
[Meiren Homestay]
Do I have to start another
form for my parents?
No.
I still need to ask Tiantian.
Hello.
How is it?
Did you succeed?
To be brief.
In two minutes, I'll
be on time for my date
with my September boyfriend.
I'll try.
Now there's an unexpected situation.
Tell me.
My mom seems to have found it out.
The romance drama turned into a family drama.
It's too fast for the audience to appreciate.
What should I do?
There are pros and cons to this.
What do you mean?
The disadvantages
are naturally the parent-child crisis.
Your integrity rating in your family
will be downgraded again.
Your wording is quite professional.
You can't say that it is again.
Let's talk about the pros.
The good is that
you can use this chance to carry forward.
Professor Zhuang promised to cooperate with you.
It's risky for his reputation anyway.
I think he would value
his reputation more.
What do you mean?
I also value my reputation, okay?
Yes.
Anyway, you should take this opportunity
to show all your love.
He'll cooperate with you.
That's true.
Maybe if he cooperates with you,
my parents will believe it.
Yes.
When you two are in love,
even if your mother suspects that
she heard it wrong,
she will not doubt you.
By the way,
don't do anything rashly with your parents yet.
It's better to find out what's going on
to take the right action.
Good point. You are worthy of being my adviser.
I won't talk to you anymore.
I can finally start my date on time.
Bye bye.
Hey…
♫ Pretending to be passionate about coldness ♫
♫ The shackles of pretending to be free ♫
♫ What have you become in the end ♫
My boyfriend Li Xian
is really more handsome than the last one.
[Linda]
Hello, Linda.
You need to work overtime today
on Mr. Jin's business.
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
Qin Ya.
I'm listening.
With a picture promotion sent out last month,
their PR department is satisfied with
the amount of exposure.
Exposure is useless.
The key is the conversion rate of sales.
Look at Yu Meiren's video blog.
It's Yu Meiren again.
I'm telling you
that her latest idea
has topped the Weibo hot search.
Mr. Zhao, next time I will…
- Next time?
- I will…
There's no next time in business.
Qin Ya has terminated the cooperation with us,
and switched to Xingjin Entertainment.
Mr. Jin.
This is the file you ask for.
Thank you.
If there's nothing else, I'll leave now.
Wait a minute.
Thank you for your hard work.
Why don't you come in and take a break?
No need.
I seem to have interrupted your date, right?
You've interrupted several times.
What did you say?
Mr. Jin,
I have a small suggestion,
can I mention it to you?
Just say it.
Mr. Jin, if you have any work needs
after working hours next time,
could you let me know in advance?
Then I can arrange it in advance.
It's my fault this time.
It happened suddenly.
I'm really sorry.
To compensate you,
I have prepared something for you.
Mr. Jin,
I won't take these small favors…
Look.
Just this once.
[Sampling Tool Box]
Professor Zhuang,
which brand of sleeping bag do you usually use?
Don't look at me.
I don't mean anything else.
I just think that
you have a little more experience than me,
so just ask you.
Qingshui Mountain is not far from here.
Observe plant specimens during the day,
don't spend the night in the mountain.
Who said I will sleep there?
So you're giving me this book?
These books are not good,
which have nothing I want.
There are only
a dozen species of Euphorbiaceae listed.
I don't know what reference books should I take
to collect specimens up the mountain.
Journal of the Chinese Medicinal Plants.
Please lend it to me.
Or we can go up tomorrow
and read it together.
I don't have it.
Then what do you usually read on the mountain?
I don't believe that
you can memorize
the characteristics of thousands of plants.
No way, you can
really memorize them?
Okay, tell you the truth.
I just want to go with you.
It's more exciting
to spend the night in the mountains.
Besides, your waist
may be not strong enough
to allow you to walk on the mountain tomorrow.
Then I have to go up and carry you down.
Thanks for your concern.
My waist is better than you think.
Forget what I said.
I shouldn't say a man's waist is bad, right?
But I can't carry this lens for nothing.
It has to be of some use, right?
I only want to see Artemisia annua this time.
It's more meaningful for you
to recognize more plants
and collect more specimens.
Professor Zhuang, do
you think I'm in the way?
Don't worry.
My legs are fine, so I
won't be in your way.
The purpose of the field trip is different,
so we have to design the trip accordingly.
Yes, it seems that our purposes
are not the same.
But why don't you go up in the daytime?
I don't want to miss the blossoms.
This store is really good.
It's hard to buy these, right?
Little thing.
I have to thank you.
If you like,
I can buy you every day in the company.
No need.
No merit, no reward.
If colleagues see
that, the impact is bad.
I've sent the file,
and enjoyed all the
milk tea, then I'll leave.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
You shouldn't be able to date this time.
I'll ask Fang to send you back.
No need.
It's faster if I take the subway.
Maybe I can still catch the second half.
What?
Why is there a second half?
Wait.
What's the matter?
Can you get the file over there for me?
Over the window.
Okay.
You're truly a capitalist.
No matter standing or sitting,
you're going to bleed people dry.
There really is such a view.
The view is great.
When I'm free,
I like to watch the scenery here while ru...
You want to say running, right?
Me? Did I?
Sneakers, skateboards,
and golf clubs.
All these can show
that you love sports.
Do I?
Should I say I love?
I'd better admit it.
No need to answer.
Your eyes already tell me.
If you have a dream, just say it.
In fact, many times I wish
my right ear was not deaf.
Let's not talk about these sad things.
Do you want to have some fun?
What could be happier than drinking milk tea?
Let's go.
What's inside?
A variety of toys that
can make you experience the supreme pleasure.
Supreme pleasure.
It's not what I think it is, is it?
Have a look inside.
Okay.
The door is heavy.
[Peace and Happiness]
Act accordingly, shouldn't act rashly.
It's not a big problem.
How is it not a problem?
What is a problem with you?
You don't care about it at all.
Does this dance make
you feel more alive?
I just don't understand that
why she did not tell me.
Maybe she has some troubles.
She has troubles, she
should tell me directly.
There is no need to do so.
Don't be angry.
Anger might harm your body.
You are not angry
because you only know how to eat melons.
To deal with this kind of thing,
you have to pay attention to the attitude,
and the way to do it, right?
Is it so serous?
How do these two people look so angry?
Mom, you're back from the dance.
You…
Have you eaten dinner yet?
Yes.
Mom, you don't look so good.
Are you having trouble with Auntie Xiumei again?
No.
Is there something you're not telling me?
Dad, if you have
something to say, just say it.
Don't hide it from me.
What is this about?
No, nothing serious.
I can't talk to you.
I need to ask Zhuang about this.
Zhuang, what does it matter to him?
Where is Zhuang?
He's in the room.
My mom has learned to break the weak points.
No, I have to follow her.
What can't you take me with you?
Wait for me.
What are you doing here?
Why do you always go to Zhuang for everything?
Your daughter is a living person here.
Follow me.
- Watch out.
- Why are you following me?
Why are you favoring outsiders?
Don't come to Zhuang for everything.
He's a researcher,
not an encyclopedia.
Are you sure you don't want to ask me first?
You probably won't get much out from him.
What's wrong with me talking to Zhuang?
Is this in your way?
What's wrong with you today?
Why are you stopping me?
Please come in.
Zhuang.
- Handsome boy?
- Auntie.
Where is Zhuang Yu?
Didn't he tell you that he went to investigate?
Of course he did.
I forgot that.
What's wrong with you?
About your boyfriend's schedule,
you need his student to remind you.
Can't you care more about Zhuang?
Mom, I saw you
and Dad looking sad,
so I was so busy caring for you that
I forgot about him for a while.
We don't need you to care about,
you should care more about Zhuang.
Why didn't you go
with Professor Zhuang?
The fieldwork he assigned me to do
is more suitable to be done during the day.
Zhuang is really strange,
why did he go to the mountains at night?
He does not want to lose a minute.
He wants to see it first.
How do you know that?
Of course I know.
It seems that your relationship
is closer than I thought.
Of course.
After all, we're lovers.
Of course I know his things.
I am right, mom?
You and my dad must have had
such a tacit understanding
to have a daughter as transparent as me.
Zhuang is not here.
I'll ask him when he comes back.
I'll leave.
What's the thing indeed?
The situation is not good.
My mother wants to avoid me
and ask Zhuang Yu about something.
Are you tired?
No.
Interesting.
Continue, great.
Would you like something to drink?
No.
Are you afraid of losing to me again
so you deliberately disrupt my rhythm?
You're pretty good.
Here you are.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
Although you're not good at playing,
your taste of picking a drink is not bad.
I gave in to you just now.
I'm not going to let you win this time.
You'd better be careful.
Were you unable to keep up with the rhythm
without the music?
You can turn it on a bit,
My ears won't be tingling.
I'm the best at this game.
Not to mention without music,
I can beat you even with my eyes closed.
Okay, let's compete fairly.
What happened?
It's 10 o'clock.
It's only two TV episodes,
why hasn't she finished watching it?
The adviser is not here, I
have to do it on my own.
Whatever my mom
asks you, tell me in sync,
and don't do anything rashly.
Forget it.
The old man should be sleeping at this time.
Zhuang.
- Good morning.
- Breakfast time.
Okay.
Let's go get ready.
Earthquake?
[Two hours ago]
Mom, what are you doing?
What time is it?
Neither of the guests are here,
let's go up to the hill and camp.
Have a nice trip.
Be safe.
Not only we three,
it's our whole family that go to find Zhuang.
Get up.
Find him?
Don't you miss your own boyfriend?
Of course not.
If I don't miss him, who do I miss?
I really miss him so much.
It's good to be here.
I can just use the trick
of going with the flow.
It's rare that I get up earlier than you.
Didn't you say I might let out your secret?
I've thought about it.
It's better to show it rather than cover it up.
If we work hard and perform well,
we may be able to dispel their doubts.
Do you think that makes sense? Professor Zhuang.
Are you going to the cave?
Are the flowers in blossom?
Soon.
Zhuang, breakfast is ready.
Come and have some with us.
Mom, Zhuang has work to do.
Don't delay him.
Can't my son-in-law eat breakfast?
What will having breakfast delay?
It's okay, Auntie.
With this light and temperature,
the flowers won't bloom for a while.
Zhuang has said like that.
I think that
you just don't want to leave him alone with us.
No.
I am afraid that
too many people will squeeze the flowers.
You just talk.
Zhuang, this way please.
Come on.
Are you ready?
Zhuang, we've finished. Come on.
Come on.
Zhuang, drink some water of black wolfberry.
It's wild and very good.
It is anti-fatigue, anti-aging,
anti-depression, and anti…
- Anti-radiation.
- Anti-radiation. Right.
It resists everything anyway.
Resist all.
Mom, you're exaggerating.
According to you,
doctors should all change
to grow black wolfberries.
The black wolfberry only
has anthocyanins in it,
and it's not stable.
The water is so hot,
there may be nothing left in it.
You know again?
Zhuang, who studies plants, said nothing.
Right?
Tell her, Zhuang,
is this black wolfberry particularly nutritious?
Of course.
Having black wolfberries in summer
can make people drink a lot of water.
Look, Zhuang has said so.
He also said that if you drink too much water,
there is no place for you to pee.
You bad girl.
Come on.
Eat breakfast.
Eat.
What's wrong with you?
Didn't we say we were going to try to behave?
Sister, what are you doing?
Can you think about me?
In the morning, I want
to eat something healthy,
don't feed me dog food.
Just eat.
We're playing so hard,
how can they ignore it?
Maybe,
you're overacting a bit.
No.
I think they don't like watching this.
Zhuang,
why is there no picture of you two together
in your moments?
Got it.
Mommy, take a picture of us.
OK. No problem.
Remember to turn on beauty.
I know.
Beauty camera.
Okay.
Come on.
Look here.
Smile.
Great.
In fact, for many times I wish
my right ear was not deaf.
Although I can't make up for
your regret of enrolling in a major back then.
At least with it,
you can enjoy movies
and games with sound like everyone else.
Come in.
Mr. Jin,
this is for you.
For me?
What is this?
Longan jujube tea.
It can nourish the Qi and protect the liver,
which is most suitable for people like us
who stay up late at night.
I can't believe a girl gave me something
before I took the initiative to send a gift.
She's really a
fairy, not a mortal.
What?
Has he found out that
I brought it to him after doing too much?
Mr. Jin, why don't you drink?
I will.
So hot, no, so sweet.
Oh no.
Doesn't he like to have sweet drinks?
I'm screwed.
My life of working overtime.
By the way,
Mr. Jin, I think the files over there
are too high for you to take.
Why don't I ask Linda to come over
and help me move those files
to the low cabinet over there?
Then when I'm not here,
it's also convenient for you to take.
The fairy is too thoughtful.
I'm just speechless.
I can only think of two words,
beautiful and kind.
Why does he look in that way?
Is it too obvious that
I don't want to get the files?
- I'm not trying to…
- Tiantian,
here's a gift for you.
A gift for me?
[Huiya Hearing Aids]
Hearing aid.
This is a very expensive brand, right?
Try it on.
What's wrong?
I can't take this.
Why?
I…
I give you a gift just because
I'm sorry for making you work late all the time.
Okay?
So I give you a gift.
I don't mean anything else.
Don't think too much.
Mr. Jin, I'm working
here to pay off my debt.
I don't want to think about my ear issue now.
If you really feel sorry about it,
can you convert the overtime hours
into working hours to offset my debt?
How about that?
No problem.
Working hours are hours, but gifts are gifts.
If it's a gift, I can't take it.
I should send a present in return.
This is too expensive,
I can't afford to return it.
Mr. Jin, I really can't take it.
If it's convenient for you later,
I'll ask Linda to come
and move the files with me.
What happened?
I've never been so passive
in front of any girl before.
Okay.
I'll leave.
First win people's hearts,
then make people work hard.
Capitalists' tactics, I
know them very well.
What happened?
Is it because my brain is not working well
after my feet are not working well?
Look, my photoshop skill is good, right?
Great.
How is it?
I'm good at it, right?
Don't worry, I'm fair.
I fix you too.
But you have nothing to fix.
I sent it to you.
Mom, last time you said that
Zhuang Yu does not like to post on Moments.
I am very satisfied with this photo today.
I'll let him post it now.
Look at you,
you are exactly the same as your mother,
force others to post to show your love.
It's Zhuang's own
business to post or not.
Don't force him.
I'm not forcing him.
He is voluntary to do that.
Right?
- Yes.
- Fine.
Please.
Please post it on the moments
to let my parents see it.
Good luck to good people.
Zhuang, you've posted it, right?
I will be the first to give you a like.
- Look.
- I'm going to like it too.
Look.
What's wrong with you?
You…
How could you post the original picture?
Which is the original picture?
This one.
Look, how round my face is.
This one is the fixed one.
This is the normal one.
How could you even get this wrong?
I don't see any difference.
Yes, it's great.
I knew it.
Are you trying to embarrass me on purpose
because I didn't retouch your pictures?
Luckily it's only for
mom, dad, and Yu Meinan,
otherwise you'd be in for a treat.
Who commented?
Do you open your relationship with Miss Yu?
Congratulations.
Good for you.
Why didn't you tell me
about this great news in advance?
Why didn't you set up groups?
What's that?
Mr. Jin,
we've got the contract with Qin Ya back.
A week later,
there is an offline promotion for the brand,
they hope that
Meiren can be there.
This is the theme and image reference for it.
Miss Li is going to dinner.
Okay, I get it.
I'll tell her. You can leave.
Okay.
[The program of Qin Ya's promotion]
After such a long break,
it's about time to come back.
You posted like this,
everyone will see it.
They're blooming.
It's not right.
When this Artemisia annua blooms,
isn't it past the first bud stage?
The content of artemisinin should not be high.
The samples of the first bud stage
have been collected.
Who said Artemisia annua has only one use?
It is also very beautiful when it blooms.
Then…
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ You suddenly break in ♫
♫ and also open up my heart ♫
♫ Tell me this moment can be our future ♫
♫ The expectations of two ♫
Miss Meiren.
Who?
Handsome boy.
Professor Zhuang, Miss Meiren.
You're on the mountain so early.
It's so dark,
you're unable to see anything, right?
It's 9:30, is that early?
And it's pretty bright today,
so I can see everything I should see.
God.
When is it so bright?
And… And the sun is nice today.
Isn't it?
You…
What are you doing here?
I'm here for my botanical expedition.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
I didn't expect that I just said last night,
you can forget it so quickly.
Right, you told me you were coming here.
But it's still a little surprising
to see you here.
You guys work on your samples first.
I'm going to see if my
mom needs any help.
Calm down.
A kiss is a touch of
the skin on the lips.
A handshake is a touch
of the skin of the hands.
It's all skin.
So it's just like a handshake.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
It's useless to think about it,
I should think about
getting rid of Sherlock Feng.
Mom,
I'm back.
Meiren, where's Zhuang?
Eat a grape.
No.
Mom and Dad, you've
been whispering for days.
What is it that he
can know but I can't?
It's useless for me to tell you.
You just know how to fool me.
I... When did I fool you?
Mom, just tell me
what's going on?
I don't want outsiders to laugh at me.
Who's an outsider?
How can Zhuang be an outsider?
You've already known that,
how could he not be an outsider?
Yes, since it's like
this, tell Meiren.
Fine.
I'll tell you, but
you must promise
not to stop us from talking to Zhuang.
Chen Guilan of our dance team,
do you remember Aunt Chen?
No impression, right?
This is normal.
When she was young,
she was on good terms with Wang.
So she took Wang as the village beauty.
Can Wang Xiumei compare with…
You.
You are the most beautiful woman in our village.
Just cherish and don't brag.
Low profile.
Where was I?
Wang Guilan.
Not Wang Guilan.
That's Chen Guilan and Wang Xiumei.
Sorry.
Keep talking.
This Wang Guilan.
Stop.
Their names are so similar,
so they must be in a group.
Since I became the captain,
they do not obey me at all.
I don't know
if it was Wang Xiumei who urged her behind,
now she always comes in late and leaves early.
These days she even didn't come.
She didn't respect me as captain at all.
Isn't she too much?
She's too much.
But what does this have to do with Zhuang?
Don't hurry.
Let your mom slowly unravel the fog of history.
It's not that long.
At first I thought
she had some opinion on me personally.
I thought it doesn't matter
whether she comes or not.
It's good that they don't dance anyway.
I'm good at it,
so I'll stand out,
right?
Then I thought, no.
I am the captain.
If I lead this team like this,
it will fall apart.
It won't be good.
I think
I should probably go to their home to check.
If there is any problem,
we should spread it
out to talk clearly, right?
When I went to
their house, oh, no,
something really happened to them.
We don't grow grapes so we don't know that.
This year, our village is certified organic,
so no pesticides are allowed to be applied.
So now the grape production
has been greatly reduced.
Mainly because of the pest.
Right.
The couple are so worried at home
that she is in no mood to dance.
I think Zhuang can help them.
Zhuang is studying plants.
He's so knowledgeable
that he can definitely
help them, right?
So I just want Zhuang to help them.
That's why you're so sad these days?
Yes.
See?
Beautiful and kind.
How can I not love her?
It is a good thing,
why didn't you tell me?
It's because of you.
You either say that Zhuang is busy at work,
or he is engaged in
confidential scientific research.
I'm afraid that if I tell you,
you'll say we're disturbing him.
Mom, in your mind,
I'm so narrow-minded?
Did she just say that Zhuang is an outsider?
She did.
Why?
What did you mean?
I didn't say that.
What outsider and insider?
We're all family, aren't we?
You think it's better
for me to talk to Zhuang
or you to talk to him?
Of course it's me…
Of course, you tell him.
I'm going to see what Meinan needs.
Come back.
There's something wrong with you today.
What's wrong?
When I talk about Zhuang,
usually you are very active.
Why are you so evasive today?
I'm not.
Are you two having a fight?
No.
Mom, you're kidding.
We're fine.
Uncle, Auntie.
- Zhuang, you're back.
- Yu Meinan,
what can I do to help you?
Come here.
- Come here, Zhuang.
- Come here.
I have nothing you can help me with here.
Lv Jian, why are you here too?
Come and sit.
Have some fruit.
You go back to rest.
Yes, Auntie.
You're carrying something so heavy.
Take a break.
Get the flowers to my office.
Mr. Jin, aren't you
allergic to pollen?
It doesn't matter.
No girl would refuse
so many flowers, right?
That's true.
Not to mention such
beautiful flowers.
Not to mention that they're from me.
You deal with it. I'll go up first.
Okay.
I'll get someone to take them up.
Great.
It's more and more of my style.
Linda,
help me put the coffee machine back.
Yes.
Taste it.
Okay.
My son-in-law's
coffee is truly different.
Is it?
Let me try it.
Delicious.
Brother-in-law,
you brought these things to the mountain,
you really have a sense of ritual.
Of course.
That's why your sister likes him, right?
Thank you, Professor Zhuang.
Thank you.
Auntie,
I'll do what you just told me.
I'm just about done with my own work.
I'll take a look when I get down the mountain.
That's great.
I'm so lucky to have
such a good son-in-law.
Don't be polite to your own family.
I'll come with you, Auntie.
If there's anything
you want to tell us, just say it.
Having lived here for so long,
I've already regarded it as my own home.
Something happens to
my family, I must help.
That's great.
Thank you.
On behalf of the village chief, thank you.
I'll drink first.
Be careful, Miss Meiren. It's hot.
Left.
I'm full.
I'll take a walk to digest.
What?
Why does she have such a small appetite today?
Yes.
Come on, Zhuang, pour it for me.
I want to drink more.
Five years ago, I was strong enough
to go up and down without breathing.
Why do I get heat stroke so easily now?
Otherwise, why is my face flushing?
Unexpectedly.
♫ Migrant birds fly into the forest ♫
♫ The world of two ♫
♫ is what we're proud of ♫
♫ I'm walking toward you ♫
♫ The forest shines with its radiance ♫
♫ Waiting for the birds to fly back ♫
♫ I'm sure you are ♫
♫ my future ♫
Mom,
take a picture of us.
Okay.
Remember to turn on beauty.
I know.
Beauty camera.
Okay.
Smile, ready.
Smile.
Great. What do you think?
What's up?
It is better to use the original camera.
What's wrong?
It's good.
Take another one.
Okay, original camera.
Look here.
One, two, three, smile.
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ I like the sunshine on your face ♫
♫ You show up in my sight ♫
♫ My heart flips are like the summer rhapsody ♫
♫ Dashing around without directions ♫
♫ Look at the starlight on shoulders ♫
♫ Even the clouds turn heart-shaped ♫
♫ Two long shadows at eight o'clock ♫
♫ I want to lean on your shoulder cozily ♫
♫ You are shining for me like stars in the sky ♫
♫ Your image is engraved in my eyes ♫
♫ Your smile seems to announce every time ♫
♫ Heartbeat is the exclusive formula for love ♫
♫ You make all the stars
in the sky shine for me ♫
♫ I can sail a boat in the starry river ♫
♫ Love is like sweet honey in our hearts ♫
♫ Even the air is filled
with the scent of flowers ♫