[English subtitles are available.]
[Queendom Comeback Competition]
I can't tell you how much I wish
Like a scarecrow
Knowing that tomorrow is coming
Now I’m worried.
It would be nice to work in pairs.
[Don Spike: Giving advice to Hye Jeong&Minnie]
[I’m gaining my confidence.]
Slowly I gained confidence.
[Lia Kim comes up to help the performance squad.]
Hi, I'm Lia Kim.
[Lia Kim Dance School begins.]
Cool!
After that, after that
[What is the stage for the performance squad?]
[Middle-check by vocal squad]
I love you when you call me senorita
[Senorita-95]
It’s true lalala
[Instagram-AI]
I know tomorrow is coming
In the Instagram Instagram
[Scarecrow-BOM&]
I don’t know
It’s been only one year
[Next vote after mid-check, 951 votes.]
I and Kei
Hwa Sa Kei
[952 votes.]
[BOM&Hyo Jung 1 vote.]
HyoJung & Bom Park
[AI 1 vote.]
AI team
[AI 2 votes.]
AI
[AI 3 votes, AI 4 votes, finally AI got 15 votes.
AI is the No.1 of mid-check squad.]
Minnie and sister Hye Jeong
[Who is the truly No.1 in the 3rd round of performance competition squad?]
The voice
Gonna be crazy!
[After the seminar, MAMAMOO is taking the 3rd performing competition meeting.]
Fighting, Minnie and sis Hye Jeong!
[Our No.2 singers are shy.]
Our 2nd singers
[MAMAMOO Solar We’re gonna take the next performing competition.]
We are going to have another round of
performing competition.
[(Yep)]
The next round of performing competition.
Our performers, our vocals
[Performance members on the left, vocals on the right.]
Performers, vocals
[Recently, Solar is learning the insider words of vocals hardly.]
Where did you learn from?
-Vocals-Members
[MAMAMOO Solar How do you get along with Kei?(Smile)]
How did you get along with Kei?
Kei is a very nice friend.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa Kei is very nice.]
Yes, she is.
[Including myself, she surprised we peers.]
Of the same age?
I am not clear either.
I thought she’s a younger sister.
Me too.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul But…When we had a picnic…]
But when we were having a picnic…
-Picnic?-We sang together.
[Emotional Uncle What…picnic?]
What kind of picnic?
Let’s have fun.
[Picnic style]
What?
[So far away.]
It’s old-fashioned.
That’s the seminar.
I thought it was mountaineering association.
[I thought it was mountaineering association…
Yeah, it’s the seminar.]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul They are very different at the seminar…]
Yeah, it’s the seminar.
During the seminar, they performed differently.
[What do you mean?]
What do you mean?
Are you coming from the cyberspace?
[Are you coming from the cyberspace?]
Their styles are kind of different.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul Do you know the meaning?
(Got it)]
Absolutely!
[MAMAMOO Solar I think the appearance of Kei...]
I think the appearance of Kei...
[MAMAMOO Solar She is cute like a baby... kind of appearance.]
-She is cute like a baby.-Wow!
This kind of appearance.
[MAMAMOO Solar But her voice…]
But her voice
[(Oh…Sister…?)]
isn’t cute.
It’s mutual, which surprises me.
[MAMAMOO Solar (Voice) It’s very mutual, which surprises me.]
A bit of a reversal.
[Sa gets the goods on you! “Which surprises me.”]
I was a little surprised.
You sound more mature.
[Sure enough, the hounds.
Catch the interesting goods.]
Special sound impact
[I want to say that (Kei) her voice makes me surprised.]
And I'm a little bit shy.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa My friend, Kei, is a bit of shy…]
[Come on, don’t you say that she is very positive and lead you.]
Don’t you say that she is positive?
Lead you.
Lead me.
[Come on, don’t you say that she is very positive and lead you?
Lead me…]
Absolutely different.
[I buy this story.
Talk about the words, for example.]
For example,
like “You are mine.”
[Like “You are mine.”]
Very positive.
[Her positive makes me excited.]
Walk towards me.
[Walk towards you with the nori.]
Would you like to have nori with me?
It’s mine.
It is fate.
[Got moved by the fate.]
Could you make it?
You must be excited.
[MAMAMOO Wheel In You must be excited hearing the voice.]
Beyond the cardiac
[Beyond excited]
Really?
No no, but now, I…
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Kidding me, not now, I am...]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: This kind of situation pushes me to work together?]
This kind of situation pushes me to work together?
Because of positive
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Because of positive]
So after”this friend”
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: So after 'this friend']
They two guys are very opposite
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: They two guys are very opposite.]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: I’m curious about the feel when two people cooperate.]
I’m curious about the feel
when two people cooperate.
It’s good to work with Kei.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: It’s good to work with Kei.]
I’ve never thought of before.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I’ve never thought of before.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: And there is no chance.]
And there is no chance.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I got the chance.]
I got the chance.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Dance with Kei together.]
Work with Kei together.
[Whom is Hwa Sa calling the video to?]
[Slash]
[Ji Yeon]
-JiYeon.-Hi.
[The subject of the video is Kim Ji Yeon.]
Hi!
Where are you? Where are you?
[Where are you? Where are you?]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I am going to join an activity.]
I am going to join an activity.
[Lovelyz Kei: Warmhearted Have you had a meal?]
Have you had a meal?
I ordered just now.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I ordered just now.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I am shooting.]
I’m shooting MV.
I'm on my way to the set.
[Real friends, 95 share everything to each other.]
This is Jeolla road.
Are you shooting the music video on Jeolla road?
I miss you.
[Straight power: I miss you.]
Oh my god, so do I.
[Panic power: Oh my god, so do I.]
Me too.
[Wow]
[95: I miss you]
95: I miss you.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: So sweet. I’ll see you soon, Ji Yeon.]
All right, Ji yeon. I'll see you soon.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Has the competition song been recording?]
Have you recorded?
I'll record tomorrow.
[Lovelyz Kei: I’ll record tomorrow.]
Well.
[Lovelyz Kei: I've got the sound source.]
I’ve got the sound source.
I am practicing as you said before.
[Lovelyz Kei: I am practicing as you said before.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: But I can’t do it well.]
But I can’t do it well.
Do it in Ji Yeon’s style.
[Do it in Ji Yeon’s style.]
It’s great!
[Lovelyz Kei: It’s great! Shy No…]
No…
[Lovelyz Kei: The first time I heard it, I thought it was the original.]
The first time I heard it, I thought it was the original.
[What about the burning smell?
Kei also sends out a lot of caramel today.]
Ji Yeon, you’re great.
Really great
[Ji Yeon, SOS...]
Ji Yeon~~
[Lovelyz Kei: After the first and second bars are sung separately.]
After the first and second bars are sung separately,
[Lovelyz Kei: Start at the bridge.]
start at the bridge.
[Lovelyz Kei: It seems nice to be together.]
It seems nice to be together.
Then it's good to feel like this.
[95 is sharing her advice.]
Ok, do it in this way.
Don't starve...
[Don't starve...]
Have a nice activity!
[Have a nice activity!
Have a nice shooting!]
Well, have a nice shooting!
[Lovelyz Kei: I’ll practice until the rehearsal.]
I'll practice hard until rehearsal.
Fighting, fighting.
[Fighting, fighting!]
Love you.
[Love you]
Then... Love you.
[Panic...
Then... Love you.]
[Best friend, tacit understanding of 95 will go on a few minutes later.]
Love you.
Give you my heart!
Good bye~
If three is all. Two is you and me.
[Kei is recording on the second day.]
Someone need to leave eventually.
[Lovelyz Kei: Can I listen to Haw Sa from beginning?]
Can I listen to Hwa Sa from the beginning?
Ok, here it goes.
[Listen to Haw Sa's voice]
I can't tell you how much I miss you.
[It seems that Kei is in harmony with the tone.]
[Lovelyz Kei: Communicate with each other via text messages or phone calls.]
Communicate with each other via text messages or phone calls.
[I want to go to this kind of Neon night street!
Hwa Sa: So the ambiance is positive.
So decadent to go ~? I put orange highlights in the black.
Hwa Sa: How about black highlights in orange? Hwa Sa: Good.
I want to know all orange or orange bright spot via message.
95 are thinking about the stage and clothing together. ]
So now I also received her recording file.
[Lovelyz Kei: So now I also receive her recording file.]
I listen to the music
[Lovelyz Kei: Hearing the music]
and think of 'singing with Hwa Sa together'.
[Lovelyz Kei: Thinking of 'singing with Hwa Sa together']
[Lovelyz Kei: Practicing alone]
Practicing alone.
I've been thinking about
[Practice for the best stage.]
[On the other side, Haw Sa keeps practice during overseas public performance schedule.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I've dreamed of the squad stage for a few times when I'm listening to the music.]
the squad stage for several times with the song.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I think I've heard it a thousand times.]
I think I've heard it a thousand times.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I've been thinking like that.]
Thinking like that.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Ji Yeon sent her record file to me.]
Ji Yeon sent her record file to me.
She has her own style.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: She has her own style.]
I think it's appropriate.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I think it’s appropriate.]
Hwa Sa did it well
[Lovelyz Kei: Hwa Sa did it well.]
[Lovelyz Kei: And performed well.]
and performed well.
[So what’s the stage of sweet 95?]
[Minnie is very happy to be FNC where Shin Hye Jeong belongs.]
FNC
[(I’m here!)]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Can I take a photo?]
Can I take a photo?
[She thinks FNC is very special.]
[Minnie comes to FNC.jpg]
[Hi.]
Hello!
[Feeling like dreaming]
How are you?
[AOA Hye Jeong: Still cute.]
The tone is still lovely.
We sang once before.
[AOA Hye Jeong: We sang the song once before.]
That was a good reaction.
[It’s great at the seminar.]
I heard that was a good reaction.
I know tomorrow is coming.
[Minnie: When I sang the first part,]
[getting "goosebumps".]
[AOA Chan Mi: Wow, her voice is nice.]
Wow, her voice is nice.
I still can't put my phone down.
[Minnie’s unique timbre surprised everyone.]
I won’t vote.
[And then there's Shin Hye Jeong's timbre crit.]
I'm not the only one.
In the Instagram Instagram
[Oh, that's it!]
Well, awesome!
Problem, problem
Our members said that was really great.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: That stage that day,
Our members said that was great.]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: But part 2 is a problem.]
But part 2 is a problem.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: It doesn't matter if we continue this way in part 1.]
It doesn't matter if we continue in part 1.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: If keep singing in this way from part 2 to the end,]
If keep singing in this way from part 2 to the end,
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: the stage seemed a bit boring.]
the stage seemed a bit boring.
Oh no… I don’t know.
[Go? Oh no… I don’t know…TT TT]
How many did we pick?
[Review the alternate songs that came out at that time.]
Right!
What are the songs
[(What are they?)]
coming out before?
[！]
Just
The song is really good.
[Crush-Just A song with a medium - speed soft tone]
[It’s always distressed to select songs.]
But this key is particularly ambiguous.
[AOA Hye Jeong: But this KEY is particularly ambiguous.]
[Just looks so pathetic.]
Just looks so pathetic
-Too low.
-Yeah.
[AOA Hye Jeong: The key is too high for a female to sing.]
The key is too high for a female to sing.
Yeah.
There is rap in this song.
[There are even Rap songs.]
Can you rap?
[Can you rap? No!]
No, I can’t.
Try first.
Like this?
[(Let's sing it first.)]
Just sing it.
[AOA Hye Jeong: Calm down, just sing it!]
Good job.
[You are unconscious of me]
You are unconscious of me
[Quick to give up]
Well,
Let’s choose .
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: It would be better to sing .]
[Finally, AI decided to choose the mid-check song.]
I like the guitar.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: I like guitar very much.]
[AOA Hye Jeong: Do you play an instrument? Piano!]
Can you play an instrument?
Piano
Can you?
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Do you play the piano? (It’s not bad.)]
Yep.
The piano melody is also very suitable for the song at the mid-check.
[The piano melody is also very suitable for the song at the mid-check.]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: This would be my first time to play the piano…]
This would be my first time to play the piano…
[Confidence
I can play if chords are simple.]
I can play if chords are simple.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Positive strength
I can do it with practice.]
I can do it with practice.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: I’ve listened.]
I’ve listened.
There aren't a lot of chords.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: There are few chords.]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Because it keeps repeatedly.]
Because it keeps repeatedly.
I can do well with practice.
[I can do well with practice.]
[They two decide the direction of the arrangement after selecting the song.]
Like this.
[The melody of part 1 is slowly.]
Slowly.
Kind of freestyle.
It becomes rhythmic from the part 2.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: It becomes rhythmic from the 2nd part.]
[You know that feeling of wanting to dance?]
At this time,
we come up
[(So shall we dance?)]
and dance.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: I have an idea, sister. (like what?)]
I have an idea, sister.
The feeling of sing it together.
-You keep singing Problems problems…
-Problems problems
[The idea of Minnie: How about singing like a chorus.]
-All in the worlds -All in the worlds
When we come to “love songs” in the chorus...
[Finally, the chorus finished together.]
Love songs...
Because...
[Problems, problems]
- Problems problems
[All in the worlds, all in the worlds]
- All in the worlds
[Definitely a love song~]
Definitely a love song!
It feels great.
[Burst of enthusiasm
Minnie keeps come up with ideas.]
Plus impromptu singing.
I am on behalf of the team.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: I represent my team (G)I-DLE.]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: So like on my face,]
So like on my face,
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: there is ‘(G)I-DLE’.]
there is ‘(G)I-DLE’.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Well done is (G)I-DLE well done.]
Well done is (G)I-DLE well done.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Bad done is (G)I-DLE bad done.]
Bad done is (G)I-DLE bad done.
So they believe in me
[Want to work harder for the members]
and recommended me.
Minnie’s voice is number one in Korea.
[Minnie’s voice is number one in Korea.]
I never heard the voice before.
[Minnie was strongly recommended by the members.]
[(G)I-DLE So Yeon: It should be our highlight.]
It should be our highlight.
[(G)I-DLE So Yeon: Show the style of (G)I-DLE.]
Showing the style of (G)I-DLE will be fine.
To be number one! Fighting!
[To be number one! Fighting!]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Members would be disappointed
if I don't do well.]
Members would be disappointed if I don't do well.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: So I have to try my best.]
So I have to try my best.
[AOA Hye Jeong: That passion and that stuff.]
That passion and that stuff
[AOA Hye Jeong: Shall we say it's blazing?]
Should we say it's blazing
That’s very excellent.
[AOA Hye Jeong: Compliment Minnie for seeing that.]
[AI for recording after the orchestration session]
I know tomorrow is coming.
[Minnie goes first.]
I can’t put my phone down.
[Sing it calmly, one note at a time.]
Not at all sleepy
Keep playing Instagram Instagram
[Perfect! Perfect!]
Perfect! Perfect!
[Arranger Cherry Grove: Excellent!]
Very excellent!
The further you go, the harder it gets.
[Minnie keeps recording seriously after praising.]
Only me?
Good!
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Wow... So this song can be sung in this way.]
Wow... So this song can be sung in this way.
Intricate
[It’s different from original .]
and rapidly changing
So much for
the information age
[Minnie and Hye Jeong have really nice voices.]
Minnie and Hye Jeong have really nice voices.
It would be nice to hear that.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: It would be nice to hear that.]
[AOA Hye Jeong: How long did the recording take?]
How long did she took?
I tried bravely.
[Arranger Cherry Grove: A lot of ideas, and very enthusiastic.]
I’m also very enthusiastic.
Did it take a long time?
[Arranger Cherry Grove: Longer than I thought.]
Longer than I thought.
Minnie did
[Minnie carefully and enthusiastically completed the recording.]
the chorus of each part.
[Arranger Cherry Grove: It took almost 5 hours.]
It took almost 5 hours.
[(Minnie works so hard...)]
A hole in my heart
[Hye Jeong 's recording began.]
Nobody can fill in
I am sinking
[ fulfilled by Hye Jeong ‘s voice]
Around the sea
Once again for the front part.
[Arranger Cherry Grove: Once again for the front part.]
Okay!
[Emanating the breath of the senior
Hye Jeong is recording with ease.]
A hole in my heart
Nobody can fill in
Great!
[Arranger Cherry Grove: Praising.]
Lonely lonely so lonely
[Hye Jeong is singing at ease.]
Why so tired?
[Recording… It’s not easy actually.]
[You are the general, arranger Cherry Grove is praising.
The feeling finished at once.]
Will the feeling be over once?
Good
In your instargram
[In your instargram~]
[Arranger Cherry Grove’s special praise!
You did very good job!]
Well done!
Listen to it!
[Arranger Cherry Grove Listen it!]
Good!
[Sincerely*10000000
Wonderful!]
Very good!
[You had hard.
Arranger Cherry Grove: We finished the recording in 1 hour.
Well done!]
To the end to the end
You've had hard.
[AOA Hye Jeong: I didn't get a chance]
I didn't get a chance
[AOA Hye Jeong: to show it in singing.]
to show it in singing.
[AOA Hye Jeong: But now with the opportunity of ,]
But now with the opportunity of ,
[AOA Hye Jeong: I can show people a little bit of that.]
I can show people a little bit of that.
[AOA Hye Jeong: Both beckoning and afraid.]
Both beckoning and afraid.
[AOA Hye Jeong: It’s an interesting challenge.]
It’s an interesting challenge.
[On the other side, where did the dining car in front of BOM&Hyo Jung’s studio come from?]
[Hi! Hi!]
Hi!
What are you doing?
[Dining car is the supporting coffee car from Park Bom’s fans.]
What’s this?
Why did you choose this...
[I have so many beautiful photos.
Why you guys choose this one.
This looks…]
With mouth open
[Park Bom: Fans got a coffee car here.]
The fans even got a coffee truck here.
[Park Bom: Thank you so much.
I have to try my best.]
I must try my best!
Say hi to Hyo Jung.
[This is my partner.]
Hi everyone.
[Park Bom: We’re gonna sing together. OH MY GIRL]
We’re gonna sing together, OH MY GIRL.
Yeah, I’m from OH MY GIRL.
[Do you want to see our chemistry?]
One two three, strart.
- One two three.
Hold on.
[Hold on...]
-Three four
[Three four, “What's up! We found you!”]
What's up! We found you!
No no, restart.
[No noX2]
What's up! We found you!
[Do it again.
One second late BOM&Jung]
BOM
Jung
No no!
[It took a lot of practice to act like this.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Look at seniors (other teams of stage).
They have reactions.]
I saw your performance on TV shows.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: That’s funny.]
That’s so funny.
Why?
[They are excellent. (?)]
Oh, they are excellent.
[The second round of performance competition
Watching  of OH MY GIRL]
[Like this.]
Oh, they are excellent.
[Get along well.]
Me? Before?
We are not familiar at that time.
When you said 'Oh, they are excellent'
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: It's so cute.]
So cute.
-Really?
-Yeah.
[Park Bom of (G)I-DLE played the crane dance very well.]
You played crane dance before.
What?
Crane dance.
[Carefully
How to dance this?]
How to play that?
[Ahaha, shall I dance here right? I danced as you asked.]
Shall I dance right now?
I danced as you said.
[Becoming Queendom]
Becoming Queendom
[After the seminar, Bom&Jung become sisters that have known for a long time.]
One two three!
[Bom&Jung to be NO.1 Fighting!]
We found you!
[I found you!(Hyo Jung)]
[Full of love in the recording room]
I found OH MY GIRL!
We found you!
[Fine, senior!!]
Senior!
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Stop playing and the second arrangement came out today.]
The second arrangement came out today.
I think I should sing it again.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Start practicing.
I feel like I'm going to sing again.]
You’re right. We need to sing it again.
[Park Bom: You’re right. We need to sing it again.]
Keep trying.
Listen to the arrangements first,
[Practice begins, Bom&Jung]
then we choose the suitable part.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Am I singing the first part?]
I’m the first part.
Let me check on my lyric paper.
[Park Bom: Wait, let me check on my lyric paper.]
Do you prepare the lyric paper?
Yes, I do.
-Hold on.
-What’s this?
[Wrinkled. Park Bom: I have something else in my bag, hold on.]
I have something else in my bag, hold on.
Something you can’t know.
[Park Bom: Something you can’t know.]
[Glance]
-No.
-Maybe the song you’ll sing at the third performance competition.
[It must be the song you’ll sing at the third performance competition (2nd round).]
Definitely!
[(Panic)]
No, something else.
[Glance
We’re a team.]
We’re a team!
No, even if we’re a team.
[No, even if we’re a team!]
The first part I sing
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: The first part sung by me]
is a very important part.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: is a very important part.]
I’m worried about, but I am trying hard.
[It’s very important so that I take notes on the lyric paper.]
But it’s difficult
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: But it’s difficult]
to understanding the feeling of this song.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: to understanding the feeling of this song.]
[Park Bom: When I got  at the first time...]
J.Y.Park explained
[J.Y.Park explained the meaning of ,]
the meaning of the song to me
[Park Bom: which hit my heart directly.]
which hit my heart directly.
You thought I forgot you.
[The meaning of every single line.]
And thought I was happy with the other.
[Bom is explaining her feeling.]
I still can’t forget you.
Scarecrow is always standing there
which means everyone is gone.
[When everyone is gone, scarecrow stands there alone.]
But scarecrow still there
And always there.
This makes me moved.
[The song is expressing the feeling of lonely.]
[Park Bom: The song comforts our heart.]
The song comforts us.
[Park Bom: I hope when the audiences watch our performance,]
I hope when the audiences watch our performance,
they can feel the meaning.
[Park Bom: they can feel the inside meaning.]
I am worried about that.
[Park Bom: I am worried about that.]
But this time,
[Park Bom: But this time,]
I want to try at Queendom.
[I want to try at Queendom.]
This song feels like being alone in the darkness
[Park Bom: This song feels like being alone in the darkness.]
and very tired.
Do you feel tired?
[Park Bom: Have you ever being very tired?]
-Tired time...
-Such as...
[Hyo Jung is thinking about it.]
Tired time...
[When I’m alone…feeling tired…]
Alone and tired.
[Hyo Jung also feels tired.]
-In the darkness.
-Tired.
When I’m very tired, I want to get help...
[Park Bom: When I’m very tired, I want to get help.]
[Park Bom: But no one replys.]
But no one reply.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I feel like…when I’m tired...]
I feel like…when I’m tired...
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I feel like…]
I feel like…
That…
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: That…]
I'll pretend I’m ok.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Pretend I’m ok.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: And forget the tired alone.]
And forget the tired things alone.
Opps…
I’m a little…
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: When I was little, I met something made me tired.]
When I was little, I met something made me tired.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: For me, those things….]
For me, those things….
[I want to be a better me
So I’ll carry on.]
I’ll create another me in fancy.
So...
I know what you mean.
[Choking]
-Why are you crying?
-No…
I know what you mean.
[Why are you crying?]
-Why are you crying?
-Don’t cry.
What’s wrong?
[Park Bom: What’s wrong?]
[Hyo Jung cried.]
[Bom hugged her without saying anything.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: How to say…]
How to say…
I’m staying alone for much of the time.
[I’m staying alone for much of the time.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I hope everyone likes me]
I hope everyone likes me
since I was young.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: since I was young.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: If people don’t like me,]
If people don’t like me,
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I’ll blame on myself.]
I’ll blame on myself.
I should love myself.
[I should love myself.]
I feel lonely because I don’t love myself.
[I feel lonely because I don’t love myself.]
That kind...
[Talk about the lonely self behind the open look the first time.]
[Bom hugged Jung.]
It’s okay.
[Crying sadly…
Just cry out and let off!]
Just cry and let off!
It’s okay.
I don’t know the tired things.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I don’t know the tired things...]
Senior,
[Not much to say can also feel lonely.]
why do you cry, senior?
[Why do you cry, senior?]
Why?
[Park Bom'; Why? Do you feel lonely?]
Do you feel lonely?
We all get through lonely.
[Park Bom: We all feel lonely.]
Were you sad at that time?
[(Um…) Park Bom: Were you sad at that time?]
Being a human is tiring.
Being a human is tired.
[Park Bom: Aha…]
I have to support myself.
[Park Bom: I have to support myself.]
The more you want
[Park Bom: The more you want]
[Park Bom: the more you have to pay.]
the more you have to pay.
[Park Bom: There will be a lot of time feeling lonely.]
There will be a lot of time feeling lonely.
So I held her in a grip.
[So I held her in a grip.]
[Park Bom: Singing the song with the feeling.]
Sing the song with the feeling.
Okay.
[Park Bom: And let off the stress through singing.]
Let off the stress through singing.
[Park Bom: On this basis]
Sing on this basis.
[Damn guys go away.]
Damn guys go away!
[Park Bom: Just sing it out.]
Just sing it out.
[Park Bom: I believe you]
I believe you.
Me too.
[Park Bom: Now I’m more and more convinced.]
Now I’m more and more convinced.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I didn't have a lot of confidence.]
I didn't have a lot of confidence.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: But I believe]
But I believe
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: my partner.]
my partner.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: And I am happy to]
And I am happy to
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: work with Park Bom.]
work with Park Bom.
[BOM&Jung are listening to the arrangement.]
[Park Bom: It’s different from the first version.
The feeling fades without interlude.]
-The feeling fades without interlude.
-A little bit.
[Park Bom: How about this?]
How about this?
[How about this?]
There is two words “I and you”,
[Park Bom raises up ideas for the beautiful song.]
how about deleting one word?
Praying to come back to me...
Then come to the next.
You sing the part “Though you may think
I have forgotten you”.
[Arranger Cherry Groove: Not so bad.]
Not so bad.
[Park Bom: I think it’s better.]
I think it’s better.
-Still use the interlude
-Yes.
[After meeting, Park Bom start the recording first.]
Looking at you...
Pray that one day you will come to me...
[Park Bom: Let me try again.]
Let me try again.
Looking at you...
Pray that one day you will come to me...
[Again and again until she’s satisfied.]
Is this ok?
[Arranger Cherry Groove: Okay ,listen to it.]
Okay, go on.
[Park Bom: It’s a little bit strange for “pray”.]
It’s a little bit strange for “pray”.
Praying~
Looking at you
Pray that one day you will come to me
[Park Bom checked the tone of every word.]
[Park Bom is totally different from usual.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Very small details]
Very small details
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: are handled well.]
are handled well.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: It’s a difficult song]
It’s a difficult song for me actually.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: for me actually.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: But after listened to her song]
But after listened to her,
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I was overwhelmed.]
I was overwhelmed.
Park Bom is awesome.
[Park Bom is awesome.]
I thought I was small.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Then I thought I was small.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Though I am worried,]
Though I am worried,
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I still keep trying.]
I still keep trying.
[Next step is Hyo Jung’s recording.]
Any love waits for time to pass.
You ask me why.
[Listen now.]
Listen to it.
How about it?
[Park Bom: I think you have the best voice.]
I think you have the best voice.
I know you have the feelings alike.
[Park Bom: I know you have the feeling.]
But you can be more emotional.
[Park Bom: But you can be more emotional.]
[Continue recording with more feeling as suggested.]
I won’t be sad...
[Great!]
Great!
Can you try to use fade away
[Park Bom checks the tone.]
in front of that?
-Okay, I’ll try.
-Ok.
-Fade away~~
-Just the tone.
Fade away~~
Like fade away...
Any love would fade away
[Hyo Jung sings again as per the advice.]
[Wow!]
How can I don't know
[Park Bom: Isn’t it better?]
Isn’t it better?
Great.
[It’s better.]
It’s better
Let’s listen again.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I have no confidence at the beginning.]
I have no confidence at the beginning.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: But the senior is praising me.]
But the senior is praising me.
She said a lot of words like
[You did it well.]
'You did it well.'
'Don’t be worried.'
[Be confident, Hyo Jung.]
'Be confident.'
[Encouraged Hyo Jung]
I'll do better on stage.
[Park Bom: I hope she can do better.]
I hope she can do better.
[Park Bom: And it makes me happy by encouraging her.]
And it makes me happy by encouraging her.
[The day of rehearsal for the third round of performance competition]
Hi!
[Hwa Sa and Kei arrived at the rehearsal.]
Where to go?
[Next Minnie&Hye Jeong arrived.]
Hi!
[AOA Hye Jeong: It’s 7:16. Morning or evening?]
It’s 7:16.
Morning or evening?
[Did my baby Minnie arrived?]
Did Minnie arrived?
So nervous.
[Pretty nervous
What is the stage like for vocal squad?]
[On the day of the third performance competition]
[Six Puzzle arrived.]
[I’m swollen from sleeping.]
I’m swollen from sleeping.
[I have four circles on my face.]
I have four circles on my face.
[Last one arrived.]
Wow!
[Wow.]
[Let’s go.]
Let’s go.
[The last member of Six Puzzle
Who is the clone of Park Bom?]
[Audience judgement group assembled for the evaluation of the third round of the performance competition.]
[Audience judgement group consists of fans of same numbers for girl groups
and students majoring practical music, students from Vocal Schools, dance clubs.]
[I’m here for Lovelyz.]
I’m here for Lovelyz.
I’m here for Park Jung.
[I’m here for Park Jung.]
Of course AOA!
[Of course AOA.]
MAMAMOO is the best at the starry night.
[MAMAMOO is the best at the starry night.]
OH MY GIRL
[OH MY GIRL miracle]
(G)I-DLE
[(G)I-DLE fantasy island]
[I love AOA, like Egotistic‘s stage.]
I love Egotistic‘s stage.
[MUMU]
MAMAMOO fighting!
AOA beat them, fighting!
[AOA: Beat them, fighting!]
Queendom Fighting, love you!
[ Fighting, love you!]
[The audiences enter. START]
[Audience judgement group fills the studio,]
[MCLee Da Hee MC Jang Sung Kyu]
[It’s about to begin.]
[AOA Chan Mi: Grand opening ceremony.
It's like an awards show.]
Oh my god. It's like an awards show.
[Oh my god.]
[MAMAMOO Solar: Recently So hot.
I am really fascinated by Jang Sung Kyu.]
I am really fascinated by Jang Sung Kyu.
[Lovelyz Seo Ji Soo: I heard his wife's pregnant with the second child.]
I heard his wife's pregnant with the second child.
[Congratulations!]
Yes, I saw the news.
K-Pop representatives, girl groups,
return at the same time on the same day.
[K-Pop representative girls groups return at the same time on the same day.]
A head-on showdown that
determines the true number one
[A head-on showdown that determines the true number one]
[Queendom Comeback Competition]
Queendom Comeback Competition
[Lee Da Hee: I’m Lee Da Hee, “Queen” of Queendom.]
I’m Lee Da Hee, MC of Queendom.
I’m Jang Sung Kyu, MC of Queendom.
[Jang Sung Kyu: I’m Jang Sung Kyu, “dom” of Queendom.]
[Lee Da Hee: Today is the pre-performance competition]
Today, the comeback competition,
the pre-performance competition
before the final round, begins.
[of Queendom comback competition.]
[Lee Da Hee: Which group will win the first prize of]
In the third round of the pre-performance competition,
which team will get the real first place?
[Lee Da Hee: the third pre-performance competition.]
[Lee Da Hee: This will be decided by you guys.]
It will be decided by you.
[Jang Sung Kyu: No.1 to No.6 is decided]
The final ranking from 1st to 6th
is based on a total of 3 kinds of scores.
[Jang Sung Kyu: by the total of three kinds of scores.]
First of all, the pre-performance competition score
[Final ranking statistical method:
1.	Sum up the pre-performance competition scores,
including the first round, second round and the third round.]
obtained through 3 pre-performance competition.
[Final ranking statistical method:
2.	Pre-source scores of returning song
Pre-source scores of returning song published at the same time(Oct. 25th)]
Pre-source scores of returning songs
released on the same day.
[Final ranking statistical method:
3. Live voting scores
Calculate the score of votes cast by live SMS.]
Finally, the final live scores
at the returning stage to be hold on October 31.
[Final ranking statistical method:
The full scores of the pre-performance competition is 35,000 points.
The full scores of pre-source of returning song is 15000.
The full scores of live voting score is 50000.]
Determining the final ranking by
summing up the scores.
The total score of the third performance competition’s
[Lee Da Hee: The total score of]
[Lee Da Hee: the third performance competition’s is 15000.]
is 15000.
[Lee Da Hee: It will be divided into two rounds.]
It will be divided into two rounds.
The first round
[The first round of the third pre-performance competition,]
is about 5000 scores,
[squad round.]
Squad round of Queendom.
[50000 scores at squad round of Queendom]
[Oh my god~ Squad round!]
Squad round!
Oh my god!
The situation of vocal squads is
[Jang Sung Kyu: The situation of vocal squad is each leader singer of their groups.]
each leader singer of their groups
wins the scores in pairs.
[Vocal squad 1 VS Squad 2 vs Squad 3
The score of each squad will be reflected in the score of their groups.
Jang Sung Kyu: Teams of two will be formed to score team points.]
Vote to whom you think is the best!
[The method of voting for vocal squads:
Vote to the best one among the three squads.]
Pick up the best one!
And according to the results of voting,
No.1 of the vocal squads will win 2500 scores,
[The scores of vocal squads:
No.1: 2500 scores;
No.2: 1500 scores;
No.3: 5OO scores.]
No.2: 1500 scores,
No.3: 5OO scores.
The situation of the dance squad is
[Jang Sung Kyu: The situation of the dance squad is]
finishing the stage in groups of 6 members.
[Individual scores will be counted to the group scores.
Jang Sung Kyu: After the stage in groups of 6,]
They will win individual votes.
[their individual scores will be counted to their group scores.
Jang Sung Kyu: Get the single scores.]
Just press the number
[The method of voting for vocal squads:
Vote to the best one in the groups of 6.]
of the person you pick
after the dance squad stage!
[Love you!]
Love you!
Ye In!
[It's so cruel. ]
It's so cruel! Queendom
So cruel!
The scores of the vocals and dancers are respectively...
[Jang Sung Kyu: The scores of vocals and dance member is determined by...]
[The final scores of the 3rd performance competition]
Add up with the scores at the second round
and Pink DORA's box,
[is determined by adding up the score of  and .]
then they are reflected in the final scores.
Next let’s enjoy the first squad of
the third performance competition
at Queendom Comeback Competition.
[The first of the third pre-performance competition begins now.]
[Lovelyz Lee Mi Joo: Why am I nervous?]
Why am I nervous?
[AOA Hye Jeong: I am stressed out.]
I am stressed out.
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: Believe yourself.]
Believe yourself.
Who's Running the Show?
[Who's Running the Show?]
Queendom
[Queendom]
[Knock, knock]
I’m here to ask the senior to go.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I’m here to ask the senior to the stage.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Shall we think about the greeting words]
Shall we think about the greeting words
and introduction words?
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: and introduction words?]
You must be good at it.
You’re the leader of OH MY GIRL.
[Park Bom: You must be good at it.
You’re the leader of OH MY GIRL.]
[Gotta go now.]
Gotta go now.
[Programme Group: Park Bom and Hyo Jung, get ready.]
-Park Bom!
-Yeah!
-Hyo Jung, get ready!
-Okay!
-Fighting!
-Thanks.
-Try your best!
-I will.
[Lee Da Hee: The first round of the third performance competition at ]
The first round of the third
performance competition at
begins now.
[Lee Da Hee: begins now.]
[(It starts, it starts…)]
It starts, it starts.
Squad performances only in
[Lee Da Hee: Squad stage only in ]
[Lee Da Hee: is waiting for everyone.]
are waiting for you.
Fighting!
[Fighting!!]
-Fighting!
I think there are special connections between Park Bom and I.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I think there are special connections between Park Bom and I.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I want to say that]
I want to say that
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: believe us, we will create a wonderful stage,]
believing us, we will create a wonderful stage
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: because we’ll try hard.]
because we’ll try hard.
[Park Bom: I hope you enjoy our stage.]
I hope you enjoy our stage.
We’ll show you the wonderful stage.
[Park Bom: We’ll show you the wonderful stage.]
[We’ll fighting!]
We’ll fighting!
[Lee Da Hee: The first vocal squad will be announced soon.]
The first vocal squad will be announced soon.
Chorus of Soul Queen and Perceptual Queen
[Lee Da Hee: Chorus of Soul Queen and Perceptual Queen.]
[Chorus]
Park Bom and Hyo Jung from OH MY GIRL
[Lee Da Hee: Park Bom and Hyo Jung from OH MY GIRL.]
[SO NERVOUS]
I've got goose bumps.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: Our leader was shaking her hands at the rehearsal.]
She was shaking her hands at the rehearsal.
Yeah, she seems to be very nervous.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: I decided choose them, Bom and Jung,
after listened a small part at mid-check.]
I decided choose them, Bom and Jung,
after listened a small part at mid-check.
[Em?]
[Bom and Jung walk to the stage.]
[Greet to the senior shyly.]
-Hello everyone!
2! 3! What's up! We! Found you~
[2! 3! What's up! We! Found you~ Bom and Jung]
- Bom
- Jung
[(Very fluently!)]
[Show me the screaming!]
Excited!
[(G)I-DLE So Yeon: Excited!]
Say “Fighting Hyo Jung!”
[OH MY GIRL Seung Hee: Gving instructions Saying ’Fighting Hyo Jung!’]
[Copy that! Fighting Hyo Jung!]
Fighting Hyo Jung!
I want to be NO.1 because I perform with the senior.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: 'I want to be NO.1
because I’ll perform with the senior’.]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I came up with the idea that]
I came up with the idea that
showing a wonderful stage for the senior.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: showing a wonderful stage for the senior.]
[Park Bom: Hopefully, people who have a lot of pain in their hearts.]
Hopefully, people who have a lot of pain in their hearts
will find a lot of comfort after hearing this song.
[Park Bom: I will find a lot of comfort after hearing this song.]
[Lights on the stage and glow sticks of Bom&Jung’s fans]
[(G)I-DLE So Yeon: What’s this? What?!]
What’s this? What?!
[AOA Ji Min: It's about to start. It's about to start. The stage is beautiful.]
It's about to start. It's about to start.
The stage is beautiful.
[MAMAMOO Solar: It feels like turning off the lights.]
It feels like turning off the lights.
Shall we enjoy the music turning off the lights?
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Gesture of appreciation
Shall we enjoy the music turning off the lights?]
Okay.
[No lights Yes Enjoy the music]
[OH MY GIRL Mimi: Oh my god, I've got goose bumps.]
I've got goose bumps.
[AOA Yu-Na: Come on, it starts.]
It's about to start. It's about to start.
[Scarecrow-Bom&JungOriginal singer: Lee Ha-YiLyrics by: J.Y.Park
Composed by:J.Y.Park
Arranged by: Don SpikeCherry Groove,HolyMoly]
[To be continued.]
[Scarecrow-Bom&JungOriginal singer: Lee Ha-YiLyrics by: J.Y.Park
Composed by:J.Y.Park
Arranged by: Don SpikeCherry Groove,HolyMoly]
No matter what kind of love after the passage of time
would change.
How can I don’t know before.
Just one year will not be the same.
No more heartache for me.
But I know my heart.
I know I won’t change.
Because there are people in this world
Doomed to fall in love
Never be forgotten.
Although you will think I have forgotten you.
Think I’ll be happy with someone else.
But I still can't forget it.
Like even if everyone left
a scarecrow is still standing alone.
[Lovelyz Jin: I've got goose bumps.]
- I've got goose bumps.
-Yes.
It’s such a sad song.
[AOA Ji Min: It’s such a sad song.]
Everyone went home after the sun went down.
And I stood alone in the open field.
Although I was gradually trapped into the darkness.
I fear that I am alone.
I don't know when to open closed eyes.
See the beautiful stars shining.
Like when you were far away from me.
I stared and prayed
that one day you would come back to me.
Although you will think I have forgotten you.
Think I’ll be happy with someone else.
But I still can't forget it.
Like even if everyone left.
A scarecrow is still standing alone.
[OH MY GIRL Seung Hee: Oh, she cried.]
She cried!
[AOA Ji Min: She cried. What can we do?]
She cried. What can we do?
Oh my god!
A scarecrow is still standing alone.
[Full version video of Bom&Jung’s performance showed on YouTube NAVER TV]
[They communicated with each other.]
What can we do?
[It's too sad.]
Crying.
- She is crying so much!
- What can we do?
[OH MY GIRL Seung Hee: She is crying so much!]
[AOA Hye Jeong: She said it was a song with a story.]
She said it was a song with a story.
What to do?
[AOA Ji Min: What to do?]
I really feel like crying.
[AOA Chan Mi:I really feel like crying.]
[Bom& Jung exit in the comfort of the audience.]
Don’t cry.
-Don’t cry.
[Feel the sincerity of the two from the song.]
You’re right, sister. I feel like crying too.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: You’re right. I feel like crying too.]
[MAMAMOO Solar: I wanna cry!]
I wanna cry!
[Lovelyz Kei: Such an impressive performance]
Such an impressive performance!
[Queendom: The singers know the feelings better than anyone.]
Why so sad!
[Jung begins to worry after finished the show.]
Are you ok?
I almost screw up when the mood rushed up...
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Almost screw up when the mood rushed up...]
So excited!
[Park Bom: I can’t see clear with tears in my eyes.]
I can’t see clear with tears in my eyes.
[So sad…]
So sad…
You’re so cute.
[Jung is so cute.]
Thanks.
I got comfort from the senior
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I got comfort from the senior]
when we were practicing.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: when we were practicing.]
I released the sad feeling.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: I released the sad feeling.]
Shall I say in this way?
We felt like knowing each other
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: We felt like knowing each other.]
Assuming we’re scarecrows.
We know the feelings.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: Assuming we’re scarecrows.
That’s what I felt.]
So we got comfort from each other at the end.
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: So we got comfort from each other at the end.]
Queendom Comeback Competition
[Queendom Comeback Competition]
Next show time of the second vocal squad!
[Next show time of the second vocal squad]
[Wow! Hye Jeong!]
Wow Hye Jeong!
[(The general is nervous.)]
- Hye Jeong!
- Hye Jeong fighting!
You can do it! It’s easy! It’s easy!
[Magic spells Hye Jeong, you can do it! It’s easy! It’s easy!]
[Yeah…]
Yes!
[Minnie get ready!]
Minnie get ready!
[It’s time.]
-Minnie Come on!
-You can do it!
[Minnie Come on!]
-Minnie fighting!
-Fighting!
[Encouraging hugs
Accept the strength of the members
GO GO to the stage]
Fighting!
[After smiled]
[After smiled, AI(Minnie•Hye Jeong) feel the nervous.]
[(Fighting!)]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Enjoy it! Yep!]
-Enjoy it!
-Yep!
Two people with charming timbre meet.
[Lee Da Hee: Two people with charming timbre meet.]
Enjoy the performance of Hye Jeong (Timbre angel)
[AOA Hye Jeong (Timbre angel) & (G)I-DLE Minnie(Sound craftsmen)]
& (G)I-DLE Minnie(Sound craftsmen)!
[Hi everyone!]
Two three! Hello everyone! We are AI!
[Two three! Hello everyone! We are AI(AOA•I-dle)]
-Cordially invited.
Oh no!
[Lovelyz Kei: [both of them are nervous] Oh no!]
[Why do I feel nervous…JiGiJiGiJa]
Why do I feel nervous? JiGiJiGiJa...
-JiGiJiGiJa...
-So nervous.
[Ji Min is so nervous that spluttered.]
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: [Minnie playing the piano] She must be very nervous,
because of the instrument. Afraid of hitting wrong note.]
She’s more nervous
because she has to play an instrument.
-Right.
-Afraid of hitting wrong note.
[The most nervous moment]
[They two want to defeat the nervous by smiling.]
[Rehearsal on the day before the competition]
[Minnie& Hye Jeong are working on the fit.]
[Arranger Don Spike is watching the rehearsal.]
The facial look is well.
[Don Spike is giving advice for the best stage.]
But the action, do like this.
[Not only the song, but also check the expression and waling lines.]
Do you know the meaning?
When the key goes up, step a bit forward.
[Don Spike: Even if just one small step(action).]
The audiences will be more devoted.
[Don Spike: You will get more concentration of the audience.]
[AOA Hye Jeong: Because she has a lot of actions before.]
Because I played a lot of actions before.
Mostly I didn’t sing quietly.
[It’s kind of unnatural for Hye Jeong to stay still.]
And with facial expressions.
I need to think about how to perform calmly this time.
[AOA Hye Jeong: [in trouble]How to perform calmly and coolly?]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Very upset and I need to play the piano.]
Very upset and I need to play the piano.
This time, just me and sister.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: This time, it’s just me and sister.
It’s more difficult than usual.]
It’s more difficult than usual.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: [On the stage] Even so, if there is the chance,
I’ll catch it and do my best.]
Even so, if there is the chance,
I’ll catch it and do my best.
[What is the performance that Minnie and Hye Jeong prepared?]
[Instagram-AI Original singer: DEAN Lyrics by:Deanfluenza
Composed by: Deanfluenza,highhopes
Arranged by: Don Spike,CherryGrove,HolyMoly]
Tomorrow is coming.
[Ka~ exactly to the heart. It’s over, it’s over.]
It’s over. It’s over.
[Lovelyz Kei: The voice is beautiful.]
Beautiful voices!
Tomorrow is coming.
I can’t put my phone down.
Without sleepiness yeah
So I keep surfing at Instagram instagram
There are so many talented people.
Where do you have fun?
Just skimming without liking
I'm the only one.
In the instagram instagram
[With one voice. Well done!]
Sing well!
[Wow~]
It’s a problem, problem...
In the world
Cookie-cutter love songs
Untouched in my night
A myriad of thoughts
[AOA Chan Mi: You’re a good singer, Hye Jeong!]
Hye Jeong sings well!
It's complicated. Changing at the slightest leisure
[It’s excellent!]
Excellent!
[What rhymes? Not Minnie, but onni.]
Not Minnie, but onni!
It's complicated. Changing at the slightest leisure.
Stop it. The damn information age.
It’s completely wrong.
Feel much lonely
knowing a lot.
Harder and harder.
Only me.
No clubs, no movies.
Staying at home
A hole in my heart
Nothing can mix it up.
I am sinking.
Around the sea
Awesome! Great performance!
[It’s wonderful, great performance.]
[You’re the best, Hye Jeong!]
Bravo!
It’s a problem, problem...
In the world
Cookie-cutter love songs
Untouched in my night
A myriad of thoughts
Lonely lonely so lonely
Is it so hard?
No way no way in this dynamic
Just a different world from mine
[Crazy! Wow!]
I’m so proud. I want to cry.
[I’m so proud. I want to cry.]
[I’m agree with leader.
I’m so proud, too.]
-Me too. I’m so proud.
-So proud.
[(For the first time)]
For the first time
Uploaded photos in vain
My heart hidden behind
No one knows. I'm lost again.
In the instagram
Wasting the time
In your instagram
[Full ver. Video of AI is on YouTube NAVER TV.]
Thanks for listening.
[You did it!]
Great job!
[They’re timbre thieves.]
They’re timbre thieves.
[Lovelyz Kei: Performed well.]
Performed well.
[Wow!]
[OH MY GIRL Hyo Jung: No way. [at least beyond 10 years’ vocal]
Minnie isn’t like a newbie.]
Minnie isn’t like a newbie.
[Empathy Strongly agree.]
I think so.
[She is like a senior and professional.]
She is like a senior and professional.
[Resurrection
Become a lovely girl again.]
Finally finished!
[The performance ended happily.]
I feel so happy.
You've had a long day.
[A look of satisfaction]
[Already a team
AI hugged each other.]
Well done. Thanks.
Maybe we are No.1!
[Maybe we are No.1]
[Self-confidence Charging 100%]
I am confident.
[Really? Respect
An unusual person]
She is awesome.
I’m satisfied.
[Very satisfied.]
It’s the best we’ve been.
[AOA Hye Jeong: It’s the best we’ve been.]
Good job!
[Good job!
We’re great!]
We’re great!
[Welcome!]
Excellent!
[After the performance, come back in triumph.]
[Hye Jeong]
Hye Jeong!
[Come in!]
Come in!
-So good!
-Wonderful!
[With trill
Great! Great! Great!]
Great! Great! Great!
Nervous?
[Nervous?]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I just think about coming back.]
I just think about coming back
[My baby, fighting!]
Fighting!
Keep on!
Without seeing off
[Without seeing off]
Come on. You’re the best!
[Believe you, lead singer~]
[Now it’s Kei.]
Now it’s Kei.
[Naughty
Oh my god!]
What to do?
[Superstar Kei]
Superstar Kei
[Nervous...]
What to do?
[Hwa Sa comes out to pick Kei.]
[Knock knock...]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Kei!]
Kei!
[Knock knock...]
Um?
Come in.
[Somehow nervous]
[Hwa Sa shows up.]
-Hello!
Do you come to pick me?
[Do you come to pick me?]
[Why don’t you come out?]
Why don’t you come out?
- Fighting!
-Fighting!
[Fighting!]
I’ll go now. Fighting!
[Lovelyz Kei: I’ll go now.]
[95 set off with enthusiastic cheers of Lovelyz.]
What to do?
-Nervous?
-Yeah, a little bit.
[Nervous? Yeah, a little bit.]
[I’m here. Don’t be nervous.
Fighting!]
Don’t be nervous.
-Fighting!
-Ok.
-My group members said that make a good ending.
-They said.
[Lovelyz Kei: [the last vocal squad]
Make a good ending.]
[Lee Da Hee: The performance of final squad]
The performance of final squad is coming soon.
[Lee Da Hee: is coming soon.]
[Lee Da Hee: The Chemi queens meet,]
The Chemi queens meet,
who create an incredible stage anywhere, anytime.
[Lee Da Hee: who create an incredible stage anywhere, anytime.]
Enjoy the performance of
MAMAMOO Hwa Sa
[Lee Da Hee: Enjoy the performance of MAMAMOO Hwa Sa and Lovelyz Kei.]
and Lovelyz Kei.
[Clap slightly]
[Now I'm used to walking in arm in arm.]
[Arm in arm. So cute.]
-Arm in arm.
-So cute!
Arm in arm.
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: [finally comes] I’m looking forward to this stage!]
I’m looking forward to this stage!
[Expectant audiences]
2 3 hello everyone! We’re 95.
[We’re born in 1995. Hello, we’re 95.]
[The day before the competition
Final rehearsal]
Hello! Hello!
[Oh my god!
After respective practice long time no see Hwa Sa and Kei.]
-Oh god!
-Changed a lot!
[Discipline a friend
What’s wrong with the bare arms!]
What’s wrong with the bare arms!
Let me help you pull it up.
[Let me help you pull it up!]
[Today is also lazy Hwa Sa style.]
It’s a fashion.
[Now two people look comfortable like old friends.]
Because of shooting MV.
Preparing for the MV.
[Lovelyz Kei: [worrying] How about your throat?]
How about your throat?
I’m ok.
[Pretending I’m ok.]
[Lovelyz Kei: Have you heard the recording?
Of course.]
-Have you heard the recording?
-Of course.
[Hwa Sa&Kei record the parts separately and put them together.]
They fit each other. Good to be together.
Afraid of so many differences before.
[Lovelyz Kei: Afraid of too different before.]
[Lovelyz Kei: More harmonious than expected..]
More harmonious than expected.
[Rehearsal begins. Come to the final check.]
We'll now begin the camera rehearsal.
[Shows a mix of styles of clothing.]
I can't tell you
[Almost the same as the second day
of performance competition
Rehearsal is going on.]
how much I wish I didn't wanna stay
I just kinda wish you were gay
[Singing as their own practice]
[Rehearsal finished.
Hwa Sa’s appearance isn’t well.]
[Kei is also unsatisfied.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Unsatisfied.]
Unsatisfied.
[Lovelyz Kei: The first time to match up.]
The first time to match up.
[Lovelyz Kei: Can’t sing well.]
I can't sing well.
[Lovelyz Kei: How to play well?]
How to play well?
I think we have to reorganize and think about it.
[Lovelyz Kei: I think we have to reorganize and think about it.]
I hope there is something funny.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I hope there is something funny.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Thinking…]
Thinking…
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: We’re a bit of embarrassing.]
We’re a bit of embarrassing.
[We don’t enjoy the stage now.]
We don’t enjoy the stage now.
-So we need to make fun.
[95 want more reactions of the audiences.]
-Communicate with the audiences...
-Like this.
[Communicate!]
[Lovelyz Kei: Still embarrassing.]
Still embarrassing.
make you feel
I’ll sing once the bridge ends.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: After the bridge ends...]
I just wanna make you feel okay.
But all you do is look the other way.
[95 have the meeting to check the position.]
Then unplug the microphone and walk out.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Unplug the microphone and walk out.]
Okay.
[Because it's a monotonous song,
Hwa Sa wants to spice it up.]
Unplug in advance.
Do in advance.
It can look exaggerated if you're not careful.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: It can look exaggerated if you're not careful.]
It’s difficult to keep the extent.
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: It’s difficult to keep the extent.]
I'm on the stage.
[Lovelyz Kei: I'm on the stage
and wonder what the stage is going to be like.]
And wonder what the stage is going to be like.
[Lovelyz Kei: Would they (the audience)watch it with fun?]
Would they watch it with fun?
Fighting Hwa Sa!
[Fighting Hwa Sa! Gentlely Fighting Ji Yeon!]
Fighting!
Fighting Ji Yeon!
[95~s]
95s
[Vibrant standby room of Lovelyz]
[Fighting Kei. Kim Ji Yeon.]
Kim Ji Yeon!
[Lovelyz Lee Mi Joo: I’m so nervous. Why?]
So nervous.
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: Looking forward to it.]
Looking forward to it.
[Baseball field...
Fighting~]
Fighting!
Begins! Begins!
[Begins! Begins! Excited. Sit down!!!]
Sit down!
[wish you were gay-95 Original singer: Billie Eilish
Composed by:O'Connell,BILLIE,O CONNELL FINNEAS
Arranged by:O'Connell,BILLIE,O CONNELL FINNEAS]
Baby I don't feel so good.
Six words you never understood.
Amazing!
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: The first part (I love it.) is amazing! Amazing!]
How could she sing in this way!
[Lovelyz Baby soul: How could she sing in this way!]
I'll never let you go.
Five words you never say.
I laugh alone like nothing's wrong.
Four days has never felt so long.
[Is she our Kei?]
If three's a crowd and two was us
One slipped away
They fit each other!
I just wanna make you feel okay
[Wow, talking by expression.]
Awesome!
[Awesome!]
I just wanna make you feel okay.
But all you do is look the other way.
I can't tell you
how much I wish I didn't wanna stay.
I just kinda wish you were gay.
Is there a reason we're not through?
Raised eyebrow!
[Girl Crush: Raised eyebrow!!]
[Look at her.]
-Cute
-Eyebrow
Is there a reason we're not through?
Is there a 12 step just for you?
Our conversation's all in blue.
Eleven heys
Ten fingers tearing out my hair
Nine times you never made it there
I ate alone at seven,
you were six minutes away.
How am I supposed to make you feel okay
[Excited
Use her eyes for every movement.]
to make you feel okay.
When all you do is walk the other way.
I can't tell you
how much I wish I didn't wanna stay.
I just kinda wish you were gay
[Lost my soul]
Well done.
[(G)I-DLE So yeon: I heard the song at the first time.]
I heard the song at the first time.
Me too!
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: Kei is so awesome.]
Kei is awesome.
Wish you were gay
To spare my pride
To give your lack of
interest an explanation
Don't say I'm not your type
Just say that I'm not your
preferred sexual orientation
I'm so selfish.
[Throbbing]
So awesome!
[She is so great!]
I'm so selfish.
But you make me feel helpless yeah
And I can't stand another day
Stand another day
I just wanna make you feel okay.
But all you do is look the other way.
I can't tell you
[Wonderful!]
I like it so much.
[I like it so much.]
I can't tell you
how much I wish I didn't wanna stay
I just kinda wish you were gay
[Full version of 95's performance is on the YouTube NAVER TV.]
Exceptional!
[They’ll win.]
They’ll win.
[Calm down. 95~S]
-95 -s
[Succession exclamation]
Awesome!
-Awesome!
-That's awesome!
[(G)I-DLE So yeon:	 There is a chemical reaction.]
There is a chemical reaction.
[It’s impressive!]
It’s impressive.
Amazing!
[Close, close...]
[The excellent performance of realistic friends, 95.]
So cute.
[So cute~]
Thanks.
[Hwa Sa&Kei: Thanks.]
[Arm in arm till the end]
Great!
You've had a long day.
[You' ve had a long day.]
[Lovelyz Kei: A little bit pity after the performance.]
A little bit pity after the performance.
That is to say!
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: I feel so happy to sing together.]
I am happy.
Enjoyed.
Talk the singing later.
[Lovelyz Kei: Talk the singing later.]
It’s meaningful to perform with you.
[Lovelyz Kei: It’s meaningful to perform with you.]
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Me too.
When would we sing like this time?]
Me too.
When would we sing like this time?
This is gonna be memorized.
[We’ll keep the experience in mind forever.]
Let's not care about the scores.
Yeah!
I have no regrets.For real.
[Q: Have you enjoyed the stage?]
Are you satisfied?
Feeling always unsatisfied
[MAMAMOO Hwa Sa: Feeling always unsatisfied.]
But I had fun.
[Yes. I had fun.]
Yep.
That feeling...
I’m glad that we accomplished.
[Lovelyz Kei: I’m glad that we accomplished.]
[Lovelyz Kei: It’s nice experience.]
It’s nice experience.
Queendom Comeback Competition
[Lee Da Hee: The first round of third performance competition on Queendom Comeback Competition.]
The first round of third performance competition
Next we’ll see dance performances
[Lee Da Hee: Next we’ll see dance performance]
only in .
[Lee Da Hee: only in .]
[It’s Chan Mi TIME]
Chan Mi!
[Exciting, Chan Mi!!]
Let go!
OK.
[Bravely bravely]
Let go! Let go!
Is it over?
[Soo Jin~~]
Soo Jin~
[Soo Jin, let’s go.]
Sister fighting!
[Seo Soo Jin~~]
Seo Soo Jin
-Sister!
-Fighting!
[On the contrary, YooA is]
Sister, fighting!
-I’ll go now.
-Fighting!
[unruffled.]
Bye~
[I’ll be back soon.]
-Bye.
-Fighting
Put up a good show!
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: I’ll try my best~]
I’ll try my best!
-Bye.
-Fighting!
[Energy up]
I’ll try my best!
-Be careful.
-Fighting!
[Six Puzzle: All set off with the encouragement of their members.]
You’re the best.
Ye In is the best.
[Dull~]
You know I have to go.
[Young girl, you know I should leave now.]
[Like a couple of 30 years of marriage]
Okay, fighting!
[Take an unusual path]
Well.
[Just go.
Have fun! Fighting!]
Okay, fighting!
[Leader of Six Puzzle also comes now.]
Come on!
Everybody
[Everybody! Keep pace with me!]
keeps pace with me.
Moon Byul comes.
[(Is everybody here?)]
Earphone monitor
[MAMAMOO Moon Byu: l I was about to cry.]
I was about to cry.
[The performance squad is still moved by the former stage of Park Bom.]
Really?
I want to cry while listening.
Soo Jin~
-Director!
-Go Go!
[Now it’s our turn.]
Everybody
[Let them forget about the vocals.]
let’s overwhelm the vocals.
Try our best!
Fighting!
[Feeling the strong confidence of Six Puzzle]
So that’s all.
Fine.
[15 days before the third performance competition]
[MAMAMOO Solar: Let's start with the performance squad.]
Let's start with the performance squad.
In what kind of ways?
What to do?
It is said that...
[It is said that...]
[Tense atmosphere]
We reached an agreement.
Because of six members,
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Because of six members, we can’t perform our own styles.]
we can’t perform our own styles.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: So we mix individual performance and team performance up.
And gathered opinions.]
So we mix individual performance
and team performance up.
and gathered opinions.
[I’m serious.]
I’m serious.
[AOA Chan Mi: I danced for a few songs]
I danced for a few songs
which can be counted on one's fingers.
[(really?)which can be counted on one's fingers.]
I use o lot of strength from beginning to end.
Like this.
[I use o lot of strength from beginning to end.]
[AOA Chan Mi: I feel…The first time I feel I’m too slow.]
I am really...
The first time I feel I’m too slow.
[Chan Mi of AOA is good at fast dance but also feels strenuous this time.]
-I always go fast.
-Yeah, you’re fast
The first time feeling slow.
[Shaking their heads.]
I’m serious.
We should be 6.
[Only 5 guys at the seminar
Solar is curious about the last puzzle.]
Yes, we have 6 members.
-Park Bom used the chance.
-Oh
[Chance for Park Bom]
-But now...
-Unknown.
[Clone of Park Bom is still unknown.]
Nobody knows.
-Really?
-Not telling.
-So practice separately?
-Yes.
-Until the day?
Can you do it?
-Someone else?
-Yes.
I don’t know.
[The 6th of the performance squad will be published soon.
'Clone of Park Bom']
Completely confidential.
Have you practiced?
[Lia Kim: Have you practiced?]
Yes.
[Skew~~]
Practiced!
[Six Puzzle is practicing with the dance video choreographed by Lia Kim.]
I went to Paris.
So there is no time to teach you.
-Did you remember the actions?
-Yes.
Is there any problem?
[Lia Kim: Is there any problem?]
[Looking at each otherX2]
No problem?
How about performing?
[So tight…]
It’s so tight.
Very tight choreography from start to finish.
Yeah.
[Little Mix choreographed by Lia Kim with strong rhythm
plus speed and strength.]
Because it has to be tight.
[Lia Kim: Because it has to be tight.]
-Popped us.
-It’s a performance.
Finished once
[Consequences of choreography by Lia Kim:
1.Killing self]
We can’t move our neck
at the beginning.
[Consequences of choreography by Lia Kim:
2. Loss of shin function]
I have sore back.
[Consequences of choreography by Lia Kim:
3. Excessive display of the presence of the spine]
Back...
To that extent?
Yes.
Waist...
[Stop complaining. Act like a real dancer.]
I always dance with my waist.
But...
We won’t shake the head
when we dance on the show.
[AOA Chan Mi: We won’t shake the head when we dance on the show.]
Really?
-Because you can't bend your head.
-Right.
-But this is how you turn your head.
-Okay
[Never tried intense choreography at that time.]
I dance a little bit like ...
Using our necks...
[No way to change…go back…and accept it.]
[This will show the different charming.]
It’s so difficult.
Often use the necks...
Let me check.
[Lia Kim: Let me check.]
Watch you dance.
And see how much you learned.
[The positions of the members have not been decided.]
The positions of the members have not been decided.
Still unclear now?
-Dance at the original position.
-Ok.
[Ye In and Chan Mi prepare to come.]
I forgot.
What’s up?
I don’t know the part.
[Panic YooA forgets the latter part.]
Keep going on.
[Ye In and Chan Mi joined seamlessly.]
[(…like this…?]
[Perfect]
[II A temporary rest]
[(Um...)]
I’m over.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: I’m over.]
I can’t remember the actions.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: I can’t remember the actions.]
[OH MY GIRL YooA: I was shocked and worried.]
I was shocked and worried.
[Predicted the tough work after seeing the first time of Six puzzle practicing together]
[What is Lia Kim’s reaction?]
I remembered before.
-You two almost accomplished.
-Always looking at me.
[Chan Mi & Ye In are almost perfect.]
[Actively]
You’re busy today, right?
[(Stop saying.)]
[So ashamed...]
-Regard as being busy.
-Well, I’m busy.
[Out of breath…(Nose should keep working.)]
I’ll help you remember the sequence.
[Together with teacher Karin•Yeji Kim]
Before we started the hard work.
[Before we started the hard work]
Everyone!
[Hello.]
-Hello1 –Hello!
[Park Bom shows up.]
-What’s this? -Teacher, please.
[Teacher! Please!]
Is this a bribe?
[Chief Park Bom of Bom Entertainment is working.]
-Thanks for your bribe
-I hope you take care of En Jun
[Please take care of Eunji.]
I hope you take care of En Jun.
[The clone of Park Bom•Eunji, the last puzzle]
[Eunji is the main rapper of Brave girls]
[with outstanding softness.]
[A few days ago, the company that Brave girls belongs]
[Park Bom Brother]
Brother.
Who are you?
[Boss and producer: Brave Bro]
-Hi.
-When did you come?
[Park Bom: I have something to ask.]
I have something to ask for help.
[Park Bom: I have three stages this time]
I have three stages this time.
[Park Bom: According to the rules of the third competition,]
And I got the chance from Queendom quest.
[Park Bom: I succeeded in the lemon task so I passed the quest of Queendom.]
[Park Bom: And I got the chance of production group.]
[Park Bom comes for 'Brave Bro'.]
So I came here to ask Brave Bro for help.
[Park Bom applied for the reinforcement.]
[Park Bom: I am shooting on a program called Queendom.]
I am shooting on a program called Queendom.
[Brave Bro: Good to know before.]
I know. You become the central point.
-Yes, No.1 in topics.
-It’s funny.
[No.1 in topics.]
[Sadness of single man Brave Bro
You've always been alone.]
Sometimes there are only you.
So,
I need to perform three times.
Eunji had performed the stage
of  with me before.
[Park Bom: Before she get to the point,
Eunji had performed the stage of  with me before.]
[Eunji from Brave girls had cooperated
the featuring stage  with Park Bom.]
I want to take her to my dance squad.
[Park Bom: I want to take her.]
[Park Bom wants to take Eunji from Brave girls to her dance squad.]
And I need her to dance instead of me.
I think she would be pleasure.
[Happy Brave Bro: She may be honored.]
I would appreciate it.
[Brave Bro: She treat you as... !Respect!]
She respects you.
[Glad]
Really?
I hope she could help you.
[Very kindly, the reinforcements were successfully invited.]
Of course.
We’ll fight!
[Park Bom: Straightforward, we'll try our best.]
I’ll go now.
-Fighting. -Where are you going?
[So (leaving now?) Where to go?]
I’m going to pick up Eunji.
[I’m going to pick up Eunji.]
Straightforward!
[Time is tight, so let's go straightforward.]
[Seeing off without hesitation]
-Keep in touch.-Ok, brother.
-Goodbye.-Ok.
[Park Bom gets some relief thus.]
-Fighting. -Fighting
-I’ll win the competition.-Okay.No.1
[So Eunji from Brave girls is the 6th member of six puzzle]
-Hello.-Thanks.
[She is my clone. Please take care of her.]
She is my “clone”. Please take care of her.
I am happy, because I met Eunji before.
[Lovelyz Ye In: I am happy, because I met Eunji before.]
[Lovelyz Ye In: It has been a long time.]
It has been a long time.
She looks optimistic.
[AOA Chan Mi: She looks optimistic.]
She must be good at facial expressions.
[AOA Chan Mi: She must be good at facial expressions(acting).]
[AOA Chan Mi :She is the kind of member]
She is the kind of member
who is pretty just staring at the camera.
[AOA Chan Mi: who is pretty just staring at the camera.]
Fighting!
Chan Mi, let me take a look at you.
[Embarrassed OH MY GIRL YooA
Chan Mi, let me take a look at you.]
No way.
It’s kind of strange.
One more time. Again.
It’s much more stressed out than being Brave girls.
[Brave girls Eunji: It's much more stressed out]
[Brave girls Eunji: than being Brave girls]
[Brave girls Eunji: I need to perform well]
I need to perform well because it’s the senior’s stage.
[Brave girls Eunji: because it’s the senior’s stage.]
I’m worried.
[Worrying]
[What's the tacitness between six puzzle members?]
-Music.-Okay!
Hold up no you didn't bow bow
I ain't the chick to walk
behind you around town
[Finally remember the dance movements.]
Just 'cause you 're packin'packin'
whoop down south
[Eunji get used to them without strangeness.]
That don't mean I'm ever gonna
take it lying down baby
You're the man but I got the
I got the I got the power
You make rain
[Brave girls Eunji: It's my pleasure to be the clone of Park Bom.]
Thanks Park Bom
[Brave girls Eunji: I'll do my best.]
For being here as her clone.
I’ll try my best.
[Park Bom: Thank you so much, Eunji.]
Eunji, thank you so much.
Don’t worry about the ranking.
Just enjoy it.
[Don’t worry about the ranking.]
[On the other side...]
One more time. Again.
DRIVE UP.
[Moon Byul & Soo Jin are practicing with sweat streaming down their back]
Up down
Pull up
Next, lalalalala
[Shake the shoulder Dalalala~~]
Shake your shoulders!
[Dalalala~~]
lalalalala
Shoulders and legs!
[Soo Jin is so funny.]
Act shamelessly!
Do it now.
[Try again.]
lalalalala
More shaking!
[Still unfamiliar..]
-So weak.
-What to do?
Start!
[Oh no~~~]
So weak!
[How would the stage be?
Confused unfamiliar queen, Soo Jin]
Hip bone and shoulders at the same time.
Start!
[Shoulders unworking]
Shaking your shoulders!
-Moon Byul does great.-Shaking like this.
[Thanks to one-to-one teaching.]
Yes, keep going.
[Stagger]
Hold on, hold on.
Keep in line.
[Oh~God~~]
[Becoming performers through painful practice]
We have to prepare for the stage together.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: We have to prepare for the stage together.]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Though it’s difficult, I believe we can!]
Though it’s difficult, I believe we can!
I keep thinking that I won’t let you down.
[(G)I-DLE Soo Jin: I keep thinking that I won’t let you down.]
[(G)I-DLE Soo Jin: I thought a lot.]
[(G)I-DLE Soo Jin: Fighting!]
And keep trying. I’ll beat you down.
[I’ll beat you down.]
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: Our group name is six puzzle]
Our group name is six puzzle
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: which means the puzzle recombines]
which means the puzzle recombines after separated.
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: after separated.]
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: It will be different.]
It will be different.
The happy feeling on the stage.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: I Feel so happy on the stage.]
It's not about winning, but creativeness.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: It's not about winning, but creativeness.]
[OH MY GIRL YooA: It’s funny.]
It’s funny.
The first time to be here alone.
[AOA Chan Mi: The first time to be here alone.]
I’ll behave myself.
[AOA Chan Mi: I’ll behave myself.]
[AOA Chan Mi: And try to make a legendary stage.]
And try to make a legendary stage.
[D-7 It's a race against time from now on]
[Members work hard to exceed their limits without a day's rest.]
Hold up no you didn't bow bow
I ain't the chick to walk
behind you around town
[Solo stage]
Just 'cause you 're packin'packin'
whoop down south
[And group stage]
That don't mean I'm ever
gonna take it lying down baby
[Step by step, day by day.]
Oh I'm a machine when I do it
[Six puzzle members keep sweating.]
I'll be catching fire gaso when I do it
Just 'cause you 're packin'packin'
[Don't miss it!]
whoop down south
That don't mean I'm ever gonna
take it lying down baby
[The legendary stage is coming soon!]
You're the man
The stage consisted by six puzzle
[Lee Da Hee: The stage consisted by six puzzle.]
[Lee Da Hee: six puzzle]
Let’s go.
[So nervous behind the stage]
[Show time!]
Wow, they’re coming.
[Smiling like a mom]
[Together fighting six puzzle!]
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: They are the real girl group.]
They are totally a true girl group.
（G）I-DLE has 6 members too.
2 3 Hello!
[Six puzzle Hello! We’re six puzzle~]
We’re six puzzle.
six puzzle, hello!
It seems that it is not easy for everyone
to fit in the practice schedule.
[Jang Sung Kyu: It seems that it is not easy for everyone]
[Jang Sung Kyu: to fit in the practice schedule.]
A little bit of difficult.
Yesterday's rehearsal was the first time
we all cooperated.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Yesterday's rehearsal was the first time we all cooperated.]
[Six puzzle Live rehearsal]
[#The first puzzle Jeong Ye In]
I learned modern dance as a child.
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: I learned modern dance as a child.]
Prepare to bring into play.
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: I Prepare to bring into play.]
I haven't danced till sweat like a pig for a long time.
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: I I haven't danced till sweat like a pig for a long time.]
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: I was very moved when I remembered
a lot of things in the past.]
I was very moved when I remembered
a lot of things in the past.
I'm going to do a couple dance today with tango.
[#The second puzzle Soo Jin]
[(G)I-DLE Soo Jin I'm going to do a couple dance today with tango.]
[Open your mouth!]
Wow, I was tempted.
[Wow, I was tempted.]
[#The third puzzle Chan Mi]
It’s kind of short. So I just dance a bit.
[AOA Chan Mi: The table will be higher tomorrow.]
This should be higher tomorrow.
[Production group: It would be dangerous if too high.]
It would be dangerous of being too high.
It’s okay.
[AOA Chan Mi: It’s okay.]
-Is it ok?
-Yes, I’m fine.
[AOA Chan Mi: I was going to show the interrogation room]
I was going to show the interrogation room
with two male dancers.
[AOA Chan Mi: with two male dancers.]
I don't know if I can make it.
[AOA Chan Mi: I don't know if I can make it.]
[AOA Chan Mi: I prepared.]
I prepared.
[Chan Mi voluntarily performs a difficult maneuver.]
Oh god.
[AOA Chan Mi: I screwed up though I tried in a difficult way.]
I missed it though I added ambition.
[AOA Chan Mi: I should practice more.]
I need more practice.
[#The fourth puzzle YooA]
The teachers said the no one succeeded
[OH MY GIRL YooA: No one succeeded]
in covering Michael Jackson.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: in covering Michael Jackson's dance]
Even so, I can't fail.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: Even so, I can't fail.]
[OH MY GIRL YooA: And practice it a million times while thinking about it.]
And practice it a million times while thinking about it.
[#The fifth puzzle: Moon Byul]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: It was a chance for me]
It was a chance for me to show you something new.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: to show something new.]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Inverted music also catches the eyes.]
Inverted music also catches the eyes.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: I hope you appreciate it.]
I hope you can see the awesome stage if you appreciate it.
[Six puzzle: Group dance rehearsal after individual stage rehearsal]
There is an accident.
We can complete with us.
[Because it was the first time,
the members are worried about the match.]
We haven’t matched up before.
3 2 1 Start!
[Rehearsal starts.]
You're the man but I got the
[After solo, Moon Byul joins in the midway of group stage rehearsal.]
I got the I got the power
You make rain but I'll make it
I'll make it I'll make it shower
[The movements become cautious.]
[Oh no!]
[Grim-faced Lia Kim]
Thanks.
[Lia Kim: Action is not neat.]
-Action is not neat.
-Got it.
-It needs to be a little bit adjusted.
-Okay.
[Lia Kim: It needs to be a little bit adjusted.]
-Try again!
-The most difficult part.
5 6 7 8
[Six puzzles is adjusting moving lines in an orderly way.]
I got the I got the I got the
-Move like this?
-Yes.
Okay.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: It would be difficult]
It would be difficult
for the first time.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: for the first time.]
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Or we should try it. We should try it by ourselves.]
Or we should try it. We should try it by ourselves.
It’s better after the adjustment.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: It’s better after the adjustment.]
Dance matches up for the first time.
[Synchronicity through continuous practice]
-Is this oksy?
-Yes.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: Because we're a team]
Because we have to prepare for the same stage.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: We prepare for the same stage.]
We’re excited and worried.
[OH MY GIRL YooA: We’re excited and worried.]
[Brave girls Eunji: We practiced a lot.]
We practiced a lot.
[AOA Chan M:i I hope you're looking forward to it.]
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: We’ll try our best]
We’ll try our best
[Lovelyz Jeong Ye In: to bring a wonderful performance.]
to bring a wonderful performance.
[Six puzzle's stage was prepared hardly]
[What about the stage of the first puzzle Ye In?]
Why do you paint the eyes with red color?
It looks kind.
[To be continued.]
[Dance squad
Stage prepared by six puzzle]
[Power 6puzzle]
Why do you paint the eyes with red color?
-Kind gold-Yes.
[This line... Sympathy for Lady Vengeance]
[Feeling good right now?]
Great.
Awesome.
If it’s real.
Why paint your eyes red?
It feels more kind.
[]
[Like a movie very much]
[Touched feedback(?)]
[Automatic exclamation wow~]
Awesome.
[A perfect combination of modern dance and music]
Nice.
Excellent.
Amazing.
[Our youngest member. She is so beautiful.]
So beautiful.
[Screaming~~]
[Senorita-Camila Cabello & Shawn Menders]
[Oh yeah~]
Sexy.
[I can’t help myself.]
Killing me!
[Is she shy? Soo Jin?]
Awesome.
Crazy!
[Crazy~]
Cover the eyes
[Not joking. Blustered]
So sexy!
[(G)I-DLE Minnie: It looks so amazing.]
It looks so shocked. Really!
[OH MY GIRL Mimi :That's really daring.]
That's really daring.
[Oh my god! Our youngest!]
The youngest!
[Concentrated Sh*4]
Shsh
[Strip - Little Mix]
[Wow!]
Wow.
Perfect!
[Wow!!]
[Perfect!]
[Well done.]
[So proud of the youngest. Burst out]
Burst out
[Next coming…]
[Smooth Criminal - Michael Jackson]
[Look! YooA is awesome.]
Let’s go.
[Let’s go.]
Wow!
[Wow!]
Awesome. Surprised me!
[Wow! Awesome. Surprised me!]
[Wow!]
Awesome.
[LovelyzBabysoul: Awesome!]
[Standing and clapping gratefully]
[Well done, my baby.]
Well done, my baby.
[A variety of performances with a variety of charms composed of combination stage]
Varied styles!
[She comes out!]
Coming out!
She comes out!
[(G)I-DLE So yeon: I'm really curious.]
So curious.
[Two moons- Moon Byul]
[OH MY GIRL Mimi: Wow She is…amazing.]
It’s easy.
What?
[What? Knife sound?!]
Like assassins.
[MAMAMOO Solar: Wow popping!]
Poppin
[Awesome!]
Awesome
[Only cheers!]
I don’t know who will be No.1.
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: I don’t know who will be No.1]
[Eunji from Brave Girls]
[Shocked um? Oh god.]
Park Bom’s
[Eunji, clone of single singer Park Bom
Awesome!]
clone.
Awesome.
-What to do?-Eunji from Brave Girls
[OH MY GIRL Seung Hee Park Bom left after the words ”Please”]
After said please.
[Wow, look at the momentum.]
Like a live concert!
[AOA Ji Min: Like a live concert now!]
Really!
[Power - Little Mix]
Crazy!
[OH MY GIRL Seung Hee: [sigh with emotion]
They’re awesome.]
Awesome!
I almost cry.
[I’m crying…]
[Full ver. video of Six Puzzle’s performance and original video without cut are uploaded on YouTube NAVER TV]
Is this Queendom?
[Applause! They are great!]
[(G)I-DLE Yuqi: All of them do the best.]
all of them in this group dance well.
Really?
[Sincerely, if they debut, we can’t catch up with.]
If they debut, I’d better keep practicing.
-Really Encore, encore, encore.
Let her debut as a member of six puzzle.
[I’m in debut.]
Send her away.
She danced easy part for cooperating with us.
[She is amazing.
She has been dancing easy part for cooperating with us.]
Power
[The majesty of the group
Six Puzzle showed the powerful stage.]
-Really-They are awesome.
[Accomplished the performance...]
Finally it’s over.
It’s over.
Well done.
[You' ve had a long day.]
Rest room
[It's a wonderful stage performed by excellent us.]
Well done.
You've had a long day.
[It’s over.]
[Congratulation time!]
It’s over.
Over, over.
[Touch themselves.]
Over.
It’s the first time to
[AOA Chan M:i It’s the first time to]
[AOA Chan Mi: cooperate dance with you.]
cooperate dance with you.
[AOA Chan Mi: It’s funny.]
It’s funny.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: I’ve forgotten it was a competition.]
I’ve forgotten it was a competition.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: It’s enough for we 6.]
It’s enough for we 6.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: We’re closer (relationship)]
We’re getting closer
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: for preparing the stage.]
for preparing the stage.
[MAMAMOO Moon Byul: It’s a good time.]
It’s a good time.
[It would be hard to forget the stage.]
There was a feeling that
it would be hard to forget the stage.
Round 2 is going on by the songs recommended by fans.
Pinkdora’s box
I am crying.
Don’t cry.
Cute.
Oh my god.
This is.