[English subtitles are available]
[I Don't Want To Be Friends With You]
Li Jin Bu.
You're over-reacting.
You can't be so vulnerable to criticism.
I've told you that
you are not supposed to ask for
drink or food at anybody else's house.
Did you forget the rule?
I didn't ask for that.
The aunt gave it to me.
You are not supposed to take it
even though she gave it to you.
Why?
No reason.
This is the rule.
The rule I set for you.
Humph.
Li Jin Bu.
Come here.
Repeat it.
I ask you to repeat it.
[Episode 4: This is my rule]
What if he hits you?
He wouldn't dare.
Don't worry.
I don't beat girls.
No.
Don't go out.
Hurry up!
I think we should have...
That day...
Du.
Egg!
What...
Stand there. Go back.
What happened?
Nothing.
Chen Jun He.
We are at school.
Who are you?
It's none of your business.
Calm down, buddy.
Don't be angry.
Move back.
He pushed me.
So?
What are you doing, Mao? He pushed me.
Sit down.
What do you want to do?
What?
What are you doing?
Who is making trouble?
Ms Yang.
Why are you dragging me?
I just dropped by to say hi.
Who?
Who pushed me?
Why didn't she hit others but you?
I don't know either.
I was just about to ask her,
but you came and dragged me out.
I'm the victim.
You are the victim?
Do you think that I don't know that
you are swaggering around at school?
Tell me,
during your three years
in high school
how many times has your uncle come?
Do you want me to
expel you?
No.
I'm warning you the last time.
If I know
you make trouble at school once again,
I promise that
you'll never have a chance
to get into this school.
Got it?
Yes.
Say it loudly.
Yes, I got it.
We've been standing here so long.
Then,
can I go back to the classroom now?
Come back.
You won't tell me the truth, will you?
But,
I've told you everything.
I just bumped into him when I was walking.
It was accidental.
I have apologized to him,
but he just refused to let it go.
What else can I do?
Why did you kick him then?
If what you said is true
and you've said sorry to him
why would he go to our classroom
to make trouble?
Do you think it's logical?
I've told you the truth,
but you don't believe me.
So we'll just keep standing here.
Stand here.
Who made the mistake?
You stand.
As a girl,
why do you always clash with boys.
Do you think it's right?
Mr Wu.
It's me that was bullied.
You need to figure out the truth, right?
I can let it go,
but you must promise to me that
you'll focus on your schoolwork.
If he comes and finds
you again, just tell me
and I'll handle it.
But you are not allowed to
have conflicts with him again.
Got it?
Yes. Thanks, sir.
Come back.
By tomorrow afternoon,
write a 300 word self-reflection
and submit it to Ms Yang.
What?
You didn't say that.
I'm telling you now.
Just wait and see.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Did Mr Wu scold you?
No.
How did you get into trouble with him?
Do you two know each other?
No.
It was a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Why?
I heard that you just rushed up
and beat him.
Mr Wu had questioned me for 45 minutes.
Are you also questioning me?
-Okay, enough.
-I...
Go back to your seats.
Let me talk to her.
Don't worry.
As long as I am here,
if Chen Jun He dares to find you again,
I'll protect you.
Li Qing Tong.
Everyone can get involved in it
except you.
Why?
You just let it go.
And you are not supposed
to have any contact with him.
This is the rule.
The rule between us.
Do you hear me?
Promise me.
Okay?
Yeah, okay.
I'll leave you be.
Remember.
Don't have any contact with him.
Hi, buddy.
We have taken it out for you.
Specifically, we have
deflated their bicycle tires.
What?
What have you done?
We have deflated their bicycle tires.
We don't know which bicycles
belong to Lin Jin Bu and Lin Qing Tong,
so we deflated the tires
of all the bicycles.
This is what they get
for making my buddy angry.
We are brilliant, right?
What's the matter with you?
Who asked you to do this?
We were letting out your anger.
Don't you feel ashamed to
deflate girls' bicycle tires?
Yang Ai Ling is watching me.
Are you asking for me to be expelled?
What...
What should we do then?
Go inflate the tires!
Chen Jun He.
No matter why Li Jin Bu
got into trouble with you,
you just take your anger out
on me.
Don't hurt her.
Hey, buddy.
Are you trying to solve this problem?
No matter what happened,
I apologize to you.
It's Li Jin Bu's fault.
Ask her to apologize to me.
This is my rule.
Got it?
My bicycle is deflated.
Mine too.
Who did this?
So is mine.
You bicycle is deflated, isn't it?
Did you do this?
As if you have caught me.
No one could do this except you.
Yeah, I did.
What can you do?
What do you want to do?
You
inflate the tires now
and I can let it go.
Who are you?
Why should I do as you told me.
Inflate the tires!
No.
You dare to hit me?
Okay. No fighting.
Chen Jun He.
We have some conflicts,
so I wouldn't be angry even
if you smashed my bicycle.
But you shouldn't deflate the others.
Don't you feel ashamed
to deflate their bikes?
You jerk.
You wench.
You dare to call me a jerk?
Do you believe I will
pull your hair today?
Chen Jun He is bullying me!
Help me!
-Help!
-Catch her, quickly!
Chen Jun He is bullying me!
Help!
Stop!
Stop.
What are you doing?
Stop there.
Go home.
What are you doing?
[Learned, Inspired, Educated]
Why are you still here?
Chen Jun He is making trouble again.
What did he do?
Wait for a while.
We'll go home after he leaves.
You guys, as strong men,
deflated bicycle tires?
Don't you feel ashamed?
This is the last time.
If I see this again,
I will punish you severely.
Got it?
Yes, Mr Wu.
We will never do it again.
See you, Mr Wu.
Buddy.
Humph.
If he didn't inflate the tires for me,
I would beat him unconscious.
Let's go.
Listen, I am not afraid of him.
Today, I hit him with my bag.
Where is my bag?
[Female bath]
Where is my uncle?
There.
Cover me.
Stop.
Where are you going?
To scrub the bath.
Not you.
Come here.
Uncle.
Why did you come home so late?
Today's Niu Xiao Huo's birthday.
I went to his home.
Niu Xiao Huo's birthday?
Do you think that I don't
know Niu Xiao Huo's birthday?
You changed his birthday?
Uncle, I've got something to do.
Stop.
What's wrong with your bag?
Why do you have a pink bag?
I picked it up.
Then give it to your teacher.
Stop scrubbing the bath.
Go and do your homework.
Your uncle will scold
you when he's back later.
If I don't do this, he will.
His back aches.
The doctor has told him not
to do heavy work many times.
You'd better care for him directly
and not make him angry.
Scrub the bath.
Tell me the truth.
Whose bag is it?
It must belong to a girl.
I have told you that I picked it up.
Don't ask me the details.
Is the girl more beautiful than me?
Not going to sleep yet?
What should I do?
How could I go to class
without books tomorrow?
My mum will scold me if she knows.
Don't worry.
I'll take it back for you tomorrow.
No.
You better not clash with him again.
I'd rather throw it away.
[Tieyuan No. 3 Middle School]
Morning, Ms Yang.
I'll go to find Chen Jun He
and take your bag back..
Where is my bag?
Give it back to me.
Apologize to me and
then I'll give it to you.
Impossible.
Alright.
I'm a kind person.
Here you are.
[Ugly Monster]
You are an ugly person.
Your whole family is ugly!
[Ugly Monster]
Don't be angry, Tong.
You can use my bag.
Who gave you this stage name?
What's up?
Chen Jun He.
You're a man.
Do you feel better
by bullying girls?
When have I bullied them?
It's just a joke.
A joke?
Do you want to make trouble?
What are you doing?
Ms Yang.
Morning, Ms Yang.
We're chatting here.
See you.
I'm pissed off.
I'm pissed!
Pissed!
I'll get revenge!
Don't be angry.
Calm down.
I can't tolerate his bullying me.
Does he think that I'm afraid of him?
If he really makes me furious, I will...
I will beat him up myself.
If I am not strong enough,
I'll use tools.
I... I would use swords.
I'm good at martial arts.
I'm also powerful.
Come on.
Just don't respond to him.
What if he bullies us again?
[To teach and educate]
Ms Yang?
[Tieyuan No. 3 Middle School]
It's so long.
[Written by Chen Jun He]
[Daily Neccessity Supermarket
and Restaurant]
Your dumplings.
Thanks.
Have a taste.
Enjoy your dumplings.
-Thanks.
-Alright.
This time
I played a trick.
I am sure this time
Chen Jun He would get into trouble.
Will your trick work?
[A gift for Ms Yang]
What... What's this?
This is the self-reflection
you submitted to me.
No.
Ms Yang, I didn't draw it.
What's this?
Enough of it.
If you dare do it, you should
dare to bear the responsibility.
Except you, no one
dares do such a thing.
Ms Yang,
I didn't do it.
Believe what you will.
Still so obnoxious.
I'll call your uncle to school tomorrow.
No problem.
As long as you don't betray me.
Impossible.
I'll be the first to say,
whoever betrays you,
I'll beat him.
I think
it must be Li Jin Bu.
Of course.
I know that.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's go and find them.
How?
We have no evidence.
If we make trouble in
their classroom again,
I'll definitely be expelled.
What should we do then?
Stop!
Buddy.
I didn't draw it.
I can really
do nothing with you.
Mr Wu,
I didn't
do that.
You didn't do that?
Wang Xiao Min has told Ms Yang
everything.
No use denying it.
Wang Xiao Min, that traitor.
I don't want to bother about it anymore.
Ask your aunt to come to school tomorrow.
Got it?
Give applause to the artist.
Hey.
I think your painting is brilliant.
Can you draw a picture for me?
Can I stand up?
My... My legs are numb.
Don't stand up.
What is it going on?
Tomorrow,
ask my aunt to come to school.
Hua, let me explain it to you.
Shameful.
Betrayer.
Traitor!
Mr Wu,
I'm really sorry.
We've caused you trouble again.
It's not a big deal.
As long as she
apologizes to Ms Yang and Chen Jun He
and focuses on her schoolwork,
then I can explain it to Ms Yang.
I won't apologize.
It's impossible.
Hua.
Don't disrupt
your teacher.
It's fine, Mr Wu.
-I'll go back and reprimand her.
-Alright.
I'll ask her to apologize.
-Good.
-Thanks.
Apologizing is not enough.
Hi, Ms Yang.
Ms Liu has told me everything
and I've asked Chen Jun He.
She purposely framed others.
It's a serious problem.
Ms Yang, it's not that serious.
They are kids.
They don't know better.
You are Li Jin Bu's aunt, right?
Yes.
Look at it.
[A gift for Ms Yang]
It...
It's too much.
How could you draw
such a beautiful teacher
like this?
How could you?
Chen Jun He.
What do you want to say?
Ms Yang,
Mr Wu and auntie,
I think.
Li Jin Bu's behaviour is really terrible.
I can look past the trap
she planted
even though it's not the first time.
But she
stigmatized
the image of Ms Yang.
That I can't tolerate.
How could she stigmatize Ms Yang!
You better stop.
Mr Wu,
I'm the victim.
Li Jin Bu has
left a trauma on me.
I require that
Lin Jin Bu apologize to me publicly.
Otherwise, I won't let it go.
Li Jin Bu,
as a student,
you should not frame other students.
Such behaviour is intolerable.
Then
you write a self-reflection
of more than 5000 words.
Reflect on your actions
in Year 3 Class 1.
And apologize to Chen Jun He
in public.
If you can't do these,
then you should get out of the school.
This school can't
tolerate students like you.
A little excessive, huh?
Get out.
Mr Wu,
I'm really sorry to trouble you.
I'll reprimand her back home.
Thanks.
Hua.
Go home.
Hurry up.
Pretty accurate drawing.
Hua.
Come here.
Come.
I want to have a talk with you.
Hua.
You
have lived here for a long time
and I really take you as
a member of this family.
I've never scolded you.
Your mum
is abroad.
As an adult,
I think I have the
responsibility to guide you.
Alright.
Since you agree with me,
then I'll have to talk to you today.
You
are such a good girl,
but why
do you always have conflicts
with those bad boys at school?
What's his name?
Chen...
Chen Jun He.
Why do you have conflicts with him?
He is such a bad student.
I'm sorry, auntie.
Hua.
There is something you don't know.
Just now, Du's mum phoned me
and told me that Chen Jun He's uncle
has known Ms Yang
for many years.
And they
were lovers.
Come on.
Don't gossip in front of kids.
It's not gossip. It's true.
I...
I'm telling them that
the problem is serious.
Come on. We know.
Let's have dinner.
-Have dinner.
-Stand up.
It is your turn now.
What's wrong with me?
What's wrong with you?
Hua is a new arrival.
She knows nothing.
You should have told her everything.
Why did you
get involved yourself?
I didn't.
And it's not all our fault.
Chen Jun He
also has done something wrong.
We,
to some extent,
are upholding justice.
Upholding justice?
I think you are too much recently.
Dad,
I didn't do anything wrong
but Mum still scolds me.
Go back to your room
and do your homework.
Li Qing Tong,
you won't be eating dinner tonight.
You are terribly spoilt.
You...
You should let her have dinner.
I'm sorry, auntie.
I'm really sorry.
I assure you that I won't do it again.
You should
let them have dinner.
Don't be so angry.
I'm going to scold you too.
What's wrong with me?
You know what you have done.
Our daughter
is terribly spoilt by you.
That brat.
I barely said anything to her
and look how she reacted?
This is bad.
Once she starts,
she won't stop any time soon.
How long does such situation last?
One or two days to
one or two weeks.
It mainly depends on
how my father pacifies her.
Fortunately, you're not like that.
Me?
I have no right to lose
my temper at my home.
Only my mum has the right.
My family is better.
At least I have the
right to lose my temper.
Does your mother scold you?
Of course.
But only for a short while.
And she has a virtue where
she'd forget everything
after a night of sleep.
That's like me.
Never hold grudges,
easy to coax.
What a coincidence.
But not everything
you said is true, isn't it?
What do you mean?
You mean that I have no
right to criticize your daughter?
Even a word is not allowed?
Of course you have the right.
You are the boss.
You are always right.
Li Wu Si,
Li Qing Tong is the way she is
because of you.
Go on and spoil her more.
You continue.
I'll see
how much worse she'd become.
What...
What does it have to do with me?
Aren't you eating dinner?
What should we do.
It's a mess in school.
It's a mess at home.
Don't think so much.
Do your homework.
I don't have the
mood to study.
I can't study now.
Study.
If you don't study,
I'll tell your mum.
Aun...
Give it to me.
[Tieyuan No. 3 Middle School]
Can I talk to you?
No.
Could you ask Yang Ai Ling
to stop getting involved with the
conflict between you and Li Jin Bu.
I tell Yang Ai Ling?
Why she would agree?
She is asking Lin Jin Bu
to say sorry to you.
If you tell her that you
have forgiven Li Jin Bu,
she would probably let it go.
Firstly.
Yang Ai Ling is angry because Li
Jin Bu drew an ugly picture of her.
Secondly,
why should I forgive
her without her apology?
She is supposed to say sorry to me.
Don't forget that she hit me on my face.
She should apologize to
me for what she has done.
What if I apologize to you for her?
No.
Read it in your class
and also in Year 3 Class 1.
Why?
Is this the way
you should speak to a teacher?
I'm sorry.
Lin Jin Bu.
You only have one day.
If you don't read it today,
don't bother coming to school tomorrow.
Got it.
Hua.
I think you'd better
apologize to Chen Jun He.
It's not a big deal.
No.
You should be sensible.
You hit him on his face, didn't you?
It's your fault.
Who are you helping?
I'm trying to find a way
to solve this problem.
Now, at school,
you've offended Chen Jun He
as well as Yang Ai Ling.
What if they continue to make trouble
for you?
Then I'll drop out of school.
It doesn't matter.
You are not reasonable.
I'm reasonable.
No, you are not.
I think
you should be reasonable.
And you always refuse to
tell me the reason for the conflict
between you and Chen Jun He.
Do you take me as your best friend?
Fine.
You go and find him.
You are so silly
that you are cheated by him.
I'm silly?
And you're smart?
Your trick
got yourself in trouble.
Mum!
I'm not your mum.
Your mum is dead.
Why do you say that?
It's not auspicious. Mum!
Honey.
We're hungry.
Stay hungry.
There's no dinner tonight.
Mum!
Dad, I'm hungry.
Let's go.
We're going to eat out.
Go.
[Daily Neccessity Supermarket
and Restaurant]
[Today: Chicken feet special,
buy one free one]
I think that they are
reluctant to talk to me recently.
I don't want to talk to you either.
But, Xiao,
it' not all my fault.
I
was threatened by Chen Jun He.
I had no choice
but to disclose the secret.
Come on.
Stop talking about it.
Do you
know why Lin Jin Bu
hit Chen Jun He on his face?
Even Li Qing Tong doesn't know.
How can I know?
I just think it's a bit weird.
She just came back recently
and we're not in the same year
as Chen Jun He.
Thus
they shouldn't have conflicts.
Right?
But why are they so against each other?
Maybe...
Maybe something happened previously.
It's obvious that she is seeking revenge.
What conflicts could they have?
Don't bother trying to figure
things out related to women.
Those things are so complicated.
It seems that you know a lot.
I know much more than you.
I've found out the basic
rules from my mum.
If
she says that
she isn't angry,
then she must be angry.
If she says
she doesn't want to eat it,
then you shouldn't eat it either.
If she says that it doesn't matter,
then she must be furious.
If she says that she's
put on weight recently,
you must say that she is slim.
If she complains to you about someone,
don't ask who it is.
Just complain along with her.
My dad and I survive this way.
So,
you should know how they think.
Don't say anything that you shouldn't say.
Don't ask about anything
that you shouldn't know.
I don't agree with you.
My mum is different.
My mum tells us what
she's thinking directly.
That's why.
Your mum and mine are different species.
Together with those girls,
it would take us a long
time to figure them out.
Li Jin Bu.
Dear teachers
and schoolmates.
I wrote this self-reflection today
to reflect upon my mistakes.
I've thought a lot
about what I've done.
I feel regretful
for breaking the rules.
I know that I've
made a serious mistake
and I'm ashamed of my mistake.
Finally,
I want to express my
sincerest apology to Ms Yang.
I'm sorry to have let you down.
Chen Jun He,
I have something to tell you.
I blew it this time,
but I'd never say sorry to you.
I just want to say that
you deserve it.
Interesting.
Hua.
You shouldn't be too
stubborn under such situation.
We should know how to minimize the loss.
I don't know how to explain it to you.
But I really dislike him.
Well, well, well.
What are you doing?
I don't know why you hit me on my face,
but it doesn't matter.
Since you dislike me,
I won't hold back either.
Now, I will let the whole school know
that you're as terrible as me.
We would often have conflicts.
We are both bad students.
The worst outcome is
that we're both expelled.
I don't care about it.
Me either.
Chen Jun He,
you are too much.
She said that I deserved it.
Then I'll show you how I deserve it.
Everyone,
don't leave after school.
Let's go home together.
Humph.
Look at the way he swaggers.
Oh my God.
This time we really pissed him off.
Things will be tough from here on out.
Don't be afraid of him.
He can't do nothing to us.
What's up?
I want to solve this problem with you.
Solve this problem?
How?
Lin Jin Bu is studying here because of me.
I have to be responsible for her.
The conflicts between you and Li Jin Bu
should be solved now.
I can't do much.
But I can apologize on her behalf.
With this,
the grudge between you two
is cleared.
Okay?
I told you.
Whoever did it should bear
the responsibility.
Ask her
to say sorry to me.
You have your rules and I have my rules.
Give me your shoe.
What are you afraid of?
So many people are watching.
Take off your shoe.
Okay.
Here you go.