[Episode 22: What You Think Matters]
How many more times will you watch it?
Missy,
I'm here to meet my mom's divorce lawyer,
not to admire your diamond ring, okay?
But it's really sparkly.
You said it was urgent.
So I stood up the lawyer and came here.
It took me a fortnight
to make an arrangement with him.
Was it just to hear this from you?
I helped you too.
That's why I came. I thought...
Never mind.
Thought what?
I'm forced to marry?
I tried on wedding dresses a few days ago.
How did you feel?
It cinches in at the waist
to make you look slim.
Okay, Mrs. Lu.
Honey,
turn around.
Good dog.
Finished, Mr. Lu.
Not bad.
Don't eat this.
Who are you video chatting with?
My dog.
Show me the rear.
What's on your mind?
Why the silence?
I felt...
good.
Really?
If it's good,
why do you need my approval?
Why wasn't I cast in First Love?
You said I've improved!
So you knew it all along?
Tell me why.
Do you know Fang Fang?
An emerging actor.
He wants the role.
A superstar plays a supporting role?
His agent told the casting crew
that no remuneration
or billing order is required.
Did you support me?
It's my project.
I don't want them to think you swing it.
So what?
I want the role, the role!
It's based on popularity and buzz.
At least help me!
Hey, isn't the pal you?
Isn't the ex Ren Xi Zhou?
You two dated secretly
and treated others as pawns.
I lent you items and assisted you.
Wasn't I good enough to you?
After all, I once...
I wanted to go public.
But she thought it wasn't stable
and didn't want others to know.
Or we'd be awkward if we broke up.
Is that the concern?
You helped me.
It's my fault for not getting you the role.
I apologize.
No, that's not right!
I helped you not because of the role,
but because I wanted to help you as a friend.
So I thought you'd also
do me a favor as a friend.
I'm not only your friend,
but also the scriptwriter.
Maybe next time.
You're talented. You became famous at 28.
You have so many opportunities.
But I'm not. I don't.
Next time?
Which time?
If there's a chance next time,
and the investor wants me...
I'll think about it.
I suggest you refuse.
Why?
If you need others' approval to do something,
you'd better refuse it.
I think it's pre-wedding anxiety.
I just want your comfort.
I'm not here to comfort you.
I want you to make the right decision.
Thanks to your return with your dad,
my mom and I could handle the crap back home.
I'm grateful to you.
But if it means
sacrificing my friend's marital freedom,
then I don't want it.
Understand?
What's the right decision?
You don't have to be a heroine.
As a friend, I want you to be happy.
If you don't want marriage,
you can refuse.
It's the right decision for you,
not me!
You know what?
Among a shoal of serranidae,
usually one to three males
swim around a female.
It gives the females a sense of security,
and is conducive to foraging.
I'm not like you.
A black-crowned night heron can fly in the sky,
but serranidae...
I can only swim around my dad.
Xi Zhou,
if I don't get married,
my dad would neglect me,
as if I weren't his daughter.
Yet I can't survive alone.
All I can do is paint.
But if my paintings don't sell,
I have to crash a meal at my friend's place.
I don't want to live this way.
I fear hardship, poverty,
even more than the loss of freedom!
More than the loss of dignity,
happiness,
and everything?
Money is everything.
But that's not what you want.
That's the way I am!
You can sit here and persuade me,
because you don't have it in your life.
If you had it,
you'd struggle and suffer like I do,
and try your best to get it, wouldn't you?
Xi Zhou,
I've made my choice.
Say something.
Did I make the right choice?
You're right.
I'm not you.
Perhaps it's the wrong choice for me,
but not necessarily for you.
We're different.
But whatever you choose,
as long as you're happy, it's good.
Are you happy?
I wish you happiness.
Maybe I should change my career.
Hello?
Harbor crew?
Yes, yes, yes. I'm available.
Add me on WeChat.
By this number.
Hello, sir. I'm Zhu Qiao Fei.
Audition address:
Guangcheng Crown Hotel.
Time: 16:00, September 1st.
Okay.
We haven't checked in yet.
I'll tell you the room number later.
The room number for an audition?
What does that mean?
Is she going to...
No, no.
Thank you for your appreciation.
Maybe next time...
[Lu Shang &amp; Li Nan Xi]
Li Nan Xi's wedding?
At Guangcheng Crown Hotel?
Hello?
I'm getting married.
With whom?
That's so sudden.
A tall, rich, and handsome guy.
Will you come?
If you will, I'll cover it.
Wow.
Does "wow" mean yes or an exclamation?
If I go, I'll audition too.
It's said to be an audition, but maybe...
Next time.
Which time?
If there's a chance next time,
and the investor wants me...
I'll still...
[Wedding of Li Nan Xi and Lu Shang]
Take it.
Just your former company.
You'll have a court hearing in Nanwan that day.
And we're looking for another lawyer.
I don't have the mood.
You quarreled?
Not really.
Is it obvious?
A mother knows her daughter best.
A classical Chinese quotation?
From a TV series
written by your friend.
It's quite good.
He is a famous scriptwriter.
[I'll be in the firm at 15:00 this afternoon.]
[If you're available,
we can discuss with the defendant.]
I got it, Lawyer Zhou.
I'll be right there.
Mom.
The divorce is between him and me.
Please don't interfere.
Besides, I'd better handle it myself.
Don't worry.
Got it, Ms. Ren.
But this time, if you can't handle it,
you must, absolutely,
tell me.
Okay?
Okay!
You needn't attend the trial hearing.
A friend's wedding is once-in-a-lifetime.
Didn't you quarrel?
She gave you an invitation
and a way out.
I know.
And it's bilateral.
- You and Nan Feng...
- We don't!
Obvious too?
You're so stubborn.
Quarreled with Qiao Fei?
You knew it?
He's absent for so long.
Vexed with the wedding?
Let's flip a coin.
Heads, you go.
Tails, you don't.
Which side?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is your thought
when checking it.
Why not somewhere else?
With my former setup.
Improperly folded.
Go and play there.
Chipped bowl.
Li Nan Xi.
Is it on purpose or by accident?
So awkward.
Should he speak first or should I?