[Episode 21: Penniless Means Helpless]
Forget it.
Let it be.
My vacation will be over tomorrow anyway.
Tomorrow, we won't...
What about my meals?
Time to cook for yourself, honey.
Eat up.
Xi Zhou has grown up.
Why don't you ask her to support you?
Yes, she has.
She should have her own life.
I try not to trouble her.
It's a big deal after all.
He comes.
Hey,
Wang Qiu Ping.
It's been a long time since we met.
You're prettier.
- Your husband--
- Her husband died
in a car accident after the divorce.
Alright, hurry up.
Let's see how much it takes to get a divorce.
A car accident... after the divorce?
[Ren Xi Zhou]
[QQ: 634321218]
[You've earned a Qzone Cottage badge for mutual visits
with Ren Xi Zhou for 7 consecutive days.]
[Keep it up for 30 days
to earn a Qzone Villa badge.]
[Access permission required]
What am I doing?
You're all dressed up... at home?
Come in.
Do you have a straw?
I heard that drinking without a straw
would deepen nasolabial folds.
I saw the casting call for First Love.
I want to record an audition video.
But I lack a narrator.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Hello. I'm Zhu Qiao Fei.
I played Jun Lan, the supporting male lead
in Wish Fulfilled Early.
This is my pet, Bento.
It mimics the environment.
Likewise, I adapt my performance to each role.
I want to play
the supporting male lead in First Love.
Your advice is appreciated.
My performance will begin.
We... welcome.
Welcome...
Mom. Li Nan Xi is too shy
- to attract customers.
- Hey!
After all, I did her a favor.
Welcome.
Welcoming me?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Mr. Li wants the property.
As for
the shabby tables and seats, they're unwanted.
- Just remove them! Remove them.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm calling the police.
Yes, call the police.
Call the police?
Funny.
This is my house.
I can remove as I wish.
- Do it.
- Come.
- What are you doing?
- What? What?
This is not your house.
Get out of here!
Ren Hong Xia,
do you know any law?
We haven't divorced.
We're a couple,
and this is joint property. Understand?
Even so, joint property
shall be settled by both parties.
It's illegal for you to remove unilaterally.
You brat!
Hello, Mr. Li. You're here.
[Hongxia Diner]
Look.
This is the property I mortgaged.
What do you think?
Nan Xi?
Dad...
Come here.
Dad, I...
Three,
two,
one.
Xi Zhou.
Is it good?
Compared to the first time I saw you,
you've improved a lot.
So you recognized me?
Why...
Your line delivery was terrible then.
You cared too much about your look,
thus you
kept one pose for the camera
and wore a hat.
A hat makes my face look smaller.
I was a bit anxious about my look then.
But I'm much better now.
Thanks. If you need anything,
just let me know.
Can you show me
your Qzone?
What?
What's going on between you and Ren Xi Zhou?
Oh, right.
My actor friend
wants your advice.
A role interests him,
but pays poorly,
with a quick-tempered director,
and a demanding producer.
He really wants to play it
and thinks it's good.
So,
should he go for it?
Don't hesitate over what you like.
You're right.
Don't dawdle and miss the chance.
Bye.
If she posts anything, I'll let you know.
I'm on your side.
Close the curtains.
Don't get tanned.
You won't be tanned.
You agreed to return.
Why the tantrum?
You said if I returned,
you'd postpone the acquisition.
Oh. Didn't I do that?
If it's profitable,
you wouldn't give up easily.
You knew I was back in Nanwan,
thus acquired her diner deliberately,
and forced me to return, didn't you?
So what if I did?
You know why
I didn't stop you from going to Nanwan?
Turn off the AC.
Yes, Mr. Li.
Turn on the AC.
- Turn it on.
- Yes, Mr. Li.
Because I want to teach you
that one can give up pride,
dignity,
principles,
but not money.
Penniless means helpless.
You're much thinner.
You must have suffered a lot.
Suffering can be good.
It teaches you a lesson.
Such a hypocrite.
You're good,
boasting about your art dream
to your friends.
A spoiled artist?
Don't worry.
Even if I know,
I won't expose you.
After all, you're my daughter.
Nan Xi,
I've been good enough to you.
To get an investment,
you exploit my marriage!
I'm not forcing you to get married.
I'm just introducing you to him.
If you like him, stay and get married.
If you don't,
you can be a waitress or an artist.
Really?
Really.
Please.
Hello, Ms. Li.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Lu Shang.
Have a seat.
It's alright. I only waited for half an hour.
It's 26 min.
What?
I'm helping my mom with her business.
So I'm sensitive to numbers.
Don't mind.
Waiter, serve the food.
Chef-made appetizer,
pan-fried wagyu beef with pea puree.
I have six. What about you?
Let's eat first.
Wait, wait!
She has nine.
I'm sorry, sir. I'll get you a new one.
You're known for the best dishes
and excellent service.
How could you make such a basic mistake?
I'll get you a new one,
and the charge is waived.
Will this do, sir?
Yes.
Eat up.
It's okay. Let's wait.
Try it on
to see if it fits.
If you don't want to get married,
tell me earlier.
In case you regret.