=Deity of Love=
=Episode 28=
I can't feel the mark on Xiling anymore.
The mark disappeared.
She must have betrayed Department Head.
Oh?
Really?
In this world,
no matter who you are,
no one can disobey me.
Master is right.
Since she wouldn't do it,
I'll go there by myself.
Snake Demon.
This time,
you can never escape from me.
Xiaoqing,
I knew you would come.
I told you.
Stay away from me.
Calm down.
As a Demon Hunter,
you should fall in love with a demon!
People can be good or bad.
Demons can be kind or evil.
Moling Bird.
Come out.
Why are you angry?
I am here, right?
Have you brought everything?
Xiaoqing.
Sister.
I am Xiaoqing.
Do you remember?
I'm Bai Xiling.
I am not the person you are looking for.
How come?
Was it a mistake?
Nothing went wrong.
Although your memories were restored,
the Intelligence Mirror can't go wrong.
Then why didn't my sister...
She didn't restore her memories.
It is naturally because
she is not your sister.
The simplest truth.
Impossible.
She was...
It's all because of you.
You harmed my sister.
I am not Fa Hai.
I am Xiuning.
Where is my sister on earth?
Your sister is at the place
where the Leifeng Pagoda stands.
I've been there.
There is no Leifeng Pagoda at all.
Of course.
Since the Leifeng Pagoda was sealed,
it has been hidden
inside the barrier of the Soul Department.
There is a barrier
in the Soul Department indeed.
I'll go to the Soul Department.
And smash the Leifeng Pagoda.
Sister,
I will definitely save you.
I'll go with you.
Don't follow me.
I don't need your accompanying.
If it weren't you,
my sister wouldn't
have been imprisoned in the Leifeng Pagoda.
I am Li Xiuning.
Why do you treat me as Fa Hai?
Because you two are the same people.
You lied to me.
Are you satisfied?
Thinking about the days
from the beginning till now,
don't you know what kind of person I am?
I know exactly what kind of person you are.
Get away.
Xiaoqing.
No matter what relationship
I had with Fa Hai,
but now,
I am Li Xiuning.
You think
I will believe whatever you say?
I will prove it to you.
Prove?
There are something you aren't able to change.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.)
(Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)