=Deity of Love=
=Episode 5=
If you eat a person for me,
I can spare your lives.
Alright.
Definitely.
Boss, please don't kiill me.
I'd better have Fu Ling
do this kind of matter.
Ling.
Isn't Xiaoqing trying to restore her memory?
If you can help her,
Xiuning must be very happy.
That makes sense.
Since she saved me yesterday,
I will help her.
Well,
I heard that
if you go to the back hill alone...
I know I know.
Just give me the address.
I will ask her.
Fu Ling has the simplest mind.
As long as Xiaoqing is gone,
Xiuning will be mine sooner or later.
Brother.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Sister.
Take this
and find the Snake Demon.
Okay.
With the power of the Snake Demon, the Heart Lock Seal will be combined into one piece.
Ghost!
Look carefully.
I'm not a ghost.
Why are you here?
To send you good news, of course.
This is for saving me yesterday.
Here.
What is this?
Aren't you looking for you memory?
It is said that this place
holds what you want.
But you have to go alone.
Ah.
That's the girl?
It's her. It's her.
Then what are you waiting for?
Do it.
Are you from here?
Can you help me get my memory back?
Get your memory back?
We don't take such low-skill jobs.
What?
So you do have a clue, right?
Won't tell you. We won't tell you.
You lied to me.
Yes we did.
Do the job to save our lives.
This is called the work ethic.
Snake Demon's breath.
Boss, boss.
Boss, please don't kill me.
That girl asked us to do it.
Right.
If we don't, she'll kill us.
Shut up!
I want you to help me retrieve my memory.
You can do it.
Boss.
We were talking nonsense.
That's right.
Just let us go.
Why should I spare your lives?
I might as well eat you.
Don't!
Boss.
If you keep us alive,
we'll do whatever you ask.
Help you get back your memory.
We have parents and children to look after.
Please let us go.
Snake Demon.
I finally found you.
I wonder if Xiaoqing has retrieved her memory.
Did she really go to the back hill alone?
Yes.
Didn't you ask me to tell her that?
What?
Miss Xiaoqing went to the back hill.
There are so many demons there.
What a Snake Demon!
The seal didn't change you for the better after all these years.
Demon?
You call me a demon?
Do you know me?
Don't play with me.
I'm taking you back to the Soul Department.
This is not good.
The hairpin is back with the Snake Demon.
I have to tell the Department Head.
Sister.
Xiaoqing.
This is for self-defense.
Do you like it?
The hairpin can turn into a sword.
Miss Xiaoqing.
Who is she?
How could her power make the Heart Lock Seal explode?
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.)
(Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)