Episode 4
Timing and Subtitling by the Totally Awesome Team @ Viki.com
Who're you?
Get out of my way!
Just because you tell me to move, doesn't mean I have to move.
You're being rude.
Call Hong Seol Joo immediately!
Hong Seol Joo?
Just because you're dressed fancy, did you lose your mind?
Hey Lady! Hurry up and get lost while I'm still talking nicely!
W-Who are you?
Hey. You're being rude.
Aigoo!
T-That person!
Ah wait...
I think there's been a bit of a misunderstanding!
These bastards are disturbing the sleeping tiger!
Aigoo! Aish!
Aish!
Huh? This bastard...
What the heck!  How dare you come in—
Oh, you're that lady.
Where is the teacher?
He's over there.
Go! Go!
Wow! This place is huge.
Yup, it has to be at least this big to have a good match.
Right?
- Do you know each other?
- No, I do not.
What do you mean you don't? We've met, so now we know each other.
Anyhow, you look like a fair lady, but why do your hands look so rough?
I'm sorry, Teacher.
It's dangerous for a lady to be walking around alone, right?
So this guy is your tujeon teacher, right?
(traditional Korean card game)
Why is a young lady like you just playing tujeon instead of getting married?
And also, usually with tujeon, you need to learn it from a skilled player like me.
But this guy seems to be quite old, and has a bit of a weird gleam in his eye.
Watch.
Well... Well this is s-supposed to change so...
Do you want a drink?
Of course I do!
If you have no more business with us, you should...
Business? Of course I still have some business with you folks.
I've marked this lady to be my wife from today on.
You little!
Other people may not know it, but I know from just one glance
that you are going to be my wife.
Do you really want to d-die?!
Now, now.
Sit down. He's just at the prime of his youth.
Forgive me.
Thanks to you, I had an enjoyable time.
Follow me.
If my wife is leaving, I will have to go as well!
Ouch! That's hot!
Hey you twerp, acting like an adult already. Do you really want to get married that badly?
Well,
you can start by paying the bills first.
I think we have a misunderstanding. Those people will pay the bills.
Those dishes were your girl's.
And the dishes here, you ate them.
Is this enough?
As a commemoration of me meeting my wife today, it's on me,
so take this and don't be too grateful.
Hey, kid, looking at your attire, you'll have a funeral before your wedding.
But don't be too upset, I'll at least take care of your expenses for you to go to the afterlife.
Here.
The thing that moves this world
is not the King or the high ranking officials, but money.
Just
money.
Starting today, you take care of this, Dam Seo.
Yes, Teacher.
Aish!
This bastard. As he eats a lot, he must have a long life line.
While seeing you off to the afterlife, I might just die before you out of impatience.
It seems you've appeared again when we were having so much fun, My Lord.
Stand him up.
So, you're a gambler going all over Joseon Peninsula, right?
Why don't you take a guess? Is it heads or tails?
- It's heads.
- Are you confident?
I'll even bet my hand that it's heads.
You're willing to bet your hand over one nyang?
If not, I'll be your servant.
This kid... hm...
What is your name?
My name?
W-What's so important with names, anyway?
- It's G-Gae Ttong.
- What? Gae Ttong?
Is that even a name for a person?
Just send him off.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Wait.
A man who knows the importance of one nyang is a true gambler.
Anyway, you're this Gae Ttong's wife,
so don't have any other thoughts.
Hong Seol Joo.
Yes, My Lord.
Do you think this gambling den is still yours?
What should I say?
It's kind of... puzzling... to answer.
It's obviously yours.
Prince Yeoning (the future King Yeongjo)
This liquor, the liquor has run out.
What are you doing, not getting more liquor?
Did you swallow the brazier?
It seems like your mouth is about to spout flames.
What?
What? What are you going to do just by glaring?
Why this—
You pay.
What?
Sorry.
Hey, put in money and get money. One nyang will become two,
and 10 nyangs will become 20.
Here, here!
Okay! Not there!
Here. If you get this right, I'll give you double.
If you get this wrong, you lose everything.
Choose one.
I don't think it's that one.
It's only daytime and you're already drunk.
Don't meddle. Originally, the gamble has to be followed by 70% of luck and 30% of spirit.
I have good luck and a high spirit.
Since you met me, you're right about being lucky.
What is he saying?
Okay.
Open these two first.
Why? Should I open it for you?
Since these two are empty, I must be right.
Why? Isn't that right?
Well, open it, then.
It's double.
Thank you.
It seems like all you have is your body.
You should conserve even one nyang.
Are the rumors true? Does he act like a hooligan?
Yes. In the daytime, he's already drunk, gambling, and even getting into fights.
But, his wise eyes are still the same.
I think I will have to confirm it with my own two eyes.
Grandpa, what are you doing, not sleeping?
Aish, really.
Why do I keep hallucinating?
Relax your shoulders. Here, straight.
Become my wife.
Would you become my wife?
Have you been following me?
Am I a dog? Why would I follow you?
That hand.
From the calluses on the palm of your left hand and on the thumb and index finger of your right hand,
I can tell you enjoy archery.
And you're a young lady at the blooming age.
Then, what are you? You must be an archery teacher for women.
Stop bothering me.
Gosh, couldn't I at least know your name?
This flower...
Next time, I will slice your neck.
Why is she pretty even when she's angry?
Oh, my! I've never seen you before.
A palanquin bearer.
Come here. I will make you feel good today.
Well I... I don't have much m-money...
Oh come on! We all know palanquin bearers make lots of money.
Don't be like that and just come here.
Orabeoni, why are you so irritable?
(orabeoni: archaic equivalent of oppa)
Did something bad happen?
Irritable?
Let's just drink!
Sit down. I said sit.
Why are you so shy?
Oh my! Look at his arms!
He must have really carried some palanquins before.
Oh my! Look at his thighs!
You are touching my leg so casually.
In order to express my gratitude for your attendance here at the Wol Hyang Restaurant,
we have prepared a special performance,
so please enjoy.
Tonight, Prince Yeoning will go to the Wol Hyang Restaurant,
so remember his face well.
Prince Yeoning. The King's child.
My enemy.
What are you up to?! Huh?! Nice seeing you again!
- You again?
- Who are you staring so intently at, huh?!
Do you want me to pull out your eyeballs?
Is that woman even your lover?
What?
Of course she is! She's my lover!
She's going to be my wife, so mind your own business!
And don't appear in front of me again!
What will you do if I don't do that?
It seems that my girl's beauty is so astounding,
that the two of you have lost your rationality.
If you really want my girl, then let's do it this way.
The person with the lowest number will win.
And the person who wins will win my girl.
Good. But...
a win without a loss is not a win at all.
Fine. I won't state this twice.
What about stripping our clothes off? Even the underwear.
Fine. A man will not go back upon his word.
No turning back.
Have I not told you this before? I'm a gambler.
A gambler, you say?
We definitely said that the person with the lowest number will win.
- There's nothing, so I win.
- What is this?
- What kind of bullshit is this?!
- There was only one rule.
Didn't you say the person with the lowest number would win?
You wouldn't go back on your word,  now would you?
Strip. Your underwear as well.
Ah, this is something you couldn't see even if you paid for it.
But you should have just drunk. You should not have started to bet people on the line.
Isn't this against the nation's law?
Your Highness, Prince Yeoning.
It's you again?
Ah, do you know who I am?
You dig around me behind my back like a rat,
so how could I not possibly know you?
Lee In Jwa.
Ah, was there another fate like this?  (What a coincidence)
Because of a single rat that has been digging around the gambling den recently,
I too have been getting severe headaches trying to find it.
Your Highness, what should we do now?
While Your Highness was gambling away,
it so happened that the Chief of Investigation
was present here as well.
Please forgive my interruption.
If you're done drinking, come out now!
Yes, Sir!
Move!
You dare to arrest me?
With my little power, how could I arrest you, Your Highness?
But these people, who have broken the nation's law,
will not be able to escape their punishment.
No matter how strict the nation's law is,
I was just enjoying myself a bit,
so I'm sure you can overlook this incident just once.
If I had not seen it with my own eyes, I might have.
But I'm deeply sorry, Your Highness.
WAIT!
L-Look here. This lady has done nothing wrong.
- Done nothing wrong?
- Yes, Sir.
I was the one who made the bet,
and I am the one who caused a ruckus by taking my clothes off.
So how could you say that that lady has committed any wrong?
You're being rude!
Regardless of gender or age or status,
it is the nation's strict law to punish everyone who participates in this type of gambling!
Then if that's the case, the punishment that that lady would receive,
I will accept it instead.
Do you not even know that even a strong and healthy man can become maimed or even die from 30 lashes?
I don't care.
Is that so?
Then I will fulfill your foolish wish.
Take him away.
Why didn't you
inform me you were going to do this?
If I had informed you, what difference would it have made?
Because of me, an innocent man is about to be punished.
Then that must be that man's fate.
You. Come see me.
Did this event take place because of me?
That was not planned to harm you, Your Highness.
I'm not sure whether you mind someone else's business too much in believing my hyungnim (Crown Prince) is backing you up.
I just wanted to see if the rumors that were going around were true.
The rumor that during the day, you're an alcoholic, and during the night, you are a playboy.
And so, you have no interest or ambition in politics.
And? Were you able to confirm it?
It seems it is raining.
Before it becomes a heavy downfall, you should get going.
So what did you see?
He is a tiger.
And on top of all that, there's not just one tiger, but two.
I was also quite surprised.
I never thought there would be a person who had the same physiognomy as yours, My Lord.
It can't be... You're saying that person has the traitor's features as I do?
Twenty eight!
I'm Gae Ttong! I won't die!
Twenty nine!
I SAID I'M GAE TTONG!
Thirty!
Aigoo, I thought you abandoned me.
Dam Seo.
Huh?
That's my name.
Ah, Dam Seo? Well this must be fate—
What are you doing?
Aigoo, just take it!
Since I'm healthy, I don't need things like that. Watch.
Are you an idiot?
Why would you carelessly mistreat your body like that?
Did you think someone would acknowledge you for doing that?
Well no... I was just...
No matter how hard you try, no one will recognize you.
You will just be a person who will never escape being poor.
You have a lowly life like that.
I!
I just need one person to acknowledge me.
Just one person. And that is the woman who will be my bride.
Hey what happened to your bottom? Were you beaten with a cudgel someplace else?
Why, this little brat must have caused trouble again as soon as we got to Hanyang!
Hey, you! Why are you acting like this?
H-hey, G-Gae Ttong!
Gae Ttong!
Father! Why am I Gae Ttong?
Just come out here!
I'm asking you why I am Gae Ttong.
You said I was a noble.
So why?
So why? Out of all the chances in heaven, why did I come out worse than a beggar?
Just why?!
Crown Prince Yoon (later Gyeongjong, King of Joseon)
Bull's eye!
How have you been, Your Highness?
I...
have been well all thanks to you. But why have you come here today?
Today I came to see His Majesty and  to lessen your worry.
You want to see His Majesty?
Yes, but for now, Your Highness just needs to shoot some arrows with me.
King.
Sookjong
He is my baduk teacher.
A baduk teacher you say...
My name is Lee In Jwa.
Your Majesty. May I dare to request a baduk game with you?
You want a baduk game with me?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'll let you have a 10-stone advantage.
10 stones?
I think you really have something you wish to tell me about.
You have no fear.
You're sitting in front of  the King of this country
and yet you seem to have no fear and seem dignified.
It's almost as if you are becoming the King.
You speak highly of me. How could I ever dream of that?
The previous General of Training,  Lee Heun Jin, and the Left Prime Minister Lee Won Jin,
were your grandparents, right?
What? Did you really think that I would not know that?
Being a baduk teacher is a good disguise. But the truth is, you're planning to hide behind the weak Crown Prince
and govern everything yourself, right?
How could I ever possibly do such a thing? You speak too highly of me, Your Majesty.
Do you resent me?
Actually. Do you want to kill me?
Because I am the man who ruined your family.
Me.
Your Majesty, the ones who were blinded by greed, and the ones who were involved in the factional war,
how could you not have taken those measures against those officials?
I do not resent you.
The three Changes of State spanning Gyeongshin Year (1680), Gisa Year (1689) and Gapsul Year (1694).
That was the result of your great decision for the people of Joseon, Your Majesty.
Raise your head.
You really mean it.
Your eyes tell me you really meant it.
So what is your reason for using the baduk teacher disguise to see me?
Your Majesty. I'm sure you already know the answer to your question.
What is your reason for being so hesitant?
I am here to tell you
about regency.
Let me hear your reasons.
If we have the Crown Prince govern, the Norons  ("Old Learning," one of the two political factions in the court)  will be against that,
but if we don't do that, the Sorons  ("New Learning," the other of the two political factions in the Court)  will also not be pleased.
But Your Majesty, it is said that no one can stop water with just their bare hands,
and therefore, no one can stop a flowing river.
The decision to let the Crown Prince govern is just like the flow and current of the river.  (meaning it is bound to happen)
So, why are you worrying unnecessarily about this decision?
Worrying unnecessarily?
Is that so? Then it's quite an easy decision.
But you.
Do you know of a 100-eyed, 1000-eared monster?
Are you talking about a monster that rains blood and eats human flesh?
So you do know. Do you perhaps
wish to become that monster?
You speak too highly, Your Majesty.
I just wish to be the Crown Prince's baduk teacher, no more no less.
That is all I want.
Is that so?
Then that means you will have no interest in politics.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How could a person like me ever wish to participate in politics?
How did it go?
Do you know of a 100-eyed and 1000-eared
monster?
Huh?
Even though I may have no interest in politics
I do have an interest in that throne.
Just you wait. One day, I will definitely
take that throne from you.
How long are you going to live like that? Every day, all you do is drink, play with women, play tujeon, and even fist-fight!
As a descendant of the King, are you not embarrassed? How could you be such a hooligan—
Yes! I am a hooligan!
So what if I am a hooligan? So what if I am a playboy?
If I live like this or that, what difference does it make?
Royal Mother should also stop caring for me now!
Royal Mother!
For now, learn to be more respectful and careful. That is the punishment I am giving to you as a mother.
Royal Mother. Was that good enough? Would that do?
Lady Sook Bin Choi
You did well. You endured it very well.
Please endure it over and over again. You have to survive this in order to benefit.
You must survive if you wish to inherit the throne.
It seems the once-lowly water maid is sitting on the top of power now.
This is all thanks to you, My Lord.
Wait. How were you able to gather that much?
Father! What is all this?
What do you mean, "What is this?" That's the money we're going to use to make you a noble.
N-Noble?
What are you doing, brat? Hurry and take off your clothes!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
H-H-Hot!
If you do this, it will cool down a bit.
Sheesh, making such a big deal out of this.
What are you complaining for? What? Are you embarrassed?
This is nothing to be embarrassed about when it's between father and son!
I said I'll do this by myself.
You brat. It won't be enough to spend a whole night cleaning your 20-year-old dirt. Hurry and take it off!
Woah! Woah!
Why are you doing this?
You're as big as a cow, but you're such a crybaby.
Aigoo.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Come over here!
- I told you before to not hit my butt!
- Come here!
- I'm going to splash you with water if you come any closer!
I'm going to splash it!
Do I look good?
Here, turn around a bit!
My back side? How is it?
Wow! You look nice! Here, turn around again!
How is it?
The clothes you have will be wasted with that face.
Aish! What are you saying? Look at this face!
Hey, turn around! Turn around!
Father.
If you're a noble, don't you have a noble name?
A noble name?
Of course you do. It's in the family registry.
Family registry?
What's the point having lots of customers?  They're meaningless  (as all the profit will go to Lee In Jwa).
He isn't my husband. How am I seeing things?
This place is the same as usual.
And you're also the same as usual.
Is this really you, Orabeoni?  (older brother)
I don't have a sweet relationship with Orabeoni like this. So what's the matter?
After making some money, and sleeping in warm places...
Get to the point.
There is one thing that's been on my mind still.
The family registry.
Isn't a noble's family registry practically money?
No! I said you can't have the family registry!
Hold still!
No! I said you can't have that!
So what's the point of coming back now to look for it?
It's for a child. My child.
Wow. For that newborn baby? Well, too bad. The family registry isn't here anymore.
Actually, Orabeoni. Do you have 300 nyangs?
If you can pay me that, I have ways of getting it back.
Family Registry
Family Registry? Could this be the family registry?
It is the family registry! The registry!
From now on, your name will be Dae Gil.
Baek Dae Gil!
The 13th generation in the Nampo Baek clan, Baek Dae Gil!
Dae Gil? Baek Dae Gil?
I am no longer Gae Ttong.
I'm a noble! A noble I say!
I'm a noble now!
Dae Gil! He is the 13th generation in the Nampo Baek clan, Baek Dae Gil!
Sook Bin's child?
That Gae Ttong is Baek Man Geum's child?
Yes! He even came back to buy back the family registry.
Fate is quite a hard thing to predict.
Are you there, Dam Seo?
Tonight, with one man's death, we will start the first step of our plans.
Dam Seo, you personally instigate the plan.
My Lord! Would you accept my drink?
You'll give me a drink?
Oh wait, My Lord!
My Lord. Your name... You don't seem you have your name as Gae Ttong...
- I'm Baek Dae Gil.
- Alright!
Baek Dae Gil! He's Baek Dae Gil!
My Lord! Which generation of Nampo Baek clan are you from?
The... The...
Actually, I totally forgot it!
You are the 13th generation!
You are the 13th generation of Nampo Baek clan, Baek Dae Gil!
My Lord! Haha!
- Hey look.
- Man, the moon is so bright.
It seems our orabeoni will easily find the way to go to the afterlife.
Why are you here at this hour, Sister?
I do feel bad telling you this when you address me as Sister,
but don't be too upset with me. I'll even bury you in a sunny place.
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?
Well anyway, today is a good day,
so stop dawdling around here and just go home.
I do feel a little bad about this. Oh, what should I do?
On a great day like this,
do you really want to feel the fury of this noble, Dae Gil's fists?
Dae Gil!
Hey, kid, next time don't interfere.
Since you were the one who drew the blade first,
don't resent me, okay?
Noonim! Aigoo, Noonim!
Let's leave Hanyang!
There is nothing more for us to do here! Let's go!
You must not kill Baek Dae Gil.
He talks sh*t. You're telling me to hold it in when I've been attacked like this? Huh?!
Hey, get your weapons ready! I'm going to end this all today!
Which way did they go?
That way! T-That w-way!
Are you alright? Gae Ttong!
Are you okay?
Of course I'm alright. Do you think I'll die like  this?
If I die like this, I am not your son.
That's right. You just need to survive. You can do anything as long as you survive.
Gae Ttong, let's go.
Stop wasting your time talking, and let's move!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go!
- There's a boat over there!
Get in the boat quickly. Hurry!
Push it!
Let's go, let's go!
Shoot them.
But—
Why are you hesitating?
During your time here, did you fall in love with that man?
That's not it.
Anyway, you are this Gae Ttong's bride, so don't think otherwise.
I!
I just need one person who will acknowledge me.
Just one person, the woman who will be my bride.
Teacher, I—
Hurry and row!
One day, I will take your child from you.
Gae Ttong...
Gae Ttong? I am Dae Gil. Baek Dae  Gil.
How many times do I have to tell you?
What are you doing?
Father, Father!
Man Geum!
Father! Father!
How could this happen? What happened?
Orabeoni!
Gae Ttong, from now on, listen to me carefully.
Listen to what?! Get in!
First, get in the boat! Hurry!
- Hurry!
- You bastard!
This is the last time, so listen to me carefully.
No, this isn't the last time! You aren't going to die. I said you're not going to die!
If you don't want to end up like me, don't gamble,
and move away to some faraway countryside,
and don't even think about taking revenge, and just...
and just live your life, okay? Now just go.
-Got it?
- NO! I'm going to live with you!
Until I die, I will live with you!
Get in! GET IN!
- Get those bastards!
- Orabeoni!
Stop right there!
Elder...
Man Geum!
Stop right there! Right there!
Stop! Catch them!
ELDER!
GO!
Timing and Subtitling by the Totally Awesome Team @ Viki.com
Gae Ttong... I mean Dae Gil...
You are my son.
No matter what anyone says, you are my son.
You are Baek Man Geum's son, Dae Gil...
♫  Longing for you even if the tears well up  ♫
♫  I will withstand you. Even if my heart fills up more  ♫
♫  Because the words which have not yet been said  remain  ♫
♫  Because I cannot live  ♫
Jackpot
♫  a time without you  ♫
Why did it have to be his father?!
There is nothing else to make someone stronger than hatred does.
Don't look for me.
You little bastard! At least you need to be alive.
Where's the bastard who killed my father?
Are you just itching to die?!
Last night, I heard that our Prince Yeoning brought in a man who was half-dead.
What is the identity of this maiden?
Don't misunderstand this. You are not my style.
Just stop at this point.
I am saying you should just live a normal life.
I will give you a chance.  Now shoot.
Shut up! I don't need your petty advice!