Episode 7
Thankfully, the Crown Prince has accepted the regency,
and it went as we planned.
But it is still hard to read his (the King's) thoughts.
If we don't know the King's thoughts, we can just change them.
Changing the King's mind?
Even so, if we can't change the King's mind,
what will you do then?
If that's the case, then we must change the owner of that mind.
Heaven's will is determined by the people.
Are you going to change the king?
Your Highness, do you know the precepts of Mencius?
- What did you say?
- The monarchs are the boat, and the people are the water.
It is ultimately the water's decision to either flip or sink the boat,
so it's okay for iniquitous (bad) monarchs to be killed.
We were merely discussing the precepts of Mencius.
I definitely heard you say—
Was it a coincidence that you were involved
in the personal discussions of the Ministers or ...
have you been spying on us?
Since I think Your Highness has misunderstood, why don't you join us?
Do it in moderation.  Your acts seem risky in my eyes.
Your Highness, are you really just going to leave them alone like this?
It's not the right time yet.
I need to find strong evidence that can lock those people up.
Evidence.
Do you really not know how bold and shameless that Lee In Jwa is?
Have I not told you all this time  to not associate yourself with that man?
Did what I said mean nothing to you?
Royal Mother.
That man is planning to hide behind the Crown Prince and control the King and the court.
And he even kills people for his own personal interests.
He killed people?
I don't have any evidence, nor do I know why he did so,
but it seems he has killed a gambler named Baek Man Geum.
If it's the gambler,
Baek Man Geum...
Do you know him?
No.
How would I know him?
Please be careful.
Catching Lee In Jwa will not be easy.
Besides the chief officer at the Left Branch Police Bureau, there are 12 police officers
and 20 prosecutors under the chief prosecutor at the Bureau of Prosecution.
And also a total of 10 inspectors including the chief at the Bureau of Inspection.
Keep this in mind.
It is the duty of the Office of Inspection to catch any traitors.
Tonight, Lee In Jwa definitely has to be captured. Do you understand?
Yes, Your Highness!
The proof has been shown, and you bet your hand, right?
Owner, what are you doing? Hurry up and cut this man's hand off.
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME?!
Aigoo... What should I do now?
What's so difficult about cutting someone's hand off?
Hey noble, I am Demon, an actual demon.
Remember that well.
Baek Dae Gil...
What are you doing? CUT IT OFF!
Cut it off! Cut it off!
What the...?
This wench. What do you want?
Hold on a moment.
You were just a kid who didn’t know the difference between water and fire.
I am surprised at how fast you’ve grown up.
But I am also quite disappointed.
Even till this day, I've never used any underhanded methods.
So I dislike anyone who uses any underhanded methods or swindles.
So I cannot forgive whomever ruins a game through tricks.
But that tag came from your sleeve!
When you grabbed my collar,
you probably secretly slipped it into my sleeve then.
But it's also my fault for not noticing your gimmicks.
So I will forgive you this time.
They say the person who farts is the one who blames.
And now a person who swindled is the one who forgives?
It seems you still don't understand.
Then, I will prove it to you.
Owner Hong.
Blindfold me.
What is he trying to do?
The 10-point tag. If you're that confident, draw that one.
What? What the heck?
He really drew the 10-point tag.
Do it again.
The 1-point tag.
So you want the 1-point tag...
What do you think this tag is?
Stop speaking nonsense, and hurry up and reveal that tag!
What? Seriously?
Is he a ghost or something?
Is this proof enough?
What? How the heck did he do that?
How did you do that?!
If you're curious, you figure it out yourself.
You came quite close this time.
You came close to the truth you desired, by luckily being able to choose the nine.
What are you doing? CUT IT OFF!
And even using methods which aren't like you,
you cornered me into a difficult predicament.
But if your final blow had been stronger, you could have caught me.
But it seems your luck and skill could only bring you this far.
In the end, you won't be able to find out the reason behind your father's death.
Lee In Jwa.  It's not over yet.
Did you forget?  We have an agreement.
With a messed up body like this, if I fall down from that cliff I will die for sure.
If I survive, I'll take it that you'll grant my wish.
The promise that I will go ask for forgiveness at Baek Man Geum's tomb.
What will you do if I don't do it?
You've been acting almighty and awesome by yourself,
but in the end you're also just a cunning person?
Are you hypocritical chaff junk?!
Still, I wanted to save you.
What nonsense is that?
If I really intended to kill you, I would not have stabbed you here but here.
Or I would have slit your throat.
You survived not because you were lucky, but because I let you live, you punk.
No matter how much you show your claws, a tiger's cub is just a cub and not a tiger.
Just a tiger cub who can't even cope with the teeth of a hungry jackal.
Stop right there!
Darn it. Who is that now?
I'm sorry for spoiling the party,
but you guys would refuse someone dying but won't refuse someone joining the game.
Lee In Jwa.
Isn't this something you've seen many times?
What are you doing? Arrest these men this instant!
Yes!
- Let's go.
- Protect him!
Sister! Sister, this way. Move aside!
Go out!
Arrest everyone without missing anyone!
I said go out!
Father, did I lose?
Did I lose again?
Lee In Jwa!
Let go!
Let that guy go.
What about you?
Don't worry.
Let's leave for now. Hurry!
Let them be.
Take that away.
It will only take a while.
Don't act like you worry about me.
For calling the man who killed my father your teacher, Dam Seo, you're just the same beast.
That's right. I must be that kind of person to you.
I'm sorry.
I take it back. I take back saying that I'd take you for my wife.
I've marked this lady to be my wife from today on.
Anyway, you're this Gae Ttong's wife, so don't have any other thoughts.
Even if I should die, even if you come after me with a sword, I will do it.
Whether it's 100 or 1000 tries, I'm going to stand up against Lee In Jwa again.
So don't think about stopping me.
At least say something.
Your Highness, no matter how much evidence you have,
things won't work out as you wish.
Illegal gambling, taking lands, cornering and hoarding salt, ginseng and water buffalo horns  (used for bows).
Even with the list I just mentioned, you will face a death sentence. Why?
Will you feel relief after I investigate the death of Baek Dae Gil's father as well?
You probably should slay me with a sword right now.
Right now is the only chance for you to kill me.
Fine, wait here for a moment.
I will punish your disgusting mouth with the righteous laws.
You survived not because you were lucky, but because I let you live, you punk.
No matter how much claw you show, a cub is just a cub, not a tiger.
You are just a mere cub that cannot even cope with the teeth of a hungry jackal.
Dear God who controls Joseon from the south to the north,
if our Dae Gil has died, please let him accept this food.
And if he is alive, please take good care of him.
Take care of me, my ass. I just came back from death.
This old man is now hearing things.
No way, who are you?
It's you, Dae Gil!
Dae Gil, Dae Gil!
You came back alive. Let me take a look.
Let me look.
Let's see if you've lost any teeth.
Aigo, my face is going to wear out, stop touching it.
Is getting worn out the problem? Let me take a look.
Come here.
Here, eat quickly. It was made for your memorial food anyway.
Since you have come back, everything is yours. Enjoy it.
Grandpa... Dad's enemy... I wanted to get revenge.
I really wanted to get revenge, but...
It's okay, you've done enough. Your father won't want much more either.
No... It is not because of Father, but now I cannot endure it myself.
I... I want to overcome that guy.
I'm really gonna die!
Stop!
Your Highness, what brings you here?
I came to see if the investigation was going well.
How come there are only these people?  Where is Lee In Jwa?
Who?
These guys' leader, Lee In Jwa.
That man must be in the Royal Investigation Bureau.
The  Royal Investigation Bureau?  Why is only that man in the  Royal Investigation Bureau?
I'm not sure. Well, for that,
don't you think the prosecutors would know?
Sir!
Let all of these guys go!
Yes!
Timing and Subtitling by the Totally Awesome Team @ Viki.com
The prosecutors have forgiven their crimes.
So we no longer have any power over this situation.
He's not here either?
It is true that he was sent here, the Royal Investigation Bureau, to investigate the truth of the ledger book.
But as soon as the ledger book was confirmed, the Inspector General took him personally.
What do you mean the Inspector General? You mean from the Bureau of Inspection?
Your Highness, you belong to the Bureau of Inspection but you did not know that?
Why did the Inspector General do that? Why on earth?
The ledger book. Where is the ledger book?
As you can see, all these are fabricated ledger books.
Revenue and Expenditure Account Book
There is not one single true record.
The ledger books and information in them are all fake,
and the people that were listed as receiving bribes
from Lee In Jwa, all their names and positions were all fake.
This just means that this is fake.
Lord, how could you share drinks with a criminal?
Criminal?
Your Highness, who are you saying is  a criminal?
Lord!
You should sit as well, there seems to have been some misunderstandings.
Right Branch Police Chief!
Your Highness, I heard that you made a big mistake today.
A mistake?
Are you saying arresting that man was a mistake?
Isn't that right?
First of all, you arrested an innocent man without any evidence.
Second, you neglected your duty at the Bureau of Inspection, where you are supposed to keep your eyes on the corruption of the officials,
and seized a gambling place that has nothing to do with your duty.
Third, you exceeded your authority by giving the police and the prosecutors orders for personal matters.
I am not sure how big, but there'll be quite a commotion in the royal court due to this matter tomorrow.
Right Branch Police Chief! What did you just say?
Your Highness, perhaps you took action after receiving  approval from the crown prince?
Huh, you arrested the crown prince's teacher without evidence, but you didn't even say a word to him?
Hmm... that is...
He seems to have a lot he wants to say to me,
so will the two of you step outside for a moment?
Let's do that.
How much did you really give to those guys?
First of all, calm your anger and take one glass.
Your evil influence, how far has it spread? Where's the root of it!?
Where the heck is it?
Do you really think that I am the root of the evil influences?
He's acting up fearlessly when he is just the son of a mere water maid.
He doesn't know how things work. It just shows that he couldn't shake his lowly origin, just like an ox that is set free.
That is why I kept his leash tightly tied to the Bureau of Inspection.
Keep this in your mind, Your Highness. No matter how smart you are,
the truth is that you cannot do politics alone.
On top of that, your origin is...
Stop there!
You were talking about the righteous national law, but end up wielding a sword?
That is also not much different from the king.
What did you say?
Well then, try slaying me.
I will stay right here.
I can see it in my eyes.
You'll slay me, slay the Sorons (New Learning faction), slay the crown prince.
In  the end, isn't it that you want to sit on the throne?
Shut up!
I will take my leave now, Your Highness Prince Yeoning.
What did you say? Kick out Lee In Jwa?
When it's not even enough even if you ask for forgiveness, but you are asking an absurd...
Your Highness, how much do you really know?
What are you talking about?
What kind of man he is, what kind of ambition he has, and what his goals are
and how far he has spread his roots in this royal court.
Do you know about it?
That man Lee In Jwa is—
- That man Lee In Jwa is my friend.
What more do I have to know?
I will definitely protect you, My Prince.
You are?
Yes, My Prince.
However, if I save you from the pit, what will you give me?
I will give you everything.
If you save me, I will give you everything I have.
Even... Even... Even if that is the throne, I'll give it to you.
You have to sit on the throne.
I'll just take your considerations.
That man Lee In Jwa is my right hand, left hand and a man who has hold of my heart.
I will not regard your mistake today as an issue.
Hence, no matter what Lee In Jwa does,
feign ignorance and let it pass.
That is for my sake.
and for the sake of the royal court
and for the sake of this nation, Joseon.
I mean it is not your concern, Prince Yeoning.
Is there nothing
that I can do?
Despite being a prince of the nation,
indeed there is not a thing
I can do of my own accord?
Indeed?
King Sookjong
Are you crying?
So you are finally growing some sense.
Are you unharmed?
What became of it?
Baek Dae Gil, right after the ruckus, returned home.
That bastard Ban Poon, we need to get him.
Demon and the minions from the salt field as well.
They returned to Ganghwa Island upon release from the police bureau.
The gambling den as well.  Tomorrow they will open as a normal business.
I feel fatigue.  You should go and rest as well.
Yes, Teacher.
Moo Myeong.
Keep watch over Baek Dae Gil.
Whom he meets where, and what he does.
Every little detail.
What became of that child?
I wonder.
By that child, do you mean, Yeong Soo?
Prince Yeoning said Baek Man Geum, the father who raised that child,
died at the hands of Lee In Jwa.
If that is the truth...
My Lord.
Sit.
Tell me what happened to Prince Yeoning today.
I'll keep this a secret.
And you must do so as well.
He ran a sweep at the gambling den and successfully captured Lee In Jwa.
But the Police Bureau, the Royal Investigation Bureau and Office of the Inspector General  colluded as one.
And in the end, he was released.
Hence he is in His Majesty's audience, crying?
The unfairness and the infuriation?
According to Prince Yeoning, the gambler named Baek Man Geum
was killed at the hands of Lee In Jwa.
Do you know the story behind it?
Though Baek Man Geum's corpse hasn't been discovered,
a man who is his child kept going against Lee In Jwa in the name of revenge.
His child, did you say?
Yes, a man named Baek Dae Gil.
However, why do you...
Baek Dae Gil.
You were alive, child.
He got it right at one go?
How did he do it?
You think you know something but you don't.
A visible sign is something that novices use.
Then...
Can't be...  The weight is different?
Weight?
See.
Look. These gambling tags.
They are made with dozens of thin paper sheets.
They are hardened with a brush of oil.
Now, depending on how many more or less thin sheets were used,
the weight could change.
But it would still be only a difference of one sheet of paper. How can he know that tiny difference?
That's not an act a human can commit.
White-Faced Scholar, Lee In Jwa.
You should know too since you saw him.
His gaze isn't that of a human.
Never in my life even until now have I ever used a trick.
Lee In Jwa?
Grandpa, how do you know the name of the White-Faced Scholar?
Lee In Jwa? I don't know him.
You better speak now.
Alright, I got it.
There are ill fates in my life.
The first ill fate is the one that snatched away my eye.
The second ill fate is the White-Faced Scholar. Lee In Jwa.
In the eight provinces of Joseon,
he is a gambling master among gambling masters, ranking in the top five.
At the time I was known as Namsan Goblin
with quite some fame as well.
But somehow before him, I could never garner any power.
So why did he kill my father?
What was the reason?
I don't know the details of that either.
However, one thing is for certain.
It's that on that day, he said something strange to Man Geum.
Bear that in mind. Once that child is fully grown,
I will take your life away.
But why haven't you told me all this time?
Because I was worried about you.
In order to save you, I've kept my mouth tightly shut about it.
Grandpa, listen clearly to what I'm about to tell you.
I am going to get stronger.
White-Faced Scholar.  I will become twice as strong as him and return.
Alright.  You are a rascal who even defied death.
You will do well.
Don't skip any meals, Kid!
Dae (big) Bak (ship) =  Jackpot
Jackpot!
The rascal is going on his path!
Timing and Subtitling by the Totally Awesome Team @ Viki.com
No matter how you show your claws, a tiger cub is still a tiger cub and not a tiger.
Just a tiger cub who can't even cope with the teeth of a hungry jackal.
So did you find out?
He is Hwang Jin Gi, who once served as military officer of the Bureau of Declaration. In martial skills, he is tops by far.
As you know, he was deemed a traitor, and is currently locked up in  the  Royal Investigation Bureau.
Indeed, he would be a perfect choice as your underling.
Furthermore, this man
also shares an ill fate with the king's sword.
What is it?
I, Baek Dae Gil, who was supposed to be Joseon's best gambling master,
shall serve you as my teacher starting today,.
Why would a guy who wanted to be a gambling master serve me as his teacher?
You've got the wrong guy. You should go back now.
Today, I will die.
Why should I care whether you die or not?
You should care.  Because I'm about to become your disciple.
Why, you rascal! Listen to what you're saying—
Your only disciple is going to go die now.
It's up to you, Master, to let him die or live.
What a lame fellow.
Tonight is the last chance.  The last chance to leave this place.
Let's go.  How long will you live like this?
I'll block them so you guys run away together without looking back no  matter what.
You... why are you doing this?
You should go back to your hometown.
What are you guys doing?
Ban Poon, I'm grinding my teeth whenever I think about the lashings I got because of you.
You came on your own feet.
What are you waiting for? Get them.
Yes, Sir.
What are you doing?  You're not going to open the door?  How long will you live like this?
What are you waiting for, you idiots!  They're all getting away.
Get him!
After them!
Ban Poon, did you have a good sleep?
Dae Gil.
What?
It's not Ban Poon.  It's Dae Gil.  My name.
Alright, Bae Dae Gil.
But doing when ordered to do, scarfing down when given food,  barking when told to bark, biting when told to bite.
That's how they're supposed to live. Who are you to take over their lives?
Huh? Do you own this country?
What about you? Why do you treat people like animals? A mere thing like you.
That is the order of the world.
Ones who lack get stepped on. Ones who have more get to do the stepping.
You know that?  They're all going to croak because of you.
Because of you, those guys will all get captured and die.
Caught one so soon?
Seol Im.
What happened to you?  I'm sorry.
What?  This bastard Ban Poon haunts you so you couldn't run far?
Bring the sickle.
Stop.
What? Can't watch?
You...  you're going to die by my hand.
The bastard.
The nerve you have!  What do you have to rely on for you to be so full of yourself?
Alright, we'll find out soon whether you die or I do.
Watch it well.  This wench here,
she dies because of you. Got that?
Help me!
Help me, please. Help me, please.
This grace, I will, with the rest of my life, repay you a hundred, a thousand times.
So don't just watch and help me! Help me!
This bastard's really gone nuts.
Watch.  Seol Im, this is all self-inflicted.
Understand?
What the?
I'm a little busy.  Come all at once.
That bastard's eaten something wrong.
What are you waiting for, you goons?
You came to my house on purpose, right? So I'd come here.
Don't be so impertinent.
Get him.
Look.  These vermin.
They will not be eradicated just because you step up alone.
No, I'm not alone.
What the?  These bastards.
Go!
Even a worm will squirm if you step on it.
Even a mouse, when cornered, will bite the cat.
Much less the people.
Look! Do you know what this is?
The wench has gone crazy.  Put that down or else!
Slave Contract
- Kim Bok Ttol.
- Here!
Grandpa, go back to your home to see Grandma now.
Crazy...
- Kim Gan Nan.
- Yes.
- Park Se Hong.
- Here.
- Jang Chang Yong.
-That's me.
- Go Gap Soe.
- Right here.
- Lee Gil Beom.
- That's me, me!
- Yoo Soon Jin.
- That's me, though.
Gye Seol Im Slave Contract
Born on Year of Gap-oh, Month 2, Day 3 with healthy body.
Seol Im. Gye Seol Im.
That...
Watch.
We are now free.  Free.
The wench wants to croak.
Hey.
You are all crazy.
Crazy.
Now we should go back to our home towns.
To our home towns.
Home town!
We're going back. We are.
♬    How many tears must I shed    ♬
♬   How much more must I ache     ♬
♬   Will I be able to forget you and erase you    ♬
♬    I will turn my back at time   ♬
♬    so I can't see you     ♬
♬    so my foolish heart can forget you   ♬
♬   My heart can'd forget you distant heart  ♬
♬   Like a fool approahcing my heart    ♬
♬   Even if I weep soundlessly   ♬
Let's meet again for sure.
For sure.
♬   I miss you, miss you, more so today than yesterday     ♬
♬   I miss you, oh my love     ♬
♬   I miss you, more so today    ♬
You said you wanted to be my disciple, right?
Follow me.
Kim Che Geon?
That king's sword you spoke of must be Kim Che Geon then.
It's getting interesting.
How's Prince Yeoning?
He's immersed in collecting information.
Every little thing related to you, Teacher.
Is this all the information on Lee In Jwa?
Yes, other than the census registry at Hanseongbu  (today's Seoul) , the information here is everything.
But why all this...
Because I need to know
what kind of a person the prey I plan to hunt really is.
Where he was born, who his father is, whether he has a wife and kids.
I must know everything about him.
Only thus can I catch him.
Lose the fat first.  Here, here, and here.
Losing is losing but shouldn't I get a bite first?
Shouldn't I?
From now on, say "master" and with respect. Got that?
Yeah.
Still?
You guys messed with the wrong man.
Aigoo. I should've just looked on other people's trouble indifferently as if it's fire on a far-away mountain.
I'm Demon.
Demon that eats people.
What? Bastard.
Hurry and drop me down.
You said you're a demon that eats people.
Your friend is here, so you two have a good time.
What?
Wow, he's really mad I think.
Why?
Because of you the female died!
The one and only female within hundreds of miles died, so he must be so pissed. Don't you think?
Let me down, you bastards!
Let me down!
♬  Will I be able to see time stop then?  ♬
♬  Will your heart be with me then?  ♬
♬  Longing for you even if the tears well up  ♬
Jackpot
♬  I will withstand you. ♬
Forget capturing any beasts with that skill of yours, you'll lose your limbs first.
Lee In Jwa.
How about it?  We battle for life or death today.
Don't you see the people's bloody pus and bloody tears?
Forgive me.
Grant me permission, Teacher.
Are you ready?
You are Lee In Jwa?
You will have a lot to do soon.
I am aware of Your Ladyship Consort Sook Bin's past as well.
- You wench!
- Help me get an audience with His Majesty.
The king you serve deserves death.
Why do you cast such a heavy mission upon your son?
What exactly is your identity, Master? You're a traitor?
I plan to kill the king.