Episode 18
Royal Father.
Royal Father!
Royal Father!!
Where are you going?
Now I have to do what I need to do. Call Yeon Hwa please.
I have something to say when we're all together.
Understood.
Prince Yeoning, future King Yeongjo
Your Majesty. Royal Father!
Royal Father. Royal Father.
Your Majesty.
Please open your eyes!
(King Sookjong)
Your Majesty.
(Crown Prince Yoon, future King Gyeongjong)
Please get up, Royal Father.
(Prince Yeonryeong, Yi Hwon, King Sookjong's sixth son)
Kim Che Geon
Royal Father.
Father.
Stay back.
It's you, Father, right?
I told you to stay away.
Father, what happened to you?
How did you come back alive?
Though things may look like this, I'm still your father.
Your father... Your father is very sorry.
So very sorry.
Is saying sorry all? How could you show yourself now, when you've been alive this whole time?
I thought you had died. Do you know how hard I searched for you?
Tell me. Why did you pretend to be dead?
What is the cause?
Though his pulse is weak, his heart is still beating. Though it's shallow, his breathing is stable,
and his temperature is normal too.
The cause. I am asking you the cause
for His Majesty, who was completely healthy up until last night—the reason he suddenly collapsed.
T-T-Though I am not... certain,
it is the opium incense.
Incense.
Yes.
Because it's made from the opium poppy, it dulls pain.
Its poisonous properties are potent, so I cautioned him not to burn it often.
Are you saying you prescribed opium to His Majesty?
Y-Yes.
But how is it that no one knew of that fact?
Y-yes. H-His Majesty
commanded it should be kept an absolute secret...
- Your Highness.
How is his majesty's health?
(Prime Minister Kim Chang Jip)
Fortunately, he seems to have passed the critical stage.
It is truly fortunate.
Choi Yi Seok, Jo Il Soo,  Kim Il Gyeong
Then I will see you again.
Your Highness.
Is this all?
Yes, Your Highness
Of these, which incense has opium mixed in?
Can this incense make it possible to lose consciousness?
The poppy flower has potent poisonous properties. If one is not careful, it is possible to lose one's life.
Then why in the world
was opium prescribed for His Majesty?
For the last two years, His Majesty has been suffering from pain due to a gallstone.
At times he would vomit blood too.
Royal Father
has been suffering without letting it be known?
Deceiving the Crown Prince, me, and all the court ministers of all ranks?
How is this incense with poppy mixed in being supplied?
The incense used by the Royal Pharmacy is all from the Bureau of Medical Administration and Education.
But I don't know how the materials are traded there.
Have you confirmed it?
I'm asking if every single incense holder permitted into the King's sleeping quarters has been verified.
Yes it has, Your Highness.
We checked them by burning them, one by one, to confirm,
It is not possible to burn them all... I offer my sincere apologies, Your Highness.
So you made a deal with Yi In Jwa?
Father, did I ever say I wanted to be King?
I've never thought of a thing like that, and I don't want to do it either!
I just... need you, Father.
Father, stop what you're doing now and just come live with me, please?
I can't.
Why can't you?
Dae Gil, your life... from this moment on is not only yours alone.
If my life is not mine, then whose is it?
The people's.
And even my life isn't mine alone.
Why is your life not yours, Father?
What are you talking about?
You'll find out soon. It's not time yet.
Please explain in a way I can understand. Please?
Dae Gil, I'll tell you starting now, so be alert and pay careful attention to what I say.
Dae Gil.
Who is he?
Dae Gil, mark my words. Understand?
Father.
Your father will return. Until then, you know what to do, okay?
You saw Man Geum?!
What are you saying?
Your father is alive?!  Is this for real?
Man Geum! Let me see you, too.
He said we shouldn't look for him.
What do you mean, don't go look for him?
It's not time yet.
I have stuff I have to do, so you do what you need to do.
All right?
Father
has been alive.
You're saying Man Geum has been alive!
Heaven has helped him!
It's because of heaven's help he is still alive.
Man Geum!
Man... Huh?
What's matter?
The king has collapsed?
Hence, it appears I have to stay beside the King and protect him for a while.
Yi In Jwa.
It's Yi In Jwa's doing.
Do you have proof? How can a person who's in prison...
Or that traitor Jeong's doing.
Even though there is no proof, I know it.
That the King collapsed or that I almost parted from my father for good,
all of those must have happened in the palms of Yi In Jwa's hands.
Does the King's life end here?
(Yi In Jwa)
He is still a big fish even though rotten, and the tiger is still a tiger even though he lost his teeth.
His force is so strong that I can't read his fate at all.
He doesn't seem to have expired.
How did you get the news so quickly?
Because I am sharp-eared.
By the way, what order of business brings you here?
Of course, I don't like you and your comrades.
Your lucky fate that evaded thunder and cut through even the raging waves,
(Kim Il Gyeong)
I can't help but acknowledge it.
So have you changed your mind?
I'll save you.
I'll persuade His Highness the Crown Prince and get you acquitted.
What do you think of the position of Royal Secretary responsible for the Ministry of Agriculture and Commerce?
Ah. If not, then how about the Minister of Justice?
Isn't that what you want?
Are you mocking me right now?
For someone who evaded a thunderbolt
and cut through the raging waves, such as I, Yi In Jwa,
would be able to give you such a trifling position, don't you think?
If you don't like that position,
I'll put a sword in your hands.
- Sword?
- Yes.
I'll let you hold a sword in your lordship's hands.
With your hands,
how do you think you'd remove the Noron ministers?
Your Highness.
I'm worried the people will be swayed and their hearts will be agitated over this matter.
Please pardon the criminals to show them your virtue,
and stabilize the minds of the disturbed people outside of the palace.
Excuse you.
Your Highness. Including Yi In Jwa,
by punishing the traitors who plotted treason by beheading,
(Prime Minister Kim Chang Jip)
you should harden the royal resolve at a time like this.
- Excuse you.
- No, excuse YOU.
Stop.
In a situation where the King is unconscious,
how can I carry out an execution and disturb the people?
Then,
as for the traitor Yi In Jwa,
are you saying you're planning on having him released?
Let's talk privately. Now.
What is your true intention?
Your intention for opposing me?
If our father the King wakes,
how on earth are you planning to deal with the aftermath?
I am this nation's Crown Prince.
Appropriately, in place of  His Majesty,
I have a right to discuss the nation's affairs. But you!
What are you that you're on such a high horse?
Really,
do you intend... to protect the traitor Yi In Jwa?
He is not a traitor! How is that fellow a traitor?
Crown Prince,
it is because he covets the throne.
Covets the throne, you say?
Then,
can you swear that you don't covet the throne?
I see.
I should have caught on earlier.
Military authorization tag.
Your eyes when you showed that military authorization tag and threatened me!
Now I know...
who is a friend
and who is a foe.
Trample on them.
If anyone looks down on you,
never forgive them, do you understand?
You must not make mistakes like I did.
What kind of deal did you make with my father?
So you met Baek Man Geum?
I expected that.
Since I am in prison and even Royal Consort Sook has passed away,
it was time for him to show up.
So,
how does it feel to meet again the father whom you had thought was dead?
If I could,
to cut off this tiresome ill-fated connection
and go somewhere far away with my father, that's what I wanted
until a little while ago.
But,
after I saw your disgusting face,
I don't have the courage to do that anymore.
The courage to forgive you,
and to forget everything.
That's exactly it.
The reason why I can't give you up.
Your strong will.
You think you can avoid execution, don't you?
You know already of the misfortune that has befallen the King.
That was your doing, wasn't it?
Do you have proof?
Return home.
Royal Investigation Bureau
I'll get out of this prison first, then I'll look for you again.
Someone said to come here.
They say you just met your father.
I heard that the King has collapsed.
It's incense that was mixed with opium.
There were only ashes left in the jar that Father had been using.
There is no proof.
However, the bigger problem lies
with the ministers who are against sentencing Yi In Jwa.
Your Highness! Please pardon the offenses of the criminals!
Please pardon the offenses of the offenders, Your Highness!
As well as the Sorons, even among the Sungkyunkwan scholars,
they are writing petitions to free Yi In Jwa.
What should we do?
I'm ordering
the release of the offender Yi In Jwa with an acquittal also and grant his subordinates a special pardon.
Your Highness! You must not do that!
You must not do that! Crown Prince!
Crown Prince!
You must not do that!
Yi In Jwa has
been acquitted.
Your Highness.
You've suffered a lot.
Your grace is overflowing, Your Highness.
Baek Dae Gil.
What's your identity?
What in the world is your identity that you sell your name here and there?
Was it Your Highness... who released Yi In Jwa?
That sword is...
is really treasured by Father.
He has never given me such a gift.
You really look like
Prince Yeoning—
No, more like Her Highness Royal Consort Sook.
You really do look like Royal Father.
Your father is the gambler Baek Man Geum, right?
How did you know?
You probably don't know, but long ago, your father was arrested and brought to the palace.
I don't know! I said I don't know.
It was something that happened when I was quite young, so my own memory about it is a bit faded.
What is your birthday?
I don't really know.
Yi In Jwa recommended you.
He asked me to give you an official position.
I don't know the reason so I can't just give it to you.
I can no longer fully trust Yi In Jwa, who was charged as a traitor, either.
That's why, Baek Dae Gil, I want you to dig into him.
Since you are a disciple of Kim Che Geon, from this point on, I grant you the position of a commissioned cavalry officer at Capital Garrison Command.
Put this on.
If I refuse, what will happen?
Since the King is sick and bedridden, the Crown Prince's order is the same as the King's order.
Accept it since it's not such a high position.
You look cool in that uniform.
Accept this.
Commissioned Cavalry Officer?
Even though it's been a while, I was also a commissioned cavalry officer.
Even though the position is not high, you can enter and leave the palace freely.
Compared to other positions, there is less interference and more freedom of movement.
So what about it.
Since you are a military officer, you should take pride in yourself.
You little brat.
Royal Father!
Your Majesty!
Sir.
They say His Majesty the King has regained consciousness.
However, as soon as he awoke, he called for you, sire.
Your Highness. Your Highness. Your Highness.
Please wait a moment.
Before discussing the national affairs,
for the sake of stabilizing the minds of the people, the offenders will be specially pardoned,
so release Yi In Jwa and all his subordinates.
Hwon.
Please step out for a moment.
Yes, Royal Father.
You released the traitor, Yi In Jwa?
Yes, Your Majesty.
After Your Majesty had lost consciousness—
Now I'm tired of even being disappointed in you, yet again.
Get out right now.
I...
really resent you, Royal Father.
What?
Around when can I ever gain your favor?
Even after becoming the Crown Prince, and even reigning as a regent,
I have been always pushed to the back by Prince Yeoning and Prince Yeonryeong,
always taking a backseat in your heart.
Am I truly the eldest son?
Why on earth did you install me as the Crown Prince?
Your Highness Big Brother,
may I see His Majesty the Royal Father now?
Summon Kim Che Geon.
He's waiting for you.
It looks good on you.
Yi In Jwa recommended you, didn't he?
Is it possible he's trying to create an estrangement between me and Baek Dae Gil?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you a friend or a foe?
Your Highness.
Who are you?
My name is Baek Dae Gil.
Baek Dae Gil.
Can I see you privately for a moment?
You may take your leave of me now.
Are you a friend, or are you a foe?
Distrust spreads faster than anything else.
Baek Dae Gil and Prince Yeoning will soon know
who is a friend and who is a foe.
You. Have some.
There was opium in the incense, wasn't there?
He said he didn't tell because he was afraid of the responsibility.
So you knew?
- Yes.
- Your Highness.
Even though you try to take care of it by yourself without telling us,
they are not people who would fall into your hands.
Your Highness. He already plotted treason 20 years ago.
And he has controlled the royal court from behind the Crown Prince for 20 years.
If I had opened my mouth, he would have hidden his tails.
- Further since I don't have proof, so the results won't change.
- Your Highness
You are not the only one who lives in this palace.
Don't do things by yourself, seek help when you need it.
Yes.  I will do that next time.
Congratulations, Commissioned Cavalry Officer, sire
Congratulations, Sir Commissioned Cavalry Officer.
- Wow, look at the uniform. It's really cool.
- Stop it
Yi In Jwa has been set free.  Now is not the time to be celebrating.
I know.  I just wanted to make you laugh a little.
Can't you think of this as a short break after a long race?
We can capture In Jwa anytime.
Don't be too down, okay?
I'll promise, instead, that I'll make it so no one will get hurt.
Never again, not a single one of my people.
That sword of yours,
who do you raise it for?  (where does your loyalty lie?)
Only for you, Your Majesty.
Kill Yi In Jwa.
Attacking in the dark or from behind or assassinating...
Don't use such a dirty trick.
Open the front gate and confidently,
because you are me,
because you are my sword,
bring
Yi In Jwa...
that bastard's, neck!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Are you inside?
Jeong Hee Ryang
There are many who are keeping tabs on me.
You are treading on dangerous ground here.
Then I also have to express my thanks to you.
Actually, I had wished that he'd just die.
It's regrettable how things turned out.
You're not here to tell me that.
Do you really want to make that fellow Baek Dae Gil king?
If by chance you want to be king...
- I have no desire to become king.
- Then what?
I am planning on testing you.
With your outstandingly fortunate luck, you saved yourself from execution.
However, if all you have is luck,
it's a bit hard for me to become allies with you.
So?
I guess you don't know yet. The King has awakened.
I am planning on
testing your skills, using this moment. I, Jeong Hee Ryang, will do so.
What are you thinking of?
First, Baek Dae Gil.
I plan on prodding him. Second,
since the king who has awakened has no intention of letting you be,
we will see what your next move is.
The king has awakened...The king has...
Today is the anniversary of his passing, isn't it?
- Why are you here again?
-  Don't be surprised.
Today I came as Yi Soo's friend.
I have a lot of debt. I ceaselessly sprinkled blood.
When I lost comrades due to the failure of the great cause in the year of Jeongchook (1697).
Also, to those who had lost their lives
preparing for the great cause for such a long time—
Don't justify Father's death.
I can't make any justification. No matter how beautifully it is presented,
I can't lift my head confidently before your late father.
Your father, Yi Soo, and the countless other people who came together for the same cause, and died,
with their dreams and their blood and sweat,
their lives were laid down for the great cause.
Accomplishing that great cause is the only way to console the souls of those who are deceased.
Teacher, he has never once
come here to ask forgiveness.
Don't you know yet? Your teacher is still waiting.
After the great cause is accomplished, the day to apologize to your father,
he is counting the days until that time.
That's a disgusting excuse.
Please go back now.
Think back on it, how your teacher
looked at you.
Probably, to Yi In Jwa,
you were the only one.
You have to hurry.
The best swordsman in Joseon, Kim Che Geon,
will kill your teacher.
For you, I'm planning on sending a small gift.
My Liege. If the Current Crown is on the move,
isn't it wise for us to hide ourselves now?
What do you mean, "hide," when we were just cleared of all charges!
Hwang Jin Gi
Tell them to come! Whoever they are, I will defeat them with a single blow!
I feel uneasy.
Pack our things right now.
Yi In Jwa.
To implement the king's command,
I came here to take your neck.
So, he was chasing after me.
That bandit didn't even have a topknot, just a bare head with a big—
Grandpa, go inside with Seol Im.
Seol Im, come here. Hurry, hurry.
Yes. Kim Che Geon. Let's see the end today.
If you want to.
Where did Dam Seo go?
Jang Gil San
The King of a nation
is playing such a foul trick?
If you have something to say, say it to the Lord of Hell.
Dam Seo.
Think back on
how your teacher looked at you.
Probably, to Yi In Jwa,  you were the only one.
Teacher, you looked at me like this at that time, too.
Dam Seo, you are my daughter,
you are my life, and you are my everything.
That is my Great Cause
And that is my belief.
Now, I'm going to lay everything down.
Move aside.
If you want to slash my teacher, you have to slash me first.
If you don't want to waste your precious life,
quickly move aside.
Stop!
- Dam Seo.
- Baek Dae Gil.
Master.
Bring
Yi In Jwa... that bastard's neck.
NO!
Dam Seo.
With my life, once... please.
Only this time, please stop just once.
Dam Seo.
Why on earth... Why did... Why did you...
I resented you so much.
Because I thought of you as my father,
all those times, I couldn't help but hate you...
It felt so heavy.
Dam Seo.
Now,
I'm going to stop
hating you or asking for forgiveness.
No. You can't...
You can't die. You can't... Don't die.
Dae Gil.
How could I have gone around the long way?
From the beginning, I should've asked for forgiveness with my life.
Dam Seo! Dam Seo!
All right! All right!
Kill me! Kill me! KILL ME!
Salvation Pass
Are you really... going to use that to save this man?
You told me before. There are swords that kill people,
and swords that save people.
Just one time... We can at least save him one time.
Dam Seo put her life on the line to request it of you.
He's a tenacious one.
Letting this man live...
You are most definitely going to regret it later.
Dam Seo...
DAM SEO!
♬   I want to love you.  ♬
♬   Even if it's for a single day   ♬
♬   Buried in my longing    ♬
♬   You who are in my heart    ♬
♬   When I close my eyes and draw you     ♬
♬   It feels as if I can grasp you    ♬
♬   Shattered by my tears    ♬
♬   You drift away    ♬
♬  With your back fading in the distance,   ♬
♬   I won't wave goodbye     ♬
I thought I could see your smile after all of this was over, but...
♬   If we are under the same sky  ♬
♬   we will surely meet again  ♬
Dam Seo. If we could make a world where you could smile,
♬   Even if you are away from me briefly     ♬
then at that time, I thought I could see you once again...
♬   And as long as I breathe and my heart beats    ♬
I'm sorry...
♬   My heart will always     ♬
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you, Dam Seo...
♬   Be by your side     ♬
♬    Until the heavens permit  ♬
♬   me to hold you in my embrace  ♬
♬   Don't be hurt again  ♬
♬   Because I cannot wipe away your tears  ♬
♬   give me your sadness  ♬
♬   In your cozy tree leaves  ♬
♬   though I may just live full of tears  ♬
♬   Because you are that one person, even in death   ♬
♬   I want to love  ♬
Timing and Subtitling by the Totally Awesome Team @ Viki.com
Current Crown,
I won't stop
at slicing just one finger.
Who are you?
My name is Yi In Jwa.
Yi In Jwa?
Aren't you His Highness Big Brother's baduk teacher?
Yes, Your Highness.
Do you know the meaning of the Three-Jong Bloodline?
(Three-Jong Bloodline: heir of King Hyojong, Hyeonjong, Sookjong)
As of now there are only three who can ascend the throne: His Highness the Crown Prince, Prince Yeoning,
and Your Highness, Prince Yeonryeong.
So, did you come to win me over?
The prince the king holds most dear is not the Crown Prince or Prince Yeoning, it's you, Prince Yeonryeong.
What are you doing right now?
What do you think?
Would you like to have a seat on the throne?
How insolent of you!
Or do you want to turn Joseon upside down with me?
You bastard! What nonsense are you saying?!
Go back immediately! Is there anyone out there?
Your Highness,
my daughter has died
by the King's hand.
How do you feel?
Do you feel my pain a little bit?
My family has been destroyed and I've lost my friend,
along with losing my precious daughter-like disciple—
DO YOU FEEL MY PAIN AND SADNESS NOW?!
Huh, I guess you can't talk.
My Liege. If you kill Prince Yeonryeong now, how will you be able to deal with the consequences?
I guess this much
won't take my pain away, will it?
Resent your father, the King, for this.
From now on, whether I, Yi In Jwa, die or the King dies,
one of us must die in order for this to end.
I will definitely slash the King's neck.
Go into the afterlife and await your father.
♬   It's okay I can be in pain  ♬
♬   I'll just regard this difficulty as a guest,  ♬
♬   Crying afterward and even a single laugh  ♬
♬   If you just like me have the same wish  ♬