[Under the Moonlight]
[Adapted from the novel
"Jin Nang" by Shui He]
[Episode 19]
Lv Wanchang's family
may not meet with them directly.
There must be someone else
setting them up.
Song might be the one behind in Hejin.
There must be a mole in Linfen Yamen.
Wait.
How could he have a connection
with the petty official in Linfen?
Mr. Yang
is Mr. Cai's junior.
I'm afraid that's a common thing.
Hejin and Linfen are
in the same province.
We officials
are all locals here,
so many of us
are related somehow or other.
Alright,
let's arrest Song first.
Then we'll know about the other one.
No way.
Why?
You don't have any evidence.
Even if you
tell Hejin's magistrate the truth,
he won't believe you.
We can only look for loopholes
from those two kidnappers.
Do you have any ideas?
I do have one,
but...
Miss Luo,
why are you being so hesitant?
Come on, tell us.
Yeah.
Maybe we can help.
Right.
Think about it.
Jin Liu
could risk his own life
to get money
for his wife.
It means that
he really loved his wife, right?
Yes.
But today,
from Mrs. Jin's behavior,
she is very unkind to Jin Liu.
If we could
take action against her,
it would surely provoke Jin Liu
to reveal the truth.
How to take action?
Are you gonna ask someone
to disguise as a rich man
to seduce Mrs. Jin?
That's a good idea.
But
who's gonna do it?
Don't look at me.
I can't do it.
I absolutely can't.
I don't even like her!
We didn't say you have to like her.
You can do it.
Just play with her.
What do you mean by that?
No, no.
You want me to seduce
another woman?
You...
If you really
don't want to do it,
we won't force you.
We'll think of another way.
How do I look, Miss Luo?
I'm better than him, right?
Where?
Look at your big round face.
My big...
Who are you calling big round face?
Do you look in the mirror?
Your face looks like a basin,
and you call me big round face?
Look at yourself.
You big round face.
You big face.
Big round face.
You basin face.
Alright, stop it.
I know you're trying to help,
but you can't do this.
Why?
Your quality is just not right.
Not scaring her away
is already good enough.
It's even hard for you to succeed.
Go away.
If we can't find a suitable person,
I'll be the one
who is disguised as the rich man.
What?
I'll go.
Mr. Qi.
Seriously?
Yes.
Mr. QI, you really
should have said earlier.
We wouldn't have had
to force ourselves to dress up.
If you do this,
you'll definitely succeed.
Let me make it clear...
Stop it.
I'm not doing this
for Linfen Yamen.
I just don't want Luo Shu...
Don't want to see you in a tight spot.
Alright.
I owe you
a big favor.
I'll go prepare for you.
Good.
Let me help you.
Don't touch me.
I was passing through here
and I seem to have lost my way.
May I
ask for a bowl of water, my lady?
Just a bowl of water,
sure.
Please come in.
Are you getting a cold?
Then you shouldn't drink cold water.
Please come inside,
and rest for a while.
I'll go make ginger decoction.
Thank you, my lady.
I can do it.
Here you are.
It's hot. Take your time.
May I know your name?
My surname is Meng,
Meng Lin.
Mr. Meng.
Please sit down.
This ginger decoction
is really warming and refreshing.
It's been cold these days.
Why are you going hunting?
I was supposed to
hunt deer with my friends,
but we got separated.
I was stuck
in the mountains overnight.
I just came down.
Fortunately, I met you.
Do you live alone?
Yes.
I've been living alone for years,
all by myself.
So is your husband
doing business outside?
If he's really
a businessman,
I must be so fortunate
in my lifetime.
I'm telling you.
Don't be scared.
My husband is a
bandit who kills and robs.
What?
He's in jail now,
and will be executed after the autumn.
What?
You're so beautiful.
How could you marry such a villain?
He didn't marry me
with a formal wedding.
He is a villain.
He raped me
and forced me to be his wife.
I'm just a broken woman
with nowhere else to go.
I...
I'm so miserable.
Please don't cry.
My lady,
you're still young
and beautiful as Xi Shi and Diao Chan.
[*Two of the Four Ancient Beauties]
You'll meet someone
who loves you wholeheartedly.
You'll have a good life in the future.
Mr. Meng, don't joke with me.
I'm serious.
If what you said comes true,
it will be my good fortune.
I've been here for a while.
If I stay any longer,
it might be inconvenient for you.
I'll take my leave.
This silver ingot
is a token of my gratitude.
Thank you, my lady.
What are you doing?
It's just a bowl of ginger decoction.
You don't need to do this.
It's a repayment
for your kindness.
A thousand gold coins
in return for a meal.
I'm just following the ancients.
If it's difficult for you to accept,
how about taking it
and treating me tonight?
Alright,
if you say so,
I'll prepare a fine dinner
with good liquor and delicious dishes.
You
come tonight.
Alright,
I'll come back tonight
to ask for another bowl of water.
By then,
you don't regret it.
You look prettier than a girl
when you dress up like this.
Is that a compliment?
You're as handsome as Pan An,
[*One of the Four Most Handsome Men]
tall, elegant, and charming.
How about that?
That's better.
Help me out.
Which one?
This one.
Look at me,
with this outfit,
how can Mrs. Jin
refuse me?
A man and a woman
in the room at night.
After drinking some liquor,
there might be...
You're just playing with her.
Don't go too far.
Don't worry.
I promise.
Nothing will happen.
What's that mean?
You gave Mrs. Jin
two liang before.
It's on me.
But it's more than two liang.
This hairpin is also on me.
When you go to see Mrs. Jin,
give it to her as a gift.
It's not a big deal.
Take it.
You shouldn't pay for this.
Why?
You got public money from the yamen?
No,
it's my own money.
So, you spend your own money
to help Han Muzhi with the case,
but you don't want my money to help you.
Han Muzhi was
so ruthless to you.
Don't tell me you still
have feelings for him.
I owe him.
I want to help him
solve this last case.
Then we'll be even.
I support you.
Pay him back as soon as possible.
But you can
continue to owe me.
This one is also pretty good.
Mr. Meng, here you are.
Thank you, my lady.
You heart thief.
Why are you still being polite
at this time?
You can call me
Yuzhen.
I can tell from your accent
that you're not local, right?
I've lived in Taiyuan
for quite some time.
Taiyuan.
That's a great place.
Mr. Meng.
Yuzhen,
to be honest,
I've traveled all over the place
these years,
and seen plenty of beautiful women,
but I've never seen one
as endearing as you.
Really?
Of course.
It's really unfair.
You shouldn't
be with such a brute
who shoved you into
such a miserable life,
making you suffer.
A beauty like you
should have met me earlier.
Lin.
Yuzhen.
Now that we've met,
and here we are.
It's not too late for anything.
Let's have a drink.
Have a drink.
Cheers.
What a waste.
Lin,
don't you like me?
I like you of course.
No, no.
Lin,
you're clearly rejecting me.
I'm not.
Yuzhen,
get up.
Come on.
Are you hurt?
Stand up.
Yuzhen.
I'm gonna take you back to Taiyuan.
Once we're settled,
we can be intimate, alright?
You really want to take me
back to Taiyuan?
Once that person dies,
we'll set off immediately.
We'll be a pair
of long-lasting spouses.
We have plenty of time ahead,
So tonight,
let's just drink.
Just drink.
Come on.
Eat the head of cabbage for vegetables.
[*Guizhou Folk Song]
Marry the leader among thieves
for a husband.
Steel knives clang
in the middle of the night.
I wear silk,
while my husband wear brocade.
Lin, you're awake.
Yes.
I'll go fetch water
to help you wash up.
Lin, be careful on the road.
Don't alarm the neighbors.
Lin.
Don't forget to do something
to let the neighbors see.
That hairpin,
better to give it in front of others.
Lin.
Yuzhen.
Why are you back?
This is for you.
Let me help you.
You look so beautiful.
I'm off.
How did it go?
You...
You just think about my task.
You don't care about me.
But you're back,
aren't you?
Yes,
but I'm feeling bad.
Why?
She hasn't bitten on your charm?
No.
She's been
hooked on my bait.
That's why I'm upset.
I am
such a man of integrity.
Now I'm being
hugged by her.
Don't you...
Don't you mind?
I do.
You really do?
Oh, no.
You must think I'm dirty now.
And you'll look down on me.
Alright.
What are you thinking?
You know
my background,
but you never look down on me,
and you consider me a friend, right?
I know your character.
I know
you're not someone
who's easily captivated by beauty.
I know it's difficult for you.
I really appreciate it.
How could I look down on you?
Really?
Really.
Alright.
With your words,
I'll do it again.
Again?
You feel good about it?
No, I don't.
That's not what I meant.
I get it.
What?
You've finished your task.
The hairpin on your head
was given to her.
So you succeeded.
Leave the rest to me.
Slow down.
Be careful.
Excuse me, is this Zheng's house?
Who are you?
Are you Zheng San's wife?
I'm from Linfen,
Ma Tianjin's family.
My husband is in jail now.
He'll be executed after the autumn.
If you seek revenge,
go find him.
I'm just a widow with my children,
trying to live peacefully.
Don't worry.
I'm not here for revenge.
Here, this is for you.
Thank you.
Take it.
Give it back.
It's alright.
They're in a stage
of physical growth.
They should eat more meat.
Thank you.
Wait.
I know
your husband didn't kill Ma Tianjin.
What are you talking about?
Just like Jin Liu,
he's framed and bought by someone.
I'm sure you know that too,
right?
I just want justice.
Mrs. Zheng,
put yourself in my shoes.
If you were me,
would you stand by
and watch your family
die without a clear cause
while the murderer goes scott-free?
I'm really sorry for your loss,
but what's the use of
asking these questions?
How much silver did they offer you?
You raise two children on your own.
You have a long way to go.
Those money won't last you long.
If you help me
get them retract testimony
and find the murderer,
no matter how much they offer,
I'll double it.
You're not like Mrs. Jin
who's alone with no children.
Once her husband is dead,
she will take the money
and live happily.
I heard
she's hooked up
with a rich young man recently.
But you,
with the same money for three people,
you have to
think about your future.
As the old saying goes,
it's every man for himself.
You can't
just let her live comfortably
while you endure hardships, can you?
Why don't you go to talk to her?
To be honest,
I went to see her,
but she wouldn't help.
Even with the double money?
She's eager for her husband
to die early,
so she can live happily
with that rich young man.
For her,
if she marries that young man,
she'll have endless wealth.
Even triple the money
won't change her mind.
Mrs. Zheng,
even if you don't think about yourself,
you really should
think about your children.
I'll come again
in a few days.
[Jail]
Mrs. Zheng, you're here too.
You've come.
Yes.
Why did you bring such a good meal?
I'm dying soon.
Leave them for the kids.
Don't worry about that.
Eat up.
Here.
I'm so envious.
Liu.
Come join us.
Come here.
Thank you.
That's your meal?
My lazy wife
just sent me steamed buns.
Yuzhen is really something.
How can she only consider the new
and not the old?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Eat some more.
Mrs. Zheng, what's going on?
Liu.
There's something
I don't know if I should say.
But I feel
so unfair for you.
Yuzhen
hooked up with a rich young man.
What are you talking about?
That's true.
That young man gave Yuzhen
lots of jewelry.
You saw she wore
a gem-encrusted gold hairpin today.
Alright, stop it.
Let's eat.
Jin Liu,
your wife is here.
You've come.
Here you are.
Just two steamed buns?
We don't have vegetables at home.
Yes.
I've done what you asked.
Don't forget your promise.
They offered me thirty liang.
So you need to give me sixty liang.
I want silver ingots.
Here's a hundred liang.
You're right.
It's every man for himself.
Did you give her?
To repay Han Muzhi's favor,
you really spent a lot.
Stirring up trouble
is not what I want.
This one hundred liang
may bring me peace of mind.
Bring you peace of mind.
You spent one hundred liang
for that.
That's expensive.
May I ask you
where you got
so much money?
I can't tell you that.
You really keep a low profile.
How many things
don't I know about you?
Too many.
San, I'm sorry.
I'll retract testimony.
Listen to me.
It might not be
what you think.
Wait for your wife to come next time
and ask her.
Make a decision after that.
No need for that.
Your wife is honest and straightforward.
If she said it, it must be true.
No.
I risked my life to get the money.
She can't share it with a young man.
I'll retract testimony.
Liu.
I want to retract testimony.
Is there anyone? I'll retract testimony.
Where's the magistrate?
I'll retract testimony.
Shut up.
Are you crazy?
I'm not.
I'm gonna retract testimony.
Keep your voice down.
Did you get kicked in the head?
What am I gonna do if you retract?
San, don't worry.
I'll just retract my part.
You can still take the money.
Stop watching. Go to bed.
Sit.
What is wrong with you?
You confessed together.
Do you really think
you can retract your part?
I don't care. I'm gonna retract my part.
San, I'm sorry.
I just can't let it go.
In my next life, I'll be your slave
to repay you.
I'll retract testimony.
I want to talk to the magistrate.
If you don't let me see him,
I'll shout here.
I'll shout loud enough for everyone.
Shut up.
I'll retract testimony.
Alright.
Do you think shouting like that
will bring the magistrate here?
Fine.
I'll go to invite him.
You wait here.
Shut your mouth.
Go to bed.
How is it?
He bit.
Jin Liu.
Get up.
The magistrate wants to interrogate you.
Be quiet.
Go.
San, I'm sorry.
That way.
Why is the magistrate
interrogating me
in the middle of the night?
Doesn't he sleep?
You talk too much.
Just go.
Where is this place?
Why isn't here even a light?
There's no need for lights
on the way to your afterlife.
Song.
It's really you.
You tried to kill me?
Even if I die,
I'll drag you down with me.
Your Honor,
I didn't kill Ma Tianjin.
I commit murder and robbery.
I know I'll lead to a bad end.
So I just wanted to
use my worthless life
to get some money
for my wife.
But I never expected her
to hook up with a young man
before my death.
Who bought you to take the blame?
It was him.
He coerced and threatened me.
I was blinded by greed
so I agreed to him.
San can testify for me.
Song.
You took bribes and violated the law,
and then attempted murder.
If you're convicted,
you'll be sentenced to death.
Your Honor, please spare my life.
Please spare my life.
I know you're not the head.
There must be someone behind you,
right?
The head will definitely
be severely punished,
but the accomplice may not.
So,
your life is in your own hands.
Do you wanna be
the head or the accomplice?
It's up to you.
Song, at this point,
what are you hesitating about?
Do you want your life or money?
I...
Just tell the truth.
I... I confess.
It was an old man.
Last month,
he asked me to do this.
The testimony.
He taught me about the testimony.
What's his name?
I don't know.
Don't play games.
I...
I really don't know.
All I know is that
my teacher introduced him
as his good friend.
He didn't want to be identified.
So I didn't dare to ask.
Who is your teacher?
Is he from our Linfen Yamen?
Even if you don't say,
we'll find out eventually.
We'll just take a bit more time.
By then,
you'll lose the chance
to get a lenient sentence.
It's...
It's Mr. Wei from Linfen Yamen.
Mr. Wei
has worked at the yamen for many years.
You don't know that old man's name.
You should remember his appearance.
He has silver hair and a long beard.
He looks shrewd.
Any other features?
No, I don't think so.
Wait, I remember that
every time I saw him,
he was always
holding a small round box.
There was a woman
holding a child on it.
And he opened the box sometimes
and took out some powder,
sniffing it through his nose.
It's Snuff.
I heard that
an western missionary
called Matteo Ricci
came across the sea.
Among the tribute
he presented to His Majesty,
there was Snuff.
It's a small box,
with exquisite patterns.
It's indeed rare.
I went to the capital
with my father before.
I saw it being used
in a noble's mansion.
Are you alright?
I got it.
Who?
Mr. Wu.
He's a well-known shyster in Linfen.
He's skilled at distorting facts
and helping others retract testimony.
He succeeds every time,
and always makes a huge profit.
I've seen him before.
He was holding
such a little thing
and sniffing it through his nose.
Mr. Qi.
Mr. Qi, are you alright?
So hot.
Zhan, go get the doctor.
Okay.
Mr. Qi.
You're awake.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Fortunately, your fever's going down.
The doctor said you had a cold.
It must be because
you fell into the water last time
and didn't take care of it,
which resulted in you catching a fever.
It's my fault.
I've been focused on the case
that I neglected you.
I even asked you to deal with Mrs. Jin.
How can it be your fault?
I did it willingly.
♪The red of the setting sun
tinges the pristine snow♪
♪Swans return successively,
fulfilling the promise of spring♪
♪From whence does the wind invite
a few plum blossoms to float?♪
♪I entrust my longing,
waiting for you to know♪
♪A single lamp flickers,
with curling smoke in the air♪
♪Magpies perch on branches,
guarding our lifelong attachment♪
♪No matter how far you go,
home will illuminate your night♪
♪Returning through the snow,
back to each other's side♪
♪Warm gazes have brought
all the comfort in sight♪
♪Time flows like a long scroll
Let's write our story♪
♪Hand in hand through life and tomorrow
We'll meet as we go♪
♪Coming back from the snow
Let's enjoy the warm spring days♪
♪Dressed in white
Everything looks fresh♪
♪Time connects our feelings
The world is full of love♪
♪Holding onto life's warmth♪
♪Love is right in front of us♪
♪Coming back from the snow
Let's enjoy the warm spring days♪
♪Dressed in white
Everything looks fresh♪
♪Time connects our feelings
The world is full of love♪
♪Holding onto life's warmth♪
♪Love is right in front of us♪