What do you want to say?
I come in peace.
Peace? What’s time?
Probably in the afternoon.
Huh!?
You asked about the time.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing,
Just tell me what you want.
I have some reasons why I must return here.
Hmm, and what are those reasons?
I can't tell you much.
It's a rule of time.
Your memories will only return when you sleep.
All I can say is that I came back here for you to remember me.
I... uh...
I remember you.
Why do I remember you?
Because... we were in love
two thousand years ago.
Two thousand years?
Who could possibly remember that?
I even forget why I walked to the fridge when I'm thirsty.
Please go back to where you came from.
I can’t return.
Have you heard that a person dies twice?
First, a physical death.
Second, a death from memory.
When you remember me,
then I will depart forever.
That is my mission.
So, ghosts have missions too?
Humans have their world,
why wouldn't ghosts have their own world?
But isn't that a bit selfish?
It's just your own desire.
I have an exchange to offer.
What about exchange?
Tell me.
I will protect you from your enemies from a former life.
Enemies from a former life?
Does it really exist??
It’s true.
Huh?
You can hear me?
Okay, but we have to make a deal.
Deal?
Yeah,
cohabitation agreement between a person and a ghost.
I’m not an ordinary ghost.
I’m  far superior to that.
Don’t flashing in and out to scare me.
Okay.
Let's live separately and not bother each other.
If you forbid me from interfering with you,
then I have no reason to come back here.
Then don't interfere unless it's necessary.
Okay deal.
And most importantly, don't enter my room.
I can’t agree with this one.
And why do you have to come into my room?
I must sleep with the one I love every night.
No way.
Why not?
1 You are not my lover,
2 Do ghosts even need to sleep?
1 Your past self was my lover.
2. Ghosts need rest too.
So you admit you're a ghost?
Don't change the topic.
I have to protect you,
if your enemies from a former life come to harm you while you're asleep.
How can I help you?
Your memories will only return when you sleep.
If your memories don't return,
I can't go anywhere and have to stay here forever.
Is that what you want?
Fine,
I'll allow you into my bedroom then.
But you're not allowed on my bed.
I agreed.
Ah, and is there anything you want to beg me?
I don't like shaman.
Could you not bring it here?
Okay, you don't like Shaman,
I won't bring it here.
I have something to beg you.
I'd like you to change your outfit.
Why do you want me to change outfits?
Your nipples bother me.
This is called a car.
Car?
Hmm, it's developed from a cart.
Cart?
Your body odor smells the same as always.
How about this one?
No.
I... I'm embarrassed.
Hey, what was your career in your past life?
Do you sell khanom krok?
You're so good at flirting.
I don't have any career other than being the son of a king.
Are you boasting to me?
Boasting?
Yes, boasting, like showing off.