Why are you still outside after getting home?
I'm tired today.
Do you want me to help you with anything?
Can you help me up to my room?
I can't walk anymore.
Of course.
Do you want me to help you with anything else,
or take a bath?
Okay, no problem.
And if...
If what?
What if it's more than that?
Well... that's okay too,
no problem either.
But you're tired.
Seeing your face makes my tiredness disappear.
Then why wait?
What's wrong with you?
Just say whatever it is.
You know?
I see you're quiet.
You've looked overthinking since you arrived.
Is there something you want to tell me?
I'm just thinking about us.
About us?
Well, you and me. Our status isn't clear.
You're a ghost,
and I'm human.
I just don't see how we can make this work.
Am I being here with you every day, every moment, not enough?
Never mind.
Trust me, I will be with you.
Whether it's last life, this life, or next life.
Even if one day you can't see me,
my heart will be with you forever.
What do you mean?
It means I love you,
Good night, Navee.
Good night, my ghost.
This ghost smells so good
Good morning.
Um, good morning.
Wow... Is there anything I can help you with?
No, just sit down.
Be careful, I might get spoiled
if you do everything for me like this.
Is that not good?
It's good, but...
Hmm?
Never mind.
Do you want to help, don't you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Then go chop the vegetables. That's the easiest.
No matter how much time passes, my love for you will never change.
Even after tens of thousands of days, I still miss you deeply.
It has never changed.
Our love transcends time.
I wait for destiny to bring our hearts together.
I'm truly confused, honestly.
Suddenly, you appeared and said we used to be lovers.
And then you just vanish abruptly after showing up
That also scares me.
This is going to end up on The Ghost Radio; poor P'Jack.
But as time goes on,
more things surprise me.
The idea that we were once in love—at first, I half-believed it, half-didn't.
In the end, it turned out to be so true; being with you directly was utterly astonishing.
My heart tells me it's indescribable, like falling in love.
Over time, it made me forget you for a while.
But in the end, I slowly came back to loving you.
No matter how long it's been since we last met or saw each other,
I still love you the same.
No matter how much time passes, my love for you will never change.
Even after tens of thousands of days, I still miss you deeply.
It has never changed.
Our love transcends time.
I wait for destiny to bring our hearts together.
No matter how long it takes, I will only love you.
You don't need to be this close.
Step back a bit.
Have you ever realized how annoying you can be sometimes?
But then when you're not around, I feel so lonely and empty, I can barely stand it.
I won't do anything to you here.
Don't be afraid.
Oh, you!
That's not what I meant at all!
Your head is always full of those kinds of things.
Done.
It wasn't difficult at all, was it?
It's easier to just order.
If one day I'm not here, how will you do it yourself?
Listen, if one day you're not here, I'll just order delivery!
but I've been having strange dreams.
I don't know if there just dreams or if there is about two thousand years ago.
Then I will help you remember.
No, no, I don't want to hear it.
You don't have to tell me anything.
I have somewhere I want to take you there.
Where is it?
You'll find out soon enough.