If the next life exists,
I wish to encounter all forms of love
that have been accepted no matter who it’s with.
The fortune of those born on Monday is currently not good.
The fate has turned upside down,
and Enemies from a former life are not going away,
causing unhappiness in their lives.
Your fortune is very bad.
Would you like to go make merit?
Say it again.
Who will go to make merit?
It’s you.
you should believe it sometimes,
When they tell you or warn you, it's for your own good to be careful.
It’s not wasted.
No way.
I will go to work,
see you tomorrow.
May any ghost come and haunt my friend.
Make him catch a fever and go bald.
Tomorrow night, the National Astronomical Research Institute of Thailand
invites everyone to watch the super full moon phenomenon!
It's a Halloween treat,
as the moon will appear exceptionally large, much bigger than usual,
and will be at its closest to Earth in many years.
This will be seen again for about 2-3 months,
and that's just an estimate.
Don't forget, tomorrow night from 9 PM onwards.
What am I dreaming?
Nowadays it's all about telling ghost stories.
You gotta play on beliefs.
People are all thinking about the spiritual stuff.
What spooky stories do you want to tell us tonight?
Have you ever heard the belief about Halloween?
Halloween is the day that spirits return to meet someone they miss.
Whoa! I’m Goosebumps!
That’s so scary.