[English subtitles are available]
[Love Under The Full Moon]
[Episode 10]
Then we helped her
find Summer Time.
You know the rest.
So that's it.
I'm glad you're back.
I'm glad I waited until you got back.
Based on
what was said,
you're currently just
twenty-two years old.
But I'm already...
Thirty-two.
It's alright.
That's not important.
What's important is that you're back.
It's fine.
I'll protect you.
You've always been
taking care of me like a sister
in the past.
Now it's my turn to take care of you.
I won't complain that you're young.
Since you fainted,
you're probably not feeling well.
So tonight you should stay at my place.
I'll take care of you.
Why are you looking at him
just to come stay at my place?
Well, you see...
Didn't I lose my wrist band?
I can't stay too far away from him.
No matter how far I go,
I'll still be back at his side.
Then would you mind
sleeping on the sofa at my place?
I...
I don't mind.
Get lost.
That's decided then.
I want to go too.
What does this have to do with you?
How's this?
Doesn't this
look quite cool?
Yuan Yuan,
why are you staying at a warehouse?
The rent is low here.
The money that I save
has to go to sustain Summer Time.
Come in and take a look.
Why don't you move in with me?
I won't charge rent.
No one wants to stay with you.
My place is a little small.
Yuan Yuan,
your home is decorated quite nicely.
Life is tough
so I have to treat myself nicer.
It doesn't look very decent.
You're the indecent one.
Jin Xiao Rui,
you are making yourself at home, huh?
Chu Xia,
the bedroom is this way.
We can sleep together
tonight.
You're mine.
Xu Xiao Dong,
you'll sleep on the sofa, okay?
Okay.
Is this distance alright?
No problem.
What about me?
Look,
there's a lot of space on the floor.
Pick a spot.
How is it?
My room.
Your room is really tasteful.
Right?
There was actually nothing here
when I first moved in.
These were all
slowly added to the decoration.
Look.
There's a small balcony.
When I came,
everything was empty.
I thought since I'm staying here,
I should treat myself better.
So I decorated it.
Now it looks not bad, right?
When we earn some big money,
we'll stay in a bigger home,
and have more flavour in life.
Let's work hard together.
What's wrong?
Why are you not getting ready
to sleep yet?
Were you scared about
what happened just now?
I'm fine,
but the customers got scared.
Don't worry about them.
People love to be
nosy.
The bigger the issue the better.
But,
luckily Xu Xiao Dong showed up in time.
You didn't see
how anxious he was
when he picked you up.
Thanks to him.
Based on my strong sixth sense,
my instinct says that
Xu Xiao Dong definitely
has feelings for you.
What about you?
What about me?
Playing dumb?
I'm asking if you like him.
I better think about
how to stay alive here.
You're such a killjoy.
I think Xu Xiao Dong
is definitely the first choice.
I'll be the first to vote for him.
Vote with both my hands and feet.
Alright, time to sleep.
You can make anything work.
Xiao Dong is just on
the other side of the door.
Go to sleep.
Stop talking.
No, it's because the two of you...
Don't talk when you're eating
or sleeping, okay?
Okay, I'll sleep.
You should sleep early too.
Sleeping soon.
I feel so happy
breathing the air of Yuan Yuan's home.
Xiao Dong,
tell me.
Yuan Yuan was able to finish
all my sentences about love.
Don't you think that
we're extra compatible?
Even though she's a lot older than I am,
I feel that she doesn't mind that at all.
What do you think?
Your best friend is talking to you.
Can you give some response, please?
The girls might just be
having pillow talk in the room.
We should communicate so that
we have each others' backs.
Okay.
Do you think I should be
more straight forward
and take a lot more initiative?
I'm afraid you might not
be able to even sleep on the sofa.
Okay. Let's stop talking about me.
Let's talk about you.
I saw you
coming back with her.
That feeling between you two...
I will definitely not believe it
if you say you don't have feelings
for each other.
You're a man.
You should just confess your feelings.
It's not the best time
to confess my feelings.
Chu Xia just experienced
a serious physical condition.
If I confess now, I...
Didn't they say online that
spending time is
the most romantic confession?
I think I'll just spend time with her.
You're right.
I'm going to
spend more time with Yuan Yuan
in the future too.
Okay. Go spend time with Yuan Yuan.
Go to sleep.
Okay, I know.
You couldn't sleep either?
Do you want to have a drink together?
Don't you think that
the moon is quite full today?
I remember the day when you appeared,
the moon
was a round, full moon too.
You were probably scared out of your life.
What if I told you
I remembered something today?
What did you remember?
After I fainted,
some scenes popped up in my mind.
I saw myself running
[and someone kept chasing from behind.]
[So I kept running,]
until I reached the end of a cliff
and fell off.]
[He held on to me]
[but then he let go.]
[So I fell.]
[He just watched me.]
I can't be sure if
this was a memory
or an illusion.
I just feel that this whole thing
isn't simple at all.
Tell me,
do you think I got here
because I fell off a cliff?
That would be a huge coincidence
that you fell right on top of me.
I remember how much
that slap hurt till this day.
What should I do?
I can't fall asleep.
It's a long night,
what should we do?
I have an idea.
Do you want to give it a go?
What idea?
Hashtag,
include,
quotation marks.
Hello,
include...
[Include.]
Chevron.
[Chevron.]
Standard input and output functions.
Include hell.
Company.
Bracket.
[Even though I don't know
what your memories mean,]
[I would spend time with you.]
[That's my way of liking you.]
[The moon is my witness.]
Chu Xia,
you should rest here
for these two days.
Don't worry about the shop.
Master Wang can take over.
Come back when you're well rested.
I'm going back to Xiao Dong's home today.
You're going back today?
The first place I went to
when I got here
was his home.
I feel safe after staying there
for a while.
There's already a space for me
over at his place.
Okay.
Xu Xiao Dong
is actually
pretty reliable.
Remember to tell me
if you need anything.
Take a good rest there then.
-Okay.
-Come back when you're well rested.
Okay.
Give it to me.
Mr. Wei,
the reason we're still here
in a meeting at this hour
is because the Family First app
kept having issues.
-Yes.
-In consideration of our funds,
I suggest to axe it.
The Family First app
is very important to Cyber Tech.
We'll be able to overcome
the current obstacles.
The deadline is approaching.
If Family First
fails to go online,
we as investors
won't invest with you anymore.
[Software System Test Report]
[Dad]
[I heard that]
[the investor's meeting]
[didn't go well.]
[Xuan He,]
[all these years your work
hasn't been outstanding.]
[You never achieved]
[what I asked of you.]
[If you can't do it,]
[just pack up and come home.]
[All these years]
[your work hasn't been outstanding.]
[Just pack up and come home.]
Mr. Wei.
Are you still considering?
You're going to regret it if
you miss this chance.
Is it possible that
we didn't do it ten years ago?
[Yao Yang Tech AI Project
Partnership Framework Agreement]
Xuan He,
you can't do that.
You'll destroy yourself.
I only have this one chance.
That's not true.
You have talent and capability.
You can openly
get achievements that only belong to you.
You don't understand.
I only have this one chance.
I'm not as good as you imagined.
Sunny Girl.
Now that you're no longer here,
no one will stop me.
[Wei Xuan He]
[Partnership Agreement]
You should go back.
I'm not in the mood to meet guests.
I know you're in a bad mood.
That's why I came over.
I'm not planning to leave.
Even if you stay
I won't start to have feelings for you.
A lot of people approach me
because they want to
get something from me.
Some want a successful career,
some want to have a higher
social standing.
What about you?
You've put in so much effort on me.
What do you want from me?
I want everything.
I want a glamorous life,
the title of Mrs. Wei,
and most importantly, I want you.
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
I don't have a lovable heart.
It's not worth getting.
Xuan He,
you were never perfect to me.
But I want all of you,
the good and the bad.
Anything that is Wei Xuan He's
will one day belong to me, Qin Yue.
If I can't get your heart
then I'll get your body.
I'm confident...
that you heart will be mine one day.
You're taking everything
no matter good or bad?
Everything.
Let me tell you.
People shouldn't be so greedy.
I am exactly that greedy.
Xiao Dong.
Xiao dong...
I sent something good to you.
Check your phone.
That's it?
Turing can get more of these sappy
love notes in a blink.
How is that the same?
These are the exclusive version
of Xiao Rui's Love Notes.
I saw how you were last night.
Lei Chu Xia and you were telling stories,
reading codes,
but not confessing your feelings.
I'm dying of anxiety.
So as your best friend,
I think I should give you a hand.
I don't need it.
If you really want to help me,
help me make an appointment
with the psychologist.
Dr. Tian Yu?
What do you plan to do?
I want to bring Chu Xia
over for a session.
Take the trash out.
Do it yourself.
[Psychologist Tian Yu]
How do you feel now?
At that time...
You see a light
[shining on you.]
Relax.
Three, two, one.
How is it, Dr. Tian Yu?
The scene that Chu Xia saw
wasn't an illusion.
Are the scenes in her memory
all true?
Scenes that were shown
basically match what Chu Xia described.
This means it's not an illusion.
Look,
running,
falling,
being chased.
It hints at a lack of security.
It's bizarre.
She is especially resistant and nervous
with this one memory.
That caused her to see
sporadic scenes.
This further points to
a big probability that
this is a true memory.
Based on what you said,
the man that let go and caused her
to fall down the cliff in her memory
really exists too?
It's highly possible.
Of course,
we can't rule out that this is something
that stems from her extreme fear.
We need more memories
to come to a
relatively accurate conclusion.
Got it. Thank you, Dr. Tian.
It's windy.
Don't overthink.
It's possible that the person
who hurt you is already dead.
It's also possible that
just like Dr. Tian Yu said,
he's just a visualisation of your fear.
This person might not exist in reality.
If someone really
pushed me off a cliff ten years ago,
something terrible must have happened.
I have to investigate.
Okay.
Mum.
Chu Xia.
It's been a few days.
Why don't I go back to the room with you?
It's more comfortable to sleep on a bed.
You're not sleeping well here.
I'm fine.
I don't dare to sleep now anyway.
You can go back to work.
I...
I'll just lie down here for a bit.
Madam, can I have a sugar pancake?
Okay.
Where did she go?
Lei Chu Xia.
What are you doing?
Are you having another nightmare?
I just went to get breakfast.
The wrist band is
still with Professor Chen.
We can't stay too far apart.
You need to control the distance.
Since you're awake,
let's go together.
I want to sleep a little bit more.
Stop sleeping.
You've said so much,
it's time to get up.
Get up.
Hey,
I saw with my own eyes
that there was only one
sugar pancake left.
It's a shame if we don't get it.
The last one?
I'll go with you then.
The best way
to control your distance,
a leash.
This is what you meant by the last one?
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Sure thing.
Is this sugar pancake really that good?
You don't get it.
Sometimes you just have to
get what you're craving for.
If you don't, you won't be happy.
Xiao Dong!
We have to go.
Oh no.
-Xiao Dong.
-Good morning, aunty.
Why do you have a leash on?
This is usually for dogs and kids,
I've never seen it on boyfriends before.
This is something new.
Yes.
Women shouldn't be too possessive.
If you really want to tie him down,
it shouldn't be done with a rope.
Exactly.
Let me tell you,
if a woman wants to tie a man down,
you need to tie him at his heart.
Yes.
Aunty, young people like us
prefer it like this.
Bye!
Kids nowadays.
Why are they all like that?
There's always something new.
It's true.
[Chu Xia's dream]
[is a projection of
her wanting to get her memories back.]
Because she's pushing
to know more about the past,
she kept dreaming about it.
As for what the dream represents,
we would need
more information to decipher it.
We can actually try
getting her to get in touch with people,
places and events
[that she's more familiar with.]
[This might help her a lot more.]
[Since Dr. Tian Yu said that,]
[why don't we go to my home?]
Catch.
Chu Xia,
take a look.
Hurry.
♫ Broken ♫
♫ Zoning out all night ♫
♫ The time machine is broken ♫
This was when I was young?
I think so.
[Run.]
What happened?
Was that it?
Did it end or is it broken?
Is it out of battery?
This might be broken.
Let's find a place to fix it.
We definitely need to fix it.
This unit isn't an old model.
It's an antique.
It's done once it's broken.
But the video inside
is pretty precious.
Could you help us take a better look?
If it stopped playing half way,
there's one possibility.
The battery slot is broken.
It turns on at first,
but stops after awhile.
That means
if I can find a new slot
and replace it,
it'll work again, right?
But this type of slot
has been obsolete for a long time.
It's not easy to find at all.
I can try and give it a go.
-Thanks a lot.
-Great.
Let's go and find one.
Okay.
[Hold on to the leader's leg]
[Let the Leader wear it]
[Dear players,]
[here's the newest announcement
from Winter.]
[In search for home DV parts]
[or user manual.]
[What if it can't be found?]
[Model B-612.]
[This model is so rare.]
[Please send it to Summer Time.]
[Game announcement]
[Attach you game ID]
[and you'll get an achievement from heaven.]
[Bumped into Darwin.]
[Darwin appeared in the notice board
in the city.]
[Who is going to have
an antique like that?]
[I suspect that Darwin
is the boss behind all this.]
[I have it at home.]
[I'm going to dig it up right now.]
[I heard that Summer Time has two owners.]
[Which one is Darwin's girlfriend?]
[Summer Time]
[Courier]
-Here. -Thank you.
-Please visit us again. -Okay.
Summer Time,
I have a delivery for you.
Coming.
What is it?
I don't think I ordered anything.
It is addressed to the owners.
Thanks.
There's still more there.
There's more?
The whole truck.
That many?
Jin Xiao Rui,
come and help.
Help me place them on the second table.
-Okay, no problem.
-Thanks.
So many parcels?
Don't stand around.
Help me move them.
Okay.
I don't know who...
Battle of the Saints...
Why is there a bracket,
"Battle of the Saints,"
behind all the senders' names?
What is Xiao Dong trying to do?
Who's trying to do what?
You know who's behind this?
No.
I'm moving the parcels.
Weird.
Is this it?
Players of Battle of the Saints
sent a lot of
parts and user manuals to us?
Didn't you say that you're
looking for parts of the DV?
So Winter
helped you in the game.
So now Summer Time
has been flooded by
aide parcels sent by the fans.
What fairy tale is this?
I didn't tell Winter that
I'm trying to fix a DV.
Did Jin Xiao Rui
tell Winter?
Jin Xiao Rui
-counts as Winter's online friend too.
-Is this it?
And he helped Winter
help out Summer Time before.
Here's the problem.
I didn't tell Jin Xiao Rui either.
Xiao Dong,
my back feels like it's burning.
Every time you need help,
Winter will appear in time.
This means...
-he's around us.
-He's around us.
But there's only the two of them
around us.
They're Winter!
How's that possible?
Stop staring.
Keep looking.
Okay.
Winter knows me very well.
Xiao Dong knows me best, after you.
He's Winter?
I heard that
Winter is the
mature and reliable type.
Is this it?
That's it.
So the both of them...
-Yes.
-You found it.
-Found it.
Xiao Dong!
Found it.
♫ Broken ♫
♫ Zoning out all night ♫
♫ The time machine is broken ♫
♫ it's running so fast ♫
Oh my gosh.
Have you been so naive
since you were a kid?
[Mum!]
[Are you happy?]
[Yes.]
[Our Chu Xia loves sausages.]
But you were really very cute
when you were young.
[Run!]
[Run.]
Are there no more videos?
That's all the videos
that are in the DV.
Chu Xia,
did you remember anything?
I just feel that I'm pretty adorable
when I was a kid.
If it's not for Winter,
I wouldn't get to watch all these.
But how did he know?
I forgot to tell you.
The owner of the electronic store
sent a message to me.
He said he plays Battle of the Saints too.
He bumped into Winter in the game.
After Winter found out about this,
he tried to ask around.
Are you leaving comments for Winter?
Yes.
Chu Xia,
don't you feel that the way you're
[Thanks Winter. I found the part for the DV.]
communicating with Winter,
[I'll thank you in person if I get the chance.]
it feels like...
He wants to be in
a virtual relationship with you.
Do you want to die?
He's never even seen me.
That's why it's called
a virtual relationship.
When you meet it's called
bringing it to the real world.
Think about it.
A friend whom
you have never met
keeps giving you a helping hand.
He also fulfils all your requests
using the public for personal gain.
There's only one truth to this,
and that is that he likes you.
That's impossible. Stop guessing.
Okay, I'll stop guessing.
We don't need to care
what Winter thinks.
Let me ask you then.
Do you have feelings for Winter?
He might just be casually helping out.
It's like doing
the daily missions in the game.
Winter is a gaming genius.
And your favourite game
was designed by him.
Wouldn't you fall for
someone with so much talent?
Xiao Rui,
have you heard that
crazy gamer boys
only shower once a month
and have shiny, greasy hair?
No way.
Winter is a hot guy,
and definitely a very hot one.
If he's so mysterious,
it's possible that he's just
an emotionless pig that only lives online.
Who said you could
talk about my friend like that?
What about me?
You...
are my friend too.
Then let me ask you this.
If I fell into the sea with Winter,
who would you save?
I can't swim.
I'm saving neither.
Lend me your phone.
What do you want to do?
[Thanks, Winter.]
[I found the part for the DV.]
[I'll thank you in person]
[if I get the chance.]
Chu Xia doesn't sound like
she has feelings for Winter
other than being thankful.
As for meeting in person,
she's not going to get a chance.
What are you sneakily watching?
Watch... watching?
Don't move.
What were you watching?
Jin Xiao Rui.
A good relationship
would allow us to see each others' phones,
and we might not need
to see each other's phone.
But I think
I'll pick the former.
What do you think?
What would you choose?
There's nothing that I can't show you.
See, there's nothing there.
Good.
Why don't you see it later?
Not now.
You would have deleted
what needs to be deleted.
You think I'm dumb?
Yuan Yuan, this...
What's your password?
I... I've forgotten.
Really...
[Lei Chu Xia: Thanks, Winter.
I've found the part for the DV.]
[I'll thank you in person
if I get the chance.]
Winter asked me
to settle things here.
I can't expose Winter's information,
but I think he's probably
better looking than Xu Xiao Dong.
[Jin Xiao Rui...]
Could he be Winter?
You're Winter?
I'm not.
-You have feelings for Chu Xia!
-I don't!
You have feelings for Chu Xia!
Go away.
You did so much for Chu Xia?
Did so much!
Trust me. I really don't
have feelings for Chu Xia.
How do you explain Winter?
How do you explain it?
Jin Xiao Rui, you liar!
Jin Xiao Rui, you're such a liar!
I won't believe you anymore.
-Yuan Yuan...
-You're a liar!
A liar you are!
I told you to wait a little longer.
Now we're exposed.
We can't let Chu Xia
know my identity yet.
There's more danger
if more people know about it.
What should I do with Yuan Yuan then?
She's going to ignore me!
I must come clean.
If you're my best friend,
you need to help me.
If you're my best friend then you
should tell her that you're Winter!
Xiao Dong,
please help me.
Yuan Yuan is going to ignore me.
What should I do?
Okay.
No, no, no.
No.
I...
Jin Xiao Rui!
No!
It's dangerous! Slow down.
So you are the real Winter.
Correct.
Winter is my actual identity.
But due to some unique reasons,
I had to cover my identity
with the identity of a game programmer.
But don't worry.
I won't hurt Chu Xia.
Then why did you tell me?
If I don't tell you,
I'm going to lose
Jin Xiao Rui as my brother.
He doesn't want you to misunderstand.
Yuan Yuan,
I hope that for now,
you won't tell Chu Xia yet.
I'll tell her personally
when the time is right.
I don't have to tell her now,
but when is it the right time?
When my place in Chu Xia's heart
overtakes
Winter's place.
I really don't understand
what you men
think about all day.
Okay,
I've come clean.
I hope you can help me keep this secret.
Thank you.
Good luck.
[Summer Time]
So Yuan Yuan,
please don't ignore me.
Let go.
No.
Are you going to let go?
Sit over there.
So based on what
Xu Xiao Dong said,
that car wasn't yours?
Well...
He doesn't drive it.
I just drive it for fun.
What about the watch?
Xiao Dong gave it to me.
I'm just a
common finance worker.
Why would you
keep pretending like
you come from money?
You can't hit me
if I tell the truth.
Tell me.
It was love at first sight
since the first time I saw you.
But you look
a lot more mature than I am.
I worried that you'd think I'm too young,
so I thought that
if I have money,
you probably wouldn't turn me down.
Really?
Yes.
I keep hearing people say
mature women
have seen a lot in life
and are very realistic.
So I thought a relationship
without stable financial grounds
will not last.
I'm acting all the time because
I want to sustain our love.
So in Jin Xiao Rui's Heart,
I've always been
a woman who just loves money?
Let me tell you,
I don't need that.
What era is this?
You think this is the past?
Women must rely on men?
Jin Xiao Rui,
I'm breaking up with you.
Hold on,
when were we officially together?
Why didn't you inform me?
That's not important.
We've broken up now.
Why am I just being informed
about a relationship and our breakup?
Wait for me.
[Summer Time]
What's going on with you and Jin Xiao Rui?
That Jin Xiao Rui...
He thinks I'm a woman
who is after fame and fortune.
Am I?
No.
And he
pretended to be tall, rich and handsome
in front of me.
Does he fit?
Which part of him is tall,
rich and handsome?
Xiao Dong, if you don't help me
get Yuan Yuan back,
I'll just stick to you
for the rest of my life.