[English subtitles are available]
[Love Under The Full Moon]
[Episode 14]
[By making reference to the back mountain,]
[the search within a radius
of 50 kilometres is completed.]
[Chu Xia's location data is not detected.]
[The search took six hours.]
[Chu Xia's location data]
[is not detected.]
[The search took 18 hours.]
Expand the search area.
Continue.
What are you doing?
Mum, don't move!
These are the traps that I set up.
Like I said,
I won't go anywhere today.
Do you want some fruits?
I am not good enough to crack the trap.
If you want, come and get it.
Mum, switch off the TV.
It is irritating me.
In that case, go back to your room.
Darling.
Will you stop throwing the newspapers away?
Even if you tie it up nicely,
it is only worth a few pennies.
Those are old newspapers.
They are taking up space at home.
I remember putting them away.
Why did you bring them out again?
These newspaper
are very meaningful.
Look at this.
There's an article about our neighbour's son
winning an award.
There are a few more,
including the news about
our neighbourhood chess team
taking part in a local competition.
And this...
What is this?
[Important! The top secret of Piggy Tech!]
Piggy Technology?
Chu Xia.
This is a document related to Piggy Tech.
Does it belong to Xuan He?
[Piggy Tech?]
[Important! The top secret of Piggy Tech!]
It's mixed between the old newspapers.
[Is this the document Xuan He is looking for?]
This may hold up something important.
[Xu Wei Yi]
[How strange.]
[This document is not about Piggy Tech.]
[Xu Wei Yi]
[This is Xiao Dong's dad's patent certificate.]
[Why is it in Xuan He's hands?]
[Why did Xuan He]
[hand over Xiao Dong's dad's patent certificate]
[to Piggy Tech?]
[Wait a minute.]
[That means]
Xuan He has
what they need the most.
That means you are a sleeping shareholder.
It seems that
you really trust that friend.
It's just a deal of profit.
It doesn't involve trust or what not.
[So, Xuan He]
[stole Xu Wei Yi's patent]
[and gave it to Piggy Tech.]
[It's true that you have]
[what Piggy Tech wants the most.]
[But they are not after your talents.]
[They want Xu Wei Yi's patent]
[that you stole.]
What should I do?
[Renowned IT genius,]
[According to insiders,]
[Xu Wei Yi's life at stake]
[the renowned genius,]
[Xu Wei Yi who is
a information technology engineer]
[had a heart attack]
[and was sent to the hospital
for emergency treatment.]
[His life is at stake.]
[Xu Wei Yi took part in numerous]
[international software development projects.]
[He is the top in the industry.]
[According to the investigation
conducted by the reporter,]
[Xu Wei Yi's health condition]
[could be a result]
[of him being accused of stealing]
[Piggy Tech's patent.]
What a shame.
A genius has fallen.
No doubt we don't know Xu Wei Yi in person,
but he would rather die than
being wrongly accused.
I'm sure he would never
steal someone else's patent.
If someone
could prove his innocence,
he wouldn't have had suffered from this.
[On that night,]
[about 7.30 p.m.,]
[you left home all of a sudden.]
[Xu Wei Yi]
Finally I know the purpose
the universe made us meet.
It is for me to change the trajectory
so that I can save Xu Wei Yi
and prevent the tragedy from happening.
It's for you.
Dad.
Where is Xu Wei Yi?
According to the news,
he is receiving treatment at Lin Shan Hospital.
All right, got it.
Why did she ruin her own trap?
What is wrong with her?
God knows.
We can ask her when she is back.
[It is 8 p.m.]
[The date is November 18, Friday.]
Hello!
May I know the direction to Lin Shan Hospital?
It's over there.
Thank you.
Hey! Out of the way!
Your phone.
[Lin Shan Hospital]
[Tongcheng University]
[Tongcheng University Back Mountain]
[So, I came to the back mountain]
[because I wanted
to give the patent certificate]
[Tongcheng University Back Mountain]
[to Xu Wei Yi.]
[Lin Shan Hospital]
[The cloud-like logo.]
[Tongcheng University]
[The badge.]
[This is the road sign]
[I saw in my memory.]
[The universe has given me
a second chance.]
[Why did I end up here again?]
[Could it be...]
[Am I still going to...]
[No, it won't happen.]
Chu Xia.
What are you holding?
You lied to me.
Give the document to me!
Stop running!
Stop running, Chu Xia.
Chu Xia!
Chu Xia, stop running.
Don't come any nearer.
Listen to me.
It's not what you think.
[It's the same moon in the memory.]
Give me the document.
[The same move.]
[The same glare.]
[Is it going to...]
Chu Xia!
What is wrong?
I think something has gone wrong
with the circuit.
Seriously?
Why is this happening?
Lei Chu Xia?
When did you come in?
Why are you here?
You should leave first.
Let me talk to her.
On what basis?
Why should I leave?
Leave now.
No.
I will contact you later.
Like I said,
I am not wrong about it.
The load figure is normal.
It's 8.32 a.m.
The pulse energy
is overloaded.
It is abnormal.
My painstaking effort.
My work.
Lei Chu Xia,
I need you.
Say it.
What kind of surprise
did you bring me this time?
I went back to ten years ago.
I found out the truth.
Great.
Tell me the truth.
[Sending to Wang Yi Xin]
[Wang Yi Xin, I want to see you.]
Chu Xia's location data is detected.
Have you found Chu Xia?
Connecting.
The call request is denied.
Turing.
Share Chu Xia's live location to me.
Also, inform Xiao Rui and Yuan Yuan.
We will pick her up.
Got it, Xiao Dong.
[Xu Xiao Dong]
Chu Xia!
I know you are here.
Chu Xia.
Why are you hiding from me?
Chu Xia!
I knew it.
Regardless of the time and space,
the universe has sent you to me.
I have faith that
no matter what happens,
the universe will let us
meet each other again.
I have always had the urge to tell you,
but this is...
the first time I've confessed to you.
Lei Chu Xia.
I like you.
Let's be together.
Tell me the truth.
I went back to the day
when Xu Wei Yi met with the mishap.
It was also the day I fell off the cliff.
I saw everything.
You stole Xu Wei Yi's patent certificate
and passed it to Piggy Tech.
Then, you became
the sleeping shareholder of Piggy Tech.
When Piggy Tech was listed,
you obtained a sum of money.
I guess
the money was used
to set up Cyber Tech.
Due to your greed,
you took an innocent person's life.
You even ruined a family.
Why did you do that?
I asked you the same question before.
What do you mean?
You were the one
who stole Xu Wei Yi's patent certificate.
Fine, since it has happened,
let me tell you
the real truth.
As you know,
my family
is quite high-profile in the city.
In the industry, my dad
is highly respected.
He thinks highly of his son
and he has high hopes
for me.
He wants me to live up to
my name as his son.
So, since young,
I've lived a depressed life.
Then, when I went to the university,
I met you.
You were a cheerful lady.
You lighted up my life.
Soon, we got together
but my dad was totally against our relationship.
[The Resume of Lei Chu Xia]
Not everyone
is qualified to enter our family.
[He said,]
[you were not qualified
to be a part of our family.]
[I was really upset,]
[but I chose you.]
I even cut ties
with my family.
I stayed by your side all the while.
We worked hard together.
I also worked hard to start a business.
What are you trying to say?
At the beginning,
my research objective
was similar to Xu Wei Yi's.
However, I was no match for him.
I lost.
My failure
affected our engagement.
It had never crossed my mind that
[you would seek help from a friend
who worked at Xu Wei Yi's company]
[to steal Xu Wei Yi's patent certificate]
[and sold it to my investor, Piggy Tech.]
You told me back then
you would make sure that I succeed in life.
Why should I believe you?
You can take a look at the document.
On the day Xu Wei Yi's
plagiarism scandal was reported,
all the enterprises that had entered
into an agreement with him
[Piggy Tech sues Xu Wei Yi]
went to his company
[for patent infringement]
to ask for compensation.
His company closed down.
He hid away too.
Then, you finally realized that
it was getting serious.
You were scared.
You went to his company too.
[IT genius, Xu Wei Yi is accused of plagiarism]
[Wei Yi Tech]
But I didn't know him.
That's right.
That's my question to you.
You didn't know him,
but why did you go to his company?
I have the video clip of the news.
You can take a look.
[Wei Yi Tech]
This is the real truth.
[received collective complaints]
The evidence is here.
[from the public]
If you don't believe me,
you may verify it on your own.
How do you justify
the night I fell off the cliff?
On that night,
you found out Xu Wei Yi had passed away.
You blamed yourself for that.
You intended to surrender yourself
with the patent certificate.
Between love and justice,
I chose you.
I couldn't bear to see you
ruining your own life.
[Tongcheng University Back Mountain]
[Tongcheng University]
[Lin Shan Hospital]
[Tongcheng University Back Mountain]
[I chased you to the back mountain.]
[Tongcheng University]
[Lin Shan Hospital]
[Tongcheng University Back Mountain]
[I tried my best to stop you.]
Stop running.
Listen to me.
It's not what you think.
Chu Xia, stop running!
Don't come any nearer.
Don't be foolish.
Chu Xia!
No!
Don't let go!
I can't face Xu Wei Yi.
I can't put you in trouble too.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Chu Xia!
[This is the real truth.]
Chu Xia.
Let the past be the past.
Stop blaming yourself.
How will I face Xiao Dong?
What do you mean?
Xiao Dong is Xu Wei Yi's son.
Lei Chu Xia.
I like you.
Let's be together.
They are over there.
Chu Xia!
You're finally back.
Don't ever leave us again.
I envy you.
Why?
That's something I yearn.
Be careful, don't burn your hands.
Aren't you envious?
Don't do that.
It's between me and my best friend.
Chu Xia.
If you don't feel well,
I can take you to Professor Chen
for a check-up.
Chu Xia.
What is going on?
Why did you
disappear all of a sudden at the back mountain?
Also, where were you the past few days?
We have been looking for you.
You missed out
the tenth anniversary of Summer Time.
Yuan Yuan, stop asking.
All right, I'll stop asking for now.
I went back to ten years ago.
I went to the back mountain
trying to recall my memory.
Then, I felt dizzy.
When I woke up, I was back to ten years ago.
Did you find out how you fell off the cliff?
[Everything]
[happened because of me.]
Then, how did you come back?
I felt dizzy again.
Then, I came back.
I want to go back for a rest.
Sure, let me send you home.
Can I go to your place?
Of course.
-But...
-Chu Xia.
Why don't you go back to your own place?
[Hurry up, persuade Xiao Dong.]
[Do you want me to betray my buddy?]
[Am I that kind of person?]
[Then you don't deserve to be a human.]
[You will be single forever.]
[Got it!]
[Leave it to me.]
Xiao Dong.
Come with me.
No need, you may leave first.
Xiao Dong, let them talk.
-Let's go back. Let's go.
-No need.
-Let's go.
I said, no!
Chu Xia.
No matter what happened to you in the past,
you can always share it with me.
We can face it together.
They are finally gone.
Only two of us here.
Let's have
a talk between best friends.
Chu Xia, what is wrong?
We received the location from Turing
informing us that you were
at Tongcheng University.
When we got there,
we saw you and Xiao Dong hugging each other.
Did he confess to you?
He is quite the romantic.
He confessed to you in public.
He always looks a little sheepish.
I didn't expect him to do that.
Did you say yes?
No.
[Sorry.]
[The number you have dialled]
[is not available.]
[Please try again later.]
[Sending to Zhao Yao Yang]
[Look into Xu Xiao Dong. Do it now.]
Chu Xia.
In the past yen years,
I have been doing a lot of preparation
just in case you came back out of the blue.
In my life,
I never take any chances.
However,
the proof that I collected back then
still comes in handy
after ten years have passed.
I don't get it.
You didn't know Xu Wei Yi ten years ago.
[Piggy Tech sued Xu Wei Yi for patent infringement]
Why were you in his office
on that day?
Open the door, Wang Yi Xin!
It's you again.
I have told you everything.
It's up to you to believe it or not.
I believe you.
I saw Lei Chu Xia
appearing out of nowhere.
What?
Appearing out of nowhere?
Yes.
When did that happen?
Where?
It happened this morning.
At Wei Xuan He's place,
she appeared out of nowhere.
In the morning?
The machine overloaded this morning.
The energy in Lei Chu Xia's body
is connected to the energy that I collected.
I have succeeded.
I have succeeded!
Wang Yi Xin, tell me!
What is going on?
Ask Wei Xuan He!
Stop bugging me!
You were the one
who stole Xu Wei Yi's patent certificate.
[No doubt we don't know Xu Wei Yi in person]
but he would rather die
than being wrongly accused.
I'm sure he would never
steal someone else's patent.
[You sought help from a friend
who worked at Xu Wei Yi's company]
[to steal Xu Wei Yi's patent certificate.]
I can't face Xu Wei Yi.
I can't put you in trouble too.
It's a life.
Let go.
Don't let go!
Let go of me!
Hello, Chu Xia.
Dr. Tian Yu.
I would like to be hypnotised again.
The sooner, the better.
The interval between two hypnoses
is too short.
I worry that it will cause a negative impact
[to your mental health.]
[If you insist,]
you have to be accompanied
by family or friends.
Sure, I will take someone with me.
[Wei Xuan He, Xu Xiao Dong, Yuan Yuan]
Hello, Chu Xia?
Sure, I'm coming.
Xuan He, I need to talk to you.
We can talk later.
I need to attend to something.
Xuan He!
By the way, with regards to Lei Chu Xia,
don't tell anyone about it.
Don't interfere in it too.
Are you going to see Lei Chu Xia again?
[I like you.]
[Let's be together.]
[No matter what happened to you in the past,]
[we can face it together.]
[Xiao Rui]
Hello.
Hello, Xiao Dong.
Yuan Yuan said that
Chu Xia has gone to Dr. Tian Yu's clinic.
She is quite upset.
Do you want to check on her?
Okay, got it.
Chu Xia.
If you force yourself too hard
to recall the memory,
it will wear you out.
Have you made up your mind?
I must recall
the ins and outs of the incident.
I must find the evidence
of the crime that I committed
to prove Xu Wei Yi's innocence.
Chu Xia!
♫ Set the aperture of the lens to the maximum ♫
♫ Take a candid shot
when you accidentally turn around ♫
♫ Missing you under the moonlight ♫
Let's go.
♫ Can you hear me whispering? ♫
[Silver Secret]
♫ Meeting and parting happen in an instant ♫
♫ How big is the universe that when we blink ♫
♫ We might never meet again? ♫
♫ How do we spend the summer? ♫
♫ Who will watch the coastline with me? ♫
♫ How do we spend the winter? ♫
♫ How to put an uneasy heart to sleep? ♫
♫ Which autumn night ♫
♫ Is the time for me to wait for you? ♫
♫ Though you're in my heart ♫
♫ You're far away like the galaxy ♫
♫ I can't see you ♫
♫ The longer I have not seen you ♫
♫ The more I long to see you ♫
♫ Those who missed out
on each other will meet again ♫
♫ When will the full moon be here again? ♫
♫ I have missed out on you
and I want to meet you again ♫
[Qin Yue]
I can feel that
you are not in the right condition.
Are you troubled?
It's nothing.
It's okay.
We will try it again.
-Stay relaxed.
-I'm sorry, Dr. Tian.
Don't worry.
Did it go smoothly?
It's okay.
Don't force yourself.
Take your time.
Let me send you off.
Dr. Tian.
Can I borrow an umbrella?
Sure.
[Silver Secret]
Let's go.
Your hand is burning.
Are you having a fever?
Chu Xia.
I...
Xu Xiao Dong!
Let me know when it is almost done.
Sure, thank you.
Don't worry.
I have always been in good health.
This is an exception.
Are you really okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Do you need a check-up?
-It's okay.
-I will eat it only if you remove the skin.
You are so hard to please.
Perhaps I will feel better after eating fruits.
Let me get you some fruits.
Chu Xia.
I don't mean that.
Why is your hand so cold?
While receiving IV drip,
my hand naturally cools down.
Chu Xia.
For some unknown reason,
this time round, when I see you,
you are very close to me,
but I can't help but feel that
you are so far away.
Did you experience something bad?
Don't worry, just share it with me.
I am always here.
The doctor said that
you have to stay in the hospital today.
Take a good rest.
Hey,
is it a good idea
to leave Chu Xia alone at the hospital
to take care of Xu Xiao Dong?
What if something happens to Xu Xiao Dong?
Chu Xia won't be able to handle it alone.
Now,
we need to let them spend some time alone.
Don't worry.
Xiao Dong is taken care by Chu Xia.
He will recover in no time.
What do you think?
My love hack
is something, right?
What kind of
love hack is that?
It is all
because of your foolish idea!
You were the one
who told me to come out with some ideas.
Now, you put the blame on me.
All right.
Let me show you some love.
It's my fault.
I won't hit you so hard next time.
I am not angry anymore.
After all, you are my girlfriend.
I am not your girlfriend.
Yuan Yuan.
Here is a riddle.
Riddle?
Superman is a member of the Justice League.
Iron Man is on the Avengers.
Do you know what league are we in?
What league are we in?
What league is that?
The "Forever League".
What do you think?
I learned it from the internet.
Goodness.
I didn't know that
you came prepared with that old school pun.
What are you doing?
Will you learn something better
from the internet?
Don't you feel sorry after hitting me?
Why should I feel sorry?
I'm heartless.
Of course it won't hurt.
Are you sure you are not sorry?
Fine, I got it.
What do you know?
Are you angry?
No, I am not.
Are you really angry at me?
I was just kidding.
I am not angry.
Are you sure you are not angry?
It is my bad.
I was just kidding.
Look, I am so adorable.
Don't be mad at me.
I am sorry.
Kiss me
and I won't be angry at you anymore.
I want you to kiss me.
All right, it's a deal.
You will stop being angry after I kiss you.
Chu Xia, you are back!
Sorry to interrupt.