I'm sorry.
What about you?
He hasn't replied to me for the past two weeks.
He's been busy at school.
Do you know these young people?
They talk about dancing,
do this and that.
I rarely see them.
He has his own life.
They are like strangers.
Be a father.
Be more proactive.
Take more care of him.
I understand.
YoYo English Channel YouTube
Daddy.
Let me go.
Help.
Duan Shao Zeng.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Today's situation is special.
For safety,
Mr. Gong will wait on the boat.
When he gets the body,
he will go on the boat immediately.
You and I can't afford it.
I know.
Excuse me.
Is there a boat going to Longwei?
What's going on today?
So many people are going to Longwei.
Has anyone been there?
What does he look like?
How many people?
Three men.
They are as private as you.
They said they were going to find a daughter.
Is it Ah Ji and Rima?
When did they go out?
They went for an hour.
I don't know what they want to do.
Keep doing what you should do.
You...
Dan Di.
Are you okay?
Come.
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Take your daughter.
Okay.
That way.
Go.
Two people died today.
Su Lian Yu
and Li Yi VerApplause
He just left us.
Look.
He ran away without a sound.
This isれて cumulative.
It's the first time for him to hear Bang's story.
No one backs him up again.
Therefore, he ran away this day.
Madam,
I beg you.
Let me call him first.
Fill the form,
then he'll check it after he gets permission.
Just one minute.
If you're still staying silent on this issue,
you can't prove you guys were related by blood.
How do I know what you're doing?
I have a right to promise.
Madam.
Madam!
This case,
from a car accident,
to the discovery of human organs,
to the company,
it seems like they are training young people to be stars.
In fact,
they are trying to trick them into doing human organs business.
They have a very detailed deployment.
They also have a complete criminal system.
It also involves medical staff.
We have officially arrested
Dr. Zeng, Zeng Qing Shu,
and his male assistant Chen Jing Hui.
They have severely violated professional practices
and are suspected of participating in human organs business.
Dr. Zeng admitted to being the one who was drunk and hurt in 2018.
It was Ricky who took the initiative to find someone to help him.
From that moment on,
he has been helping Ricky.
The guards on the island
are all the victims and Ricky's men that were discovered before.
They have committed murder,
illegal imprisonment,
and hurt people.
I have already called the students in the training camp to record a statement.
They are all willing to testify against these bad people.
Good job.
This mission
has broken the first human organ business
in Hong Kong for some time.
I also want to thank
ICAC and the deputy executive officer Liu Yu Fan.
They have helped me a lot.
You can handle all the departments.
I didn't see the wrong person.
Thank you, sir.
Also,
I think I have a reasonable reason
for these cases
to be suspected of being related to Qian Feng Group.
Is that so?
Xu Si Si's case
is not related to the case of the criminal.
This time,
a wanted criminal was escaped.
This time, I met him on the island.
I think it's definitely not a coincidence.
I know you
never let go of Xu Si Si's case.
But we are police.
We should be very careful
to suspect everything without evidence.
Yes, sir.
Thank you this time.
You want to thank me?
In the future, when the case of the legal and legal justice case is sued,
don't take the case so tightly.
Of course you want to be more relaxed.
You don't follow the rules.
Will the staff die later?
If you wait one more minute,
you can't save people.
Will you wait?
Doctor, how is my daughter?
She has poor nutrition
and a wound inflammation.
And she has a kidney defect.
Let her rest more.
Take time to recuperate.
Then, turn to a gynecologist
to deal with the scars on her body.
Thank you.
She is her father.
You are her mother.
How is it?
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
I'm sorry.
I didn't take good care of you.
Daddy.
I trusted those people
because I thought I could go to Korea.
That's why I'm like this.
Then,
don't blame yourself.
You are a victim.
You are harmed.
Do you know?
Anyway,
promise daddy
to come back and live with me.
With daddy here,
no one will bully you again.
I thought you wouldn't come to me.
After I was taken away,
I was so scared and regretful.
I didn't talk to you
or talk to you.
I thought you would be angry with me
and wouldn't come to me.
Silly girl.
Why didn't daddy come to you?
No matter where you are,
daddy will come to you.
Do you know?
Since mommy left,
you often just work
and take me to school.
I thought you didn't want to see me again.
Daddy sent you to study
because he didn't want you
to think about it at home.
Why didn't daddy want to see you?
I'm sorry.
After mommy left,
I was so ignorant.
You only know to blame you.
I never asked you how you were.
I never asked you if you were good or bad.
When I grow up,
I feel strong.
I want to prove to you
that I can take care of myself.
But I was wrong.
I'm really so inhuman.
Since mommy left,
I thought I wouldn't mention the past.
That's the best for you.
But I was wrong.
I didn't know you at all.
I didn't know what you like.
I didn't know what kind of friend you knew.
Even if daddy wanted to see you,
I didn't do anything.
But anyway,
I never blamed you.
As long as you're doing well,
I'm relieved.
You're here.
What's wrong?
Let me see.
Nothing wrong, right?
I'm fine.
But I don't know
if I got a little bit of heat
and sunstroke on the island yesterday.
Since you're not feeling well,
take a break.
I...
I'm fine.
Take a break.
I'll make you something to eat.
I'll call you when I'm done.
Okay.
Are you sitting here?
I slept for too long.
I want to sit for a while.
Then,
you're not feeling well
because you ate lightly today.
You don't have a choice.
It's okay.
I'll eat whatever you make.
Done.
Then,
enjoy yourself.
Hey, you're leaving?
I'm leaving.
Why are you still here?
Bye.
Wait.
It tastes weird.
Weird?
How come?
I've always done this.
No.
Did you turn the sugar and salt upside down?
You think I'm you?
If you don't believe me,
come and try it yourself.
No way.
It should be fine.
Try it yourself.
This?
Here.
Try it.
It's fine.
Really?
It's fine?
Maybe I made a mistake.
Eat.
Actually,
are you pretending to be sick?
Pretending to be sick?
No.
We police don't pretend to be sick.
The tomatoes are delicious today.
Let's eat tomatoes.
It's better to eat vitamins than skin.
The emergency meeting this time
is because the police and ICAC
in a joint operation
found the largest number of firearms
in the West Palace's Longwei Province
in the past ten years.
Sam, please report.
We found 20 AK-47s
and 45 modern guns,
60 handguns with 7.62 caliber,
120 handguns
and 100,000 bullets.
According to the latest investigation,
these firearms were exported from
Southeast Asia and transferred by the central government.
We don't know if the actual use is smuggling
or organizational storage.
In addition,
we found that
the gun lines in the previous shooting case
and the weapons we found this time
were all used by the police.
We suspect that
some of these firearms
have been imported into Hong Kong.
Hong Kong is an international capital.
I don't allow Hong Kong's security
to be threatened.
Especially when the guns are imported,
these crimes that may cause
public safety
may lead to danger.
I hope that
you can cooperate with us
in this case.
We will find out the source
and organization of these firearms
as soon as possible.
We will also find out
the source of these firearms
and organize them behind the scenes.
If necessary,
we will also prepare for it at any time.
Our navy will strengthen the search
and monitor all suspicious items
that are imported.
We will monitor at the entrance
whether there are any suspicious criminals
who entered and left Hong Kong.
We are still investigating
the source and use
of these firearms
that we found this time.
According to the information
that we have mastered,
we have a reason to believe
that some of these firearms
have been imported into Hong Kong.
They may be used as a terrorist attack.
Considering this situation,
we decided to
raise the level of
terrorist threat in Hong Kong
to a high level.
Chief Gao,
we have repaired
Wang Zhen Xiong's phone.
Look, there is a clue.
Dirk, have you found anything?
Chief Gao,
there is a space card
in the phone.
There is nothing in it.
There is only one game in it.
This game
was very popular seven or eight years ago.
It can be said that
it was the earliest
to be used by the government.
There must be
a couple of friends playing with it.
But now it is closed.
Why is it closed
and there are still people playing?
It should be that someone
stole the information
and opened a private house.
You mean
that the government
has been closed
and the people who are playing
are not allowed to play?
You mean
private server?
Yes.
Everyone knows that
our colleagues
have found a batch of
smuggled weapons
through the organ trafficking case.
So I hope that
all units
will start
to search
and gather information
from now on.
Let's catch them first.
This case is not that simple.
I think this batch of weapons
is related to
a huge criminal organization.
We should send people
to investigate along this line.
If there are any more reckless actions,
I'm afraid that
we will call our colleagues
to die again.
That is to say,
the owner of the private server
can approve it.
Who can go in
and play this game?
Just like a private party.
Some people
don't like to play with strangers.
I know Wang Zhixiong.
He doesn't know how to use a computer.
He doesn't know how to play computer games.
Why would he download
a game that no one has ever played?
And why would the server's owner
invite a person
who doesn't play the game
to the party?
This game must have other uses.
But there is one thing
that I have a little objection.
I don't want
Zhou Junjie to be responsible for it.
I know that Zhou Junjie is very capable.
He was the one who found
those missing girls
and broke this
machine business case.
But if all of our police teams
are like him,
is that okay?
There is no discipline in the army.
Why don't we
transfer them to the special forces?
We will all act separately
in the future.
No need to report,
no need to say anything
about the spirit of the group.
The reason why I say this
openly in front of everyone
is because the director
has announced today
that the level of threat
of the terrorist attack
has been raised to a high level.
I hope that all of you
can be safe.
No one will be
led to a crime
because of reckless actions.
And it will lead to
a criminal's death.
Oh, right.
There is also a chat room.
December 27th,
which is the day
when Wang Zhenxiong
goes to court.
All the players
will leave the chat room together.
December 12th,
is the day
when the killer intercepts the witness.
If I'm not wrong,
all the players
in the server are the same age.
If it wasn't for Zhou Junjie,
we wouldn't have found
this batch of firearms.
He was taken back by his life.
Zhou Junjie was brought out by you.
Of course you said so.
Someone wanted to
make up for the mistake.
So,
he gave the information
to him
so that he could
find this batch of firearms.
Or is he really
so unlucky?
He found it for no reason.
I believe
my men are all
capable.
Not by luck.
Speaking of luck,
I think you're the best.
You've broken
the case of 600 million
of drug drug cases in ten years.
The case of the drug king's
thousand-dollar kidnapping.
The case of the sale of the population.
All the big cases
were broken by you.
How could it be so coincidental?
It's the same as
what happened to Zhou Junjie.
Shut up.
Is this how you talk to me?
Sorry, sir.
Wang Zhenxiong took advantage
and leaked the witness location.
I believe it's not a single case.
There must be other police
involved.
Even the senior officers of the police.
What do you mean by
showing me these?
I believe it's their way
to communicate with each other
and to explain the task.
So I officially
apply for a case investigation
of this large-scale
police corruption group.
First of all, thank you
for your appreciation
for coming to my party.
I've served the police for 34 years.
I've also experienced
the times of three major thieves.
Now,
the whole of Hong Kong
has stabilized.
Sometimes I ask,
whether Hong Kong citizens
still need police?
I finally figured it out.
The existence of the police
is not for the crime,
but for the citizens.
I'm not a criminal.
I'm a criminal.
Our ultimate goal
is not to arrest people,
but to prevent the crime from happening.
So I really hope
that the police can continue
to play this role.
This is the best protection
for the citizens.
Sir,
congratulations on your retirement.
On behalf of all colleagues,
thank you for leading us for four years.
Thank you, Aki.
Aki,
Lei Xue Sen and Ouyang Jun
are the best in the same class.
I can't tell
who is better as your successor.
Only this can be done.
Sam is from the front line.
He often rushes to the front line.
He has a battle plan and a reputation.
All colleagues like him.
Ouyang is a police officer.
He knows how to deal with
internal and external affairs.
Especially,
he has political skills.
The next four to six years
will be yours.
Who do you think can help you?
If it's a big deal,
Ouyang is more suitable.
You don't think Ouyang
used to follow you in the O.G.
Everyone was born and raised,
and had revolutionary emotions.
That's why you chose him, right?
More or less,
I have some feelings.
It's rational to discuss
which one is the best.
Come in.
Director.
Ouyang, what's up?
About the personnel's transfer,
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
I want to ask why
I only transferred from the Department of Forms to the Department of Personnel.
But Lei Xue Sen,
he was promoted to SACP so quickly.
This is what the former director meant.
I'm just doing it for him.
Has the personnel selection been decided?
Not yet.
But
everyone seems to know what it means.
SACP
is temporarily one of the positions.
Sam has a lot of experience in the frontline.
So I temporarily transferred him to the Department of Action.
When the other SACP retire,
it's your turn.
Lei Xue Sen is the fastest
to be promoted to SACP in our same period.
That means he has been selected.
I haven't even been in the position.
You're just saying that?
And I only retired for four years.
How can I be so fast?
Actually,
not only you and him,
but also others in the police force
are very competitive.
Yes.
Maybe you and him will be the ones to be competitive.
So during this period,
you should show your ability.
Now you're transferred to the Department of Personnel,
it depends on whether you're suitable to be a civil official.
Do your best, okay?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're still saying nothing?
You're just looking at the watch.
You're so passionate.
You know such an old-fashioned word.
You're called a heroine.
Of course I know. I learned it from the TV.
You shouldn't be so careless.
Here you are.
Congratulations.
Aunt Ren Ren Chu, I miss you so much.
Me too.
This room will be yours from now on.
I'll clean it up for you.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Is it really okay
to move in with her?
Annie has grown up.
If she moves out,
I can't be the one to decide.
But you'll still worry about her.
How can I not worry?
Especially when such a big thing happens.
But I've learned it.
Now she has her own world.
I also have to learn how to let go.
I've thought about it too.
Don't think about the past.
Start over.
Why are you staring at me like that?
I'm afraid you're drunk.
I haven't drunk for eight years.
I can't get drunk with such a little thing.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
If I couldn't have signed the lawsuit for you,
you wouldn't have wasted eight years.
Maybe you're a famous architect now.
Maybe you have a very happy family.
You have a very good life.
Listen.
You've never been sorry to me.
For eight years,
you've been the only one who believed in me, helped me.
You've been trying to help me catch Dai Zu Fu and Gong You Cheng.
Actually, I've been the one who dragged you down.
I really want to help you.
I know it the most now.
I know who is really good to me.
I thank you.
Thank you for the past eight years.
I'm afraid you haven't given up on me.
The End
There's a deserted house on the island.
There's a lot of military supplies there.
I don't know what it's for now.
Is it for selling?
It's not popular now.
It's not profitable.
Is it free?
Free?
It's enough for such a large number of soldiers to fight.
It's better to check it out in person.
Lin, check if there's a registered owner of this abandoned house.
Yes.
Black Bull and Brother Qiang, go to the sea near this area.
Ask the boatman if he has seen suspicious people or goods that have been moved to the island.
Yes, sir.
Gennan, Zhu Zai, you go to the dock.
Check the surveillance.
See if there's anything.
Yes, sir.
If you understand, do it.
Wang, come to my room.
I need to talk to you.
Zhe San, what can I do for you?
Sit down.
Have you heard of this plan?
Yes.
I think you should get promoted.
Try it.
Actually, I've reported it many times.
Either there's no recommended person or there's no competition.
I know you have a blood-sucking obstacle.
I've thought about it.
This is a past topic.
Do it again.
Then I'll take you to the mock interview.
If you can't, you can try.
Zhe San, thank you.
But who can be recommended by me?
Only those who have more than SP can be recommended.
I've done all the work for you.
Check it yourself.
Thank you, sir.
Hello, welcome.
Hello.
Hi.
You're so energetic.
Yes.
I started dancing a few days ago.
So good.
You have to work harder.
We all think you can go to Korea to debut.
Thank you.
Hi.
This is Aunt Rachel.
Hello, I'm Ah Jie.
This is my wife Tina.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Ah Jie.
This is my wife Tina.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Jenny.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Everyone is here.
Why are you all standing here?
Let's go in and sit down.
Give me some more time.
It should be done soon.
Still waiting?
Daddy, have you really learned from the British chef?
I prepared some good things for everyone.
So I spent more time.
Family master.
What do you want to do for us?
Wellington steak.
A steak.
This is my specialty.
I used to work in the Western restaurant.
Really?
I am too.
I also learned from the foreign chef.
Really?
How about this?
Ladies, sit there and wait for the meal.
The three of us will be responsible for this meal.
Okay?
It's settled.
Do you want to open it or break it?
I don't know.
Your mushrooms are also in the water.
Raymond, didn't you say you learned from the chef?
Now it's a beef steak.
Not a fried steak.
Congratulations.
Cheers.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, you finally got into SAC.
Thank you.
This gift is for you and me.
Don't worry, it's not more than 3000 yuan.
Don't worry about being arrested.
Okay.
It's beautiful. It suits me.
Thank you.
It suits you.
In the future, when you investigate big cases,
you should take good care of it.
I just got in.
Assistant investigation director.
When can I get into that big case?
You're smart.
You'll be there soon.
I want to ask you something.
I'm supervising a construction project.
I think there's something wrong.
Some workers say the architecture is wrong.
Did you report to your boss?
I'm going to see it tomorrow.
Maybe your boss found a problem supplier.
How about this?
Give me the information.
I'll report to my boss and open the case for you.
If you open the case,
it's not your first case.
Right.
You can pay for it.
No problem.
I'll pay for it.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I don't want to go to court.
Can we settle it outside?
No.
If we settle it,
you'll be a label forever.
And you're a plaintiff now.
You can't be a defendant.
Don't worry.
We'll help you.
And I believe the court
will give a fair trial.
I'm counting on you.
I'll stick to it.
What's wrong?
Is there a problem with the last account?
We found the latest
installation contract
in the bank
with the Business Investigation Department.
Installation contract?
Didn't we get a copy?
That one is old.
This one is the latest.
What?
It's impossible.
This contract
was signed by Gong Youcheng.
How can it be signed by Richo now?
If the file is sent to the court,
it will be written as
the short-term witness is Richo.
I know.
What can it be?
The report is Richo.
This is a false witness.
You can't find out
who framed Richo.
And you're here to submit the file?
I made it up.
I asked someone to identify it.
They said it was Richo.
I'm not sure.
I asked someone to identify it.
They said it was the contract.
It's true.
I asked the witness to confirm it.
What can he do
if he changes his statement?
I said I would give up the case
and not sue Gong Youcheng.
Change it to sue Richo?
The charge of this case
is established.
The charge is established.
It will be in jail for eight years.
Forget it.
It's been eight years.
I think it's time to let it go.
By the way,
are you developing with Jenny?
She's pretty good.
Richo,
Raymond told me
you used to do architecture.
I have a friend
who opened a new architecture company
and asked me to hire him.
Are you interested?
Thank you.
But I really don't want to do
anything related to architecture.
I'm interested in cooking.
A friend has already
found me a job
and worked in a restaurant.
It's good to change the environment.
I'm so hungry.
Can they really
do it in the kitchen?
Don't worry.
Choser said they would definitely do it.
I guess they will
give us some food.
Do it again.
Do it again?
It's already late.
It doesn't mean it tastes good
if it doesn't have a good appearance.
Men's business
is best done
by saying and doing.
Do it again.
I can't do it without faith.
This time,
you don't have to work.
You do the work.
I'll do the work.
But I think
she really wants to get back together.
Then hurry up.
Save the last chance.
That's true.
Just understand some things in your heart.
Don't say it out.
Help her do it.
It's really good.
I told you
I learned it from the chef.
Awesome.
Before eating,
I really want to thank you
for coming tonight.
And thank you
for helping me so much
when I was missing.
You saved my life.
I'm so grateful.
You're welcome.
Come on.
Try the dishes we cooked.
Okay.
Wait.
Huilin's food is so good.
I'm so happy.
Wait.
The essence of Huilin steak
is the cut part.
I'll share it with everyone.
Wait.
What's wrong?
The essence is the essence.
I want to take a picture before eating.
Okay.
Take the camera.
This one?
Yes.
Okay, let's sit closer.
Okay.
Look at the camera.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
And you.
Yes, you.
I'll take a picture too.
Wait.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
I'm so hungry.
Let's eat.
You're so big.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Hurry up.
Don't show your essence.
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Drive home safely.
Bye.
Jianing.
I have something to tell you.
I went to Rongji.
I know you didn't buy the soup.
You made it.
If you like soup, I can order more.
Thank you for caring about me.
I want to say that
we're just the boss and subordinate.
And this relationship will not change.
Adults
hope it won't affect your work performance.
Good night.
Wait.
I have something to tell you too.
Yes.
I like you.
I know you don't accept me.
But you don't accept me.
It doesn't mean I can't continue to like you.
Don't worry.
I'll keep my professionalism at work.
Good night.
Since the first shooting,
the crime rate has increased by 50%.
If it goes on,
Hong Kong's security will only get worse.
I can only say that it's very timely
and very meansful.
This is a serious matter.
I approve that you can act with guns.
I suggest that we tell the special forces
to use emergency measures to open the surveillance power.
We should be the first to do it.
The season without you by my side
is more obvious
The fallen leaves
are also tired of the wind
Tired of chasing
the perfect world
Who can take me away
Who is at the far end
Who will fight with me for the world
Is there anyone
who guards for me
No need for too many reasons
Light up the fire in the dark
Don't retreat
Smile if you are all around me
Until the end
Is there any remorse
The season without you by my side
is more obvious
The fallen leaves
are also tired of the wind
Tired of chasing
the perfect world
Who can take me away
Who is at the far end
Who will fight with me for the world
Is there anyone
who guards for me
No need for too many reasons
Light up the fire in the dark
Don't retreat
Smile if you are all around me
Until the end
Is there anyone
who guards for me
No need for too many reasons
Light up the fire in the dark
Don't retreat
Smile if you are all around me
Until the end
Is there anyone
who guards for me
No need for too many reasons
Light up the fire in the dark
Don't retreat
Smile if you are all around me
No need for too many reasons
Light up the fire in the dark
Don't retreat
Smile if you are all around me
Until the end