[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
[Episode 9]
-Cheers.
General,
you're good at drinking.
I admire you.
Stop...
Stop swaying.
General,
I must tell you something
from the bottom of my heart.
Look at you.
You're very
young, handsome,
and have a successful career,
but your mansion
is very deserted.
There are only trees
and grasses
without any flowers.
Look at the tiles on the roofs.
People could tell you keep fighting at one glance.
It's not like a home.
If it were my home,
I would plant
rows of cherry trees.
Their petals would fall
after being blown by the wind,
and I would feel very happy.
By the way,
I have a gift for you.
It matches with your sword, doesn't it?
It's pretty.
Come on.
Cheers.
General.
General, you're drunk,
so I'll send you back to your bedroom first.
I'm not drunk.
Not at all.
Let me send you back first.
I must do.
No need.
General.
I've never drunk that much.
Since my childhood,
I've been following the example of my father
and setting strict demands on myself as a general.
I've never gotten relaxed.
Since I was young,
other than my...
my sister,
no one has thought highly of me.
They said I was bad at everything
and always ran away.
But I've changed now
because I make a friend
with you who are very powerful.
If I go back home,
I swear that I'll show off to them.
You're at good at cooking.
I've arrived.
My god.
I'm good at drinking,
but he almost got me drunk,
although it was his first time drinking.
Fortunately, I took hangover medicine in advance.
How could he have such an exquisite sachet
since he doesn't get along with women?
If it wasn't given by his lover,
there must be
a secret in it.
Let me check it
when he's drunk.
General, listen to me. I...
I'm better
at drinking than you.
Let me go.
Well,
I only got an order for stealing,
and I didn't agree to sell myself.
Oh no,
why did I fall asleep?
I'm sure that last night...
Why didn't the hangover medicine work?
Where am I?
What happened?
My god.
I made a mistake after drinking.
Why hasn't she woken up yet?
Why hasn't he woken up yet?
An Chen, why did you oversleep again?
-Because of him.
-Because of her.
Just pretend that I didn't see anything.
Vice General Xiao
won't say it out, will he?
My soldiers
can keep the secret.
An Chen and General...
General, listen to me.
I'm used to shouting when training the soldiers,
so when I faced that situation...
Shut up.
Do the Horse Stance in the yard for an hour.
Reflect on yourself.
Yes.
Wait.
How about the mission I asked you to do?
I wanted to report to you today.
The PE class
has been experimented officially
in the schools of the city.
Besides,
you've mentioned to enhance
the physical training on the soldiers in the mansion.
And this is the list
of those who have poor physical
capability.
Our Lie family won't keep weak soldiers,
so train them as soon as possible.
If you fail...
I'll kill myself to apologize.
General,
there is another thing.
Mr. Jiang came to you this morning.
Qi?
Right.
Yesterday, we made an agreement to play chess today.
Should I
go to invite Mr. Jiang now?
Forget it.
I'll go to him in person
after I finish dealing with military affairs.
How many people
heard that thing this morning?
This morning?
Do you mean the thing happened
between you and An Chen?
Don't worry.
The servants in the mansion
are tight-lipped.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I promise.