[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
[Episode 29]
I'm the Second Prince
of Southern Jiang,
the future Southern Emperor.
If you dare to touch me,
our army will bear down upon the border.
Rui Kingdom is weak.
Without Lie Yun,
how many days can you last?
Lie Yun had guarded the border for years,
but tens of thousands of people he protected
would die because of your
impulsive move.
Kill me.
Kill me!
Seeing you miserable
is better for venting my hatred
than killing you.
Only that without you,
I feel a bit lonely on the battlefield.
Don't worry.
I'm faithful in word.
[Rest]
The Anhun Token
has been removed.
[Memorial]
You're free now.
Live well
in guilt
and agony.
[Dingnan General's Mansion]
A brilliant general passed away.
What a shame.
Your Highness, your clever strategy
has eliminated such an
important enemy for our country.
Since Lie Yun
is dead,
Your Highness,
you'll soon conquer Rui Kingdom
and inherit the throne.
[Dingnan General's Mansion]
Give my orders.
Lie Yun's death is confirmed.
Carry out the plan.
Yes!
[Pastry]
Lie Yun, you're back!
Finally...
Miss, you made a mistake.
You want to see me?
Is An Chen
still miserable?
Yes.
We couldn't console her.
She's always stubborn.
When she comes round in a few days,
she'll get better.
Now that the Death Token has been removed,
I have to report to the Pavilion.
Please take
good care of An Chen.
Don't worry.
It's my job.
Lie Yun has just passed away.
You must be sad.
Get more rest,
and don't spoil your health.
If you need anything,
send a message to...
I mean,
if An Chen needs anything,
send a message to me by pigeon.
I'll reply you
as soon as I get the message.
OK.
I get it.
It's my honor
to have you
here today.
Here,
let me drink to you first.
Come on.
Make presentations.
Let me see
what you've got.
How dare you!
You dare offend His Highness!
It doesn't matter.
I've practiced archery since childhood.
I can see hundreds of miles away
and I never miss a shot.
It's my pleasure to work for Your Highness.
You can release such great internal power with the bow alone.
You're a real master.
Sit.
Thanks, Your Highness.
I have no
particular skills
other than making
explosives.
Sir, would you please
try this?
Great!
I'm an iron man.
My body
is as hard as steel
and can resist blades and swords.
I'm willing to
serve
Your Highness.
Good.
With your help,
victory is
within reach.
Someone!
Reward!
Thanks, Your Highness.
Imperial edict.
Xiang Yao, the Second Prince,
accept the edict!
You are dismissed.
Yes.
His Majesty
orders
Xiang Yao, the Second Prince,
to set off
to the border on this date.
In one month,
he must capture Rui Kingdom.
Any mistakes
in the battle,
Xiang Yao
shall be held solely responsible.
Prevarication isn't allowed.
That's all.
Orders taken!
Congratulations to Your Highness
on acquiring the Deployment Map
and getting a chance
to lead troops to the battle.
If you
win the battle,
you'll have a chance
to get His Majesty's special attention.
If you lose,
I'm afraid
you can never leave
the Venom Moon Sect.
Your Highness,
please take care.
Rest assured.
I must
complete the task.
Your Highness, don't be angry.
He's a stooge of the Crown Prince.
It's not worth getting angry with him.
Who the hell is he?
He doesn't deserve me to be angry with him.