[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
In the second year of Tianyao,
[Xishuang Kingdom, Anhun Pavilion, Southern Jiang Kingdom, Eastern Rui Kingdom]
General Lie Yun defeated the invading army in Southern Jiang
and returned in triumph with Deployment Map, his family heirloom,
making his name famous throughout the world.
Meanwhile,
Anhun Pavilion, a ganghood force, was offered with award
to send the top master to sound out Lie Yun's weakness,
seeking chances to steal the Lie family's Deployment Map.
[Episode 1]
Here comes Dingnan General!
Open the gate!
[The Capital of Rui]
General lost his mother at a very young age.
He took over the chief commander of the Lie's Army
at the age of 12 when his father was killed,
and devoted himself to military camp for guarding the border till now,
[Lie Yun, Dingnan General]
which made him the key stand of the Rui Kingdom.
Great!
[An Chen, the First Thief of the Anhun Pavilion]
Where are my melon seeds?
And my wine?
Who steals my chestnut?
-Wow, what a cute guy!
-What are you looking at?
He just gets his face rouged,
unlike me.
I never wear make-up.
General Lie is a superb fighter
with both skill and dash.
He's resolute when killing the enemies,
[The Capital of Rui]
who trembled with fear on hearing of his name.
Well,
rumor has it that
General Lie grew up in the army
with a queer temper,
which is why it's said
he keeps women away.
General, how are you doing?
I'm fine.
I've invited Mr. Jiang
for a visit to the mansion to work out the antidote.
It's all my fault.
[Xiao Tong, Vice General]
If it wasn't for saving me,
you wouldn't have suffered from insect poison by the witch of Southern Jiang
and got yourself battered.
I'm so sorry.
No need to blame yourself.
As your brother,
I'm supposed to get you covered.
Let's check what I've got today.
[Anhun Token. Steal the Deployment Map in Dingnan General's Mansion in a month.]
I can be free
and come back home to raise crops
once I finish the last mission.
Where is my wine?
Where is it?
Are you looking for this?
An...
An Mei,
what brings you here?
Says the person who stealthily put croton seed in my food
that made me suffer from diarrhea for three days
[An Mei, an assassin in Anhun Pavilion]
and stole away my Board Token.
What do you think why I'm here?
Mei,
it's a misunderstanding.
How can you think of me in that way?
Look at you.
Slim and pretty.
Do you have any idea what I've been through in the three days?
Cut the crap!
Give me the Board Token.
Mei,
leave the mission to me, please.
I'll be free once I get it done.
And I can be promoted to the hall leader.
Winning freedom
and coming back home for farming are my dreams.
Mine is being the hall leader of the Dripping Hall.
No more nonsense.
Give the Board Token to me.
Well, then.
[Anhun Token]
I knew you'd play dirty.
I can play more than that.
An Chen,
you're dead!
General Lie!
Lie Yun!
General Lie, I'm here!
Hello, everyone.
Lie Yun!
[I won't marry anyone but you.]
General Lie!
Hello, guys.
It makes sense.
General Lie's a real knock-out.
Unfortunately,
General Lie's not interested in women.
Where are there so many women?
Something's wrong.
Speed up.
Yes!
Lie Yun, I'm your die-hard fan!
Lie Yun, I love you!
Xiao Tong,
stop them!
Lie Yun!
General!
Stop them!
Oh, no.
The poison is showing effect.
General, run!
Mei, knock it off.
The target's coming.
I'm serious.
I'm not done with you until I get the Board Token.
Mei,
we grow up together.
Can't you give it to me?
I just want the Board Token.
Save your words!
This is not negotiable, is it?
You stole my stuff.
Of course, it's not negotiable.
-General Lie is here.
-General.
Run!
General Lie is here!
Xiao Tong!
Stop them!
General Lie!
General Lie, I love you!
General Lie, General Lie!
Wait.
Mei,
Look!
My face!
[Lie Yun, I love you.]
Rich guy.
General,
are you alright?
General.
He's my target.
Summon our men back to the mansion, now!
Yes.
You think you can get away?
Protect General!
What are you doing?
Don't worry, general.
You'll be safe
with me here.
Then are you supposed to turn around?
By the way,
get your hands off my waist.
I'll go get the assassin.
General!
Forget it.
Let's head back to the mansion.
[Dingnan General's Mansion]
I can't believe I, the top thief of Anhun Pavilion
failed this time.
It must be his good look that sets me back.