[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
[Episode 21]
When I just came here,
you always made fun of me
and forced me to work early in the morning.
I was so angry and afraid of you.
But gradually,
the more you did that to me
the more I wanted to get near you.
In fact,
I've had a crush on you for a long time.
But I was worried
that you may dislike me
after knowing my identity.
I kept telling myself not to like you
until
you gave me your most precious sachet.
You told me
that I'm not a speck of mote.
Then I told myself
that I could no longer hide myself.
Lie Yun,
meeting you
costs all my lucks.
I want to tell you
I like you.
I like you very much.
I like you very very much.
♫I like nerve-calming tea♫
♫Aromatic herbs♫
♫More than a high ranking♫
♫More than having gold♫
♫Being a woman♫
♫Dressed as a man♫
♫Love wine of Rui♫
♫And tulips♫
♫In General's Mansion ♫
♫With clouds and dust♫
♫We look at each other♫
♫Holding hands as refined steel♫
♫Through the glazed window♫
♫In candlelight♫
♫We appreciate the scene together♫
♫It's hard to hide my feelings♫
♫I can't help loving you♫
♫Our hair is tied together♫
♫General, please keep it♫
You two
are becoming harder to be trained.
I told you to run laps at the training site.
But look at yourselves.
General,
I assure you
that I will well train them.
Come on.
Go.
Yun,
you're so handsome.
An Chen,
An Chen.
I'm coming.
Vice General Xiao,
Did General send you here?
No.
It's me.
I'm coming for personal affairs.
I know I'm beautiful and striking.
But,
I've fallen in love with General.
So, I'm sorry.
No kidding.
General would punish me.
I'm kidding.
Don't be angry.
Let's go.
Come on,
what is it?
Is this your senior sister's?
It's An Mei's favorite bracelet.
You're going to die.
You broke her bracelet.
She will kill you.
An Chen,
can you tell me
what An Mei likes
and what she dislikes?
Do you
also have a crush on An Mei?
Crush?
I don't think so.
Are there many men liking her?
If they stand in line from east to west of the town
in snake shape,
there would be eight lines.
You are
too ugly
and too stupid.
You have no chance.
Well,
you may not tell me about her.
But how can you insult me?
I didn't say no.
Tell you what?
My senior sister
likes jewelry,
gold,
silver,
jade
and diamond.
The more valuable
the better.
General.
What's the matter?
You've been wandering all morning.
I'm counting my savings.
Why?
Do you need money?
No.
I
just want to buy a bracelet.
What do you need a bracelet?
An Chen told me
that all girls like beautiful jewelry.
What else did she say?
She also mentioned gold,
silver,
valuable stones,
and diamond, a kind of stone that can blind the eyes.
Whatever, the more valuable the better.
Oh.
OK.
Let's go.
I need you to do something for me.
Be careful.
Watch your steps.
Don't drop them.
Slowly. Slowly.
Attendant An.
I'm coming.
What's inside this?
It's so heavy.
Shoo.
This
is…
Attendant An,
General said
you'll manage mansion expenses from now on.
Come on. Open these chests.
All these will be taken charge by me?
Am I a rich woman now?
I should go thank God.
Move those inside.
Be careful.
Wipe your mouth drooling with greed.
These are all worldly possessions,
certainly less important than my General.
But
General,
why do you give me these valuable things?
Well,
it's
because of this.
Cramp?
No.
this.
Counting money?
No.
It's falling for you.
Little miser.
Sweet and Sour Fish.
Shoo.
General,
what are you looking for?
Come on.
Help me change my clothes.
Fish.
Sweet and Sour Fish.
A spoonful of salt,
a spoonful of vinegar,
add the heat.