[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
[Episode 19]
I've known Jiang Qi for eight years.
We played chess in Mansion,
and trained soldiers together.
I was wounded many times on the battlefield.
It's him who treated me.
I didn't believe in the saying of hitting it off.
But after chatting with you,
I feel like
you are the one who knows me best in the world.
Long distance
separates no bosom friends.
I'm a free and unrestrained doctor,
longing for seeing great mountains and rivers.
General Lie,
you shoulder great responsibilities.
I couldn't stay here forever.
When you're back,
I'll surely treat you with good wine.
Mr. Jiang,
you go first.
Qi.
Are you okay?
It's poisoned.
General.
Doctor,
how is he?
His life is saved,
but I could do nothing
about his legs.
What do you mean?
You must save his legs. It's an order.
General,
I know my own condition.
About my legs,
there is nothing I could do.
Don't force him to do what he can't.
Qi,
I'm sorry.
it's all my fault.
It's not your fault.
Using my legs
to exchange your safety
is worth it.
I couldn't believe
that he is the spy from Southern Jiang.
The one I took as a brother
turns out to be the traitor who hurts me the hardest.
He fooled us all.
I've forgiven you.
Are you
really not mad at me?
How could I still be mad at you?
You risked your life to save me.
That proves everything.
And
more importantly, I've known my heart.
Even in the state of illusion,
I wanted to trust you.
An Chen,
you were on your own before
and suffered a lot.
From now on,
I won't allow anyone
to make you do anything against your will.
You've always wanted this.
It's yours now.
It's the last thing I have from my mother.
It's also what I cherish the most.
I've known for long
that you're a woman.
Kidding and making fun of you
and watching you angry
make me so joyful.
I've been wondering
why you're the only woman I like
and want to get close to.
I feel relaxed
only when I'm with you.
Seeing you smile,
I would smile too.
An Chen,
could you
stay?
Um.
What did you say?
I didn't hear it.
Actually, it doesn't matter where to live.
I'm well-fed and well-treated here.
It's okay to stay here.
Then I must try to
make you feel comfortable here
and reluctant to leave.
General,
you're not recovered yet.
you must take care of your health.
Xiao Tong,
go to the training site and run 20 laps.
Violating the order will get a military punishment.
General,
it's important to rest.
You may have some rest.
I'll come to see you tomorrow.
Look at me.
Can't you stay to take care of me?
Just have some rest.
I'll see you tomorrow.
When you're recovered, we…
Xiao Tong.
I just knew that you're unwilling
to leave me.
[Do Not Disturb]
Vice General Xiao,
what's going on?
Do not disturb.
What's the smell?
It stinks.
What are you doing there?
An Chen,
are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to see you.
Ah, roses.
Yeah.
Roses help relieve depression
and nourish qi and blood.
I could try it.
I'm going back to my room.
[Do Not Disturb]
Does she like me or not?
She just run away.
It's obvious no.
Then, you tell me what liking is.