[English subtitles are available]
[Follow My Dear General]
[Episode 31]
Imperial edict arrives!
Lie Yue, accept the edict!
[Imperial Edict]
Secret orders from His Majesty,
on and after this date,
Dingnan General Lie Yun
is granted the title of Dingnan Marquis.
In three days,
Lie Yun must arrive at the border secretly,
join up with the 100,000 troops of Rui Kingdom,
kill the enemy by surprise,
and exterminate Southern Jiang.
No mistake is allowed.
Orders taken!
Back in the day,
before your father went to the battlefield,
I also read the imperial edict for him.
It's been 10 years already.
General Lie,
I wish you'll defeat the enemy
and return in triumph.
Thank you, Lord Tan.
I'll live up to His Majesty's trust,
defeat the enemy with all strength,
and protect the safety of our country.
Camp here for the night.
Set off around five in the morning.
-Yes.
General.
You've finally
had the life you want.
You can live a
carefree life
in the small courtyard.
Xiao Tong.
General.
There's something wrong.
Lead a team to search around.
Yes.
I cut the mountain.
I built the road.
Anyone who wants to pass,
Leave your toll fee!
Ma'am, you want money.
But I've handed in all my money.
I have nothing to leave.
What should I do?
Then you have to leave me.
Are you going to dump me?
When did you know I wasn't dead?
The day you asked your father
to bless me with peace and joy.
She lived a
hard life before.
From now on,
I hope she'll be safe and sound.
If I return in triumph,
I will never let her
go again.
If I can't,
I don't want her to be sad again.
So, don't let her know
I'm still alive.
I know
this is
the only way you must pass to go to Southern Jiang.
I know
you don't have the heart to leave me behind.
you're reluctant to part from me.
So I came.
An Chen,
I knew you would do this.
To be free is the dream of your life.
You don't need to risk your life for me.
I've lived
in the house you bought
for me.
I've realized all my wishes.
Now I have a dream.
You said
you would give me anything I wanted.
Does that still count?
I will keep my word.
♫Beautiful music♫
♫Beautiful melody♫
♫Fragrant cherry blossoms♫
My dream is
♫Autumn breeze in yard♫
to realize all your dreams.
♫ Beautiful rain of pedals♫
♫Pray for everlasting love♫
My dream is to
♫Holding hands and looking at each other♫
accompany you through the four seasons,
♫Milky sunset glow♫
and taste the sweets and bitters of life.
♫Rising moon♫
♫Love is proved♫
My dream is that
♫Pray for being together every day♫
we'll never be
separated again.
♫Till the end of time♫
♫Year after year♫
♫Love never changes♫
♫Your arms♫
♫Are what♫
♫I am longing for♫
♫Your dreams♫
♫Are my blueprint♫
♫Cold winter♫
♫Without caring about the time♫
♫Our deep love will last eternally♫
♫You love♫
♫Is my♫
♫Sweet dream♫
♫Stormy whether♫
♫ Flying dust and clouds♫
♫Won't change my heart♫
In this war,
♫Going crazy, laughing and crying with you♫
I'll protect you well.
♫Spending happy time with you♫
When I suppress Southern Jiang,
♫Forever♫
I'll return to the countryside
and live a quiet life with you.
We'll definitely return in triumph.
How can you leave me behind
and have fun in Southern Jiang alone?
An Mei,
why are you here?
Do you want to steal away
without me again?
Don't you remember
I must get even
with Xiang Yao?
What a coincidence.
Why are you here?
Tonight,
which
tent do you pick?
An Mei,
let's sleep in that tent.
Yeah.
Go.
Elder,
In five days at most,
Lie Yun and Xiang Yao
will meet at the border.
[Anhun Pavilion the First Elder]
Hum.
A good play
[End of Season 1]
is going to start.