[English subtitles are available]
[Be My Princess]
[Episode 30]
Why?
You promised me already,
why are you marrying someone else?
I abide by the late Emperor's edict to teach Your Highness,
I have never had other thoughts.
I don't believe that.
If you don't feel anything for me,
then why did you keep the Double Seventh Festival promise?
I have never had affections for Your Highness.
It is my fault
to have given Your Highness the wrong impression.
Wrong impression?
You can tell me that
you have your own pain and difficulties,
or you have to marry someone else.
As long as you admit that
I have indeed lived in your heart once.
[Virtue can give off real fragrance.]
I was born of a humble family.
I wouldn't dare to out-marry Your Highness.
I'm begging Your Highness
to let me go.
You said "to let you go"?
Fine.
Since it was my misunderstanding,
it is not your fault.
Look at me.
I will let you go as you wish,
but I will make you
never forget about me.
I thought I could feel
at least a little sincerity from you by doing this.
Seems like I was wrong.
You really have no feelings for me.
What else do you want me to do, Your Highness?
[Virtue can give off real fragrance.]
Pingxi Royal Highness and I fall for each other.
Grand Tutor,
please report to His Majesty and Empress Dowager that
I'm willing to marry him.
As for the date of marriage,
let's make it the same day
as yours.
In fact,
my first choice is Grand Tutor,
and the second is His Royal Highness.
Since you have already committed to someone else,
I won't impose myself on you.
I won't make it
to your wedding.
I can only congratulate you in advance.
May you have a baby soon.
and I wish for many years of happiness for the two of you.
[Happiness]
-Congratulations, Grand Tutor. -Congratulations, Grand Tutor.
The Chief Cabinet Minister and Her Highness are holding their weddings on the same day.
It is surely a busy day for the capital.
Yes.
So Her Highness's wedding
must be even more luxurious than this, right?
The Chief Cabinet Minister is only below His Majesty.
As for such an important event,
his ceremony may not be inferior to the royal family.
You are right.
There will be a lot to look on today.
Hyah.
Sir, you can't do this.
Your Highness.
Chief Cabinet Minister, have you thought it through?
If you break in any further,
it will be resistance to the edict.
You will be no different from the rebels and traitors.
[Happiness]
Your Highness.
I will take you home.
Sir.
If we miss the propitious time,
what shall we say to His Majesty?
Congratulations, consort.
Congratulations on the joyous union of this happy couple.
Please.
Thank you, consort.
Thank you all for coming to my wedding.
Here, let's have a toast.
Congratulations, consort.
Grand Tutor.
I know
you have feelings for me.
Is this a dream,
or is this real life?
If this is a dream，
I hope
I will never wake up.
[Gengle Pavilion]
[Wolan Pavilion]
I, Mu Yun,
greet Your Highness.
Your Highness.
It's turning cold. Please take care.
Let me help you take on a cloak.
No need. I'm not cold.
Make me some tea.
Leave me alone for a while.
Yes.
[Gengle Pavilion]
Her Highness and consort seem to be happy on the outside,
but actually at variance.
Her Highness must be having a hard time.
Yes. If the late Emperor is still alive,
he must be so distressed
seeing Her Highness going through all this during pregnancy.
[Ten years later]
I didn't know you were here, Your Highness.
Forgive me.
Your Highness.
I can't afford this.
Your Highness, please get up.
The consort was accused of conspiracy.
I am not asking for forgiveness.
But please save my two children.
They are innocent.
Now His Majesty only listens to you.
I have already decided to see His Majesty before going to court tomorrow,
and ask for forgiveness for two lords.
Your Highness, don't worry.
Even if I have to die,
I will protect them.
All that I pursue in life
is to make sure Your Highness
can always be superior,
and never have to bow down to others.
Your Highness, when you knelt down,
you also denied my life-long pursuit.
I failed the late Emperor's trust.
I...
Even death cannot atone for my offense.
Your Highness, please get up.
I will.
Get up too, Grand Tutor.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You have done nothing wrong.
In this world,
no one else can be like you.
You have considered everything for me.
But I
haven't done anything for you,
and even put you in such a situation.
I have no regret
in my life
since I have met you.
How have you been
over these years?
Jin'er died from illness
three months after the wedding.
Later I adopted a son,
and named him Mu Ze.
He is a grown man now.
Does Mu Ze treat you well?
He treats me like his real father.
If everything started all over again,
would you lie to me again?
His Majesty has ordered
to hold me in confinement at the Princess Palace.
I can't get out
from now on.
You...
need to take good care of yourself.
Don't do everything yourself
at this age.
If there's an afterlife,
I wish we wouldn't do each other wrong again,
and could stay together.
If there's an afterlife,
I, Mu Yun, will definitely put everything behind,
only to stay with you
for a lifetime.
Grand Tutor.
Grand Tutor, without His Majesty's order,
you can't break into the palace.
I have to see His Majesty today.
If I let you in, I will die.
Move.
Grand Tutor.
[Hanyuan Palace]
Your Highness.
Your Highness, big trouble.
What happened?
News just came from the Imperial Palace.
His Majesty wouldn't withdraw the edict.
Two lords were already sent to the dead cell.
Tomorrow, between 11 a.m. to 1 p.m., they will be...
They will be...
If he can't persuade His Majesty...
Prepare my zither
and wine for me.
Your Highness.
[Hanyuan Palace]
Because of me,
you lost your title as Chief Cabinet Minister.
Do you regret living an ordinary life with me
in this village, for the rest of your life?
For you,
not only in this life,
but for infinite days and nights,
I'd like to be a countryman willingly,
and will never regret it.