(Keishi) My daughter Yui Yagami➡
In the afternoon of October 28th➡
I was kidnapped.
(Camera shutter sound) Today is the fourth day.
Screen) I hope there is even the slightest clue➡
We have launched a special website➡
We received a lot of information.
(Screen) But still...
(Daisuke) Is this possible?
(Gun) Hachipapa is too funny.
screen) Right now, while I'm doing this➡
I wonder how scared you feel...
(camera shutter sound) screen) (coughs)
Screen) Sorry.
screen) (camera shutter sound)
Screen) Yui.
Screen) Are you having a hard time?
Screen) How are you feeling?
Screen) Did you eat dinner?
Screen) Dad is➡
I'll be waiting for your return.
screen) Then...
Screen) Daisuke Hayashida.
Wow. Screen) Are you watching?
Screen) Please return my daughter.
Screen) This is it.
screen) (camera shutter sound) (sound of tapping on the shoulder)
Celebrity.
Screen) Hayashida-kun.
(Screen) Should I say "Linda-kun"?
(Screen) Can we meet together with Yui?
Did you come like that?
Screen) 4pm on the 3rd day after tomorrow ➡
When Yui was little➡
In the place where we often practiced together➡
I'm waiting.
(Screen) I already know the location.
(Screen) I won't tell the police, and of course I won't tell the media either.
What are you saying, old man?
(Screen) We will also pay you a fee.
Screen) Therefore➡
Please bring Yui.
Screen) Tomorrow all day➡
Please think carefully.
Screen) I'm waiting.
♬～
Screen) I'll be waiting for you at 4pm on the 3rd tomorrow.
(Anna) I wish I was born here.
(Ukai) I understand! Yui-chan I’m jealous!
(Customer) Hey, hey, it's a kidnapping. (Yamaguchi) Sorry to have kept you waiting.
(Sakagami) This is the first time I've ever seen the father directly address the criminal.
That's amazing!
(Ebihara) Let me tell you, Yagami and his son➡
I don't know what will happen to this place of memories!
(Miyazono) Huh? Haven't you been taught?
Yes, I haven't been told that. What is that?
Do you think it can be resolved without the police?
Ah, just let me do what I want! Yeah.
Hachi, do you know where it is?
(Yui) I think it's about Kinuta's dojo.
It was the only place where I practiced Aikido with my father.
Is it a place of memories?
Linda, what should we do? If you take me➡
You won't get caught and you'll get money. Oh?
If I get caught somewhere in the future➡
Linda will go to jail.
I can't rely on Mr. Gunn to help me for the rest of my life.
In that case, I think the best thing to do now is to do as my father says.
Even if the police were there, I would rather keep running away and get caught➡
Wouldn't the punishment be lighter?
I guess that's why you didn't want to go home.
It's just a period of rebellion, isn't it?
Just pretend you're home once.
Once you've calmed down, I'll take a chance and run away by myself next time.
Do you seriously think you can do this?
Don't you get homesick looking at your father's face?
It hasn't happened! That's what happened!
If it hasn't happened, what do you think...! (Riri) Wait, everyone➡
What are you talking about? What?
Wasn't it an elopement?
bad.
I was lying.
Actually, I kidnapped Hachi.
Kidnapping...?
At first, I was supposed to get 300 million in exchange for this guy.
picture…? Sorry for lying.
I wanted to escape, so I used Linda.
So I asked Riri-chan... (Riri) Wait, I don't understand.
You say you don't understand... Huh?
Does that mean the two of you weren't dating?
Yeah.
Is it kidnapping?
At first.
Tell me everything from the beginning.
My ex-boyfriend was a kidnapper and I hid him there without knowing it➡
I had such a fun time and now I'm panicking, Riri-chan.
Huh...
Do you remember Mr. Saito?
president? Big-chan's.
Yeah.
I heard it.
(Saito) What is the escape route?
(Yamaguchi) The cart will become heavier after the kidnapping...
(Saito) When security is weak... What is kidnapping?
(Saito) Were you there? Why did you do that?
I can help you if you tell me the reason.
(Yamaguchi) Don't come in without permission. I don't have any money to give you.
Money is fine, just a little bit. Don't get involved!
Forget everything you just heard.
Well then, before I forget, I'll go to the police. Daisuke!
There must be a very good reason why the old man was kidnapped.
That's why I'm helping you.
(Yamaguchi) Isn't that good? Yamaguchi-kun!
(Yamaguchi) I don't think I'll be able to move even if the police pick on me.
This is it➡
It's revenge.
We had something important stolen from us by Keishi Yagami.
revenge? Did you say that?
ah.
What did my father do?
Old man's daughter➡
Apparently, he died at the age of 4 because of Hachi's father.
picture….
Eh... why?
My father was originally working on drug development with your father➡
At that time, there was still no medicine to cure my daughter's illness.
That's why when you research hard and it's almost ready➡
Your father betrayed you and you're no good.
Why?
I don't know. When was that?
I don't know.
Ah... if I were alive now➡
He said it would be 30 this year.
So before I was born...
Why now? It's been twenty years.
surely.
Don't you know? I helped you with that.
Because the old man was in bad shape➡
If that makes you feel better, just say it.
Isn't that it?
Let's do what we can do now?
In the end, I didn't get any money➡
For some reason, he continues to run away with hostages until now.
It's true...
What is Saito-san doing now?
I don't understand.
On the way, I was found by someone from Hachi's family and I couldn't contact them from there.
Yui-chan.
I didn't ask, but what about your mother?
She died when she gave birth to me.
I see...
Who is your father➡
You had some good memories, right?
Things have changed...
♬～
That's what I thought➡
I wonder if he was originally like that...
♬～
(Bandai) I don't have time.
(Shiraki) But he met me.
(Shiraki) Are you in a hurry?
(Bandai) I just want to get Yui back as soon as possible.
Do you know where we practiced together?
i don't know.
President, didn't you tell me?
Even if you knew, you wouldn't say it.
Wait... what is it?
Huh…｡
I really haven't been taught anything.
I was away for a while.
Sendai.
Maybe they didn't even know they were going to hold a press conference?
Hehe... that makes you impatient.
After being sent to Sendai, I was out of bed.
Therefore...! I have no choice but to follow you.
Please stop! Then I'll stop!
You can't say that...
(Komiyama) I'll take it.
(Komiyama) In the end, it's a parent-child fight.
Shiraki-san, do you think Hayashida will bring Yui-san?
I don't understand.
Well, but if President Keishi and Yui meet again➡
I want to know what the two of you will say at that time.
It's such a private thing. That's why it's so interesting, isn't it?
Ah, but if Yui-san came back like that➡
Will Bandai not be rewarded?
I've been looking all over the place until now.
It doesn't matter.
I'm in trouble.
I need Mr. Bandai to gain the trust of the president.
Yeah.
Well...
It's a match until 4 o'clock the next day.
Ah, the date has changed, so it's tomorrow.
Why are you so obsessed with this matter?
Bandai-san, have you ever met your predecessor, Kyoichi Yagami?
home.
That's a monster.
Just by looking at your face➡
Everything can be seen through➡
It's like being eaten up.
Hehe...
Me ➡
He is possessed by the ghost of Kyoichi Yagami.
(Sakagami) That's amazing, Daisuke Hayashida.
How much can I get?
(Yamaguchi) You won't get it, it's a trap.
(Sakagami) No, but what if the deal was actually completed without the police➡
Shouldn't it be a billion? (In a whisper) Please contact me...
picture? What? Don't play with it, clean it up!
I'm scared.
What? Are you going to fire me?
Lie, lie, lie…｡
Isn't it morning...
Oh...I don't even play a werewolf.
I can't help but laugh. Shall we do it now?
I'm hungry... let's eat breakfast.
Don't borrow eggs. (Riri) Yeah.
(refrigerator opening/closing sound)
picture?
what happened?
(Riri) Saito-san➡
He died.
teeth?
(Riri) ``The suspect, Takeharu Saito, who is believed to be one of the kidnapping group, is➡
He died on the day of the incident."
Mr. Gan.
I want to contact the old man. (Gun) What did you say?
Do you know my contact information? Linda...
I don't have a cell phone, and my account was stolen.
Linda calm down... You're calm!
Saito is dead.
You heard that you have a heart problem, right?
I was listening but...
Huh?
Did Gan know?
I knew.
I see.
(Sound of picking up chopsticks)
(sound of mixing eggs)
(Masaki) I'm ready.
(Misaki) Huh?
(Masaki) Challenge yourself to make the perfect 1000 kcal with Sendai souvenirs!
I see... Misa➡
I know you're tired, but... No, that's not it.
come here for a second.
I feel like this person resembles someone➡
I'm really confused.
Ah! Isn't that? “That”?
Ah!
((Cancelled today for now?))
(2 people) A haunted spot!
Well then, I'll go.
Yes, please come.
There are, right?
yeah?
You won't disappear while I'm out, right?
Yeah, I'll tell you exactly when I leave.
I'm coming.
(sound of door closing)
I might even use a vacuum cleaner...
How many times do you call?
Hey.
Why don't you go to Mr. Saito's funeral?
Huh? You really want to go, right?
There's no reason.
Who wants to look at a dead old man's face?
I don't even know when or where the funeral will be held.
If you do that, you'll be found and arrested right away.
I had Gan-san's help with that...
That's fine.
The old man is alive inside me.
I'm bored.
Even Shiritori is fine.
Now, let's talk about Mr. Saito. Huh? Why?
You have free time, right?
(Shhh…)
please.
correct answer! Seriously!?
I told you, you can do it.
Good luck on your exam tomorrow!
Usu! Hahahaha…｡
test? Mechanic exam.
I was reluctant because I had to study ➡
You're making a lot of noise, telling me to get a job.
It was noisy though➡
I was happy. Don't tell me.
So? Did you pass the test?
That's a hit.
I see.
Mr. Saito➡
I guess he was thinking about Linda's future.
What else?
Did you go somewhere together or eat something delicious?
Ah...｡
If it was really bad, I would eat it.
My dad told me he couldn't make lunch, so I made this for the first time.
Peperoncino.
Well...the noodles were hard and tasteless, so it was really bad.
But the old man was so kind that he forced himself to eat it all➡
After that, I felt really unwell.
Hehe... I feel sorry for him. No...
I'm really sorry about that.
a….
I'm going to have peperoncino for dinner today. I don't like it.
Revenge! I don't like it, please stop.
Let me make it.
already….
(knock)
Yes.
Mr. Gan.
Do you know when Mr. Saito's funeral will be held?
I would like to meet you for a moment.
Isn't it okay to visit a grave when the weather has cooled down?
If you can see my face, isn't it better as long as I can see it?
Mr. Gan➡
You know Mr. Saito, right?
Somehow.
Mr. Gan➡
Don't you think it's better to say goodbye properly?
If you weigh the risk of being caught, there's no room for consideration.
And even if Linda regrets it in the future➡
It has nothing to do with Hachi.
400g is fine, right? Yeah... Oh, did you add salt?
I'm home. (Yui: Daisuke) Welcome back.
Good thing they were having fun fighting.
Oh, is it Peperoncino tonight?
Great answer~
(Gun) Thank you for the meal. (Riri) It was delicious.
That's great. I could do it.
Ah, I'll do the washing. Is that okay?
I would appreciate it if you could do that because I have something to talk to you two about.
Please take your time.
What? Talk to me.
It's about Saito's funeral.
Tomorrow 1pm ➡
He will be buried directly. Chokso?
There will be no gathering of people, just cremation.
Well, he's a kidnapper.
Why is that...?
Just in case Hachi asked me to.
If you want to see my face, that's the last time.
No, I'm not going.
Please, go. I don't understand.
Why do you go out of your way to rush into such a dangerous place?
If something were to happen, I would be arrested as well.
To the police, it's not kidnapping➡
He says I asked him to run away with me.
Are you an idiot? It has nothing to do with you.
It's relevant, because it's about Linda.
Huh? Are you in love with me? We're talking seriously.
Me and Linda➡
Because the environments we grew up in were so different➡
I think we feel and think differently, but...
I imagined it.
For Linda➡
What kind of person is Mr. Saito?
Look.
When fixing a puncture➡
When I asked, “What can you do?”➡
You said, "Because it's a car dealership."
I feel like there's something wrong with me.
I didn't know it at that time, but...
It's because I take pride in my work.
That's...
It's really nice.
Do something that will make the police take care of you➡
But when I met Saito-san➡
I was told about my work➡
I also received support to obtain qualifications.
It's like you taught me how to live.
Am I saying something like a textbook again?
I have a big feeling of envy, but...
There's something... I can't convey it well.
no.
It was still on the way.
Standing on his own as a fine mechanic...
I wanted the old man to see it.
I wanted someone to praise me and say, ``You did a good job.''
♬～
Is this the kind of thing where we would hug each other if we weren't here?
But this is me.
That's right.
If it's just the two of us, we can forgive something.
Riri too? "too"?
It's almost like you forget that you're in the middle of a crime that will shake the world.
Really.
Well, I'm also carrying the burden on one side.
Cancer-san can do so many things➡
Is it okay to use it for crimes?
A job where you can be properly evaluated in the sunlight ➡
I feel like I want you to do that➡
Is that wrong?
It's impossible.
Once you commit a crime, you can't go back.
There's no place to go back to.
♬～
Huh…｡
Yui... I wonder if he'll come.
(Kyoichi) Come on, please.
Yuuka-san.
Have you gotten used to Yagami's house yet?
(Yuka) Thanks to you.
Keishi-san also treats me well.
Maybe I shouldn't ask this, but...
Please ask me anything.
Will the day come when I can see my grandchild's face?
I go to treatment, but it's not easy...
Ah... I see.
Let me introduce you to a clinic that I know.
Huh...
(Gun) Yes.
I'm sorry, always. It's true.
Hachi is also... bad.
Please say goodbye properly.
That's why I don't ask Riri to answer the call.
Everyone, do well.
I'll be waiting.
(3 people) Yes.
⚟First of all...⚞ I'm sorry.
(Ebihara) What?
Saito's cremation is today, right? Is that it? what up?
I want to go there, Hayashida might come.
There's no way they knew that the cremation was today.
There's a possibility. Even if we know ➡
Do you think he'll come when he's getting so much attention?
Saito is Hayashida's benefactor.
Ha...
Is he the kind of person who would risk his life to attend the cremation of his benefactor?
(Detectives laugh)
(Komiyama) Hahaha... Hahahaha...! (Detectives laugh)
(sound of tapping on desk)
Surprisingly, he's that kind of guy.
Bring six people.
yes.
(Tabata) Thank you!
Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
(Tomoko) Hello. Smartphone) This is Bandai from Yagami Pharmaceutical.
No matter how many times I try to call Daisuke's phone, I can't get through.
It seems that the phone is no longer in use.
Smartphone) So what is this time?
Do you have any idea where Daisuke Hayashida might go?
A place you might go?
A place where you can hide and someone who can take care of you.
harbor…?
a….
♪~ Saita
♪~ Tulip flowers
lend me.
How could you do that?
I just looked it up on my smartphone.
Oh no.
Are you really going alone?
Well, don't let it get in your way.
teeth? It's a joke.
I'll go home properly.
Oh... that flag has been raised.
The joke is harsh.
yes.
Because 30 seconds is the limit. 30 seconds!?
30 seconds.
Thin!
♬～
Linda: The coffin has arrived.
It's probably the detective who's stuck.
learn.
Earphones) (Gun) There are other detective-like things...
There are 5 people.
Hey, Komiyama, there's also a new discoverer.
Hey, let's go there.
♬～
Excuse me.
(sutra reading)
It's time to go~
Rajah.
♬～
(alarm sound)
(Sutra reading) (Alarm sound)
(Etsuko) Ah!
(Staff) Everyone! Please evacuate outdoors!
Don't panic! Hurry! (Tabata) Komi-san.
Komi-san, what should we do? (Komiyama) Hmm... I can't help it!
Don't smoke! (Tabata) Don't run, don't run!
It's now.
Go!
♬～
Old man...
You have 30 seconds, do you understand?
♬～
He's seriously dead...
Why...?
I need you to see me now that I'm a full-fledged person...
Old man...
♬～
There was still a lot to talk about...
(buzz)
I'll go back. Huh? yes!
Hey, it's enough.
It's coming! Go!
Hey!
Tsk...
Eh, Gan-san? I'll bring you. But... it's okay.
Hachi, can you drive? Well, I'm a paper driver, but...
Just stay in the driver's seat. Huh?
If you see your car, leave it.
Because I'm fine.
♬～
Don't stay alone...
Come on, let's go!
quickly!
(Komiyama) ⚟Daisuke! ⚞
Hey! Daisuke!
Daisuke!
♬～
Get better! yes!
(Tabata) Hey! Hayashida!
door won't open
Oh my...!
I have no choice but to jump.
Huh!? There's no escape now.
No, it's on the third floor! Here!
Good thing, fall into that loading platform.
Please show me an example! You idiot, go first➡
You took me. It's impossible, you'll break your bones!
If you get caught here, nothing will happen.
In that case, it would be much better to negotiate with Hachi's father.
(Tabata) Hayashida! You can't run away now!
(Sound of running down the stairs)
Go quickly!
Ah, ah…｡
Go! Ah~!
Ah...!
Are you a genius?
Mr. Gan!
Say hello to Hachi! Huh?
Mr. Gun!? Mr. Gun!
(Investigator) Hey! There it was! (Investigators) Yes!
Oh my...!
Ha ha…! already…! Already!
Huh...
you?
Who do you think it is?
Don't move. I've planted a bomb.
Where? Front planting.
I guess it's the area where everyone evacuated.
Are you a cooperator who is going around deleting the security camera footage?
How are the stars doing?
Did you enjoy your business trip to Sendai?
Maybe you're a cancer?
Tabata: Follow Hayashida.
It's going to explode.
Go! yes!
Yes Dokkan! (click)
Mom, I want to go home already!
I was surprised! already!
It's a bluff. Hurry up! (Tabata) Yes!
♬～
Linda.
Mr. Gan!? I don't understand! Hurry!
Huh? (Tabata) ⚟Wait! ⚞
Wow! (engine starting sound)
Shit!
Don't neglect adults too much.
I'm quite an adult, too.
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Mr. Gan, what should we do?
I said, "I'm fine," but...
Are you going to throw away your car? A detective saw it.
Gan-san told me to do that too.
♬～
((I don't have a cell phone))
I wonder if it's really a good thing that I left Gan behind.
It's Linda's fault, right? I said 30 seconds.
30 seconds is a short time for a final farewell.
Think about the situation.
It can't be helped.
The old man has a surprisingly calm face...
What is it?
My car is here. Huh?
Bandai may be coming to see Riri.
<Important announcement: “ESCAPE” is the latest episode on TVer➡
All episodes now available on Hulu! >
＜TVer, this is going to be amazing! ＞
Huh…｡
(chime)
Riri Kosaka?
Yes. I'm a police officer.
I'll take a look inside.
Huh... Huh?
(Detective) Excuse me. (Riri) Hey...!
Wait a minute!
♬～
(coughing)
Are you okay? (coughing)
Wait a minute. (coughing)
(coughing)
Huh… hah…｡
♬～
thank you.
Sorry for including Riri-chan.
I'm the one who got you involved.
Because someone sold me...
Who is it?
It might be my fucking old hag.
picture? Grandma?
That's wrong, mother.
People change when money is involved.
Are you usually a nice person?
Well…｡
I'm sure he was raised by me.
I understand.
We...
(Masaki) A man was just taken away by an ambulance...
(Misaki) As for why we were able to take this video...
This is...
(Misaki) Yes!
(Masaki) We may have rubbed off on each other!
(Misaki) No, anyway...
I decided.
I'm going to meet my dad. What?
Your voice is loud.
(Shiraki) Phew...｡
Will it move soon?
It's pointless if Hachi gets caught, so what are you going to explain to Mr. Gan?
Because Gan-san and Riri-chan are causing trouble➡
It's all my fault for throwing the stars around, right?
You knew that from the beginning. I thought you knew, but...
I don't understand anymore.
So, is it blurring again?
That's different.
Aikido practice➡
It was really fun.
(shout)
♬～
Okay, let's go one more time.
Yeah.
(Yui's voice) That's...
I think it was something you could call love.
But when you were using GPS, you didn't think it was love, right?
Because it's changed.
Why? I don't understand.
I suddenly felt like a different person.
((breathing heavily))
♬～
Something must have happened. I don't know.
So listen. That's why I want to hear it.
Ah...｡
Even if I do...
(Fuji) President, are you heading over soon?
That's right.
Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
yes.
Smartphone) Me.
Huh... Yui?
Smartphone) Yes.
I want to talk.
Ah, let's do it.
A long time ago, I cried so hard just once, right?
Yeah.
Smartphone) The place...
Do you remember?
Ah...of course.
Then at 4 o'clock➡
Please come alone.
(Fuji) Is it from Yui-san?
I have specified the location.
how was it?
Maybe...➡
I don't remember.
Then it's no good, right?
(Fuji) If it's about Yui-san's childhood ➡
How about asking Mr. Jonouchi from Utsunomiya?
This is Yui testing me.
Don't contact anyone, not even the police.
yes.
(Sound of smartphone operating)
What will I do if he doesn't come?
I'll never go back to that house.
So why don't you come?
Come and ask what you want to hear➡
So what should I do if I decide to go home?
Hmm...｡
One case settled?
I'm cute.
Hehe...
You should get the money and run away.
I'll tell the police as much as possible.
As good as possible? Yeah.
If you get caught and go to court➡
I will testify so that the punishment will be lighter.
There's no way you'll believe me.
I don't know, though.
Well, that's fine.
Just think about your father now.
Well, it's okay. You're kind, aren't you?
Or rather, are you nice?
Thank you.
picture?
I'm glad I got to see the old man's face.
Thank you.
♬～
After all, you're such a nice person.
Wait here.
Are you sure? Yeah.
♬～
Shall we go?
Linda, please wait here. Huh?
What would you do if Ichichi was hiding?
At that time…➡
Come out with a knife.
♬～
Take it.
I'll stop it after all.
♬～
(Bandai) Mr. Fuji! Ah...｡
Mr. Jonouchi also mentioned this park, right?
Is it the president too? yes.
Ah, good for now.
Oh wait... Mr. Bandai!
(Chaim)♪～
♬～
Yui.
Are you feeling okay?
Go home...
Yui?
Dad.
yeah?
You tried to kill me.