(Daisuke) Get away! (Shiraki) <In the wake of the kidnapping incident➡
He was living a strange life on the run➡
With Yui Yagami, also known as “Hachi”➡
Daisuke Hayashida, also known as “Linda”>
<Two people who have no way of knowing that President Yagami has collapsed➡
We decided to leave for each other's sake.
I'll turn myself in.
(Shiraki) Um...
It's Yui Yagami, right?
Don't you want to know who you are?
(Yui) What is it?
Would you like to shake hands?
Yui-san➡
You can tell about me when I shake your hand.
Do you know about this kind of thing?
It's "Satori", right?
"Satori"?
That power is called "Satori".
Poor guy.
It's all been kept secret.
(Keishi) Take care of Yui until now➡
thanks so much.
Please do your best in Utsunomiya.
(Akira) Thank you.
that….
Chairman Kyoichi is now➡
You've been hospitalized, right?
Yes, that's right.
Actually…➡
I was kept quiet, but...
Yui-chan is the owner of "Satori".
Yui...?
Sorry for being silent for so long.
Ah... no... no, that's impossible.
picture? What... What do you mean?
I first noticed this when Yui was in kindergarten.
The chairman said, ``I'll never let anyone know.''
Huh...
Is Yui talking about this...?
Only me and the president know.
Yui-chan herself➡
You probably don't know the details.
Wait... what's that? It's called "Satori".
a! I'm sorry, maybe he didn't know yet?
You know, you can see color when you touch it, right?
Huh? Color?
It's the color.
That's interesting.
It's the voice of my heart flowing into Yui along with the colors➡
...Is that what it feels like?
Don't you know?
No, actually, about “Satori”➡
I have talked to many people➡
With people who actually have power➡
This is the first time I've had a proper conversation like this.
Who did you hear that from?
These are people close to the Yagami family.
Those close to the previous president, Kyoichi➡
Ah, of course I was acting as Yui's mother➡
Also from Akira Jonouchi.
The power of Satori is inherited by the Yagami family.
Meet your grandfather➡
Like Chairman Kyoichi Yagami.
picture?
So does that mean Hachi's father also has one?
Dad is an adopted child.
Ah... then what about mom?
Mom is not a Yagami person.
teeth?
Mr. Shiraki.
That's what I hear, but is it wrong?
I also recognize that.
picture? What do you mean?
Yui’s biological parents are➡
It means there are others.
Who is that person➡
Does Shiraki-san know?
yes.
♬～
Huh…｡
(cry)
What does that mean?
I told you that artificial insemination was successful!
Answer! Answer!!
(Hasunuma) It was a success!
With your wife➡
It belongs to Chairman Kyoichi!
It was good.
Yui seems to be doing well and growing up.
Are you still a doctor?
Ha, do you want to sue?
The secret of Yui's birth will be made public.
Please don't hate me.
There is no one in this industry who can go against Chairman Kyoichi.
No way…➡
Yuka died... Haha...｡
That was an unfortunate accident.
But➡
He died without knowing the truth➡
Maybe I was happy in a way.
(Shiraki) When I questioned my doctor at the time➡
I readily admitted it.
It's like a cuckoo's egg.
President Keishi was used to preserve Yagami's blood➡
I raised you without even knowing it.
(breathing heavily) What do you think?
Is there anything that comes to mind when you hear what I just said?
Wait! You must be confused!
Hachi: Don't trust this guy.
I'm just saying the right things and having fun.
But don't you think Hachi makes sense?
4 years ago President Keishi was ➡
I learned that you are the son of the hated Chairman Kyoichi➡
His attitude suddenly changed!
So much so that I want to make you a dead person!
(breathing heavily)
Stop it!
Mothers die during childbirth, right?
From the perspective of President Keishi➡
I feel like I am my beloved wife who risked her life to give birth to me➡
I must have cherished you for 16 years➡
Did you know that all this was done to connect Yagami's blood!
Don't worry! What did you come here for?
If you want money, go to Hachi's father!
By the way, did you know that the prize money has been raised to 300 million yen?
teeth? Yagami Pharmaceutical is➡
A hostile TOB is being launched by the American Hoover Company!
President Keishi must be under a lot of pressure.
Yui has the power of “Satori” that I don’t have➡
I want to get it back no matter what!
Hey! (breathing heavily)
Are you okay? (breathing heavily)
(breathing heavily)
Please come back.
If I go back, I'll never see you again!
I've never seen a bee like this before!
(breathing heavily)
Please give me a break.
Well then…➡
Please contact me when you have calmed down.
♬～
Also.
Hey... (breathing heavily)
Calm down, it's okay. (breathing heavily)
Don't trust such a questionable reporter.
I…➡
I wasn't my father's child...!
Don't trust me!
Mommy... thinks she's daddy's child...
It's okay, it's just a bad joke!
Grandfather...
So… it has nothing to do with bees!
The blood of such a person flows through my body!
(cry)
Please leave me alone...
♬～
I'll buy you something to drink.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
Huh… hah…｡
♬～
(cry)
I thought I might be hungry, so I bought some meat buns...
What are you doing?
(cry)
Did it get covered in gasoline?
Wait a minute... Bring it over here.
What am I...➡
It was a mistake to be born!
That's not true.
Because of me...
Everyone...
Everyone was unhappy...
That's wrong!
(cry)
♬～
Ah! Huh...
What are you doing? (coughing)
Ha ha ha ha...
I wonder what you're doing.
It's a shared destiny.
♬～
(Sound of lighter being thrown)
(cry)
(car running sound)
♬～
(cry)
Ha!
Hey! (Headbutting sound)
Let it out! Hey! (Headbutting sound)
⚟Where is the bee? ⚞
If something happens to Hachi, I'll throw him away!
a….
a! Hey! hang on!
hang on! hang on! Well... wait!
⚟Wait~~~~!! ⚞
(Tomoko) Huh… hah…｡
So➡
I can't contact Daisuke either.
(Yamaguchi) Do you have any other smartphones?
there is no.
Hey!
If you lie, I'll kill you.
♬～
(Knock) (Kyoto) ⚟Yui-chan⚞
⚟Can I come in? ⚞
please.
(Kyoto) Welcome to our villa.
Aunt...
♬～
That's right.
We're the same.
Fuck... Fuck...!
Anyway, I'm glad you're safe.
Weren't you anxious for days?
Don't worry.
I haven't told Keishi-san that Yui-chan is here.
Um...what?
Linda...
What about the person you were with?
Who kidnapped Yui?
Ah... that's true, but it's not.
picture?
Ha...! Are you a genius?
(Shinobi) Take a bath.
picture?
Sorry for the late reply.
(Tsboi) So, Hachi-chan is safe?
yes.
I'm coming to a relative's house for various reasons...
I'll explain properly when I get back.
It's fine as long as it's okay.
Because it's your life.
I'll contact you again.
thank you very much.
Looks like you don't need my help.
I was just trying to live on my own.
But➡
There are many things I want to talk about with my aunt.
Yeah.
(Tabata) It looks like this.
The place that was shown on "Mami Channel".
(Miyazono) That's right.
(Tabata) This smell... (Miyazono) It's gasoline.
(Tabata) Wow...｡
Oh, Miyazono-san, this is it.
(All) Itadakimasu.
Yeah! It's delicious!
Good! Delicious!
It's my first time eating something so delicious!
yes? yes.
Is this an inn?
It's my villa, right?
I agree.
Have a professional chef come ➡
I also ask for housekeeping➡
Well, it might be something like an inn.
Wow...
He's an honest person. He's like a child.
It's much better than trying to be cool and acting like you know something.
yeah?
Haha…｡ Hehehe…｡
Well, I had to apologize first.
I'm sorry for acting so poorly.
I thought he was a violent kidnapper.
It’s true!
But the old man is quite strong.
Hahahaha…｡ Hehehehe…｡
But why us?
I was worried because Yui-chan was kidnapped➡
Keishi won't tell me anything➡
I wonder what's going on when you suddenly appear on TV.
Hey. That's right.
Kyo and I are Yui-chan's allies.
I want you to believe that.
♬～
I also have something to apologize to Yui-chan.
What my father did.
Don't you want to hear it?
I want to know.
(Kyoto) I have an older brother➡
My father is raising my older brother as his successor➡
I was treated like I didn't exist.
I was born➡
As a spare in case something happens to my brother.
When he found out it was a woman, he was extremely disappointed.
After that, my younger brother was never born➡
My father was increasingly interested in my brother.
So all I was thinking about was leaving Yagami's house.
But➡
My older brother was diagnosed with an incurable disease and passed away at the age of 15.
My father suddenly started paying attention to me➡
I continued to ignore it.
Look for a job by yourself➡
I chose my marriage partner myself.
That's when I thought we had broken ties➡
My father told me one day.
"Do you have children yet?"
but….
We had decided.
I don't have children.
I thought Yagami's blood would just die out.
Me too, if that's what Kyo wanted, that would be fine.
(Kyo) That's why I lied when my father asked me.
``I'm not in a position to have children,'' she said.
My father was confused.
I really thought this was the end.
But my father's obsession didn't end there.
I never expected something like that...
I am the one who upset the fate of your family.
I'm really sorry.
That's different.
picture?
After all, isn't your aunt a victim too?
The only one at fault is old man.
♬～
I'm sorry, but you're an idiot.
But if my aunt hadn't lied➡
Hachi might not even exist in this world, right?
Then that is...➡
Isn't it wrong to apologize?
Maybe so.
You're not stupid.
Haha...
Is that so? That’s awesome. Haha…｡
Yui-chan.
Thank you for being born.
You are my precious family.
♬～
I'll protect you from now on.
(Misaki) Yeah, it was 100 million before...
No, because...
a little bit….
here you are.
thank you.
Aunt. What?
There are so many things I want to ask you.
Ask me anything, it's safe here.
Ah...!
Replacement. Hahahaha…｡
This villa is amazing! There's even a bar!
That's right.
Your uncle is the president of some company or something, right?
No, no...
I'm just the third son of a Japanese sweets shop.
Huh? Again!
Kyo is amazing.
Well... it sure looks amazing.
The store where everyone in the Kiryu family threw spoons➡
Kyo was able to rebuild it all by himself. Hey.
(Bartender) Please excuse me.
(Shinobu) This is our signature product. Oh...
Eat it. Itadakimasu.
Hmm!
Hey, I'm so drunk I can't taste it.
Hahahahaha…! What is this? yeah?
Recently, I bought a tatami shop that was about to go bankrupt.
We also do business to preserve culture.
Isn't it amazing?
I love my uncle Kyo.
I agree.
Wow.
Fufufufu…｡ Fufufufu…｡
What about your family?
Ah... I only have one mother.
You must be worried.
Nothing happened just now.
When my aunt touched my hand.
That's right, so were my father and brother.
Nothing happens between people who have ``Satori''.
“Satori”….
What happens when Yui-chan touches someone's hand?
I can see the color.
Colors that look kind and colors that look unpleasant.
It's the color.
I can hear the sound.
Is it a sound? yes.
Soft sounds or sharp sounds➡
I can hear things like compatibility with me in the form of sounds.
Hmm, that's right...!
We're lonely.
Because this color means this➡
No one will tell you, right?
So, as I accumulate experiences within myself➡
``Oh, if it's this color, I'm on my side.''➡
That's the only way to make predictions.
That's right.
I can't talk to anyone➡
Even if I'm smiling, I don't want to see scary colors➡
I've gradually become less close to people.
But I pretended to fit in so that I didn't stand out from the people around me➡
I didn't really show it to anyone.
That's right! That's right!
If they found out about my powers, I'm sure they'd be scared.
People won't believe me when I say it's just the color.
It makes you think that you can hear all the voices in your heart.
Keishi-san must be scared too.
With my father when I loved him➡
Linda's color was the same.
(Kyoto) Is that so?
And Linda, even though she knows my power, she's not afraid.
Instead, he said, ``Let's go to the casino.''
Hehe... You seem like an idiot.
I don't understand that.
Yui-chan.
Don't let him go.
Shinobu-san➡
He told me, ``It's been tough up until now.''
When I talked about power.
When I was at Yagami's house➡
The maid and my father's secretary were all scared of me.
But Shinobu-san➡
For realizing that I was lonely➡
He said, ``I'll be by your side.''
"You can touch me as much as you like," he said.
Eh! Hehe...
It seems like the complete opposite of Linda-kun➡
Isn't it the same thing in the sense that you don't care?
I agree.
I don't think I'll ever come across one.
(sneeze)
Ah... Shhh... Shhh...
Replacement.
I'll give you back what I kept.
Oh, that's it!
Smartphone. Smartphone.
Sunglasses. Sunglasses.
88 yen. 88 yen.
Acorn.
Acorn...
Do I need these handcuffs and knife?
No need, I'm going to the police tomorrow.
a….
I will turn myself in.
yes.
Ah... I guess these acorns will be confiscated?
Well, what do you think?
No, I won't be kept.
I can't keep it.
(Shinobu) I can't keep it.
(Cancer)((Your mother has increased her debt again))
Huh... no way.
♬～
Smartphone) (ring tone)
Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
Why not... Smartphone) (Ring tone)
What kind of sound does your uncle make?
(Kyoto) Hmm... I guess it sounds like the earth.
Earth? It doesn't look like that, does it?
But it's thick and warm➡
It sounds like it can handle anything.
I feel like I understand it somehow.
I thought you were unconsciously looking for something like a father➡
I'm horrified though.
I think it's different.
I saw that my father and Linda had the same color➡
I thought maybe he wasn't a bad person➡
To be honest, they don't look alike at all.
Honestly, I can't think of anything similar.
Fufufu…! Fufufu…｡
Did you hear everything you wanted to hear?
What I can think of now is
good.
a….
((If you can't see the color just by touching it➡
What if I kiss you? ))
Was it still there?
No! No, no.
Yeah.
Please use this room.
♬～
a! Sofa! Ah yes, there is.
I'll sleep over there. Yeah. Yeah.
♬～
Were you able to speak slowly?
Yeah.
Something was good.
yeah?
Please take me to a nice place like this.
I agree.
At first I thought it was over for real.
Linda, weren't you scared?
That's scary!
I was suddenly beaten up and locked in such a strange place.
No, before that. Ah?
gasoline.
Ah...｡
If I had started the fire, they would both have died.
Haha... that's right.
Take better care of yourself.
You say it?
Because... I had a reason.
There's no reason why I should die.
I really don't want to cause alarm.
sorry.
I was trying to turn myself in.
It won't change today or tomorrow.
I see.
(Salesperson) Thank you.
(Shiraki) Why do you go to the trouble of sitting next to me even though there are other seats available➡
Did you think...?
This is Shiraki from “Weekly Shinryu”.
Excuse me, please give me the same one.
(Salesperson) I'm very smart.
Mr. Komiyama, you know Daisuke Hayashida well, right?
Who is he?
Maybe you're a prince? (Komiyama) But…｡
(Shiraki) It's... it's so bad.
(Komiyama) Because you say strange things!
No, did you say something strange like that?
That guy is just a thug.
Oh really?
Have you met Daisuke? Yeah, well.
Where?
That's a bit.
But it seems like he's willing to turn himself in.
Now online➡
Things like Hachirin are popular among young people➡
Well, I don't think it's out of the ordinary.
But Mae was there, and she also took part in the kidnapping.
There's something wrong with her...or maybe she's just clumsy.
I was removed from the kidnapping case. Huh?
Mr. Gochisousu. Thank you very much!
(Shiraki) Is that so?
(Sound of door opening and closing)
Is the bee coming back? yeah?
No...it would be fine if I were adopted by two people.
That's not what I was told.
I think I can lead a good life.
Come to think of it, my aunt told me she would protect me.
Isn't that so?
Hmm...but I guess it's different.
Train with Mickey ➡
I can now stand on my own feet➡
I want to be a person who can protect someone.
Hmm.
Should I sleep there after all? teeth?
No, look, size-wise. It's weird, isn't it?
Hachi lives with a relative, but I'm just an outsider.
After all, Linda hasn't been sleeping in a proper place lately, right?
It's okay! Even if I catch a cold, I won't be in trouble.
Good, good, good...! Okay, let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Good! If you don't show it, you'll lose➡
Rock, paper, scissors poi!
It's Aiko! Oh!
It's Aiko! Eh...｡
It's Aiko! Oh...!
It's Aiko! Oh! It's Aiko! Oh!
It's Aiko! Ah! It's Aiko! Oh no!
It's Aiko!
After all, it's me... It's okay.
I'm good at sleeping.
(sound of seconds ticking)
Dad…➡
Do you think it was hard?
There's nothing to feel sorry for.
Even if it’s hard➡
There's no reason to make bees feel bad.
Yes, but... it's not that easy.
In front of the fountain➡
Even if I asked you, you wouldn't answer properly, right?
(Yui's voice) I just kept saying, "It's not a lie."
((Trust me))
((It's all for Yui))
(Yui's voice) That makes me even stronger➡
I can't trust my dad anymore...
Now that I think about it➡
I wonder if he really thought of me and didn't say that.
yeah? What does it mean?
When I try to explain ➡
I'm not my father's child➡
You'll have to say that, right?
Ah...｡
But➡
If only I had decided not to say that...
Maybe it was my misunderstanding.
But it was such an unpleasant color, wasn't it?
Hmm…｡
But that may also be a misunderstanding.
what kind?
What is Mickey's color?
Did I mention that there were both soft and dark colors?
Mickey's➡
The dark and painful color is ➡
I thought the color was blaming myself.
So maybe➡
That color of daddy too➡
Maybe it meant something different than I thought.
♬～
Hey, I'm talking about something serious.
You're tired, aren't you?
Why would you go to such lengths?
but….
Even if it's not me, I'm sure you'll do it.
♬～
Smartphone) (artificial voice) He was imprisoning and brainwashing his daughter Yui➡
Yui Yagami's bounty is 300 million...
Smartphone) Keishi Yagami is the devil's deed...
(Masaki) It's getting worse and worse.
hey.
Smartphone) (artificial voice) The evil deeds hidden behind these tears are dangerous...
(Sound of keyboard hitting)
Huh…｡
yeah….
Huh… hah… hah…｡
(sound of door opening)
Do you remember anything?
So➡
You say you don't know Daisuke's current contact information, right?
Hmm, I'm in trouble...
Eventually, the people at the company became suspicious➡
I'll go to the police. Well then➡
Don't let me know if you're going to take a break.
♬～
good morning.
I ended up sleeping there.
I couldn't sleep.
Are you excited? ah….
That's wrong! It's because you're not sleeping well!
That's a lie! It's true!
That's a lie! The ribs here are broken.
What are you talking about? Huh?
Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
Ah. Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
Is it Mr. Gan? Mr. Gan?
If that's the case, I'd like to talk too. Smartphone) (vibrating sound)
hello.
hello!
Smartphone) (Yamaguchi) Hayashida?
Smartphone) Ransom: Don't try to keep it all to yourself.
Mr. Yamaguchi, why is this number...?
(Smartphone) You called me, you motherfucker.
Your mother kept it.
If you want me to help you, bring Yui Yagami with me.
Don't lie.
Smartphone) Does it matter what happens to the mother?
If it's true, let me hear it.
Hey, say "help me".
Daisuke I'm fine! Hey there!
(Gashan) Smartphone) (Tomoko's scream)
Smartphone) (Yamaguchi) Bring Yui Yagami within three hours from now.
(Smartphone) I will tell you the location later.
Smartphone) (sound of disconnected call)
what happened?
It's nothing. It didn't feel like nothing.
It's nothing.
Please let me have breakfast➡
Hachi is back with Mickey, right?
Hey, what are you hiding?
Don't hide it.
The person on the phone is Yamaguchi, right?
That's someone who was part of the kidnapping party, right?
It has nothing to do with bees. It has nothing to do with it.
No way.
Hey.
We share a common destiny, right?
Mom➡
Captured by Yamaguchi.
If you want me to help you, bring me Hachi.
I?
Huh... I forgot about his existence.
He was the one who suggested we kidnap Hachi in the first place.
Is that so?
It seems that he has a grudge against Yagami Pharmaceuticals.
Well, don't worry about it. I will.
It's okay. What?
I don't care what happens to that damn old hag.
It's your mother, right?
I'm always being held back.
picture…?
It's because of him that I started working part-time jobs.
Why?
You lose money gambling.
No matter how much you earn, you end up in debt like an idiot➡
I'll borrow money from some crazy place➡
Even I had to make money.
(Riri)((Yui-chan ➡
Have you met Dai-chan's mother? ))
((Ugh))
(Riri)((Ah, no... I heard it from Dai-chan after all))
picture….
So what about Riri's 200,000 yen? ah.
He went to borrow it without permission.
Is that why you broke up?
It looked like I wouldn't be able to get away with 200,000 yen.
That's why you should leave that guy alone.
Is it really good? It's okay!
Getting beaten up is the worst, I don't care if I die.
Rather, I feel like I'm thanking the plague god for disappearing.
Don't make that face.
I can go. Huh?
Yamaguchi-san's real purpose is me, right?
Are you an idiot? No matter who you are➡
I don't want you to go through hardships on my behalf.
That's how you say it, Hachi.
That's why I didn't want to say it.
So how should I contact Mr. Komiyama?
Why is that so? If the other person is Mr. Yamaguchi➡
With the help of the police, it may be possible to resolve the matter without paying a ransom.
That's no good.
I don't know what he's doing.
♬～
♬~ After all, you want to help your mother.
♬~ “No matter how bad your parents are➡
♬~ Children cannot abandon their parents”➡
♬~ Linda said that.
♬～
♬~
♬~ It's time for Yagami-san's temperature check...｡
♬～
♬～ Huh...⁉