I said "I love you" to him.
But he acted like he didn't hear anything.
I'm sure that Mia told you she likes you,
or that she even loves you.
But don't believe her.
She just says those
things without thinking, okay?
Someone once told me
no one would ever love me.
I love you, Patrick.
I love you!
You shouldn't have
brought him into this world at all!
What did you say?!
You shouldn't have had a child
if you were only going use him.
You shouldn't be in here.
The paint might spill on you
and you'll disturb my work…
[theme music playing]
[Matmat giggling nervously]
I think I should get my eyes checked.
I still don't see a painting.
Mia.
Mia Hernandez! Mia Hernandez!
[giggles]
Finally we meet.
[unsettling music playing]
Hi, Matmat.
[gasps, giggles]
Mat-Matmat.
Matthew Gonzales.
Matthew Gonzales, 35 years old.
Ms. Mia Hernandez called me Matmat.
[both chuckle]
Want to take a selfie?
[giggles]
[unsettling music continues]
[camera clicks]
[giggling]
[unsettling music fades]
He can't get away with this
just because he's a congressman!
Doc, did you hear me?
Yes, Eden. Loud and clear.
Thank you for your concern about Patrick.
He's my employee of course I need to.
I want to file a complaint
against the Congressman.
But he'll probably just bury it
or turn it against us
because of our lapses in his son's case.
Unless we have proof.
[Anok chuckles]
[quizzical music playing]
[quizzical music fades]
[camera clicks]
Matmat!
Have you started painting?
Not yet.
Not yet. Look.
- [Matmat giggles]
- Nice.
You two took a picture.
Would you like a selfie too?
You don't have class today?
Why are you here?
Because I'm here for someone.
For someone?
Stop beating around the bush.
- Stop using Matmat--
- Am I bothering you, Gemma?
Fine.
I am here to visit
your beloved Mister Samuel.
So today, I'm not a teacher.
I'm a visitor.
Why don't you go
fetch your patient for me,
Nurse Gemma?
[tense music playing]
- [chuckles softly]
- [music ends]
[giggles] Miss Mia is
smiling because she's happy.
You know what would make me happier?
What? What?
[chuckles softly]
[foreboding music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello, Matmat? Where are you?
You're not at the mess hall.
Where are you?
At the lobby with…
[giggles]
…with Miss Mia.
[foreboding music continues]
Mia?
[Matmat] Mia. Mia Hernandez.
The author of…
"The Boy Batibat Visited,"
"The Demon Child," and…
Stay there. I'm coming.
[foreboding music continues]
Hello?
He hung up.
Wait…
Wait, Miss Mia.
Matmat will finish your drawing.
[foreboding music crescendos]
[Matmat giggles]
Wow.
You're really great.
[chuckles]
Great Matmat.
I mean it.
You are really great at drawing.
50 pesos.
[quirky music playing]
You're charging me for this?
That's what Jason pays Matmat
at the chicken barbeque.
Mm-hmm.
But…
But for you, it's free.
Really?
[giggling]
Because…
you're beautiful.
Your…
Your hair is long and beautiful.
[giggles]
You like my hair?
Thanks, Matmat.
[Matmat giggling] But…
But the one for
Doc Anok is a big painting.
That's Matmat's new work.
Matmat will get paid for that.
[Patrick] Matmat, let's go.
That was fast, Patpat.
- So fast--
- Let's go.
Come on.
Matmat doesn't want to leave.
He's with Miss Mia.
- Matmat…
- He's right.
Why don't we just stay here?
Don't you want to see
me spend time with my dad?
Your dad is here, Miss Mia?
I don't want to go home, Patpat!
- Come on.
- I don't want to!
- Let's go, Matmat!
[whining]
Didn't I tell you to wait for me there?!
[morose music playing]
Patpat is yelling.
Patpat is mad.
Wait for me here.
[morose music continues]
[morose music fades]
Can you leave me and my brother alone?!
What's that?
Who did that to you?
You didn't fight back again, Patrick?
Is that really how you are?
You should've fought back!
You get mad at me over small things,
and when someone
hits you, you just take it?
Why?
Go ahead, tell me. What are you feeling?
Tell me what you're feeling.
Are you sad?
Do you feel sorry for me?
What?
You don't know what to say.
You don't even understand your emotions.
You're just loud like an empty can.
Stop acting like you understand me,
because you don't!
[somber music playing]
Before you tell me
anything about myself…
…understand yourself first.
[somber music continues]
[ominous music sting]
Mat--Matmat?
[phone ringing]
Have you seen my brother?
[phone ringing continues]
Hello, Mama Li.
What?
Where's Matmat?
Why…
Why did Patpat look angry?
Was it because…
Was it because Matmat
didn't want to go home.
He wanted to stay with Miss Mia.
P--Patpat was mad because…
Because Matmat
didn't want to come out front.
He didn't want to go outside.
- [Matmat] He's mad--
- Matmat?
Oh, dear.
Here, this is good.
Want some? It's still warm.
Let's eat at the table.
I don't want that.
You don't? Alright, I'll put it away.
[whimpering]
Patrick is waiting for you outside.
You have to go.
We're going to clean this place.
You'll get wet and dirty
if you stay down there. Come on.
Your bag will also get dirty.
- [Matmat whimpering]
- Your bag will get dirty.
Give it to me!
[yelps]
[groans]
Um…
Matmat, do you want
to talk about what happened?
[tender music playing]
[music turns somber]
[huffs]
[wheelchair rattling]
[somber music continues]
Hello.
[music fades]
Do you remember me, my dear father?
Mia, just a reminder.
Your father is still
recovering from his surgery.
Maybe you'll remember my voice instead.
What did I use to call you?
Daddy?
[scoffs]
Do you remember me, Daddy?
[somber music playing]
Do you remember me now, Daddy?
[somber music continues]
You…
Sir Samuel, do you remember her now?
[morose music continues]
You…
Why are you still alive?
That's the reaction I know.
You should've been dead!
- [Gemma] Sir Samuel! Sir Samuel, stop.
- [music turns ominous]
Sir Samuel--Sir Samuel!
[grunting, breathing heavily]
Sir Samuel! Sir Samuel, stop it!
[body thuds]
- [groans]
- You shouldn't have…
[ominous music continues]
- [young Mia wailing]
- [Gemma] Sir Samuel!
Mia, please die!
[wailing]
- Sir Samuel, that's enough.
- [Samuel] I want you dead!
[Gemma] Help! Sir Samuel, that's enough!
- Sir Samuel!
- [grunts]
You should've been dead!
- [coughing]
- You should've been dead!
- [laughing]
- [sobbing]
- You should've been dead!
- [eerie music playing]
- [sobbing]
- [laughing hysterically]
[Samuel sobbing] You should've been dead.
[eerie music continues]
[coughing, laughing]
[screams] You should've been dead!
[laughing hysterically]
[eerie music continues]
- [Bella] No, they said--
- [Kai] Oh, there she is.
- Oh, there! Miss Mia!
- Miss!
Miss Mia!
I was just going to ask
about our next class discussion
so I can study
and read up on it right away…
- Miss Mia?
- She's in a rush. Where is she going?
Kai, I think she's mad at me.
[dark suspenseful music playing]
[woman] You deserve what happened to you.
You shouldn't have come here.
Don't ever come back.
[dark suspenseful music crescendos]
[Anok] Huh?
Samuel strangled Mia?
May it be intentional or not,
that's what he did to her.
What did Mia do afterwards?
Doc, she just laughed.
I'm not sure whether
she thought what happened to her was funny
or if she just tried to laugh it off.
Oh, well.
Doc…
Mia doesn't really
seem worried about her father.
She doesn't care if he is in pain
- or why he did that to her.
- Hmm…
[inhales deeply]
Uh…
We'll never really know
unless we talk to Mia.
Uh…
Can you tell Doc Emman
to update me on Samuel?
And ask one of the nurses to call Mia.
I want to talk to her.
- Okay, doc.
- Thank you, Eden.
[creaks]
[pensive music playing]
[pensive music continues]
[Anok] Does your daughter
share the same condition as you,
Ingrid?
[pensive music fades]
Patrick.
Miss Li.
Looks like we're going to have
a lengthy conversation.
I'll take Matmat home.
It's okay, Miss Li. I'll wait for him.
He'll come out once he's feeling better.
It's fine. I'll take Matmat home.
- Miss Li, I can't just--
- It's okay.
Get some sleep and eat.
Take care of yourself and
whatever else that you need.
Gossip spreads like wildfire.
It's already reached the kitchen.
Here.
Go on.
- Thank you, Miss Li.
- Here.
Don't bother cooking.
We'll have dinner at my house.
- Okay.
- Alright.
[birds chirping]
[engine revving]
[engine rumbling]
[tender music playing]
[tender music continues]
[tender music fades]
Mia can be a handful,
especially when you're near her.
I don't want you around my brother.
Why? Are you jealous?
We'll go out.
We'll have fun, right?
Liar! Patpat's a liar!
Mia doesn't really
seem worried about her father.
So, he's capable of hurting other people?
Enough of this! You don't own me.
You're so confusing!
You're driving me crazy!
Everyone has emotions.
We should let people know how we feel.
[sentimental music playing]