Mia Hernandez…
has antisocial personality disorder.
Who would still buy
your book if they found out
the writer's mentally unstable?
People like him deserve to die.
What if he dodged it and you fell instead?
- You could've died.
- And so?
It's not like it's the first time
someone's tried to kill me.
Come here, hold on.
- What?
- Wait.
The butterfly hug isn't enough.
It only works when you're with me.
So I want you to be my safety pin.
- Safety what?
- Safety pin.
Someone I can rely on.
Aah!
[cries]
Matmat, I'm here.
- They're coming to take Matmat!
- Matmat!
No one's taking you.
We'll move away from here.
[theme music playing]
He's the one
who disrupted your event!
Ow! Ouch! Ouch!
- You're the lunatic!
- [woman] What?!
It's you who's spouting nonsense.
[influencer] The boy that
the dad touch on the head
has a medical condition.
He just wants to blame Mia
for what he did wrong.
So, Mia girl, you have my support!
[man] She's a public personality.
Mia should really be more careful
with her words and actions in public.
[woman] For me, Mia was right.
I mean she gave the man
a taste of his own medicine.
He could've just walked away.
See Miss Mia, people understand your side.
[door opens]
Mia? Mia, we need to talk.
If it's about what
happened at the bookstore,
don't worry about it. People get me.
It's not that. Come here, come here.
It's about Dennis.
What? He's alive.
Exactly the problem, he's alive.
Oh…
You want him dead?
[quirky music playing]
- You want me to kill--
- No, Mia! What are you thinking?!
[exhales deeply]
What if Dennis talks
and says you pushed him?
Are you asking me?
Yes!
No. Ugh!
[clicks tongue]
The thing is…
you keep getting into
this mess after mess.
Don't you notice?
Oh, Vincent…
I know you'll figure something out, right?
[breathes deeply]
I know, I know.
I know I can, but…
[quirky music continues]
…maybe sometimes,
you could help me too?
Don't just vanish without a word.
[quirky music continues]
Where'd she go?!
Yes, boss.
Me and Miss Mia are close.
She tells me all her life plans.
[thud]
Ugh!
[quirky music continues, ends]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [ship horn blares]
[chains rattling]
[Jason] We are home!
- [Patrick] Come on!
- [Jason] I missed this heat!
Ugh!
Hmm, smells fishy!
- [Gemma] Patrick!
- [Jason] Excuse me.
Excuse me.
[Gemma] Matmat!
- [Jason] Hi, Gemma.
- Welcome back to Maravida!
- [chuckling]
- [upbeat music fades]
Matmat…
is it okay that we came back here?
Do you remember this place?
It's okay.
[pensive music playing]
Shall we go?
- [Jason] Come on, let's go!
- Let's go! Let me help you.
[Jason] Thank you, gorgeous!
- Let's go.
- So where are we eating?
[Patrick grunts]
- [car alarm beeps]
- [Jason] Let's go, Matmat!
[Jason] Hey! Wait for me!
[engines revving]
[engines rumbling]
This is our house.
- Jason--
- Present!
You'll stay downstairs.
It's a big space!
Oh! Thank you, Gemma love.
Matmat, slow down!
- [Jason] Matmat, wait for me!
- [Gemma] Did you miss the beach?
I'm going to swim at the beach.
[Gemma chuckles]
- Don't worry about Matmat.
- [Matmat] Hmm!
The compound
owner's actually our relative.
They trusted Mama to manage this place
since the neighbors trust her.
So Matmat's safe here.
That's awesome!
Your mama's got
power around here! I like it!
[laughs]
Come on, I'll show you your room.
Okay. Matmat, come on.
Let's check our room.
Gemma, by the way,
you haven't given me your account number
so I can send the rent for me and Matmat.
[Jason] Gemma love,
that's kind of unfair!
Patrick hasn't even paid
yet but you're already chasing me!
Hey! You had so many requests
for your room, I had to get it fixed.
Yours just needed a bit of cleaning.
Come on, let's go.
Welcome to your new home!
- Wow!
- Oh, wow!
Wow?
Your room's right here.
It's beautiful! Just like you!
- [Gemma] Wow, huh?
- [Matmat] Wow!
[Gemma] It's already been cleaned.
[Jason] Whoa, it's huge!
[light-hearted music playing]
Patpat, this place is amazing!
[chuckles]
[light-hearted music continues]
You like it?
[Patrick] We're finally back, Ma.
But this time,
we're starting over differently.
[light-hearted music continues]
[waves crashing]
[Li] Coming home's
better when there's soup waiting!
- [Matmat exclaims]
- [light-hearted music fades]
Let's eat!
- Come on, let's eat.
- Thank you.
This is too much.
You didn't have to go and do all this.
I just cooked what Gemma bought.
That shrimp? She ordered
it from her uncle the other day.
Ma!
Hmm?
Patrick, I feel like I know you already.
Gemma talks about you a lot.
Ma, let's eat, right? [chuckles awkwardly]
[Gemma] Patrick, what do you want?
You must be Matmat?
Matthew Gonzales, 35 years old.
Just call me Matmat.
Hi, Matmat.
Uh, I heard about your mother.
Where did you live here before?
In Kahilom village.
Kahilom village?
What's your mother's name?
Tessie Gonzales, 38 years old.
Mother of Matmat and Patpat.
I know her.
She used to buy food
at our eatery all the time.
Oh, what do you want to eat?
[Matmat] Anything, just not Jason's pares.
What?!
But you always finish it when
I serve it to you! You're unbelievable!
Let me do it, Miss Li.
Just call me Mama Li.
That's what everyone here calls me.
Mama… Mama Li.
Mama Li…
If it's okay with you,
I'd love to be like a mother to you too.
What do you think, Matmat?
We already have a mama.
Can we have two?
Can we call her Mama too?
Is that okay with you, Matmat? [chuckles]
[chuckles] Happy day!
- Happy day!
- [light-hearted music playing]
- [everyone exclaiming] Happy day!
[music ends]
[inaudible PA announcement]
Where's his room?
[Dennis] To my dearest followers…
I'm in the hospital
because of Mia Hernandez.
- I'll tell you everything…
- Dennis!
about your favorite writer,
tonight, 7 PM on my socials--
Wait! Hold on!
Dennis, can we please talk first?
- Talk?
- Yes.
All I wanted was an interview.
And this is what I got!
I have a witness.
Mia's boyfriend.
Boyfriend?!
Hey! Mia doesn't even have a boyfriend!
I'm taking Mia down and
suing her for my physical injuries!
Don't come near me!
Even if you hurt me now, I'll still sue!
[Dennis's voice] Just one night.
Mia, think of it as a one-night stand.
That's enough for me to stay quiet.
You think I didn't know
you were recording me this whole time?
I'll just have this edited.
And everyone, including your followers
will know just how
much of a pervert you are.
[quirky music playing]
Dennis. Here, have some fruit.
I picked it myself.
Hello, friends!
Big reveal time about Mia Hernandez!
She's the kindest person!
She's the reason I'm here in the hospital
because she paid my hospital bills!
You're heaven-sent, Mia.
Thank you so much!
- [emojis bubbling]
- [quirky music crescendos]
[line ringing]
Madeth, come meet me.
I want updates.
[elevator dings, opens]
[mellow music playing]
[Matmat screams] Butterflies!
- They're coming back!
- [Patrick] Mama! Mama!
- [Matmat] Mama!
- The butterflies are coming!
- Mama! Mama!
Sorry, Mama,
it took me this long to visit.
[mellow music continues]
We couldn't come
back right away because…
Matmat and I kept
moving from one place to another.
We lived wherever we could.
Whenever someone kind enough took us in,
I'd leave Matmat there for a while
whenever I had a job.
But we'd never stay there long.
[screaming]
[Matmat] The butterflies!
- They're here!
- [Patrick] Matmat!
They're coming after Matmat! I want to go!
[Patrick] They won't take you!
We're leaving!
Okay? We're leaving this place!
We kept moving from one place to another.
That's how we've been…
for so many years.
[mellow music continues]
I decided it's time to come back, Ma.
Maybe being here will help Matmat
face his fear of butterflies.
And so we don't have
to keep moving around anymore
and finally live a quiet and stable life.
[music intensifies]
[exhales]
It's hard, Mama.
It's hard.
But we have to face it.
I have to face this.
[mellow music softens, continues]
[music fades]
[wind blowing softly]
[Gemma] Nurse Patty?
- She's here.
- Okay, thank you.
Who's here?
[Gemma] Oh, it's Cynthia Graciano.
Thirty-five years old.
Dealing with
dissociative identity disorder.
What are her other distinct identities?
An 8-year-old girl
called Little Chin Chin.
- Nurse, please fix up her room.
- [Patrick] What triggered it?
Trauma caused by her father.
She comes all the way from Estrella Sur.
She's been in and out several times.
Your patients really do
come from all over, huh?
Mm-hmm.
They choose this
place because it's isolated.
[gentle music playing]
[Gemma] I'll show
you where the patients stay.
If they're not at the dining area,
they'd be in their rooms.
Make sure to change their sheets
and pillowcases every other day.
Don't hesitate to ask
anyone if you need help.
Or me. I'll help you.
Follow me.
[gentle music continues]
[Cynthia whining] I don't want to!
- [Patty] Come on.
- I said no!
- Let's go.
- I don't want it here!
Let's go, Chin Chin.
Look, your room's really nice.
- [crying]
- See? We're here.
[whining] I don't want it here.
Chin Chin,
why don't we lay on the bed now?
This bed's nice.
[continues crying]
- [Patrick] We want you to be comfortable.
- Welcome back, Cynthia!
I mean, Chin Chin.
[gentle music continues]
[crying] I don't want to be here!
[wailing]
I don't want to be here!
Hush now.
Chin Chin…
Let's take your medicine.
I don't want that! I hate that!
I want candy!
- Candy?
- [continues crying]
After you take this…
I'll give you candy.
[whimpers, sniffles]
You promise?
- Promise.
- [music fades]
- [whimpering]
- [pill rattling]
[sobs softly]
- [sobs louder]
- There.
Hush now.
Get some rest now.
[pensive music playing]
Nurse Patty?
She's a patient, Zelda, right?
The one with depression?
[Patty] Yes.
She's friendly with the other patients,
but she's often alone.
Okay. Thank you.
[pensive music continues]
[pensive music fades]
[birds chirping]
[man grunts, shudders]
[somber music playing]
Are you a new nurse?
Nurse aide.
[shuddering]
K-Kai.
Person with alcohol use disorder.
[continues to shudder]
Nurse.
It's nothing new to me.
I-I just want to go home!
[sniffling]
[somber music continues]
[continues to shudder]
I get myself treated,
get discharged after a month.
Then the moment I smell alcohol,
I relapse! I'm sick of going in circles!
You can get through this.
You're only saying
that because you work here.
[breathes shakily]
Want to know the truth?
I've had patients who got worse.
But I've also had one who recovered.
He's been sober for two years now.
- R-Really?
- Mm-hmm.
You're already here anyway,
so might as well try.
[breathes shakily]
Let's go to your room?
[somber music fades]
[breathes shakily]
[Gemma] Patrick!
Hey.
How's your first day going?
It's going well.
It's pretty good here, right?
Just look at the place.
It's great. The patients
look like they're just on vacation.
[chuckles softly] Let's go.
Who do you think's going
to be the new nurse manager?
I have no clue.
Gemma, I was hoping
to talk to Doctor Lumbera.
Sure, I'll take you to him.
Thank you.
[woman] I am so sorry. I have to run.
[doctor] Oh, no problem, ma'am.
Thank you so much.
You're one of
the biggest donors of this hospital.
If it weren't for people like you, we
wouldn't be able to accommodate patients
who can't afford a facility like this.
Thank you very much.
You're very welcome, okay?
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Okay.
Doc, this is Patrick.
- Doc, I'm Patrick.
- Ah! Patrick.
Come, let's talk inside.
[Gemma] I have to go. Go on.
Person in the autism spectrum?
And has post-traumatic stress disorder?
Yes, Doc.
We've been moving from
place to place because of his trauma.
Sure, Patrick. Bring your brother here.
[gasps softly] Thank you, Doc.
You can deduct the fees from my salary.
Don't worry about that, Patrick.
We have a charity
care program in this facility.
The fee will be very minimal.
- Really?
- Yes!
Thank you so much.
I'm happy to help.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [elevator doors open]
I knew it.
What do you mean by "I knew it"?
You knew Sir Nurse is in Maravida?
No.
I knew that he's from there.
Oh, yeah. It's his hometown.
But, Miss Mia, did you also know that…
Sir Nurse works at the hospital
where your father is confined?
No.
[mysterious music playing]
I-Is that okay with you?
I thought you didn't like your father.
Is it okay--
[door slams shut]
Miss Mia?
[knocking]
Miss Mia, can I go home now?
[mysterious music continues]
Why am I even asking?
I can just leave.
I should go now.
- [giggling]
- [mysterious music ends]
- [whimsical music playing]
- [Mia] "In the middle of a forest,
in a grand palace lived a princess.
She was lonely for she was always alone.
As the princess continued
tossing stones into the river,
she unexpectedly hit something…
A young boy.
The princess had
unknowingly saved the boy.
From that moment on,
the shadow that once
loomed over the princess vanished."
"Why do you keep following me?
Do you want to be my friend?"
[uplifting music playing]
It's you, right?
[uplifting music continues]
We'll see each other again soon.
[ominous music plays]
We have to strike while the iron is hot.
Where's Mia?
From what I see,
you really want
your brother to overcome his fear.
But it all has to start with him.
The light bulb… The light bulb…
They say, that's how
the spirits in the hospital
warn that something bad is coming.
Finally.
We meet again.