TODAY IS AN OUTING DAY
This is tough.
Isn't it hard to make
decisions as a group?
DISCUSS AMONG YOURSELVES
AND SPLIT INTO TWO GROUPS
I'm thinking
I'd like to go with Taeheon too.
There's not much time left.
I keep hoping he'll pick me. If he do,
I'd be really happy.
Mmm.
I'm going with Taeheon.
You said, you know, "It's my life,
so I should make my own decisions."
"And it's okay to be more selfish,"
or something like that.
When I heard that yesterday,
I really related to that.
Since I came here,
I haven't had a chance to go on a date.
- It has to be just the two of us.
- Whoa.
Nice. He's really going for it.
DESIGNER
- Ah, that's good!
- Oh my gosh!
…you and me
Life's too short to play
Any other type of way
Hands up and release
- Your worries start to ease
- This is hard.
- Not much left to say
- Hmm. Ahem.
It's a sweet escape
The person I want to go out with today
is…
Today, I'd like to go out with Jobu.
Go on, you two. Enjoy.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
I see.
- Let's have fun.
- Let's go out, the three of us.
Either way, we'll have fun.
- Hiroya wanted to go on the date.
- We're in this together.
- "Think easy," she said
- She said
"Forever young and so wild"
"Or pull a gun and then fire it"
- "Easy," she said
- She said
"You're never young if you don't run
So get over"
- We still got walls on both sides
- Sides
Maybe
- I wanna know how to climb
- Climb
We're blind, blind
- Blind
- How'd we get air all this time?
- This time
- These things
- I never thought when you were mine
We used to break it together
Oh, oh, oh
We used to dive
In our highest feelings
Are we growing older together?
Oh, oh, oh
I don't wanna miss anything
When I'm dreaming about
When we were dazed and confused
- It's beautiful.
- It's a ranch experience.
Wow.
- Wow, there are so many cows.
- Oh…
Aw, so cute.
Put one piece of feed on your palm
and please try feeding
whichever cow you would like.
Ah!
- Here's the trio.
- Making the most of it.
Wow… amazing.
- It's kind of warm.
- Warm?
- Yeah.
Wow, you're good at that. Here you go!
Uh… Okay!
Ah, sorry, sorry.
That was my fault, right?
Yeah, my bad. Sorry!
Go for it! Ah, wait.
Oh! Sorry! This, this, this… Here!
It's coming, it's coming!
- Yay!
Sorry, sorry.
It was the way I fed you, huh?
Yeah, that was on me. Sorry!
LAKE KUSSHARO
APRIL 17, 2025
- The weather's great today.
- Yeah. It's windy.
- But the mountains look beautiful.
- Feels good.
Jobu's gotta be happy about this.
He is.
So handsome.
Oh, nice.
Whoa, swans in the background.
- I'm happy.
- Hmm?
- I'm glad we could come.
- Yeah, me too.
Was I actually taking that long to decide?
It felt really long to me.
I kept thinking,
"Come on, just choose already."
But in the end,
we still got to come here together.
I was honestly really conflicted.
Yeah, I get that.
Hmm.
I chose him out of the two,
and I wanted to understand
my feelings a bit more,
so I chose to spend some time
alone with him to figure out if…
these were real feelings for him.
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
- It's quiet.
- Yeah, quiet.
You're not the type
to eat ochazuke?
- I do.
- You do?
When I'm lazy.
I never thought
we'd get close enough to come on a date,
to tell you honestly.
Not at the start.
Remember our first coffee truck shift?
- I forgot.
- Forgot? I remember it clearly.
- We were totally silent.
- Silent.
So I'm happy we got closer.
Well, there's no need
to dig too deep into that.
What kind of encouragement
did your mom give you?
My mom?
I talked about you so much.
Oh?
She said,
"Either keep pushing,
or just ask him straight up."
She also said, "It'd be such a waste
to end things without even trying!"
I see.
The moment I started wanting
to know you more
was probably right around then.
Mmm.
Before that,
Izaya and Will left, right?
Yeah, right.
I wondered
what kind of bond you had with them.
Mmm.
And also, you were, well… crying a little?
I wasn't crying that much.
And also…
Hmm.
…your mom cooked and brought food
all the way out here.
That was nice.
If she cared enough to do that,
then her son must be really
a kind person too, I thought.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah, that happens.
- Makes sense.
- Hearing that must feel nice for him.
- It feels good.
Receiving a compliment about his mom.
MT. IO
- Wow.
- That's cool.
It's smoking.
- Whoa! It's probably really hot.
- No way.
- Oh! It's warm!
- Just warm? That's it?
Yeah, it's warm.
Oh, wow.
This is like, you know…
- Look at him!
- Not good.
It's that thing you use
on the spots you want to fix up.
My face looks better.
- It even gave me double eyelids.
- It's not gonna.
- It did.
- It's up to the work you put in.
No way… that's crazy.
Wow.
This steam show…
That's awesome.
- Love it.
- Amazing.
Cheers.
- Mmm, that's great.
- This is good.
- This is insanely beautiful.
- It's pretty.
You know how, at electronics stores,
sometimes they have those 8K TVs?
- I see that! I see that!
- The demo footage on them, you know?
This feels exactly like looking at that
8K display. Like, literally the same.
So, we have a little over a week left.
Can I share how I wanna spend it?
- Mmm.
- I wanna hear.
It's a little embarrassing.
I honestly really,
really want to see Huwei.
Yeah, I get that.
- I kinda came back early just for that.
- Ah, really?
We haven't really said it out loud,
but we've kind of moved forward a lot.
Mmm.
So I wanna make things clear between us
in this last stretch.
I want us to talk more,
and really settle
what our relationship is.
Mmm.
And you?
What about you?
For me, like I've said--
right now, the one
I'm most interested in is Taeheon.
- Oh.
- I've told him, too.
Mmm.
That's good.
We live together,
and he's the one I can talk about work
and everything else with the most.
Yeah, yeah.
- He just keeps looking better to me.
- Yeah, right.
But even if I'm the one who's into him,
if he's not feeling the same,
like in the first half,
it can't become a relationship.
So somewhere in the back of my mind,
I've been wanting to know
how he really feels.
Yeah. I think it's important to tell him.
I'll say what I need to say.
I won't run from it.
Mmm. That's really important.
That's good.
That's what I want to do.
Wow, that's some serious determination.
Ah.
Wow, this is really nice.
And so quiet.
It said "villa," so…
- Wait a sec. A sleepover?
- They're staying over?
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
- Wow! Incredible.
- Great view.
- Yeah, amazing view.
- Oh, it's a bedroom.
Whoa!
It's huge.
Oh.
I'm speechless.
So nice!
Oh, they're getting in the bath…
Yep, they're doing it!
- That was fast!
- Quick start!
Huh?
- What? I'm here?
- Yeah.
Aah!
I've never sat like this
in a sauna before.
- First time?
- You don't usually do this.
No!
My belly looks like it's in rolls.
Wait. Is that Taeheon behind him?
It was Taeheon who started it, right?
- What is going on?
- Taeheon!
He's so bold!
This is a soup made with
hair crab from Kushiro.
- Let's eat.
- Let's dig in.
Having a dinner in such a nice restaurant
like this… it's my first time ever.
- Really?
- First time.
I have to thank the three of them.
A while back, you know…
I was watching season one.
- I watched it with my friends.
- Mm.
And while watching it, we'd say,
"Taeheon is handsome, right?"
Like, "He seems so mature,
I'd love to talk with him."
You know, just joking around.
And now you're literally
right in front of me.
And we're eating together. It's surreal.
A year ago, I never imagined this.
It's a strange feeling.
I'm having fun.
Give me another way to say it.
- Huh?
- Rephrase it.
- Rephrase?
- Yeah.
I didn't think
we'd come here together, at first.
- Sapporo?
- Sapporo too.
I didn't think we'd get this close.
I didn't think I'd meet someone like you.
I didn't think I'd meet someone
I'd actually want to be with.
Yeah.
A mosquito, jeez.
Are you lying down? Right now?
Mmm!
Yeah.
- Can I ask you something?
- Mmm.
- In the beginning, in the Green Room?
- You said you were into William, right?
- Mmm. Mm-hmm.
I don't think you only have one type
when it comes to people you like.
He and I are
pretty different, right?
You mean looks?
- Looks or personality.
- Personality? But…
The things you have in common…
- Like, you both have a playful, cute side.
- Playful?
Cute personality.
Will has a really cute side to him.
He says random things, he's kinda spacey…
he's just naturally like that.
I see.
Those, you know,
playful parts are similar.
You two are similar in that way.
Is he hoping
he'll say they're the same? Or different?
Seems he's waiting for a certain answer.
Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- Mmm?
Just that I'm having fun.
What's fun?
Just thinking how nice it is
being here with you.
- You wanna sleep?
- Mmm.
Nice.
Good night.
What? What's that face? What's that face?
- I can't see your face right now.
- That's why I said good night.
- Good night?
- You can't see my face anyway.
- Then I won't sleep yet.
- Can you tell who I am?
No idea. I have to get closer.
- Aah!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
- You're close.
- Sorry.
You're really close.
- You don't like it?
- What?
Mmm.
- Mmm.
- Aah.
Come here.
I'll stay with you.
I'm already right here with you.
- That was amazing, right from the start!
- That's wonderful!
We were literally like this,
glued to the screen!
- They got so close so fast.
- Yeah.
That was so good.
When those two got in the bed, like,
"What's gonna happen?"
And he said "Good night!"
That "Good night" was--
That really means, "Are we
really stopping here?" Right?
- That was so good!
- You liked that?
I could hear that a hundred
times in my life!
That's why he's straight out
of a shojo manga.
He wants to be pulled in, but can't
say it, so he says "good night" instead.
That hand gesture was like
a signal of "Pull me in."
He loves sending all those little signals
and then getting pulled in tight.
- No?
- I get that.
It cannot be just having fun.
He's like, "Tell me more
about how you feel about me."
- Yeah.
- He's a princess.
Yeah.
But he keeps talking about
how much he admires Taeheon.
Yeah.
It probably makes him
unsure how to respond.
Even during the story about
the first coffee truck shift being rough,
he listens with
that unreadable expression.
When someone says,
"I liked you from the last season."
I'm sure he wonders if
he likes him on the TV show
or he likes the real him off-screen.
He probably can't tell.
So he wants to hear
something more specific.
Whether he likes the real him
or just admires him as a reality TV star.
Let's eat.
From before coming here
to today, has something changed?
It has, um…
A lot has changed, right?
- Something has.
- Something?
Yeah, we've gotten… closer.
When we walked into that place,
I already couldn't hold it in.
And once we got into bed,
of course I wanted to sleep next to him.
I think I was the one
who got closer to him.
But
he kissed me first.
- Oh my!
- It was sudden.
- Like, bam.
- Bam. He came in strong.
He did.
It felt like something just snapped,
and everything started,
all at once.
We didn't go all the way.
Mmm.
It was good.
I honestly wanted to in the morning, too.
Has something changed? Anything?
Being alone together
lets us talk about a lot of things.
And there were things I realized,
like what kind of person you are.
- You did? Really?
- Yeah.
I'm glad.
- Ah, man, -that was fun.
- Yeah.
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Welcome back!
- We're home.
- Lunch is ready.
- Really?
Yeah, it's lunchtime.
Is everyone doing well?
- We're good!
- That's a lot of soba.
- Did you have fun?
- It was great!
The place was amazing. It was so good,
I almost feel bad for you guys.
- Really?
- Really. It was incredible, right?
- In a wide open field.
- Wow.
- Thank you guys so much.
- That's great.
I'm glad. Mmm.
"Hiroya will be taking
today's shift at the coffee truck."
- Here we go!
- So he's got a chance.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
Oh! He went that way!
- Here?
- Finally!
I thought I'd like to team up
with Jobu for the first time.
I'm excited. Let's go.
- Have fun.
- We're off!
Finally.
- Isn't that kind of… very Hiroya?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Before going to the person he wants--
- He used to do that a lot early on.
- We saw those moments all the time.
- Exactly, early Hiroya!
Thanks for waiting.
One small drip coffee. Thank you.
- Thank you, thanks for waiting.
- Hope to see you again.
That end rush was wild.
Wow, that's amazing.
TODAY'S SALES:
6,650 YEN
All right.
Aah!
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
I've been wanting to try ramen
like this. It's pretty rich. Wow!
Mmm. This is good!
This is crazy good.
Crazy good? Is that Hokkaido slang?
How are you going to spend this last week?
Yeah, I guess
I'll probably express what I'm feeling.
So there's stuff you haven't said?
You went to Sapporo.
I haven't said it at all.
- Oh, really?
- I haven't said it.
Maybe it's kind of obvious in my behavior.
Yeah, it's obvious.
- But not in words.
- Come on, literally everyone can tell.
I haven't… I haven't said it.
Oh, really? You're not the type to say it?
I haven't said it yet.
What am I supposed to say?
Like, "I like you."
I haven't. I didn't say it to Will either.
But I can't say it unless it's, like,
getting really serious,
or "I want to be with you."
So I haven't said it yet.
- That's interesting.
- But this time, I might say it.
- I think that's good.
- I might be able to.
- You should.
- It feels stronger than last time.
My feelings. Mmm.
But what about you, Hiroya?
I mean, with you here, it's awkward,
but yeah, I have feelings for Taeheon.
But,
like, in the first half,
you can fall in love,
but you can't have a relationship alone.
Yeah, true.
It depends on
what the other person thinks.
Before entering the Green Room,
I couldn't express myself.
- But I've been working hard on that.
- Mmm.
If I'm into someone, I say it.
That's what I decided.
- Mmm.
- So I'm doing that with Taeheon too.
I think I'll just keep expressing
how I feel, all the way through.
- I guess that's what I'm doing.
- I see.
He probably wanted
to say that properly to Jobu.
Probably.
It's pouring.
Hey, are you any good at Othello?
I'm not good.
What do you want if you win?
- What do you want if you lose?
- If I lose…
- A wish.
- A wish?
- If you win…
- If I win.
I'll grant your wish.
You will? Really?
Yeah. And I'm gonna win. For sure.
Okay.
First or second? Rock, paper, scissors.
Tie. Go. Go.
- Which do you want?
- I won.
White or black?
- Black.
- Black? Okay.
Wait, wait.
- I'm totally gonna win.
- Slow down.
Wait a sec.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Is this spot shaved?
- Hmm?
- It's not growing?
- Huh?
- There's nothing here.
Hmm.
Yeah… It got shaved.
Here!
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Huh?
- Huh?
- What's your strategy?
- Strategy?
- Are you focused?
I am!
Don't underestimate me.
- Jobu can't focus.
- Yeah.
- It's cute.
- He just wants to flirt.
I really wanna win.
Aww, I lost.
Yeah, I definitely lost.
I was on the harder side, wasn't I?
You said you'd grant any wish.
Oh, so that means I'm the one
taking the penalty then, right?
No, no, no.
All right, what should my wish be?
- Make it spicy.
- Maybe I'll make it really spicy.
Something you can't even handle.
Is there even something I can't handle?
Well…
I'm actually practicing cooking right now.
So I want you
to eat my homemade food.
- That's my wish.
- Okay.
- But just the two of us.
- Got it.
- Sometime after tomorrow.
- Okay.
That's all you want?
That's such a cute wish.
We're out of bananas.
We ran out?
- I ate the last one this morning.
- How dare you?
That's why I'm not puffy anymore.
How could you? I was looking for one.
I'll buy more later.
- Ryuki!
- Welcome back.
- You look fresh!
- Ah, you cut your hair!
- Ryu-ryu!
- Welcome back.
You look… more mature?
- It's the haircut.
- He's smiling so much.
It felt like forever!
- It's been a week.
- Finally got to see you.
Huh? Are we missing one?
Huwei's in Thailand right now.
Oh, in Thailand?
Thailand? Yeah?
- A souvenir?
- Should we ask?
Ahem.
Ahem. Hmm, hmm, hmm.
I forgot to get souvenirs.
- Having Ryuki back is the real souvenir.
- Yeah, that was the souvenir.
Sorry, guys.
- Hu-hu!
- What! You're back!
- Welcome back… Wait, no. I'm home!
- Not welcome back.
Why are you saying welcome back?
- I missed you guys!
- We finally have everyone.
Did that elephant T-shirt
come in that color?
- It's a different color.
- Yeah.
I'm just so happy. Happy.
- I missed you guys.
- We missed you too.
- Welcome back!
- I'm home!
- You surprised me.
- I've been waiting.
Waiting for a long time.
They kept missing each other,
so it's been a while.
- Ryuki also just got back.
- Really?
Oh, right. I brought souvenirs.
- No way, you didn't have to!
- You didn't need to.
- You didn't have to!
- You don't have to.
You weren't even looking at Huwei.
You were looking at me the whole time.
I kind of wanted Ryuki
to try a little bite.
- Oh?
- Durian.
- Ugh.
- Freeze-dried durian.
What? I've never had durian.
- Why me?
- You said you hated it.
- Why get that for me?
- You bought something he hates!
Bomi, you're jealous!
- It's the king of fruits!
- What?
Oh. Wait…
This souvenir… Sorry.
Hold on, I might not handle this.
- Have some. Have some.
- No, I'm okay.
- I'm good.
- Try it!
- Give it a try!
- I'll see your reaction first.
- Wait.
- It's a souvenir for you.
A souvenir? Thanks.
The souvenir that you didn't bring.
One bite.
I can't bite it.
- What do you mean?
- I can't… I can't bite this.
- You try it once.
- You can't bite?
- It's too smelly?
- You don't want to?
Try it once.
Did you just age ten years?2
- Oh.
- Aah… Ugh.
What flavor is this?
It's durian.
Huh? Weird.
But it's good.
Yeah, the durian
just explodes in your mouth.
- It's normal durian.
- Regular durian.
Over there, they're the type
who can eat durian like it's nothing.
Oh, here it comes.
I'll announce today's shift.
"Ryuki will be the one
taking today's shift."
Ooh!
"Ryuki, please choose
one person you want to work with."
- Taeheon!
- Teho's really popular lately.
- Let's do it.
- Let's go.
- Have a good shift. Good luck.
- Have fun.
- Okay, then.
- See you.
Maybe he wants
a little life guidance from him.
Could be that too.
- Oh! I'm happy for them.
- Aah!
- That's great!
So…
what did you do last week?
We actually did a lot.
First, we went to a farm.
- Cows.
- Yeah, we fed the cows.
It was like a date activity.
- Jobu likes Taeheon, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hiroya wanted to go with Taeheon too.
- Mmm, mmm.
- Then Jobu got picked.
- Mmm.
- And those two went on a sleepover date.
We went to the farm, fed the cows.
- And went to the volcano café.
- That sounds so fun.
That's why I wanted to go with you.
- I wanted to go too.
- Together.
This switching from portrait
to landscape is cute.
Very cute.
Hmm…
I missed you.
Hmm?
- Nothing.
- Huh?
He just said it so smoothly.
I seriously missed you.
- A lot.
- Huh?
I missed you a lot.
- I missed you too.
- Mmm.
Huwei is back!
I'm really happy.
But about the souvenir…
I had mixed feelings.
I was like, "Was it for Ryuki?"
If you like someone,
you think about the other person.
Like, "He might like this."
Even small thoughtful things
make you happy.
Yeah.
I want to know how much
Huwei actually likes me.
- You end up wanting that.
- Sure.
Nice weather.
Yeah, it's really good.
KUMAYAKI
Hello.
- Would you like some coffee?
- If you'd like-- Oh, so cute!
Hello.
- You okay?
- Want some coffee?
Are you guys from Korea?
Yes, I'm from Korea.
- I'm from Osaka.
- Oh, I see.
Ah, sorry.
- Cute.
- Cute!
- Where did you put that thing?
- Found it.
All good.
- Thank you.
So cute!
Thank you so much.
Like Kazuyuki, when I get a boyfriend,
I want to have a dog together.
- But it's sad when they're gone.
- Huh?
Wouldn't you be sad when they're gone?
What do you mean? Kazu?
No. The dog.
- The dog!
- Doesn't mean I wouldn't miss Kazuyuki.
I think we are above 5,000.
TODAY'S SALES:
6,400 YEN
Well, we did great today.
- Shall we sit here?
- Yeah.
The snow is melting.
- The season is changing.
- And the sunlight.
- I've been wanting to ask.
- Ask what?
- About… coming out.
- Ah.
Your situation, coming out
after leaving here,
felt similar to mine, you know.
So I want to know
how your feelings changed
before you said it.
Mmm…
Well… I struggled a lot.
I also thought about giving up many times.
Mmm. Yeah.
I thought about many things.
But being in a place like the Green Room,
I'm so glad I met everyone.
First, we became friends,
and we built a real bond.
And I started realizing that
I'm not alone, you know?
Even the worst case scenario,
even if my parents,
uh, didn't fully accept me,
if I think of the Green Room boys
as my family,
it didn't feel as scary anymore.
That's how I felt, I guess. Um…
At first, of course,
being on this show meant
being in a situation
where I had to come out.
I mean… I put myself in that place.
But as I spent time with everyone,
my thoughts slowly changed, day by day.
I didn't want to say it unwillingly.
Uh…
I wanted to talk and express it properly,
you know?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Mmm.
There are a lot of emotions here.
And Taeheon is giving advice
about what comes after this whole
experience of being on this show.
I think Ryuki came here with
the intention, or at least the resolve,
to eventually talk to his dad about this.
But it still feels like he hasn't
fully settled into that decision yet.
Which is completely understandable,
because it's not easy at all.
I think that's why he wanted
to ask Taeheon about a lot of things.
Right. Taeheon's advice isn't
just pretty words.
- It comes from real experience.
- Exactly.
It's the hardest thing, right?
To speak with real weight
and real credibility.
Being able to do that,
that's his emotional maturity.
Absolutely.
Taeheon's different
than when he's in princess mode!
- The contrast is huge.
- In love, he becomes a different person.
- So that's what love does.
- People are like that.
And to be fair, Jobu still hasn't
actually said "I like you."
Yeah. Even though he said things
equal to "I like you."
Yeah. Maybe the reason
Taeheon was insisting,
"Say something else, say something more,"
is because
Jobu never actually said the word.
- I see.
- That's what I got from it.
And then Huwei came back
and Ryuki came back.
That's good.
That timing, when Hu said,
"I missed you." Wasn't that perfect?
So cute. It's the first time
they looked at something
on a phone together without drama.
- In this series!
- True!
Exactly.
- Oh.
- Good morning.
Ah. You okay, Jobu?
- I'm good.
- You good?
- Yeah.
- Good, good.
I'm planning to make dinner
for Taeheon, but not everyone.
Just for him. For him?
- Nice, go for it.
- I promised him I'd cook.
- With Taeheon?
- Yeah.
I'll cook for him for the first time.
I bought the ingredients.
So what do we do about our dinner?
Just cook for yourselves.
Not for me and Taeheon.
You aren't eating today's meal?
- Mmm.
- Okay.
- What will he make?
- Wonder what it is.
- You using this stove?
- No.
- Okay.
- Actually… no. I'm not using it.
Just the oven.
Watching Jobu
take his time preparing
the surprise meal for Taeheon today…
Um, I guess, I felt like
our pace is just different.
Of course Taeheon gives him
a different kind of response
than he gives me.
But I thought… "Wow, Jobu is amazing."
- That's nice. Romantic.
- Lovely.
You're eating here? Cute!
- Welcome back.
- I'm back.
Here they are.
Let's eat outside tonight.
- Huh? Outside?
- Only us. I made dinner!
- Let's eat, just the two of us.
- Two of us?
- Outside?
- Outside. Over there. Right there.
Which side do you want? This one?
- This side.
- Okay.
I made it!
What did you make?
- Lasagna?
- I made lasagna!
- Thank you.
- Ah, lasagna!
- Not sure if it turned out right.
- You worked hard.
Cheers.
- Good job.
- Cheers.
- Mmm. Here we go.
- Mmm.
Is it hot?
Maybe.
I hope it's cooked all the way.
Is it cooked? Not cold inside?
- It tastes good.
- Good? I'm glad it's good.
- Glad to hear it.
- It's really good.
I kept worrying,
messed up a few times making it.
Doesn't this take a long time?
About an hour and a half.
- An hour and a half?
- Well, maybe an hour.
Thanks. You really put effort into it.
I wanted to try making it.
Whoa! Deer. A parent and a baby.
- So cute. Really cute.
- They noticed us.
It's nice coming home from work
and having dinner made.
- Mmm.
- Especially when it's just for me.
When you won the game, why did you
pick the option of cooking?
Why choose something that takes effort?
Hmm…
I wanted to do something.
I wanted to try cooking.
And I wanted it to be just us.
- Just us?
- Yeah. I wanted us to eat together.
And I didn't know if I'd make it well.
When I talk with you,
it's a little different
from talking with the others.
I get butterflies when I'm talking to you.
And it's fun.
And sometimes I get a bit self-conscious.
You know… my whole body gets warm.
Since the day I met you…
um… my feelings…
haven't changed.
I like you, Taeheon.
Now…
…I want to
know more about you.
And I want you to know me too.
That's how
I feel now.
What should I say?
What should I say right now?
I haven't said that in a while, so…
it kinda makes me blush.
Guess we were never meant to be real
Turns out we never truly promised
What?
Was anything you said even real?
- I'm happy.
- You're happy?
In my mind
Please stay
Don't let my life
Fade
I want you to know me too.
And I want to know you as well.
- That's how I feel.
- Hmm.
But the thing is,
during our last date, honestly…
If I'm completely honest,
um… I wanted to talk
about a lot of things with you.
Mmm.
Of course, the stuff
we already talked about,
like what we talked about was,
it was like this at first,
but now it's different.
Well, those memories…
For me, those memories are ours, and…
fun to look back on them.
Since I realized we didn't
really get to talk about other stuff,
I felt a bit unsettled about it.
When I tried to talk seriously,
I mean, kind of… you'd dodge it a little,
or you'd laugh it off.
That's you, Jobu.
I don't think…
just being attracted to each other
means we move to the next stage.
At least, that's how I feel.
In my life
Hey
Stay in my mind
Please stay
Don't let my life
Fade
Oh.
We can finally see, after all this time,
where Taeheon's head is at.
- Jobu's just been saying the same thing.
- Exactly! That's it.
- Things were one way, but now he's happy.
- Or, "On the first date it was like this…"
- Maybe his conversation is too simple.
- He wanted to talk about more things.
So basically,
he felt like there was more to say, right?
So what exactly
does he want him to talk about?
The future.
- Oh… his vision?
- Yes. And, um… sorry.
- I might be overstepping--
- That's right!
- Please, go ahead.
- Yes, that's me.
- You remember Izaya?
- You taught us a lesson.
We're the type who wants to hear
just roughly what kind of life
or family someone wants to build.
Anything about the future.
Even a bit shared makes us feel reassured.
- Ah, I see, that's it.
- Oh! Good, thanks. Sorry, sorry.
- I'm his representative!
- Sorry, I totally forgot.
Yes, his advocate.
- He's into future vision talk.
- Stuff about the future, huh.
If there's a clear topic to discuss,
of course that would be great.
Even without a set topic, as we talk more…
Look at her go.
…a vision of the future naturally forms.
Wait… are you a robot?