The year is 1936 (Showa 11).
Natsumi has wed the navy sub-lieutenant, Ebata Takimasa.
Though these two began as an awkward couple,
they're slowly bridging the gap between them.
Reporting home safe and sound!
Though the two experienced their first fight,
Fumiko and Fukami's intervention turned the situation around.
I'm home.
Afterward...
[Katsudo-Benshi]
Please allow me to aid you.
And after that...
- Could you pass on a message to Fumiko-san for me?
- Yes.
And after that...
Please tell him I will see him there.
A rendezvous for two?
Natsumi's maiden heart becomes thoroughly excited with this development.
Shall we?
Yes.
[Café Bond]
Stay sharp, Takimasa-sama.
Look, there's Fumiko-san.
Though some applaud this new concept of "marrying for love,"
most scorn the sight of an unmarried man and woman together.
I am aware.
We must keep watch over them, and if trouble comes their way,
we are to claim they met by pure coincidence.
Understood.
But if I may ask, why are we dressed this way?
To keep them from noticing we're tailing them.
You seem to be enjoying this.
I cannot help it; I've never witnessed a rendezvous before.
I see.
Though I can't say this sits well with me personally...
I'm glad you and your wife managed to patch things up.
As am I.
Make sure to please your wife every once in a while, okay?
- Please her?
- What?
Don't tell me you've never pleased her before.
- Damn!
- Shh!
Quit smirking.
Careful, or she'll quickly tire of you.
- You know what? This guy's never please―
- Hey, Fukami!
I only hope this makes Natsumi-san happy...
It seems Fukami-san has yet to arrive.
Fukami's coming this way!
Ouch.
♫ Hey, the "sorry" that I was about to say yesterday ♫
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
♫ I managed to lie and say, "I'm not bothered" ♫
♫ But I want you to understand that I feel uneasy sometimes ♫
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
♫ Tonight's love story; shooting stars are shining brightly ♫
♫ I'll tell you the rest of what I was going to say ♫
♫ Hooked on you. I say, "I love you." Stay in my sight forever ♫
♫ In the next life or even past ones, I'll always want to see you ♫
♫ Hooked on you all the time. I'll tell you so just listen ♫
♫ I'll call your name many times or even tens of thousands of times ♫
♫ Will you stay with me forever? ♫
[A Calm Sea and Beautiful Days with You]
[Episode 6]
Why isn't he calling out to her?
Welcome.
It seems I've kept my companion waiting.
- Shall we?
- Right.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Here is our menu.
- Please call once you are ready to order.
- Thank you.
I recommend the coffee here. It's a famous blend.
They also serve milkshakes.
If you're feeling particularly peckish...
- Ouch.
- Shh!
- Welcome.
May we take this table?
- Yes, please have a seat...
- Shh!
Thank you for joining me today.
I'm quite surprised you arrived before our scheduled time.
I heard the navy expects one to arrive five minutes early.
That only applies to our duties.
But in that case, I should have arrived five minutes earlier as well.
I could have been captivated by your profile a moment longer.
You say such cringy dialogue with a straight face.
I feel both disdain and a minuscule shred of respect for you.
What an unexpected reaction.
Did you hear that just now, Takimasa-sama?
Oh, how dreamy!
Is that the sort of thing she wants to hear?
But it's so... cheesy.
Excuse me.
- Our apologies. Let us take our seats.
- Right.
Excuse me, please stay right there.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'll be frank. Please do not use Natsumi-san to do your bidding.
You had her pass the message along, knowing I couldn't refuse, right?
Of course not! You're only 80% correct with that claim.
However, thanks to her, we get to have a nice, long chat today.
Are you able to pick up on their conversation, Takimasa-sama?
I can read the lips of your friend.
But not Fukami, as I can't see his lips from here.
The real issue is these glasses. I'm not entirely used to them...
Then may I try them on?
Of course.
Does that look okay?
I see no issue, no.
I'll get straight to the point.
I believe...
you are an ideal marriage candidate.
I will request a matchmaker, of course.
But I wanted to hear your thoughts on the matter first, Fumiko-san.
You've chosen a woman who speaks out against men.
People will call you eccentric.
Am I truly that odd?
I require no affection from this relationship,
nor would I appreciate support from the sidelines.
I would rather wed a woman who can take charge of the home and is my equal.
In other words, you believe such "feelings" are not necessary?
If you are referring specifically to romantic emotions...
Then yes, feelings are a hindrance.
Loving before marriage will lead you to hold expectations for your partner.
And if they betray those expectations, you'll be disappointed.
Expectations are nothing but trouble.
Besides, marriage is simply an act to propagate the household.
It is a means to create a successor for the family line.
So long as we both fulfill our duties, I believe we're free to do whatever we please.
You make... a fair argument.
I knew you would understand, Fumiko-san.
- In that case...
- I will keep this perspective in mind for the future.
Am I not an ideal pick? We share similar values.
I dislike men who place their elbows on the table.
I reckon you thought of that just now.
What a shame.
Fumiko-san, though we'd be no match to them,
I truly believed we could become a nice family.
- "Them"?
- Yes, "them."
I see they offer something called a "shortcake" here.
[Café Bond: Beverages / Meals]
Then let's order it.
I was thinking of getting a quick snack myself.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, Sir.
Why have they really come here?
May we order a shortcake and a sandwich, please?
Of course.
Thank you.
But please make sure to leave room for dinner.
That, I will.
I reckon his wife was worried and decided to check in on you.
They've been staking out this café from the start.
I never knew you had a smile in you.
Should I call myself lucky?
The smile was not for you.
Not yet, at least.
Surprising me, I see.
What do you mean?
Wow, this all looks delicious!
- Western food is nice once in a while.
- Indeed.
Let's see... Excuse me.
- Yes?
- The restroom is...
Right that way, Sir.
- That was close.
- Yes.
I thought he had noticed.
- Excuse me.
- Welcome.
- Table for four, please.
- Four?
- Yes.
- How about we move closer to them?
Yes, let's.
- May we sit here?
- Yes, of course.
Thank you.
- Please stand right there.
- Pardon?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I can feel their stares digging into me like daggers.
I reckon the two haven't deepened their relationship yet.
I was worried you'd never forget about him.
How are your nights faring?
- We haven't yet.
- What?
No issue, he says!
Please excuse the rude statement I am about to make.
What do you think of Ebata and his wife?
I reckon the two haven't deepened their relationship yet.
At the very least, he'd have lent his coat to her by now.
Maybe they even hold hands, falling asleep, the few times he is home.
As for kissing... No, they had to have gotten that far.
But I predict someone passed out due to oxygen deficiency.
Natsumi-san? Natsumi-san!
I'd say that's the extent of their progress.
They have yet to go any further. This much I'm certain.
How could this be?
How did he...
We haven't told a soul about any of this!
How did he know about the oxygen deficiency?
Yes, Fukami poked fun at me for our first night.
Boasting about your wife already, are you?
We haven't done anything of that nature yet.
Besides, it's nothing we need to hurry.
You told him of our first night?
Of course not!
- Oh?
- What?
When did they...
Excuse me, have you seen the people who were sitting here?
Yes, they left a moment earlier.
Earlier? Thank you.
It seems they've left.
Is that so?
Excuse me, is it possible to take these out?
My apologies, Ma'am. We're dine-in only.
I see.
- What are they doing?
- It seems we cannot take out.
Then let us head out, after we finish our orders.
Yes.
What?
I never knew you had such a smile in you.
Unexpected, right?
Please don't take my line.
My apologies, Madam.
Are you on good terms with Ebata-san.
You two seem like complete opposites.
We get along because we're opposites.
He's an honest, sincere fellow.
I enjoy watching him unravel when I poke fun at him.
You have quite a mean streak.
I feel at ease around an honest guy like him.
I can entrust my back to him
when our lives are on the line.
Was that a bit much?
Perhaps I feel a similar way.
Natsumi-san is kind and pure. I find that I cannot leave her be.
Yet watching her somehow puts me at ease.
It seems we're quite similar after all.
Well...
Well?
I cannot say I agree in the slightest.
Still no good, right?
You're a stubborn one.
You hoped for someone who was your equal, were you not?
Touché.
I had hoped to tail them for Natsumi-san's sake,
yet we ultimately lost them.
Perhaps this attitude of mine is why...
I reckon the two haven't deepened their relationship yet.
Takimasa-sama.
M-My apologies! The door, right, I closed it.
- I was not aware you were changing!
- No worries!
- I promise I did not look.
- It is all right!
- It was an accident!
- I am now clothed.
You may turn around.
My mother sent us a letter.
She asked when we would come to visit.
Shall I answer by telling her we will visit around New Year's?
Yes, please do.
[Dear Natsumi...]
Right, there's still something I can do for Natsumi-san's sake!
- Let us go.
- Pardon?
Let us visit as soon as possible.
I apologize for how long it has taken me to come and greet you all.
I am Natsumi's mother, Satsuki.
I am her eldest sister, Harue.
I am her older sister, Akina.
This is Ichiko, and this is Rinko.
Unfortunately, our husbands had urgent business to take care of in Osaka.
I see.
Are they perhaps... avoiding me?
I can feel their stares digging into me like daggers.
So this is the man who didn't show at their wedding.
It's high time we see what he's made of.
Has Natsumi been providing well for you?
I'm certain my tutelage was lacking in some manner or another.
No, I owe plenty to Natsumi-san.
She has changed my life on land for the better.
I am truly grateful to have married her. She is wasted on a man like myself.
It sounds like everything has been going well.
Nacchan looks so happy!
- But...
- That won't be enough to gain our approval.
Right?
I'm absolutely relieved.
I knew my insistence would pay off.
Yes, having you both meet beforehand worked out indeed.
What?
Your father tried to rush the marriage. Thank goodness I convinced him otherwise.
What? I never knew they met beforehand.
We assumed it wasn't anything you both needed to know.
This is the first time I'm hearing it!
Takimasa-kun, do you remember?
Shibahara-san told me she left a wonderful first impression on you.
What? O-Oh, yes. I remember.
Nacchan, you remember this as well?
O-Of course!
This is bad. I have to remember.
What to do? I have to remember.
But now that I've lied, I can't ask...
Natsumi? Do you truly remember meeting him?
Yes, of course.
Nacchan, those ohagi were delicious! Where were they from?
From my husband's childhood friend's shop in our neighborhood.
More importantly, are things really going well with your husband, Natsumi?
Is anything troubling you? Has he ever put you in a fix?
Does he bring you discomfort?
Is he still leaving you home alone?
Calm down, you two.
You'd best speak your mind here.
You don't need to worry―
Of course, we do.
We know practically nothing about your husband.
Yes, exactly.
Takimasa-sama treats me well.
When we visited an inn, we viewed the stars together.
The stars.
And in the summer, he took me around town.
We've also promised to see some fireflies together next year.
Gosh, how romantic.
The other day, he helped me tail someone as well.
Tail someone?
My friend was meeting with a man on her own.
I was worried so we followed them in disguise.
I see. How courteous.
And? What else?
Well... Over here, Fuyu-chan!
Her letter wasn't exaggerating.
I suppose not.
If anything, he seems to really cherish her.
Maybe he's more dedicated than we thought.
Still, Natsumi's husband...
One, he didn't attend their wedding.
Two, he is often away for long periods, due to his work.
Three, he hadn't come to greet his wife's family, let alone her parents.
Four, he looks stoic.
Five, he can't even say something is "delicious."
"No issue"? Well, I see plenty.
And you only called Natsumi―
[Try again]
You only called Natsumi's food delicious while she was asleep.
Of course, her sisters would worry.
We cannot accept him just yet.
Although it seems he treats you well...
He really ought to take the lead like a man.
Well...
What should I do? I'm sullying Takimasa-sama's reputation!
Takimasa-sama's duty is of great importance to the country.
As for his manliness...
M-My apologies! The door, right, I closed it.
- I was not aware you were changing!
- No worries!
Yes, he had quite a set of abdominal muscles!
- What?
- I mean...
Sorry, my mistake.
- What's that?
- Tell us more.
- What?
- Yes, what's that supposed to mean?
Fuyuko, it's time you head to bed.
- But I want to know, too.
- You must be tired.
- Good night.
- Night.
And where are you going?
Now then, Natsumi. How are your nights faring?
Fuyuko.
How is he at night?
Is it true? Do military men have a... strong drive?
Wh-Wha—
I heard they ask to do it several times a night.
My goodness, that sounds quite exhausting.
But conceiving children is important business.
I'm sure we can give you advice, so tell us everything in detail.
Well...
We...
We?
We haven't done the act yet.
Wh-What? Hold on.
B-But you two have been married for...
Over half a year, yes?
Takimasa-sama isn't home often due to his naval duties.
As such, he said we ought to get better acquainted first.
- Still, that is quite...
- Yes.
Is our predicament so strange?
While I cannot interject much in the matters of other married couples,
having children is an essential part of being a husband and wife.
Yes, quite so.
Natsumi, does the wait not bother you?
I... feel that my heart is entirely not ready yet.
Nacchan?
Let's call it here for the night.
Wait right there.
No issue here...
I knew my insistence would pay off.
Yes, having you both meet beforehand worked out indeed.
How does that taste?
Yes, I see no issue with it.
No issue, he says!
It's a catchphrase of Takimasa-sama.
- Is that so?
- My apologies.
It's no worry at all.
Somehow the staring feels... different today.
Nothing, after half a year?
My condolences.
- Takimasa-san, are your abdominal muscles quite refined?
- Oh, really?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Fuyu-chan said something strange, that's all.
- Strange? I just said―
- No!
- Fuyuko! Enough.
- Shh.
- Aw, I can't ask?
Muscles?
Breakfast sure tastes better with a full table.
What muscle?
Oh my...
What am I missing?
I'm once again glad you two met before marriage.
Right, I almost forgot.
I almost forgot.
I must remember when we met!
If I don't remember the meeting, it couldn't have been anything official.
In other words, it's likely, we met someplace Natsumi-san frequented.
If we met anywhere, it must have been close by.
In that case, if I suggest we take a walk and take Takimasa-sama around...
Natsumi-san.
Could I ask you to possibly give me a tour around the neighborhood?
Of course.
Thank goodness he asked.
- So about those muscles...
- Mother.
- My...
- Fuyuko!
What?
So this is the school you attended.
Yes. I have many nostalgic memories here.
I often played tag in these streets with the other children.
What a lovely shrine.
My family used to frequent this shrine every new year.
This town is full of jovial memories for me.
I only need to pick the right spot.
Then I'm sure to remember!
[Hatsune Station]
I can't recall a thing!
I would ride the train from this station to school.
I see.
What else...
I fell ill at this station at the beginning of last year.
Is everything all right?
My friend accompanied me, even though she was ill...
I shall carry her to a doctor.
Never mind.
This is one story I cannot tell Takimasa-sama.
Well, um...
Oh!
[That Night | Now showing at WakakusaTheatre]
Around this time last year, I went to the theatre with my parents.
I remember feeling especially drowsy, except...
He's sleeping without care.
He must be tired.
Somehow I feel my eyes shutting as well...
I awoke with the applause signaling the show's end.
I've experienced something quite similar.
Thank goodness I'm not the only one.
Commander Shibahara had taken me to a show after an all-night shift.
I fell asleep as soon as it began.
When I woke partway through, I noticed the person next to me was asleep as well.
Guess I'll get a bit more sleep myself.
I was asleep until the very end.
What an incredible coincidence.
Wait.
Now that I think about it...
Say, what did you think of the individual next to you?
Next to me?
Oh, the sleeping lady.
I suppose she seemed to go at her own pace?
Then I'll get that underway.
Pardon?
Did your folks ask you anything odd after the show by any chance?
Now that I think about it...
Watch your finger, Dear.
You're doing great.
I wonder how that went.
Natsumi, did you think anything of the young lad next to you?
Next to me? Perhaps she meant the individual who was asleep.
I suppose he was fine.
My, is that so?
This must be it!
What?
Judging by your reaction, did you not remember either?
You as well, Takimasa-sama?
It'd be more surprising if we did.
Agreed. I wonder if Ikuko-san knew.
I will have to ask.
With that settled, shall we head back?
Yes.
Minmi?
Hisa-chan?
I knew it was you, Minmi!
It's good to see you!
"Minmi"?
Would this man be the one you wrote about?
Yes. He's my husband.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Minmi's friend, Saejima Hisa.
Thank goodness.
I was so worried to hear of your sudden marriage.
I thought you'd still have unresolved feelings to work out.
- "Feelings"?
- Remember?
After you collapsed and that man saved you,
you'd search for him here every weekend afterward.
- Did you find him?
- No...
Hisa-chan, you're the only one who saw his face.
What about that station attendant?
No.
I think he looked a bit scarier.
D-Don't say that about him...
We used to peek around these corners all the time,
but we never ended up finding him. You were so down about it.
I was worried you'd never forget about him.
T-That was over a year ago.
Well, I only wished to thank him.
No, that was the beginning of a romance, I tell you.
It was not! I truly hoped to thank him, that is all.
- Hey, Takimasa-sama will misunderstand!
- Now, now. Don't be so embarrassed.
- Hisa-chan!
- It's all right.
I understand this was all in the past.
- Come now, don't say something so sad.
- Hisa-chan, please...
It was the moment you two first met.
I was shocked to see your husband's face, truly.
How did you two reunite with each other?
What?
Oh?
Is everything all right?
Back then, I assumed a station attendant had assisted me...
She got ill because I took her around...
[Hatsune Station]
I understand. I shall carry her to a doctor.
Please guide me to the nearest clinic.
Yes, Sir.
If she stands out, some sordid rumors may float about...
- Ah, right.
- My apologies.
Please put up with this while we travel.
I must thank him for his trouble.
But for now, I only wish to sleep...
Did that help you to remember?
I will... make an effort to do so.
I believe fate was at play, somehow.
May I... get a bit closer to you?
- See you again.
- See you.
To think such a thing could truly happen.
Thank you again for your help back then.
Truth be told, I don't remember the occurrence myself.
I see.
- My apologies.
- No, it's all right.
If I may, could I see your hat?
What?
I suppose if it's for a moment.
You covered my face like so, to keep my identity under wraps.
Did that help you to remember?
I will... make an effort to do so.
Thank you.
To think I was unknowingly being arranged to wed my savior.
This is almost like a miracle.
Or perhaps this is fate?
Y-Yes?
What is it?
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
♫ I managed to lie and say, "I'm not bothered" ♫
♫ But I want you to understand that I feel uneasy sometimes ♫
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
It seems the train will be a while longer.
♫ Shooting stars are shining brightly ♫
♫ I'll tell you the rest of what I was going to say ♫
♫ Hooked on you. I say, "I love you." ♫
♫ Stay in my sight forever ♫
Here you go.
Thank you.
To think that was you, Takimasa-kun.
I heard you left your information with the clinic so they would bill you for the charges.
I had entrusted my husband to deal with what came after,
but he instead entrusted you with our daughter's hand!
♫ Will you stay with me forever? ♫
♫ Stay with me forever ♫
Shall we turn in soon?
Yes.
It seems our match was neither the work of fate nor a miracle.
Perhaps.
Even so...
I believe fate was at play, somehow.
The fact remains that you saved me that day, Takimasa-sama.
Natsumi-san...
This was fate.
May I... get a bit closer to you?
I will not force you, of course.
It is... quite warm, is it not?
Yes.
Takimasa-sama?
I know I made the suggestion,
but if you stick so close, I...
I cannot...
Natsumi-san.
Yes?
If...
If you still feel anxious...
No, of course not.
The...
The only person I wish would touch me...
The only person I wish would embrace me...
Will forever be...
you, Takimasa-sama.
I feel the very same.
Even when we are apart,
I'll make sure you won't forget me.
Natsumi-san.
You're beautiful.
A gift?
[Preview]
You won't be getting one for yourself, Takimasa-sama?
- Could you repeat―
- No.
There has been development between these two!
I'd like you to rely on me. We're a family now.
[This drama is fiction.]
I've decided to make this year end celebration a special one for Takimasa-sama.
♫ I am in love with you ♫