The year is 1936 (Showa 11).
[Katsudo-Benshi]
Natsumi has wed the navy sub-lieutenant, Ebata Takimasa.
Though these two began as an awkward couple, they're slowly bridging the gap between them.
In that case, I must absolutely return home, right?
However, Takimasa is burdened with a difficult past.
Have I forced you to recall a sad memory?
No.
Natsumi was then invited to the Floral Fleet Commune, a gathering for naval wives.
There, she met a woman named Yoshimori Fumiko.
Pardon me, Ma'am.
I am happy to see you all at our Floral Fleet today.
Ladies, our duty is to protect our homes, raise our children,
and support our husbands while they are away.
I'm sure you all are well aware of the immense responsibilities you shoulder.
So let us allow ourselves this day to relax, and unwind.
- Mitsuko-san, may I?
- What is it?
Natsumi-chan.
Ladies, this is Natsumi-chan. I mentioned her at a previous gathering, as you may recall.
I am Ebata's wife, Natsumi. It's an honor to meet you all.
- It's our pleasure.
- Pleased to meet you.
Has married life been faring well for you and your husband?
Yes, Ma'am.
My, a newlywed couple indeed.
I pray you grow accustomed to life as a naval wife, Dear.
Especially with the potential for "other women."
Takimasa-sama would never do something of that nature.
When greeting my aunt, beware to never interrupt her.
My, how absolutely adorable!
I'd expect nothing less from newlyweds.
We remember when all of us had times like this, don't we?
You must be cherished by your husband.
How unexpected of Ebata-kun!
And I must say, your tea was a delight as well.
It seems you are as thorough with your work...
as Fumiko-san claimed.
Thank you very much, Ma'am.
That was a job well done.
I owe it all to you, Fumiko-san.
If I may ask, is it quite common for naval folk
to frequent geishas and have mistresses?
I cannot help but be curious.
I see.
I can only speak on what I know, but perhaps it may help.
One wife keeps her husband on a well-kept leash by being good friends with his geishas.
Another sent all her husband's children to university, legitimate or not.
And another lives in harmony with her loyal husband, despite having no children of their own.
Each has her own style and none are similar to the other.
As such,
I believe you, too, shall simply build a relationship of your own, Natsumi-san.
Takimasa-sama.
Thank you;
your advice fills me with confidence.
You're quite welcome.
Now then, let us get to our main topic of the day.
November will bring an end to these latter drills,
leaving the younger officers with plenty of downtime.
As such,
let us choose which ladies to send as their potential marriage candidates.
Fumiko-san.
Why do you think I've invited you today? You are to join us.
You cannot remain a bachelorette forever.
How about this lieutenant commander?
- My, what a handsome man!
- He looks wonderful.
I suppose.
Say, what of the sub-lieutenant named Fukami?
I would consider him.
Sub-lieutenant Fukami? For you, he is a bit, well...
- Right, ladies?
- Yes, I wholeheartedly agree.
Though, perhaps he is well suited for my youngest daughter.
She is quite the beauty, and they would make a fair match.
Fumiko-san,
was that perhaps on purpose?
Is this "Fukami-san" an acquaintance of yours?
No, I only know his name.
But with his looks, personality, and well-off family,
he is an incredibly sought-after bachelor.
So raising his name will divert the conversation, won't it?
I see.
Caught a cold?
No. Someone must be gossiping about me.
You're quite the M, after all.
"M" means a popular man.
Oh, how I wish that were me.
How about you also start a family of your own?
Wow! Never thought I'd hear that sentiment from you, Ebata-kun.
Quit pulling my leg.
I'm sure plenty of ladies are dying to have your hand in marriage.
Isn't there anyone you...
- You loveー
- No way!
What now?
Love isn't necessary for marriage. If anything, it's a burden.
You married your wife without ever meeting her before, didn't you?
I suppose I did, yes.
I know I'll have to marry eventually.
But
I'm not expecting anything grand from marriage.
Marriage is done to propagate the family line, nothing more.
I'm almost impressed with how rational you can be.
How can they be so jovial every time?
Meanwhile, I'm on pins and needles...
This individual is...
The wife of Lieutenant Akiyama, Junko-san.
Junko-san, is something bothering you?
Natsumi-san, I believe?
Yes.
We must strive to gather information on our own initiative.
It's not as if the navy will explain its every detail to us.
Our duty is staying informed via newspaper or radio
and building viable connections here.
Yes, I agree.
But what were you worried about?
Let's not talk about this. It's nothing a newlywed needs to be burdened with.
Oh...
More importantly, do you know your husband well?
Personality and preferences are one thing. But knowing his past is just as important.
Have I forced you to recall a sad memory?
No.
His past...
You cannot call yourselves husband and wife without knowing that much.
♫ Hey, the "sorry" that I was about to say yesterday ♫
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
♫ I managed to lie and say, "I'm not bothered" ♫
♫ But I want you to understand that I feel uneasy sometimes ♫
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
♫ Tonight's love story; shooting stars are shining brightly ♫
♫ I'll tell you the rest of what I was going to say ♫
♫ Hooked on you. I say, "I love you." Stay in my sight forever ♫
♫ In the next life or even past ones, I'll always want to see you ♫
♫ Hooked on you all the time. I'll tell you so just listen ♫
♫ I'll call your name many times or even tens of thousands of times ♫
♫ Will you stay with me forever? ♫
[A Calm Sea and Beautiful Days with You]
[Episode 4]
You cannot call yourselves husband and wife without knowing that much.
Excuse me.
Yes, one moment.
Fumiko-san!
I apologize for stopping by without notice.
I realized I hadn't thanked you for your help the other day.
No, I should be thanking you.
If you happen to have time...
Would you like to cook curry and rice together?
Is this a waitress' apron?
Now I'm not interested in cafes that have changed anymore,
but I longed for the waitress outfit when I was younger.
So I figured dressing cute would lift the spirits a bit.
Shall we get cooking?
Yes, let's.
Will you be wearing a smock, Fumiko-san?
Frills are not my style.
I cut the vegetables into chunks...
I'm sure that will be fine.
Are you taking notes?
Yes. This is my first time making curry and rice.
I'm surprised.
[Golden Curry Powder]
- Please try this.
- I will.
- Too spicy?
- No, this is a taste for mature palettes.
It's delicious!
Thank you for visiting today, Fumiko-san.
These past few days, I've been stuck pondering something Junko-san mentioned.
Knowing his past is just as important.
You cannot call yourselves husband and wife without knowing that much.
I had even considered asking Ikuko-san about Takimasa-sama's past.
However, I do not know if I am allowed to do so.
Then let us go.
- Thank you for the meal.
How delicious!
I never knew adding chocolate could enhance this flavor.
It's a secret ingredient of ours.
I shall keep it close to heart.
I appreciate you both for so generously sharing your lunch.
But what's the occasion?
Natsumi-san has something she really wants to ask you, Ikuko-san.
Do you really?
No, or rather...
I wish to know more about Takimasa-sama.
I see.
All I know of Taki-kun's past is that his parents passed when he was 14 years old.
He came to our home about six months later.
That is all.
I know very little about his life before he arrived here.
Is that so.
I'm terribly sorry I was no help, Dear.
No, thank you for sharing regardless.
Remember what I told you before, Dear.
Taki-kun will accept whatever you have to say.
I suppose so.
- Did she fall asleep?
- Yes.
It seems a full stomach lulled her to bed.
Or perhaps she had been so anxious about Taki-kun's past,
that she hadn't been eating well.
I've truly pushed her into an unfair predicament.
Ikuko-san...
Ideally, the two would have met before marriage.
I ought to have gotten her better acquainted with Taki-kun.
And yet, we had them rush the marriage
for our own selfish reasons.
Selfish reasons?
You see, Taki-kun tends to treat himself without care.
He lived a cycle of study, work, and drills.
The few breaks he was given, he would spend on the vessel,
without giving himself a moment of rest.
Eventually, he had even considered enlisting in the army in Shanghai.
We were afraid he would willingly dive headfirst into battle of his own will.
We wished to stop him.
And as a result, we used this poor girl.
We quite forcefully negotiated their marriage.
But what if she still had dreams she wished to accomplish?
What if there was someone else she loved?
I cannot help but worry.
The family that you'll marry into is decided.
The ceremony is next week.
I understand now why everything was so sudden.
What would have become of me, if I didn't marry Takimasa-sama?
Would I have gotten married to someone else?
Natsumi-chan.
Seta-kun?
Doing well?
Fuyu-chan!
We thought you'd be lonely so we decided to drop by, Nacchan.
Oh, Fuyu-chan!
Is this the main room?
- Where do you all sit?
- Takimasa-sama sits on this side.
Oh! And what's this room here?
That would be where we sleep.
- Do you place your bedding side by side here?
- Yes.
Oh, you lovebirds!
Gosh, don't say that, Fuyu-chan.
Here, let me serve you both some tea.
This is rough.
Seta-kun?
I'm stepping out to get some fresh air.
- But our dango* (Japanese sweet dumplings)...
- I'll have one later.
Damn, why did I...
- What?
Perhaps you shouldn't have gotten married to me at all.
I'm so pathetic...
I want to support this person.
I wish to know what happened when your parents passed.
Cute.
- What?
Natsumi-san, are you all right? A trespasser wasー
Who?
A-And you are...
Takimasa-sama?
Natsumi-san... Thank the gods...
I apologize for my behavior earlier.
No, we share the blame.
We apologize for visiting while you were away.
So this man is... I feel a little uneasy.
My wife has told me much about you, Seta-san.
And I hear your work keeps you quite busy.
Oh no, not at all.
Did you have some business with my wife today?
Yes, I've come at her parents' request. They've asked that I check up on her.
They worry because you two haven't come to visit yourselves.
My apologies. I had planned to visit before the new year.
You truly are a busy man.
You must worry, leaving her home alone for long periods of time.
Gosh, I wouldn't be able to handle it.
You make a point, yes.
But she understands my circumstances, and for that, I'm eternally grateful.
Nacchan, don't you think those two are getting along well?
- Maybe they're more like-minded than we thought.
- But I'm grateful to her
- You think so?
- for understanding my preferences so well.
It took me ages to get Takimasa-sama to open up
or even smile.
Seta-kun, you sly fox!
Your tea, Takimasa-sama.
Thank you.
Here's yours, Seta-kun.
I made sure to make it extra bitter, just as you like it.
Right, thanks.
As he likes it?
Thanks, Nacchan.
That's so bitter.
Sorry, was that too much for you?
I guess that was a bit childish of me.
No, this is just fine.
She knows this man's preferences?
I will entertain these two for a bit, Takimasa-sama. How about you go ahead and change?
Right.
No, I shall remain.
I have things I wish to discuss, after all.
If you insist.
That means... he wants to speak more with Seta-kun, right?
What?
I cannot have them reminisce about childhood memories!
Why were you able to break Takimasa-sama's shell so easily?
- What's with the face?
- No reason.
She's never shown that sort of expression to me before.
- Then quit it.
- Quit what?
- You know what.
- You two sure get along.
Seriously, stop it with the face.
- What?
- You know what.
Oh, erm, well...
Though it may not be much for a souvenir,
I have some leftovers, if you'd like.
Caramels? And they're only leftovers?
He has navy money, and he visits other port towns.
Couldn't he bring something more decent...
Thank you.
Oh, I want some, too.
I have no more.
Nacchan, give me one.
Oh, but... Well...
I see now.
No wonder you were making a face.
What are you talking about?
You were jealous your husband was opening up to me.
I was not.
This is just like the time that stray cat only warmed up to me.
Don't liken Takimasa-sama to a cat.
What? He's totally like a cat.
No, he's not!
I apologize for the ruckus on your precious day home.
It's all right.
Rather, I'd like to know what you two were talking about earlier.
Earlier?
After I handed you those caramels, you were whispering amongst yourselves.
That is of no concern to you, Takimasa-sama.
Is it something you cannot tell me?
T-Takimasa-sama?
Tell me.
Seta-kun had told me
that I was jealous of him because you two were getting along. And that was spot on...
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Takimasa-sama?
I'm so pathetic...
I must apologize.
I had gotten unreasonably anxious.
Anxious?
Don't get so close to other men.
Okay.
Takimasa-sama, I've finished bathing...
He must have been tired.
You'll catch a cold if you don't properly tuck in.
Cute.
Takimasa-sama, um...
Softer than I anticipated.
Were you perhaps listening?
Yes.
So now I'll consider ourselves even.
I only poked once. You pinched about ten times.
Isn't that unfair?
I'm including your inappropriate use of the word "cute" as well, Natsumi-san.
O-Oh, well...
There are no rocking boats, cold metal rooms,
sounds of cannons, nor scents of oil within these walls.
Shall we get some sleep?
Yes.
I suppose this is what they call a home to return to.
And yet...
You must worry, leaving her home alone for long periods of time.
I'm so lonely...
To Natsumi-san...
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
No.
Is something wrong?
- Well...
- Perhaps you shouldn't have gotten married to me at all.
Pardon?
Staying with me
will only cause you more loneliness.
You may have been happier marrying another man.
I had given this some thought as well.
If I had not married you, where would I have been?
- As I thought—
- But that is simply impossible.
Any doubt I had disappeared as soon as I saw you, Takimasa-sama.
For I can only imagine a future where I have married you.
So...
Would you please tell me everything?
What?
I wish to know what happened when your parents passed,
and what became of you afterward.
- It isn't a happy tale.
- I don't mind.
You'll be burdened with its weight.
That is my exact wish.
Please,
let me shoulder this burden with you.
I understand.
But...
where do I even begin...
If I tell her my father passed due to an accident during a drill,
how will she react?
She will be left all alone with her thoughts tomorrow.
Takimasa-sama.
Please.
I will only tell her what she can handle now.
My father passed away 9 years ago,
during the summer.
I was fourteen.
My mother, who always had a weak constitution, took a turn for the worse after he passed.
She then followed him, two months later.
Afterward, I stayed with my father's relatives in Hakone, who ran a hot springs inn.
You're a damn stranger, understand?
Be grateful we even keep you around.
I'm starving...
After some time, I received a letter from my father's old friend, Commander Shibahara.
[Shibahara Kunimitsu]
In his letter, he wrote that my relatives were using my father's pension for themselves.
I went on a mad rampage.
I destroyed all the imported furniture and precious pots I could find and ran.
I ran until I found myself back here.
- I knew that was—
- Unforgivable.
Folks like them
deserve to stub their pinkie toes for the rest of their lives.
No, they ought to step in dog dung every day they set foot outdoors!
- Are you... angry?
- But of course!
I ought to storm their place myself.
I...
I've learned something new tonight.
It's alleviating to have someone get angry for your sake.
I'm glad I spoke to you about this, Natsumi-san.
And I'm glad
I've come to know you better, Takimasa-sama.
- A shooting star!
- What?
You're right.
I've never seen one before.
They say if you wish three times before a shooting star passes, your wish will come true.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
I should have said something.
We've seen two already. This could be a meteor shower.
I'm sure there will be more to come.
Really?
I want to support this person.
I will become his home to return to.
What is it?
I was simply marveling at how...
beautiful the stars are.
So...
am I.
Split...
No.
I'll be off.
Please take care.
The vessel was capsized in a storm, and they sunk.
I'm terribly sorry I couldn't prepare your favorite flounder today.
No, I surprised you with this one-day visit.
I shall look forward to it when I'm back for longer.
I have no issue with these dishes.
How about we enjoy the dango we received yesterday as well?
It seems Fuyu-chan ate most of them. This was the only one left.
She's quite the hearty eater, I see.
Please, Natsumi-san. Go ahead.
I can have dango at any time. You should enjoy it, Takimasa-sama.
In that case, shall we split it?
Yes, let's.
Split...
- No.
If I tried to do such a thing...
We aren't children.
I can practically hear him say it.
If I tried to do such a thing...
I cannot do something so embarrassing.
I can practically hear her say it.
Let's take them off the stick, and divide them into two each.
Yes, I shall go do that.
Thank you.
I sort of wanted to give it a try, though.
[Shibahara Kunimitsu]
[Ebata Takimasa]
Safe travels.
Thank you. I'm going.
Is something the matter?
No.
I'm leaving.
Safe travels.
Do you always stand there until you cannot see me anymore?
Yes, I do...
I would feel bad for keeping you out. Please, head on inside.
If you insist.
I will be off.
Please take care.
[Shibahara Kunimitsu]
[Ebata Takimasa]
What to do...
It seems I'll never be able to depart.
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
And thus, several weeks passed once more.
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
"Our photograph..."
"... has arrived..."
"safely."
What else...
♫ I'll call your name many times or even tens of thousands of times ♫
♫ Will you stay with me forever? ♫
[Momoyama Photography Studio]
I wonder what she's up to.
Junko-san! Good afternoon.
[Japanese Cuisine Restaurant | Miyasada]
You are Natsumi-san, was it?
Yes. Were you getting groceries?
Say, have you heard?
Of what?
They sunk.
Pardon?
The vessel capsized in a storm, and they sunk.
Perhaps this is a bad omen.
[Preview]
Marrying Takimasa-sama means I must remember anything can happen at any moment.
There is a need for resolve and a readiness of heart.
[This drama is fiction.]
♫ Hooked on you. I say, "I love you." Stay in my sight forever ♫
♫ In the next life or even past ones, I'll always want to see you ♫
♫ Hooked on you all the time. I'll tell you so just listen ♫