The year is 1936 (Showa 11), spring.
[Katsudo-Benshi]
Natsumi has wed Ebata Takimasa, a sub-lieutenant of the Navy.
Unable to attend their ceremony due to sudden military duties,
Natsumi only discovers two weeks later how he is expressionless
- and difficult to get a grasp on.
- I see no issues with these plates.
His character leaves Natsumi thoroughly perplexed.
However, bit by bit...
I believe we must first get acquainted with each other.
She comes to realize his kindness.
Yet Takimasa is once again called to duty.
Two months fly by after his initial departure,
and our tale resumes, with summer on the horizon.
- You have a letter, Ma'am.
- Thank you.
[Sender: Ebata Takimasa]
He returns... the day after tomorrow?
[See you in Tateyama at 2 p.m. the day after tomorrow.]
I wonder if Takimasa-sama has arrived.
This will practically be your honeymoon!
- Oh, no...
- You must get dolled up, my dear.
While I appreciated Ikuko-san's enthusiasm then...
Dressing like a moga is truly not my style.
A "moga"...
Is short for "Modern Girl" or the Western "flapper."
I'm already nervous enough to see Takimasa-sama.
But what will he think of this dress?
♫ Hey, the "sorry" that I was about to say yesterday ♫
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
♫ I managed to lie and say, "I'm not bothered" ♫
♫ But I want you to understand that I feel uneasy sometimes ♫
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
♫ Tonight's love story; shooting stars are shining brightly ♫
♫ I'll tell you the rest of what I was going to say ♫
♫ Hooked on you. I say, "I love you." Stay in my sight forever ♫
♫ In the next life or even past ones, I'll always want to see you ♫
♫ Hooked on you all the time. I'll tell you so just listen ♫
♫ I'll call your name many times or even tens of thousands of times ♫
♫ Will you stay with me forever? ♫
[A Calm Sea and Beautiful Days with You]
[Episode 2]
N-Natsumi-san?
Takimasa-sama?
Oh my... He's dressed all in white!
He's... so handsome!
[For Awa Hojo Station]
Wh-What is with this ado... adorable...
Well...
[Tateyama Hojo-cho]
It has been a while.
Yes, it has been a while indeed.
I shall carry that.
It's all right.
No, allow me.
I will handle it.
Thank you so much.
Are you feeling peckish?
So this is a "cream bread."
I've never had one before.
[Cafe Tateyama | Cofee, Bread]
Neither have I.
Thank you for the meal.
How delicious.
Well...
I see no issue with this.
Are those koi? Come this way!
- Spin more!
- Hey, wait!
Careful. Watch where you're going, all right?
Sorry, Sir.
Are you unharmed?
Yes, thank you.
Then allow us to continue.
Actually, it hurts a bit because I hit my hand in surprise.
Well, Natsumi-san.
Yes?
Are those clothes the ones you wrote about?
[Alcohol, Chicken Cutlet, Sandwich]
Yes, I went to purchase them with Ikuko-san.
So you remembered.
Her legs are quite exposed.
A skir...
Pardon?
Nothing. Let us be off.
What's wrong with Takimasa-sama?
A skir...
Skirt?
Your skirt is far too short!
How unbecoming of a navy wife!
Takimasa-sama!
Is my skirt bothering you?
What?
Let us be on our way.
As expected, he thinks my dress is unbecoming!
What am I to do?
What a wonderful view.
May I get a bit closer to the water?
Of course.
The sea is so beautiful, Takimasa-sama!
I had grown accustomed to the water after seeing it day after day,
but I'm reminded again how the sea is a beautiful sight.
Is that boat your vessel, Takimasa-sama?
It shouldn't be visible from here.
Is everything all right?
Yes, there's no issue here.
Please put on this coat.
Why so suddenly?
Why? Because the wind may flip your skirt and it bothersー
Because it is chilly by the waters.
Then I shall.
If I am to be honest...
I am... bothered by your skirt.
I knew it...
This dress must be unbecoming for a navy wife such as myself, right?
What? No, it's no like that.
It's... well...
I...
I simply don't know where to look because your legs...
They're visible.
- Pardon?
- That's why...
Takimasa-sama, if it's only you,
I don't mind you seeing...
A lady mustn't say such things so easily!
This wasn't easy to say!
It required immense courage.
Don't use your courage here.
You started this, Takimasa-sama.
I simply did not wish to lie to you, Natsumi-san.
I shall go change, after all.
You can't! Not when you look so adora—
You surprised me with your white naval wear as well.
I thought you looked quite...
- Handsome.
- What?
A seashell.
May I?
There you go.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
Sorry for the wait.
[Tateyama Inn]
Not at all. Were you able to relax?
Yes, the baths were wonderful.
Please enjoy your stay.
They've already readied our bedding.
They have, indeed.
It's still early to turn in for the night.
Right! May I shut off the lights for now?
- Why?
- The darkness would do us better.
Does that mean...
But I'm not mentally prepared yet!
- Natsumi-san.
- Y-Yes!
See? It's a beautiful view.
Natsumi-san?
What happened?
Please do not ask.
What?
The stars and sea make for a beautiful pair.
The night sky is stunning from our boat at sea
so I wanted to see it from land as well.
Stargazing from the boat?
What a refined pastime during work.
No, it's my work to observe the sky.
- By using the sun and stars, you approximate the ship's...
- One moment!
Please wait.
Am I allowed to know of this? Is it not a military secret?
Not to worry, even merchant ships practice celestial navigation.
He smiled.
So you can use the stars to approximate a ship's position? Mysterious.
If you use a Sextant, you can calculate a ship's position as well.
Once you're out at sea, it's all sky and sea.
This is why you use celestial bodies as a guide.
Initially, I thought nothing of stargazing. Yet now...
I've become intrigued because I'd hoped to share this starlit sky with you.
As if I could ever tell her that.
The stars spreading across the sky are so impressive.
Your work sounds fun.
What does your day usually look like, Natsumi-san?
Me? I do household chores, such as cooking and cleaning.
- I see.
- Yes.
Are the chores not taxing for you?
No. My sisters and mother taught me plenty at home so I had experience.
As I recall, you're the third of four daughters, yes?
I am. Harue Onee-san*, the eldest, is smart and dependable.
(*An older sister)
Akina Onee-san, my older sister, is fashionable and a former department store clerk.
My youngest sister, Fuyuko-chan, is bright and adorable.
She also has many friends at school.
I am proud to call them all...
To call them all your sisters?
Yes.
Harue Onee-san is wed, yet helps our father with his business, and...
My apologies.
It must be quite boring to hear me ramble about my family.
I don't mind.
Please, let me hear more.
Well...
Akina Onee-san quit her job in the department store upon marriage.
However...
Natsumi-san? Is everything all right?
Well, when you stare at me like that...
I get quite embarrassed.
A-Ah, I see.
I understand.
I promise not to stare, but with your permission...
May I...
touch you instead?
I-If that is too much,
I would like to at least come a bit closer.
Takimasa-sama...
Natsumi-san...
Natsumi-san?
Natsumi-san? Natsumi-san!
Natsumi-san? What?
Natsumi-san?
Natsumi-san!
Oh gods...
Water, water.
Ouch!
So you have to wait alone, without knowing when he'll be back?
Long time no see, Natsumi-chan.
Since navy men are away for long, it's not so uncommon for their wives to fall for other men.
You've become beautiful.
Seta-kun.
Seta-kun?
Yesterday night...
Takimasa-san and I finally kissed...
Natsumi-san, you're awake!
How are you feeling?
I apologize for last night.
I got ahead of myself.
N-No, I must also apologize for falling asleep.
You passed out due to oxygen deficiency.
In which case, it's my fault.
Oxygen deficiency?
Next time, please breathe through your nose.
Next time...
This is not a topic for the morning.
Agreed.
Shall we get dressed?
I asked the innkeeper about various spots we ought to visit.
Let's go a little further to visit there.
Sounds wonderful.
She recommended a sweet shop as well.
Where would that be?
It seems it's close to this shrine here.
What is this marker for?
That was for a delicious udon shop.
Udon? I'd love to give the place a try.
Will you be able to eat both udon and dessert?
I always have room for dessert.
- Ebata-sama!
- Y-Yes! Please!
Pardon me.
Sir, a messenger from the Navy called for you.
His expression hardened in a second.
Sorry, Natsumi-san. I got an urgent call, and I must return to the boat.
We'll most likely be setting sail as soon as I board.
I truly apologize.
It's all right. Please take care out there.
Thank you.
It can't be helped. This is his duty.
We spent the whole night yesterday, didn't we?
That is enough.
What do the other wives do when they're alone?
Ikuko-san told me some wives visit home.
Maybe I should give them a visit for a change as well.
But I cannot know when Takimasa-sama will return next.
I will only say this once. Listen well.
And keep still.
I will return to Yokosuka on August 24 after our drills.
- Is that not a militaryー
- Shhhh!
Promise not to tell a soul.
[Sekiya Tokuzo]
One week later, Natsumi found herself back home.
Nacchan?
It's been a while, Fuyu-chan!
- What's the occasion?
- Taki...
I mean, my husband said I could visit home.
What's your husband like? Is he handsome?
- Well...
- Fuyu-chan.
Your mother will scold you for causing a ruckus in front of your house again.
Then it'll be our secret.
Thanks for carrying my bags.
Are you with my father's company? It's nice toー
- By any chanceー
- Long time no see.
- What?
- I guess we haven't spoken since elementary school.
Right, Natsumi-chan.
- I'm home.
- Welcome back.
Oku-sama.
(*More polite expression of "oku-san")
Would you please confirm this?
My, already? As expected. Thank you.
Natsumi! Welcome home, Dear.
- I'm back.
- Good.
"Sa-ku-ra." Good.
Harue-san. The items you requested.
My, thank you. You were so quick.
Seta Juntaro... Is this really the Seta-kun I knew?
- Mommy, can we go play outside?
- Of course.
- Just be careful.
- We will!
Oh my goodness! they ripped it again...
To think you've forgotten all about me, Natsumi-chan.
No, I... remember.
But you were always chasing me with bugs and snakes.
You stole my books and gave me a weird nickname as well.
My old impression of you is so strong, you seem like a stranger now.
I'm really sorry for all I did when I was a brat.
I guess old memories tend to stick, right?
I honestly thought you'd have forgotten the nickname by now.
How could I? You constantly used it.
Since you no longer go by your maiden name,
I called you by your given name, but was that all right?
It should be.
Do you remember? Your mother once heard me call you "Natsu Mikan."
"Natsu mikan*"?
(*A Japanese summer orange)
I thought I was in for a scolding for sure.
Thank you for always playing with my daughter.
If you like natsu mikans, we have plenty. Here, take some.
I wasn't expecting your mother to misunderstand.
How nostalgic. Those were the days.
- Natsumi, come help me prepare dinner.
- Sure.
- Seta-kun, you'll be joining us, yes?
- Yes.
- Thank you for having me all the time.
- Of course.
Oh, you fixed the screen so nicely!
I'll entertain the twins until then.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
How ironic.
Her family name changes, and I finally get to call her by name.
Oh my? What a pompous young man.
Could he possibly feel a certain way about Natsumi? Oops!
- All together now. Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you.
I've missed this sort of atmosphere.
Your father would have loved to see you, too, Natsumi.
- He's in Osaka on business, right?
- Yes.
He should be back the day after next. Can you stay until then?
Yes, I can.
Will your husband manage at home alone?
Taki...
My husband is on duty for a while.
- How long is a while?
- Well...
Promise not to tell a soul.
It's a military secret. He can't even tell his family.
What's that about?
So you have to wait alone, without knowing when he'll be back?
- Fuyu-chan.
- Well... Yes.
What a coldhearted guy. I feel sorry for you.
Fuyu-chan, stop. Don't say that about a man who works for our country.
But that lifestyle sounds so lonely.
Takimasa-sama is kind and cares for me as much as possible.
I'm not someone to pity. I'm not lonely, either.
This one.
No.
I fumbled with my outburst yesterday.
I only made everyone worry.
Natsumi-chan.
Do you have a moment?
Come over here.
Welcome home, Fuyu-chan.
I'm sorry about what I said yesterday.
Seta-kun told me more about naval duties on my walk home from school.
I called your husband cold without knowing a thing. I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
You quite hit the nail on the head.
I am a bit lonely after all.
Then I have a great idea.
Gather around, everyone.
But I'm busy.
Nacchan, I'm sure that you won't depend on your husband when he goes to work, right?
So let's all teach her how to act sweet on him together!
But I'm busy.
Entertain her; this seems fun.
We shouldn't meddle in the affairs of other couples in the first place.
It'll serve as great reference for Nacchan.
Fuyu-chan, I don't...
Let her do this, Natsumi-chan.
She gave it a lot of thought in her own way.
Nacchan, come here.
I think it would be difficult for you to suddenly act sweet toward him.
So how about this?
"I want ice cream, please?"
- See? So let's start with an easyー
- Yes, we'll get you some.
We have no choice if you insist.
Oh, I feel like you're all treating me like a baby!
Nacchan, now follow my lead and try it on Seta-kun.
Ready, and action.
I would like some ice cream.
Keep it casual, all right? That's important.
I want ice cream, please.
Of course.
Perfect. How was that, you two?
I think that was good.
I believe Takimasa-sama would respond by saying,
- "I see no issue with that."
- There's no issue here.
I see no issue.
It's a sort of catchphrase of his.
Haru-Nee* , your turn for advice.
(*A casual expression of "an older sister)
A wife supports her husband; she does not depend on him.
Oh, come on...
In that case, your mother has an easy trick you can use.
- What?
- Here.
First, make a downcast gaze, without looking too far down.
Then, gently grasp your husband's sleeve.
Make sure to use your thumb and pointer finger.
Seta-kun, would you?
Yes, madam.
Yes, perfect.
Now slowly gaze up at him...
Tilt your neck,
look him straight in the eyes, and say...
Takimasa-sama?
My, calling his given name sounds so sweet!
Gosh, this is embarrassing...
What a technique! How was it?
I think it would be effective.
Men are weak to these sorts of things.
I figured.
- She said, "Takimasa-sama."
- If you'll excuse me.
- So?
- What?
How do you feel now?
We're out here on the sea for another two months.
Quit griping, I'll take you to a good res next time we're on land.
"Res" means a high-end Japanese restaurant.
You'd better bring an "inch," Fukami-san.
"Inch" means a geisha one is well acquainted with.
I have no inches.
What? Why not?
Because it's just a hassle.
- See you.
- Later, Sir.
Getting excited for S-play already? What a hasty bunch.
"S-play" is a codeword for "playing around with geisha's."
Conversations of the sort were rather crude to discuss in public.
Hence, the many codewords and slang.
I wonder if Natsumi-san has made it back to her home by now.
Someone's looking rather jovial.
Fukami.
You used to be all about work and look at you now, giddy with a wife.
Leave, I am not "giddy."
Your chopsticks are backward.
In any case, quit messing with people like that.
Say, are you going to buy the wife a souvenir?
- No.
- Why not bring her flowers like a Western man?
- Flowers?
- Being considerate is important, you know.
Since navy men are away for long,
it's not so uncommon for their wives to fall for other men.
What?
Natsumi-san would never.
- Your concern is unnecessary.
- What an irritating expression.
Quit en-ing me unconsciously, will you?
"En-ing" is boasting about one's wife or lover.
Oh well, act nonchalant while you can.
Seta-kun.
- Thank you for everything today.
- It was nothing.
How long do you plan on staying?
I'll be heading back once I greet my father tomorrow.
Then we won't see each other for a while.
Next time, I'll be sure to visit with Takimasa-sama.
Right.
Natsumi-chan.
You're smitten with your husband, aren't you?
Wh-What? I am not... to that extent.
I simply respect him.
You sure? You look like a boiled octopus.
That's because you've suddenly begun to tease me again although I thought you changed.
Don't be mean to me.
Of couse, I put on a nice front.
This is my employer's home, after all.
You haven't changed one bit, Natsumi-chan.
And one more thing.
You've become beautiful.
Well then, take care, Natsumi-chan.
You too, Seta-kun.
Two more months pass, and summer comes to a close.
The public was abuzz, as a Japanese swimmer made history
being the first Japanese woman to place on the Olympic podium.
And thus came August 24,
when Takimasa was set to return to Yokosuka.
I want to give my regards to your wife since we're here.
I got impatient.
Natsumi-san, you couldn't have!
Takimasa-sama, there is something I must speak to you about.
Takimasa. Your delusions are running wild.
Oh, Ebata!
We're finally back on land so why do you look stiff?
This is how I always look.
You'll scare your wife.
I told you I always look like this.
Does your wife use her maiden name?
Of course not.
Is she cute? Or is she pretty?
Why are you tailing me?
You live the other way. You should go home now.
Why? Do you have to ask?
I want to give my regards to your wife since we're here.
You're just enjoying this.
Hey, hold on now.
- Fukami-san!
- Oh!
Kogiku-chan and... Hisamomo-chan, was it?
- You got us mixed up.
- Yes, it's the other way around.
What brings you to these parts?
Our sisters sent us out on an errand.
We'd love to dine with you again.
But of course.
These two are geisha apprentices, also as known as "Hangyoku."
Where are you headed off to alone, Fukami-san?
Oh, I'm not alon...
He got away.
Why not bring her flowers like a Western man?
Being considerate is important, you know.
Though he arrived at the florist, our Takimasa is now stumped.
[Flower shop]
Welcome.
Were you looking for anything particular?
Erm, well, actually...
I came to...
Such frivolous actions are impossible for a Japanese man!
I came to ask for directions.
Is that so?
Well...
Sir, where are you headed?
Damn, I only wasted time.
Natsumi-san.
Takimasa-sama. Welcome home.
I have returned. Were you waiting by the gates for me?
I think I was grinning wide just now.
I got impatient.
I cannot allow her to see me so lax!
I wonder what happened? He looks particularly grim.
Is he perhaps tired?
- Let us head inside.
- Yes.
[Shibahara Kunimitsu]
[Ebata Takimasa]
I knew it; something is amiss with him.
But how should I ask?
What?
Gaze up at him.
Slowly gaze up at him...
Tilt your neck.
Tilt my...
Oh no, I already made eye contact!
I'm so nervous, I got it all wrong!
Wh-What is with this coy behavior?
No, calm yourself, Ebata.
Natsumi-san.
Yes?
My short sword rests on that side. Let go of my sleeve.
Right. Of course, my apologies.
No worries.
What is the matter?
My mother and sisters taught me much while I was home.
I see.
Personally, I wouldn't mind if you—
It went so well with Seta-kun, and yet.
"Seta-kun"?
Erm, S-Seta-kun?
Did you have a younger brother? Or perhaps a cousin?
No, he is a neighbor and childhood friend.
I met him again after eight years when I visited home.
He hadn't changed at all.
It's not so uncommon for navy wives to fall for other men.
No... impossible.
You've become such a beauty.
Seta-kun...
Don't bother with a man who'll leave you lonely.
Come to me instead.
I will convince your father one way or another.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
Natsumi-san, you couldn't have!
Takimasa. Your delusions are running wild.
I will prepare dinner.
Please relax, Takimasa-sama.
[Seta-kun]
Who the hell is this man?
Were they secretly fond of each other since childhood?
And upon reuniting with him after many years...
What if she made him home-cooked meals?
Or... But I've never laid on her lap before!
No, Takimasa. Those are your delusions.
Is everything all right?
Oh, erm, well...
You're wearing a smock today.
Yes, to keep my kimono clean.
I embroidered some ocean waves onto my pocket as well.
You're quite dexterous.
Embroidery has always been a favorite pastime of mine.
In situations like these, I ought to compliment her, right?
I...
I see no issue with that.
That's wonderful to hear.
Oh gosh, I left the pot on the flame!
Please give me a moment longer for dinner.
I'm sure if I lived with her every day, I wouldn't worry about other men.
How does that taste?
I see no issue with it.
Just say it tastes good, Takimasa.
Well...
Takimasa-sama, there is something I must speak to you about.
What?
No, can this be?
Actually, there is another man I've pined for since long ago.
Takimasa, knock it off already.
Understood.
Go ahead.
Well...
How can my cooking taste more like your mother's?
- Oh.
- Yes.
I hesitated since you are not one to bring up your parents,
but taste is an important matter after all.
S-So that's what you wished to ask.
My mother was frail and seasoned her dishes sparingly.
Then I will also—
But as a child, I always felt it was a bit lacking.
Natsumi-san, your cooking suits my tastebuds far more.
Your seasoning...
is my preference.
I am happy to hear that.
The Sekiya household tends to cut down on the sugar.
My mother and sister taught me their cooking tips when I visited home.
Your home.
If I may ask,
is this Se... Se...
Were you able to relax while you were home?
Yes, quite a bit. Thanks to you.
That's great to hear.
Was the whole family doing well?
Yes, they were.
My father wanted to meet you, Takimasa-sama.
My nieces were bounding with energy as well.
Fuyu-chan and Seta-kun were also—
Is that... Se-what's-his-name,
a childhood friend of yours?
Yes.
He's always been quite the bully. When I visited the other day...
You're smitten with your husband, aren't you?
Oh gosh, don't remember!
But enough about him.
Why is she turning red?
Does she really...
No, it can't be!
When I am finished, please prepare the bath for me posthaste.
I request you bathe quickly as well.
Pardon? I mean...
Yes, of course.
Tonight, we will see our first night to its end.
Pardon?
♫ Hey, the "sorry" that I was about to say yesterday ♫
♫ And my unreliable responses ♫
♫ I'm crying underneath. I love you ♫
♫ I managed to lie and say, "I'm not bothered" ♫
♫ But I want you to understand that I feel uneasy sometimes ♫
♫ My love for you grows stronger and it's like a roller coaster ♫
♫ Will it reach you while spinning, shaking, and crashing? ♫
♫ Tonight's love story; shooting stars are shining brightly ♫
My name is Fumiko Yoshimori.
[Preview]
I am only here to assist.
How graceful!
I imagined what it would be like to have a child like you, Takimasa-sama.
You mean...
Good fortune, during war?
[This drama is fiction.]
Talk to him. He will accept whatever you have to say.
♫ I'll always want to see you. Hooked on you ♫
♫ All the time. I'll tell you so just listen ♫
♫ I'll call your name many times or even tens of thousands of times ♫