=The Revenge of Begonia=
=Episode 9=
Tell me. Where is she?
Who?
I don't know.
Don't make me ask again.
Over there.
Stop right there!
Don't be rash!
Let me go!
Be careful!
Sir, it's all a misunderstanding!
Spare me! Spare me!
You dare touch my girl?
I...
I didn't know who she was.
Spare me!
He's lying.
He knows I'm Begonia.
I...
So, who told you to do this?
No one told me to do it.
It was just a moment of confusion,
Mr. He.
I have solid goods here.
I heard you're short on weapons.
Why not let my brothers bring them up
for you to see?
I'll bring them
to show you.
Put down your guns.
Put them down!
Are you deaf?
Go!
Protect yourself.
Capture them alive!
I will swallow them whole!
Boil them alive in oil!
Xingzhou! Xingzhou!
Stop hitting him! Stop!
Xingzhou!
Stop!
- Go in!
- Yes!
(Fairy Tree with Good Reputation)
Don't move!
You handle the aftermath.
Make sure to find out who's behind this.
Take them away.
Yes.
Why?
Senior.
Why haven't you avenged me?
What's wrong?
Had a nightmare?
My head hurts.
What's wrong with me?
You've been unconscious for three days.
The doctor said you were frightened
and it affected your pregnancy.
You need to rest in bed for a while.
Three days?
What about the theater?
Don't worry.
I've applied for your leave.
Just lie down and rest.
Sleep easy.
I'm here.
Useless!
You couldn't even handle a woman!
It was going smoothly at first.
Who knew He Xingzhou
would come so quickly?
Begonia's reputation is growing,
and she's meeting
more and more important people.
In the future, she will certainly
be a great asset to He Xingzhou.
If we don't kill her now,
it'll be troublesome later.
She's just an actress.
How powerful can she be?
You!
When will your brain
ever grow?
Zhao Zheng's incident
already fully showcased her capabilities.
Last time,
it was just like a blind cat
meeting a dead rat.
Are you trying to piss me off?
Since it's come to this,
might as well be thorough.
Dad, what do you mean
by that?
Even if I told you,
you wouldn't understand.
Where are they being held?
Open the door.
Vice Commander,
Mr. Xingzhou has ordered
that except for him and the Commander,
no one else may see these prisoners.
Open it.
Open it!
Yes.
Commander Ma.
Everyone out.
Well... Yes.
Commander Ma, Commander Ma,
please let us go.
All useless!
You deserve to die.
Attention!
By the Commander's order,
hang the bodies of these criminals
at the city gate
as a warning.
Yes.
My Lord, it's been found out.
The fake news
and the kidnapping of Begonia
were indeed planned by the same person.
Who?
Vice Commander Ma.
It must be
because you made him lose face
last time with the Inspector.
He wanted to get back at you.
It's not that simple.
What about the prisoners?
Mr. Xingzhou!
The criminals we caught last time
were all shot dead by Vice Commander Ma
and hung on the city walls
for public display.
It's his way of doing things.
They're all dead.
- This is no use now.
- Yes.
It's my fault,
I didn't assign enough people
to watch them.
Since he dared to go,
it must have been
under the old man's order.
It's okay.
There will be opportunities
to make him pay.
The priority now
is you need to find me a costume.
A costume?
It's been five whole days,
and I haven't seen you smile.
Do you really need to see me
make a fool of myself?
Regret it now?
Yeah.
But it was worth it.
Xingzhou.
Thank goodness you're alright.
My Lord, the Commander...
He's dead.
♪Listen, a night of rain stirs the heart♪
♪The moon hangs low on the branches♪
♪Only a tear falls into my hair♪
♪Wait, as the petals fall into a pond
when the wind rises♪
♪Yet the begonia remains unflinching♪
♪Rouge gently dabbed
on the lips in the mirror♪
♪A promise to an old friend,
a lifetime of shackles♪
♪The helpless and silent heart♪
♪Gazing across the mountains♪
♪Memories save me from nightmares♪
♪Sleeping peacefully in your arms♪
♪Believing in the affection in your eyes♪
♪All farewell songs sung♪
♪Sentimental in vain against time♪
♪How many acts
till the end of the old play♪
♪All destined, hard to fulfill♪
♪Yet such good times can't match destiny♪
♪An unresolved wish♪
♪Being with you is but a solitary bet♪
♪All blades mute♪
♪Heartless, greedy for the moment♪
♪The song ends, yet the dream's not over♪
♪In this life, we shall not meet again♪
♪Until the day when all flowers bloom♪
♪No one to keep the appointment♪
♪All given to the ruins♪