=The Revenge of Begonia=
=Episode 13=
I won't let you die so easily.
I'll keep tormenting you.
I'm afraid you'll never
have that chance!
Commander.
What?
Ma Sihai has escaped.
When did this happen?
Just now.
Ma Yaozu and their relatives
are missing too.
Order a citywide manhunt now.
Yes, sir.
Why aren't you resting in your room?
What are you doing here?
I want to see Ma Sihai.
Why do you want to see him?
He previously
had someone else impersonate me
to meet with the Inspector.
He didn't take me seriously at all.
I need to slap him
to vent my anger.
Take me to him.
Go and slap.
He's escaped.
I'm sorry.
You'll have to settle
for slapping the place
where he was held.
He Xingzhou!
You're so easily teased.
Alright.
When we catch him again,
I'll let you personally execute him.
How about that?
Not great.
What's wrong?
(Not that pattern.)
Nothing.
Let's go.
(Now the trail is cold again.)
(If the killer isn't Ma Sihai,)
(then who could it be?)
Anning,
are you asleep?
(It's so late.)
(Where is he going?)
Right, turn around.
Good.
Great, great.
Xingzhou, come.
Let's write this character.
Write the character "person".
One stroke down and another stroke up.
Standing tall and upright.
Xingzhou,
when you grow up,
you should be a person
who stands tall and upright.
(Memorial Tablet
of the late Mr. He Zhenyun)
So, you're here.
Mr. Xingzhou... No, Commander.
Merchants from Nancheng
have sent representatives
to ask if they should continue to give the money
they used to pay Vice Commander Ma
to the Commander's Mansion.
Tell them
to operate as usual.
Aside from basic taxes,
all other fees are waived.
Yes, I'll handle it immediately.
Anything else?
Xingzhou.
Mrs. Mingting.
I came specifically to congratulate you.
Not only did you
successfully clear your name,
but you also completely
took over Yuncheng.
Xingzhou,
you don't know,
if it weren't for my secret help,
Yang Anning wouldn't have been able
to get the key evidence
to overturn your case.
Is that so?
Thank you.
I don't want any thanks.
I just hope you can forgive me.
I don't need to be your wife.
I could just stay by your side,
serving tea and water as a maid.
It would be better
than being with He Mingting.
Yongxi, it's over between us.
Now, Anning is my wife.
I won't do anything to betray her.
It seems,
you really have fallen for her.
Yes.
If you want to leave my brother
and leave here,
I won't oppose it.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at how foolish I am.
I used to think
as long as I stayed by your side,
one day I would surpass her.
I didn't expect
it to be my wishful thinking.
Yongxi.
Done talking with Xingzhou?
I'm here to take you home.
(Cheng's Medical)
Now that the trail
with Ma Sihai is cold.
Could it be He Mingting,
whom I never investigated?
But he seems like a good person
and loves opera so much.
He wouldn't do anything harmful
to Senior.
Alright, Anning.
Don't overthink this now.
Such matters can't be rushed.
You'd better think
about the baby first.
What do you mean?
The baby is fine, right?
You never thought
about abortion, did you?
Anning,
have you really fallen for He Xingzhou?
No.
Am I
betraying Senior?
Don't talk nonsense.
You always saw Meng Xueqiao
as a brother.
Even if your master
had arranged a marriage for you two,
now that he's gone,
you have the right
to pursue your own happiness.
The baby is fine.
Go back and eat well.
Put Xueqiao's matter aside
for now.
Thank you, Yumei.
No need to be polite with me.
Wait here.
I'll get you some prenatal medicine.
(Body Measurements Diagram)
What are you looking at?
You're back.
Acupuncture.
Since when
did you start learning medicine?
As a child, I often watched Yumei do it,
so I picked up bits and pieces.
What have you been busy with lately?
Why did you come back so late?
Did you miss me?
How much did you miss me?
As much as you missed me,
My Lord.
Playing mind games with me again?
He Xingzhou, you're like a dog.
With a beauty by my side,
it's a feast for the eyes.
What's wrong?
You're pregnant.
We'll do it later.
Xingzhou.
Alright.
You go to bed now.
I'll take a shower.
♪Listen, a night of rain stirs the heart♪
♪The moon hangs low on the branches♪
♪Only a tear falls into my hair♪
♪Wait, as the petals fall into a pond
when the wind rises♪
♪Yet the begonia remains unflinching♪
♪Rouge gently dabbed
on the lips in the mirror♪
♪A promise to an old friend,
a lifetime of shackles♪
♪The helpless and silent heart♪
♪Gazing across the mountains♪
♪Memories save me from nightmares♪
♪Sleeping peacefully in your arms♪
♪Believing in the affection in your eyes♪
♪All farewell songs sung♪
♪Sentimental in vain against time♪
♪How many acts
till the end of the old play♪
♪All destined, hard to fulfill♪
♪Yet such good times can't match destiny♪
♪An unresolved wish♪
♪Being with you is but a solitary bet♪
♪All blades mute♪
♪Heartless, greedy for the moment♪
♪The song ends, yet the dream's not over♪
♪In this life, we shall not meet again♪
♪Until the day when all flowers bloom♪
♪No one to keep the appointment♪
♪All given to the ruins♪