=The Revenge of Begonia=
=Episode 2=
You must be Begonia, right?
Unbelievable.
(Lu Yongxi, daughter of the Lus)
The legendary Begonia
is so beautiful.
You're flattering me.
You're the true beauty of Yuncheng,
well-versed in poetry,
a beauty with brains.
You know me?
No.
But
I know this.
(He Zhenyun, Yuncheng's Commander)
Come in.
Sir.
We're at home. Why call me sir?
You needed me?
Heard you went to Nancheng
to suppress bandits.
That's Vice Commander Ma's territory.
He complained to me.
What territory?
Yuncheng belongs to the Hes,
not the Mas.
Good. That's assertive.
You're truly my son.
Still, the Vice Commander
is highly respected.
Respect
is due.
I heard you brought back an actress.
Messing around is fine.
Just don't take it seriously.
Like you did with my mother?
Scoundrel!
Who are you
to lecture me?
Get out!
I'm leaving, sir.
This hairpin
was a gift from Xingzhou
on my 18th birthday.
I heard
you'll marry Xingzhou's brother soon.
Such a useless thing.
Why keep it?
How dare you throw my thing?
It's nothing special.
I have one too.
If you like it,
I can give it to you.
No, impossible.
Xingzhou would never give you this.
He's being with you
to spite me.
Miss Lu,
you've made your choice.
Don't regret it.
Be at peace as his sister-in-law.
Accept it.
You lowly actress,
dare compete with me for Xingzhou?
Dream on!
You dare hit me?
I'm trying to wake you up.
Miss Lu, don't forget
the one lying next to Xingzhou
is me,
while you
can only be his
sister-in-law.
Shall we
make a bet?
What do you mean?
Bet on who
Xingzhou truly cares about.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Miss Yang?
Why are you pushing me?
Miss Lu!
Xingzhou, save me!
Xingzhou!
My Lord!
Get up there!
My Lord! My Lord!
Xingzhou!
Xingzhou, I'm so cold.
Xiaochuan, take off your clothes.
Yes.
My Lord, what happened?
I don't know
how I offended this Miss Yang.
She pushed me without reason.
We'll talk about this later.
Let me take you back first.
Get her out of the water.
Yes.
Miss Yang,
maybe change your clothes first?
Be careful of catching a cold.
Thank you, Mr. Zhao.
This way, please.
Where's my brother?
Mr. He just went out.
Go and get bath water
and clothes for Miss Lu.
Yes.
You rest for now.
Xingzhou,
don't leave.
Please stay with me.
Mrs. Mingting,
have some self-respect.
Don't call me Mrs. Mingting.
I beg you.
Don't call me that.
You're my brother's fiancée.
What else
should I call you?
Don't forget
how you betrayed me.
Xingzhou,
I know I was wrong.
Please forgive me.
I was forced by my father.
Lu Yongxi,
if my brother's legs weren't disabled,
would you still try so hard
to reconcile with me?
Xingzhou,
I know I was wrong.
Please, for the sake of our childhood,
give me another chance.
Please.
Xingzhou,
you've forgiven me, right?
I knew
you would forgive me.
Our relationship ended
the moment
you chose my brother.
Someone is waiting for me.
I won't let you find that woman.
She's a vixen.
She will ruin you.
Lu Yongxi,
how long will you keep this act?
I might not expose you, but I know.
You're deliberately framing Yang Anning.
Take care of yourself.
Madam, please change your clothes,
or you'll catch a cold.
Don't call me Madam!
Get out!
My Lady.
Who is this?
Well...
Greetings, My Lady.
(Liang Rufen, Commander's wife)
You are?
My Lady,
this is the lead actress
of Yuncheng Grand Theater,
Begonia,
a friend of Mr. Xingzhou.
Another singer?
Our family really is cursed,
constantly bothered
by these shameless, despicable people.
Last time it was Snowdrop.
Now, it's Begonia.
Truly, all flowers bloom.
You know Snowdrop, My Lady?
A gender-ambiguous person
who dirtied my eyes.
I heard he committed suicide.
He must have been involved
in some disgraceful acts
and couldn't face
living in this world anymore.
You're amazing, Senior.
Here, take your medicine,
or your fever will hurt your throat.
Who are you calling dirty?
- Miss Yang!
- Who are you calling dirty?
He was the gentlest and cleanest person,
thousands, hundreds of times purer
than anyone in your family.
This is too much!
Take her to the backyard!
Let go of me! Let go!
This is infuriating. Let's go.
Let go of me!
Stop!
Now, you're quiet.
You disgraceful little wench.
Were you blind?
How dare you offend me?
Which hand was it
that pinched me just now?
Put on the clamps.
Clamp her fingers hard.
Put more strength into it.
Clamp her hard.
Harder, come on!
Wait.
Mingting, what are you doing here?
(He Mingting, Commander's eldest son)
It's so hot today.
You might get heatstroke.
Fan for him, quickly.
I don't need it.
Mother,
please, for my sake,
spare this lady.
What?
Is she a friend of yours?
No.
I just really appreciate
her performances.
A flick of the red sleeve
dispels the dust of sorrow.
A twist of the vine
recalls ten thousand miles.
She's just an actress who sings on stage
and laughs off stage,
no different from a prostitute.
What's there to praise so highly
and plead for her?
Mother.
Mrs. He hates actresses so much.
Could it be
because an actress stole your man?
Thank you, Mr. Mingting,
for your high regard.
An actor dedicates ten years of effort
just for this kind of recognition.
Miss Yang, you're too kind.
Well,
it seems
I've underestimated you.
You're
seducing my son.
What are you looking at? Keep clamping.
Clamp hard!
Mother.
Mother, I spoke out of turn.
Please let her go.
Calm down.
Mingting,
I'm doing this for your own good.
People like her
are a disaster,
better to get rid of them sooner.
Let's go, come on.
- Mother.
- Let's go, let's go.
Get lost!
What makes you so bold
to harm my girl?
It was me.
What about it?
Mr. Xingzhou, do you want to shoot me
to defend your mistress?
Miss Yang is my friend.
Isn't this a bit too much,
My Lady?
What friend?
I suppose
a friend from bed?
Mother,
the servants are here.
Mind your words.
Don't be a laughingstock.
What laughingstock?
We've been humiliated
the moment
that cheap girl Jasmine entered.
How dare you mention her?
He Xingzhou!
How dare you point a gun at me?
Someone!
Arrest this rebellious beast!
Now!
Fine.
You've decided to rebel today,
haven't you?
Alright, Mingting,
let's go.
We'll see what your father
has to say about this.
What are you all arguing about?
♪Listen, a night of rain stirs the heart♪
♪The moon hangs low on the branches♪
♪Only a tear falls into my hair♪
♪Wait, as the petals fall into a pond
when the wind rises♪
♪Yet the begonia remains unflinching♪
♪Rouge gently dabbed
on the lips in the mirror♪
♪A promise to an old friend,
a lifetime of shackles♪
♪The helpless and silent heart♪
♪Gazing across the mountains♪
♪Memories save me from nightmares♪
♪Sleeping peacefully in your arms♪
♪Believing in the affection in your eyes♪
♪All farewell songs sung♪
♪Sentimental in vain against time♪
♪How many acts
till the end of the old play♪
♪All destined, hard to fulfill♪
♪Yet such good times can't match destiny♪
♪An unresolved wish♪
♪Being with you is but a solitary bet♪
♪All blades mute♪
♪Heartless, greedy for the moment♪
♪The song ends, yet the dream's not over♪
♪In this life, we shall not meet again♪
♪Until the day when all flowers bloom♪
♪No one to keep the appointment♪
♪All given to the ruins♪