=The Revenge of Begonia=
=Episode 6=
Say it.
The gifts for the Inspector
were all returned.
It must be Vice Commander Ma
messing things up behind the scenes.
Should we warn him?
On what grounds?
If it gets blown up to the old man,
it would just make me look incompetent.
Let's think of another plan.
But the Inspector is leaving in two days,
and we haven't even met him.
Xingzhou.
Talk to you later.
Xingzhou,
are you busy?
Mrs. Mingting, what brings you here?
It's about Begonia.
I don't know whether I should tell you.
Then don't say it.
But I think
you should know.
Wait for me, Xingzhou.
Mr. Mingting,
you...
You can't be like this.
When you face an enemy,
you can't retreat,
or show fear.
You need to hold the gun steady
like this,
and then...
Mr. Mingting, you're so skilled.
Have you learned it?
Have a try.
Mingting, I don't need you
to teach my wife.
If you're free,
you should teach your own woman.
Yongxi,
do you want to learn how to shoot?
I can teach you.
Since you're not interested,
and I'm tired anyway,
let's go back.
Bye, Begonia.
What are you standing there for?
It seems you really enjoy
challenging me.
I'm just learning how to shoot.
Who else would teach me
since you refused?
Really want me to teach you?
Steady your hand.
Why are you looking at me? Look ahead.
If you ever see Mingting again
behind my back,
you can get out of the He's Mansion.
My Lord, you're quite fiery today.
Could it be
that something has upset you?
I have encountered some troubles lately.
I heard that a high-ranking official
named Zhao from the capital
specifically requested
to hear Begonia perform.
It just so happens
I'm on leave for a while.
I heard Manager Li
is nearly driven mad by this.
Xingzhou, where are you taking me?
To meet Zhao Zheng and perform for him.
So, I'm just a stepping stone for you?
I could help,
but what's in it for me?
What trick are you playing now?
I dare not.
But I haven't done my makeup yet.
Going like this,
not only would it not work out,
but it might also bring blame.
Turn around
and take Mrs. Xingzhou back for makeup.
(He's Mansion)
Are you ready?
Going to see the Inspector
requires presenting
the best version of myself.
You wouldn't want me
to embarrass you, right?
Where are my pearl earrings?
What are you doing?
Put me down.
We'll talk terms in the car.
He Xingzhou!
The Inspector is not here today.
Please return.
I have urgent matters.
Tell me where the Inspector is.
Knowing the Inspector
loves Begonia's performances,
Vice Commander Ma,
invited him to Lingyun Restaurant
to listen to a play.
Unnecessary people should not disturb.
Inspector, it's tough on you.
I'll drink to that first.
(Ma Sihai, Vice Commander of Yuncheng)
Does this restaurant's wine
not suit your taste?
I'll change it right away.
Change the wine!
The wine is good,
(Zhao Zheng, Inspector)
but the accompanying dishes
do not match this fine liquor.
Sorry. I almost forgot!
Today's focus
is on Begonia.
Begonia usually performs
at Yuncheng Grand Theater.
I've been here a few days
and heard she was ill and on leave.
But you managed to invite her.
It must have been difficult.
Begonia is still unwell
and might pass the illness to you,
so you have to hear the play like this.
Who knew
spring
was covered
by snow?
If I sang like this,
I'd have broken the stage by now.
Stop.
That's not Begonia.
Maybe the illness
affected her voice.
Inspector, don't be upset.
Vice Commander Ma,
during my days in Yuncheng,
I treated you with utmost respect.
I didn't expect you
to deceive me like this.
♪All flowers bloom♪
♪All are given away freely♪
Begonia.
Inspector, if you want to hear a play,
just notify us and it will be arranged.
I'm at your beck and call.
This is
the second son of Commander He,
the young marshal of Yuncheng.
Today's performance
is a surprise
specially arranged for you.
A surprise.
Take your people and leave.
Don't spoil my mood.
And you.
I'm leaving now.
If you have any instructions later,
let someone inform me immediately.
Apologies for the intrusion,
and please don't take offense
at our forwardness, Inspector.
Fair enough.
Begonia,
you and Mr. He are...
Well.
Perhaps that's a question for Mr. He.
He Xingzhou, you're quite bold,
using your power to bully others
and monopolize Begonia.
Inspector, you misunderstand.
Begonia is my lawfully wedded wife.
You're the second son of Commander He.
How could you have married
an actress as a wife?
Do you think I'm a fool?
Inspector, you speak of justice
for Begonia,
yet your heart harbors the same prejudice
against the theater as others.
This shows you're not truly
a lover of the arts.
You...
I could kill you right now,
and He Zhenyun
wouldn't dare say a word against it.
Mr. Zhao,
I may not understand opera
or enjoy watching it,
but I fully appreciate
that a minute on stage
is the result of ten years of hard work.
Since I have married her,
I will not allow anyone
to belittle or insult her.
Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Zhao,
this is my fault
for not making things clear.
How about we drink this glass,
and I will perform a song just for you
as an apology?
A song of apology,
and a loyal and righteous Mr. He.
He Xingzhou,
you are a friend
that I'm glad to make.
Come, let's drink.
He Xingzhou!
Relying on his family
and bossing around over me?
That's outrageous!
Dad, that Begonia
is a natural seductress.
She's best at enticing men.
Today,
she must have completely
enchanted the Inspector.
You seem to know her well.
I've just heard, you know.
Who in Yuncheng doesn't know
that she's available to everyone?
It's a pity about Snowdrop.
If he hadn't died,
it wouldn't be Begonia's turn.
I told you not to mention
that person anymore.
Have you lost your mind?
Yes, I won't do it again, Father.
Begonia.
It seems this woman
cannot be kept around.
♪Listen, a night of rain stirs the heart♪
♪The moon hangs low on the branches♪
♪Only a tear falls into my hair♪
♪Wait, as the petals fall into a pond
when the wind rises♪
♪Yet the begonia remains unflinching♪
♪Rouge gently dabbed
on the lips in the mirror♪
♪A promise to an old friend,
a lifetime of shackles♪
♪The helpless and silent heart♪
♪Gazing across the mountains♪
♪Memories save me from nightmares♪
♪Sleeping peacefully in your arms♪
♪Believing in the affection in your eyes♪
♪All farewell songs sung♪
♪Sentimental in vain against time♪
♪How many acts
till the end of the old play♪
♪All destined, hard to fulfill♪
♪Yet such good times can't match destiny♪
♪An unresolved wish♪
♪Being with you is but a solitary bet♪
♪All blades mute♪
♪Heartless, greedy for the moment♪
♪The song ends, yet the dream's not over♪
♪In this life, we shall not meet again♪
♪Until the day when all flowers bloom♪
♪No one to keep the appointment♪
♪All given to the ruins♪