=The Revenge of Begonia=
=Episode 10=
(Ma's Mansion)
Yuncheng is a must-have for me.
He Xingzhou, you just wait to die.
Commander.
- Let her in.
- Yes.
Tell me.
What does Mrs. He have to tell me?
Your illness seems to be getting worse.
Why not change the doctor?
No need.
It's an old ailment,
hard to cure completely,
and just needs gradual treatment.
By the way,
I heard
Anning is pregnant again.
Yes.
You must be careful this time.
All food and medicines
should come directly
from the small kitchen.
Don't let others handle them.
I will.
What happened to your mother back then
was my fault.
Commander,
I really did nothing
to betray you.
Can you believe me?
With all the evidence against you,
what's there to argue?
The butler admitted it.
You seduced him
and even gave him your intimates
as a token of love.
You're slandering me!
It was clearly a set-up.
My Lord, please believe me.
I really didn't do it.
My Lord, let me handle her for you.
You little wretch.
I'll teach you for your infidelity!
Don't bully my mother!
Xingzhou!
Xingzhou, are you alright?
My Lord, I've always said
you can't marry an actress.
They're all lowly.
Soon she'll corrupt Mr. Xingzhou.
Someone,
lock up Jasmine.
No one is allowed to visit her.
Commander!
What should I do?
Back then,
I was blinded by anger.
But who knew
she would commit suicide?
Suicide?
Wasn't it a cover-up murder
just for your so-called honor?
Xingzhou, you...
Are you saying...
You've always thought...
Although
I wasn't good enough to her,
I definitely wouldn't do it.
She would never commit suicide.
My Lord,
your death was so tragic,
leaving me alone.
What am I supposed to do?
My Lord!
He Xingzhou!
You heartless beast!
You conscienceless jerk!
You killed your own father!
Do you have no conscience at all?
You're
playing the thief
shouting ''catch the thief'' again,
aren't you?
My Lady!
He Xingzhou.
You dared to poison Commander He
to seize power.
Someone,
arrest him!
Yes!
Stop, this is the Commander's mansion!
Are you trying to rebel?
Vice Commander Ma,
you said Xingzhou killed Commander He.
Do you have evidence?
Of course,
and it will convince you beyond doubt.
Tell me.
Who entered the study tonight?
Only...
Only Mr. Xingzhou.
And who brought in
that poisoned medicine?
It must have been
Mr. Xingzhou.
Must have?
So, you didn't actually see it
with your own eyes?
After Lord He fell ill,
he became very suspicious,
only eating food
made in the small kitchen.
Only Mr. Xingzhou had the opportunity,
and I personally heard them
arguing in the room.
Is that so?
What were we arguing about?
I didn't hear it very clearly.
Something about a will.
Right.
This is the will.
Lord He had only recently
discovered the true colors
of He Xingzhou.
So,
he changed the heir in the will.
Xingzhou,
how could you...
(It seems this is a carefully laid trap.)
Someone,
tie up He Xingzhou,
and take him to jail
for strict interrogation.
Yes.
No need.
I will go by myself.
Xingzhou.
Take care of yourself,
and wait for my return.
Mrs. He,
why have you come?
I've come to seek cooperation
to deal with
He Zhenyun.
Is that so?
Weren't you deeply devoted
to that old man?
Now,
I just want him
to die sooner.
If you don't show some sincerity,
how can I believe you?
(Gales make mighty warriors,
adversities grieve this man)
First bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Family responds.
My Lady, I'm sorry.
Guests arrive. Take off the hats.
First bow.
(The Commander's death)
- (is clearly a conspiracy.)
- Second bow.
- (It definitely involves Liang Rufen.)
- Third bow.
- (If that's the case,)
- Family responds.
(they surely won't let him off easily.)
A guest arrives.
Take off the hat.
First bow.
Second bow.
Third bow.
Family responds.
My Lady, I'm sorry.
I will surely reveal the truth
and give Zhenyun justice.
Thank you, Vice Commander Ma.
You wretch!
Why are you still here?
Get out of here now!
My Lady, there's no need to rush.
The truth hasn't been clarified yet.
Moreover, as the daughter-in-law,
I should stay at the Commander's wake.
You still dare to talk back
when it's come to this?
- Mama, are you alright?
- My Lady.
Mother, you've been overworking
these days.
Go back and rest now.
These family matters
can be handled after the funeral.
I...
Don't let the guests laugh at us
and accuse us of being petty
and treating her harshly.
Wait a few days,
and see how I'll deal with you.
Be careful.
Begonia, don't worry.
Though Xingzhou
made a mistake in a moment of confusion,
the crime should not extend
to his wife and children.
Mr. Mingting,
I believe Xingzhou is innocent.
There must be
some misunderstanding here.
I also hope so.
Begonia,
if you need any help,
just tell me.
Mr. Mingting,
over a year ago,
did you invite an actor here for a play?
Was Vice Commander Ma also present?
It seems
he was.
Begonia, why do you
suddenly ask about this?
I'm just trying to understand
Vice Commander Ma a bit better.
I think the matter with Xingzhou
might have been orchestrated by him.
That day,
it seemed he had a conflict
with Snowdrop.
♪Listen, a night of rain stirs the heart♪
♪The moon hangs low on the branches♪
♪Only a tear falls into my hair♪
♪Wait, as the petals fall into a pond
when the wind rises♪
♪Yet the begonia remains unflinching♪
♪Rouge gently dabbed
on the lips in the mirror♪
♪A promise to an old friend,
a lifetime of shackles♪
♪The helpless and silent heart♪
♪Gazing across the mountains♪
♪Memories save me from nightmares♪
♪Sleeping peacefully in your arms♪
♪Believing in the affection in your eyes♪
♪All farewell songs sung♪
♪Sentimental in vain against time♪
♪How many acts
till the end of the old play♪
♪All destined, hard to fulfill♪
♪Yet such good times can't match destiny♪
♪An unresolved wish♪
♪Being with you is but a solitary bet♪
♪All blades mute♪
♪Heartless, greedy for the moment♪
♪The song ends, yet the dream's not over♪
♪In this life, we shall not meet again♪
♪Until the day when all flowers bloom♪
♪No one to keep the appointment♪
♪All given to the ruins♪