♪Raindrops patter,
falling on red bricks and green tiles♪
♪Tears stain the red, gold-stamped
wedding invitation♪
♪His profile in the candlelight♪
♪Old photos and yellowing oil paintings♪
♪Reflecting the falling light♪
♪Worldly people, with heartfelt words,
don't feign naivety♪
♪Without you, spring doesn't come,
and autumn doesn't go♪
♪No winter or summer
in the vast expanse♪
♪Countless restless nights♪
♪I can't retain a single strand of hair;
in the end, it's a lie♪
♪Whoever the ending belongs to,
I won't be afraid♪
=Crush=
=Episode 6=
(Chiyan Gang)
Sir Fu has arrived.
Sir Fu.
Fu Yunzhen,
how dare you
kill Wang Hai?
You've ruined
our Shen family's business,
causing us great losses.
What do you intend to do?
A mere dog
dares to bark at our Chiyan Gang?
You...
Fu Yunzhen,
you killed my partner.
You need to give me an explanation.
Uncle,
open your eyes and see
who truly deserves to be your partner.
Under the guise of partnership,
Wang Hai was only
filling his own pocket.
Uncle, why don't you calculate
(Hefeng Bank)
how much profit
(6,000 silver coins)
he embezzled from the Shen family?
I helped the Shen family
eliminate a traitor
feeding off you.
How should the Shen family thank me?
We'll get
to the bottom of this matter.
But
Sir Fu,
you only talk about others.
Haven't you also been scheming
against the Shen family?
And
your affair with Moli
is unclear and suspicious.
You've reminded me.
Luckily, I saved her for Sir Xize.
Otherwise, if he found out
someone
deliberately sent Moli
to another man's bed,
the Shen family would be in chaos.
You owe me one.
I'm waiting for you to return the favor.
Let's go.
Will Master Shen let it go?
All he cares about is profit.
How Wang Hai died
doesn't matter at all.
That Wang Hai
was unscrupulous
and greedy.
Why?
Why did you give Moli to someone else?
(Fu Yunzhen.)
You came here
just to yell at your dad
for a woman?
Dad,
you know I like Moli.
Why did you still do this?
For the Shen family,
and for the both of you.
I think you did it for yourself,
for profit,
and for power.
Bastard.
Dad,
why don't you
estimate the price of me and my sister?
Whoever can afford us
can have us.
Shen Xize,
you little jerk!
You...
Master!
Are you alright, master?
The Shen family is vast
and secretive.
Recently,
I heard from one of their distributors.
Master Shen has a ledger,
recording all the profit links
and smuggling warehouses
hidden around Long City.
So if we find this ledger,
we can uproot the entire Shen family
and tear Master Shen to pieces.
I've searched everywhere possible
in the Shen family,
but found nothing.
Leave this to me.
Don't get involved.
Yunzheng,
now that I know everything
and have infiltrated the Shen family,
I can't stand by
and let you face danger alone.
Yunzheng,
why don't we join forces
to steal the ledger?
No.
What are you thinking?
Fu Yunzhen,
revenge is something for both of us.
Don't leave me out, alright?
Yunzheng,
what will it take for you to agree?
Unless
you kill me.
Sir Fu,
everything has been arranged.
(Chiyan Gang)
Yunzheng,
I've thought it over.
You're doing it all for my good.
I shouldn't have been unreasonable.
I'm here to apologize to you.
Yunzheng,
why aren't you drinking?
Are you still mad at me?
Eat something first.
Poisoning
and assassination,
I taught you those.
Trying to kill me with these tricks?
You know I can't bring myself
to kill you.
Alright,
I'll give you another choice.
Pick a target.
Didn't you say
you couldn't hurt me?
Then choose someone else.
You're crazy.
These are innocent people.
Did the Shen family
spare our innocent mom?
What do you want to say?
I just want to ensure your safety.
If you can't shoot a stranger,
someone from the Shen family
should be easier.
What's he doing here?
Earlier, I had Wei Zhan write a letter
in your name and handwriting.
It says because of the filth
of the Shen family,
you couldn't bear the humiliation
and decided to leave Long City.
He's now searching the city for you.
Hello,
have you seen her?
No.
Did you do all this
just to make me give up?
Once you decide to seek revenge,
it's only a matter of time
before you shoot him.
Shoot him.
(What's your name?)
(It's all my fault.)
(Come with me.)
Yue,
I'm already in hell.
You don't need to fall with me.
But have you thought about it?
If you fall into danger,
I'll be in danger too.
I won't give up.
Sir Fu,
after Miss Yue returned,
she locked herself in her room.
Keep an eye on her.
Who is it?
It's me.
Who said you could drink?
Where's Wei Zhan?
Didn't I tell him to watch you?
Stop blaming others.
It's you.
You bullied me.
I'll take you back to your room.
I don't want to go back.
You have to give me an explanation.
What explanation do you want?
Yuzheng,
why do you
keep pushing me away?
Is it because I'm useless?
You asked me to kill you,
but I couldn't do it.
You asked me to kill others,
but I couldn't do it either.
Do you hate me?
You're drunk. Don't talk nonsense.
I'm not drunk.
You...
You won't abandon me, will you?
Even if I have to give up
everything,
I'll never abandon you.
I knew it.
You think about me in your heart.
Yunzheng, come here.
I have a question.
Yunzheng,
do I smell good?
What's wrong?
My leg.
It hurts.
♪As winter evenings grow darker♪
♪When the air itself feels restless♪
♪When the hand that once held mine♪
♪Is no longer warm♪
♪When memories gradually♪
♪Lose their brilliance♪
♪Fireworks fall, and the night
crumbles into ruin♪
♪When neon lights outside the car window
are vibrant♪
♪When you said you liked them♪
♪When the summer night sky lit up♪
♪The loneliness of the night♪
♪When your gaze begins to avoid mine♪
♪When it all becomes unbearable♪
♪When the story ends♪
♪When the dialogue fades,
and what was said still lingers♪
♪I remember every answer you gave♪
♪All the habits we shared♪
♪Unwilling to part, leaving no regrets♪
♪Out of a hundred encounters,
only one is lucky enough♪
♪To find the right bond♪
♪When there's still a chance
for a different ending♪
♪When you begin to warm♪
♪When I remain courageous♪
♪When I still remember♪
♪When you still like me♪