♪Raindrops patter,
falling on red bricks and green tiles♪
♪Tears stain the red, gold-stamped
wedding invitation♪
♪His profile in the candlelight♪
♪Old photos and yellowing oil paintings♪
♪Reflecting the falling light♪
♪Worldly people, with heartfelt words,
don't feign naivety♪
♪Without you, spring doesn't come,
and autumn doesn't go♪
♪No winter or summer
in the vast expanse♪
♪Countless restless nights♪
♪I can't retain a single strand of hair;
in the end, it's a lie♪
♪Whoever the ending belongs to,
I won't be afraid♪
=Crush=
=Episode 23=
Sir Xize.
Mr. Kudo,
you're still alive?
Fu Yunzheng
only injured my leg,
but couldn't kill me.
Sir Xize,
the current state of the Shen family
is all Fu Yunzheng's doing.
You can't let him get away with it.
So, what do you think
I should do?
We should join forces
and take back the goods
Fu Yunzheng stole.
Then you can make a comeback.
Get lost.
My dad's death
is connected to all of you.
Mom,
we've avenged you.
You can rest
in peace now.
My brother and I
can openly be together now.
Mom,
I wish you were still alive.
Then we all
could be happily together.
♪On cold nights, I often ride on dreams♪
Mom,
I'm sorry.
(In Memory of Beloved Mother, Fu Yaru)
I promised you to find a good husband for Yue.
I broke that promise.
But don't worry.
As long as I live,
I'll always keep Yue safe.
♪Sweeping my sleeves, I wish to write♪
♪Sighing, I put the pen down again♪
♪Each word pierces the heart,
chaotic as hemp♪
♪No longer the leisurely elegance
of the past♪
It's snowing.
♪The cold, deadly wind still blows♪
♪The needle-like rain keeps falling♪
♪No more romantic moments in the world♪
Mom heard us.
This snow is a gift from mom
to bless us to grow old together.
♪No desire to linger in prosperity♪
♪I wish to become countless snowflakes♪
♪With one drifting down to you♪
♪I am weathered by time♪
♪Black hair turning white,
lamenting the endless road of love♪
(The moment of surprise
when we first met)
(has now passed into winter.)
(Today we're in the snow together)
(sharing our lives forever.)
Brother,
let's go see the snow.
Still call me brother?
Fu Yunzheng!
♪I am weathered by time♪
♪Black hair turning white,
lamenting the road of love♪
Let's go.
♪Let love and hate be abandoned
in this lifetime♪
Who are you?
Isn't this Miss Shen?
Get her.
You know who I am?
Get lost then!
Fiery enough.
I like her.
Someone, help!
Stop shouting.
The Shen family has no one left.
No one will come to save you.
If you don't want to die, get lost!
It's Fu Yunzheng.
Chiyan Gang! Run!
Yunzheng.
Shen Zhiwei harmed you so many times.
Why did you still help her?
The Shen family has fallen.
Master Shen is also dead.
Shen Zhiwei no longer has
the right to be arrogant.
Fortunately, the weapons
didn't fall into the hands
of the Japanese.
This is Master Shen's
last bit of good fortune.
Don't worry.
Those weapons are
in Chiyan Gang's warehouse.
I'll return them to the guerrillas
when they arrive.
What are you looking at?
There will be an exhibition
in Lin City soon.
Will you come with me to see it?
Sure.
Zhiwei Restaurant has new dishes.
Will you come with me to try them?
Sure.
The New Year is coming.
Will you buy me some new clothes?
Sure.
Why are you agreeing to everything?
I...
I've agreed to three things.
Shouldn't you agree to one thing I say?
What is it?
Who wants to have children with you?
That's fine too.
As long as you stay with me for life,
that's enough.
♪We grew up together since childhood♪
♪With you, no mountain is too high,
and no path too tough♪
♪I won't be scared♪
Miss Yue.
Come in.
Miss Yue,
a child delivered it.
He said this is from your old friend.
Got it.
(To Moli)
(Moli,)
(tomorrow,)
(I'll leave Long City.)
Xize,
you...
I didn't expect
you'd come to see me off.
You said in your letter
you're leaving Long City.
Where are you planning to go?
Anywhere I can go.
Anyway,
Long City isn't a place
for a fallen young master like me.
Xize,
take care.
Just pretend
we never met.
What if I say
I can't do that?
Sir Fu.
The luggage is here,
but he's gone.
Kudo must have gotten wind of it early
and fled.
He won't give up
on Master Shen's goods easily.
He should still be in Long City.
Keep searching.
Yes.
Sir Fu,
bad news.
Miss Yue is missing.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Sir Fu,
it's that car.
Our men saw with their own eyes
Shen Xize took Miss Yue into the car.
Stop it.
Soon,
he'll lose to me.
Where is Shen Xize?
I don't know any Shen Xize.
Whose car is this?
Why driving so fast?
Someone gave me ten silver coins
to drive fast in the city.
All the money is here.
I don't want it.
Oh right.
The person also left something.
He said to give it to
whoever catches me.
Sir Xize,
is the plan
going smoothly?
No problem.
My dad's death
is connected to all of you.
As far as I know,
your enemy
is already with your wife.
He stole your wife.
You wouldn't
be magnanimous enough
to ignore it, right?
As long as we can get back
the weapons from Fu Yunzheng,
we both will be saved.
I can help you retrieve those weapons,
but in exchange,
you must eliminate Fu Yunzheng
and the Chiyan Gang.
Of course, I want to kill Fu Yunzheng.
But
it's not that easy to deal with him.
You don't need to worry about that.
I know Fu Yunzheng's
weakness.
Sir Fu, what's this?
Yue's bracelet.
Her bracelet?
How did it end up on the road
to our gang?
Oh no.
We've been lured away.
I'll make your eyebrows thicker.
And don't forget
the lipstick.
Yes, just like this.
When I first saw you,
you were like a newly blooming
jasmine flower.
Shen Xize,
you colluded with the Japanese
to besiege the Chiyan Gang.
You traitor!
You're treacherous
and a disgrace to the country.
Don't touch me!
Shut up!
♪As winter evenings grow darker♪
♪When the air itself feels restless♪
♪When the hand that once held mine♪
♪Is no longer warm♪
♪When memories gradually♪
♪Lose their brilliance♪
♪Fireworks fall, and the night
crumbles into ruin♪
♪When neon lights outside the car window
are vibrant♪
♪When you said you liked them♪
♪When the summer night sky lit up♪
♪The loneliness of the night♪
♪When your gaze begins to avoid mine♪
♪When it all becomes unbearable♪
♪When the story ends♪
♪When the dialogue fades,
and what was said still lingers♪
♪I remember every answer you gave♪
♪All the habits we shared♪
♪Unwilling to part, leaving no regrets♪
♪Out of a hundred encounters,
only one is lucky enough♪
♪To find the right bond♪
♪When there's still a chance
for a different ending♪
♪When you begin to warm♪
♪When I remain courageous♪
♪When I still remember♪
♪When you still like me♪