♪Raindrops patter,
falling on red bricks and green tiles♪
♪Tears stain the red, gold-stamped
wedding invitation♪
♪His profile in the candlelight♪
♪Old photos and yellowing oil paintings♪
♪Reflecting the falling light♪
♪Worldly people, with heartfelt words,
don't feign naivety♪
♪Without you, spring doesn't come,
and autumn doesn't go♪
♪No winter or summer
in the vast expanse♪
♪Countless restless nights♪
♪I can't retain a single strand of hair;
in the end, it's a lie♪
♪Whoever the ending belongs to,
I won't be afraid♪
=Crush=
=Episode 4=
(Don't let him get away.)
Dare to take someone from my place?
Where are they?
Over there.
Don't let him get away. Go after him.
Let's go.
Go.
- Yunzheng.
- Go.
We have to go together.
Go find help.
Hurry.
Go.
Stop.
Stop there.
Get him.
Beat him up.
(You're very tough, huh?)
I've sold so many women.
This is the first time
someone stole one from me.
Drag him away.
Yes.
I want to break his bones one by one.
♪Your comings and goings
decide my emotions♪
♪Your words and actions
control my expressions♪
♪I can't hide the sound of crying♪
♪My tears are too willful♪
♪You swept through like a storm♪
♪Taking away my love♪
♪Leaving behind a wrecked past♪
♪Eventually, I found solace
in someone else♪
Mom.
Yunzhen,
promise me
to take good care of Yue.
Mom.
Find her a good husband
and take care of her for life.
I swear,
I'll take good care of Yue.
Mom,
don't die.
I don't want anything.
I only want you.
Mom.
Mom!
Master,
who do you think
dared to cause trouble
in our Shen family?
Go,
investigate that Moli.
Master,
are you suspicious of her background
or does she not suit your taste?
She's just like this orange.
It looks enticingly green,
but we must ensure
it's harmless
before we
consume it.
♪We both sensed it long ago♪
♪The words you want to say♪
♪Are just words of farewell♪
♪Our reflections♪
♪Split into two worlds♪
♪Like clouds waving goodbye to the sun♪
Why is she in my house?
Miss Zhiwei,
Sir Xize brought her back.
She dared to seduce Yunzhen.
I haven't settled the score with her.
She's delivered herself to my door.
Let's go.
Shen Wende is very cunning.
He won't be easily fooled.
I've already sent someone
to handle Miss Yue's identity.
Send someone else
to watch her 24 hours a day.
Yes.
Sir Fu,
Master Shen is waiting.
Moli,
are you going to find Xize?
He left with my dad early this morning.
Thank you for letting me know.
Then I'll just wait for him.
Waiting is so boring.
Let me take you around
and play host on Xize's behalf.
Let's go.
Xize said you're a student,
working part-time at a flower shop.
My family isn't well-off,
so I work during the holidays
to earn some money.
No wonder.
Whenever there's a wealthy man,
you want to hook up with him.
Miss Shen, what do you mean?
You just met Xize
and now you're living in his house.
You barely knew Yunzheng,
and you're already seducing him.
You want to climb the social ladder?
You don't look like
an innocent student at all,
more like a shameless wretch.
What are you doing?
I'm a guest of your brother.
Who you are doesn't matter to me.
Any woman who tries
to get close to Yunzheng
must die.
(Being impatient will ruin my plan.)
(Confronting her head-on
in the Shen family)
(will only hinder my plan.)
Let's go.
♪We grew up together since childhood♪
♪With you, no mountain is too high,
and no path too tough♪
♪I won't be scared♪
♪This is the result
of all the obstacles♪
♪Countless fates and lifetimes
have brushed past♪
♪As we gaze at the horizon♪
♪Worldly people, with heartfelt words,
don't feign naivety♪
♪Without you, spring doesn't come,
and autumn doesn't go♪
♪No winter or summer
in the vast expanse♪
♪Countless restless nights♪
♪I can't retain a single strand of hair;
in the end, it's a lie♪
♪Whoever the ending belongs to♪
♪I won't be afraid♪
Yue! Yue!
Moli.
How are you feeling?
What happened?
You should ask Miss Shen
about what happened.
Zhiwei, stop denying it.
I was worried she might be dirty,
so I helped her wash off in the lake.
Zhiwei, you're a woman too.
How can you compare her with me?
Xize,
don't fight with her
because of me.
Don't let me be
the cause of discord between you two.
If your sister doesn't like me,
then I'll just leave.
Moli.
Shen Xize.
This is all my sister's fault.
She should be leaving,
not you.
Today was just a small lesson.
Anyone who dares to mess with my man
won't have it easy.
And I'm telling you,
Moli can stay in the Shen family
for as long as she wants.
If anyone bullies her,
there'll be consequences.
Xize, thank you.
Moli, you must've been frightened.
I need to apologize
on behalf of my sister.
I'll book a table
at the best restaurant here.
Then I'll take you
to the new department store
to buy new paints.
Xize,
thank you so much.
I'm lucky to have you here.
Speak.
Who sent you to follow me?
♪As winter evenings grow darker♪
♪When the air itself feels restless♪
♪When the hand that once held mine♪
♪Is no longer warm♪
♪When memories gradually♪
♪Lose their brilliance♪
♪Fireworks fall, and the night
crumbles into ruin♪
♪When neon lights outside the car window
are vibrant♪
♪When you said you liked them♪
♪When the summer night sky lit up♪
♪The loneliness of the night♪
♪When your gaze begins to avoid mine♪
♪When it all becomes unbearable♪
♪When the story ends♪
♪When the dialogue fades,
and what was said still lingers♪
♪I remember every answer you gave♪
♪All the habits we shared♪
♪Unwilling to part, leaving no regrets♪
♪Out of a hundred encounters,
only one is lucky enough♪
♪To find the right bond♪
♪When there's still a chance
for a different ending♪
♪When you begin to warm♪
♪When I remain courageous♪
♪When I still remember♪
♪When you still like me♪