♫  Broken hearts and dreams  ♫
♫  Burn all your troubles away  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
I can't...
forgive myself since that night.
But since you're in front of me right now,
I keep thinking you're actually alive.
I feel so pathetic for thinking that.
The memories from the past are hard enough,
so I can't do this with you.
I want to stop.
- Ram Woo.
- Please stop calling me that!
Jeong Hee Wan! He's in there...
You can't go in.
My friend is still in there.
Move quickly!
Jeong Hee Wan!
He's still in there...
Ram Woo!
Jeong Hee Wan! Jeong Hee Wan!
You want to draw posters when you're hardly even here?
You need to change it up each season
so the customers know we care about the interior.
Why are you making one
for each season and even for Christmas now?
Well, because...
it's easy to do all of it at once.
How's the business? Going well?
Sometimes it is, and sometimes it isn't.
How about you?
How are you doing in Seoul?
I'm fine.
You call all the time. Why do you ask?
You never answer calls in time.
You answer maybe one out of every 20.
So... why did you start drinking again?
Can't you sleep? Do you still have strange dreams?
It's not like that.
I was drinking while hanging out with school friends.
Really?
Which school friend? Do I know any of them?
How would you know?
Seriously...
I got scallions.
You're back.
You have to go to work without eating because of me.
Work?
- What work?
- She has a job.
She's saving up with friends to go
freediving or whatever in Cebu.
I told you not to tell her.
I already got the plane tickets.
I'll go now.
Hey.
- What?
- It's dangerous.
- Cancel it.
- What do you want me to do?
Do nothing?
Should I stop seeing friends and stay in my room like you,
- staring at the ceiling all depressed?
- What?
Come on, Hee Joo. Go.
I don't want to.
Yes, I can get into an accident on a trip.
I might die from it.
But is that the only way you die?
I could get hit by a car as I leave here,
or something could fall on me and kill me.
People can even die while drinking water.
I could die anytime. I'll do whatever I want,
so you should finally start living, too.
Ignore her, Hee Wan.
Hee Wan.
- Excuse me.
- You scared me.
I've been watching you from back there.
You look so sad.
People tell you that often, right?
Goodness, the negative energy is...
pushing you right here.
Your shoulders and the corners of your lips droop,
and it makes you look ugly, right?
I know a good place. Come with me.
Excuse me.
Because of what happened last time and everything,
I was going to ignore you,
but it's too upsetting just to pass by.
You look so sad right now.
Your energy feels off.
You hear that often, don't you?
I know what people like you need.
I know an amazing place nearby.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Come here. Just trust me.
Let's go.
There's a place I know.
It's really nice there.
You'd increase your energy level like this.
Is it locked?
Hey, it's open here.
Really?
What are you doing? Hurry!
What do you think?
Only Tae Kyung and I know this spot.
But...
it must say "Do not enter" for a reason.
Maybe there's a ghost here
or they found carcinogenic substances.
I'm not good at stuff like this.
Just do it. You don't have to be good.
Just paint like this without thinking.
Brush, brush, brush.
You know,
we have a guest at home once in a while.
Guest?
Is that not the right word?
Well, I'm not exactly happy to see her.
She's my so-called dad's wife.
I'm not sure what to call her.
Anyway, she...
often leaves money at our house.
She's probably
paying us so I live like I don't exist.
But I was always curious.
Why does this so-called father never come?
Isn't he curious about me?
Do you want to see him?
I'm not sure.
I don't really know how I feel either.
I've been thinking about this since I was little,
but I still don't know.
I'm like that too.
My mom passed away when I was four.
The day I started elementary school,
my dad was crying alone among smiling people.
So I asked him why he was crying.
He said, "Mom really wanted to come here."
He cried because he missed her so much.
I was too young
and didn't remember much of her,
but I cried with him
and said I missed her.
Honestly, I still don't know if I truly miss her
or if I'm supposed to miss her.
You're splattering, I said.
Stop it.
Be careful.
Can't you stamp?
- Stamp?
- Yes, stamp.
Could you do it over there?
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
It's like the night sky.
I know.
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
A shooting star.
This makes it a shooting star.
If you do this,
it's like Saturn.
What?
You came.
What is Jeong Hee Wan doing here?
He was feeling lost in front of his house,
so I lifted his mood.
This is our secret spot, though.
You did that without telling me?
Oh, right.
Why don't you answer my message?
- We need to make a reservation...
- Right, this weekend.
Goodness, I forgot.
I'm checking out a place with Dad in Seoul. Sorry.
Dad suddenly said he was free only that day.
Does our plan not mean anything?
Why would you say that?
I'm sorry.
I've been all over the place because of college. Seriously...
Okay.
You don't have to explain if you're busy.
You're busy hanging out with your new best friend anyway.
It was annoying always listening to you talk about college.
- Tae Kyung, it's not that—
- Annoyed?
That's going too far.
Looks like you two are connecting.
- Have fun, then.
- Hey.
How can you be like this? What's the deal?
Geez.
- Daebak.
- What?
It's still here.
How's Tae Kyung, by the way?
Tae Kyung?
Well...
I don't really know.
What do you mean? Did you fight again?
She's probably not in Korea.
How about Hong Seok, then?
We never kept in touch.
The only high school friend you have left
is this Grim Reaper? Isn't that too extreme?
The door is open.
I think...
I need to see Hong Seok.
I miss him.
I miss Hong Seok.
- So, I think I should meet him.
- What is he doing?
What are you doing?
Okay.
Let's see. Let's see. Let's see.
Where could Hong Seok be?
Here.
I'll meet Hong Seok and...
Want to die?
Play a board game. I'll do that first.
Geez.
You're out of your mind.
He probably deleted my number.
No, he didn't.
Hey...
Hello?
- Well...
- What's going on?
I'm working.
I'll hang up.
Happy now?
I see.
Meet my friend, Lee Hong Seok.
Hey, you can't do that—
You can't worry about that right now.
What matters is
how you'll get out of here.
I'll open it if you agree to meet Hong Seok.
Will you stay in there?
Fine. Open it now.
Thank you.
Buddy, what matters is
we can't defend either of them.
That'd be like crossing a river forever.
I feel bad. I'm partly responsible for this.
I think...
we need to get away from school
since they fought here.
It sounds like you want to go on a trip.
- A graduation trip?
- Yes.
How about we all go together?
Hong Seok, too?
Yes. Tae Kyung is going as well.
Forget it. Go without me.
I'm sorry...
but I no longer want to do things with her.
I know.
This might be our last trip as a group.
"Our" trip?
What's the reason for this trip?
It's Mamidang.
Mamidang? You mean the bakery?
They're closing next week for a year.
What? Why?
It's that old man baker's...
sabbatical year.
There's no time, let's think about it.
Let's go.
I'll think about it.
It's too shiny.
Isn't it a trash bag?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? What are you wearing?
Doesn't this look expensive?
Hey, stop. Don't touch. What are you doing?
Let's go. It's time.
- Let's go, guys.
- Check it out.
This must be...
making you really sweaty.
It gets so hot in here.
Hold on. My phone. My phone...
Where did you put it?
Geez. Hey!
It's fish. It's fish. It's fish!
Where?
- Stay here!
- Over there. It's right there.
Wow, it's true!
Where? Where?
Where?
Gosh, the line is already so long.
Who insisted it was that way?
I'll go to the right. You go to the left.
Here's what you need to get.
The myeongran baguette, choco crumble, and cream cheese croquette.
But the cream cheese croquette is likely sold out.
You need to get the salt croissant instead. And...
- Won't you write it down?
I already know. They're so famous.
Sorry. Please say it again.
- Are you kidding?
- Seriously.
- You're getting in the way. Get out.
Just carry our bags instead.
- Myeongranjeot. Myeongranjeot...
- Hold our bags.
- Leave, leave.
- Myeongran baguette. Myeongran baguette.
- Quiet. Just leave. Go.
- Myeongran...
I'm sorry.
This would make a great photo.
I don't think I've ever seen one.
It'd be...
so romantic to see it together.
Congratulations on opening a studio!
It's so nice.
It's way nicer than I expected.
I know.
- Hey.
- Mom, did a lot of people come?
Yes, a lot of people came.
The thing is, it turns out there's a meteor shower festival nearby.
Really?
Yes.
So you know the opening party...
Are you ditching me for Hee Wan?
No, i-it's not that.
I'm just curious.
Two hundred meteors fall per hour.
Tell them to have fun all they want.
Ram Woo, I saved cake for you.
Come to the table.
Yes, we can have another party.
Have fun.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hey.
♫  Everything's a glow  ♫
♫  Our eternal memories in time  ♫
♫  Everything's so bright and  ♫
♫  I know, oh oh oh  ♫
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
Did it work? I think it did.
♫  My, my  ♫
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
This one.
Sorry.
I guess I was serious about it.
I thought we'd always be together,
but I'm the only one not going to college.
Thinking of being left behind
made me feel helpless.
I'm serious, too.
So...
whatever we do in the future,
we'll stay together.
We come as a set.
Do you mean it?
If you write a letter,
we'll mail it when the next shower comes.
- No, I'm okay.
- No need to pay for postage.
- Who is it?
- My mom.
Why won't you answer?
I don't know. She wants me to retake the exam.
Coming this far is the best I can do.
I'm satisfied with it.
I don't need to go to a good college.
I can be satisfied and have a fun life,
even if no one believes me.
What's your address?
I'll write one.
Thank you.
Are you writing me? Why?
Because I want to.
Why are you making my heart flutter?
Just tell me your address.
But you have something more important to tell me.
What?
The stars. Include the stars.
The stars...
You're right. I like Kim Ram Woo...
I mean, Jeong Hee Wan.
When were you planning to tell me?
Since when did you know?
Me?
After I confessed my love to her
and got rejected brutally.
But I noticed today that
Hee Wan is always looking at you,
and you're always looking at her.
Maybe I noticed it, too.
Is that why I wanted to ignore it even more?
Anyway, I'm trying to tell you
not to worry about me and do what you want,
but don't expect me to cheer for you.
Don't get too comfortable, either.
I really don't have anything to say to Hong Seok.
- What should I do?
- I have a lot to catch up on with him.
You can tell him for me.
He saw you.
Hi.
Gosh, it's so awkward.
What's with you two?
What? Why...
What's wrong?
Hey, what are you doing?
He's doing nothing right now.
You act so busy.
Can I ask why you came?
I need to get going soon.
- Well...
- Wow, he's acting so tough.
I came because...
well... I have something to tell you.
What I want to say is...
I have something to tell you, but the thing is...
Do you show your left profile
- because that's your flattering side—
- What?
Well, no...
Do you still think your feet smell is addictive?
Stop it.
What?
I'm not talking about your feet.
I have a lot on my mind,
so I'll stop thinking.
Okay. Just ask him about your relationship.
You've been well, right?
Did you return from the military safely?
He did.
Are you working here now?
Hey...
What book is that? Are you studying?
I'm just preparing for an exam.
Wow, you're taking an exam?
An exam? What exam?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not sure what you're trying to do.
Honestly, I'm baffled and dumbfounded.
Being with you like this is uncomfortable for me.
You have nothing else to say, right?
- Well...
- Please leave, Hee Wan.
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
Kim Ram Woo.
What's wrong with him?
I'm sorry, but you do this alone.
You can. He's your friend, not mine.
Hey, hold on. Please?
Forget about me. How about you?
Is this okay with you?
Don't you have anything to say to him?
I'll leave the room if you can't talk because of me.
What's the point now?
You're doing this for a reason.
Could this be your last moment with him? Is that okay?
Jeong Hee Wan.
The board game. Did you touch it?
What?
Well...
- the thing is...
- Be honest.
Why did you come?
What do you mean?
Is it because of Ram Woo?
Is it Kim Ram Woo again?
- Hee Wan!
- Kim Ram Woo!
Are you okay?
- Sit comfortably.
- What can I do?
Breathe slowly. It's okay, it's okay.
Hand me a bag. A bag!
It's nothing. It's not a big deal.
Here.
Are you okay?
Breathe slowly.
Here's the bag. Breathe in it.
It's not a big deal. It's okay.
It's okay.
Take your time. Take your time.
It's okay. Two...
One...
two...
She's okay now. Thank you.
It's not coming anymore.
- What?
- The ambulance isn't coming.
Be careful.
How embarrassing...
I suddenly showed up and did this. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry I suddenly cornered you like that.
Should we walk a bit?
I just...
can't seem to do it.
Pretending nothing happened.
I'm different from you,
and considering what I did,
I guess I couldn't accept it.
How did everyone get okay so quickly?
To be honest, I was jealous of you too.
You were jealous.
You know, I didn't want to say this,
- but why do you think only you suffer?
- What?
I really didn't want to answer when you called earlier.
I was afraid something happened again.
You know how that feels.
We imagine the worst when we hear about an accident in the news,
afraid it's someone we know.
You know, too.
But why do you... think only you feel that way?
Whenever you suffer because of Ram Woo,
I change the subject as if it isn't a big deal.
Do you think that was easy?
Do you think I meant to?
Asking you to stop talking about Kim Ram Woo...
Have you ever imagined
how I must have felt saying that,
even once?
I was there too, Hee Wan.
We're watching the shooting stars together.
- You're hungry, right?
- Oh, yes!
It's food. Thanks.
There's a countdown at 8 o'clock.
Really?
- Wow, I think I saw one.
- Where?
- Where? Where?
- There.
- Where?
- Over there.
Where? Where?
It disappeared.
It's crunchy. This one is tasty.
What is it? Where did you get it?
It's so tasty.
Hello?
Yes, this is Jeong Hee Wan.
We need to keep watching, you never know.
Really?
What?
Where are we going?
It's starting soon.
Congratulations, Jeong Hee Wan.
You know the observatory event?
I won. I just got a call.
Wow, that's...
Why are you congratulating me, then?
You said you've never seen a shooting star.
It's my gift to you.
It's your last chance to be called Jeong Hee Wan.
You know,
I got into my dream college
and I made up with Tae Kyung.
I'm on a trip with my favorite friends, too.
I achieved everything possible,
so I'm extremely happy right now.
And...
I...
I want you to be happy today
because you are Kim Ram Woo, who is also called Jeong Hee Wan.
Want to come with me?
Come with me. I need to tell you something.
- Tell me something?
- Yes.
I want to tell you today.
It's okay. Go without me this time.
Here. Read it on the way, okay?
Read it alone, so...
You'll be watching the stars at the observatory later.
Read it then, okay?
You'd be in a good mood then. Read then.
Bye.
Kim Ram Woo.
Switching names with you was so troublesome,
but it was the most fun thing I did in high school.
Later,
do you want to sit together when we go home?
Okay.
♫  It feels like you're coming to me by chance  ♫
♫  I can smell the scent of spring  ♫
♫  It seems you're coming along with it  ♫
♫  From far away, your scent drifts in  ♫
Hello. What's your name?
Jeong Hee Wan.
Confirmed.
Hello. What's your name?
♫  I remember the springs of days gone by  ♫
♫  In the whirlwind of time rushing past  ♫
- Why are you coming alone?
- You look so happy.
I'm not. I'm not.
♫  I drag my tired body and cross this street  ♫
To Kim Ram Woo who's called Jung Hee Wan.
You know I'm good at writing letters at least.
But it's taking me forever to write this one.
Because I'm writing as sincerely as possible.
I have a confession to make.
I hate my name.
It's too ordinary.
But Kim Ram Woo,
your name feels different each time I say it.
And I like my ordinary name now, too.
Because you took on that name.
What more can I say than that?
Kim Ram Woo,
I like you very much.
I'm not sure since when.
I wonder if you know.
I'm curious how you feel.
What do you think of me?
Gosh, so bright.
Breaking news.
At the Byeolmaru Campsite's
observatory in Jinsung-gun,
- a gas explosion occurred.
- Isn't it so nice?
- Let's visit the scene.
- Breaking news.
I'm at the gas explosion site
at the Byeolmaru Campsite observatory.
There were two explosions about 40 minutes ago.
The building caved in, and chaos ensued.
Follow closely!
We need more help at the scene.
It's dangerous. Step back!
Just one second. Just one second.
Move quickly!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Jeong Hee Wan! Jeong Hee Wan!
Ram Woo! Ram Woo! Kim Ram Woo!
Ram Woo!
Ram Woo! Kim Ram Woo!
Jeong Hee Wan!
Ram Woo!
I need to go save him!
My friend is in there!
Ram Woo!
Jeong Hee Wan! Jeong Hee Wan!
Kim Ram Woo!
Jeong Hee Wan! Ram Woo!
Kim Ram Woo! Jeong Hee Wan!
You didn't like me.
You were with me because you missed Ram Woo.
I know that.
- Hong Seok—
- But I was serious.
I guess I wanted us to feel better together.
I thought you'd get better
if you pretended to feel better.
That's what I wanted to believe.
Maybe that's why I changed the subject by looking happy.
I still can't get used to the siren either.
That's why...
I want a job that doesn't require me to get used to it.
I'm actually preparing for the firefighter exam.
Firefighter?
Whether it's the siren or whatever,
I'll just keep getting startled by it.
You're allowed to with that job.
I have to.
I guess I didn't want to admit it either.
That I'm actually hurting, too.
I also...
struggle with the fact that
I left Ram Woo there alone.
But I was hoping you'd ask me once, Hee Wan,
if I was okay...
and if I was having a hard time.
♫    ♫
I thought you wanted to forget about him.
How could I forget him?
He was such a good friend.
♫  My stars have gone away  ♫
♫  Oh, my love is far away  ♫
♫  Even if it disappears far away  ♫
♫  I couldn't leave behind  ♫
Hong Seok.
I plan to forget everything and live a good life.
I won't have time to call you, and I plan to live a totally happy life.
Don't feel sad about not hearing from me, and have a nice life.
And I'm sorry...
that I was mean to you.
I'm sorry I was so selfish
♫  My name is calling you ♫
Make sure not to skip meals.
Don't be on the news.
Okay, I won't be on the news.
I'm leaving.
♫  I'll let you go now  ♫
♫  My stars have gone away  ♫
♫  Oh, my love is far away  ♫
♫  We were so bright and happy  ♫
♫  In our only time together  ♫
♫  Our beautiful days  ♫
♫  Your name  ♫
♫  My stars have gone away  ♫
Do you expect too much just because people call you handsome?
You're not that handsome. You still look the same.
This is where we stopped.
We planned to continue after the trip.
I still feel angry about it.
I was about to win.
You agree, right?
Your fly is down.
It's been down since you were punching.
Wherever you are and whatever you do,
have an amazingly fun life.
♫  Bye  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
Come with me. I need to tell you something.
Okay.
If I didn't let Ram Woo go alone then...
- Wow, I think I saw one.
- Where? Where?
- Over there.
- Really? Where?
Over there. Over there.
Over there.
If I didn't answer because I didn't recognize the number...
If I weren't so silly and fell for
the pink night sky then...
I'm home.
Hey, you're back. Sit.
This is great.
If we didn't go on a trip...
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
♫  If you  ♫
If I didn't like Kim Ram Woo...
If we didn't become friends at all...
If we didn't do the silly name switching...
If then...
Jeong Hee Wan...
Hee Wan!
♫  I'm here to stay  ♫
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  If you, ooh-ooh  ♫
♫  When the dazzling sunlight turns to sorrow  ♫
♫  If I could turn back the tangled end of our story  ♫
♫  Take my hand  ♫
♫  I'm here to stay  ♫
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  Never letting you go  ♫
We need to go somewhere.
I need to meet someone before I die.
Who is it?
My teacher.
Your mom.
♫  Shine for you  ♫
Let's go. Let's finish your bucket list now.
♫  If you, ooh-ooh  ♫