♫  Broken hearts and dreams  ♫
♫  Burn all your troubles away  ♫
♫  Some people want to keep it all; are they running from  ♫
♫  Monsters in the dark, trying to hide all the pain  ♫
♫  It's not going away  ♫
♫  Monsters in the dark  ♫
But you died.
Four years ago.
Yes.
I came because I needed to tell you something.
Kim Ram Woo.
You'll die in a week.
What?
You'll die in 176 hours, 12 minutes, and 35 seconds.
I'll die in a week?
Yes.
How do you know that?
Are you the Grim Reaper?
Yes.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
I'll leave it at the door.
Excuse me, hold on.
- What?
- Please help.
There's a weird guy inside.
You should call the police.
I'm a delivery man.
Is he hiding in the bathroom?
No, he's right in front of us.
- W-Where?
- Here. This person.
What? What person?
He can't see me. Don't waste your time.
- Aigoo. He has a long life left.
- What's there?
Thanks for your hard work. You'll live long.
You can't hear that either?
Hear what?
- I'm so busy I'm dying.
- You won't die.
No, that's not it... I'm sorry.
Whatever. Whatever.
They think delivery men are a joke.
Hello? I'd like to talk to the doctor.
I'm Jeong Hee Wan.
I'm in a hurry right now.
The drug you prescribed to me.
Is hallucination one of the side effects?
It is, right?
You checked all the pills, right?
Yes, it usually takes a few hours to accept.
But you'll regret wasting time like this later.
You regret so many things after you die.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
♫  The Bodhisattva of Compassion  ♫
♫  When he meditated deeply  ♫
Excuse me.
I...
have years of experience.
This is basically my work anthem now.
Have you come to your senses now?
Let's clean the house first, then.
Look at these side dishes.
You didn't even touch them.
Ahjussi and Hee Joo would be so upset
to see this after you die.
What are you, really?
What? I'm Hee Wan.
Cut the crap.
I'll flip out if you call me that again.
I'm Jeong Hee Wan and you're Kim Ram Woo.
I can't believe this. Hey.
You're the one who insisted on switching names.
Wow, the yearbook.
They switched our names here.
We had to put stickers on each copy. Remember?
We had cleaning duty for a month as punishment.
Here it is.
It was so hard to stick these...
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
I had salt, chicken blood,
and all sorts of stuff thrown at me.
But a fire extinguisher...
is a new one.
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
- What?
- Do you know Bang Ji Soo?
- Who?
- Bang Ji Soo from 10th grade.
She's looking for you.
You know the hair treatment ad.
Well, my handwriting is not good.
I saw the letter you wrote for my friend.
You made it look so pretty.
The word must've spread all the way there.
Is it a love letter?
The pricing tiers are basic, premium,
special, and platinum.
I choose the platinum.
The platinum level is a bit pricy.
- It's okay.
- It's 30,000 won.
It's okay.
A week is enough, right?
I'm confessing my love in a week.
Our 100th day would be Christmas if we start dating then.
I guess it's not possible that he'd say no.
Well, no.
I brought the letter here.
"Your dizzying beauty."
"The heart-wrenching smile"?
Is there someone like this at our school?
"I don't normally approach people first,"
"but you, Oppa Ram Woo, are an exception"?
Yes.
It's Oppa Kim Ram Woo.
Not you, Unnie.
Oppa Kim Ram Woo, who's called Jeong Hee Wan.
Kim Ram Woo is the recipient of this letter?
The Kim Ram Woo I know?
Yes. Why?
Is that a problem?
No, not at all. No problem.
But would Ram Woo like this stuff?
I'm not really sure.
Would he not?
Instead of doing this,
should I just confess to his face?
No, no, no. The letter sounds good.
The letter would be perfect.
Writing is more expressive.
- I love it.
- Okay, then.
Here's the 30,000 won.
Hold on a second!
Yes, Unnie. What is it?
There are modern, classic,
petit, and lovely options.
What would you like?
Since you're closest to Oppa Ram Woo,
choose the theme he'd like the most.
Fighting!
Fighting...
Geez.
"Your dizzying beauty"?
She couldn't sleep thinking about him?
Quit drinking coffee.
Darn.
Darn it!
Geez, so annoying!
Kim Ram Woo.
What's wrong? You look like a zombie.
What is it?
She's outside again.
Bang Ji Soo? Is it Bang Ji Soo?
Just write it however.
Hey, hey.
Tell her I'm sick.
No, say I'm in the bathroom.
No, no.
Tell her I didn't come to school today, okay?
I can cover myself like this.
I'm not at school today. Okay?
Please call Unnie for me.
She didn't come to school today.
She's at the teachers' office.
She's at the infirmary.
She got into a traffic accident.
She was hospitalized.
- Unnie.
- If I...
said she transferred, you won't believe it, right?
How long will you keep this up?
I feel sorry for you.
Just write it quickly and be done. What's this?
It's the platinum level.
But I can't come up with anything.
Don't you think Ji Soo is all about her hair?
No, does the hair look good because it's her?
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
Just confess your love to Jeong Hee Wan first.
What?
What are you talking about? You're crazy.
Stop dragging it.
Get it off your chest and get dumped quickly.
The bigger the heartbreak is,
the bigger the leap it brings to your life.
Why? Look how singers make masterpieces after a breakup.
Why are you being like this?
Spit out your words now.
(T/N: Don't jinx it)
Spit them out.
Unnie!
- Hey, hey, hey. Finish the noodles.
- Go, go.
- Go, go, go!
- Unnie, Unnie!
- Go!
- Unnie, hold on. Unnie, Unnie!
- Hold on! Hold on!
- Go! Go!
She was right here.
Hey, hey!
What?
Geez! Seriously!
Unnie?
- Gosh.
- What class is she from?
- Did she really jump?
- What do we do?
Yes, this is Heewantang.
Suicide attempt?
Dad!
I can't believe this.
She looked so cheerful and carefree when we saw her then.
She still is totally carefree.
How could you say that?
I mean, she always does unbelievably weird things.
You're so uncaring sometimes.
If you're struggling too much,
you act bubbly so as not to let it show.
Did Kim Ram Woo attempt suicide?
Is she okay?
Did something happen to her?
I don't know either.
That's what I mean.
Let me know if I can help with anything.
She's gone crazy. Seriously.
I think she lost her mind.
Everyone really thought you lost your mind.
We were so worried.
But where are we going?
What do you mean by "we"?
Whatever. I shouldn't react.
- Just accept it as it is.
- Seriously.
You aren't crazy.
- I can't hear you. I can't hear you.
- I'm the Grim Reaper.
- I can't hear you! I can't hear you!
- Hey, hey. Look.
I can't hear you. No, no, no...
Welcome.
One adult, please.
You're clever even at times like this.
Hee Wan, do you still have that dream?
The dream where your friend dies.
Is the person you see right now
the person from your dream?
Why are you so down after a bath?
Gosh, I feel refreshed for the first time in a while, too.
My body felt stiff,
but after the sauna, I feel alive.
"Feel alive"?
A weird thing for a dead person to say, right?
Let's say I'll actually die.
Why is it you, of all people, who's telling me that?
Well...
it's like calling in a favor from a friend.
- Let's just say it's like that.
- A favor?
Leave, then. I don't need you.
Come back when I die.
Hey, you can't just barge in...
- How long has it been?
- 18 every five minutes.
Administering it.
Assist.
No shock. Switch now.
It's a patient! Coming through!
Excuse me.
- Get him a GS operation room.
- Okay.
It's dropping. It's 40 now.
Doctor.
Let's stop.
Time of death, 4:55 p.m.
Mr. Im Soo Hyeon, you have passed away.
Born in the morning of October 12, 1991, between 11 am and 1 p.m.
Died at 5 p.m. on April 1, 2024.
Im Soo Hyeon. Im Soo Hyeon. Im Soo Hyeon.
Let's go.
Does it finally feel real?
You're sure, right?
Yes.
How do I die?
I can't tell you that.
A week, did you say?
Yes.
What do you want to do in the remaining week?
I'll go home and sleep.
What? Hey.
You're dying in a week. You want to sleep now?
What should I do, then?
Seriously.
Is there really nothing you want to do?
Someone you wanted to meet,
a place you wanted to go to,
food you wanted but was too expensive,
or something you like?
Like visiting the top bakeries in the country.
How about solving a difficult math problem?
Isn't that what you want to do?
There's something else I want to do.
"Riding a tandem bike"?
"Drinking beer while looking at a night view."
What's this?
It's my bucket list.
Isn't that something you do before you die?
I did die already.
Join me.
You need to hold it steadily in the front.
I veered off because you steered to the side.
I was holding tightly in the front.
You're going too fast. You need to keep balance.
This keeps happening because of you.
Be careful. Be careful.
Geez, what's wrong with you?
I don't want to.
Do it alone if you must.
You can't even do this much for me...
between us?
Hey, I've been looking for you everywhere.
Why did we keep missing each other?
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean?
I feel pressured because it's the platinum level.
I want you and Ram Woo to work out.
So, I've been thinking really, really hard—
So, where's the letter?
Aren't you done yet?
Well,
it's almost done.
There's only 1% left.
Because I want you and Ram Woo to really work out,
I'm pouring my heart into it.
Unnie, do you like Oppa Hee Wan...
I mean, Oppa Ram Woo, by chance?
What?
Hey, why would you say that?
Pretty girls have unrealistic imagination like this at times.
Right, Tae Kyung? Right?
Gosh, Ram Woo and Hee Wan?
I think I'll throw up.
Are you okay? I think I'll throw up, too.
Seriously. I think I'll throw up.
You're acting even more suspicious now.
No, no, no.
I really... I... I hate him.
He's the type I hate. You know what I mean?
How could you not like him?
He's tall,
has broad shoulders, and his face is tiny.
She hates tall men because of her cervical disc issue.
Not only that, his eyes look like half-moons when he smiles.
It's so adorable!
Gosh, I hate it. I hate it.
I really hate that type.
I hate it when men smile.
She has a terrible taste.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Because Ram Woo is so kind,
I thought someone unqualified might be after him.
Gosh, I'm sorry I misunderstood you!
Yes, she must be sorry.
I'm glad I was mistaken.
I'll take the letter now, then.
It's in the classroom, right?
What?
Gosh, Unnie. The letter. The letter.
You said only 1% was left.
Can't you finish that now?
It's a traditional font style, Unnie.
Yes.
It's such a heartfelt letter.
I thought I should refrain from decorations.
Oh, I see.
How about the last 1%, then?
What's left?
The poop brown one?
Oppa Ram Woo likes the color brown, right?
It's at 100% now.
Thank you!
Why the night view? It doesn't suit you.
And why did you want a tandem bike?
I would've had to ride on your back if it were a normal bicycle.
Whatever. Cross those off the list now.
Finished riding a tandem bike.
The remaining ones are,
watching migrating birds at a migratory bird habitat.
Attending a classical music concert at Seoul Arts Center.
Eating cup ramen in the Arctic.
Backpacking in South America.
Entering "National Singing Contest."
What's this now?
"Buying a house."
"Giving pocket money to grandchildren"?
Are you kidding me? What?
How will you buy a house and make grandchildren?
Come on.
It's a bucket list. It can't all be realistic.
I want to do these before I really die.
Right. It wouldn't be a bucket list otherwise.
Right. Yes.
It's too sad.
Traveling alone as a Grim Reaper isn't fun.
Just 10 of them.
Just 10.
You can do that for me, right?
If I do these, will you leave then?
What?
Promise me.
That you'll leave me after this.
That you'd never come back.
Okay.
It'll be over once we finish this.
I'll get out of your sight immediately, then.
Fine now?
By the way, isn't the night view here amazing?
Your taste is so obvious.
Are you done? Gosh.
Let's do the next one if you're done.
You're so strict.
Let's go do the next one. Hurry.
Hey, Kim Ram Woo. You're so weird.
We need to take this bike with us.
♫  I realized I'm blessed  ♫
♫  When I held your hand  ♫
♫  The sky turned blue  ♫
♫  Time became too precious  ♫
♫  And the days started feeling short  ♫
♫  I fill my days with us instead  ♫
♫  I'd go back to day one, to the beginning  ♫
Hey. Wake me up when it's over.
How uncivilized.
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
I've been thinking.
A friend is better than a boyfriend.
About Jeong Hee Wan again?
How long could a high school romance last?
It's over once we graduate and go to college.
He'll have another girlfriend in college.
But they'll break up once he joins the army.
He'll get one again after he gets discharged.
But they say you break up when you start a job.
It keeps getting repeated.
But not with friends.
Which one is better in the long run?
- A friend.
- Sounds like self-justification.
But you make a good point.
And dating is too much of a hassle.
You need to celebrate the 100th and 200th days and the birthdays.
And the Pepero Day too.
There's Christmas too.
And you have to hold hands in summer when you're all sweaty.
- Gosh, I hate it.
- It's the worst.
I know.
Jeong Hee Wan and Bang Ji Soo won't last long either.
So, who's the winner in the end?
Me, who didn't confess my love.
There's Ji Soo and Jeong Hee Wan.
Wow, something about this looks romantic.
I bet she's confessing to him now.
Jeong Hee Wan is smiling.
He's smiling with those half-moon eyes.
But I'm sure they'll break up quickly, as you say.
Hey, your crutch!
Hey, what are you doing?
Move! Move!
No!
Unnie.
Is your leg okay?
Hey, where's your crutch?
Are you sure you're okay?
Unnie.
What did you mean, "no," by the way?
What?
Well, the thing is...
I like you, Kim Ram Woo.
What did you say?
I'm sorry. I like Ji Soo.
I feel uncomfortable, so I can't be friends with you anymore.
I want us to be strangers from now on.
No.
I like you. I like you, Ji Soo.
I can't let you have her.
I see.
I hope things work out between you two.
Gosh, Unnie!
That's why you've been doing that.
We'll stay friends forever, then, right?
No, no, no, no.
Gosh, Unnie! I almost humiliated myself.
You're a lifesaver, Unnie.
- Oh, my.
- I don't care if there's spinach in your teeth.
I still find you pretty.
No.
Are you kidding?
When will you play board games with me if you start dating?
Hey, I'm sorry.
Play with Kim Ram Woo from now on.
What?
This isn't it!
Gosh, look how romantic you two are.
This is way too cringe.
Where's an eye mask to cover my eyes?
An eye mask. I can't see this. No.
I'd rather cover my eyes and not see this.
Andae*. An andae to cover my eyes.
(T/N: Andae = eye mask, sounds like "no")
Unnie.
No matter how much I think, that makes...
...no sense.
Unnie?
What? Well...
I...
Please. Just say something.
To be honest...
Kim Ram Woo!
Ma'am!
She got hit here.
She jumped off a bathroom window recently.
And I don't know what happened,
but she's acting strange.
She was normal before.
But she's been acting strange lately.
I looked it up. An extreme bipolar disorder...
What's with Kim Ram Woo and Bang Ji Soo?
Did you see them? It was daebak.
What happened?
It's over.
Right after he brought you here, Ji Soo...
confessed publicly.
Everyone was cheering. It was crazy.
I see.
That ended up happening.
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
Kim Ram Woo.
Are you okay?
Why did you skip the night study session?
Are you very sick? What did the nurse say?
Give me that. I'll carry it.
Gosh, what's with all the fuss?
Fuss? I'm worried.
You got hit by a soccer ball and fainted.
Did you have a concussion?
You said you write letters for people.
I closed down my business.
Closed down? Why?
I don't know.
Write one for me before you close it, then.
You know I have terrible handwriting.
It's an important letter.
30,000 won.
30,000 won? The others said it was 15,000 won.
I said it wrong. It's 40,000 won.
40...
It's more expensive than I thought.
Is there a friend discount, by chance?
Even just a bit...
Hey, after what you did,
I need to add 5,000 won for an MSB, okay?
Hey, I closed business.
Be thankful I'm doing this for you.
What's MSB, by the way?
You don't have to know.
You mean as in "Ignore"?
Is it "Someone you hate"?
It's not "Ugly jerk", is it?
Why does he write letters in an old-fashioned way?
Does he think this kind of confession will work?
Gosh, why am I crying?
So annoying.
I have to write this again...
No.
I still need to be professional. Professional.
Kim Ram Woo, are you crying?
That whole bucket list thing.
Don't you think it's a marketing strategy?
What if a genius marketer started it to sell stuff?
I'll help him sell it, then.
Come on over!
He's calling us. Let's go.
Hurry, hurry.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
It's too high up. Hold on.
Seriously.
Be honest.
You came to take revenge on me because you hate me, didn't you?
Why would I take revenge on you, Ram Woo?
Why are you doing this to me, then?
Come on. Stop talking to yourself.
They won't let you go, thinking you're a weird person.
Gosh, I hate it.
Hey, you look ridiculous right now.
Are you okay?
I did have one of those things, too.
Something I wanted to do before I died.
I just didn't know it'd come true like this.
Whether it's an illusion my brain created
or a variation of my usual nightmare,
In any case, Kim Ram Woo is in front of me now.
Great.
You're ready to go.
Will you not wear a helmet, by the way?
I guess you don't need to.
No, I don't need a helmet.
Because I'm not doing this.
- What?
- Next person, please.
- Yes!
- You're ready, right?
- One person, right?
What are you saying? We came because you wanted to ride it.
I can't ride this stuff.
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
- Let's go. Fighting, fighting!
- Wait a minute, Ahjussi.
Hold on! Hold on!
- Okay, okay!
- Hold on!
It's okay. Look over there. How fun!
- It looks so fun.
- Him, not me...
- Come back safe!
- It's okay, it's okay.
See you down there!
Don't cry. Don't cry.
It's okay!
It's not scary!
Hold on to it. Hold on.
- Run. Let's run.
- Wait, wait!
Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
It's okay! It's okay!
See you!
No, no, no.
Hold on!
♫  Everything's so bright and  ♫
♫  I know oh oh oh  ♫
♫  You are my best luck  ♫
Wow, that was quick.
Since we're friends,
I made you a platinum tier one.
Thanks.
"Ji Soo"?
Why "Ji Soo"?
J.S. Ji Soo.
Your girlfriend.
My girlfriend?
She's not.
J.S. is Jeong Sook.
"Jeong Sook"?
Who's Jeong Sook? What class is she in?
Jeong Sook is my mom.
What?
My mom.
She doesn't like her name. She thinks it's tacky.
You're confessing your love to your mom, not Ji Soo?
I'm not confessing my love.
It's a letter for my mom's birthday.
That's why you wrote, "You've worked hard all this time."
Yes.
Anyway, I just need to change the name in the beginning.
It's 45,000 won, right?
Hey, no, no, no.
Why bring money into our friendship?
Keep it. Keep it.
- No, but still—
- No, keep it.
Keep it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Hey, Jeong Hee Wan.
What about Ji Soo, then?
What about her confession?
Why ask something like that? It's embarrassing.
I just apologized to her.
You apologized?
You turned her down?
Why would you turn Ji Soo down?
I need to focus on the college entrance exam now.
And I need to keep getting the scholarship.
I need to maintain my grades, too.
Gosh, seriously.
Are you crazy?
I'm proud of you. You're so filial.
You'd win if you went on "Show Me the Money."
Ms. Jeong Sook must be so happy.
Give me that. I'll make you
a Gold Dragon Diamond version.
Hey...
It hurts.
Kim Ram Woo!
Gosh, hold on!
Stop!
Please, stop!
♫  I open my eyes to this spring  ♫
♫  All the words I once held back, the confessions I rehearsed  ♫
♫  Today, I want to tell them all to you  ♫
♫  It feels like you're coming to me by chance  ♫
♫  I can smell the scent of spring  ♫
♫  It seems you're coming along with it  ♫
♫  From far away, your scent drifts in  ♫
Seriously.
What have I done?
♫  This gentle feeling, this flutter  ♫
♫  Without realizing, it's suddenly spring  ♫
I do all sorts of things because of you.
Kim Ram Woo?
Kim Ram Woo.
Kim Ram Woo!
Hey...
Where's Kim Ram Woo?
Where did he go?
Kim Ram Woo.
I'm right here.
Hey.
Did you think I disappeared?
Why are you so shocked?
You missed me while you were away from me, right?
Anyway, how was it?
It wasn't scary once you took off, right?
It was fun, right? You don't regret it, right?
It wasn't fun at all.
Hey, what will you do on your 100th day?
Not much.
We'll take a walk by the Han River
and we'll have pasta
at a restaurant with a night view.
Hey, that's so cheesy.
What do you mean?
I want to try all cheesy things.
I want to ride a tandem bike by the Han River.
I'll drink beer while watching a night view.
And I want to take a trip and do paragliding.
Paragliding?
I'll watch a classical concert like an adult, too.
- Wow!
- How sophisticated.
- It doesn't suit you.
- What else is there to do?
Why are you riding a tandem bike?
I'll ride it with my baby.
- Baby!
- With my baby!
I'll ride it with my baby.
- I'm losing my mind.
- Where's your baby?
"My baby," she said.
I don't see her baby.
Has he even been born?
Where's he? Right here? Where?
♫  Take my hand  ♫
Seriously. Where's your baby?
Why's she always like that?
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  Never letting you go  ♫
♫  If you, ooh-ooh  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
Where's Jeong Hee Wan?
She hasn't come to school since two days ago.
It really must be her fault.
What do you mean?
Someone told me that.
Kim Ram Woo died because of Jeong Hee Wan.
Because of the name?
You're right.
She suggested switching names first, too.
Right.
♫  I'm here to stay  ♫
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  Never letting you go  ♫
♫  By your side  ♫
♫  Forever yours  ♫
♫  May every moment  ♫
♫  Shine for you  ♫
♫  If you, ooh-ooh  ♫