♫  Broken hearts and dreams  ♫
♫  Burn all your troubles away  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
All the stars are gone.
They were pretty.
They aren't.
What do you mean?
They aren't gone.
You don't see them because it's bright, but they're all there.
Try imagining it.
You can see them, right?
There's only one day left.
What's this?
I'll try everything I can.
"Discount Pilates. 250,000 won for 8 classes"?
Are you planning to die while doing Pilates?
It's my bucket list.
I wasted most of the week,
but I have a day to say goodbye to this world.
I'll give it a try before it's too late.
Saying goodbye.
Are you shopping to gift your father?
- Yes.
- If so,
a black one like this is nice and practical.
He must have a lot of weddings and funerals to attend at his age.
Would you like something brighter instead?
No, I'll take this.
Okay. I'll prepare it for you.
What would be good?
Well...
For people who are starting snorkeling or scuba,
I recommend short fins since they're easier
on your ankles when you do underwater kicks.
I must never cry.
You can do it, okay?
Good luck.
I'll be right back.
Dad!
Hee Joo, I'm back!
Ta-da! Look at this.
It's a surprise gift.
Don't worry. I got my time deposit.
I hear a lot of designers use this these days.
- Let's unbox.
- Hurry.
- No, no. Don't tear it open! Don't!
- Hurry, hurry.
Why not? Let's see what it looks like.
I hope you can get a refund.
I'm making you use the laptop I got you when
you started school. I felt bad about it.
But you're graduating soon. So, I'm being generous.
But I'm really okay.
What do you mean, you're okay?
I called you last time and you were crying.
So, I asked you why and you blamed it on the crappy laptop.
- You said you lost all of your homework.
- You believed that?
Hee Joo contributed all the money she earned from her part-time job, too.
- Thank her.
- It's okay.
I'll get it back when I graduate.
I have two years left.
Sign up for a time deposit if you haven't.
You really didn't have to buy this.
It suits you well.
Just a moment.
He's practicing saxophone these days.
To perform at our weddings.
- Weddings?
- Yes.
What are you thinking about?
A gift for my dad.
What could I have gotten him besides a suit?
I should've gotten his hair dyed.
I should've taken better care of him all along. Why do this now?
Come on.
Let's do the next one now. The next one.
Where's the flyer... Here it is.
I've been looking up restaurants in Honolulu all night.
I got no sleep.
I couldn't sleep because I was nervous.
Hey, the bus is here. Bye.
Hurry. What should we do?
"Pack lunch and go on a picnic."
"Spend all day at an amusement park."
"Eat nothing but gimbap all day."
You called me childish.
You're just like me, too.
Hey, isn't that a passport?
What?
What should we do?
- Should we split up and look for her?
- What?
I'll call you loudly if I find her.
Okay. I'll look over there.
What do we do?
Excuse me, you dropped this, right?
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
- Thank you!
- It's nothing.
Thank you!
We can go now, right?
- Hey, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
What should we eat?
I wonder what they're talking about.
Be well.
I'll miss you.
Don't be sad when I'm gone.
Don't skip meals.
I told you not to cry.
You think you won't find someone more handsome than me?
I suppose. It'd be too hard.
Can't we just go together?
You should stay here.
Stay here and save this world.
I don't want to.
I just need you.
A superhero shouldn't say something so irresponsible.
My superpower isn't enough.
I can't do it alone.
You can do it without me.
Remember, even if you don't see me,
we'll always be together.
Survive until the end...
and let's meet again.
Can I leave this world in your care now?
Yes.
You can count on me.
What would've happened to us if you didn't die?
Would we have become a cringe couple like them?
Or we could've gotten fed up and broken up.
We could've had a normal relationship, gone on normal dates,
fought for obvious reasons, made up,
gotten sick of each other and broken up.
We could've been a fleeting encounter.
Do you think...
we're still like this because time paused then?
We wouldn't have fought so much.
I probably would've tolerated you often.
Because I'm open-minded, thoughtful, and generous.
You're open-minded, generous, and old-fashioned.
Ridiculous.
It's better to be old-fashioned.
You would've given me such a hard time.
Geez, what's the point of talking?
We'll know once we try it.
"Going on a...
ordinary and cliché date with Kim Ram Woo."
We have less than a day left, right?
Let's see who gets sick of it first.
Okay.
Let's go.
What kind of date do you want to start with?
♫  It feels like you're coming to me by chance  ♫
The adult comic books are on another level.
Can't you read faster?
I want to read it soon, too.
What is it?
What? Is it over?
It ended with a cliffhanger.
Where's volume 11?
Wow. Gosh.
This world is filled with things I don't know yet.
This won't do.
Let's buy all these. Buy, buy, buy.
Let's go.
- Which one?
- The chocolate one.
Chocolate. Okay.
Catch it quickly. How cute.
How cute. Catch this.
Catch this. You can't, right? You can't.
You can't. You can't.
Catch it. You can't. You can't.
Hurry and catch it. Come on.
- Ahjussi!
- Catch it. You can't.
- That's enough. Stop.
- Clumsy, so awkward.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Did you finish it?
I'll tell my boyfriend. He's a scary man.
Oh, I got it.
"You're kind-hearted and not greedy.
You help people since you're compassionate."
"You're living an impractical life due to your compassion.
Stay away from luxury and vanity."
"Luxury and vanity"?
I knew it when you were buying your family gifts.
A good-looking, kind-hearted,
and a well-mannered spouse would be a good match for you.
That's so me, right?
No, no. Nothing is correct. Look.
Your longevity line is strong and clearly defined.
You'll be wealthy at an old age due to offsprings?
I don't think this is right.
♫  Don't hide it anymore  ♫
♫  Somehow now, you're standing right in front of me  ♫
♫  This gentle feeling, this flutter  ♫
The longevity line.
What? Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I made it longer.
I'll extend another one. The intelligence line.
Hey. Stop, stop.
- I'll do yours, too.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- What?
- One sec.
Geez.
Is it that senior again?
Why does she keep calling me?
Answer it. It might be something urgent.
She keeps bringing up the graduation exhibition.
I said I can't do it.
Hello?
H-Hello? Hee Wan.
Jeong Hee Wan, where are you right now?
- I'm outside.
- Outside? Why?
Are you alone right now?
Is something going on?
Well, yes.
Y-Yes, there is.
There will be fireworks since it's the last day of the festival.
Fireworks?
Yes, fireworks.
They use our tuition money for it.
Wouldn't it be a shame to miss it?
Well...
There's something I need to do.
I'll call you later.
What are you doing, exactly?
From when to when, where, and with whom?
Well, I need to hang up.
Hee Wan, I'm sorry. I'm not angry.
You haven't hung up, right?
The lineup today is no joke.
IVE is coming. IVE.
You know IVE, right? "LOVE DIVE."
It's all the rage right now.
- You need to come now.
- I-I can't talk right now.
I'll call you back.
Hee Wan, it's IVE. Hello?
Gosh.
She seems kind of weird.
Geez, that Grim Reaper. Seriously...
Kim Ram Woo, are you okay?
We took a class together once.
You know at least one person at school.
Let me.
Will you... Will you be okay?
- I can put it here, right?
- Yes, there.
Do you even know her name?
My name is Go Yeong Hyun.
Gosh, I'm screwed.
That jerk.
What do I do?
You should've used nice salt.
Go away! Go!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Sunbae!
Sunbae!
Sunbae.
Why is the weather so cold?
The weather will be cold throughout the festival period.
Yes, it's a spring-cold spell.
It's for the cherry blossoms.
I know.
Is it because it's colder than usual?
They're blossoming late.
I knew it.
You must see me. How?
It's none of your business.
Life must've been hard.
Yes. Because of jerks like you.
So, get lost.
Why should I get lost?
I end up learning too much about what I don't want to know.
So, leave.
Understood.
You were tossing salt and stuff.
I thought you wanted to talk to me.
Anyway, sorry for the trouble.
I'll get going now.
Is it because of Jeong Hee Wan?
I mean...
why are you hanging around her? Why?
Why do you think the Grim Reaper came?
Do you like fireworks?
It'd be nice to see them with someone.
W-What are you saying?
I wanted to see the fireworks together instead of shooting stars.
Anyway, think about who you'd see them with.
It'd be nice if you saw them with Hee Wan.
Hello.
Is work going well?
Thank you.
Ma'am, could you tell me where Jeong Hee Wan lives?
Jeong Hee Wan?
So, Jeong Hee Wan...
ordered supplies and disappeared with our money.
You're asking for her home address, Sunbae?
- Yes.
- Her personal info?
Right. In that case, could you just tell me
which direction? Is it East, West, North, South...
I don't think so.
And only she didn't take the yearbook photo.
She couldn't have put in an order for everyone.
Are you sure you aren't mistaken?
Hye Ran, this is urgent.
A person's life depends on it.
M-My life. My life depends on it.
You know I need to graduate.
Sunbaenim, you're trying so hard.
Stop the fireworks, at least, then.
Just don't do it, Hye Ran.
What about the fireworks?
They're already setting up for it.
They're setting up?
Yes.
Gosh, this is driving me nuts...
Seeing cherry blossoms.
Not happening since they didn't blossom.
A trip to Northern Europe.
There's no time and I don't have a passport, so no.
Contacting Tae Kyung. I couldn't do that either.
I should've found out her contact information.
Hey,
did you see shooting stars that day?
At the festival?
I did.
How about you?
They were pretty, right?
Yes.
I wanted to see them together.
Thinking now, while I've been with you this week,
I haven't had that dream once.
What dream?
I often had dreams of you walking away when I last saw you
at the Meteor Shower Festival.
In my dreams, after I send you there,
I later realize something went wrong.
So, I call for you.
I tell you not to go. To wait.
I run and manage to catch you.
But the person who turns around isn't you.
That's why I felt so relieved there yesterday.
Because you were there without disappearing.
I see...
Is that why you kissed me?
By the way,
how do I disappear?
What?
How do you disappear this time?
Can we meet again?
But... I think your bag disappeared just now.
Hey!
Hey...
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Gosh, seriously!
You're still a fast runner.
Stop right there, you two!
But why are we running?
Everything my dad gave me is in there!
You don't need any of that anymore.
Whatever! Hurry!
What's this?
I feel better.
So, how do I die?
I guess I choose to.
Kim Ram Woo.
I don't understand.
Why would I think of doing that?
Thinking now, I should've known earlier.
I'm not really sure how to feel about it.
You already know.
You don't want to die.
That's enough.
Don't die...
and live.
Is that why you came?
Was the week-long vacation an excuse, too?
Did you come to stop me from dying?
It wasn't an excuse.
This is what I really wanted to do.
You came to save me?
After dying because of me back then?
I didn't die because of you. And—
What happens to you if I live?
Can we not see each other again?
Hey, look. The sun is setting.
Don't change the subject.
Hey,
you don't want to see the Grim Reaper again.
Stop joking and tell me.
Will we not see each other again?
No.
We won't.
I died and you're alive.
And you'll continue to live.
That's nonsense.
Ram Woo,
tell me you'll be well.
That you'll live well.
You told me that...
time finally seems to be flowing.
That's enough.
Don't forget that.
Keep that mindset.
No.
That's because you're here.
You can do it without me, too.
We created this week together.
We even had an ordinary and cliché date today.
So, let me go now.
Stop talking nonsense.
Remember the people at the airport?
They were all full of hope.
I'd like you to live that way, too.
Full of hope. With a racing heart, wondering where you'd go next.
I'm not ready at all.
There are so many things I want to do with you.
You can do them from now on. I'll be watching.
I need to tell you so many things, too.
I'll be listening.
Kim Ram Woo.
Yes, Kim Ram Woo.
Don't forget.
Our time together... won't disappear.
It's all in you.
You...
You're Jeong Hee Wan and also Kim Ram Woo.
Please, please, please...
Please...
♫  I'm here to stay  ♫
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  Never letting you go  ♫
Kim Ram Woo.
Jeong Hee Wan.
Okay!
Okay, I'll live. I'll live well.
Don't worry.
I'll live happily.
You're listening, right?
I'll live well. You're listening, right?
I'm sorry.
You're listening, right, Ram Woo?
I can't do this.
I can't live without you.
Don't go.
Want to come with me?
Come with me. I need to tell you something.
It's okay. Go without me this time.
Jeong Hee Wan. Jeong Hee Wan!
Jeong Hee Wan! Hold on.
Jeong Hee Wan! Jeong Hee Wan! No! Wait a moment!
Wait! Jeong Hee Wan!
Hold on! Jeong Hee Wan!
Done. Let's go see the show now.
When are the fireworks starting again?
The last performance is starting now.
It'd be around nine, probably.
Sunbae, you're coming to the afterparty later, right?
I don't know. I'm busy now. Go.
I know you'll come.
Come to Railroad Bar by 10.
Everyone is paying 10,000 each.
Did you say "Railroad Bar" just now?
Yes, the one we go to all the time.
In front of the crosswalk.
­
Right. There's a crosswalk there.
It must be near there.
Fireworks. Fireworks.
Fireworks. Fireworks...
Railroad. Railroad.
Geez. This is killing me. Gosh.
The cross. The cross.
I couldn't do anything for you.
I couldn't say sorry
or ask for forgiveness.
You gave me everything,
but I let you go this time, too.
No, Hee Wan.
How do I live after letting you go?
I can't live without you while
remembering the past week.
Hee Wan.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
And thank you for everything.
Jeong Hee Wan! Hee Wan!
H-Hee Wan. Hold on.
Hold on.
Hee Wan, no.
D-Don't do this.
C-Come down quickly.
It's dangerous up here.
Let's talk for a moment.
Come down and talk to me for a second.
- Pardon?
- What can I tell you
to c-change your mind?
Hee Wan, l-life isn't so easily...
Well...
But Hee Wan, to die...
To die, you need...
to be in excruciating pain.
I'm sure the Grim Reaper was, too.
What did you say just now?
Did you meet Ram Woo?
How did you... When did you meet him?
Calm down, Hee Wan.
He wants to see the fireworks with you.
Everything will be over if you die.
Your pain right now will disappear too.
That's true.
But Hee Wan, the things you experienced, remember,
the sense of longing, and the times you shared with others
will all be gone too.
Hee Wan.
N-No, please don't do this.
Hee Wan, hold on.
Jeong Hee Wan. Jeong Hee Wan!
Jeong Hee Wan! Hold on.
Jeong Hee Wan! Jeong Hee Wan! No! Wait a moment!
Jeong Hee Wan!
Hold on! Jeong Hee Wan!
Kim Ram Woo.
You have 30 seconds left.
Let's watch it together.
♫  The blue memories inevitably resurface  ♫
♫  When such a night comes again  ♫
♫  The feelings I cannot get rid of inside me  ♫
♫  When the wind that was returning blows  ♫
♫  I close my eyes missing you  ♫
♫  My stars have gone away  ♫
They're even prettier because we're together, right?
Yes, they're pretty.
♫  Even if it drifts far away  ♫
♫  I couldn't leave "us" behind  ♫
♫  I'll let you go now  ♫
♫  Into eternity  ♫
I told you.
You would've given me such a hard time.
Kim Ram Woo.
Kim Ram Woo, who's both Jeong Hee Wan and Kim Ram Woo.
I'm sorry.
That I lost you for the second time.
You didn't lose me.
You just won't be seeing me.
You must've wanted to live.
You didn't even have the choice.
But I couldn't save you even once.
I'm sorry, Ram Woo.
I'm so sorry,
Jeong Hee Wan.
You understand now, right?
Saving yourself...
is saving me.
I'll leave now.
Survive until the end and
we'll meet again.
Can I leave you in this world now?
You can count on me.
♫  Even if it drifts far away  ♫
♫  I couldn't leave "us" behind  ♫
Kim Ram Woo.
♫  Bye  ♫
Bye.
Gosh, shouldn't I wear a shower cap?
It didn't get on you. Why would you use that?
So sleepy.
Geez.
Hey, I need to graduate, I said.
I can't do assignments in this weather.
I need to graduate, too.
You and I aren't the same.
You have to graduate in one go.
It'd be unbearable if you don't get it in one go.
I'm sure it'd hurt.
Hey.
Do you have no sense of hierarchy?
Seriously.
How pretty.
Spring is the hardest.
Everything is beautiful,
but only I'm like this.
But I'm not the only one, actually.
It might look like others can easily get over things,
but we all feel the same inside.
I think the Grim Reaper knew that.
Hey!
Explain it clearly.
You're just the Grim Reaper. How do you know Hee Wan?
I think you'd hit it off with Kim Ram Woo.
What? K-Kim Ram Woo?
Who's Kim Ram Woo now?
So, why are you doing this to me? Of all people.
You seem to know what it's like to be left behind.
Isn't that why you can't ignore Kim Ram Woo?
So, please take good care of her.
But I'm still not used to being left behind.
Even when I think I'm okay,
I sometimes go back to that time.
If someone disappears from this world,
there'd be a hole this big.
But your memories with them are still there.
You just live with the hole.
That's what it's like to lose someone.
The more you try not to forget, the more vivid it becomes.
It'd probably stay that way
even after many springs come.
That's not too bad.
- What?
- That hole.
You can just live embracing it.
Well... Keeping it in a drawer
and looking at it once in a while sounds okay.
Let me see. Here it is.
Here. I took it at the festival.
But you dropped it and left.
I finally get to give it to you.
Kim Ram Woo, who's called Jeong Hee Wan. Hi, it's me.
How are you doing?
You've been appearing in my dreams a lot lately.
Sometimes I wonder if your visit was all a dream.
But every time I do, traces of your presence come to me like gifts.
The sand in my shoes,
pictures of us together.
The scribbles you left in my yearbook.
And there's a gift that came after your visit.
Yes.
There are early bird tickets for Incheon and Honolulu.
- You'd better book it now.
- I finally got in touch with Tae Kyung.
Hee Joo wanted to go freediving with me.
- We booked three months' worth yesterday.
- What about the flight?
You were supposed to come.
Ta-da! I got a passport.
You mean you didn't have one? Why?
Are you bragging since you live in Hawaii?
I also have a new habit.
These days, I often ask people
how they're doing.
♫  Since I'm a woman  ♫
♫  I wait another day  ♫
♫  You dummy, say it to me  ♫
Dad says he wants to make it to the top of the amateur saxophone competition.
I'm going to learn freediving because Hee Joo insisted.
Hong Seok seems to have passed the exam.
He's building his body for a calendar photo shoot as a muscular firefighter next month.
And the most important thing is my graduation exhibition,
but I couldn't think of what to do at all.
And you know what I found?
Your handwriting is fascinating no matter how many times I see it.
For instance, your "ng" character looks like a flat peach.
And I can't tell if some of your vowels are consonants or not.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
✨ The Marvellous ✨ Team @ Viki.com
Hee Wan.
Dad. Hee Joo.
- You came.
- Good work, my daughter.
- Congratulations, Unnie.
- You came.
- Is this it?
- It is.
- Beautiful handwriting.
- Is this your work, unnie?
It's mine.
To be honest,
yours is the best.
Don't say stuff like that.
Be quiet.
The flowers or green leaves won't come back.
There will be new flowers and green leaves.
There will be new warm days.
Nothing comes back
and nothing gets repeated.
Because everything is real.
Channel Manager:
miss_rochester
Editors:
frkszltn (Chief Editor), vicky_daebak (General Editor)
koriyan03, subwayhongsamkopiko &amp; yoneyone311_918 (Translation Editor)
Chief Segmenter:
queen_sung_kyung
Cover Designer:
juli_ann__
But I no longer want to change anything.
Hey, Kim Ram Woo.
Hey.
Because everything really happened to you and me.
That would always be true as long as I remember.
I'll remember you.
I'll continue living.
Because to us, loving myself
means loving you.
♫  Take my hand  ♫
♫  I'm here to stay  ♫
♫  I'll circle your path  ♫
♫  Never letting you go  ♫
♫  If you, ooh-ooh  ♫