I'm so nervous
what's the plan for leaving the island today?
We'll meet in Beijing and Shanghai.
No, it's at the sea.
We'll meet at the sea across.
If I leave the island,
I'm going to rent a boat
and stay here
and visit you every day.
Can you do that?
Watch this.
I don't know what to say.
Like this.
Hey.
Hold on.
Like this.
Like this?
You guys are awesome.
My shape is different from yours.
How about this?
It's good.
It's really good.
Look at this.
Like this?
Both sides in the middle
hold on.
Like this.
And then this.
I can't.
Will I get senile in the future?
That's not it.
I don't know either
some people just can't make it.
Do you do this?
How about this?
What does that mean?
Keep this position
stay here.
Don't move.
Move this part.
All three of us have problems with our hands.
This is the hand of the handicapped.
I was thinking
we can both...
What's your problem?
The hand would dislocate easily.
So you can't do a lot of supporting
and then stand up.
I can't really.
Yeah, because the hand is born
It's anti-articular, so
I thought that was normal.
I often test a lot of people.
They all have to do this here.
They turn over.
This is normal, right?
Right.
It's normal that
to turn their backs.
It's abnormal.
The three of us are abnormal.
Today I found
something's wrong with me.
You never acted normal.
Blow it!
I'm alright.
It's okay. Do it yourself.
Do it yourself.
You'll each have 10 seconds.
Counting down.
Elegance, that's it.
Come on. Blow it.
Next.
I'm not renewing my subscription.
How to renew it?
I don't have money now.
And I want one.
Right.
Do you have to pay for things like this?
Your skin is so tight.
He's got sharp lines.
It's really just the muscles.
And the skin.
I knew before.
He's really skinny.
Very skinny.
I used to weigh only 120 kg.
What about now?
They weighs a lot.
You should practice from 120 to 60.
Right.
When did it start?
10 years ago, 11 years ago.
That's why you worked out for 10 years and 11 years.
Right.
I went every day.
What time?
I usually go during my lunch break.
12 to 2 p.m. in the afternoon,
Is my training time.
So it's about the same to be here.
Don't you eat at noon?
I only eat for five minutes.
I'll eat right after I practice.
Then I'll go back to work.
In that case,
but still maintain your efficiency in the afternoon.
If I don't practice, I'll be sleepy.
When I do, I'll feel refreshed.
But at home, as long as I don't have to go on a business trip,
I'll go to the gym and practice for one hour.
But I don't do it by myself.
I need a personal trainer.
See my muscles?
I can see it.
It's obvious.
Don't just say it's not true.
Yes, it is.
Let me show you a close-up.
A little bit.
Right.
Why isn't there a swimsuit party?
We'll hang out together.
Boys can take off their clothes.
I will definitely lose this game.
What game?
But I can't keep my eyes open.
The thought of it fills me with joy.
This is a paid membership fee.
Okay. Start eating.
Happy New Year.
I want a piece of meat.
I want the chicken, too.
Pickled mustard green.
It's olive and vegetable brothers.
About the same.
Actually, we really love olive food in Guangdong.
We also eat in Northeast China.
This one seems to be from Shantou.
From Shantou.
But I think you look a bit like the Shantou people.
Do I look like the Shantou people?
You really are.
You also speak Cantonese, right?
They speak Chaoshan dialect.
We are Hakka.
Hakka?
You can't understand me when I speak Hakka dialect, right?
What?
Can't you understand?
Hakka dialect.
All right.
This time.
Please translate them.
What does it mean?
Guess an adjective.
That means "Hakka dialect."
That's it?
But to be honest,
chaoshan dialect is a bit like Fujian accent?
Fujian accent?
Yeah, the Southern Min dialect spoken in Fujian
fujian.
You're from Fujian?
Aren't you from Fujian?
He's from Fujian.
Fujian.
What are you doing?
"Hui Niu" is the name of the fat cow.
"Hui Niu" in Xiangguo.
We are completely free.
You're too relaxed now.
Yeah, I feel totally different
when I first came.
A sense of mystery is needed.
Don't be too fast
all of you
so maybe it's just that
you're always outgoing,
or say something
In the past.
Right.
There will be one process that gets better.
But my character goes to
It's Guo Xu.
At the very beginning, I felt
I felt like that's his personality.
But today,
more relaxed.
Yeah, he also knows that
he's more familiar with people around him,
so he's in his best comfort right now.
Even if people think he's a little neurotic,
"Crazy"
You're a good eater.
You really know how to eat.
The "Sandwich."
Peel the corn.
It's called "Sandwich."
Here's an olive dish.
Add some olives.
It's Guo Xu.
What are you doing?
Got it.
You show off.
We should at least watch our image.
Please?
I'll add shrimp to fill it up.
Don't worry.
Make it up
this group is so happy.
I know you're being crazy.
But I didn't expect you to be this crazy.
During the interview last night,
I said that he's the best when it comes to love.
It smells so good.
Help me hold this.
Hold on. Continue peeling the eggs.
Alright, thank you.
Recently, everyone's accent
have been taught by Jiang Shangru.
By me.
Really?
It's true.
That I had such a great influence
that's right.
After all, he's our hero.
In my opinion.
No.
Let's start eating.
Yes.
Start eating.
Let's eat.
I finally know who you look like.
Who?
I finally remembered it this morning.
Finally.
Xin Yun, come here.
Xu Weizhou is somewhat
and some. Right.
He is.
Xu Weizhou is more like
his mouth,
and eyes and eyebrows.
It's hard for me to answer.
I didn't know who he was.
Very handsome.
A very handsome man.
No, you are Song Wei Long.
Don't be patronizing.
And you're Zhang Yuanying.
Any more.
Don't eat it then.
Give it to me.
Don't worry.
Can you not eat the food others have had?
You can have mine.
I won't have yours.
I'm homophobic.
I've already vomited from the corn these days.
Corn, brown rice, sweet potato
egg,
you won't throw up if you eat eggs.
I want to eat hotpot.
Spicy pot?
Two-flavor hot pot.
I love spicy food and not spicy food.
I don't really like spicy anyway.
A pot with the same ingredient.
Pickled fish is considered hot pot?
Not really. It's stir-fried.
Is a dish.
It's a dish, yeah.
It's not a hot pot.
But there are those fishborn hot pot.
What does it mean?
It means to eat fish slices
I can't have any.
It smells fishy.
Maybe you haven't had anything delicious.
The real one.
Is there anything delicious in Shanghai?
There is. This fish-raw hot pot.
Very fresh.
Fresh and thin slice.
It's done in three seconds.
It sucks.
Cooked in three seconds.
Treat me when I'm in Shanghai.
Alright.
Have you ever had stinky tofu?
Certainly.
Stinky tofu.
Is the Taiwan stinky tofu.
I've never eaten Taiwan Stinky Tofu before
I've never been to China, Taiwan.
That's mind-blowing.
Please give me a chance
you're fair to everyone.
I'm sure he will.
I am the "Master Duan Shui"
All the islanders, please pack your bags
please gather at the public chat area.
It's so hot.
You look like you're getting hit by Water Light Muscle!
You know?
Do you have any paper?
It's fine.
Let's search for it.
I'll look for it. It's fine.
Don't be so tired.
Fu Jie, fighting!
Fighting!
I have sand in my eyes again.
It's okay. I'll wipe it for you.
I think there's sand.
Close-up.
The makeup is not perfect.
Don't worry.
OK.
Alright.
Can I have one?
Here you go.
Here's one. If you want to use it,
I don't have to.
Don't you have to?
You're sweating a little.
We cut it here
and he has
she is so lively.
Your friend?
You seem not right today.
You don't have enough energy.
Not enough energy.
This isn't
he doesn't have batteries.
I stole his batteries.
And gave it to her to use, right?
Sorry,
he's like me in my life.
As long as they're familiar...
Aries people should be cool at the beginning.
But when they're done, it's different.
Alright?
I didn't expect that Xiao En Ya would be such
xiao En Ya is super intellectual the first day.
The short-haired girl
I know my temperament.
Hey,
guo Xu is kind of
he thinks that
what happened to him?
What happened to her?
He is not the same as the first day.
Gu Zhenxiang is a bit unhappy?
He is not.
You think it's OK?
With what you know about him,
I said I didn't know what to do
would you?
I probably would. If I were you,
alright.
I'm actually very fragile
crispy.
Mine is crispy.
Right.
The fragile boy.
I'm the fragile boy.
Alright.
Aquarius gets along well.
They get along well as friends.
Aquarians are wise.
Aquarius "jumps" and I "jump" too.
Both of us...
Yes. You both are dancing.
That's dancing.
It became boring.
But you won't always be interesting.
No, I won't.
Guo Xu is always interesting.
I've slept with him for so long.
You've slept with him?
You two sleep with him, then I'll leave.
I've lived with him for so many days.
And then
guo Xu is always interesting.
Now let's report our feelings after sleep.
No.
We slept in separate beds.
We sleep in the same blanket.
The more I explain, the worse it gets.
Okay. I wish you two good luck.
I'll leave now, guys.
Close your microphone.
Now I don't talk.
Don't you think
that Guo Xugang's gesture is like posing?
He has
and now he's...
To sit down.
Every move he makes is well-designed.
I think they are funny.
The three of them are so cute.
They look so good.
But the three of them have a new taste.
Let's welcome the first team.
Will be Hu Wei and Jiang Shangru.
Enter the survival arena.
Is it a one-on-one battle?
Fighting.
Fighting!
This is the first partner mission.
♪ To practice love ♪
The same answer.
Great.
The last question.
I think the last question is really hard.
Very great.
The last question is really difficult.
I was shocked.
I still chose "no" in the end.
All the previous questions are easy.
I was not sure about the last one.
Let's welcome the second team. = Xiao En Ya =
To enter the survival arena
enter the Survival Arena.
See you.
Fighting.
Fighting!
Okay, let's see the next group's performance.
I'm also looking forward to seeing them.
I'm not really worried about them.
I think it's very effective.
Right.
I'm looking forward to Guo Xu's performance.
Help me.
Come on.
Help? How?
Why are we not
why are we even sighing so tacit?
And thought of
whether you accept being in touch with your ex
she? What is she?
I can't.
Why?
Why can she?
Why can you?
I'm catering to you.
That's what I think.
To see
how your ex broke up with you.
And it depends on
I think it depends on the relationship.
If it's the kind of deep love, no.
Right.
One to two months can do.
That's right.
Yeah, that's my standard.
That kind of thing is completely
there'll be no turning back.
There'll be no waves.
That's right.
Right.
What is this?
You always lower your head when you have a fight.
That's right.
Will you
I will.
Will you?
As long as I don't respect principle, I will.
Then you were great.
Start to learn.
I was surprised that
that's why I was surprised.
I can accept that a relationship started as a friend
I think I can't.
I can't.
Yeah, because...
We were originally...
They were supposed to be friends,
then they became lovers.
I've never had that before.
It's weird to me.
To turn your friend into your lover?
My lover must have fallen in love at first sight.
I must have fallen in love with him
I had some feelings for him
or a favorable attitude toward me.
That matters.
Yes. All yes.
Super important.
Super important?
Whether they can talk for how long
It all depends on this.
I think it is.
Right?
Super!
A lot of things will be affected.
This will happen.
Super.
Can go in the future.
Then your relationship with this person will make you
It depends on your attitude
It all depends on this.
After becoming lovers,
they share everything with their partner.
Of course, she must.
You'd be lying if you don't say it.
My other half will know the password.
I'm someone who checks my phone every day.
I don't check other people's phone.
I don't check other people's phone either.
I don't.
But I'll be honest with everything.
But you can watch it.
At any time.
But I have no habit of reading them.
Right.
Alright.
Let's welcome the fourth team.
Chen Meng Jia and Gu Zhenxiang.
Enter the survival arena.
Check it out.
Who is it? Gu Zhenxiang is coming.
Take a look.
Really?
For the second time.
We have great chemistry.
I believe in these two.
When your good friend clearly states
that you don't like him or her,
you will continue to date him
It's so hard.
I will.
Can you do it?
Me too.
I don't want to listen.
I wouldn't listen either.
I wouldn't listen to them either.
I don't want to listen. Not at all.
You know that. I won't listen.
Unless they hit a brick wall.
Right.
Then I found
he was right.
Right.
What do you think?
It's nice.
You mean the one in the middle?
Next to the middle becomes
I think we can fit together.
Your right hand
you're good at this.
Your right hand.
You're really good at this.
I didn't know until you were perfect.
We're not at the same level.
You can't see him?
I said we can only know when we are together.
We see the same thing,
right?
Alright.
That's not right.
This is not right.
Yeah, you have to fit to see it.
Right?
That's right.
Okay, let's eat.
Polyglucolipid.
And aim for 3.1 grams of protein.
But I also see that it's high.
The amount of carbs.
Today is
Is Lu Wanfei's birthday.
Happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you
thanks.
Happy birthday to you
come on. Make a wish.
Happy!
Happy birthday.
Thank you all.
I still want to eat your birthday cake.
Just a little bite.
Lu Wanfei is happy today.
Lu Wanfei is truly happy today.
I can't even imagine.
What will happen to us
what will we do?
We'll cry.
It's obvious.
We're going to burst into tears.
How many days is today?
It's been four days.
The fourth day.
It was like this on the fourth day.
On the twelfth day,
on the 12th day.
We'll resign naked.
And come to Sanya to work.
Yes, to work for you.
And open an inn.
Guo Xu, take one.
Guo Xu wants to vote for one.
Guo Xu also wants to be the chef,
and the atmosphere.
How about this? Let's contribute
the toughest question to answer.
Then we can discuss
all right, no problem.
Do you all think
that a relationship requires us to see each other every day
you should be together every day.
I can't see him every day.
They'll quarrel easily.
She would quarrel easily.
I need some distance.
Right.
A week?
Three to four days.
Yes, the most.
Raise my hand.
I like the kind
after working in the day,
we cook together,
go shopping together,
watch movies together and watch TV series together.
That would be happy.
Very happy.
She is very happy.
I said that
his expression.
It's not that I said nothing.
My mouth
this is how I look.
My speechless look.
No. I think the answer is standard.
Are all good.
I think it's a very funny experience.
I just want to see my girlfriend every day.
I want to see them every day.
You want to see him,
but I don't have to meet him.
Got it?
Yes, I think so, but I don't have to meet him.
Right.
It's normal to miss you.
Yeah, so you two are on the same team.
They are on the same team.
Alright.
No problem.
And then
the third from the bottom.
It's us.
The first question.
The pace of development.
Is that acceptable?
OK?
Actually, I think it's different
from different angles.
For girls,
the ambition of a boy is more important.
Most of the girls aren't willing
If they have
the other half is a slow worker,
I need to see how out of step they are.
This also depends on the extent.
I think the hardest one is the last.
When your ex comes to you for help, will you?
This question is tricky.
How about you?
We will definitely help you.
We all say yes.
Everyone will vote for us, right?
I would.
Why did you ask your ex for help?
I don't think so.
Why are we asking him for help after breaking up?
He's the only person in the world?
It's the same for both of us.
I will tell you
then what was the problem?
He still keeps in touch with his ex-girlfriend.
Wrong.
We should keep things
can we keep some of her things?
Right.
And I said "No."
Of course it's No. Right?
I am "No."
Just throw them all.
I'll throw them all.
Everything.
Even the cell phone?
Cleared it and formatted it.
Phone. In my opinion...
Like the phone she gave you
then you must not give it to her.
I just don't want the memories.
I thought it would be
I can buy that.
So it's not an amicable breakup.
It will be like this.
Peace.
It's just a process comparison,
rough.
Not very happy.
You know?
Because I've been changing myself.
I found that
he's terrible.
Once and for all.
It's she who thinks you can't.
You think she can't.
She's not in my ideal condition.
I think everyone's situation is different.
It's pointless to talk about this.
So, to find someone who's on the same channel
to talk about this kind of stuff.
Because everyone's view of love
hold a totally different view of love.