Now we'll play the game Gesture and Guess.
Two groups in pairs to battle with the tacit understanding.
The game is divided into two groups.
In the first round, boys and girls can form pairs freely.
In the second round, the teams are shuffled and regrouped.
In each round,
the winner is the one
In the shortest time.
Let's do it first.
Alright.
OK.
Does he know these words?
It's a little difficult.
How many words?
Tonight...
When we vote tonight...
What do you call that?
Weight?
By the way,
great.
This is a place.
We were there.
Arena.
Survival arena.
Playground.
You can say a few words.
Five words.
Survival arena.
The third question is...
This is so easy.
Simple-minded.
Tao Zhi.
Chopping wood.
Brilliant.
The fourth question.
Guru Guru Nagetto
water.
Two words.
I'm going to...
It's a night performance.
What is it?
Night performance?
What's that?
Disco?
Right.
About the event yesterday,
three words.
A get-together.
Brilliant!
I'll do it.
Three, two, one.
Action.
Three words, where are we now?
This.
In the chat room.
Hey.
It's a huge
let's match equally.
What is this place?
What's my constellation?
What is my constellation?
This is a little awkward.
The topic.
We were there every night.
We need weights on it.
Balance Island
oh, right.
I'll say it and make a guess.
Alright?
Alright.
Three words.
What were you doing up here yesterday?
Turn a somersault.
Almost.
The
three words.
What's the antonym of front?
Backflip?
That's it.
Next.
As I mentioned earlier,
what's our show called?
Be well-matched in strength
we are
right.
Two words.
What else should we drink besides Americano?
(Latte art) Latte.
Next.
What the hell is this?
I once challenged
I can kill a pineapple
how fast can I kill a pineapple?
I usually shoot one in five minutes at the soonest.
What's this?
This is local.
Local and Minnan dialect.
If not, let's pass.
Areca?
No, the next question.
This sliced pineapple is called "killing pineapple."
Got it.
Three words.
What delicious food Zheng De Dong made for you?
Coconut chicken.
All right.
Look at the time.
1 minute 37 seconds.
It's so stressful
= 1 minute 37 seconds =
That's amazing!
I thought I was talking about this chat room.
I thought about it for so long
I thought about this
the third group, go!
Let's do it.
We?
Let me guess.
I think this team will be very
there's a tacit understanding
maybe get the first prize.
Three, two, one. Go.
You'll have to vote every night.
Every night?
The weight
that puts its weight on it.
Balance.
What?
The balance of preference.
What are we?
The islanders.
Everyone wants to do the most.
If we leave now,
going disco?
Shut up.
Two words.
Two people.
Going on a date?
Who did the cooking?
The word "profession"
The cook,
of the kitchen.
Is here to cook.
Hello, my name is Guo Xu.
My name is Chef.
The career of cooking
to be a chef.
Right.
Next.
What's the name of the place you went to get the prizes?
The supplies room.
It's done.
Everyone is so talented.
Each team is better than the last.
Then, all of you must play.
So scary.
I feel like I'm gonna lose.
It's scary.
This is so fast, you guys.
Here they come.
Three, two, one.
That...
Those animals over there
the flying thing.
Mosquito.
We see that
there is an animal flying high in the sky.
A seagull.
And...
What's this?
The splits.
Let's go to that place
working out.
Three words.
Gymnasium
that's so simple.
What's his name?
This muscular guy.
Fu Jie.
Two words,
two words.
Lift the iron.
Hey.
Roll iron!
(Pick up the flying iron) its scientific name
when we pick it up,
two words.
Work out.
Roll the iron.
That's right.
The next one.
That...
What's the name of the girl next to him?
The new guest.
Will be Chen Meng'er.
It's hard to guess.
Come on.
Ready.
Three.
Two. First,
where a boy hugs a girl
It's a gentlemanly gesture.
It's a hug.
Alright.
There's this kind of animals on the beach
those kind of animals.
The birds
It's green with a shell.
It's green.
The crab is green.
They are green with a shell.
He has a round head
four limbs and hands.
There's something thick on her back.
Living by the sea
live by the sea
you said that.
Next.
These are...
Personnel
what are the characters?
No four characters.
Then they would
camera.
That's right.
Photographer
the first two words are right.
I mean they are
It's the slightly older team
we respectfully call them
photography Brother.
The fourth word is right.
The third word.
They are
photographer.
Right.
OK. And...
What's his name?
Daniel. Danny Chen.
And then
a posture in the water.
Like this.
Freestyle.
And the circus
what performance?
Daniel's performance last night
acrobatics.
All right, stop!
It's done.
For a long time.
It's a little hard
a little hard
we have good tacit understanding.
Congratulations to Fu Jie and Lu Wanfei
very fast.
Come on.
Show it to the camera.
Alright.
This is our new matching.
The first group.
Fu Jie, feel it, please.
Black hole of games.
Three.
Two, one, go.
Turn.
What's this?
Interesting.
I don't think he understood it.
You can explain it to him
one by one.
Is this a character
big.
Reverse.
Little.
The first character.
Okay. The second is...
The air!
The bird,
as a little bird rests upon a man -- a timid and lovable little woman
the second question is:
It's Guo Xu.
Three words.
He's...
Foodie.
Three words.
Dry it.
The first word.
Dry rice.
People who have good food.
It's also Guo Xu.
Brilliant.
It's Guo Xu.
It's very bright
how should we describe this person?
He wears very shiny clothes.
Three words.
Very bright.
Right. This guy is wearing special clothing.
What?
Blind?
We might say that this person
pinyin.
Conspicuous bag.
Great.
The fourth question is coming.
Black ball.
Bubble Tea
what kind of man are you?
Four words.
The line is very
straight.
Straight man.
You guys have some chemistry.
Mainly, Fu Jie is good at guessing.
Fu Jie is good at guessing.
Brilliant!
Three minutes and 29 seconds.
Cattle.
Normally, when Daniel gestures like this,
he will never guess it.
Well, I'll explain then.
This is really hard.
Three.
Two. One. Start.
In the country,
there lives a lovely girl
we call her
princess.
But girls in Taiwan will say
the homophonic word
the last word
what do guys usually do?
Princess hug?
Hey.
When guys work out,
they will lift something up.
The lift thing up?
Lift.
Right.
Gongju is small.
And then,
girls scolding boys.
And it's related to a kind of food.
That food can be stewed
we enjoyed the food.
It's also related to your feet.
Pig trotters.
Is this how you describe
his chest muscles are like...
His two chest muscles are like
pineapple!
What is that?
His two chest muscles are like
papaya.
Not really.
And fierce.
The last character.
When we enter the room,
what's the first thing
the first thing...
Take off your shoes.
Before we took off our shoes...
They were locked.
First, we should
double-door.
Awesome!
OK.
And he's similar to Daniel.
There's
the dog.
He's the oldest.
He's a puppy.
No milk character.
The last two. Yes.
And then he's happy.
Happy puppy.
Oh, right.
OK. This one.
The first two are a kind of
a very pink
and a plant.
The pretty pink one
Is a cherry.
Botany
In blossom.
Cherry blossoms.
That's right.
What's the first word?
Peach Blossom.
In the last word to describe it,
peach blossom luck.
Peach Blossom Festival?
Isn't describing an island
taohua Island?
Is another word for island.
Another word for the island?
Peach Blossom Nunnery.
There are more?
This is so hard.
This is really hard.
How should I describe it?
Can anyone
when the weather is bad,
It's dark.
So many clouds
peach Blossom Dock.
Right.
Is over?
Is it over?
Cattle.
It's over.
How many?
Is impressive.
He Jinyi, the pressure will come.
Please say something.
All right, no problem.
You are so smart.
It has four characters.
The third character is woof.
The very fowls and dogs have no peace -- general turmoil
one three is right. The second one is...
Yes.
Two words.
What's this?
The chicken.
What will this animal do the next day?
Crow.
Cock crow and dog crow.
The last word is wrong
there was a girl in black
and took something
what's that called?
Fourth sound.
The rooster crows.
What's that
small tricks
right.
Zheng De Dong has three characters.
He's from Hainan and a local.
What does that mean?
Two words.
Strong and cool.
The first word of
got the first word right
when I drink water, I have to open it.
That's cool.
So smart.
I can't see.
Then,
Who are you?
A blind person.
And what am I doing?
Swimming.
What is this?
Touch.
Make an overall judgement of sth. on the basis of one-sided viewpoint;
What's this?
Normally, you would say hello.
Question mark?
I live upstairs, on the second floor.
I want to go down there. What do you call?
What now?
That's right.
What's this?
4 minutes and 11 seconds.
You can even guess that?
What does it mean?
The monkey means.
Great!
It's our turn, Zheng Dedong.
Action!
Talk quickly.
What do you do on Mad Thursday?
Crazy Thursday?
KFC Mad Thursday, so...
So what?
Pay me by WeChat,
transfer the money.
Yes. What's the name?
Pay for it.
No.
What's this word?
The word "V."
That's right. V is right.
Tell me now.
Then use your V to pay me, got it?
I, V, give you money. Then?
And?
How many votes do we have in total?
How much is this?
Fifty.
Right.
The numbers say
v, you're 50.
Yes, then another way to call me.
What do you call yourself?
My name is Lu Wanfei.
Her name is Lu Wanfei.
It's really hard.
Let me tell you.
V I what? How much?
V, you're 50.
It's so hard
try another way to
you were right.
The V and 50.
There's a character in the middle,
so you want to do Crazy Thursday?
I don't care about Crazy Thursdays!
Hold on.
Three words to express my love.
These two words, love you.
I, m...
Right.
That's the second character.
"V"?
V what?
V is right.
"V" is the first character.
V, I'm super arrogant.
No, that's not it.
The "V."
The first two words are correct.
Then add numbers.
Add numbers.
V, I'm 50.
That's right.
That's right!
It's so funny.
Four words,
how do we describe
he's very brave and persistent.
Four words.
Charging for love.
♫ Tell you everything one by one ♫
We describe a girl as pure.
Clear what?
What do you use to describe a girl?
Something's wrong with my mind?
Is my Chinese bad?
There's sour milk
and you didn't know
pure milk.
Yes, pure.
Pure.
Right.
Then the second one.
Master of pure love, pure God of War.
That's right.
And then the whole situation
It was chaos.
Very messy.
This is hopeless.
That's hopeless.
It's hopeless.
If there is an attack,
defense.
Yeah, that's right.
We describe some people as scavengers.
Scavengers.
Right.
That's right.
That's right. Breaking it.
This is a hot word
the homophonic phrase
really?
Your name is fake.
Right.
There's a line in a play by Cai Shao Fen
In The Chronicles of Zhen Huan
In "The Legend of Zhen Huan,"
Huan.
I can't.
Right.
Six minutes and 39 seconds.
It's fun, you two.
You tell it.
I'll make a guess.
All right.
Time.
Three, two, one, go.
The first one.
The name of the fat thief
what's the fat one called?
Pigs.
"Pig"? So what?
What is he carrying?
On his back?
Piggy back!
Honey.
Oh, right.
That's easy.
Let's learn some internet vocabulary.
300 RMB. Let's guess.
Shut up!
Every day,
this is so easy to describe.
Three words.
That belongs to
we can't do this.
I want to hear your description.
What's the highlight?
Famous scene.
Brilliant!
This is... in the show.
Couple.
Right.
Similar to each other.
Love.
Follow me.
AB? What D?
What AB is D?
AB what D?
ABCD.
CP.
And what do you call food?
Eat.
Something is wrong.
That's not right.
Your logic is wrong.
That's hilarious.
What?
That's not right.
Lingshui. What?
What is sour?
Hot and sour noodles?
And then we put them back together.
CP powder
oh, right.
This question is very difficult.
This is a little hard. Don't worry.
Four words. We have porridge every morning.
To go with the rice porridge.
An olive dish?
No, the next one needs to tear the bag.
Pickled mustard green.
By the way,
the first two words...
The first two words are
what do you need to charge your phone every day?
Charging it.
Right.
Use the electric power.
Use the power?
No, I said that
to go with the pickled cabbage.
Pickled mustard green.
Electroshock?
Electricity.
Electronic pickled mustard green.
So clever.
It's the last one.
I love you in Chinese.
I love you.
Yeah, and changed the middle part.
What cloth?
What do I not?
No, that's not right.
Something's wrong.
He can't react.
No one can react to your description.
Yes, who knows?
Do you mean accent?
What about Taiwanese accent?
Taiwan Chinese accent
remove the middle character
and change the middle word
the synonym...
I'll summon you!
Right?
Brilliant.
Great.
Really great.
That's great.
I don't know about this.
High five!
Brilliant.
We are the fastest.
Now let's announce the result.
The first place will be the first team.
Fu Jiejia, Daniel.
3 minutes 29 seconds.
Our last place
Is Lu Wanfei and Zheng Dedong's team.
6 minutes 39 seconds.
Then we'll play
the game is
"I thought you were my friend, and you're missing me like this?"
Everyone
take turns to get to the box ahead
to pick a small ball.
There will be a problem on the ball,
then we'll write down
to nominate one of the guests
then I will count down from three, two, one.
Then we'll turn the whiteboard over
and show us.
After that,
start from there.
That's it?
Alright.
Which of us has the most
In a relationship?
Positive emotion builder.
What is a machine builder?
I don't know.
Who among us
which one of us
In a relationship.
Positive emotion maker.
What does that mean?
Is like a creator of positive energy
the most positive energy.
Should it be about two or one?
I wrote one person.
I wrote the opposite.
I don't know.
Alright.
Have you finished writing?
Come on.
Three, two, one, turn.
Fu Jie,
I wrote Jia wrong.
Which word is Jia?
The "Jia" of the guests.
Great.
You mention each other.
I chose myself.
Because I think
I think I'm good.
With our brothers,
he's very positive to me.
That's right.
I chose Zheng De Dong.
Right.
I think the feeling he gave me is that
he is easy to create
they are friendly
In a very positive way.
But I didn't.
I didn't write about you.
Are you sad, Fu Jie?
I think it's quite positive.
Thank you.
My name is Jiang Shangru.
I think he is
who is brave enough to pursue his love.
I'd also choose Jiang Shangru.
Because I think Jiang Shangru
provides a good service in all aspects.
That's right.
I think Jiang Shangru's
Is the most
but you wrote Weng Fanxii in yours.
I'm thinking about their relationship.
Right.
So why do you always think about others?
And write another answer?
Jiang Shangru is fine with me.
I'm thinking about making their relationship official.
I think
maybe I need to give Weng Fanqian
a lot of emotional value just like that.
Sorry.
It's not about you.
It's fine.
And I wrote Guo Xu.
Because Guo Xu is really
release his emotions.
Next.
What are you doing?
Are you going to smash it?
Like a walnut.
These are really...
Who among us
who can make the two of you
to become friends?
I have no objection.
If all our answers
Is the same,
then there's no need to explain.
Next.
Come on.
The question is
who among us
who would
to stay in touch with their crush
just to stay in touch with someone I like.
Who would keep in touch with a crush
would keep in touch with his crush?
To keep in touch with your crush?
Let me write about you.
You can write down.
No matter what.
On your own.
I'm not that kind of person?
Three.
Two.
Turn.
I wrote down Gu Zhenxiang.
Because I think
I guessed.
I think
get along with Hu Wei.
I think you might do that.
For staying in touch
Is to stay in touch
I think you might be this kind of person.
What about you?
Zheng De Dong and I once chatted about this.
Zheng De Dong.
Right.
Can you understand me?
That's me.
He once said that
he said that I can hold back as a thief.
A thief can hold back?
Why don't you guess?
I can tolerate
I don't know...
Yes, I'm tolerant.
I can bear to go to the toilet.
Why don't you guess?
Next.
Chen Meng Jia can be
can be good friends with boys.
That's why she has it.
Right.
I have the same thought.
I chose Chen Meng Jia
because I think
who can be brothers with guys.
Who become brothers with the boy she likes.
Is actually quite devoted in love.
No, I will tell him I like him.
She's a very blunt person.
Sorry.
A recognition error.
The reason I chose Tao Zhi
because that...
That's what I want to write.
You guessed wrong.
All right.
My question is who looks the most handsome among us?
Alright.
Who cares about faces the most?
Is that how anyone focuses on faces?
They care about faces the most.
Right.
He can be like this?
Why can't you choose one?
Copy the answers of others?
Right.
Follow your heart.
Three, two, one turn.
I...
I am just...
Many votes.
You can see that.
I wrote down myself.
Because maybe you don't know
this little clip at the beginning
at my personal interview.
Asked me a question.
What was my ideal type?
I said I like to be stable and motivated.
Strong.
A string of attributes.
Handsome.
Ambitious handsome guy.
A handsome guy?
Yeah, I'm actually very handsome.
I wrote Hu Wei.
Because I think
she chooses
or the boys that she's interested in,
I think you are the most handsome boys.
Right.
I think she'll write about herself
when I was there.
Right.
I think I'm a little
appearance association.
But I prefer
don't try to hide it.
Next.
I choose Gu Zhenxiang.
That's how I feel.
He also wrote about himself.
I thought this was closed.
Right.
Closed loop.
I also choose Gu Zhenxiang.
I may not talk much with Gu Zhenxiang.
But I feel that
you are a person who has high demand for yourself.
No.
That's what I think.
It's fine.
That's all
for today.
We'll go back and take a rest.
Three, two, one.
Card.