First Partner Mission
Cultivating Love
Our current chemistry
is hard to describe
It feels like we've been friends for years
I think it's weird
Turning friends into lovers is strange
My lover must be love at first sight
Do you have to ask so bluntly?
This is really difficult for me
I need to think about it for a long time
Please turn around
Chen Mengjia, Gu Zhenxiang
Time taken: one minute fifty-eight seconds
I think there are no surprises
Because I feel
We actually have good rapport when chatting
Because we're in a
mutually respectful and understanding
atmosphere
I think this is quite good
They're the fastest
As long as no other team gets all answers correct
we'll win
Now please welcome the fifth team: He Jinyi and Daniel
Okay
See you later
Entering the survival arena
I'll try to keep it interesting for you
Good luck
Go for it
We're not bored
We're happy just sitting here
You can do it
Go Daniel!
I'm actually quite looking forward to them
Please listen to the question
Allowed
Of course
This problem is really
quite perplexing
there are many prerequisites
Please raise your sign
Answers don't match
Accept the punishment
Complete twenty burpees together
Okay
So cute
I think we work together pretty well.
Even when answering questions,
or carrying out this punishment,
He Jinyi, Daniel
Time taken: four minutes and fifty-eight seconds.
Got it
Beautiful
Now, the sixth pair
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie
Enter the survival arena
They're indeed watching
Go for it
Keep it up
You can do it
Bring it on
Listen to the question
Those two are really fast.
They're somewhat well-matched.
Isn't that just a devilish figure
So difficult
His problem is very difficult
I think this game proves
that between us
there's something special
It's not an illusion
We might genuinely have chemistry
between us
These two questions are extremely difficult
It takes me half an hour to think about them
I'm actually quite curious
how Fu Jie would answer these
The answers match
High five
Cultivating Love
It's when two people start far apart
As they get to know each other better
Their hearts grow closer together
I think that boardwalk's distance
represents the distance between
two people's hearts
Now announcing the results
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie's final score is
They definitely want to win the competition
and go on an island date
I want to go skydiving with Fu Jie
This opportunity is quite important to me today
If there's a chance for an island date
I would choose Gu Zhenxiang
I'd like to be with him too
Lu Wanfei and Fu Jie's final result is
two minutes and two seconds
Congratulations to Chen Mengjia and Gu Zhenxiang
for completing the Love Cultivation challenge in the shortest time
and earning the first off-island date invitation privilege
I think we were quite fortunate in some ways
Not every competition
allows for such perfect teamwork
But today we had it
which makes me feel particularly lucky
This is what makes me especially happy
The first place winners are Gu Zhenxiang and Mengjia
Gu Zhenxiang will likely choose Hu Wei
for the off-island date
This situation makes me feel
a bit emotionally conflicted
According to the rankings
The top three can receive
different amounts of supplies
Let's go
Go
Then you go get it
Take whatever you want
I want this one
Take it, just grab one
Strawberry
Just take whatever
Just take whatever you like
Then take two colas
This one's good
Take a blueberry
Satisfy yourself and share with everyone
Then give me yours and give this to them
She gave me that chocolate
And that chocolate was heart-shaped
It melted
Okay, I'll eat it now
So delicious
I think it's
The taste of love
I got first place
For the first time
And this is what I really wanted
when passing by the supply room
Let me open it to see what it is
Aromatherapy stuff
Very meaningful keepsake
So fragrant
I'll put it beside me
When I sleep
I'll smell it while sleeping
Then I'd fall asleep thinking about it every day
You guys were amazing this afternoon, friends
Really?
I can leave the island now!
I can eat all the things I've been craving
The things I've been longing for
Going out for a day?
I don't know, we haven't talked about it yet
This is pure happiness
I don't even know if the date will work out
Whatever
But today I came in first, I'm so happy
Don't worry, if you ask me out it'll definitely work
If you ask me out, I promise it'll work
It can hear the sound of the waves
Hello
You're like a Kardashian, aren't you?
I just forgot
to come find you
Anyway, I waited for a long time
Sorry
It's fine
I'm really sorry
And the pineapple
The lady cuts the pineapple
So elegant, cutting the pineapple
Can you open it?
My hometown grows pineapples
I've challenged myself before
to see how fast I can kill pineapples
The fastest time to kill one
My personal best is five minutes per pineapple
You're really skilled at this
No water, this
The coconut has no water.
What?
This coconut has no water in it.
Can we eat the coconut meat then?
Can we scoop out the coconut meat?
Yes.
How did this happen?
Why?
I’ll help.
This is easy too.
Here, take this.
Can we throw this in the trash?
You peeled it yourself?
Yeah, she’s really good at it.
My hometown grows pineapples.
The land of pineapples.
If I peeled it, it’d all go to waste.
Take a piece.
Thanks, bro
I'll handle it, your hands are dirty
I'll do it, your hands are dirty
What kind of iconic moment is this
Iconic scene
Fu Jie
Okay
Come on
I'll give you one back
So delicious
Let me tell you, I'm the "Veggie Washing King"
Really? Then you wash them
How do I wash them?
Put water in and wash them one by one
Alright
Come on, how do I wash them?
How do you usually wash them?
Don't you know how to wash veggies? Just like this
Pick them apart leaf by leaf to wash
Get to know this
Still calling yourself "Veggie Washing King"?
"Bragging King"
I should be the "Bragging King"
Don't mind me
Should we throw this away?
This one's fine
Is it okay?
Yes
So tired, I need to squat, my knees are giving out
Washing veggies like this makes me so happy
What's wrong?
Never washed before, huh?
Happy man
Yes, thinner slices.
Your knife skills are impressive. You must be a chef.
Nicely cut.
Hand me a wet wipe.
Okay.
My hands are a bit dirty.
Alright.
Give
There's water
It splashed on you
How is it?
It's good, sweet
Sweet
I'll get a cup
I'll pour some for He Jinyi
She's been wanting to drink coconut juice
Everything's about He Jinyi
Really
I'm the most bitter one here
I do all the work here
And then you "critically hit" me
He Jinyi
He Jinyi really
He Jinyi won
He Jinyi won, He Jinyi is the ultimate winner
Give me the cup
See, pouring it this way won't spill
That's amazing
Thank you
He Jinyi
This is the only coconut with water
Thanks
Have a drink
You drink it
It's fine, you have it
I'm done drinking, you take it
No problem, you drink it
Do you want me to mix it for you?
Coconut milk.
Do you want coconut meat too?
Yes, just a little.
Such a huge bowl, only you would eat like this.
Really.
This is really delicious.
I'm someone who never eats desserts.
But Qing Bu Liang is different
I like mine with coconut milk
Okay, that's enough. I want coconut milk.
Deluxe version
My deluxe Qing Bu Liang
Thank you
Here's a spoon
Let's eat
Fang Xu burned his hand.
It's nothing.
Soak it in cold water.
What happened to your hand?
I burned it.
Is your hand okay?
It's fine.
I think he'll be alright.
Who has burn ointment?
Do you have any?
Me.
Burn ointment
You gave it to me
I gave it to you
Where did you put it?
In the tent
Can't apply the burn ointment
Because I was burned by that thing
There's no way
Then let him bandage it for you
That's alright
It's nothing serious, just a small blister
I'm begging you
I'm not that delicate
Please, I'm begging you, okay?
No, everyone made it sound serious
I kind of did too
I got a bit carried away
It's fine
Worried but didn't know what to do
I was a little hurt
She was very worried
She kept wanting to bandage it for me
But it really wasn't a big deal
But she remained very concerned
Use that on him
She was so worried
I was actually very touched
So from that moment
I felt that I like her now
Don't want to see anyone else
I only want to get to know Enya better
I'll stir-fry
What are you going to cook?
You direct me while I cook
Pick some greens for me to cook, hurry
Today you just sit down
Just eat over there
Give it to me
Don't move
My dish is ready
Thanks for your hard work
No problem
Let's cook those green beans
Because I really want to eat green beans
I'll stir-fry them for you
Don't move
You're too slow, let me do it
Please, just listen to me
I'll turn on the stove for you
I don't know how, you do it
Sorry
I'm "useless"
No wait, it's on
Oh that's how you turn it on
Thank you
Then I won't help you, do it yourself
Stay with me
Then you have to praise me
You're amazing
You need to provide emotional support
Then I'll help you
I said you need to provide emotional support
This is hilarious
Seriously, stir-fry it
These ingredients smell so good
Really
Watch me flip it
I actually love stir-frying with these spices
Me too
I think we must eat hot food today
We must eat hot food
Where's the spatula?
No idea
Here
Where is it?
It's dirty
This one
Okay, it's clean again
Come on, buddy
Let's do this
You're adding so much soy sauce
Do you understand?
Then I won't help you, do it yourself
You're no longer providing emotional support
I'm not cooking anymore
Then don't blame me, I'll stay with you a bit longer
You're amazing, so good, thanks for your hard work
Do you want to try flipping the wok?
I can do it too
I can do it too, why don't you show me one
Show me one
You do it
I can't hold it up
I think it needs some strength
And technique
How do you flip it?
Beg me, and I'll teach you
I beg you? No, you should beg me to learn
Has some skills, but not much
Every dating show has a cooking guy
He is
They say the cooking guy has no love life
The cooking guy has no love
No, our cooking guy has love
What nonsense
Right
"Wingman" (assistance)
A pretty good "wingman" (assistance)
Don't mess around
My relationship with him before
Was quite superficial
But this time
Through cooking together
I saw him
Actually has a lot of hidden qualities
So in this aspect
It deepened my impression of him
Alright, time to eat
Great
Okay, let's eat
Thanks for the hard work
Our hero
Let's applaud Guo Xu
Where's your plate?
I'm looking for it, it's fine.
Come sit over here.
Okay.
Is this seat taken?
No.
These glutinous rice balls are so filling.
So filling.
Eat less.
Are you on a diet?
Because you've been having indigestion lately, right?
So eat less.
It's good for your health.
Okay.
Got it.
Here's an idea.
Let's each contribute one.
The most tricky.
Most difficult question you can think of.
Then we'll discuss them.
Okay, no problem.
There's this one.
If your brother was cheating.
Would you tell his.
Partner?
Our group had the same question.
The hardest question.
Because
It's possible his partner is also my friend
If that's the case, you might
I would gently remind them
But wouldn't say it directly
I might say you should be direct
Because personally,
If I knew, I couldn't bear it
It would hurt too much
Actually, I think my friend is my friend
He has nothing to do with me
I have no right to interfere
Other people's relationships are their business
I wouldn't
Right, I wouldn't get involved
I'd consider it their matter
I should definitely
Side with my best friend
But if his partner
Is also your friend
Depends how close you are
Between a bro and his girlfriend
You always side with your bro
Who would choose the girlfriend?
Go ahead, you say it - I don't know
Every question is quite difficult
Ours is so hard
Did all five of you get it wrong?
I...
Please turn around
You two are last again today
I did
Forty jumping jacks
Fifty push-ups
Serves you right
Leave them
I'm making progress now
Starting to win
Starting to look like winning
Let me explain
What was the question again?
About whether to stay in touch with ex-girlfriends
No
About ex-girlfriend's
Ex's belongings
Whether you can keep them
Right
Yes, and I was saying
No, of course not, right?
He can
Starting to get angry
She's getting angry now
I think that belongs to his
Part of the past
Has nothing to do with the present
And I believe there were indeed good times
I think it's like this
Because at that time I
The reason for saying "no" was
I wasn't saying "no"
With "yes," there's a standard
There is no standard
Actually everyone's standards are different
I just heard the part about exes
I wanted to set boundaries
Because I don't like vague things
And the funniest part was
The next question
He said
"You should be more careful"
What was it again?
What was that?
"Would you stay in touch with your ex-girlfriend?"
Right, I thought since his last answer was "yes"
The next one would probably be "yes" too
Okay, so I chose "yes"
But he chose "no"
It really wasn't my fault
I directly said
Guo Xu
Is there something you can't tell me?
After I broke up with my ex-girlfriend
I never contacted her
Not even once
And you dare
I'm angry
You're angry
Go ahead and be angry
Fine
Then let's begin
Starting tomorrow, no talking
Okay
Come on, pinky promise
Ready, three, two, one
He immediately muted himself, seriously.
Do you know how a relationship
is built through all this playful bickering?
If I don't speak, he won't either.
Guo Xu had so many "funny antics" today.
We actually reached an agreement
to not speak tomorrow.
I think it's quite "hilarious,"
but also pretty amusing.
He's the "funny guy," I'm the "funny girl"—
is that what this means?
Meeting adjourned
Let's go home
Attention all islanders,
The Scale of Preference is now open.
Please proceed to the Scale of Preference
to cast your vote.
There are new rules.
Dear islander, hello.
Today is your fourth day of adventure on Balance Island.
Before voting,
you may choose to view
one of the following two options.
You may also choose not to view them.
Option one is boring
Option two seems interesting, acceptable
Option one
I saw Enya
gave me a token of affection
Then I think she
If she gave me a token of affection
I feel
there's still potential for us to develop further
I see
I want to see Zheng Dedong's, hurry up.
It's indeed quite similar to what I decided today.
Today we won't hesitate for even a second
I only live for myself
Go
On the first day
I asked him to walk on the beach
So I was technically first
Let's see if you're making
the breakthrough I want
70% is not wanting you to leave the island
30% is because
I have some feelings for you
Depends on your performance
If you're not proactive then
There's nothing I can do
Anyway, I've made myself clear
Guo Xu, it's all up to you now
Although ten days is indeed a bit
short
We'll see
Keep it up
No hesitation
There have been changes in my feelings these four days
I initially chose Zheng Dedong
But I felt he was wavering
So I thought there's no need
to cling to this one tree
Now
I'm putting all my feelings
on Guo Xu
My new partner
I'll try my best
to show you the outside world
I'll do nineteen
You just do one
Just one
I'm begging you
I'm not that delicate
Please, I'm begging you
You just focus on looking beautiful
I'll handle all these things
I want others to
show me a little more favor
I need to make my choice
I can't be ambiguous anymore
There are new rules
I choose option one
Okay
Got it
Weng Fanxi's two sincerity weights
will be given
to Lu Wanfei's one sincerity weight
Which one do you want to eat? This one?
I want both.
Give me three more pieces.
Do you play *Final Fantasy*?
*Final Fantasy VII: Remake*
You know my favorite character is
"Zack"
Forget it
Can I change?
It feels like there isn't a single member of the opposite sex on this island
that I can rely on or depend on
This feeling...
This afternoon with Fujie
we were so in sync
It suddenly felt like
I finally found someone I could lean on
I don't want to have any more regrets
I choose to give up checking
I choose to give up
I choose number one
I think it's satisfactory
There are three sincerity weights in total
And then over at Hu Wei's side
I received two sincerity weights
It should be considered quite a significant achievement.
Jiang Shangru and I naturally got along well in conversation.
Because he's also someone very articulate
and quite courageous in expressing himself.
From our interactions,
I could sense his
frankness, enthusiasm and courage.
When these favorable impressions accumulate,
they make the scales
tilt somewhat.
Whose two sincerity tokens...
By the way,
That Jiang Shangru didn't give me
a single sincerity token yesterday.
I still politely gave him
one sincerity token.
That's fine. Your two loyal...
Actually no.
What happened?
What happened, sister?
Wasn't there a choice option?
You chose option one.
Yes, I chose one.
Today I want to choose option one.
Let me check last night's
status of all my preference tokens.
Thank you.
Gu Zhenxiang didn't put all his chips on me
Not fully committed to me
Jiang Shangru went all in for you
And this was right after our date
Completely chose you
Right
And this morning I asked
Would you change your mind?
What a great question I asked
Do you think you might change your mind?
Not at the moment
Put that on the big screen
My face turned green right then
The way you asked that question
But see how useful it is now
I'm quite certain
Jiang Shangru went all in
But as for Gu Zhenxiang
I'm not entirely sure
Because he might have other thoughts
Plus he's the kind of person
Who keeps many things
And thoughts to himself
So I think he might have
Other options
I think I'm pretty good at reading people
Sis
Come on, Professor Gu
Professor Gu, you okay?
How are you feeling now?
Same as you yesterday
Then I'm curious how you voted
It's complicated
Don't say it's complicated
Now I get to be the spectator
What should I do?
Seeing you like this makes me feel better
Don't know why
You're so "mean"
Suddenly feeling a bit better
No, it's just that
I think as long as you're clear about it
It's all for the best
I choose the second one, Hu Wei's
Jiang Shangru is two sincerity weights
I am a weight of sincerity
Of course I'm not satisfied
But
Due to my personality
I can't bring myself to pursue a girl wholeheartedly
And he (Jiang Shangru) is more of
the proactive type
Scary, wait a moment
No, you have to eat it
Oh my, I finally get to play with my favorite Zhenxiang
and play games together
High five
Being with you is really relaxing
So happy
Very harmonious
Yeah
I think I'll have trouble falling asleep tonight.
Dear islanders
Today is the fourth day of your adventure on Tianping Island.
I want to check
the favoritism status I received last night.
Off-island date
Off-island dates have lots of fun activities
I'm particularly happy
Girls really fall for this kind of thing
You know
For example
If there's a female contestant you like
As a guy
how would I impress her?
If she didn't eat much today
maybe the food didn't suit her taste
"Just eat something"
Then manly put it down and walk away
Without caring if she eats it or not, right?
As for impressing guys
When he's with his male friends
if you suddenly show him kindness
he'll feel particularly honored
He'll think
You know what I mean
Everyone's like this
wanting special attention from others
Anyway
Got it?
Like how I prepared
an ice-cold water for my teammate today
Who would've thought fate would arrange
Gu Zhenxiang to be my teammate?
Who could have predicted this?
Now let's welcome
the two who get to choose tomorrow's off-island dates
Gu Zhenxiang and Chen Mengjia to make their choices
Dear islanders
Congratulations on successfully obtaining
the first off-island date invitation privilege
Please confirm your feelings
Write the name of the opposite-sex contestant
you wish to invite on the invitation card
This invitation applies to all opposite-sex contestants
If you choose someone from the losing teams
they cannot refuse
If you choose your current partner
but they don't choose you
you'll lose this off-island date privilege
Wishing you successful invitations
Opposite sex members from the defeated team
The other party has no right to refuse
Then should I go on a date with someone?
I'll ask you out.
It's really easy to get along with you.
Very happy.
Very harmonious.
Right.
This water isn't cold anymore.
This is with ice inside.
Not hand-held.
How many guys do you like here?
Gu Zhenxiang.
And another guy talked to me too.
So next time could you...
Be quicker?
Okay, I'll definitely be quicker.
Too late.
Late again.
The big star and her two assistants.
What I mean is...
I don't really want to pursue too actively.
Chasing girls is too tiring.
Whatever he wants
If he doesn't want to go, I'll just keep eating salads on the island
Carefree attitude
The percentage chance of tomorrow's date
I'd say it's fifty percent
Because first of all, I know he
has feelings for another female guest, Hu Wei
He's quite fond of her
We should respect everyone's feelings
I believe loving someone
or not being loved by someone
is a fundamental right
and both should be respected
Will I get to leave the island for a date tomorrow?
Whatever happens, let it be
I think she might choose me
But if she chooses me
and I don’t choose her, then I...
she won’t get a chance to go on a date
I’m really torn
I don’t even understand myself right now
I'm even starting to fall in love with this island
I don't want to leave this island anymore
You look so cute in this dress
Just like a little Disney princess
Morning
Good morning
Hello
That one doesn't move
That one is an idiot
Everyone has become stupid
Eating an egg feels so good
After eating one
It feels like my body is powering on
Yeah
They've already left
Not yet
It can't be that fast
You really care so much
About me?
You were supposed to work out today
I overdid it today
I worked out till my hands peeled
Hope everyone can have fun
But I feel terrible
You already said what I wanted to say
Have you guys noticed something?
Our Fang Xu is unusually quiet today
He's found his place
Fang Xu's mind now
Is somewhere else
I just keep looking at her
Not seeing her annoys me
So pretty
That's not her below
It's her
That's her, right?
Can't take your eyes off her, Fang Xu
Good morning
Hello everyone
Right
What's going on?
Why do I have a northeastern accent?
No way
Speak Cantonese
My Cantonese doesn't sound quite right
Not working
The sound of waves is so nice
Yeah
Why is the northeastern accent still there?
Is no one going to keep me company?
Even a quick chat would do
Guo Xu
Today Jiang Shangru will use his strength to
chop down that tree ahead
to clear the view for our Guo Xu
You should work hard with Chef Brother (Guo Xu)
If anyone needs to work hard, it's him
Why should I be the one working hard?
Let's just say it depends on fate
Nothing we can do
Really
We still haven't been on a single date
We can only chat privately
What's going on?
Guys
I really want to take Enya out on a date
Okay
Alright
I'll make it happen for you
He's so cute
Laughing so happily
Because I promised her yesterday
We're in last place
What did you promise her?
Promised I'd try my best
To take you out to see the world
So romantic
I'm touched by the romance
I'll try my best
To let you see the outside world
I'm allergic to romance
I'm smitten
He's completely enchanted
I'm enchanted too
I can see your dark circles
Your eye bags are showing
But no matter what
It seems like you're going out
To stay overnight
Right?
If you're staying, you won't come back
Then let's work through the night, Fu Jie
Keeping ourselves busy, right?
Let's go
Should I bring a backpack?
Because I have luggage
You can carry a backpack
Dear islanders
Good morning
We're about to announce the first off-island date list
First
For the partner mission
The two winning islanders
Gu Zhenxiang and Chen Mengjia
Please proceed to the off-island meeting point
Good luck
Goodbye
I'll head over first then
Do your best
Go for it
Wait for me to come back
I'll bring you back some treats
Have fun
Just finished a fashion show runway
I can finally leave the island
I can eat all the things I've been craving
At least go on one date
Just imagine
A male guest by my side
And the two of us together
Watching the ocean waves
I think being paired with you yesterday
Was the luckiest thing
Cheers
I'm going to find a guy to date
Yes, I'll ask Gu Zhenxiang
Can you tell him after you go back
To come find me
Who did you say?
Gu Zhenxiang
Then tomorrow, we'll both go ask someone out
I'll ask you
We really have great chemistry
I'm okay
Don't look at me like that
Do I look that bad?
I didn't say anything
Look at you adding drama to yourself
Right
Piling it on
Adding bitterness, adding sourness
Like a bowl of snail noodles
Both stinky
Sour and smelly
Stinky and sour
Congratulations to Gu Zhenxiang for successful island invitation
Chen Mengjia's island invitation failed
Please return to the tent area
There's no way
That choice yesterday
was too difficult for her
Who did she invite?
Who else could it be?
It's
She chose Gu Zhenxiang
Gu Zhenxiang rejected her again
High five
If you choose your own partner
but they don't choose you
you'll lose this island dating opportunity
Wei, please proceed to the off-island meeting point for the date.
Good luck!
You look great today!
Congratulations to Gu Zhenxiang for successfully securing an off-island date.
Chen Mengjia failed to secure an off-island date.
Please return to the tent area.
Alright
Go back to sunbathe
I'm back again
It's fine
Come on
Hurry
Come play with us
No problem
She's still very...
dressed up carefully, right
Still beautiful
Of course
It's alright
Join us
This thread is showing
Have a seat
So pretty
No worries, today you can
go on dates with five guys
Right
I'll stay for a bit first
Okay
If it were me
This is how rejection feels
I'd absolutely break down
Exactly this kind of—
When I muster the courage to choose you
But you turn me down
It’s pure agony
I won’t cry
I used up all my tears the past three days
Oh no, my makeup is smudged again.
Crying here every day
How embarrassing
I'm going to sleep
Lying flat keeps the tears from falling
I want to exercise.
Let's exercise.
I'm going to read.
I'm going to sunbathe.
That way, I won't feel unhappy.
Hello
This outfit again
Pretty much the same, right?
Come on, hold my hand
Finally can wear jeans today
Thank you
Really?
Yeah
Didn’t expect it?
I think Mengjia would be so sad
Yeah
Absolutely
Elegant
I want to be elegant
Hope they have fun
Bring me an ice cream
Let me rehydrate
I was so happy yesterday
I can finally leave the island for a date
I can go play pool
I can leave the island
I can eat everything I want
I'm number one
First time I chose Fu Jie
Fu Jie didn't choose me either
I choose both of you
Thank you
Second time I chose Gu Zhenxiang
Gu Zhenxiang didn't choose me either
Gu Zhenxiang is my next
The date I'll strive to achieve
Looks like sis has to shine alone
Capture all the tears
What's there to cry about?
You said it's okay
He rejected you
You would respect him
You would still be happy
Then why are you crying?
You haven't even left the island
Why are you crying?
Goodbye
You cry even when you're rejected
All you do is cry all day long
Hello
So fun
Hu Wei
Don't be too happy
You didn't see Chen Mengjia just now
Crying in the room
I don't want to look to the left side
I'm heading north all the way
Leaving the season with you
This is too much
You're leaving
I know it's simple
I should be under the car
Not in the car
Shut up
I need to get my ID card
Get the ID card
What do you need the ID for?
I never thought
How important an ID card could be at this moment
I'm leaving first
Goodbye
"Massacre" "Chaotic killing"
I'm going out
I don't care
I won't take off my sunglasses
I'll wear sunglasses all day
Fine, okay, whatever
Just this cool
Just like this
And even walked right past me
It was really nice when I came out too
They've gone far away now
They were just here carrying suitcases
You're so mean
Making me come out now
Don't cry
If you cry, I'll cry too
This kind of empathy between girls
Daniel, please proceed to the island date meeting point
What?
Why?
What kind of rule is this?
What's this?
Where is it?
And?
No way
No, this can't be
I didn't expect this
What is this?
What's this?
Why?
When did he get to choose?
Did other female guests choose him?
Hello
New resident of Tianping Island
You will have the chance to choose a preferred guest
for an off-island date
Please review the photos first
Follow your heart
and select one as your date
I choose Daniel