At the time of our farewell
write a song
I hope everyone can write one sentence
as if it were from me
a gift for everyone
a song that belongs to us
I deserve this.
Seems a bit unhappy this afternoon.
I'm determined to be myself.
Okay.
Limited-time dating is available.
The second candidate is...
There's actually a second person.
There's a second candidate.
I didn't feel...
...being firmly chosen.
I'm not sure about my feelings...
...what exactly caused them.
I'm also very interested in Weng Fanxi.
I think everyone should...
...follow their heart's choice.
I might have some regrets, I think.
This is so beautiful, absolutely stunning
After I take one of you, you take one of me
Okay
Three, two, one
Let's do it again, face the camera
Three two
I'm a bit hungry
What are you doing?
I was making faces at the camera
This side of you got much darker
Super dark
Me too
They say my back got tanned
Indeed
Because I can't reach it myself
I'll just spray randomly, that's good enough
Anyway, if I can't see it then it's fine
I think you look like a Samoyed
What are you laughing at, Gu Zhenxiang?
I think it's better if you lower your head and look straight ahead.
Yes.
Just give me a side profile—yes.
No, come back a little toward me.
Right.
What? Why are you laughing?
It's really funny.
I'm very professional, okay? Don't mess around.
I was so focused on taking your photo
that I completely neglected my own appearance
What does it say?
Because it's already coming to an end
I'm very happy and relaxed
I'm also enjoying the process
I wish it could slow down a bit
Dear islanders
Now announcing an important notice
I'm a bit nervous
Drama
From this day onward
No more islanders will leave Tianping Island
Great, no one has to leave the island.
No need to worry anymore.
We can relax now.
Yes.
Tao Zhi.
Let's go.
Charge!
The timed date has begun.
Tao Zhi, please proceed to the meeting point.
Thanks, brothers.
Go ahead.
Happy.
Happy little steps.
One step, two steps.
Tao Zhi looks very handsome today.
Yes, you can tell.
Very neat.
The current limited-time dating event is open to
From the previous round's preference-based matching results
The islander of the opposite sex you selected
Chen Meng'er, please proceed to the meeting point.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, everyone.
Beautiful.
Then I'll head off first.
Have a great date.
Goodbye.
Okay, goodbye.
The most beautiful sunset.
The sunset is beautiful.
So gorgeous.
Very romantic.
When I was talking with Tao Zhi,
he told me,
"I would choose to go on a date with you."
"Do your best in tomorrow's competition,"
"and earn that date with you."
I said, "Okay, sure."
"We'll go eat something delicious."
Alright.
Hello.
What a coincidence.
It's easier to walk without shoes, right?
I thought today,
"I'd wear a skirt and heels,"
but they're really hard to walk in.
Yeah, that path over there is quite rough.
No problem, as long as you're comfortable.
Which side would you like to sit?
I'd like to sit here.
Do you want to sit here?
Okay.
You must be hungry.
So many people watching us eat...
I feel a bit shy.
As Biaozi wisely said,
"Eat when hungry, drink when thirsty, don't overthink things."
Got it.
Right, the main thing is to enjoy the meal.
Sounds good.
Shall we make a toast first?
Sure.
Sorry, I forgot.
Come on, should we say something?
"To celebrate us being here,"
"and enjoying a nice dinner together."
Okay, good.
Thank you.
Thank you for choosing me.
There are jet skis over there.
Right there.
So beautiful.
This scene is really beautiful.
Do you enjoy these activities?
I think I'd really like it.
What water sports do you usually enjoy?
I love surfing.
Actually, I'd really like to learn surfing.
I haven't really tried that before.
The kind where there's a boat in front.
Where you hold onto it.
And you stand on a surfboard like this.
That must be exciting, right?
You haven't tried it?
I haven't tried it.
Then I'll take you to try it sometime.
Okay.
Sounds good.
That would be great.
I also think that would be really fun.
And it would look really cool on camera.
So thrilling.
Very exciting.
What's this?
Beef?
Maybe.
Let me try it for you.
Seems like beef, with bread underneath.
I'll take a bite.
You can have it.
My verdict is: delicious.
Me too.
So hungry.
Want to try this? It's pretty good.
Okay.
The bread is delicious
The happiest thing for me right now is eating
Just eating—so happy
Right?
They probably never expected
A seaside date at sunset
to turn out like this
But here we are, just eating
The sunset is beautiful.
I never really paid much attention to it before.
Back when I...
stayed here for a couple of days,
at that time,
I truly didn't have time to notice that...
the evenings here...
when the sun sets...
are so beautiful.
I never noticed before.
It's wonderful.
Yesterday was the first time I noticed.
It's truly wonderful.
I really like...
one thing about you.
What thing?
You're very brave.
You take the initiative to express yourself
I think that's a very brave person
I feel like when I left and came back
my perspective changed so much
Everyone might have trained from zero to level five
But after I left for two days
I returned to find everyone at level seventy or eighty
while I'm still at level five
I don't even have the mindset of a level five anymore
This experience feels so awful
Because in my view
I don't care how others see it
But personally speaking
Personally, I really like this aspect of you
I really admire this quality because
I feel like I don't have this quality
Really?
I don't think I'm as brave as you
You wouldn't normally
take initiative to express so much, right?
Actually, that's how I am
Some people might think I'm
either reckless or foolish
But I think
I'm quite proactive in expressing myself
In my eyes, that's a very brave person
Every trait in a person
can be seen by some people
as strengths
while others might
find them uncomfortable
I feel like before
I told you about my inner struggles
stemmed from caring too much about others' opinions
I cared too much about what people thought of me
But I've realized that
with friends who truly understand you
you don't need to explain anything
So now I feel relaxed and happy
And most importantly
being with you
makes me feel so relaxed and happy
I think she's a wonderful girl
Getting her approval
made me really happy at the time
I also struggle internally
sometimes too
I think sometimes I do
But compared to you
when we compare
mine might not be as severe
Yes, mine is really serious
I've always been in a state of
not being very confident and struggling internally
You're so great
Thank you
You're wonderful
Why aren't you confident? You're so good
Just before I came out
all the girls were praising you
They kept saying how you're especially
protective of girls
And they kept complimenting you
saying your eyes and brows are very handsome
Thank you
I think so too, really handsome
So handsome
Your eyes are beautiful too
Your eyes are truly beautiful
I know
I think you have such a wonderful personality.
It's just that...
I feel like you're the type of person...
who radiates such positive energy to others.
You know...
Because I feel like you're just like...
For example, when you walked over just now...
you could tell I was struggling with these high heels...
and having difficulty walking...
so I had to lift them like this to move around.
You know what I mean?
You're just so relaxed...
and really good at spreading positive vibes.
Thank you.
That makes me so happy.
Really, being complimented feels wonderful.
Really
Yeah, just
It's really infectious, I think
I feel like we're both
discovering each other's good qualities
Right, but now that I'm back I feel
That slowly getting to know each other like this
is so relaxed and comfortable
I feel like these past two days together
have been so relaxed, just
I've been thoroughly enjoying this feeling since day one
After all, we didn't know each other before
and knew nothing about each other's backgrounds
Just having fun and being happy
Enjoying ourselves to the fullest
Right
I feel like the time I spend with Chen Meng'er
is always so simple and joyful
Without any burdens
When we suddenly want to talk about something
we just keep talking about it
And when we think of something
we just keep discussing it
My feelings about today's date with Tao Zhi
Very happy
Very relaxed
Saw a beautiful sunset
Then by the seaside
Eating spaghetti
Eating delicious bread
With such a handsome boy sitting across from me
This moment is just wonderful
I'll have another one, do you want some?
You have it
I'll eat soon, just need a little break
Date time is up
Chen Meng'er please return to the tent area
Wait until I finish eating
Then I should finish this too
I'll finish the bread
The second option for limited-time dating is
From the preference scale in the last round
There's also a second person
The second island resident of opposite sex you've chosen
Let me finish drinking
Okay, I'll find you later
My brain is overheating
Hang in there
I'll catch up with you later
Goodbye
My brain is overheating
The second available option for the limited-time date is
There's also a second one
In the previous round of preference voting
The second islander of the opposite sex you chose
Please proceed to the meeting point, Hu Wei.
Go ahead
It starts delivering according to this intention
Making trouble
I just heard the second one
I immediately felt something was off
My male intuition
How exciting
I'm doing quite well here
I didn't
I didn't... I can't believe it
Because he wanted to learn about Chen Meng'er or something
I think everyone could tell, right?
It's normal
Understand me
What does he want to know about me?
So I went
With this sense of doubt
I kept the appointment
Surprise
Indeed
I was shocked too
Didn’t know it was the two of them?
I don’t know
My brain’s fried
It's because on the first day I came back,
when casting the vote of sincerity,
it was just...
because my emotions were quite chaotic that day.
And that day, because...
while talking with you,
I felt like that day allowed me...
to guide you.
Right, so that same day,
I voted for you and Chen Menger, but...
I never expected it to turn out like this today.
I really want to toast to you.
I had no idea...
Actually, the mechanism is based on
the sincerity vote from my first day back.
On that first day back,
I was feeling a little lost at the time.
Hu Wei talked with me for a while,
and quickly cleared up much of my confusion.
So that day, I voted for her.
That's why I was truly shocked,
and also very nervous and uneasy.
I need to catch my breath first.
Today is fine, yes.
Thank you.
Right.
Don't be nervous
Let's have a drink
Thank you for choosing me
Thank you
I was just there taking photos for people
How could I be in them? You know what I mean?
Thanks to you
I can still have spaghetti
Thank you
This plate - you've already eaten
Right
Two rounds already
Yeah
Once Tao Zhi returns
we'll be the "revenge protagonists"
My brain is fried right now
Completely fried
Right, I need to think carefully about what to say
About what needs to be said
Yeah, I think keeping it casual would be best
Honestly
Since we don't have much time left
And then, right
Actually having a chance to chat is nice
Yeah
Let's talk about my first impression of you
Okay, I'd like to hear that
Remember when we had that ribbon-tying activity?
Was yours the one I tied?
That was beautifully said
I thought what you said was really special
And then
You know at first I thought
No one would understand what I meant by that
But I actually understood
I felt that you might
In your daily views on relationships
You're actually quite mature
And a very smart woman
But I think deep down you're still very
Romantic and idealistic
When it comes to love
You have a very pure pursuit
And you know exactly what you want
You're very emotionally stable
But sometimes I feel
Being so stable and mature
And intelligent at the same time
Actually means your desire for romance is relatively low
I don't know
Are you the only guy on this island
who understood what I meant by that?
But I think your interpretation
is absolutely correct
Really?
Thank you, I appreciate your approval
You mentioned earlier that I said
my desire for romance is quite low
So my purpose for coming here is actually
on one hand, for example
since I haven't been in a relationship for many years
I feel like
I could rekindle that desire
Sometimes I feel that
I'm too rational
and appear to be quite aloof
For example, there are some confusing issues
I'd like to consult you about
Life coach "Sister Nan"
Right
That might be the situation
And then perhaps
it makes guys feel
this girl is very smart and mature
and then they don't know how to approach me
Yes, I think that's possible
You might encounter this situation
Hard to approach, right?
Yes, so
In crowds, when there are many people
I prefer to be an observer
So actually everyone
You know, I noticed
everyone's behavior when they first arrived
What was your first impression of me then?
Your skin was very fair
Really?
But not anymore
That's true now
You were very fair that day, and very polite
Because you made eye contact with everyone
As if to say "I'm here"
Thank you
I notice these details
Because I was really nervous and awkward then
She actually kept comforting me
And gave me lots of positive feedback
I feel that
Having a friend like that
Would be really wonderful
Yes, eat more.
But I really think that actually...
Although I was a bit nervous today,
and somewhat didn't know
how to properly chat with you,
but I feel
quite grateful for this opportunity
to get to know you better
before everyone parts ways.
And also,
I'm very thankful
that when I first came back,
you gave me some guidance
and positive energy.
Now Tao Zhi is making concluding remarks.
Anyway, if you have anything
you want to talk about, you can come to me.
No problem.
Thank you.
You can in the future too.
Tao Zhi is a very thoughtful
and deep-thinking young man.
There's one thing I always tell Tao Zhi:
I say that you've returned
wearing the "revival" armor,
so you don't need to overthink things.
Just do whatever you want to do.
After you "revived" and came back,
have you noticed any
subtle changes
in everyone's relationships?
I felt that everyone, on the first day back,
because we were about to have games and competitions soon.
I thought everyone
seemed to hold back their words.
I felt that
they might have things they wanted to tell me
but didn't know how to say them.
Including when I saw her (Lu Wanfei) again,
I also felt that
whether it was how she looked at me
or how I looked at her,
it might have been different.
Hello.
How was your time?
Getting to know the other female guests
I think was perfectly fine.
And then,
the first day was really uncomfortable.
The first day truly
was very different from what I imagined.
If these three days have ended,
do you think everyone will experience withdrawal?
I think so.
Because my reaction was very strong.
I had completely gotten used to it,
and even started to like this phone-free,
timeless state.
I really enjoyed it, honestly.
Right.
Because for me,
my work is always very busy,
constantly checking my phone.
Before coming to this show,
I was very anxious.
I kept thinking,
"What about my work if I can't check my phone
for so long?"
For example,
right?
There were many things to consider,
but I discovered
that meeting everyone was
one of the luckiest things in my life.
Actually, I think making friends
without social barriers is more genuine.
Yes.
I also feel I've grown somewhat,
but I think there are still some aspects
where I'm standing still.
Still not back?
Guo Xu
Having too much fun
Hey, brothers
This is the taste of happiness
We've been spotted
Scatter
Start pulling
Yeah, pull
Tao Zhi
Thank you, everyone
So strong
I think you look like a Samoyed
Your eyes are really beautiful.
I know.
What are you writing?
What's up?
I was making faces at that camera.
It's so wonderful
How does it sound? Our theme song.
It's just not fully formed yet since it's freshly written.
I think when we say goodbye,
we could collect lyrics from everyone,
compile them together,
then I'll
make some revisions,
and compose a song.
Finally, we can all sing this song together
as a group.
That sounds nice.
Before leaving, having the chance
to chat with you like this,
or even take a walk around here,
I think is quite special.
Yes.
After Lu Wanfei read your letter,
I became curious about you.
I thought to myself,
"What kind of boy
is this person
who can write such tender words?"
Thank you.
Actually, none of us knew
Today's date was arranged based on the tickets
That doesn't matter
It's fine
At this point, what does it even matter?
Right
But if it's for the show's effect
Jiang Shangru should act
Tao Zhi
Give me my
No, you can do it like this
Tao Zhi, I treated him like a brother.
He stole my girl.
You don't know why Tao Zhi asked her out.
Then you anxiously waited.
That kind of...
That's a bit fake, bro.
It'll take her some time to get here.
Bro, just wait a moment.
Aren't you going to say the date is over?
She's here.
Laughing and chatting.
Do you mind if I...
Go to the guys' side first?
Not at all.
Alright.
It's fine, no problem.
It's okay now.
Everything's fine.
You're back
You were waiting for me
Waiting for you
Did you eat enough?
Not full
Still hungry? Let's go
Do you want to eat?
I'll get food for you
Let's eat
Do you want to change clothes first?
No
Do you want some meat?
One piece
I won't eat
Why?
I don't eat fatty parts
Put it here
Lean part
The lean part
Aren't you curious?
What did he talk to me about?
Then what did he tell you?
What did he say to you?
He said he didn't expect
there would be a girl as second choice
He just felt that
when he came back that day
he couldn't quite fit in with everyone
I talked with him a bit more here
He voted for you
Right
So he came to thank you
Yes
Okay
Let's just say the show's second choice
really shocked our Teacher Tao Zhi
He was so scared, wiping sweat like crazy
You said he was wiping sweat like crazy?
He was wiping sweat like crazy
Jiang Shangru remained completely calm
His mentality was very steady
Not a ripple of emotion
I believe in Tao Zhi
We share glances and gestures, right?
Every day on this island is full of surprises
Quite exciting
None of my previous days were this exciting
Have you considered my feelings?
Every day is nerve-wracking
Weren't you just completely calm?
Calm on the surface
But stormy inside
I was saying how Tao Zhi...
Right?
Gotta play along, right?
We're good brothers, right?
How could I possibly betray a brother?
Right, Tao Zhi?
Right.
No, because I had just returned that day.
Then I was chatting with her.
And since I'd just returned,
I felt a bit...
out of place with everyone.
I think many people...
She told me...
Okay.
Don't you...
Yeah.
Really.
I'm really fine.
Alright.
Because I know how you feel about...
Chen Menger.
Got it.
I understand.
I actually get along well with Tao Zhi too.
He didn't know how to say...
Next time suddenly became...
He could date two people.
So I think since he rarely comes back,
wanting to chat more with other guests
is actually quite normal.
But I still felt a little unsettled inside.
I have to say...
Just waiting on you two now.
I've got mine ready.
You go first then.
Let me write it for you, come on.
Come on, you say it first.
The moment my heart skipped a beat
Was when you showed me your favoritism
Yet somehow in the grand scheme
There's also...
I think...
I've thought of...
Come on.
Trading a lifetime of chaos
For just a few seconds of bickering with you
So poetic.
Zheng Dedong
Quick, write it down.
But I think...
We should capture his personal style
Because that line is too literary
It should come from his own thoughts
How do you feel about her?
I like you.
Enough.
He just wants to say "I like you."
That's enough.
Right, I think that would work.
If we're very similar,
like "I really like you" and so on,
then "me too."
That's her way of speaking.
I'll go get the guitar.
You all listen to the demo first.
Two people in love
It's courage, it's determination
I want from the first day to the last day
to have the same teammate
I hope the two of us can endure hardships together
Teammate, let's go!
I feel my time on this show wasn't wasted.
You look so beautiful today
Really?
Who could refuse Weng Fanxi?
I'm very happy today.
Tissue
What's wrong?
Got emotional
It's nothing
Guo Xu
Deeply moved
He's touched
The sea breeze can't blow away my longing
Just like Pirate City never has endless rainy days
I feel this line
Isn't just for the boy who makes my heart flutter
I think it's more about
Speaking to everyone present here
Because we're now living by the sea
Spending time together here
In this unforgettable communal life
I will miss
Every single one of you on this island
I hope everyone can write one sentence
Suddenly that afternoon sunset
Froze in my memory
Because it was truly unexpected
My feelings for Fu Jie
Came so suddenly and unexpectedly
Never thought I'd interact with him
Let alone develop feelings for him
The fireworks across the sea
And the bench on the beach
Actually that beachside bench
Is where I spent
The most time
On that bench
I've talked with many people
Learned many people's stories
I think for me it's also
A very special place worth remembering
The sea breeze brushes past your lips
I won't dwell on your past
It's actually reversed
What I meant was
The sea breeze brushes your lips
Hope you won't dwell on my past
I wrote
Please forgive my unspoken apology
To whom?
The "I" in these lyrics
Doesn't just represent me alone
Perhaps in everyone's heart
There are some small regrets
And things we want to apologize for
So I put that into those words
Alright
Don't cry
Okay?
There there
Stop crying
I'm really not good at comforting people
I'm fine
Alright
Wipe your tears, quickly
Okay, calm down
Breathe in
There are still three days
Save your tears for the last day
Okay?
Right
Don’t cry
It’s fine, go ahead and cry
Seeing him cry makes me...
We’ll cry together when the time comes
Three more days
Please
Keep the tears for the last day, okay?
I'm "dying" of laughter
I'm just that
emotionless songwriting machine
"Crybaby"
Now immersed in the songwriting world
Right
I think it works
Write "Crybaby"
I'm not a "crybaby"
Really not
It feels so surreal
I think this part
is actually today's
most
most interesting part
Yes
Very meaningful
Just feels unreal
Today's emotions are absolutely peak
Maxed out
Emotional value maxed out
Ending rehearsal
I'll put it later
This chair is quite comfortable
Yeah
Want to sleep now
Go to sleep
I'll wake you tomorrow morning
About to fall asleep
These two lovebirds
Heavenly sound
Going to
The time to cast our heartfelt votes has come
Attention all islanders
The Scales of Preference are now open
Please proceed in order
To cast your votes tonight
Starting today, no one will leave the island
Please make your choice
Based on your truest feelings
I'll go first
Goodbye
I don't hesitate
I know who to choose
That's why I'm first
Dear islander, hello
Today marks your ninth day
Of adventure on Balance Island
After these days together
You've come to know each other better
Among you
Some may have confirmed their feelings
Always the truest feelings
Alright
Today we'll all cast our votes
Today, I've placed all my bets on Gu Zhenxiang.
Because
I like him.
I feel extremely comfortable with Fu Jie.
It's that kind of comfort.
It's truly rare.
Two of them.
I would always stay with him.
Continue chatting and getting along.
So I firmly voted for Zheng Dedong.
The opposite sex I'd like to get closer to.
Would be Weng Fanqian.
I firmly believe she.
Probably has feelings for me.
And every day there's.
This kind of accumulation.
I think we have mutual feelings for each other.
He Jinyi is a woman I have feelings for.
I just want to give her.
Continue striving for love.
Keep trying.
I hope that if there's a chance in the future
to spend time with Chen Meng'er again
or even go on a date with her
I can get to know her better
Tao Zhi
And another one
Jiang Shangru
Gu Zhenxiang
Fu Jie
Zheng Dedong
Guo Xu
Daniel
Who's this for?
Tao Zhi
Fu Jie
Zheng Dedong
Daniel
Tao Zhi
Really
Then let's give them all to Tao Zhi
Today's votes
At first I gave one vote to Tao Zhi
But actually later
I wanted to give another vote to someone else
Because I hadn't felt
being firmly chosen yet
Hu Wei, please proceed to the meeting point
There's a second person too
Surprise
But after thinking about it
I voted for Tao Zhi again
Because I feel these past two days
he's been really brave
He did things I wouldn't dare to do
Do you think that I
asking to team up with you
or giving you votes and such
do you think that's okay?
Yes
Okay
And we've been having fun together too
Actually, I've always had
good feelings for Hu Wei
I might find time
to communicate with her more
I know this island's theme is romance
But I've gained much friendship here
It's not just about romance
I'll still give weight to Chen Mengjia
I truly believe
I'll cherish this wonderful friendship
Since there's no more departing island,
I think everyone should just be their true selves.
My feelings
have basically been settled already.
But there are still some
small regrets, I suppose.
Actually, I was quite interested
in Weng Fanxi.
What happened was,
when we were teammates before,
some qualities she displayed
made me realize she's truly outstanding,
a very independent and brave girl.
But due to timing issues
and missed opportunities,
I never got the chance
to properly sit down with her
and have a good conversation.
Let's take a walk together.
I noticed you're getting along well
with Lu Wanfei today.
I wanted to ask
what your impression of her is.
Actually, my initial
Things like feelings
are all about wanting to communicate more with you
and get to know you better
But later, when Zheng Dedong and I
got closer
I often noticed that he would
tend to
pay attention to your every move
I know—I could see his
his thoughts
I didn’t really want to be caught in the middle
so I might’ve made some biased choices
Right, so this is what I can understand.
I think these things don't really matter.
Because we're all just...
more familiar with each other.
Understanding each other's feelings.
Right?
Because I think this is a very normal thing.
Mainly I want to see...
what you truly think in your heart.
Only then can it influence my own...
judgment.
Right.
What I feel regretful about is...
I never had a proper, in-depth conversation with you.
My thoughts are similar.
Really?
I just... I really like Fujie.
I really like Fujie.
I have a strong impression.
That tanned, muscular hunk.
Fujie.
He's very distinctive.
That... what's-his-name... Jie.
It's just you and me now.
Okay.
I believe in you.
I made you some astragalus tea.
Thank you.
It helps replenish energy.
It's nothing.
No problem.
I did my best.
It's hard to muster strength.
From the first day, second day, third day...
I chose you every time.
I'm just very curious about you two.
But none of us have...
had deep conversations or anything.
So I really want to choose both of you.
One time each.
Right.
Now between Weng Fanxi and Lu Wanfei...
who do you feel most attracted to?
I'm not sure.
So I genuinely don't know how to choose.
I was just saying there are three days left
There are still some people I'd like to get to know
I hope to have the chance to understand them better
I hope that in the remaining time
I'll have the opportunity to accomplish this
No matter what the outcome may be
At least I won't have any regrets
Would you like to sit down?
Then I'll sit here with you for a while.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
That's good.
I just hope...
your emotions remain stable.
That you're okay.
That's all that matters.
I can only sense your emotions.
Nothing else.
So what emotions do you sense from me?
You've been "invisible" all day today.
"Invisible" all day.
Yes.
We're getting closer to going back.
So facing the return...
Right, I was just thinking about that too.
Yes.
But actually three days is quite long.
If you think about the first three days...
Each day felt like a year.
So these next three days...
You might experience many emotions...
and changes in thoughts.
In any case, it'll surely be...
a wonderful journey.
I think we've made many things...
too complicated.
So now I think...
I just want to keep it simple.
I'll...
do what I feel...
in my heart.
Without considering anything else.
I'm going to be completely myself now.
Really...
No matter what, I'll follow my heart.
Whatever happens, happens.
Let myself go.
After all, it's just three days left.
I really admire your courage
To be able to stay here
And firmly love who you choose to love
I don't dare
You don't dare?
I'm afraid
What I fear is
That if here
I casually agree to certain decisions
And fail to adapt to reality
Then everything falls apart suddenly
I'm terrified of that
So I don't dare make decisions lightly
You should do the same
Just be yourself
So I think we should both do well
And leave no regrets
Words that should be said
Things you want to tell someone
I think should all be spoken
I know everyone might leave here later
And still have chances to say them
But that would be
In a completely different situation
So we should still follow
These feelings in our hearts
And at this time
Go say what needs to be said
This is what I think
I told Lu Wanfei
There are only three days left
I hope everyone can
truly follow their hearts
I also hope she can properly
understand her own feelings
without any reservations because of me
I will also
in the coming days
get to know everyone I'm interested in
I think no matter what
you should take the initiative
to talk to the person you want to know most
And say those things
you've been afraid to say for various reasons
just speak them out directly
If you don't say them now
you might never get another chance
Wisdom Puzzle
You lack wisdom right now
Lovesick fool
A lovesick fool has little wisdom—you right now
Xiao Enya has big curls today
So intellectual
So sleepy
Want to sleep
Let's go
A little surprise for the girl
Only three days left on Tianping Island
Hope you cherish these last moments together
Be honest with yourself
Make the truest choice
Just three more days!
I'd also like to cook a meal for everyone
Me too
I wish
That Tianping Island could give me and Zheng Dedong a
chance to cook a delicious feast for everyone
I can cook too
Opportunity
Then the three of us can
I can do it too
Bro, I can be in charge of chopping firewood
Please, I beg you
I think all us guys should
cook a meal for the girls
I just want
to begin and end with
what we did on the first day
Combine everyone's cooking together
With everyone cooking
We might go our separate ways
I think it would complete the circle perfectly
I'm really happy that I can have
Weng Fanxi taste the food I made
The guys' cooking session
So much meat
Let's get started right away
Let's do this
I can chop vegetables
Can chop veggies
Okay
Head chef, assign me a task
I'll assist you guys
Let's wash this meat first
Alright
Let's wash all this meat first
Let me introduce to everyone
This is our head chef team
Got it
I'm going to start braising now
Gu Zhenxiang, you're cooking fish today.
Yes, I'm cooking fish today.
Put that in, wait a moment.
Right.
This is exactly the flavor.
The soup is delicious.
This is our waiter team.
Service team.
Correct.
Are there more vegetables to wash?
I can clean this basin to wash vegetables.
I've directly become an assistant.
Where?
Water's coming.
Nice.
Blanch it briefly.
I cut beef at home every day.
Finger heart
I can stir-fry sweet potato leaves first
Sweet potato leaves cook very quickly
Weng Fanqian said she wants stir-fried greens
Greens are what I'm worst at cooking
I think greens
I don't know how to make them tasty
I really want to eat your cooking
If there's a chance
I'll cook for you again when I get the chance
Let me try making it
So this is the taste of love
Something like that
Need to put in extra effort today
I'll give it my best shot
Although our game
wasn't played very well
this afternoon you came in first
How does it taste?
Here, Zheng Dedong
There we go
Weng Fanxi would want to eat this dish too
Weng Fanxi loves potatoes
How's this one? The flavor
To be honest
Is it okay?
Goes well with rice
What are those girls doing?
Sleeping
Probably
Or chatting
They're chatting, right?
Do you think guys have certain
most annoying traits?
Yes - being a "central air conditioner"
Central air conditioner type
I think
You can be caring toward everyone
but you shouldn't
make girls feel like
there's something ambiguous
Right
ambiguous or flirtatious words
that make girls mistakenly think
there might be something between you
when actually there isn't
giving everyone false hope
But the rules of the game on our island
seem a bit
Right, survival comes first
So at the beginning
you must prioritize survival
I think everyone should maintain proper boundaries
Keep a sense of boundaries
This balance is quite important
About this boundary thing
I tell you, many guys don't have it
Not even a bit
That's why there are
those extremely close opposite-sex friends
Would you mind if your
for example, your romantic interest
had that kind of close opposite-sex friend?
I wouldn't accept it
I couldn't accept it either
Regular good friends are fine
But if it's that kind of
male confidant
female confidant
Yes, female confidant, male confidant
That kind is completely unacceptable
So they say
Can men and women have pure friendship?
What do you think?
Yes
I don't believe it
I think it exists when you're single
Because for me
when I'm friends with a guy
if he gets in a relationship or I do
we stop contacting each other
It only exists when you're single
I think that's how it is
Just hanging out together
From my personal experience
there's no pure friendship between men and women
Right?
Guys always pretend
He might be somewhat interested in you
That's why he becomes your so-called friend
He doesn't want to lose this connection with you
So he pretends under the name of friendship
to stay by your side
Let me ask everyone
When it comes to emotional value
is it one of your criteria
for choosing a partner?
Absolutely
At my current stage in life, it's definitely
very important
When work gets overwhelming
you need someone with emotional stability
But what if
this stability lasts for a month
two months, three months, four months
a year, two years, three years
They might seem perfectly stable
then suddenly after years
they have an explosive outburst
Could you accept that?
I think our understanding of emotional value
is somewhat
Yes
misguided
Emotional value isn't just
about providing stability
There are many aspects
Bringing you joy is valuable too
That's how I see it
Do you check each other's phones?
Your partner's?
No.
Not at all.
Unless they show me voluntarily.
But if they're being secretive with their phone
and trying to hide something,
then I would definitely check.
Absolutely would check.
I would just ask directly.
I wouldn't check.
I would just ask.
"What were you just doing?"
Actually, women are very perceptive.
They can sense it.
She can feel it.
Can definitely sense it.
Yes.
You're different though.
If you want to investigate,
you can find out anything.
As long as the girls want to, anything is possible.
I want to start eating, I'm ready for dinner.
I'm hungry.
Can we go help them cook?
They went to cook.
Who is it?
The guys.
Welcome to Pure Love Snack Bar.
A little surprise for the girls.
The girls are so hungry they could faint.
So this is the taste of love.
What's the most hurtful thing to say during an argument?
I'm so disappointed in you.
Why are you always like this?
I really don't understand.
How could I ever be with you?
The food suddenly doesn't taste as good.