I
like
you
My feelings for her have always been at their peak
It's just constant liking, nonstop liking
Those in love go right
We should choose the same side, right?
I'm not sure
What's going on?
What's happening?
Go this way
I'm telling you to go this way
Really good
So romantic
Today is completely different
What's the matter?
Are you comparing it to the past couple days?
Come, have a seat
So romantic
The lights will turn on at night
Really?
I finally understand the feeling you described
Here's your salmon tartare, enjoy.
Your salmon tartare, please enjoy.
Thank you.
Today feels truly special.
Here.
Cheers.
Haven't you noticed something different about me today?
What else?
Guys dread being asked these kinds of questions.
Okay.
Wait a moment.
Can you give me a hint?
It just became more refined.
The effort I'm putting in today
is already what I usually put in when attending
some red carpet events.
It's just beautiful.
Let me tell you, I rarely put my hair up.
Okay.
Alright.
I don't often put my hair up.
I only do it for very important occasions.
You're being so thoughtful.
Putting in so much effort today.
Why are you trying so hard?
Because I value today very much.
Is it because the person you value is sitting across from you?
So what was your first impression of me?
My first impression was that you didn't even look at me.
That's it?
After you came in, you were talking with Gu Zhenxiang over there.
Fist bumping over there.
I thought to myself at that time,
"Is this guy okay?"
Hello.
You're so handsome!
You're even more handsome!
Have a seat.
"Is this guy okay?"
No, let me tell you,
I think everyone has different
ways of expressing affection toward someone they like.
Because for me personally,
when it comes to girls I'm interested in,
I wouldn't talk to them at first.
You didn't even greet me.
I did, okay?
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
Not happy about this?
You were embarrassed.
A bit shy, perhaps?
Is my appearance your type?
And my first impression of you was that
your eyes are super big.
So big that I felt pressured.
Seeing through you.
Right.
I just felt like
you were seeing through me.
So whenever you made eye contact and talked to me,
I thought "it's over,"
"I've been figured out, so awkward."
Quickly turned to chat with Gu Zhenxiang instead.
So what do you think
What kind of relationship are you looking for at this stage?
That's a good question, let me think
Take your time
For me personally
I would hope for
That both my partner and I can focus on our own things
And when we truly have free time
We can meet up
Chat, have a meal together
Watch movies or something
That would be nice
Supporting and helping each other
Being each other's family
That's what I'd want
Over these past five years
My views on relationships
Haven't actually changed much
What I'm looking for is
Mutual support between partners
We should help each other grow positively
Not drain each other's energy
This is very important
I should understand you
And you should understand me
I realized this situation
Would be best described by
What words in the sky?
What words?
"We're evenly matched"
Exactly
Why did we say the same thing?
This is hilarious
No wonder
We always win games together
Because we're in sync
Right
From our intensive training on the island
I wasn't even guessing what you'd say
The words just came to me naturally
"We're evenly matched"
Please add in post-production
Here
Actually I prefer the current atmosphere
It was too bright before
So bright it was uncomfortable
I feel much more relaxed now
Before it felt like the whole world was watching me
You can handle being watched by the world
Of course
That's also why when I was tie-dyeing today
I chose stars instead of hearts
So I'll do stars, and you do hearts, okay?
I feel really professional now
The result should have...
Have...
Does it?
This is what we made for each other
A very clear heart
Then will you give me your star?
Yes.
Then do you want my heart?
Won't you give it to me?
I want to give it, but I'm afraid you won't accept it.
Good, as long as you accept it.
Actually, you said something the other day
that really moved me
You said you wanted me to be a confident person
Because I feel that
I really liked how you were on the first day
I think that's the real you
when you're not caught up in love
a very free state of being
I am
I believe true love is when
you can still be yourself
and someone loves you
I never want
someone to, for example
be in a relationship with someone
and change themselves
deliberately for that person
or dim their own light
completely
I don't think that's good
I think you're shining now
Thank you
I deserve this
I think I'm not a bad person either.
Okay.
It's over.
I'm hooked.
You really said a lot of things that touched me deeply.
A feeling that's hard to put into words
Then have you thought about
when you first developed feelings for me?
It's not about first impressions
nor about appearances
Because I believe everyone
at different ages
needs different kinds of relationships
When you're younger,
you need someone to care for you
or keep you company
So when I was in my early twenties,
I had these needs
I wanted companionship
But after twenty-four,
for many years
I didn't actively seek
to pursue romance
I had my own goals to pursue
I wanted to
be myself
I wanted to develop myself
I devoted all my energy to myself
to become a better person
I think
The period from 22-23 to 30 years old
is a phase of rapid leveling up and battling challenges.
But you need to throw yourself into
a completely unfamiliar
and uncomfortable environment.
That way, you can grow faster.
I believe women also need self-development.
I think you're amazing!
It sounds quite tough these past few years.
There were hardships,
but I still consider myself lucky.
Awesome
I really want it now
Just like this, patting your head
But it seems a bit cheesy
Not quite appropriate
Your eyes are watery, I'm speechless
Really? It's not that bad
Just a little
Stop seeing through me
Eat up
I think she's had a very hard life
Overthinking things
And suffering deep wounds
So strong and independent
It can't have been easy
You and Gu Zhenxiang must've watched the sea together too
Quietly gazing at the ocean
It's not that we didn't see enough sea on the island
I want us to do something...
A little different
Sure, come to Shanghai with me
When?
When
will the recording end?
Do you want me to come to Shanghai to see you?
Yes, come.
I'm someone who's particularly hard to pursue.
Hello.
When I first saw her,
I thought she was
quite an aloof girl.
She seemed hard to approach,
which somewhat matched my ideal type.
But actually, between the two of you,
I don't lean toward either side.
Taking initiative requires some courage, okay? Courage.
This might be my only move left.
Only my boldness and courage remain.
I'm just
someone who's easily moved by bravery.
Will love make us whole?
Love will also make us whole.
Do you want me to come to Shanghai to see you?
Yes, come.
If I say I miss you, will you come?
Yes, all the people I care about are here.
I think it still depends on you.
Depends on me, alright.
Where the heart leads.
If I want it and you want it too,
then we can surely make it happen.
Are you looking forward to it?
I am.
Trust me.
Do you believe in this?
Do you think we're destined to be together?
My meeting with her was truly
fated by destiny
We just don't go out of our way to talk to each other
Yet somehow we keep running into one another
I feel like there's mutual effort between us
After spending the whole day together
I felt really happy and at ease
I've also been enjoying the process
I believe love is mutual
While searching for him
you also found happiness
His eyes welled up several times during the meal
This is a kind of special affection
I'm moved because he's moved
Because I believe when facing someone you love
you must maintain emotional sensitivity and tenderness
Otherwise, this love won't last
Wake up
We're here
Still feeling drowsy?
Acting spoiled
What a feast
The beef is even cut into heart shapes
The colors match your outfit perfectly today
That's right
Let's eat something first
I'll take this one
Actually, let's use this one instead
So constrained
Life on the island was better
Right
Find me an island to devour
I feel like a fake person
I can't adjust to modern life anymore
It's just suddenly putting me back in this state
I still haven't quite adjusted to it
I feel a little bit
Do you?
To be honest, I'm actually fine
I really don't feel that way
I think life is life no matter where you are
Who you spend it with is what matters
The way you put it
Is this your way of confessing?
You could say that
I mean it, really
I feel that
Whether we're having this Western meal today
or eating street food
the feeling between us remains the same
So the setting
is something someone like me adapts to easily
I have many questions for you
How old are you?
Guess
You're from '96?
'95
'94? '93?
'92? '91?
No, look
I'm really not sensitive about age
Why are you being shy about it?
You're from '99, right?
Yes
I'm one year older than you
One year older than me?
Right
Aren't you one year younger than me?
Aren't you from the post-00s generation?
I think liking someone has nothing to do with age
Liking someone
Means appreciating their inner qualities and spirit
That's how I see it
I think between us
Our experiences are somewhat different
Didn't you say
You particularly like "older sister types"
Like older sisters
Absolutely love it
I just like this feeling of being "tamed"
I think I have strong "older sister vibes"
Now I'm almost getting "mom vibes"
I really don't want to be a mom
I think this exact point
Is probably what attracts him
He just likes me being more sisterly
If I were even slightly cuter
He probably wouldn't like me as much
You still haven't told me what you do
Guess
What do you think I do?
"Domineering female CEO"
What nonsense
I just like this feeling of being "tamed"
I'm a brand director
Now also the founder of an online media operation
Plus I'm a blogger myself
Impressive
Applause
Let's have an honest talk today.
Okay.
Just ask whatever questions you have.
I think we submitted on the third or fourth day.
We can see who they voted for the previous day.
Who did you observe that day?
I won't tell you.
Take a guess
I can't guess
Didn't you say it's truth time?
Come on, truth time
You go first
You confess first
I'm asking you - you can't turn the question back on me.
Zheng Dedong
Right.
Okay.
Let me put it this way.
Even if I saw his advantages,
I'd still bet entirely on you.
I just wanted to see,
to satisfy my curiosity.
That's all.
Yes.
If she chose Zheng Dedong,
I'd get jealous.
These emotions get
magnified endlessly in this situation.
I'm extremely territorial.
I won't allow my partner
to be interested in anyone else.
Not allowed.
Like you said,
the beginning is a confirmation process.
But you'd already confirmed by the second day.
But you confirmed it on the second day.
What did I confirm on the second day?
You, on the second day...
You came to me on the second night.
I came to discuss this issue with you.
Because I wasn't clear.
Because you'd already talked to Zheng Dedong by then.
I didn't come until the third day.
You were on the second day.
Third day.
Second day.
It was only the second day we'd met
You appeared among my teammates
It was you on the second day
when you started fighting alongside me
I'd only just
become somewhat familiar with you, understand?
Go Guo Xu and Xiao Enya!
You're happy to come on a date
The sun can't be completely blocked for you
I'm 30% attracted to you
Yes, the third day
But on the fourth day you chose to watch Zheng Dedong
instead of watching me
I want to see Zheng Dedong's, hurry up
Keep it up, Guo Xu
I just told you
You satisfied your curiosity
He already gave you a clear answer that day
Yet you still chose to watch him
instead of watching me
But why don't you watch
I chose you entirely
and not Zheng Dedong?
This logic doesn't make sense to me
Once you've chosen someone
why care about others?
You've committed fully to one person
Why be curious about others?
But at that time it was me
just taking a look
Now I'm putting the choice before you
The new guest is still here
You can make your own choice
I won't choose
I think you can
I won't
Difficult
You took my
You made me choose
You're done for
Then I got jealous
Of course I wasn't happy
To put it bluntly, I was unhappy because I was jealous
It's that simple
I'm telling you very sincerely now
Don't just because
I glanced at him
You think what
If the other person feels it's unfair
Then you can compete completely fairly
In love, in relationships
It's naturally
Hard to measure fairness
So on this point
I've already given my explanation
Do you understand what I mean?
I think we shouldn't keep circling this issue
There's no need
No need
Right, really no need
Because at this point
You just need to know I chose you
Okay
The confirmation process can be anxious
You want
The other person to firmly choose you
But this is the process
Once you're firm
You can't make another choice
This is what's right
Right
So this issue isn't important anyway
Okay
Don't keep bringing up the past
If you keep bringing it up
This dinner table will be flipped tonight
Our conversation will be over
This topic is really too funny
I told him very honestly
I chose to look at Zheng Dedong's
Felt he couldn't fully control his emotions
Got a bit too worked up
Tactical water drinking
I'm a very straightforward person
She might be startled by my pace
For a girl
This might make her feel very uncomfortable
I admit I have my faults
I shouldn't have gotten angry or been so forceful
I'll definitely work on changing
But you should thank Zheng Dedong
Right
Actually without Zheng Dedong
there wouldn't be us
Yes, I know
I have a very practical question
It's more of a
survival competition type environment
Right
So part of you
came to me just to survive?
No
So it was just after making a meal
and when your hand got injured
my care and favor towards you
made you think "this person is good"
You just got hooked because of that
Because I asked you directly that night
If this happened to someone else, would you
You said you wouldn't
Because of your actions that day
I genuinely developed a liking
It was extremely impressive
I told you it could make me fall for you
You asked if I was interested in
any of the guests
or particularly liked anyone
I couldn't say - no one
Because no one had that special something
No defining moment
That made me feel strongly about them
Everything happens naturally
Just a little interlude arranged by fate
Destined to happen
You were so worried
You insisted I get bandaged
Kept urging me
And even though actually
You weren't skilled at it
You still helped me cook
That's when I fell for you
It was that simple
So that's why you like me?
Yes
Guo Xu burned his hand
Let him wrap one for you
I'll stir-fry
You direct, I'll cook
Hand me some greens to cook, hurry
Today you just sit here
And eat right there
Don't move
Because feelings are hard to explain
Liking someone is also difficult to express
It can only be shown through small actions
That suddenly make them bump into my heart
Yes, exactly like this
You don't seem to have any questions about me
I never like asking questions
Delivery, who were you looking at that day?
I want to listen
So you're not curious about me?
Not a single question
I am curious
But I hope
To discover through living together
Rather than asking everything now
If you just tell me who you are
What you like
What you dislike
That would be boring to me
Shouldn't we communicate clearly at the beginning
To have a future together?
For me personally
When I'm into someone, I like who they are
Whatever changes may come
Whatever aspects I might not like later
I'm willing to accept that consequence
I'll make compromises
Because when I decide, I'm committed
I'll make nineteen, you just make one.
I think this requires some strength.
You focus on being beautiful.
I'll take care of all these things.
I think Xiao Enya is very intelligent and graceful,
and also very, very
a girl with a surprising contrast.
I really, really like
I
like
you.
Do you know what I like most about you?
I think you're a very genuine person.
In this rather superficial society,
many people actually put on
this kind of external facade.
Right.
To be honest, truly.
When I came to this show,
my original intention was
if I could find love, great,
if not, I'd just be funny.
So both of us
are quite genuine people.
Regardless of how this game
has many setups,
and people might have many motives,
but we're both quite sincere.
Even if we don't end up together, just being friends
would make me happy.
Even if you end up not liking me,
that's okay.
I won't...
mind.
But my point is, as long as we're happy.
Right.
Happy now, bro.
Feeling blessed again, bro.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Are you sure you have no issues with me at all?
Let me think harder...
I think you liking me is enough.
I don't think there need to be any issues.
I just wanted to tease you.
Didn't expect you to take it so seriously.
Pretty funny.
Would you go three days without washing your hair?
It could also be five days.
Okay, then I'll change what I said earlier.
What's the one thing you can't stand about girls?
Change three days to five days.
Really, this childish emotional feeling.
It feels like going back to puppy love in adolescence.
I think there's actually an opportunity now.
For me to find love.
But it's not love yet.
It's just affection and liking.
In just ten short days.
You're asking me to say "I love you."
"I love you so much."
That would be irresponsible to others.
But getting this chance.
Has already been hard enough to come by.
So I'll cherish it properly.
Super happy, super joyful.
I'll keep striving for love.
Let's toast and wrap it up.
Did you enjoy today's date?
The food was okay.
But the person... I might need to think about it more.
Then you'd better hurry up.
What do you usually like to do?
What do I like to do?
I seem to have quite a few things I enjoy doing.
I can't stay idle.
That's good.
Actually, last night I really felt vulnerable.
I was really lying in bed thinking...
Why did I come back?
I was genuinely thinking about this.
Last night...
Yesterday I noticed you kept sighing.
Yes, actually at yesterday's gathering...
Everyone was so happy.
I was only happy for a few moments.
The rest of the time I felt detached.
You know what?
I think... what should I do?
How do I fit in? How should I blend with everyone?
That's why I feel coming here might not work.
Because my friends around me...
You can do it. You've got this.
Can I really?
Thank you.
You can do it.
I really rely on your encouragement.
So, would you think for example...
If I asked you to team up,
Or showed you preferential treatment...
Would you think that's okay?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm very happy today.
Thank you.
I feel so relieved.
This is how I feel now.
Today I feel like a weight has been lifted.
The little pig I raised as a child could swim.
Every day,
it would swim.
I would take it for walks.
While others walked their dogs, we walked our pig.
We strolled with our pig.
Then we’d go to the seaside,
toss it into the water and let it swim back up.
It would get so annoyed,
like this—
shaking its tail as it climbed out.
As soon as it caught its breath, I’d throw it back in.
Three or four times a day.
So mean.
Its squeals were adorable—
it sounded like this:
"I am a pig!"
It only made that noise when eating.
Normally, it was...
Every bite makes a sound when eating.
It goes like this.
When it eats, it really does this.
I've had moments in relationships
where I struggled deeply
For instance,
when torn between new beginnings and past attachments,
I went nearly six years without
a steady romantic relationship.
There were only casual acquaintances,
kept in sporadic contact,
until they eventually married others.
Not dating for six years
Don't you feel lonely?
No.
Actually, most of the time,
I don’t think much about relationships.
I have family and friends
filling my time.
That’s why
you wanted to join this show?
That’s one reason.
I feel I need new social connections.
I want to make some changes.
Even if coming here
just means meeting new people.
Read after me
Too long
Our meeting is also fate
Go back and send me your address.
I'll give you a wooden guitar from my home.
Really.
Because I want you to keep going.
I think you have talent
Really?
We make such an amazing pair of friends.
I feel like coming to this show was totally worth it.
Really.
Yeah, okay.
Because I have no expectations for love anymore.
But I think...
Okay, I get it. No need to say more. Let's practice.
Why do I suddenly feel a bit moved?
You go ahead and practice.
Actually, I'm really...
sometimes a very emotionally sensitive person.
I know.
You understand, right?
You probably understand me quite well.
I know.
She can play the guitar.
She even taught me how to play.
I know this island's main theme is romance,
but I feel like I've gained a lot of friendship here.
It's not just about romance.
Let's hold hands
Three
Let's hold hands after we get over there
Two
Let's hold hands right here
Why?
Hold hands there
It's the same
I don't want to
I feel like my soul has been drained
If you keep resisting, I'll "call the police"
Go ahead and "call the police"
I'll do it right now
You're really "going crazy"
I'm jealous
Let me tell you
Someone like me
That's just how it is
What do you have to be jealous about?
I feel
It feels like you don't value this ring
You're not single
Change the ring
This one doesn't look good
It looks fine
This is superstition
What happened to us this morning
The rings we wore yesterday
I told her very clearly yesterday
that we'd wear rings today
and go back together
to show off to everyone
And then?
Then she didn't wear it
Actually, I want to explain to everyone
why the ring wasn't worn
It's because my other jewelry didn't match well
so I left it there
So I casually said
I was afraid of losing it
Then he misunderstood me
How could I possibly lose
the rings we made for each other?
If it got lost
wouldn't that mean I didn't value it enough?
Right?
You all know I'm very forgetful
Look, things on my hands
sometimes just get lost easily
It's really normal
But later
Anyway, it doesn't matter
I ended up wearing it later
Right
Then why get angry?
Do you think I should be angry?
Right
Camera, don't you think I should be angry?
Okay, then I won't be angry
"Help"
So friends
don't you also think
this is hard to judge
Let me tell you
I actually value the courting process quite a bit
I didn't really believe in it before
Because I thought love at first sight
would mean staying together forever
But getting together quickly through love at first sight
feels just like a flash marriage
If the flash marriage is right, it might last a lifetime
But if it's wrong, then it's just...
The same goes for relationships
If you don't like fast-food style relationships
This is something you need to consider, right?
That's true
Right
So
Yes
I hope we can
control the pace
This is also a reason
I didn't know before
how to express this
But it's not rejection
I just think this is a
necessary process
I understand
We've reached an agreement
We're on the same page
Come on
Because I think
I'm quite impatient and straightforward
But she might be a slow-to-warm-up person
So I might have been bothering her
Maybe I'm too eager
I should probably slow down my pace
So she doesn't feel pressured
She probably needs her own space too
Let's go home
Going home
You're being proactive today
No
I was like this yesterday too
Really?
I'll be proactive when I feel like it
Depends on my mood
You get in first
Wait, this is how a princess gets in
Why do you call me Jiang Zi?
Because to me, you're different from others.
So you can't call me Jiang Zi.
Then what should I call you?
It shouldn't be too mushy, right?
Right, that's not allowed.
I can't bring myself to say it.
How about you call me President Jiang?
Why should I?
On what grounds?
You should call me President Nan, okay?
What nicknames do people in Shanghai use?
Nannan.
Then you call me Nannan.
You're pushing your luck.
What do you mean pushing my luck?
This is also too mushy.
Very mushy.
Then how about a homophone for Nannan?
Nan Nan.
Then you call me Nan Nan.
Jiang Jiang, Jiang Nan.
Our love song is playing.
"Jiang Nan."
Circles round and round.
Let me go
Okay, I'll think of one seriously
Isn't Jiangjiang nice?
Jiangjiang Jiangjiang
No
Everyone calls me Jiangjiang or Xiaojiang
You're different from others
Jiangzi sounds nice
Not Jiangzi
You call others Xiangzi
Why call me Jiangzi?
Isn't that the same?
That's exactly why it won't do
Make it different, okay?
She always says she likes calling people by their full names
But I told her no
I just don't want to be like others
I just won't have it
Just come up with one for me
I personally think
Jiang Xiaobao sounds quite cute
It gives a
feeling of being cherished
Then she told me
Don't be so mushy
Do you think
there'll be earth-shaking changes when we return to the island?
For example, two
completely unrelated partners
might suddenly become like Fu Jie and He Jinyi
Maybe
I'd be scared "to death"
Actually, you know when I last returned to the island
my feelings were complicated
Because I didn't know
what had happened to you all that day
Then are you afraid I might be taken away by someone else?
No
Why?
So confident?
It just won't happen
You have confidence in yourself
I have confidence in you
Smooth talker, huh?
The art of speaking
So everyone knows why
I think she's super charming
Casual words can move people's hearts
Shut up, I beg you
Good morning
Back at the dining table
Let's sit on these two sides
Leave two seats open for them
So much food today, such a feast
This dish is delicious
This water spinach
He Jinyi, water spinach
Thank you
Would you like me to serve you some vegetables?
Guo Xu still isn’t back
He’s gone wild having fun
They’re back
We’ve been spotted
Why are so many eyes watching?
Jiang Shangru looks even darker in these pants
Main theme
Jiang Shangru is dark
A perfect match
Good
Hello, it's so hot today
Hello
Eating
Have a seat
Why is everyone wearing red today?
All reds and pinks
Jiang Shangru, you're also dressed very...
Did she help you coordinate it?
Just casual
Casual
Casual style
Really, Jiang Shangru?
Isn't Guo Xu coming in yet?
I already miss him
You'll suffer when you come back
Back to familiar ground
Hand
Please
No, begging won't help
You're the one who broke it
When we got out of the car,
I accidentally broke the plaster cast
that we made together.
Xiao Enya
was quite angry
because we had put
so much effort into making it.
But due to my carelessness,
my negligence destroyed it.
I feel extremely ashamed.
Perhaps in the future
we'll make ten or twenty more,
but I ruined the first one.
I still feel very sad about it.
You won't learn without punishment.
No!
Don't punish me,
I beg you.
I'll carry your bag,
No, I want to coordinate.
You hold that hand,
No, I want to hold it myself.
Not allowed.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
We agreed.
Do you admit your mistake?
I admit my mistake.
I'm super sorry, please forgive me.
Look, brothers
This is the taste of happiness
Although I made a small mistake
she forgave me
She's very generous
Thank you for your generosity
It's no use
Hello
Here they come
Coming back hand in hand
Right
Done
Welcome back
Hello
Missed you so much
Guo Xu
I just made a big mistake
I need to admit my mistake
Yesterday we just
Made a hand-drawn painting together
And just now
It broke
Got damaged
Shattered
She was very angry
I'm very sorry
But she forgave me
That's what happened
Yeah
Let's eat
I thought it was something serious
We'll align the details with Guo Xu later
How's it going? Getting used to it?
Amazing, Tao Zhi
Really
One of the best men in the world
Truly
Yes
He's really that kind of great guy
Very brave and masculine
And very gentlemanly
Thank you, Chen Mengjia
I know, no romantic feelings, okay?
Chen Mengjia now has PTSD
Finished eating.
Let's go get some coffee.
Zheng Dedong, what should we do?
Come here.
It's nothing, no big deal.
Even though you broke it...
You're still the best.
Okay?
I heard you've been fighting and making up...
making up and fighting again...
several times already.
Are you happy about it?
Actually kind of enjoying it.
I think they're just the bickering type.
She's still angry.
Just accidentally broke it, that's all.
Just try to cheer her up.
Every journey has its regrets, okay?
At worst, we can revisit this place.
Promise to come back next time.
His feelings for Xiao Enya are genuine.
It's fine.
No problem.
Stop it, really it's fine.
What's wrong with you?
He had a fight with Xiao Enya.
About what?
Because he broke this thing.
Feeling a bit guilty.
When I can't see her...
When she's angry...
I feel completely lost.
I get really anxious.
When she's happy, I'm happy.
When she's unhappy, I'm even more unhappy.
Right now she's still angry.
Don't (worry too much), it's fine.
Just give her some time to cool down.
It's okay.
Guo Xu is the best.
Shouldn't I go look for her?
Don't rush.
Or I can go with you to find her.
You come with me.
I'll go with him to find Xiao Enya.
Let's go.
It's fine.
You go ahead first.
Let me go talk to you about it
Talk to you about it
I don't think it's because of you
When that thing broke earlier
And then got angry
It just amplified your emotions
Right, I think she probably
Had other things piling up
Right?
Yes
So you got a bit anxious
I was really anxious, you know
I was "dying" from anxiety earlier
They asked if I was going to look for her
Whether to go find her
Okay, really unhappy
Damn
When I came, you said "slow down, don't rush"
After I returned and you left
I kept asking them
Then I said, Zheng Dedong, come with me
I was afraid to go alone
She didn't want to talk to me, really
Yes, I originally
Wanted to talk to him
And chat somewhere
Because I was afraid he'd misunderstand me
I want you to be happy
Because if you're unhappy, I'll be unhappy
I'll get very anxious
You first
Really
Stop talking
When you're unhappy, I get really anxious
I understand
Understood
And the reason I...
felt a bit disconnected after coming back inside
At first I didn't quite understand
what Tao Zhi was trying to tell me
But later I...
When you're out for a day
Right
coming back feels kind of...
I'm adjusting
It's okay, "buddy"
Xiao Enya
There
Feeling better now, Enya?
Much better
It's nothing
I just needed to sort it out myself
It's fine, I'll stay with you
I'll be with you whether you're happy or not
No need to be so dramatic
I can handle it myself
No
Did you break everything?
Not everything
Just the back part
We can fix it with plaster
I'll piece it together bit by bit
So adorable
Then from now on
I'll be determined to be myself
Okay, sure
Then I'll firmly choose you
Don't you
Is that okay?
These words
Is that alright?
This talk
Wait, you
How should I put it
Don't speak too hastily
Just enjoy yourself first
Okay
Right?
But honestly, yesterday was so much fun
Really happy
Because there was no pressure at all yesterday
We were just purely playing games and enjoying the moment
Right?
Yes
So happy
So I think today
We should maintain yesterday's mood
No
Look, here's the thing
See, everyone's happy here
Happy
We've grown, right?
Win or lose, it doesn't matter
Okay
Right?
Yes
Alright
High five
Buddy, show us your talent
With music, everything instantly feels different.
The whole place
is healed.
Do you have anything in mind you'd like to say?
To someone you like, or something else?
I hope everyone can write one sentence.
Just one sentence.
Then send it to me.
I'll organize them.
This way, everyone's contribution is included.
And I think it'll be really meaningful.
I'll ask everyone for one sentence.
Then include it.
I'll write:
Please forgive me.
To whom?
Too long
Strong old-person smell
You're all so artistic
I don't even know what to say
I'll give it to you this afternoon.
Okay.
Alright.
All islanders, please proceed to the survival arena.
Compete for the island dating rights.
Good luck.
Okay.
Go for it.
Why so serious today?
Why are we here?
Who knows?
Before the game begins,
all islanders must jointly select
the fastest male runner on the island
and one female islander.
Fastest runner.
Let's pick Lu Wanfei for the girls.
Her one step equals three of mine.
I think she's really fast.
Lu Wanfei, you're up then.
I'm not great at running.
I'll do it.
Let me try.
Then you guys go ahead.
Alright.
Sure.
You go, raise your hand.
Like this, buddy?
Our Lu Wanfei is finally stepping up.
Now announcing the "Your Name" game rules.
The selected male and female islanders will be catchers.
Others will be free runners.
The two catchers will take turns entering the zone
to make captures.
Only one catcher can be active at a time.
Catchers tag free runners by touching them.
This counts as a capture.
When a free runner shouts
any opposite-sex islander's name
and remains still,
they enter petrification state.
Catchers cannot capture petrified runners.
(Invalid capture)
Other opposite-sex free runners can revive petrified players
by touching them,
allowing them to move again.
When time expires,
if two or more free runners remain
with both genders represented,
free runners win.
This round lasts seven minutes.
So ugly, stop curling up.
Look quickly.
I got it.
I have another way to curl up.
Move your feet closer.
Let's switch places.
Although it's useless.
But I feel like he's staring at me.
He might try to catch me first.
What's Xiao Jiang's full name?
Jiang Shangru.
Never mind, remembering two is enough.
All team members, please prepare.
Begin
Tao Zhi
Don't catch me
This is way too difficult.
Hu Wei
What? You scared me to "death" with that calling.
Come here.
Fu Jie
Fu Jie, come quick and save me!
Hurry up!
Quickly!
He Jinyi
No way, he's...
Aren't you supposed to be fast?
You're the fast one!
Jiang Shangru
Daniel
How long is this going to take?
Come here and give me a high-five!
Fast!
Save one!
Drive them all over here
Got it
She'll definitely try to catch me, I'm telling you
I'm the slowest runner
Drain them
Time-consuming
Hu Wei
Stop shouting
You're so loud
Really loud
Four minutes remaining in the match
Go
Run!
Go save him
Cool
This is unplayable
I forfeit, I'm done
Come on
High five
No
That's it, can't play like this
They form strategies very easily
I can hardly think of any effective strategy
to counter them
Don't give up
Yes, pull
Run
Got one
No rush
Stay calm
Some of you go that way
Tao Zhi
"died"
Okay, no rush.
Take it easy, easy now.
Daniel.
Spread out, spread out!
Start pulling.
Right.
Pull.
Daniel.
Daniel
Guo Xu
Be careful
Jiang Shangru
Daniel
Okay
Forget about winning or losing
Go!
One minute remaining in the match
Exit
Beautiful
Fu Jie
Fu Jie off-stage, can we not cheer anymore?
Go Lu Wanfei!
Very good
About Lu Wanfei's performance today
it left quite an impression
She didn't just stand there resting
and give up directly
She kept trying all along
So I think she did quite well
Time's up, match over
Okay
Go for it
Great, just do your best
Well done
The Freemen team wins
Please vote internally for one islander to win an island date
Tao Zhi
I think Tao Zhi
Let's choose Tao Zhi
Tao Zhi
Go on a date, Tao Zhi
Thank you
Thank you everyone
I'm really happy
And quite touched
Also a little surprised
Very grateful to everyone
We also hope that after he returns
He can truly and completely
Experience life on Tianping Island
So everyone nominated Tao Zhi
And then
No need to stand up
Sorry
Too excited
Let's go
Good luck
Thanks
You should know who to ask out