He got away.
Looks like he hasn't been gone long.
The laptop belongs to Wang Dongdong.
That kid...
Even on the run, he's still watching cartoons.
Doesn't look like he was on the run.
More like something happened.
Or someone called him away.
There's no sign of a struggle.
Probably someone he knew.
And...
The footprints look like they were tampered with.
You can't make out the shape.
What's that round mark?
Did you smell perfume?
Didn't smell it.
No.
You've got a pretty sharp nose.
Hello, Captain Duan.
A new kidnapper just showed up.
The ransom doubled.
A new kidnapper?
And the ransom doubled?
This time it's for real.
Wang Dahai is panicking now.
He's not yelling to drop the case anymore.
Wang Dahai's got a lot of shady stuff going on.
Could it be the thief crying "stop thief"?
Then this father and son are unreal.
No.
The marks here are too weird.
The footprints are only half there.
And there's a round imprint next to them.
That round imprint...
Could it be some kind of cane?
And the perfume I smelled at the scene...
Oh no!
Wang Dahai's employees are making trouble.
He told me to have dinner with the boss.
The boss hadn't even said anything yet.
You put your hand on my leg first!
Wang Dahai, you damn liar!
You said I'd be the next Jay Chou!
All I had to do was come up with...
200,000 for the debut fee.
Then I'd debut and release an album!
What's going on here?
You're just leaving me like this, Dahai?
Wang Dahai!
Stop right there!
Go!
Wang Dahai!
Stop!
Don't run!
Get him!
Get down!
How did the kidnapping news...
...get out?
Going on strike at a time like this...
If nobody's behind it...
I'll eat my hat, I'm telling you.
Your hair tie fell off.
Thanks.
I didn't see Zeng Lili.
Normally...
She's a longtime employee too.
Zeng Lili.
This Zeng Lili...
I always felt she and Wang Dahai were off.
Sister Lili...
She didn't come today?
Let's go.
Lin Shen.
What is it?
Whose room is this?
Zeng Lili's.
Is there a problem?
Perfume.
This is the scent.
It's hers.
Hello, Captain Duan.
You two, get back here, now.
The kidnapper called.
The exchange is tonight.
Captain Duan.
Right now, Zeng Lili...
...is highly suspicious.
You two come back first.
Dad!
Son!
Save me!
Dad's here.
I brought the money.
Where are you?
Come out!
What's the situation now?
The ransom's been swapped for decoy money.
What about the tracker?
It's already been set up.
But as the exchange time got close...
Wang Dahai suddenly became unstable.
He kept repeating...
...that we have to save his son.
Where are you?
Come out!
See that knife on the ground?
You die...
...your son lives.
I don't want to die!
Dad...
Fine.
A life for a life.
All right.
But...
Let my son go first.
Save me!
I don't want to die!
Dad!
Dongdong!
Son!
It's okay.
Dad's here.
Dad's here to save you.
It's okay.
It's okay, son.
Stop!
Dad!
Help me!
No!
Don't you like feet?
Still like them?
As long as you let my son go,
I'll do anything.
Anything you want.
I brought the money.
I can give you anything.
Anything at all.
Even my company.
You can have that too.
Dad!
Please!
I'm begging you!
Let my son go!
Let him go!
Then when I begged you back then,
why didn't you spare me?
I was wrong.
I was wrong!
I deserve to die.
Cut the crap.
I want you dead.
And your son lives.
I want you dead!
Did you hear me?
Fine.
As long as you let my son go,
okay.
This is insane!
Move!
Yes, sir!
Keep your word!
Let my son go!
I can die.
Dad!
Let's go to hell together!
Zeng Lili!
Don't do anything rash!
Guozi!
Save him!
Seal off the exits!
Zeng Lili!
It's over.
Stop running.
Zeng Lili!
Lu Yi!
Come back first!
Don't be impulsive!
Turn back now.
It's not too late for anything.
Who said I was running?
Zeng Lili!
Lin Shen!
Hang on!
Lu Yi!
I can't hold on!
Lin Shen...
You're my best friend.
Listen to me.
Hold on to me tight!
Hold on!
Hold on to me!
Grab on!
I should've known.
You're a cop.
So back then you
acted arrogant on purpose to drive me off.
You were really trying to protect me.
Right?
I just don't want anyone to become
another me.
You shouldn't have saved me just now.
Even if it wasn't you who jumped today,
and it was someone else,
this idiot here
would still save them without hesitation.
You're not special at all.
You know that?
If
this hadn't happened,
we probably could've been
really good friends.
Actually, sometimes,
friendship is like love.
There's no room for a third person.
Let's go.