Help! There's a boy drowning!
What if he decides to show up again?
He'll get nothing because he won't see me.
I've just decided
to do volunteer work in Urdan.
This war has just become personal.
Not now.
I thought you'd lie low
for our future child?
Good thing you're here.
Thanks for saving our son.
The PRG will no longer bother us.
The PRG comes here?
I really hope all this will end soon
so we can start a new life,
and you can be reunited with your sister.
It's a small world, indeed.
Dr. Maxine Dela Cruz.
You'll be seeing each other again.
What's your plan now?
It's just work, nothing personal.
I'm in charge of your safety here.
I'm Captain Lucas Manalo.
I believe this is yours.
This is the Medicube.
There's no hospital in the area
so we created a makeshift hospital
here in Urdan.
And it has just become operational again.
It's been a while
since there were doctors and nurses here.
Urdan is a remote area
and the roads are not passable.
The delivery of supplies here are limited.
We're all here
to give assistance to the community.
Your presence here is a really big help.
The people of Urdan
are grateful to you already.
Welcome and thank you for being here.
Thank you! It's beautiful.
This is beautiful.
Hello, excuse me.
Have some water.
I'm sure you are all thirsty.
Thank you so much.
Have we met before?
You look familiar.
Yes, I think we've met him before.
You're right.
He's the…
You were the snatcher?
Wait, "snatcher"?
Marty Talledo at your service.
Who would have thought?
You're cuter with your new look.
Hey!
Thank you.
Can you jump in place?
Wait. Why?
So we can see if your foot is okay.
I'll just see if you've healed already
and can jump.
-You had a fracture, right?
-Okay.
Look at him go.
-He's doing fine.
-I agree.
He's fully recovered from the fracture.
Is the water still cold?
-Yes.
-Still okay?
Yes, thank you.
You didn't get to talk to Dr. Maxine?
The medical mission starts tomorrow.
There's no need to talk to her yet.
No need?
Are you sure about that?
I'm here to lead this military camp
and to help the people in Urdan.
-Let's go.
-This place is nice.
-Absolutely!
-It's beautiful.
-Yes.
-Even if it's ruined.
-Has it always looked like this?
It's beautiful, right?
Doc, you can have the other cabinet.
We can share in the smaller one.
Yes, Doc. We only have a few things.
No need.
You can use that cabinet because…
I might return to Manila.
What?
Why, Doc?
I've changed my mind.
Doc, I don't mean to pry, but…
Is it because of Captain Lucas?
Is he the one you were seeing before?
Yes.
That's him.
Such bad luck
that we meet again, and here.
Is that the reason
why you're going back to Manila?
Yes.
I don't want to be seeing his face,
and it's not healthy for us
to be here together.
I'll probably die from stress.
But what a pity,
since you're here already.
She's right, Doc. And it must be destiny.
Oh, god.
Don't worry,
I'll request for a replacement.
I'll call the hospital.
I'll just step out to book my flight.
-Doc, it's late already.
-I won't take long.
I'll come back soon.
It's too dark outside!
Maxine.
Where are you going?
It's 8:00 p.m already.
The gate's closed already.
You can't go out anymore.
It's none of your business.
Actually, it is.
And of course, that includes you too.
Don't worry.
I'll be leaving first thing tomorrow.
You won't see me again.
I'm going back to Manila.
Really?
Okay, it's up to you.
Really it is!
But there's only
one flight per week, right?
I've mentioned that to you, remember?
-Is that so?
-Yes.
You can't scare me.
Whatever happens,
I'll be leaving tomorrow, liar.
Here we go again.
It's up to you if you want to leave.
Let's see
if you can catch a flight to Manila.
Hey, wrong way.
The other way.
-Which is it?
-To your left.
Please excuse me…
Is there a flight going to Manila?
I have to fly back.
There's an emergency at home.
Where is the ticketing office?
There's a ticketing office inside,
but there's only one flight per week
to Manila.
We only have limited flights as of now.
I see, thank you.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
Let's return to the Medicube.
We probably already have patients waiting.
Okay, Doc. Let's go.
Let me take your luggage.
So do you believe now
that there's only one flight per week?
Good thing there are no flights
back to Manila, Dr. Maxine.
We can't handle this without you.
I'm really sorry.
You know me.
I'm not an irresponsible person.
It's just not healthy for me to stay here.
You don't have to apologize.
We understand you
and your personal concerns.
What's important is that you're here now.
Excuse me.
Dr. Maxine.
Hello.
What's your name?
I'm Dr. Maxine. How about you?
I'm Biboy.
What is Biboy's problem?
Doctor, I just want
to have my son checked.
I'm Sheila, Biboy's mother.
He has seizures and his body gets stiff.
He even collapses sometimes.
When did this start?
When he was still a young boy.
An herbalist said…
he's being punished by a spirit.
I don't think Biboy
is being punished by a spirit.
His seizures and loss of consciousness
could be caused by epilepsy.
-Epi…
-Epilepsy.
It's epilepsy.
If you can come back tomorrow,
we can check and make sure
it is indeed epilepsy.
But, Doc, we don't have money to pay.
Don't worry about it.
You don't have to pay in Medicube.
You're not only kind, Dr. Maxine,
you're also very pretty.
Beautiful.
-Oh, gosh!
-You are beautiful.
Thank you. I think we'll get along well.
Thank you, Doc.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hold on, okay?
Does it hurt?
How about this?
I missed you, Maxine.
Thank you, Dr. Maxine.
We'll just come back tomorrow.
Of course!
Bye, Doc Max Beautiful.
Doctor, you are heaven sent to us.
But I have a request, if you may.
What is it?
I have a lot of neighbors who are sick.
Maybe…
you can help them, too.
Sure.
Is your place far from here?
It's just two hours away on foot.
You just have to cross five rivers.
Five…
Sure, we can go there now.
Thank you so much, Dr. Maxine.
Just give me a second.
Emma.
I'll go with them to Sitio Santos.
I'll be back soon.
Where is that?
-Want me to come with you?
-No need, I can manage.
I'll be back right away.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
Hello, neighbors.
This is Dr. Maxine.
She's a doctor from the hospital.
Good afternoon.
Mrs. Sheila mentioned to me
that many of you are sick.
I'm here to check on your health.
Everybody fall in line.
Okay. There's a table!
All right, please fall in line.
Oh, my God.
All right.
Just fall in line.
We may start the check-up.
I'll look at you first.
Come here.
What's going on there?
It's a medical mission.
A lot of people here are sick.
Dr. Maxine, thank you so much.
It's a blessing to us
that there's a doctor like you…
who is concerned about us.
You're not only a good doctor,
you are kind, too.
Oh, gosh.
Don't mention it, it's our duty.
Aren't we lost?
Did we pass here earlier?
Oh, we're not. This is a short cut.
It would be dangerous to be here by dark.
Mrs. Sheila?
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Nothing, it's not going through.
Captain Lucas.
Dr. Maxine hasn't returned yet.
Why? Where did she go?
She went with a patient earlier.
I was supposed to go with her
but we were busy.
She said she'd be back soon.
Did you call her yet? What did she say?
We can't contact her.
The call is not going through.
She went out of the camp?
You know that's dangerous, right?
You can get kidnapped
if you go out of the camp.
I hope not.
Oh, my God.
I hope nothing bad happens to Dr. Maxine.
I hope so. You are all my responsibility.
You shouldn't be--
Unbelievable.
Did she mention where she was going?
I heard earlier it's Sitio…
-Where?
-Sitio Santos.
-Yes, it's Sitio Santos.
-Piccolo, come in.
We have to look for Dr. Maxine.
She's missing.
Get her files, including her picture.
Yes, right away.
Maxine…
Maxine, think.
You're not lost, okay?
You just need to find the biggest river…
then go to the end of it.
Until you see people and houses.
Go ahead and try.
Let's ask them.
Good day.
Have you seen her?
She checked on some patients earlier.
I just passed by here. I didn't see her.
Do you recognize her?
Oh, yes, Dr. Maxine.
She left already with Sheila.
Mrs. Sheila…
Thank you.
Mrs. Sheila.
Mrs. Sheila, someone is looking for you.
Captain Lucas!
-Mrs. Sheila!
-Captain Lucas!
I need your help.
I've been looking in the forest
for Doc Maxine.
I can't find her.
You go this way, I'll go that way.
Where are you, Mrs. Sheila?
I'm Dr. Maxine.
Can you help me?
Which way is it to Urdan?
I'm kind of lost.
What did she say?
I don't understand her.
The way going to Urdan.
-Urdan.
-Maxine!
Hey, wait!
What are you doing here?
This place is dangerous.
Next time you go out of the camp,
inform the staff, okay?
What you did was dangerous.
You're putting the camp
and the entire medical mission in danger.
I'm coming back here tomorrow.
A lot of people here are sick.
They need help.
You can't. It's dangerous here.
There are reported sightings
of PRG members here.
And besides,
a landmine exploded here the other day.
And don't trust just anyone.
We don't know who our allies are
and who are the enemies.
Trust?
What do you mean?
I just know the word "trust."
I had that before,
but you made a fool out of me.
She is still not over it.
You see me like that?
I lied about my job,
but it doesn't mean I have bad intentions.
Whether your intentions were good or bad,
it changes nothing.
You still lied to me.
Cheater.
A cheater? Really?
You are quick to judge.
You don't even know
what I'm going through.
Cheater.
You're going too far.
Why? What? Are you pissed?
If what I'm saying isn't true,
why are you so pissed?
Answer me.
I'm not pissed.
Let's go.
They're looking for you at the Medicube.
You go on ahead.
I can handle myself.
And even if you hadn't found me here,
I'd have been able
to find my way back on my own.
I don't need you.
Maxine, don't move.
You stepped on a landmine.
What?
-What am I going to do?
-Relax.
-I'll die, Lucas!
-Don't move.
You're panicking. Relax and don't move.
-Don't move your foot.
-Don't leave me! Just stay!
It's all right. Don't move your foot.
Are you okay now? Don't move too much.
I'll step on it instead, okay?
Even if you don't like him,
I still love him.
Does it have to be that big?
-Count.
-I will count?
No, them. Of course you!
You both seem to be enjoying it.
Maybe because you always bicker
when you see each other.
Whatever. I'm still mad at him.
I already have a ticket
for Manila tomorrow.
Are you really leaving?
That is our target, Sitio Santo Domingo.
That's the primary base
and the training ground
of the youth recruited by the enemies.
Okay, Alpha Team.
No one will relax while in the area.
This is a hot spot
of terrorist activities.