Even though you are mad at him,
you didn't let your emotions
take over you.
You even helped to operate on him.
He risked his life to save me back then.
Your brother held you hostage?
Does Captain Lucas already know this?
It seems danger
always finds its way to her.
Have you asked her
how she got into the PRG camp?
She doesn't want to talk.
Could she be hiding something?
It is impossible for you
to go there on your own.
Do you have a contact inside the PRG?
Sir, we can't force Maxine to speak.
She's still traumatized by what happened.
If she will not talk,
we can't gather intel.
Big Boss, you should be ready.
For sure, the Colonel
will give Maxine a sanction.
I made a lot of violations.
General Defensor decided
to send me back to Manila.
They can't do that.
How about the medical team?
Maxine, I talked to General Defensor.
He reversed his decision.
You don't have to leave.
Because of my selfishness,
your job is getting affected.
Maxine, you know that I will defend you
at all cost.
I will do everything for you.
But you don't have to sacrifice your job
because of me.
And you don't have to defend me
all the time.
You are my girlfriend.
That's the thing. I'm your girlfriend.
I should be lifting you up,
not pulling you down.
Wait a second. Maxine, I don't get it.
I'm leaving Urdan.
It hurts.
Don't move too much,
your wound might open up.
How are you feeling?
My body feels heavy.
That's normal.
Did you watch over me the whole time?
I just want to make sure you will be okay.
I just want to say thank you.
Despite everything I did to you.
You don't have to say thank you.
I'm just doing my job.
Just focus on your recovery.
Captain Lucas needs you.
The Alpha Team is not complete
without you.
I'll be back to check on you.
Lucas won't allow me to leave Urdan.
He really loves you.
He doesn't want to be away from you.
But his job is getting affected
because of me.
If only my brother did not become a rebel,
things wouldn't be this complicated.
I don't know.
My life is such a mess. What now?
Doc, why don't you tell Captain Lucas
about your brother?
They hate each other to the bone.
It will only make matters worse,
believe me.
But, Doc, do you trust Captain Lucas?
I do, of course.
So you should not be afraid to tell him.
Because if Captain Lucas really loves you,
he will understand your situation,
whatever it is.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Don't mind me.
It's just overfatigue.
Doc, don't lie to me.
I saw you at your worse
during the earthquake.
I know it's not just because of work.
Doctor Maxine, you are not fit
to do an operation.
Let others do it.
I'll do it.
You should rest, Doc Maxine.
Are you his attending doctor?
Where is your patient?
Let me see his charts.
You are not in the camp.
Do not make demands.
I'm not here to fight.
We may have unresolved issues,
but that's not what I came here for.
I came here for your patient.
If I knew where he was,
I would have told you earlier
so we don't even have to talk.
I know we are not close.
We have differences in the past, but…
you can vent out on me.
I hate myself.
I was so unfair to Lucas.
What made you say that?
Moira, Lucas is doing everything for me.
He almost gave up his life for me.
But as for me…
I couldn't even tell him the truth.
If there is one thing I've learned
from what happened to me and Diego…
it is that nothing good comes out
from not telling the truth.
What will I do?
How do I…
What if…
What if he gets angry
and can't accept the truth?
What will I do?
He will get hurt, Doc Maxine.
He will get hurt
because you didn't tell the truth.
If you want a lasting relationship…
you should start
with a foundation of trust.
Do not let your relationship get destroyed
and end up like me and Diego.
He just woke up
after being in a coma for several days.
It is safe to talk to him.
He already tested negative for the virus.
Thank you.
I'm begging you.
The PRG will kill my family
once they find out where I am.
Listen to me.
I will help.
But you have to help me, too.
Do you understand?
How?
You will tell me where the PRG camp is.
We searched everywhere.
In San Vicente, Talisay and Sitio Verde.
But we know there is another camp.
Now, you will tell us where this camp is.
I can't tell you.
The PRG will hurt me.
They might kill my family.
Dong, I promise you.
They can't hurt your family
because I will protect you.
We will protect you.
We will not let that happen
to your family.
So, tell me where the camp is.
Don't worry I am on your side.
We are on your side.
We won't put you in danger.
Okay, I'll tell you.
We have another camp
that you don't know about.
My comrades are most likely still there.
Where?
It's by the river.
Nurse Hazel, have you seen Lucas?
No, Doc.
I will tell him the truth
about my brother.
Really, Doc?
I don't want to lie to him
and I don't want to hide anything.
Have you seen Lucas?
Yes. We left him inside.
What is he doing?
The young rebel just woke up.
Are they talking?
What are they talking about?
He left. He was in such a hurry.
-Where is the coffee? Let's go.
-It's here.
Okay.
Doc, maybe it has something to do
with your brother.
He is Bullet, the notorious leader of PRG.
Is he the one who crippled your father?
He almost killed him.
Because of what he did,
our lives turned upside down.
I promised my father…
I would do everything
to capture this person.
We will attack the day after tomorrow.
You have to prepare our comrades.
We need to plan carefully what to do.
Where is Moira?
I've been looking for her.
I need to talk to talk to her.
I heard her talking to her dad.
They are talking
about Doc Moira's reassignment.
What? Reassignment?
Yes.
She is leaving Urdan.
What?
Sir Diego, where are you going?
Why didn't you tell me
that you are leaving?
What are you doing?
Why leave all of a sudden?
When is your departure?
Why do I have to tell you?
How about your patients
and your colleagues here?
They need you.
I have turned over everything to Maxine.
Captain Moira Defensor!
Don't leave.
Let me remind you that I am your superior.
My rank is higher than yours,
Technical Sergeant Diego Ramos.
Yes.
Your rank is higher.
But I think…
we are just equals.
What do you mean?
When it comes to love,
there is no higher or lower rank.
We are all equals.
What is it again, Diego?
You will lead me on
and then break up with me again.
I can't take it anymore.
No, Moira.
You think Lucas can still save you.
As long as I'm alive,
he can't get you from me.
Do you understand?
What is it again, Talledo?
I'm sorry.
It's Big Boss.
He's not responding to our calls.
Col. Garcia is looking for him.
What? Where did he go?
Answer me!
You will pay for everything you've done.
You think you got me?
This is your end.
Don't kill him!
He is my brother.
What do you mean?
Maxine, this is Bullet!
He is also Rodel dela Cruz.
My long-lost brother.
He is my older brother, Rodel.
So please, Lucas. Don't kill him.
Listen to your girlfriend.
-Brother!
-This is your end.
Brother!
-Maxine, step aside.
-Maxine, what are you doing?
Enough!
Brother, stop it! What's wrong with you?
I won't let you hurt Lucas.
You will really choose that soldier
over your brother?
I don't want any of you to get hurt.
Brother, just let us leave. We're leaving.
You can't.
You saw earlier
that he wanted to kill me, right?
But he didn't do it.
Well, that's his fault.
Lucas Manalo owes me big time.
Maxine, he came here defenseless
and with no backup.
-So it's my chance to kill him.
-Brother!
All units, this is Snoopy.
We're looking for Doc Maxine.
They are not in the Medicube.
They are not also in the barracks.
Doc Maxine and Big Boss
are both missing.
Maybe they went out on a date.
They would not leave without permission
if it's just a date.
I have a bad feeling.
It's Doc Maxine.
What?
Let him go or I'll be forced to hurt you.
Go ahead. Go ahead and hurt me!
You already did, remember?
You held your own sister hostage.
Rodel, I trusted you.
Maxine, in the world where I am right now,
the end justifies the means.
You can even ask your boyfriend.
He will do everything
to accomplish his mission.
Have you forgotten?
He killed Janet and my child
to defeat the PRG.
That's not true.
I would never hurt women
especially those who are pregnant.
I know Janet.
I know her because she was our patient
in the Medicube.
The truth is, we were helping Janet.
-Liar!
-That's the truth.
No!
Lucas is not lying.
We took care of Janet and her baby.
We can take care of you here
in the hospital.
But you need to stay
so we can monitor your vitals
and the condition of your child.
You should take care of yourself
for your baby.
I had the entire Medicube checked
before I called you.
But she's really gone.
You should come with us.
Your pregnancy is already complicated
and it's not safe if you give birth here.
Do you want your child to grow up
in this kind of place?
I know you want to save us.
But this is your chance to save yourself,
especially your baby.
Don't blame Lucas.
Don't blame him
for something he didn't do.
Shut up!
You know, Maxine,
you are blinded by your love for that man.
-That's why he deserves to die!
-Brother!
Oh, my God, Maxine. Your brother is alive?
I told you, let's not lose hope.
I want to see Rodel.
I'm sorry,
but the reunion you want will not happen.
I love you, my child.
And I will do anything to make you happy
even if that means I will leave you here.
Tell me why you went to the PRG camp.
I already told you the reason, Colonel.
I don't believe you.
The PRG took you twice already, right?
But why does it seems like
you are still willing to go back there?
Why are they always calling on you?
I didn't know that the Doctor is a VIP.
Find out when she's leaving.
We're on our way out of Barangay Maligaya.
We'll be in the airport in ten minutes.