Today is my rest day.
So, don't expect me
to answer your calls or messages.
-I have plans.
-Where are you going?
-On a date.
-Really now.
-How was the shower?
-Good.
I saw a notice
of temporary water interruption.
Scheduled at 4:00 p.m.
Did you make it on time?
I hate some soldiers.
My brother was a former army soldier.
He was kicked out because of corruption.
Years passed
and he was declared legally dead.
I'm sorry but I have to leave.
Maybe another girl?
It's just right that you followed him.
You've had enough of men like that, right?
Lucas?
Maxine.
What are you doing here?
What is your business here
in Camp Aguinaldo?
Are you following me?
Answer my question first.
Why are you here?
We're working here.
Boys, you can go ahead.
We will stay behind.
Why are they saluting you?
Because he's the assistant of our boss.
So, of course,
we treat him like a boss, too.
Isn't that right, Big Boss?
We have an emergency meeting.
We met up here
so we can all go together, right?
-Yes.
-Didn't our Big Boss tell you that?
He did not.
But he did mention that his boss
supplies equipment to the military.
Do you have a transaction here?
No. Our boss just left.
He has another meeting, right?
-Yes, he has.
-He went ahead already.
We just waited for Big Boss to get here.
Are you telling the truth?
You came here to see your boss
and nothing else?
Yes.
Of course.
Wait. Why do you ask?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Seriously, why are you asking?
Nothing.
Come on.
Just forget it.
Maybe you thought I'm dating someone else.
Of course not. You're assuming things.
I'm not seeing anyone else, okay?
It's just you.
Who's paying for drinks later?
Wait.
Fix your things first before you leave.
Squad, attention!
You did good in your last operation.
-Did anyone of you get hurt?
-None, sir.
That's good.
I want to inform you, Captain Manalo…
You will be assigned
to the town of Urdan in Visayas,
the center of gravity where PRG is hiding.
According to the intel that we gathered,
they are getting more support
on the ground.
We really need to crush them.
They are aggressively recruiting
the young and the poor
not only in the province
but also here in Metro Manila.
I'll give you two weeks…
to prepare and say goodbye
to your families.
-Comrades, are you ready?
-Yes!
It's time for us to help each other.
That's right!
It's time for us to wake up!
Yes!
Father, you want some water?
Yes, my child. Just hurry.
We must get rid of terrorists!
Get rid of them!
PRG!
Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Destroy them!
-PRG!
-Stop them!
Terrorists!
Stop them!
-PRG!
-Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Stop them!
-PRG!
-Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Stop them!
-PRG!
-Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Stop them!
My fellowmen...
enough is enough.
Let's drive them away!
Yes! Let's drive them away!
-PRG!
-Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Stop them!
-PRG!
-Destroy them!
-Terrorists!
-Stop them!
PRG!
Father!
Hey.
Brother!
It's father!
A bomb exploded and he was hit!
Calm down. Where are you?
Don't panic. I'll be there.
At the Bonifacio Shrine.
Okay.
Father!
How is our father?
Don't worry. His condition is stable.
Thank you, doctor.
Hello, aunt.
You have to see Dr. Chavez.
The hospital will send you
to guest on a TV show.
Hey!
Hey! I'm guessing
you won't be able to sleep later.
I'm not in love.
In love? Look at that!
You've had two cups of coffee.
Don't be so defensive.
I thought you're mad
at Mr. Accountant Hunk
because he left you during your last date?
How come you were affectionately
hugging each other?
Affectionate hug? That didn't happen.
You can't deny it.
There are a lot of witnesses.
So, stop denying it.
Tell me, what is up between you two?
I don't know.
There's no formality yet.
But do you love him?
Well…
Take good care of it.
Because love is just like coffee.
It gets cold.
Is Doctor Maxine here?
I think she already went home.
Okay.
-All right. Thank you.
-Sure.
Are you looking for me?
You always assume things.
I'm just checking on my patient.
-Really now?
-That's right.
You're off duty already?
You're so hard working.
That's exactly my type.
A dedicated woman.
A special delivery for you.
My child…
When are you going to
introduce your boyfriend to me?
He's not yet my boyfriend.
Just relax, Mom.
If he professes love to me,
I won't hesitate.
I'll count on that.
It's beautiful. He should give you more.
Just one.
We've only known each other
for a short time,
but I feel she's the one for me.
-Then marry her.
-I just started seeing her.
Before you continue seeing her,
you should fix the mess you made.
I know that.
That's why later, I'll tell her the truth.
Later?
All right.
I'm Doctor Maxine. I'm your surgeon.
How are you?
I'm doing fine, doctor.
Thank you for saving my life.
You're welcome. That is our job.
It's good none of the shrapnel
hit your vital organs.
The length of time for treatment
is just minor.
Doctor, when can our father go home?
He can go home after three days.
-Really?
-Yes.
Thank you, doctor.
My brother will be very happy.
Is your brother at work?
Yes. He is in the camp.
-Camp?
-Yes, in Camp Aguinaldo.
Most of the time, he's in the province
for special missions.
He is the Captain
of the First Special Forces
of the Philippine Army.
He's not an accountant?
No.
He's a soldier, just like me.
But I'm retired now.
Why did you do that?
Well, because I'm an accountant.
I can't get into trouble with the police.
If that happens,
my job will be put on the line.
Why did your wound open up? What happened?
My boss got into a fight.
I helped him. I had to defend him.
Is that part of an accountant's job?
Well, no.
But I'm his right hand man, you know?
You are not a soldier, right?
You are an accountant.
My boss is connected with the military.
He asked them to pick me up here.
So, I can get to Camp Aguinaldo faster.
Lucas?
What is your business here
in Camp Aguinaldo?
We are here for work.
Is Maxine here? Doctor Maxine.
Oh, over there. She's on TV.
There are a lot of categories
of arrhythmia…
-Excuse me.
-Okay, thank you.
If that's so,
what are the treatments available
for patients with arrhythmia?
Nowadays, because of advancement
in technology,
there are a lot of methods
being discovered to treat arrhythmia.
The good thing is,
it has lesser side effects.
Is that so?
Doctor, you don't seem nervous even
if it's your first time to appear on TV.
-Oh, my.
-You explain very well.
Actually, I am nervous.
It's just not obvious.
Is it the same feeling
when you see your crush?
Gosh.
Yes, something like that.
Actually, the feeling
of having arrhythmia...
Like you're going through something,
but people don't notice.
Doctor, it seems like
that's based on experience.
Why did you lie to me, Lucas?
I wanted us to become closer…
because…
I know…
you hate soldiers like me.
Because of what you did…
you gave me more reasons
to get mad at you…
and people like you.
I admit what I did was really wrong.
But please don't hate all of us.
You know soldiers like us are not perfect.
We're also humans who make mistakes.
But I assure you…
there are a lot of good people
in the force.
I understand.
But you know there are still some...
Especially those who hurt my brother.
My family will forever
be burdened by the pain.
You even added to that pain, Lucas.
I thought you were different
from other men I've met before.
But you're just like them.
I don't want to see you getting hurt.
I don't know if you can ever forgive me.
It's easy to forgive.
But the pain that you gave me…
I think…
whatever we have right now…
the special feelings
we have for each other…
let's just end all of it.
This is going nowhere.
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
If that's what you want,
then there's nothing I can do about it.
Okay.
Always take care of yourself.
Thank you for coming.
Things are tense here.
What if we die in the encounter?
Let's just surrender, please?
I'll die first before that happens!
We'll finally see each other
Technical Sergeant Diego Ramos.
I've just decided to volunteer in Urdan.
I don't want to see that Lucas anymore.
So you think volunteering is a sign?
Maybe it's about time for me
to listen to the universe.
What if this is the best decision
I'll ever make in my life?