Doc, why don't we tell Captain Lucas?
-We need to stop your brother.
-You saw what he did earlier.
I don't want him to hurt himself.
We can't tell Lucas about this.
What won't you tell me?
That Captain Moira is missing.
I had a decision to make and I chose you.
But I didn't want to hurt anybody.
I've hurt you even more.
Are you sure the supplier
we will meet is good?
It's okay. Just let them go.
The important thing is I have PRG back
and no one can take it away from me.
I will finish what I started.
Tonight…
We will crush them.
Captain Manalo and the Alpha Team
just returned
from an operation against the PRG.
Technical Sergeant Ramos
has gunshot wound on his chest.
He needs an operation right now.
My brother is wounded.
He just called me. I need to see him.
No, Doc, you can't leave.
I will not allow you.
Hazel, I have no choice, okay?
I need to treat him.
What if Captain Lucas finds out
about this?
I'm sure it will cause trouble.
I'm sorry if I got mad at you.
I know you never wanted
to hurt Diego's mom.
I'm the one
who should apologize to you, my child.
I hope you can forgive me.
Good thing your wounds
were treated right away.
You could have lost a lot of blood.
I thought you're not coming.
You know I can't do that.
I told you I won't abandon you.
Are you sure
the soldiers didn't follow you?
-Maybe you are wired.
-Of course not.
I'm not like you, Rodel.
I can't put other people in danger.
I know you don't want me
to take revenge on those soldiers.
But as long as I live, I'll make them pay
for what they did to Janet and my child.
Brother, until when will you be like that?
I know you're angry. I understand you.
I know it hurts to lose a love one.
But can any of your actions bring back
the lives of your wife and child?
No.
But it will lessen my anger.
Until when will your anger last?
Maxine, you won't understand.
PRG still has a lot of plans.
We still have a lot of things to do.
What?
You will understand if you join us.
Brother, you know I can't do that.
Let's talk about it later.
I've been calling Doc Maxine,
but I can't seem to contact her.
I can't find her.
Have you seen her?
Why don't we tell Captain Lucas?
We need to stop your brother.
You saw what he did earlier.
I don't want him to hurt himself.
Lucas can't find out about this.
What if innocent people get involved?
Hazel, please give me time.
I will fix it, promise.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at lying.
I was not raised by my parents to lie.
Okay, what's the problem?
Captain Lucas, there's something
I need to tell you.
What is it?
Doc Maxine left.
She left?
Where did she go?
She went to…
Where?
Where did Maxine go?
She went to the PRG camp.
What?
Okay, you take care.
I'll go ahead.
Where are you going, Doc?
I will go back to the military camp.
You can't leave.
Don't worry.
You don't have to accompany me.
I want to head back before it gets dark.
I'm sorry, Doc.
It's your brother's order.
What?
Just stay here, Maxine.
What is she doing there?
I'm sorry.
-I promised Doc Maxine that I won't…
-Why did she go there?
Did you just find out?
You know that you are not allowed
to get out of here.
That's the protocol. It's dangerous.
No one should get out of the camp
without a military escort.
-Unbelievable.
-She insisted.
Doc Beauty, come in.
What is the meaning of this?
I'm leaving. People are waiting for me.
They might be worried about me.
Don't let her go.
Are you serious, Rodel?
You can't hold me hostage.
I'm your sister.
That's the thing!
I'm your older brother,
but you listen more to those soldiers.
So whether you like it or not,
you're now a member of PRG.
You can longer go back to your camp.
Brother, I did what you want.
I did my job. So, just let me go.
What do you want from me?
You can be a valuable asset to the group.
We need a doctor in our camp.
That's not possible.
I can't do what you want, Rodel.
I'm leaving.
Don't let her go.
Tie her up so she won't escape.
Have you gone mad, Rodel?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm your sister! You can't do this to me.
I'm sorry, my sister.
Do it.
Rodel, please!
You can't do this to me, Rodel!
Brother!
Once you see my face,
it means you can't get out of here alive.
They are doctors. They are not enemies.
-Let's go.
-Let them go.
I need a human shield. Give her to me.
You fell into my trap, Captain Manalo.
You can't leave.
It's your brother's order.
I'm sorry I got you involved in this.
Don't worry about that, Big Boss.
We owe Doc Maxine a lot.
You think Lucas can still save you.
As long as I'm alive,
he can't get you from me.
Do you understand?
I can't reach her.
Answer me.
Here. Bullet sent you some food.
I'll leave it here.
Until when will you keep me here?
That will depend on Bullet.
I'll just come back later.
Let me out of here!
Let me go!
Answer me.
Won't you answer him?
Later. We need to focus.
Come here.
Ouch, let me go.
-Ouch, let me go!
-You really won't quit!
Let her go.
Put your guns down
or the doctor gets hurt.
Put your guns down!
I will kill her.
Put your hands up.
Maxine, run!
Big Boss, I got this.
Maxine, don't move.
Why?
There are land mines scattered around.
Maxine, don't move.
You stepped on a land mine.
What will I do?
I don't want to die, Lucas.
-Stay here!
-Okay, don't move your feet.
I will step on it instead.
Hey! You're really crazy!
You are really a cheater.
Hey, this is not the right time
to joke around, Lucas.
You have done this to me before.
I'm not joking.
This is not a joke?
No.
Maxine, just one wrong move
and it will explode.
Believe me, okay?
-What now?
-Don't move.
Don't move.
-How do we get out of here?
-I will take care of it.
Just trust me.
Just hold me.
Just calm down. I got you.
You're safe now.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Are you okay?
You're okay.
Let's go.
Why did you disobey my order?
Do you know the repercussions
of what you did?
Snoopy is not at fault, sir.
I'm the one who gave him the order.
But if we didn't take action,
something bad might have happened
to Maxine.
I won't allow innocent people
to get involved.
You should use your brain.
You disrespected my authority.
I will accept whatever the consequences
of my actions are.
You should.
I will let this pass.
But next time,
I will not go easy on the both of you.
Do we understand each other?
I'm sorry. You got involved because of me.
Big Boss, come on. We are a team.
That's right.
Good thing we were not disciplined.
With all your mischiefs, Big Boss,
it's a wonder you're still here in Urdan.
Don't get smart with me.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes of course, Big Boss.
Our medical team takes good care of us,
especially Doc Maxine.
This place is really dangerous
for Doc Maxine.
I'm worried about her.
But it seems danger
always find its way to her.
That's the thing, Big Boss.
Have you asked her
how she got into the PRG camp?
I asked her earlier,
but she doesn't want to talk.
Could she be hiding something?
It looks like you're in a hurry.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Sitio Santos
to see Miss Sheila.
I will bring some medicine.
Do you want me to come with you?
I'll just ask Nurse Hazel.
I just remembered.
There's something I have to do.
Is that blood? Where did you get it?
Where have you been?
I came from the other Sitio.
Don't tell Lucas, okay?
What is it that you won't tell me?
She went to…
Where?
Where did Maxine go?
She went to the PRG camp.
Doc Maxine, we can't do things
without you.
If not for you,
the medical team will not be complete.
-You are our source of strength.
-That's true.
Whatever happens, you're still our leader.
If only my brother did not become a rebel,
things wouldn't be this complicated.
Why don't you just tell Captain Lucas
about your brother?
How did you gain access to the PRG camp?
-Do you have a contact inside?
-What?
It is impossible for you to go there
on your own without a contact inside.
I will repeat my question.
Do you have a contact inside the PRG?
Why won't you speak?
Is there something holding you back?