Because of you, I disobeyed direct orders.
It was because of you.
I sacrificed my career for you.
-For me?
-Yes, for you.
-For you!
-Did you?
Which law is more just?
The law of your profession?
Blind obedience?
Or the most important law,
which is to save the lives?
Shouting at his superior was embarrassing.
I was reminded of my brother.
So, you're comparing Lucas
to your brother?
Is he that important to you?
Do you still like him?
What I'd like is to stab him.
He really got on my nerves.
I tried to do what you want.
I tried to get mad at you
because it might be the way to forget you.
But it's not effective.
Whatever you do,
I'll fight for what I feel for you.
Seems like we won't really understand
each other.
I told you, we are different.
But why do I still like you
a lot despite that?
Doc Moira, I'll leave my team with you.
I have a scheduled visit to Sitio Santos.
Postpone it for now, Maxine.
You can visit when it's already safe.
I can't. People are expecting me there.
Don't worry, I'll go with her.
I'm not scared.
Why do you look nervous?
Is it because I kissed you last night?
I tried and hesitated a thousand
before I had the guts to do it.
I can't deny how I feel for you.
Just put your fingers on your other palm.
Then you move it in circles,
just like that…
so you can take out the dirt
in your fingernails.
Then, the other hand.
Rinse your hands properly.
Wash them thoroughly.
Are there no suds left?
Later we'll wipe them with a clean towel.
After this, I'll teach you to brush
your teeth properly.
It still has suds.
After washing your hands,
the doctor will teach you
how to brush your teeth
so your teeth won't fall off.
What did you tell them?
I just translated what you said, ma'am.
Then, why are they laughing?
I don't know, ma'am
-Captain.
-Yes?
Do you like Doc Beauty?
Why? Is it too obvious?
Don't get angry, Biboy.
I don't stand a chance with Doc Beauty.
We should take you to the love tree.
Love tree?
You should carve you name
so you will end up together!
Where? Where is the love tree?
Lucas, where are you going?
We're not yet done!
Are you sure about this, Biboy?
Maybe you're just playing jokes on me.
There. Sheila loves Norman.
Those are my parents' initials.
They ended up together
because of the love tree.
Is it okay with you?
I thought you're going to court
Doc Beauty when you grow up.
Lucas!
What are you doing here?
Doc Beauty…
I can no longer make you wait
because you might get sad.
It will take some time before I grow up.
Biboy?
It's okay with me if the Captain
becomes your boyfriend.
Did you make Biboy say that?
Of course not. I am shocked too.
He's mature.
Come on, Doc Beauty, say yes to Cap.
Kids, it's time to go home.
Go.
Just relax.
Don't worry, next time,
I won't steal a kiss from you.
And I won't surprise you,
'cause we'll be officially together.
Wow.
Your confidence blows me away.
He's almost done taking a bath.
Yes, he already ate.
One cup of rice,
a cup of pork soup, and a slice of fish.
Did you make him take his medicine?
Of course, ma'am.
I'm following all your orders
even if it's difficult to make
Master Ramos take his medicines.
You know he's a bit grouchy.
Just be patient with him.
Yes, that's what I'm doing.
Sir!
Hello, Marty?
Ma'am, abort mission.
You mean, failed mission.
You better end that call.
Who should you take orders from?
But she is a captain.
It looks like he's doing fine already.
Okay, bye.
Ma'am… Ma'am, help me, please. Ma'am?
Any more complaints?
-Janet, are you okay?
-Yes.
My back is a bit sore,
maybe from the bending.
I'll go to the town proper later.
I'll buy some medicine for your wound.
Shouldn't you rest?
Maybe our baby is tired too.
Greg will take care of it.
We're running out of funds.
Time to do some collections.
I'll go ahead.
Sir, we have a new batch of wines.
It's good.
No, thank you.
Why didn't you accept the offer?
I thought wine is your favorite?
You'll do everything
just to taste it, right?
Are you jealous of Denise?
Don't get jealous, okay?
I'm all yours.
But like what I said earlier,
I won't make a move
until you tell me, alright?
So it's your move.
I'll just wait.
Go ahead and eat.
It's my treat.
Two hundred.
So, is it clear now
where your loyalty should be?
Sir, please don't scold me.
I'm just a fan of "GoRa".
What's this? "GoRa"?
Diego-Moira, the "GoRa" couple.
Do you want to do 200 laps more?
Wait, sir. Six o'clock. Check it out.
Oh, no. That's danger.
Moira might end up with someone else
because you keep avoiding her.
What a shame.
Do you want to do 200 laps more?
If you're not a doctor,
what would you have been?
I have nothing in mind.
That's really my dream.
When my brother and I were little,
we play pretend that he's the soldier
and I would treat his wounds.
-Really? You two were really close?
-Yes.
Sometimes, he wanted us both
to play soldiers, but I didn't want to.
-Why?
-I don't think it suits me.
I guess I'm not patriotic like you.
Why, what does patriotism mean to you?
-What you are doing.
-What? Being a soldier?
Maxine,
being patriotic is not exclusive
to soldiers.
Anyone can be patriotic
and show his love for the country.
Even in the smallest way
he can, all right?
A simple example,
throwing your garbage properly.
Helping the elders cross the street,
or giving kids opportunity
because they are our future.
In doing the right thing
in whatever situation,
even it means risking your safety,
not letting other take advantage
and oppress the poor and the weak.
You act like this is something new to you.
It's the 15th of the month
that's why we're here.
Being patriotic starts
with a person's character.
Wow, there's a free lecture, too.
Lucas, I was kidding.
I appreciate everything you said.
You were right.
Just a second. Daniel…
Please, look after Doc.
I just have to check something outside.
Why? What is it? Will it take long?
-You head to camp.
-I still have a shift.
I'll leave the car keys with you.
I'll meet you there.
Okay.
What happened?
Do you know them?
No.
Don't be scared.
Tell me if you know them. I got you.
I don't want to get involved.
Do you know where Lucas went?
I'll just follow him.
Daniel.
Doc… it's better if you obey the Captain.
You should go back to the camp.
You are safer there.
Safe?
You mean Lucas is in danger right now?
You better give us money.
Have pity on me.
Just spare me.
My wife is sick.
If we spare you today,
the others will follow.
That's not possible.
Give us the money so you don't get hurt.
Please, spare me.
Hey!
Hey! Let him go.
Let him go!
Just do as the Captain says.
Greg?
Lucas.
Long time no see, Bok.
Bok.
Bok, get down!
Bok, you're wounded.
Medic! Medic!
Bok…
Tell my family…
I love them so much.
What am I, a messenger?
Tell them that yourself
once you get out of here.
Medic!
What are you doing here in Urdan?
I'm doing business.
What else should I do
after I quit being a soldier?
What kind of business?
I lend money, with interest.
You know how hard
it is to collect payments.
So, please excuse my men.
They really have no intention
of hurting the old man.
It looks like you've been here
in Urdan for a long time.
You seem well-acquainted with the place.
Do you know about the movements
of PRG here?
How did that happen?
We're just eating.
No one called for an emergency.
Doc…
calm down.
So, are there many rebels?
He should have called for backup.
Why did he go there alone?
Captain Manalo is an experienced soldier.
He can handle himself. Don't worry.
Don't worry?
It's easier said than done.
What if something bad happens to him?
What if he gets hurt?
How can I not worry
when risking his life is part of the job?
Help me!
Help!
I don't want to die! Help!
Help me!
Are you here because of PRG?
Bok, all I can say is,
you should be careful.
I'm also avoiding that group.
Even my business is affected.
They're causing so much trouble.
So, you know them?
Don't get me involved, Bok.
I'm a civilian now.
I'm done with those kinds of encounters.
Go ahead, answer it Bok.
I'll just be here.
Maxine?
Lucas, help me, please.
I don't want to die.
Please. Come here, please.
What happened to you? Where are you?
Keep those hidden.
Where are you? What do you see?
It's a cliff.
The car is about to fall
off the cliff, Lucas.
Lucas, please, Lucas…
Okay. I'll look for you. Don't be scared.
Lucas, don't…
Lucas?
Lucas!
I think I'm going to die here.
-Thank you, Daniel.
-Be careful, Lucas.
Mom…
My bank account and my insurance policies,
it's in the drawer in my room.
I'm leaving it to you.
I hope…
I hope you will be happy
even when I'm gone.
Mom, sorry if…
I stayed away from you.
It's not what I wanted.
I wish…
I wish I visited you more often.
I love you.
Mom, I love you.
I love you so much.
Tell Sandra that I also love her.
Lucas! Help!
I'm going to die.
Maxine.
Lucas!
How are you?
I'm… I'm okay.
Okay.
Open your window, okay?
Open the window, now.
Okay, okay.
Right now.
What are you doing?
We will really fall
with what you're doing!
Maxine.
Maxine, okay, the car is too heavy.
We will slide off the rocks.
This is the only way for us to get out.
How?
Are you crazy?
I will die with what you're about to do.
Don't move a lot.
What are we going to do, Lucas?
Maxine, Maxine…
I won't let go of you, okay?
You will not die.
I'll get you out of here.
-What? I'm scared.
-This is the only way, Maxine.
Take your foot off the brake.
I don't want to.
-Release the brake, Maxine.
-I don't want to!
Lucas, what are you doing?
Are you hurt?
No.
Okay, good.
Let's go back to the camp,
so you can rest.
What? What did you say?
You're unbelievable! Are you a robot?
Can't you see I'm still weak?
I'm not used to these things.
My heart is beating fast.
What are you doing to me?
Why is it like this?
So, I make your heart beat faster?
Lucas what are you doing?
Just because you saved me
and our lips touched,
do not mean you can do this.
I don't want to. I don't want that, Lucas.
I'm just giving you this to wear.
Your blouse is wet
and I can see through it.
Give me that!
We need more people like you.
If I get in, can you mentor me?
Are you jealous?
Don't worry…
because the person I like is
right in front of me.
I told you. You'll eventually
cross paths with your old buddy.
Don't worry, Bullet. I misled him.
He's not the same Greg
that I used to know.
Are you thinking he's connected
with the PRG here in Urdan?
Does he know something about
at happened with General Manalo?
If he has something to do
with what happened to my father,
-then, I can never forgive him.
-Janet!
I don't think
who you're looking for is here.
The doctor is almost here.
Here she is.
-What happened?
-Doctor, please save my baby.
Put your hands up.
Enemies!