[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty]
[Episode 31]
Back then,
you were very decisive
in front of me.
How can you deserve
Her Highness's trust all these years?
Gao Zhongyi，
you always believe
Huaishen is your man.
Crown Prince also thinks
Huaishen is his man.
So,
you are not only making a slight error,
but also being blind.
This...
Brother Huaishen,
since we are such good friends,
please say something for me.
I am kowtowing to you.
Please don't.
You are the Prefectural Governor.
I'm just a Minister.
I've already put in a good word for you.
Her Highness wanted to tear you asunder by five carts at first.
That's too painful.
Yes, yes, yes.
Finally, Her Highness decided
to give each of you
a pedal of Face Flower
exquisitely made by Resident Regent Li.
Apply it on your face，
and it'll be all over.
Your Highness, please spare my life.
Spare my life!
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Spare my life!
Spare my life, Your Highness.
-Wait! -Spare my life!
Your Highness,
You don't have to do this.
I'm punishing the traitor.
Say no more.
Your Highness, you're trying so hard
to make sure all of your men
tested and selected.
What?
Is the storm really coming?
I hope you can stand with me
when the storm comes.
Gao Zhongyi didn't pass the test.
But you passed.
I'm touched.
In order to test
whether they are loyal to you,
you took so many innocent lives
of young women in Luoyang
as the price.
Great things are achieved
without regard to trifles.
The lives of our people are not trivial.
Your Highness,
if you really become the empress,
it will be
the suffering of the world.
How dare you say that?
Your teacher Di Renjie
did his best
to assist my mother.
With the time passing now,
I can understand more and more,
how hard it was for my teacher back then.
Su Wuming.
So you won't help me?
Your Highness,
the Tang Dynasty can't stand any more trouble.
It's against heaven's will
that you try to usurp the throne right now.
My brother is the Emperor now.
But everyone knows
he is weak.
My nephew
is still young,
and can't  conquer the world.
Only I can make the empire prosper.
Besides,
how is that against the heaven's will
if I only try to restore my mother's empire?
Your Highness, please calm down.
Please calm down.
You are right.
I'd like to propose a toast to you.
Please calm down.
Gao Zhongyi sailed with the wind,
and had no face to live.
But the assassin who tried to kill Crown Prince
is drinking here safe and sound.
How ridiculous.
What did you say?
To kill Crown Prince?
Who assassinated Crown Prince?
Your Highness can ask
your trusted subordinate.
Crown Prince has returned to Chang'an.
Who assassinated Crown Prince?
Su Wuming.
Don't talk nonsense.
What happened?
How would I know?
Maybe he knew that he infuriated Your Highness,
and he would be beheaded,
so he talks nonsense.
Your Highness,
please take a look.
Do you know the person on this painting?
Xin Huaishen.
Isn't the person in the painting
you?
Why are you wearing a scarf?
This...
Who painted this?
This is painted by my sworn sister,
Pei Xijun.
According to the statement
of Lady Hu Shisi in Paradise Inn,
the person on the painting paid  her a fortune
to assassinate Crown Prince.
Don't make up stories.
Minister Xin，
your first identity
is Prefectural Governor Gao's man.
Second identity is Crown Prince's man.
And third identity is
Her Highness's man.
You used  Crown Prince's trust in you
and learned that Crown Prince didn't return to Chang'an,
but stayed in Luoyang
to supervise the case of Face Flower.
So you secretly schemed
to assassinate Crown Prince
without Her Highness's permission.
Xin Huaishen.
Am I right?
Su Wuming.
Are you telling the truth?
Although the painting looks alike,
I wouldn't be so sure
if he had no stammer.
Your Highness,
I was just trying to
to solve your problems in advance.
How dare you!
The business between Crown Prince and me
is family business.
I can handle it my own way.
How dare you assassinate Crown Prince!
Where is Crown Prince now?
I've told him
that you wanted to see him before your coming demise.
He should be
on his way here.
How dare you!
Aunt.
My respect to you, aunt.
You really didn't go back to Chang'an?
His Highness
worried about Your Highness
so he came back.
Your Highness,
the Paradise Inn
I told you earlier
is the place dwelled by the Tocharian woman
who sells Face Flower.
That place is not only old and shabby,
but also mixed with good and evil people.
It's extremely dangerous.
Crown Prince only lives there
to find clues
about Face Flower
in order to save Your Highness.
Impossible.
Su Wuming.
In two hours,
my aunt will die.
Did you find the criminal
and get the antidote?
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Her Highness is not poisoned by Face Flower.
Aunt,
what he said is true.
You're fine.
That's great.
Your Highness,
as you can see,
it is a blessing for the world to have such a Crown Prince.
Once Crown Prince rule the world someday,
he will create a prosperous era
for our Tang Dynasty.
Isn't your conclusion
made too early?
Look how hypocritical his smile is.
Is it happy or disappointed
deep inside his heart?
I'm afraid only he knows.
Aunt,
why are you saying that?
Alright. I' m tired.
Gao Zhongyi and the others
are your people now.
You decide
what to do with them.
Aunt,
there are no people of yours
nor people of mine.
Only people of Tang Dynasty.
What a good speech.
Huaishen, let's go.
Why are you laughing?
Your Highness,
you can't leave now.
Resident Regent Li.
What did you say?
I say you can't leave now.
Li Yue.
What are you doing?
I didn't expect
even Li Yue became your man.
Aunt,
I'm also surprised at
what he just said.
At this point,
why can't you admit it?
Since I can't leave,
then I won't leave.
Let's see
what you can do to me.
Li Yue, what are you doing?
You just said
there are only people of Tang Dynasty.
It's wrong.
I'm not from the Tang Dynasty.
All these years,
I have endured humiliation
just to wait for
for this opportunity.
You argued
who Xin Huaishen works for.
But you don't have any idea that
he's my man.
Uncle,
please give the command.
After killing the princess and Crown Prince,
there will only be the cowardly emperor
left in Chang'an.
Tang Dynasty will be doomed.
You despicable traitor.
You only found out today?
It's too late.
Do you think what I gave you
was a beautiful Face Flower?
Let me tell you.
What you had is no different
from what they had on the market.
In two hours,
your face will turn into a skull.
Do it!
Kill them all!
Your Highness,
please stay here.
No matter what happens,
don't come out.
Your Highness, don't be afraid.
If we are going to die,
I will die before Your Highness.
Stop! All of You!
Li Yue.
You let go of my aunt.
I'll stay.
You can do whatever you want. How's that?
Why are you doing this?
Lu Dong, don't listen to him.
Protect Crown Prince
and get out of here.
Her Highness is right.
Your Highness, please leave with me.
You are too naive.
None of you can leave tonight.
Your Highness.
My nephew.
It's my fault.
Don't let that traitor escape.
My dear bear, that man
and the woman in the room.
Kill them both
and revenge for me.
Lu Lingfeng.
The weak part of the bear lies in the nose.
Meteorite Bear is fierce.
No one can survive if you continue to fight.
Leave me alone.
Take my aunt away!
Your Highness.
This bear is too tall and big.
You can't hit its weak part.
Take Her Highness away quickly.
Lu Lingfeng.
Have you forgotten
the Ghost Four and bronze devil?
Xue Huan.
Take the knife.
Stand on my spear.
Attack its weak part.
My dear bear.
In this case,
then see you next life.
My face.
My face!
My face is so hot.
Lu Lingfeng.
Take Her Highness to find Chicken Fed.
Check if his medicine is ready.
Wait.
Your...
What are you waiting for?
Save my aunt!
Yes.
Your Highness.
What is happening to my face?
My face.
[Go to the upper east gate]
Master Fed.
Do you want to take a rest?
I'm not tired.
Once you make the antidote,
and save the people of Dongdu,
you will have great merits.
Tell me.
If I really save Her Highness,
will she award me
a high-rank official?
I don't care its rank
and I don't care
if it is a formal official or an informal official.
I'll take it as long as it is given to me.
Fed, save Her Highness!
Her Highness is really here.
My face!
Hold her hand. Don't let her scratch her face.
-Xijun. -What's happening to my face?
Hold it.
Wait a minute.
I'll get the antidote right now.
Hold it.
Look at my face.
Your Highness!
Ji'er.
Are you really my Ji'er?
Your...
The medicine is here.
The medicine...
The antidote made by Chicken Fed
has successfully detoxified
the poison of Face Flower.
Her Highness is getting better.
Dongdu has restored
its previous tranquility.
The relationship between Crown Prince and Her Highness
gets better and better.
Stop!
Where are you going?
Yingtao, let me remind you.
I am now
the Administrator of Luozhou.
Don't you have to show me some respect
when talking to me?
I don't care.
I'm looking for you
because of your sworn sister.
My sworn sister?
My father heard the news
that I was in Dongdu,
so he sent someone to pick me up.
The person who came said
he missed me a lot over the past year.
He couldn't sleep at night.
He has headaches and
his hair turns grey a lot.
I can understand and relate that
Assistant Minister Pei is missing his daughter.
You want me to go back to Chang' an?
Of course.
You have to go back sooner or later.
What?
Are you still worried that
you will never see Lu Lingfeng again?
You worry too much.
Lu Lingfeng and Crown Prince
are on good terms as before.
And he made a great contribution this time.
I think he'll be called back to Chang'an
in a few days.
I thought of that.
I'm worried about Xue Huan.
Nice place.
You recovered quite quickly.
All thanks to  Chicken Fed's medicine
and Yingtao's care.
You look so happy.
You're an hour late
even though I am buying you a drink.
Administrator Su is so arrogant.
Please.
There's no rush.
Let me ask you first.
Why did you invite me to drink?
Are you going back to Chang'an?
So what if it is?
Congratulations.
But there are some things which need to be settled
before you leave.
Early this morning,
Regimental Commander Wei sent a message that
Her Highness ordered us
to meet her
in the Meditation Abode of Blessing Temple this afternoon.
You don't have to go,
but I have to.
So you must tell me
what happened
between you and Her Highness.
Or I don't know how to answer her
if she asks me.
I have no dealings with her.
Then who is Ji'er
she spoke of?
Pei Xijun learned to pass the message.
Xijun told me this
for your own good.
Her Highness is the most powerful woman
in Tang.
But she is moody.
I'm afraid that she will hate out of love.
There's no love.
We only have deep hatred.
My parents
were killed by her.
If it weren't for Crown Prince,
I would never have save her life
that day.
I once told you
I was born in Luoyang.
I've never seen my parents since I was young.
I was raised in Serenity Temple
which is called Blessing Temple now.
At that time,
she often dressed as a civilian
to visit me.
She brought me
food and clothes.
I've seen her pay the monk.
This is the early memory
of my life.
So, even though I was an orphan,
I had nothing to worry about.
At that time, I thought
she was very cordial.
And I even thought
if she was my mother.
Until one day,
my father showed up.
Your father?
Didn't you just say that...
This man who
I called father
was actually my uncle.
How old are you?
Five.
How about I teach you how to study?
Okay.
Later I found out
my uncle only pretended to study in the temple
for the exam.
In fact, he wanted to take me away.
He told me the truth
after we were back in Fanyang.
The woman who often came to see me.
The so-called aunt
is the princess of our dynasty.
And she killed my parents.
She raised me in the temple
as a bait
to catch more of my father's accomplices.
Who is your father?
When the sound rises, the north wind rises.
The sword is strong and the south is flat.
Sobbing makes the mountain collapse.
Reproach makes wind and cloud change colors.
With this, we can defeat the enemy.
With this, we'll be able to win.
This is a poem made by Luo Bingwang
in the name of Li Jing Ye.
So,
your father was against Empress Wu Zetian
bace then.
The Lu family of Fanyang
has always been protecting the legitimate Tang.
How could he tolerate her usurping the country?
[Blessing Temple]
Her Highness asked Administrator Su to come in first.
My greetings, Your Highness.
Has he arrived?
Yes.
Do you know why
I let you in first?
I don't know.
I don't have the courage to see him.
I'm afraid he won't recognize me.
Why did you say he recognizes you,
Your Highness?
Su Wuming.
You surely know
I have many children.
But the first one
is not with me now.
It's a long story.
That was more than 20 years ago.
I was 19 years old.
Mother doted on me.
I was also willful.
One day, I went to the riverside
in the south of the city.
Who are you?
Don't move!
The guards wanted to execute him.
I pardoned him.
I knew,
I fell in love with him at that moment.
Be carefull.
During the Mid-Autumn Festival that year,
the moon in Luoyang was so round.
So beautiful.
I was
so happy and bold.
Finally I didn't come back to Palace.
That night,
I got pregnant.
He told me
he's from Caozhou.
He studied in Yi Gate of Luoyang
to be an official one day.
I've been to his hut.
But I knew
he didn't tell me
his real identity.
I accidentally found
his longsword
was engraved with the words
"From Li JingYe"
which was hidden in his hut.
I see.
The so-called scholar
is Li Jing Ye's subordinate.
After that, he tried every means
to inquire about my mother's whereabouts.
At the time, the Long Gate was opening the cave.
My mother often went there.
I know
he was looking for an opportunity to assassinate my mother.
I got angry
for he took advantage of me.
So I played along
and asked my mother to capture him at the Long Gate.
However,
he didn't blame me
after he knew it was planned by me.
But when I realized
he didn't blame me because he loved me,
he already killed himself.
What's his name?
Yang Guan.
It could not be his real name.
After his death,
my mother sent me
outside Luoyang City.
I gave birth to Ji'er there.
Yang Ji?
The year after I gave birth to Ji'er
was my happiest time.
Until one day,
my mother came to visit me and
told me
that she let me give birth to this child,
but she did not allow me
to keep him by my side.
Of course I didn't agree.
I won't leave my
child alone
unless I die.
Mother still doted on me,
so she compromised in the end.
But she told me to think it through.
But you are a princess.
It's indeed troublesome
to have a child before marriage.
No.
Mother told me to think it through，
because she hope
maybe one day
I can be an Empress
like her.
If I carry this child with me,
I will face more doubts.
Empress was using her power
to seduce you.
I was having second thoughts
at that moment.
I sent Ji'er to Serenity Temple
ruthlessly.
From then on,
I would disguise as a civilian
to visit him in the temple each month.
I told Ji'er that
I'm your aunt.
And your mother
went far away.
I will never forget that
he looked at me with longing in his eyes.
I should have
aborted him
instead of abandoning him after his birth.
God punished me
so I lost him
finally.
Lost him?
It was when he was five years old.
Where is Yang Ji?
He was taken away.
He was taken away?
Who took him away?
Where is my Ji'er?
Where is he?
If you can't
find my child,
I'll kill all of you!
The monk said
a scholar
has been studying in the temple.
He taught these children in the temple
when he was free.
Ji'er was disappeared
after the scholar returned to his hometown.
I suspect Ji'er went with him.
I sent people to look for him,
and finally it was like looking for a needle in a haystack.
After all that I've said,
the point is Lu Lingfeng.
There's a mole
on Ji'er's left palm.
Lu Lingfeng has one too.
But Lu Lingfeng
was from the Lu family of Fanyang.
He is so proud of it.
Those who took Ji'er away
were from YouYan.
Right.
Fanyang is in Youyan.
Actually, I asked Lu Lingfeng before.
But his age doesn't match.
I suspect
he deliberately concealed his age.
It must be the scholar
who took him away.
He told Lu Lingfeng never to recognize me.
Maybe what your father,
or your uncle, said
was not
entirely true.
What he said to me
is the truth.
My father's name board is
in our family ancestral hall.
Every day, my uncle
takes me to kowtow to my father.
My father never got married
because of me.
He said
I, Lu Lingfeng,
will inherit
all the glory of Fan family.
I will be successful
and bring glory to our family.
How could such a father
lie to me.
What an amazing father.
He changed my age
by two years older
to prevent my enemies from finding me.
He is wise.
I'll visit him
if I have chance to go to Fanyang.
My father
died 5 years ago.
Before he died,
he told me I might see the princess again
one day.
He asked me to promise
that no matter what princess says,
I can not
trust her.
Su Wuming.
What are you thinking?
I'm waiting for your idea.
What idea?
Today, I will recognize Ji'er.
What do you think?
No.
Why?
Since his age doesn't match,
maybe he is not
Yang Ji.
There is a mole on his hand.
It's just a coincidence.
How is that possible?
Mother and son are connected.
That day,
I can clearly feel his heartbeat
when he was carrying me
or maybe holding me.
That's my son's heartbeat!
But Your Highness,
what the Empress said
makes sense.
Although I disagree that
you become the second Empress,
you are after all a princess,
the most powerful woman in Tang.
If you suddenly
have another son,
Think about it.
What will the people think of you?
What will the people think
of the Royal Family?
I don't care.
If Ji'er acknowledges me,
I would rather give up all my power
and not be the princess of Tang.
But you have to think
for Lu Lingfeng.
He has been with me
these days.
I know him very well.
He is brave and resourceful,
versed in both literature and martial arts.
He is a man of tremendous promise.
He has always regarded his origin from The Lu family of Fanyang
as his greatest honor.
If you insist on acknowledging him,
it might cause his death.
In this world,
who dares to kill my son?
Himself.
Have you forgotten
how that scholar Yang Guan
died?
My greetings, Your Highness.
Raise your head.
Did I look ugly
when you saved me
that day?
No.
In life and death,
people will talk nonsense
because of fear.
But I don't remember
what I said.
Lu Lingfeng.
You saved me.
Tell me.
How should I repay you?
Well...
I heard that
you haven't been promoted yet.
How about I reinstate you?
No.
No?
Are you rejecting
my kindness?
No.
I deserve
to be punished
for the mistakes I made back then.
If I get reinstatement  because of my merit,
we need a formal official document from the provincial department.
Su Wuming is right.
You're too prideful.
Are you worried
I'll confer you an informal official?
Fine.
I won't interfere with your official.
Anyway, you look down apon of the title I give,
because you work for Crown Prince.
How about...
I give you a marriage?
I heard you and Pei Jian’s daughter...
You don't have to.
Lu Lingfeng is devoted to the country.
I have not considered marriage yet.
You're rejecting my kindness
by refusing me again and again.
Your Highness,
I indeed have a request.
Go ahead.
I have a disciple named Xue Huan,
who has been alone since childhood.
Now he learned some martial arts from me,
but he hasn't studied properly.
I want to send him to the Blessing Temple.
Please allow me.
This is a piece of cake.
I'll ask
the monks of this temple
to take care of him.
Don't you have anything else
to beg me?
No.
Please take care of yourself
and enjoy your leisure.
Master.
Miss.
Sir.
You don't want me anymore?
It's not that.
I hope my disciple Xue Huan
can become a talented scholar.
One day,
you will become a general
like your ancestors.
No!
I want to follow Master.
Miss,
and Mr Su.
You just don't want to follow me,
right?
Let me tell you.
The three of them
will go their separate ways soon.
Who do you want to follow?
Think about it.
Fed.
Don't cry.
Do you know
where I studied
when I was a kid?
When I was 4 years old,
I studied at Serenity Temple in Dongdu
which is called Blessing Temple now.
There are many schools in Blessing Temple.
There are the best teachers
in the world.
This is a rare opportunity.
It's not difficult for you
to learn martial arts.
But it's hard for you
to get knowledge
like Su Wuming.
Can you make achievements
and
become a real man
in the future?
It's up to your choice today.
♫The storm rises with no reason♫
♫In the night of illusions♫
♫I go into the maze♫
♫In a world of prosperity♫
♫A heart burns with obsession♫
♫With the darkness rising♫
♫I can't stop wandering through the night♫
♫With light in my heart, I'm not afraid of the storm♫
♫It's because of justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there is fog♫
♫Even if there are invisible waves♫
♫I'll tell the story of the fate♫
♫Tell the love of the world♫
♫For the memory of grace♫
♫And the resentment is not yet over♫
♫The rivers and mountains are immortal, the clouds are overturned♫
♫To be consoled by the truth, even with thorns on my back♫
♫Only for justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there are a thousand sails, it's not a waste of time♫
♫What I am afraid of is the unrighted wrong♫
♫What is the meaning of life and death?♫
♫I'll paint the sunshine into the landscape♫
♫The spirit of righteousness♫
♫Exists for the one I care♫