[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty]
[Episode 3]
Not bad.
Delicious.
How many pieces left?
Try this.
Here.
Let me propose a toast to all of you.
Come on.
I've written the co-investigation documents
with Wannian County.
After your meal,
you can get down to business.
You say we can dig out bodies
in the places you marked.
What if we can't?
It would be a waste of effort.
My wife is going to give birth soon.
Giving birth is a big deal.
I have poor eyesight.
I'm afraid I can't
handle this.
Why don't you get treated earlier?
If you're blind, even if you see a famous doctor,
that will be in vain.
I...
I'm timid.
Actually, not timid.
I have a mother.
You have to be a good son.
That's good.
But you need money to take care of your mother, right?
And you need money to cure your eyes, right?
Yes.
Bring more money home.
If your wife is happy,
she'll definitely give birth smoothly.
We will be paid?
How much?
That's right.
How much? How much?
Tell me.
So far,
there have been eight brides missing.
It is unclear whether they are alive or not.
Although someone paid a lot,
I don't want you to find it troublesome.
How about...
Sheriff Su.
This is our duty.
There's nothing troublesome.
That's right.
Thank you for your hospitality.
We will do our best.
Yes, we will.
Thank you.
I'll wait
for your good news.
-Come out. -Go.
Go!
Get out of the way.
Why this cruel?
Go over there.
Hurry!
-Squat down. -Hurry!
This is a serious crime.
Yes.
This must be serious.
Why are there so many Imperial Guards?
So Chang'an black tea is demon tea.
[Notice]
An enchanter used tea to deceive people
and caused death.
He who hides or sells Chang'an black tea would be sentenced to death.
General,
this man has been selling
Chang'an black tea in the hotel.
Many people are witnesses.
Put him into the prison.
We'll convict him
after he confesses everything.
-Please spare my life, General. -Move.
I'm just doing a small business.
General.
General, please spare me!
Our stocks in both the East and West markets
were confiscated.
It's said that many shops
sold counterfeits.
What a joke.
If Lu Lingfeng is still alive,
our life
will be hard.
We have found out his whereabouts.
Immortal Venerable,
please give the instruction.
Greetings, Immortal Venerable.
You've slept for too long.
It's time to exercise.
The imperial court is talking about
that the Imperial Guards are not in charge of the tea.
Why are you doing so?
Great General,
I didn't decide on my own.
[Lu Tong, Great General of Imperial Guards]
Do you mean that this is
His Highness' order?
Is there any instruction written by himself?
Today in the court,
His Majesty asked,
but His Highness didn't say a word.
What else do you want to defend?
Many imperial officials
died mysteriously.
This must be highly related to Chang'an black tea.
Great General,
please let me find out the truth.
I can let you investigate.
But I'm afraid
this may ruin your bright future.
I have no regrets.
Don't embarrass His Majesty.
If so,
no one can save your life.
You can investigate the case,
but stop deploying the Imperial Guards.
Sheriff Su is really a genius.
By just thinking about it,
he can find where bodies are buried.
I heard that
he was a disciple of Detective Di.
It seems
that's true.
He agreed to pay us.
I don't know when I'll get it.
How about asking?
Ask what?
Can't you see he is examining the corpses?
Disciple of Detective Di
will definitely pay us as he promised.
From now on,
we need to follow the sheriff.
Stop slacking off.
Sheriff Su.
-Magistrate. -Magistrate
-Magistrate. -Magistrate.
Magistrate Yuan, what brings you here?
I heard.
You were taught well by Detective Di.
You have great foresight.
It was surprising that you found all these corpses.
Any clues about the culprit?
I found these bodies
by coincidence.
As for the culprit, I have no idea yet.
It's already very impressive.
Your achievements today
will contribute to your great career.
Very soon.
Sheriff Su,
I have something important to discuss.
Please come with me.
The Imperial Guards
have captured tea dealers.
But they caught too many.
The Imperial Prison is overburdened.
So they sent many people here.
How should we arrange them?
Are you asking me?
Yes.
You served Detective Di for years.
You are more knowledgeable than me.
Let them go.
Release them?
The Imperial Guards have crossed the line.
Besides, the Imperial Prison is not small.
Suspects of this case
shouldn't be sent
to our county.
Yes.
But I heard
that General Lu, who arrested them,
is with His Highness.
Will we offend His Highness?
I heard
that Her Highness
also drinks Chang'an black tea.
If Chang'an County makes a fuss,
I'm afraid we may offend Her Highness.
Thank you for reminding me.
I know what to do.
General.
The Great General forbids you to deploy the troops.
So how do we attack the Ghost Market tonight
to investigate the source of the demon tea?
We have to give up.
The three of us are willing to follow General.
Go back and rest.
Let me think about it.
One more thing.
Something interesting happens
in Chang'an County.
It seems
that Su Wuming really has some theurgy.
What do you mean?
He drew something randomly on the map,
and then constables dug out
eight bodies.
They are all the missing brides.
Greetings, General.
Your forehead turned black.
You must have stayed up all night.
You can read fortune?
Tell me.
How did you infer
where the eight bodies were?
Did Di Renjie
taught you any unique skill?
What unique skill?
I just found this case strange.
So I read some
folk tales.
While reading,
I guessed something.
If you don't mind,
you can take them back.
They're quite interesting.
Pardon me.
You are from the noble class in Fanyang.
You people
may turn your nose up at these things.
I want to see
what kind of nonsense
is recorded on it?
I'm thirsty. Get me some water.
How can we treat General
with water?
I have good tea.
Mere half a liang tea cost me 3 ingots of silver.
It's Chang'an black tea.
How dare you hide demon tea?
Where did you get the money to buy it?
General.
This is my home.
Even if you want to punish me,
you should show me some dignity.
It seems
that you've never had Chang'an black tea.
Of course not.
As the saying goes,
nothing ventured, nothing gained.
You don't even know
what Chang'an black tea is.
How do you investigate this case?
The tea is really expensive.
After you drink it,
you need to pay me.
I didn't drink it.
This is your fault.
You said you were thirsty.
I made tea for you.
You have to pay me even if you didn't drink it.
Are you a crazy beggar?
You're right.
I am indeed poor,
and also in debt.
Do you owe money because of this tea?
No.
Anyway, I owe money.
You earn a lot,
and can't spend it alone.
Give me some. I need it urgently.
Sheriff.
This...
Really?
I, Su Wuming,
am a man of my word.
You share the money equally.
That's too much.
This...
This is equal to your income for a month.
We can't.
Yes, it is quite a lot
for me.
But for General,
it means nothing.
General?
Is he the famous
General, Lu Lingfeng.
Yes he is.
So, the money was rewarded by General Lu?
Yes.
The Imperial Guards are superior.
General Lu is a trusted aide of His Highness.
How would he reward me?
Is there
anything we can do?
Yes.
Report!
Su Wuming, sheriff of Chang'an, requests a visit.
Let him in.
Yes.
Su Wuming, sheriff of Chang'an.
Greetings, General.
What?
Haven't I paid you enough money?
Are you here to ask for more?
No.
I'm here to send you troops.
Troops?
I have many troops and officers.
But if we want to investigate the Ghost Market thoroughly,
I'm afraid that now General is unable
to deploy troops.
Su Wuming.
You arranged a spy beside me.
You have led your army
to search both markets.
The Ghost Market should be the next.
But you haven't moved yet.
Isn't it because you have no troop to deploy?
Fine.
Even if you're right,
but
where did you get the troops?
There are 19 constables in Chang'an County.
They are willing to follow your orders.
Actually,
I would like to be the 20th.
But as a scholar,
I'm afraid I'll be a burden to you.
Get out of the way!
The Imperial Guards are ordered
to confiscate Chang'an black tea.
Anyone who hides or sells it will commit a felony.
You!
Stand there. Don't move.
Get out of the way!
Don't move!
Yes.
Get out of the way!
Look.
Can I get a discount?
Manager!
The Imperial Guards are looking for the black tea.
They'll be here soon.
Lock the door. Now!
Take the black tea away from the back door.
No.
We have almost reached an agreement
on the price.
I won't bargain anymore, okay?
Sell the tea to me.
It's too late! The Imperial Guards are here!
I don't want to risk my life!
Don't go.
I can pay more.
Get out of the way!
Stand still!
Don't move.
Chang'an black tea.
Wen Chao.
Greetings, General.
As a minister of the household,
you are here in the Ghost Market
to buy demon tea?
I...
I just heard that the tea tastes good,
so I was curious.
Tie them all up.
Yes.
No, no, no.
Don't.
General Lu, please be lenient.
We're old friends.
Get out of the way!
Go away!
Hurry!
Get out of the way! Move!
Sheriff.
Why didn't you investigate the case
with the Imperial Guards?
Why should I be with them?
To keep you safe.
Is the Ghost Market so scary?
It was General Lu
who wanted to investigate Chang'an black tea.
But the top priority of Chang'an County
should be the disappearances of brides.
The source of the spice is still a mystery.
Both the East and West Markets have no clues.
If we still can't find any clues here in the Ghost Market,
the case is indeed ghostly.
General,
you don't safeguard His Majesty
and patrol the whole Chang'an,
but come here. Aren't you interfering with other's affairs?
So what?
For every liang of tea you sell, you can earn 3 ingots of silver.
You've been selling it for more than half a year.
How much tea have you sold?
Have you ever paid tax to the court?
Profits in the Ghost Market
are excluded from the tax.
This is the rule of Chang'an.
Besides,
confiscating my property cannot prove your capability.
My tea
is bought with gold and silver.
If you are really capable,
go to Lady Shiyi's.
I saw them entering this alley.
Why were they gone?
They shot arrows
not as bandits,
but as well-trained soldiers.
We need to be more careful.
Whom did the tea dealer
ask us to investigate?
It seems to be Gentleman Shiyi.
No.
It's Lady Shiyi.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
It'll be too late if we don't move now.
Don't leave in a hurry.
Today is my birthday.
Everyone here is my guest.
I'll treat you to tea.
Chang'an black tea.
It is delicious.
You may enjoy it as much as you want.
Master,
let's go now.
If we are caught by the Imperial Guards...
You are ignorant.
One sip of black tea
is better than immortals,
let alone unlimited drinking.
Get out!
Sir,
I sell fancy spices here.
As long as women smell one of them,
they won't leave you.
Is that true?
Sheriff.
We've seen that man before.
He almost got his hands chopped off
when he tried to steal chicken that day.
It's not his first offense.
Where is my chicken?
You chicken thief!
Whom do you call a chicken thief?
You look familiar to me.
Ghost!
What's wrong with him?
Maybe he smelled
the scent of this.
There's actually such a big store
in the Ghost Market.
Endearing and alluring is Lady Shiyi.
[Endearing and Alluring is Lady Shiyi.]
It's only been a few days,
but the banner has been changed.
We've caused quite a stir
but they're dancing like nothing happened.
They're prepared?
Wu died here.
We must be careful.
Jia,
it feels way too good
to work
with the Imperial Guards.
You bet.
Yeah.
I haven't felt so fantastic for years.
Luo, Liu,
we must seize the chance
to make our names known.
General,
let us lead the assault.
Gentlemen,
let's show those scum what we county guards
are capable of!
Yeah!
Let's go.
General.
Let them go.
If there's a trap, we'll know.
This is so humiliating.
This place is to be searched.
Where is the store owner?
Well...
We have guests.
Serve them the tea.
Yes.
Please.
What's this?
The best tea ever, Chang'an black tea.
How dare you!
We are here to confiscate this tea.
Poor guards like you
should cherish the opportunity
to have a sip of Chang'an black tea.
You're being fools to refuse it.
Are you off your heads already?
You are Lady Shiyi?
Yeah. So what?
Endearing and alluring indeed.
Shut up!
You diabolic bitch.
Surrender now and I'll be easy on you.
So bold of you to say that.
Don't scare my guests.
Go. Go. Go.
You're not afraid of us at all, are you?
No one is allowed to leave.
Whether they stay or leave
is not up to you.
Take her down!
The Imperial Guards are here.
All county guards
retreat!
Are you sure, General?
Maybe we should fight them together.
A bunch of losers!
Get out!
Do what General Lu said.
Yes, do what General Lu said.
Retreat.
You're afraid of being held accountable
if those county guards die here,
right?
Fang Xiang God?
Meet you with respect, Immortal Venerable.
You practiced sorcery
to kill people,
and sell the black tea.
You're the cancer of our society.
As a General,
I'll end your life myself.
You old prick!
Look around, boy.
You can't threaten me at my place.
The Lu family from Fanyang
is indeed very proud.
You know me?
Who are you?
Take a guess.
But it wouldn’t help even if you guessed right,
because you won't be able to
leave here alive.
These two warriors
can't be hurt by any weapons.
You're doomed to die!
This place is weird.
There might be an ambush.
Leave, General.
I'll take care of it here.
Imperial Guards!
Yes!
Kill these beasts with me.
Behead whoever dares
to resist.
Yes!
Stop!
Stop there!
Can't you just let me go?
Wait.
Sir, listen to me.
I'm not a ghost.
I'm here to make friends with you.
I'll be damned if I believe you.
The weakness of them
is their eyes?
Leave, General!
Leave?
It's too late.
General.
Don't worry.
Go!
Report this to His Highness.
I'll wipe out the Ghost Market.
All these heretics
who did harm to the country
will be brought to justice.
Go!
Bring it on.
I'm right here.
Fight with me if you dare.
You're already my prisoner.
So stop bluffing.
Lady Shiyi,
count for me.
I wanna know how many arrows
it will take to kill the General.
Stop. Stop running.
You damn ghost!
Stop chasing me!
General.
General,
come down the tunnel with me!
Shoot!
Don't let them escape!
Hurry!
Go after them!
Lu Lingfeng,
are you okay?
What are you doing here?
You can't even defend yourself.
I...
It's not safe here.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Come in.
All right.
Now we don't
have to whisper.
No one can hear us here.
No. No.
The wounded one can stay.
You, leave.
He's a defenseless nerd.
He'll die once he goes out.
But he scares me
if he stays.
Can't you see I'm trembling?
He must leave.
What are you afraid of?
Not you.
You got shot
in order to
save me.
So it's unlikely that you'll kill me.
Just…
Drop your sword.
He's different.
He...
He's not a human.
He's a ghost.
Is it because of the smell on me?
See?
He admitted it.
There is no ghost in the world.
Stop talking nonsense.
I once thought that too,
but he smelled
the Soul Returning Incense all over his body.
He has to be a ghost.
Do you mean this smell?
Is that the cloth
wrapped around the brides' bodies?
Yes.
Their bodies didn't decay for days.
I've been investigating this incense.
That's why
I ran into you
in the Ghost Market.
I'm Su Wuming, the sheriff of Chang'an.
May I know your name?
You are
the sheriff?
Yes.
My surname is Fed.
No first name.
I love eating chicken.
So people in the Ghost Market
call me Chicken Fed.
If you don't find that name funny,
just call me that.
I have a question for you, Mr. Fed.
Do you know the origin of the Soul Returning Incense?
My bad.
You were shot
because of me.
Let me pull that arrow out for you.
Come.
I know you don't trust me.
But they are looking for you outside.
You have to stay here
for the time being.
Mr. Fed is well-versed in medicine.
General,
give him some credit.
One arrow
won't necessarily kill you.
I'm just worried
that the arrow might be poisonous.
Those wicked people
can do anything.
General,
don't take his every word seriously.
After all, Mr. Fed is known
for sneaking around and stealing chicken
in the Ghost Market.
How can we believe someone like that?
You just asked me
the origin of the Soul Returning Incense.
How can you look down on me now?
Does it matter
whether I look down on you or not?
I doubt that someone like you
really know the origin of the incense.
Of course I know!
I can tell you now.
In the backyard of the government office of the West Market,
there are bizarre herbs growing there.
Go ask Kang Yuanli,
the government official of the West Market,
about what they're used for.
You think
knowing an official's name
can make you trustworthy in the General's eyes?
There are indeed
bizarre herbs in that backyard.
Su Wuming,
stop daring me.
I'm not a three-year-old.
Chicken Fed.
I trust you.
Take this arrow out for me.
It's really poison-tipped.
Damn it.
Pulling the arrow out
is just the start.
Well...
Let's have a talk.
About what?
Listen,
you got shot because of me,
but you can't blame it on me.
Right?
But you'll thank me
for saving your life.
So you must repay me.
How?
I-I'm a foodie.
I love eating chicken.
Could you promise me
one chicken every day?
Served with booze is preferred.
I can promise you that.
Leave us alone.
You look mean
and cunning.
You don't trust you.
General,
you're good-looking
and righteous.
I know you'll keep your word.
Okay.
One chicken every day.
Whether there will be booze will
depend on my mood.
Do it.
Deal.
You have a temper.
I like you.
We've searched every corner of the Ghost Market,
but we couldn't find
Lu Lingfeng and Su Wuming.
Once it dawns,
there's nothing we can do.
Don't worry.
When it dawns,
the poison will take Lu Lingfeng's life for us.
He won't
be in our way anymore.
But he confiscated
all our stock of the tea.
There's still half a month left.
Those addicted officials and nobles
can't wait.
Then tell them
that on the 18th of this month,
a batch of first-class tea
will be put on the market in advance.
They can only pre-order it by gold.
As for the price,
you can increase it enormously this time.
Is all this
a part of your plan?
Sheriff Su,
you're really considerate.
He has to wake up now,
or it'll be too late
for you to leave
the Ghost Market.
General,
wake up!
Move!
Careful!
I had to gouge out a large chunk of fresh.
Watch out, General.
Lu Lingfeng, the General of the Imperial Guards,
thank you for saving my life. You're a great doctor.
A great doctor?
That's not me.
He was so badly injured
but you helped him bounce back overnight.
Of course you're a great doctor.
That's what you are.
I hate being called that.
Sheriff Su.
Magistrate Yuan.
I heard that you
went to the Ghost Market last night to crack the murder case.
I've been worried sick.
What do you mean by that?
♫The storm rises with no reason♫
♫In the night of illusions♫
♫I go into the maze♫
♫In a world of prosperity♫
♫A heart burns with obsession♫
♫With the darkness rising♫
♫I can't stop wandering through the night♫
♫With light in my heart, I'm not afraid of the storm♫
♫It's because of justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there is a fog♫
♫Even if there are invisible waves♫
♫I'll tell the story of the fate♫
♫Tell the love of the world♫
♫For the memory of grace♫
♫And the resentment is not yet over♫
♫The rivers and mountains are immortal, the clouds are overturned♫
♫To be consoled by the truth, even with thorns on my back♫
♫Only for justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there are a thousand sails, it's not a waste of time♫
♫What I am afraid of is the uprighted wrong♫
♫What is the meaning of life and death?♫
♫I'll paint the sunshine into the landscape♫
♫The spirit of righteousness♫
♫Will last forever in my heart♫