[English subtitles are available]
[Strange Tales of Tang Dynasty]
[Episode 23]
[Commander's Residence]
The wonton made by Xijun
is so delicious.
I want another bowl.
Okay.
Let me do it.
If you don't drink,
whatever you eat in the future,
will be delicious.
Stop that.
Don't talk nonsense.
Chicken Fed has sworn that
he won't drink anything else
in Ninghu
unless he get to try the Tuo God Wine.
I...
Maybe you can quit drinking
in Ninghu.
If I'm really left no choice but
to quit drinking,
that proves that you fail as the Military Commander of Ninghu.
Brother, you have just arrived at Ninghu,
and the prefectural governor was killed.
Besides, you have to be concerned about the domineering Worshippers of Tuo God too.
Now, If you don't help Master Chicken
to get a sip of the Tuo God Wine,
you will be criticized by him.
I really feel sorry for you.
Body of several meters tall?
Didn't you say
there are no ghosts or gods in this world?
Yes.
I didn't expect
that there was really a god in Ninghu.
It seems that
I'm too ignorant.
Where are you going?
I was too angry during the day,
and has missed something.
I need to go
to the Lin Inn again.
Do you think you can see
the Tuo God so easily?
Of course we need to have a curtain separating us from Tuo God.
A curtain?
Since you're the Military Commander of the state,
let me tell you
this for your good.
You can suspect anything
in Ninghu,
except for the Tuo God.
Thank you.
[Chief's Residence, Worshippers of Tuo God]
There's another one!
Mo Le!
Yes.
Prepare the boat tomorrow morning.
I'm going to the island!
[Member of the Worshippers of Tuo God, Mo Le]
Don't worry, chief.
I will get it done.
[Detective House]
Shen Chong got
a copy of the Records of Worshippers of Tuo God.
It was handed in by the Administrator, Gu Wenbin.
He said it was from Lu Yong of the Chamber of Commerce.
What's in it?
The crimes that the Worshippers of Tuo God has committed.
How did Lu Yong get this Records?
I don't know.
Shen Chong is on the Tuo God Island
with the Records.
Go back now.
Let me know if there is any news.
Yes.
[Tuo God Island]
Tuo God,
Shen Chong is here.
this Records of Worshippers of Tuo God
was presented by Gu Wenbin.
He said it was handed in by
Lu Yong from the Chamber of Commerce.
I've read it.
It's exactly the same as the one
last time.
It should be written by Li Yu.
I'm afraid that
there are not only these two copies of it.
Li Yu has a daughter.
She came to Ninghu recently,
and I heard that she knows some martial arts.
If she have other copies of the Records of Worshippers of Tuo God
with her,
and was brought out from Ninghu,
then...
Since you've made up your mind,
just do as you wish.
I understand.
I'm here today
for another thing.
The newly arrived Military Commander, Su Wuming
brought his men to
Yaoyue Restaurant and tried to get the God Wine.
He even befriended a merchant who is still in debt.
I don't know what he's up to.
I don't think he did it to fight against us,
he just doesn't know how powerful the Worshippers of Tuo God is.
But since he has arrived at Ninghu,
what should we do to him
if he has disrespected Tuo God?
Please tell us.
Tuo God said that
we don't have to deal with that Commander Su right now.
I understand.
Su Wuming!
Di Renjie's disciple.
He is good at investigating cases.
You should be careful.
Thank you for your guidance.
I got it.
Let's go.
You...
Don't worry. It's safe here.
I remember now.
You are Minister He.
Just call me He Xi.
Why did the Worshippers of Tuo God come to you?
The officials in Ninghu
are mostly related to the Worshippers of Tuo God.
It's normal that you don't trust me.
According to their previous style of work,
I believe that Governor Li's death
is definitely related to them.
It was even clearer
when they tried to attack you secretly this time.
Miss Ying Tao,
although you haven't been in Ninghu for long,
I believe that Governor Li
had told you
about the Worshippers of Tuo God.
And they tried their best
to kill Governor Li.
Why?
I'm the Minister of Justice of Ninghu.
I'm investigating this matter.
You should trust me.
I won't force you
if you don't want to tell.
But looking at the situation now,
I advise you to stay here for the time being,
and don't go out.
You should not go to keep vigil for Governor Li as well.
It's too dangerous.
Who is so bold
to ruin our plan?
His face was covered
and we couldn't see clearly.
Covered?
Could it be
someone we know?
Banquets have never end
in Ninghu,
along with singing and dancing everywhere.
But
the people can't even decide
what to drink.
How pathetic.
The banquet today was specially
held to welcome Commander,
but are you trying to imply something?
Commander,
you are right.
Being an official in Ninghu
is unfair.
Minister Zeng,
are you drunk?
No.
The Nantian Wine.
I used to drink it every day,
but now it has became the Tuo God Wine.
I can never drink it again.
Tell me,
what's the point of being an official?
That's boring.
But Minister Zeng,
with the Worshippers of Tuo God,
even if you are
in the office once for seven days,
everything will still go smoothly.
What else do you want?
If I can drink the Tuo God Wine every day,
so what if I'm busy every day?
Well...
Administrator,
do you and the former Prefectural Governor really dare to
hand over the important matters
to the Worshippers of Tuo God?
Commander has just arrived.
It's normal for you to have such doubts.
In a few months,
your doubts will be cleared up.
I hope so.
Please enjoy.
I'm leaving.
Commander Su,
where are you going?
I'm going to keep vigil for Prefectural Governor Li.
[Bishui Pavilion]
Father,
I will avenge you.
Who?
Who are you?
How dare you play tricks here?
Come out!
Let me tell you.
I am Detective Di's disciple.
Father,
I know you can't rest in peace
because you were assassinated
even you were the Prefectural Governor.
But,
please don't scare me.
Miss.
You're awake.
How dare you! What are you doing?
This is your sword. Take it back.
I'm the new Military Commander of Ninghu.
I heard that Governor Li
was diligent in his work.
I admire him very much.
I'm here to keep vigil for him.
The moment I entered,
I saw you fainted.
I didn't expect that we would meet again
in this way.
It's you.
You're not a thief
nor a teacher,
but a Military Commander.
I didn't expect
you are Governor Li's daughter.
You ruined my plan that night.
Even if you came to keep vigil for my father,
it won't help.
What do you mean?
You don't need to know.
As the Military Commander of Ninghu,
I will urge the Minister of Justice
to solve this case as soon as possible
and clear your father's name.
Forget it.
All the officials in Ninghu
are connected to the Worshippers of Tuo God.
Even if you're new here,
I don't believe you.
Did you mean that
Governor Li was killed by the Worshippers of Tuo God?
Do you have any evidence?
No evidence is needed.
My father couldn't rest in peace.
I just saw his ghost.
Who is there?
Uncle Si, don't worry.
I'm fine.
You may leave.
He said
he was packing my father's remains.
You just said
you saw Governor Li.
I think you were hallucinating
for missing your father too much.
Give it to me.
What is it?
The Records of Worshippers of Tuo God.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you don't hand it over,
Fine.
Who are you?
How despicable!
Do you know who I am?
You?
A dead man.
Lu Lingfeng?
Wait, Miss.
Why are you stopping me?
We can't kill him.
If we kill him, we won't know
where is he from.
Tell me.
Are you from the Worshippers of Tuo God?
We were paid by our client to
get the Records of Worshippers of Tuo God
from you.
For the real identity of our client,
we really don't know.
The Records of Worshippers of Tuo God?
Even if you're not the members of the Worshippers of Tuo God,
you should die too.
Lu Lingfeng!
-Stop her! Stop her! -Please spare my life.
Lu Lingfeng, what's wrong?
Stop!
Do you think you can simply rip my clothes?
Lu Lingfeng.
Thank you for saving my life.
It's not the first time,
stop thanking me.
The women just now
isn't Governor Li's daughter.
She should be a killer.
Here.
Forget about her.
Let's talk about you.
When did you come to Ninghu?
That night,
when I was going back to Commander's Residence from the Lin Inn,
I felt
someone following me,
and he didn't mean anything bad.
I thought
if you were back,
that would be great.
I didn't expect
it's really you.
Are you too lonely
wandering around the world,
and miss Xijun
and us?
I just think that as a scholar,
you will not do well in Ninghu at first.
So I came to see you.
But I didn't expect that
Ninghu is so strange.
The entire city from the officials to the commoner,
are fear of the Tuo God.
Su Wuming.
did you worship
the alligator demon?
Not yet.
But very soon.
You...
People told me
not to talk about the Tuo God in Ninghu.
You'll lose your life. Be careful.
Can you get up?
Since no one is here,
I need to do another autopsy.
Come on.
Lu Lingfeng.
Look at his left hand.
There's a callus here.
Instead of  writing,
he should get his callus for holding a sword for years.
A swordsman with his left hand holding sword?
It's not strange.
Many martial artists
are practicing left-handed swords
to surprise their enemies.
It seems that
the victim is not Governor Li.
We can't jump to conclusions.
You and I have never met Governor Li.
How do you know he can't fight?
Lu Lingfeng.
Look at the back of his hand.
A birthmark!
Su Wuming!
Look at this!
It looks like something
for women's makeup.
Failed?
Where did you hire those two losers?
Chief Shen, calm down.
Both of them are capable.
They have never
failed before.
Li Yu's daughter is not difficult to deal with.
But we didn't expect
that the new Military Commander
would also be in the mourning hall.
Su Wuming?
Yes.
He's just a scholar.
You can just
kill him too!
He is a scholar.
But he has a subordinate,
who is quite powerful.
He has other subordinates?
Why have I never heard of it before?
Where are those two?
One died in the mourning hall,
and the other one I've already...
That's more like it.
Take some men
to the Chamber of Commerce and take Lu Yong to me.
Lu Yong?
He's very wary of us.
I'm afraid it's hard to catch him.
In Ninghu,
there are disciples of the Tuo God everywhere.
What's the use of his wary?
This is his place.
Don't bother talking when you see him.
Just tie him up and bring him to me.
Yes!
Greetings, Administrator Gu.
Minister Zeng is also here.
Commander Su,
you didn't sleep at all last night?
I ran into ghosts when I was keeping vigil last night.
How can I fall asleep after that?
Commander Su,
do you really believe that there are ghosts in this world?
I didn't believe it before.
But after I arrived at Ninghu,
I became more and more convinced.
Therefore,
Administrator Gu, please allow me
to help the Minister of Justice to catch ghosts.
Catch ghosts?
Administrator!
Administrator,
Cheif Shen of the Worshippers of Tuo God wishes to see you.
Please, let him in.
Chief Shen.
Administrator.
The murderer who killed the prefectural governor
has been caught by me.
I'll leave him to you.
Mr. Lu?
Did you mean that Mr. Lu
is the murderer of the prefectural governor?
What evidence do you have?
Lu Yong.
Who did you invite to the Yaoyue Restaurant
before Prefectural Governor Li was killed?
After it's done,
you will get one more.
Who do you want to kill?
Just say the name.
That's not right.
The coroner has examined the body.
Judging from the wound on his neck,
Governor Li
was indeed devoured by the giant alligator.
But now you're saying that
there was an assassin?
Commander Su,
do you believe the coroner's words
or the murderer's confession?
It was me who sent someone
to kill that bastard, Li Yu.
Now that I've succeeded,
I have nothing to hide.
I only want a quick death.
See? Did I force him?
How dare you, Lu Yong!
How dare you kill the prefectural governor of the city?
Li Yu and the Worshippers of Tuo God collaborated in evildoing!
He deserved to die.
How dare you!
Guards, put him on the death row!
-Yes. -Yes.
Gu Wenbin.
Where is the Records I gave you?
Are you in cahoots
with them too?
What records?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Take him away.
Gu Wenbin!
I trusted you as an imperial official!
I hoped that you could help the people of Ninghu!
I was so wrong! You'll be damned!
All of you will be damned!
Chief Shen.
Thank you.
Since the case is solved,
Chief Shen,
do you want to stay for a drink tonight?
I have to bring my people to collect taxes.
I don't have the time for a feast here.
Goodbye!
I'm really in a trance for now.
I can't even tell who is the official.
Commander Su,
you don't need to worry about it.
It is fine as long as
there are people who are willing to do the job,
and getting the job well done.
Commander Su and Minister Zeng,
do you want to stay for a drink?
Administrator Gu, I have a question.
What did Mr. Lu mean
about the Records?
I have no contact with him.
He's just barking nonsense.
Administrator!
I heard that people from the Worshippers of Tuo God
arrested Lu Yong.
Minister He, you are here.
Good news.
Lu Yong has admitted that
it was him who sent an assassin
to kill Governor Li.
Now that the case is solved,
Minister He,
stay for a celebration.
Celebration?
There's nothing to celebrate!
Lu Yong sent someone to assassinate the prefectural governor?
It doesn't match
the autopsy result at all.
Besides, when I was investigating the case,
I found out that Governor Li
had joined the Worshippers of Tuo God when he was alive.
So!
Since he had joined the group,
why would he be bitten to death by the alligator?
The fact that Lu Yong hired an assassin
is more believable.
What do you think, Commander Su?
Arresting criminal,
the Worshippers of Tuo God has done it for the city.
The request I made just now is to
assist the Minister of Justice in catching ghosts.
May I have your permission?
Before I became a commander,
I had always been a sheriff.
I dealt with criminal cases a lot,
which more or less gave me some experience.
Whatever. Do whatever you want.
Thank you, Administrator.
I see! Today's banquet
is not going to happen!
Commander Su,
do you think there are ghosts in Ninghu?
What do you think?
I think that
you can't believe about their presence,
but you also can't believe about their absence.
Minister Zeng is so wise.
[Ninghu Prison]
Please.
This is it, Commander.
You may leave.
Yes.
Lu Yong.
I'm the new Military Commander of Ninghu,
Su Wuming.
Cut the crap.
OK.
I'll cut to the chase.
Let me ask you a few questions.
You just need to answer yes or no.
Is the assassin you sent
a left-hander?
How did you know?
I just said,
you just need to answer yes or no.
Yes.
Xiao Qi is
a famous left-handed swordsman.
Second question.
He didn't come back
for the rest of the money, right?
Yes.
Third question.
There is a birthmark
on that swordsman's left hand.
Is it true or not?
But your target
is not an ordinary person.
After this,
you have to give me three more silver ingots.
Deal.
Yes.
There is a birthmark.
It's red.
I see.
Lu Yong.
You may not die.
I mean,
from the perspective of the law of Tang.
But if someone from the Worshippers of Tuo God wants to kill you,
I have no way to save you.
So,
you must show
your determination to die soon.
That way,
you'll be safer here.
Why should I trust you?
Because only I
can save you.
The headless corpse in the mansion is that assassin.
I agree with that.
But how can you be sure
that Governor Li is still in the mansion?
That's because I suddenly remembered
Yingtao said that
she saw her father's ghost
appeared.
There are no ghosts in this world.
It must be the Prefectural Governor himself.
Are you that sure?
That's because...
I saw
a figure too.
Tell me.
Where is the Prefectural Governor?
Don't bother with him.
He's a mute.
Why do I feel that
he can hear me?
Li Si,
you weren't born deaf-mute,
but mute later.
So you can hear us,
right?
Tell me.
Where is Li Yu?
I'm the new Military Commander here.
I'm not in a same group
with the Worshippers of Tuo God
who wanted to kill Governor Li.
You should trust me.
Stop pretending.
If Li Yu is not here,
why are you bringing food in here?
Li Si.
I know you are a loyal servant.
But what you did
put your master's safety
at risk.
You!
If you still won't tell us,
don't blame me for being ruthless.
Alligator!
Lu Lingfeng.
According to the Book of Things,
it has sharp hearing.
You can distract it with noises.
Couple of days ago, I was just thinking
if Lu Lingfeng came to Ninghu,
it would be great.
With his hot temper,
how could he stand aside
and see me
not having a sip of the Tuo God Wine?
I didn't expect that when he is here,
he almost died in the alligator's claw.
Why are you so full of crap!
You said that
it was Lu Yong who hired Xiao Qi
to assassinate in the mansion.
The latter was accidentally killed by the giant alligator.
But why did Li Yu
put his official robe on the assassin?
There is only one explanation.
Li Yu knew that
he is in great danger.
In order to survive,
he made use of this assassination.
But didn't he already
join the Worshippers of Tuo God？
Joining it
doesn't mean
he won't be a threat
to them.
It also doesn't mean
he will be safe.
Have you forgotten those two assassins?
They forced Yingtao
to hand over the Records of Worshippers of Tuo God.
You mean...
I guess
the Records of Worshippers of Tuo God
was written by Li Yu.
How can you be sure of that?
We have to find Yingtao.
I think you are
interested in that girl.
Nonsense!
She's the daughter of the prefectural governor
and is being hunted down.
I'm an official in Ninghu.
It's my duty to protect her.
She even knows how to use the ecstasy incense.
Does she really need protection from you, a weak scholar?
You!
I have always
doubted her identity.
Maybe her identity of the daughter of the prefectural governor
is fake.
If so,
she should have
ran away from Ninghu as soon as possible.
We'll know tomorrow
whether she is an imposter or not.
Tomorrow?
Yes.
The notice has been posted in the city.
They will bury Governor Li tomorrow.
If Yingtao comes,
she is the daughter of the Governor Li.
If she doesn't come, she's not.
This is a chance.
What chance?
A chance to see Yingtao.
That's for you, an official in Ninghu.
For me,
I have another plan.
Where are you going?
I've been here for days,
and I already have another place to stay.
Why don't you live in the Commander's Residence?
Yes.
Isn't it good
to continue to be your personal staff?
At least he provides food and wine for you.
Although Su Wuming is a bit stingy...
I, Lu Lingfeng,
live in the world,
not only for the food and wine.
It also depends on what type of wine and food.
For example,
the Tuo God Wine!
I think
he's just afraid of seeing Xijun.
What he said is not out of some heroic spirit,
he is just a coward.
I'm doing it for the people and myself.
And I don't need a burden
when I wander around the world in the future.
She
doesn't have to suffer
with me.
I heard
what you said.
You did it for me.
At first,
I can't live
in this world
without you.
Now I've found it.
And,
you left me
for my own good.
It's enough for me to know that we have each other in our hearts.
Go.
I will never pester you again.
In my opinion,
after today,
he will no longer be
that young boy of Chang'an anymore.
But you,
you're still that young boy,
Handsome Fed.
What do you mean?
Eavesdropping on the lovers' talks,
isn't it something only a kid would do?
I...
Master!
I didn't see anything.
Master. My lady.
C-Carry on.
My disciple, turn around.
I dare not.
It's not that I dare not.
It's that I shouldn't.
I came at a bad time.
My lady misses you so much.
Finally, you two...
But it was interrupted by me.
Xue Huan deserves the punishment.
Enough.
I tell you to turn around.
Otherwise,
you'll be expelled!
Xue Huan,
I'm not leaving.
I'm exhausted
from the fight with that giant alligator earlier.
I will now punish you
to boil some water for my feet
to relieve my fatigue.
Yes.
I accept my punishment.
♫The storm rises with no reason♫
♫In the night of illusions♫
♫I go into the maze♫
♫In a world of prosperity♫
♫A heart burns with obsession♫
♫With the darkness rising♫
♫I can't stop wandering through the night♫
♫With light in my heart, I'm not afraid of the storm♫
♫It's because of justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there is fog♫
♫Even if there are invisible waves♫
♫I'll tell the story of the fate♫
♫Tell the love of the world♫
♫For the memory of grace♫
♫And the resentment is not yet over♫
♫The rivers and mountains are immortal, the clouds are overturned♫
♫To be consoled by the truth, even with thorns on my back♫
♫Only for justice♫
♫That I seek a truth for this long, lonely night♫
♫The heaven and earth are held together by a strong will♫
♫The people are in peace♫
♫Carving right and wrong into a clear heart♫
♫The truth♫
♫Will reinterpret this justice♫
♫Even if there are a thousand sails, it's not a waste of time♫
♫What I am afraid of is the unrighted wrong♫
♫What is the meaning of life and death?♫
♫I'll paint the sunshine into the landscape♫
♫The spirit of righteousness♫
♫Exists for the one I care♫