♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 21=
Three.
Four.
Five.
(Rectitude, Prudence & Diligence)
(Justice Gives Birth to Wisdom)
My Lord.
About the moldy rice incident
you asked me to investigate into,
I've found a lead.
How did it go?
Is it serious?
I did what you said
and followed up the clue
we found in the rice shop.
It turns out that the barracks
are also plagued by moldy rice.
Luckily,
the problem is not as serious as
in the soup kitchen.
Some soldiers in the army
have diarrhea.
Luckily, for now,
there is no big problem.
(Book of Documents)
Soldiers are those
who defend the country
on the battlefield to death.
It is crazy for Ou family
to make money at the expense of
the health of the soldiers.
With their health compromised,
we would be sending these soldiers to die
on the battlefield.
That would be an offense to His Majesty.
Eunuch Feng.
Marquis.
I heard that you went to
the southeast for an inspection.
When did you come back?
Earlier this month.
Thank you for asking.
Come on.
Eunuch Feng,
Grand Secretary Chen was frowning
and seemed thoughtful.
Is there anything wrong
with politics?
Marquis,
you have no idea.
The rice for the military camps
was found to be moldy.
His Majesty was enraged
and has ordered Great Secretary Chen
to look into it.
(Marquis Jingyuan's Mansion)
Father,
today, Wang Zichuan of Ministry of Revenue
was suddenly arrested
and interrogated by Ministry of Justice.
Does this have to do with me?
Official Ou,
it was from the eunuch
that I got the news
of moldy rice
in the military camp.
Father, please forgive me.
About the moldy rice,
it was my fault.
But I never meant
to disrespect you.
Everything I have done
has been for our Ou family,
for you.
Tell me about your fault.
I'm not smart enough.
I told you
not to make any big move
unless you've got to be sure.
If you didn't sell moldy rice
to Xu Lingyi,
how could he follow up the clue
and find out
the problems
in the military food?
He knew about it?
I sold Vice Minister Wang out.
Because His Majesty
has asked Grand Secretary Chen
to look into this.
I made him
your scapegoat.
Father, please don't be mad.
Father, you're in charge of
military affairs in the southeast.
Building good relationship with those
who support sea ban policy
can be expensive.
I did this
because I want to help you.
You're so stupid.
Ministry of Revenue
has already been on Xu Lingyi's side.
You have no idea
what price I paid
to have Wang Zichuan planted
into the department.
After this,
Ministry of Revenue will treat us
as enemy.
Pick the brush up.
It has been a year
since Ou Yanxing left home.
We never heard from him.
Do you know where he went?
I have no idea.
I heard
that he was heading up north these days.
I think he will come back
to the capital soon.
Let me know
as soon as he gets back.
You are excused.
Aye, Father.
They look nice, don't they?
Absolutely.
I need you
to send these boxes separately
to the wife of Duke Ning,
the wife of Marquis Zhongshan
and the wife of Earl Zuo'an.
Tell them
that these are new arrivals
of Treasures Boutique.
They are welcome to have it.
Yes, Young Madam.
Dear, you're back.
What happened to you?
Is there anything wrong?
They knew about the moldy rice.
Well, Father...
I was trying to use it
to win his favor.
However,
I fell into Xu Lingyi's trap.
My plan almost got ruined.
You told me
that it went well.
Where did things
go wrong?
Xu Lingyi's wife
meddled in the affairs
and upset the apple cart.
She is the illegitimate daughter
of the Luo family.
What can she do?
On the day of disaster relief
in the soup chicken,
if it weren't for her,
Xu family would not have made it
till Xu Lingyi's return.
Xu Lingyi got suspicious
and traced the source of moldy rice
to the military camp.
If it weren't for father
who decisively made his spy
in the Ministry of Revenue
the scapegoat,
the stakes would be high.
Hearing what you said,
I would like to meet
the wife of Marquis Yongping.
Father
also mentioned Yanxing.
Why is this illegitimate son
always on father's mind?
He couldn't care less
about our family.
He would spend his days traveling around.
Speaking of his career,
he does nothing
but some unpresentable businesses.
I just don't get it.
Father just favors him.
In the capital,
I'm the only eldest son
of a duke's legal wife
who is not appointed the heir.
Our family business is rooted
in the Ministry of War.
However, father sent me
to the Ministry of Rites.
Tell me.
Tell me why.
Dear,
as far as I'm concerned,
there is no need to worry about it.
Perhaps father
is using him
to sharpen your ability.
As for the appointment of the heir,
your father will after all
consider my father's feeling.
He won't appoint him the heir.
Dear,
now I can only
count on you
and your father.
My Lord.
You're back, My Lord.
You have a lot of work to do.
Please take care.
I will leave you to it.
Shiyi.
Ou family is behind
the issue of the moldy rice.
Oh.
You knew about it.
Well...
We also found
that the moldy rice came
from the military camp.
Ou family was crazy enough
to embezzle army provisions.
His Majesty knew about it
and was enraged.
Marquis Jingyuan had to
wipe out his henchmen
in order to avoid punishment.
That's great.
This is not only about political dispute.
On a personal level,
you're protecting
Xu family.
On a greater level,
you're assisting His Majesty
in his clean-up.
This is going to matter to the whole country.
Refugees in the capital
are not settled yet.
Some may take advantage of the chaos.
You went out a lot these days.
Did you ever get into trouble?
No, I didn't run into any trouble.
Thank you for asking.
Given the fact that
you went out frequently,
you may need Wan Daxian,
who is good at martial arts,
to be your body guard.
In case of emergency,
he can protect you.
My Lord, that sounds nice.
I will consider it.
(Why is His Lordship)
(saying this to me?)
(Did he know)
(that I went to Xianling Pavilion?)
(If I tell him the truth,)
(what will he do?)
My Lord, actually, I...
My Lord.
Greetings, My Lord.
Greetings, Your Ladyship.
I was visiting Great Madam.
My Lord,
I need to talk to you about something.
Perhaps I should leave, My Lord.
My Lord,
do you know
what day it is?
So, what's the occasion?
It seems you forgot it.
Today is my birthday.
My apologies.
I've prepared a delicious meal.
My Lord,
please come tonight.
I'm afraid you'll eat by yourself.
My Lord.
My Lord, it has been two years
since we got married.
I have always been alone in this house,
feeling lonely.
I wasn't meant to bother you.
But today,
when I visited Great Madam,
she mentioned
that today is my birthday,
and that I should
invite you to dinner.
That's why I...
(For them,)
(you are the only one they can rely on.)
(You can't always turn
a cold shoulder to them.)
All right.
That's great.
I shall begin making
arrangements at once.
I will be waiting for you tonight, My Lord.
Okay.
Come, come.
Nanny,
His Lordship spent about an hour
in Concubine Qiao's room before he left.
What now?
Has His Lordship gone to Her Ladyship?
His Lordship has returned to Banyuepan.
What is going on?
A while back,
His Lordship and Her Ladyship
were getting close.
How come
they are drifting apart these days?
Qiao Lianfang, that witch
must be playing the saboteur.
What's more,
there has been no news from Amber.
If things keep going this way...
What if...
What if she was pregnant
with His Lordship's baby...
Then...
No way, no way.
We must
let Madam Luo know about this.
That's right.
Madam Luo should know about this.
Today I skirted around the issue.
But Shiyi still would not tell.
I'm not an unreasonable person.
Even if she tells me the truth,
I will never stop her
from teaching embroidery
at Xianling Pavilion.
But why is she unwilling
to tell me the truth?
My Lord,
it happened many days ago.
You are still going over that.
Are you making fun of me?
I don't think I have the guts.
My Lord,
to go in another direction,
you may understand
why Her Ladyship kept
the truth from you.
To go in another direction?
Why would you
not let Her Ladyship know
that you already knew about it?
If you are worried about
what Her Ladyship thought,
you can have a talk with her.
I am not well-educated.
I don't know much.
But I'm pretty sure about one thing.
My Lord, if you want to understand
Her Ladyship better,
you should open
your heart first.
Otherwise,
there's always
an unbreakable wall
standing between you and Her Ladyship.
It seems you got plenty of them.
Yep.
I'll leave it here.
Sure.
Nanny Tao,
what brings you here?
Where is Dongqing?
She is in Her Ladyship's room.
Are you looking for her?
Not really.
I came to you.
Madam Luo
asked me
to give this to you.
This is...
This is my sister's embroidery.
Did Madam Luo find my sister?
How is she?
Madam Luo wanted me to tell you
that you must bear her words in mind
if you want to
meet your sister again.
His Lordship doesn't like Shiyi much.
She needs someone
to help her win the heart of His Lordship.
What would Madam Luo
want me to do?
Now you are
playing dumb?
At the very beginning,
you were sent by Madam Luo
to His Lordship,
don't you know that?
But how could we do this
to Her Ladyship?
This is not the time
to worry about others.
What matters most is
the interests of Luo family
and your sister's safety.
Do you understand?
Amber?
Dongqing.
What are you doing here?
Don't slack off.
Her Ladyship wanted you
to deliver these drawings to Master Jian.
Okay.
Master Jian,
this is the new pattern
designed by Her Ladyship.
Please check it out.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
This is my duty.
Amber,
please wait a moment.
Here you are.
This is...
Just open it.
Shiyi
always thinks of you.
She often says
that you have come to the age
to marry a good man.
She has been preparing
your dowry.
Look,
she spared some time
to make a pair of
embroidered shoes for you.
Check if you like it.
Come.
Thank you, Master Jian.
Watch out.
Mr. Lin.
Amber.
You're here.
Where is Lady Luo?
She is not here today.
You look pale.
Are you ill?
What happened?
I'm fine.
I don't think so.
You seem about to cry.
If you want to talk about your feelings,
I'm here.
Mr. Lin, thank you for asking.
Actually,
it is about my sister.
Your sister?
What's up with her?
My parents died when I was a child.
It was my sister who brought me up.
It was always just the two of us.
Then I got sick,
and she sold herself to slavery
in order to get
the money for my treatment.
And nothing has been known
about her ever since.
I don't know where she is
and if she is well.
I don't know
when we can meet again.
Hey, don't cry.
Do you have any clue
about your sister?
I have many friends.
I might be able to help you with that.
My sister was sold
to a rich family.
Perhaps
she has changed her name.
There has been no clue.
Sometimes I feel
that there is nothing I wouldn't do
as long as I get to see her again.
I won't regret
even if
I'll have to betray my heart.
It is normal for us
to miss our close kin.
I understand that.
But I don't think you will do that.
No matter what,
you will stay true to yourself.
Mr. Lin...
I just got a string of prayer beads
from Baiyun Temple.
It is believed to bring people
good luck and happiness.
I'll give it to you.
May you find your sister soon.
Mr. Lin,
I can't accept
a gift this precious.
This is not expensive.
May you find inner peace.
(Virtue of Modesty and Patience)
Your Ladyship,
I've been wanting
to say this for a while.
It pains me
to keep it to myself.
What are you trying to say?
I remember
how I thought of you
as someone like Lady Erniang
when Madam Luo
sent me to serve you.
However,
it turns out that you are
so smart, kind, forgiving
and admirable.
Tonight,
you said so many good things about me.
Are you asking me to lend you money?
Your Ladyship,
there is one thing that I don't understand.
Why would you
let you guard down with me
all the while knowing
that I work for Madam Luo?
Have a seat.
This mansion
may look fancy.
However, people living in it
may have their own miseries.
I let down my guard with you
because I know
that you are a good girl.
And that you never plot against me.
That's why
I want to protect you.
Your Ladyship,
I must have done great things
in my past life
to meet someone like you.
You're a good person.
I will be punished if I ever do
something harmful to you.
Amber,
is there anything wrong?
What happened to you?
Perhaps the cold wind
made me feel ill.
In that case,
you don't need to accompany me
to Xianling Pavilion tomorrow.
Stay at home and have a good rest.
Don't make your cold worse.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You have been so nice to me.
I am really touched.
Your Ladyship, you're going to
Xianling Pavilion tomorrow morning.
You might want to have an early night.
I should leave.
Dear sister...
(Mansion of Xu)
My Lord.
Amber?
What are you doing here?
Her Ladyship asked me
to send some chicken soup to you, My Lord.
Just leave it there.
Anything else?
My Lord,
you might want to drink it while it's hot.
I'll do it myself.
My Lord,
are you tired?
Do you want me
to rub your shoulders?
You...
Did Her Ladyship ask you
to send the soup?
Not really.
Her Ladyship does not know about it.
I came here myself.
Whatever you ask me to do,
I will
do it.
Get out of here.
Zhaoying.
My Lord.
Send Amber back.
Hand her over to Shiyi
when she is back.
Amber, please go with me.
Your Ladyship...
What's wrong?
Does His Lordship not like the soup?
What's going on here?
I got soup
on my clothes
when I was cooking.
I got changed.
I asked Amber to deliver the soup
before it gets cold.
This is my workplace.
It is not a place
where everyone has access to.
Next time, you are expected
to deliver it yourself.
Those who don't obey the rule
shall be got rid of.
I need her.
And I would hate to dismiss her.
You need her?
Amber is a smart and
thoughtful girl.
I don't need to tell her my thoughts.
Yet she understands me.
How could I live without her?
I'm sorry for what happened just now.
Amber,
apologize to His Lordship.
My Lord, please forgive me.
I was being impolite.
All right.
This is not happening again.
You're excused.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
My Lord, sorry for interrupting your work.
Have a taste of the soup, My Lord.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship...
Your Ladyship, how could you know...
What you said yesterday
and your illness this morning
made me suspicious.
Dongqing told me
that Nanny Tao went to you yesterday.
I thought about it
and figured that Madam Luo
was about to make her move.
Your Ladyship,
I got separated from my sister
when I was a child.
Madam Luo is the only person
who knows where my sister is.
I have no choice
but to follow her words.
You should have told me.
I couldn't.
I was afraid that Madam Luo
would harm my sister.
Your Ladyship,
I never wanted to
betray you.
Of course,
I know you didn't mean it.
You won't dress like this
if you really have an ulterior purpose.
Today,
you are more plainly dressed than usual.
You don't even wear your hairpins.
And
you look pale.
Should I keep going?
Your Ladyship,
if I really want to seduce His Lordship,
it will cause great harm to you
no matter I succeed or not.
You have been so nice to me.
I can never do this to you.
So,
you pretended to
have followed Madam Luo's words.
But you were actually
planning to disgruntle His Lordship
and get kicked out of the mansion.
That way, you did it
without offending Madam Luo
or betraying me.
Am I right?
You're a good person.
In my life,
besides my sister,
no one has treated me as you do.
So,
Your Ladyship,
I will never hurt you.
So, what are you going to do now?
If you really want to leave here,
I can help you.
But it would really mean a lot for me
if you stay.
Your Ladyship,
through this,
I realized
what I should do.
From now on,
no matter I get to meet
my sister again or not,
I will be true to my heart.
I will not be threatened by anyone.
I trust you, Your Ladyship.
From now on,
I will be loyal to you.
Hey, don't kneel down.
I said it before.
I said
that you two
are more than maids to me.
From now on, we will support each other.
No matter what,
we will never betray each other.
Never betray each other.
It turns out
Amber has her own reasons.
I never trusted her before.
I was wrong about her.
She is a poor girl.
We should help her.
Ask old servants back home
about her sister.
Maybe we can get some clues.
Remember,
be careful.
Madam Luo can't know about it.
I know.
By the way,
it turns out His Lordship
is a perfect gentleman.
I think His Lordship loves you only.
Come on.
It seems you make everything
about His Lordship.
I got it right.
I used to think of His Lordship
as a lecherous person
because he had affairs with Concubine Qiao.
It has been a while
since we lived in Mansion of Xu.
Let alone Concubine Qiao,
His Lordship barely visits Concubine Wen
and Concubine Qin.
It seems
His Lordship is a little bit callous.
Don't you say that.
Aloof as he is,
His Lordship is not a callous person.
He is just not into
domestic dissention.
As far as I'm concerned,
you know His Lordship
better than anyone else does.
He gave me his heart,
and I would give him mine.
(Xianling Pavilion)
The wife of Marquis Zhongshan
will be holding a banquet three days later.
Ladies in the capital
are all invited.
For this banquet,
Shiyi,
I want you to go with me.
I want to take this opportunity
to introduce you to others.
Sure.
Mrs. Du.
This is
female guest registry
for the banquet.
I want you to memorize it.
Yes, Mother.
This is your first time
to attend such an occasion
as the matron of Xu family.
Remember,
behave appropriately.
Those ladies
have sharp eyes.
Sure, Mother.
I will work on it.
That's right.
You are all excused.
Yes.
Mrs. Du,
Shiyi seemed to be calm,
with no trace of pride or panic.
It was Lianfang
who disappointed me today.
Great Madam,
let's not jump to the conclusion yet.
We should
see what will happen.
(Marquis Zhongshan's Mansion)
This way, please.
Great Madam Xu, you're here.
Great Madam Xu.
Welcome, welcome.
Madam Tang,
you've met her.
This is my fourth daughter-in-law.
Greetings, Madam Tang.
Greetings, Madam Xu.
Let's get inside.
There are all my friends inside.
Let's go.
Great Madam Xu, you're here.
Great Madam Zheng.
Greetings, ladies.
Let me introduce
my fourth daughter-in-law to you.
It has been so long.
Your daughter-in-law
has become even more gorgeous.
It seems
your mansion is a good place to live.
I owe it all
to Mother
who has treated me nicely
and helped me out.
Great Madam Zheng,
you look as radiant as ever.
It seems the Duke's Mansion
is an even better place to live.
Exactly.
Mother
is getting prettier
day by day.
Now I see why.
You are making fun of me,
aren't you?
All right.
Let's get inside.
Come on, let's go.
This way, please.
The madam over there
is the wife of Minister Zhou
of Ministry of Rites.
She is talking
to her daughter,
who is the wife of Ou Lixing,
the eldest son of the legal wife
of Ou family.
Be careful
when you talk to her.
Yes, Mother.
His Lordship told me
about the relationship
between Ou and Xu families.
All right.
I will be talking
with my old friends.
I was talking about
a beauty over there.
Young Madam Ou, it turns out
you are that beauty.
That's right.
You look so stunning today.
I couldn't resist
staring at you.
Thank you for saying that.
You must be Madam Xu.
Greetings, Young Madam Ou.
I heard that Madam Xu
is good at
running the house,
and taking good care
of Xu family.
I do admire that.
Meeting you today,
I find Madam Xu
is a young lady.
Young Madam Ou, you're giving me
far more credit than I deserve.
I was just handling
family affairs.
Isn't Marquis Yongping's mansion amazing?
It has been a while since we last met.
Shiyi, your aura
has even changed.
Greetings, Erniang.
This is the wife of Wang Yu,
the heir of Duke Mao.
She is also a daughter of Luo family.
You'd think
she is the daughter
of someone's legal wife.
Look at the flower blossoms.
I heard that Young Madam Ou
is a connoisseur
who knows a lot
about flowers and plants.
Would you give me a few pointers?
Young Madam Wang,
you do me too much honor.
I'm not an expert in the field.
I just know a thing or two about it.
Look at this flower.
It is scarlet,
with numerous layers of petals.
This is...
Madam Xu,
I believe you know
what the flower is.
It is a very rare color.
Madam,
do you think
you are more knowledgeable
than the wife
of Marquis Yongping?
Great Madam, should we...
Young Madam Ou,
I beg to differ.
Everyone has his own
strengths and weaknesses.
Nobody is omniscient.
It is just a flower.
What difference does it make
if I don't know its type?
Even if I know, does it
make me superior to others?
It turns out that
being the wife of Marquis Yongping
makes no change
to one's lowness and shallowness.
You're pathetically ignorant.
Don't refer to yourself
as the daughter of Luo family.
As far as I'm concerned,
one brings shame to the family
when she plays against
her own family members.
Erniang.
Madam Xu,
I beg to differ.
We should admit our ignorance.
How could you
sugarcoat it?
Is it what you learned
from Xu family?
People can always learn from each other.
Confucius did not feel ashamed
to ask the two kids
when he saw their debate.
If we don't know something,
we can always ask.
It is not something to be ashamed of.
Now I see.
Madam Xu, you're
comparing yourself to a saint.
Young Madam Ou, I'm no match for you
when it comes to
taking things out of context.
Why not admit that
you don't know this flower?
Why keep beating around the bush?
In spring, there are
peach and plum blossoms.
The scent of cymbidium comes with wind.
The redder the flower is,
the more precious the cymbidium is.
Though the color is rare,
the flower is not unique
to prestigious families.
It can also be found in merchant families.
It is nothing but an ornament.
I know its type, but what's the point?
Merchant families?
How can you mention
our family and merchant families
in the same breath?
Red cymbidium is rare.
But people with ulterior motivations
are not rare.
Orchid is a noble plant.
Not everyone is qualified
to comment on it.
If it falls into
the filthy hands,
its nobleness
will be defiled.
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪