♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 29=
My ancestors.
Yi'er's father
and brother died too soon.
He started to shoulder
the Xu family's heavy burdens
at a young age.
He bears too much pressure
for the prosperity of the Xu family.
My ancestors,
if you hear me in heaven,
please protect Yi'er.
I hope he'll return soon.
Great Madam.
Clues have been found
to the assassination attempt
against His Lordship.
What did you say?
Great Madam.
I've brought her here.
Concubine Wen.
Were you with Lingyi
when the assassin attacked him?
I wasn't with him
when the assassin attacked him.
But someone
saw you and Concubine Qin
send Lingyi back
on the day of the assassination attempt.
We happened
to find His Lordship injured.
So we helped him home.
Is that so?
Bring her in.
Great Madam.
(Has she confessed?)
Each of you gives a different statement.
You're obviously lying.
Tell the truth now
or I'll punish you
according to the family rules.
Great Madam.
Spare me, Great Madam.
Great Madam, the truth is...
-Actually.
-Great Madam...
Great Madam, I'll tell you.
It's Her Ladyship.
Her Ladyship used
a pair of scissors to stab
His Lordship at Xianling Pavilion.
Shiyi?
It seems
they told the truth.
You stabbed Lingyi.
I am guilty.
Please punish me.
Did Lingyi treat you badly?
How could you hurt him cruelly?
He treated me affectionately.
I was unfair to him.
Please punish me.
I won't have any complaints.
If they hadn't told me
the truth,
would you've continued
to keep it from me?
I don't understand
why Lingyi
concealed the truth for you.
Since you care about him,
why did you...
Why did you say nothing?
Why did you let him
risk his life?
I failed him.
If anything bad
happens to Lingyi
because of your doing,
I will never forgive you.
Why?
Why did you do this?
Why did you...
Great Madam.
Is there any news about Lingyi?
News broke from the disaster-hit area.
Someone saw that
His Lordship died in a fire
to save the civilians.
Great Madam. Great Madam.
Mother.
-Your Ladyship.
-Great Madam.
-Mother.
-Great Madam. Wake up.
-Great Madam.
Great Madam.
-Mother.
(Meandering Path)
(Secluded Place)
Your Ladyship.
Did he just say
His Lordship died?
Your Ladyship.
-Your Ladyship.
Lingyi is a great martial artist.
He couldn't have died in a fire.
There must be something wrong.
The Ou familyhas had operations
in Shandong for so many years.
He must have killed Lingyi.
I'll settle accounts with him right now.
-Lingkuan.
-Stop.
The situation is unclear yet.
If His Lordship really died,
then the whole family depends on you.
If misfortune strikes you
as well,
what will happen to the Xu family?
Lingkuan.
I know
you and His Lordship
love each other as brothers.
But you need to think for the benefits
of me and the baby.
I'm useless.
I know someone murdered Lingyi.
But I can't do anything.
Yi'er.
Great Madam.
-Mother.
Is my Yi'er
really gone?
Will he never
come back?
My Yi'er
worked so hard
for his country and family.
But he didn't
even get to see his family
before his death.
Why didn't I...
Why didn't I stop him?
Mother.
The situation is still unclear.
Maybe the news is fake.
Don't grieve so much.
Take care of yourself.
This is all Luo Shiyi's fault.
My son was a great martial artist.
If she hadn't stabbed him,
he wouldn't have died in a fire.
Where is Shiyi?
Go.
Bring her to me.
Mother.
Please don't be emotional.
Calm down, alright?
She conspired with our enemy
and showed her heartless nature.
She is not to be tolerated.
I want her to pay
for his death with her life.
Mother.
I'm also mad at Shiyi
for stabbing Lingyi.
But I know her well enough
to assert that she would never
maliciously conspire with our enemy.
There must be something wrong.
Mother.
Don't do anything impulsive.
Yeah, Mother.
I know you want Shiyi
to pay with her life,
but you can't accuse her
of conspiring with our enemy
without any evidence.
How will we explain things
to the Luo family?
Explain?
The Luo family should
explain things to me.
Every generation of the Xu family
serves in the military.
Family rules are
as serious as military rules.
She injured the head of the family,
which is like killing
the commander before a battle.
I want her to pay
for his death with her life.
Your Ladyship,
what are you doing?
He survived the perilous battlefield
and came back.
I don't believe he died like this.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, calm down.
Your Ladyship,
Shandong is so far from us.
You can't just head there
as a woman.
I must see for myself.
I don't believe he is dead.
But if His Lordship really died,
his body will be sent back
before long.
I don't believe it.
-Your Ladyship.
Shiyi.
You must leave as soon as possible.
Mother broke down
after she learned of His Lordship's death.
She wants you to pay
for his death with your life.
She can't solely blame Her Ladyship
for the death of His Lordship.
Mother has lost
her husband and her son.
She barely survived those tragedies.
Now she is old,
she can't take
another loss.
It's inevitable that
she'll take extreme measures.
Shiyi,
since His Lordship covered up your action,
I'm sure
there's an explanation for it.
Right now, Mother has lost
her head.
You need to leave
and hide out.
Dongqing, the Divorce Agreement.
Once we show Great Madam
the Divorce Agreement,
she won't be able
to punish you.
Now I see.
His Lordship must have
foreseen this.
So he wrote a Divorce Agreement
(Divorce Agreement)
to protect you.
You're saying His Lordship
wrote a Divorce Agreement
before he left?
Why did you keep it?
I told you to burn it down.
Your Ladyship!
The Divorce Agreement is the only thing
that can save you right now.
Save me?
If he comes back,
he can do whatever he wants.
But if he doesn't come back,
I won't live without him.
Burn it down.
Bring Shiyi out.
Mother.
We haven't got to
the bottom of this matter.
We can't make any rash decision.
It is a fact that Shiyi
stabbed the head of the family.
I'm following the family rules.
What's rash about it?
I don't need your opinion
on this matter.
Luo Shiyi,
are you convinced?
I treated His Lordship unfairly.
I deserve punishment.
Unfairly?
Lingyi loved you so much.
But you stabbed him.
You even got him killed.
I want you to apologize to him
by dying.
Do you need me to take your life?
Great Madam.
Mother.
I know my crime is serious.
I deserve something
even worse than death.
But I don't believe he is dead
when I haven't
seen his body.
Please give me
some time,
so I can see him return.
If he is alive,
allow me to repent and apologize to him.
Then you can punish or kill me.
If he is dead,
I'll kill myself
beside his coffin
to apologize.
You don't deserve it.
You don't deserve to see him again.
Mother,
she is right.
Currently, little information about
the situation in Shandong is available.
We don't know what happened.
We mustn't make any decision
before we see His Lordship's body.
Let's wait
for a while.
We can decide how to deal with her
when we've confirmed the news.
Mother,
I know
the news of Lingyi's death
broke your heart.
But no matter how angry you are,
please show mercy
for Zhun's sake.
Do you want him
to lose his mother again?
I'll let you
live for a few more days.
Mrs Du,
escort Luo Shiyi
to the farm in the countryside.
Tell the steward of the farm
that she'll live
in a servant's condition.
Mother.
She stabbed Lingyi.
If you help her secretly,
then you are against the Xu family.
What did you say?
The Marquis died in a fire?
Is it true?
The news came from Shandong.
I don't know if it's true.
I am going to visit the Xu family
and inquire about this tomorrow.
There must be some truth to this rumor.
How is your sister Shiyi?
Shiyi and the Marquis love each other.
If the Marquis is dead,
then I'm afraid
she won't take the loss well.
The Marquis is the backbone
of the Xu family.
If he is dead,
the Xu family will collapse.
Father,
my mother is not in good health.
I plan to keep this from her,
so she won't worry about this.
You need to visit the Xu family often
these days.
Help them with everything you've got
if you can.
The Luo family and the Xu family
are in-laws.
If the Xu family collapses,
our family won't stay strong.
Yes, Father.
What's the matter?
Didn't you eat?
Whatever.
You've changed a lot
these days.
I'm delighted.
I heard that
Xu Lingyi had an accident.
He is high-ranking and powerful.
What could happen to him?
It's said he had an accident
when he was inspecting
the situation in Shandong.
It seems that he is dead.
Xu Lingyi is dead?
Some people relied on the Xu family
to assume airs.
I'd like to see
how they end up
after his death.
If not for Xu Lingyi's influence,
I wouldn't have tolerated you
in the past few days.
Young Madam.
Did you hear that?
He only treated me nicely
in fear of Xu Lingyi.
I was so foolish
that I thought he'd changed.
Young Madam.
Come on.
My stomach hurts so much.
Young Madam.
Servants! Servants!
Is my daughter-in-law truly pregnant?
Physician, are you sure?
Her pulse does indicate pregnancy.
Physician,
my stomach hurt badly earlier.
My baby...
Your pulse shows
that your baby
was already feeble
before you got hurt
and experienced
severe pregnancy complications.
I'm not completely confident
that I can help her keep the baby.
Physician,
I'll pay
any price
to keep the baby
she is carrying.
Don't worry, Madam Wang.
I'll do my best.
You're all here.
Come on. Drink with me.
Mother.
Why did you slap me?
You bastard.
You almost killed
your own child.
You can't let Her Ladyship live here.
Your Ladyship.
I'm executing Great Madam's order.
It's fine.
The room is nice.
Who are you?
I'm the assistant steward of the farm,
Wang Jinzhong.
I manage the internal affairs.
The chief steward is too busy
to come today.
So he asked me
to take care of you.
If you need anything,
just tell me.
Thank you.
Don't waste time
on them.
She is the matron of Xu family,
yet she has been sent here.
We were ordered
to treat her like a servant.
She must have
done the Xu family wrong.
No need
to be nice to her.
Yes.
I'll do
as you say.
This place is filthy.
It's not a place
worthy of Her Ladyship.
Her Ladyship is in a bad mood.
Let's not cause her trouble.
Focus
on getting the work done.
I wonder
where Wan Daxian is
when we're working.
Why isn't he helping us?
I told Wan Daxian to gather information
about the situation in Shandong.
I hope he'll bring good news.
♪I trimmed the wicks
the memory kept me awake at night♪
♪It was late into the night
I started missing you again♪
♪I closed my eyes♪
♪I thought of the old days♪
♪The past whispered in my ear
but you couldn't hear it♪
♪I got something on my mind, my thoughts
were stitched into my embroidery♪
♪The bright moon made me think of you♪
♪I really missed the old days♪
(Mansion of Xu)
♪Our destinies♪
♪Were entwined
we were doomed to separate♪
(We've married for long.)
(I thought)
(Divorce Agreement)
(we loved each other)
(and understood each other.)
(But it turns out)
(it was all my wishful thinking)
(and imagination.)
♪But you never heard
my prayer♪
♪We fell in love with each other
again and again♪
♪We missed each other again and again♪
♪Flowers bloom every year
our relationship didn't work out♪
You've finished your work?
Your Ladyship,
how about you take a rest?
You've been embroidering
for a long time.
What if your eyesight gets damaged?
Yeah.
This oil lamp's light is so dim.
You're going to damage your eyesight.
It's fine.
I just want
to finish this embroidery of
Bodhisattva portrait soon
to bring her blessing to His Lordship.
Amber,
fetch me
the threads for Bodhisattva's hair.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship.
We've run out of threads.
Great.
Since we've run out of threads,
she can't do any more
embroidery tonight.
She'll have to rest early.
Your Ladyship.
Go to bed now.
I'll find the assistant steward
and ask him
to get us some threads
tomorrow morning.
Alright.
I'll listen to you
and stop embroidering now.
Amber, hurry up.
Alright.
Wait.
Your Ladyship.
Maybe this will do.
Hold it for me.
I heard from Master Jian that
people have been using hair
to do embroidery
since the Era of Shengyuan
in the Tang Dynasty.
But
I've never tried it before.
I wonder if this will work.
Let me give it a try.
It worked.
Look.
Nice.
This looks even more realistic
than the threads.
Right?
Any news from Steward Bai?
Don't worry, Mother.
He is on the way.
I'm sure he will
bring back news soon.
I hope they will
bring back good news.
Yizhen.
You'll take charge of the affairs
of the Xu family from tomorrow
and manage the household.
We must not
panic.
Here is an idea.
Make an inventory
of our lands and shops right away.
Yes, Mother.
I'll make preparations.
Mother,
if Lingyi
really is dead...
Shut up.
Mother.
If he really is dead,
the Ou familywon't let us off.
The Xu family is in danger.
We...
What should we do?
Kuan'er,
why are you so scared?
Mother.
I'm not scared.
I'm just worried.
If your brother
never comes back,
then you are the head of the Xu family.
You need to figure out
a way to support this family
because the women and the children
can't shelter you.
Mother,
these things never crossed my mind
when Lingyi was here.
Son,
misfortune once
struck the Xu family.
Your father and brother died suddenly.
Then Lingyi
joined the army at a young age
to protect the family.
He risked his life on the battlefield.
He barely escaped death.
He was even younger than you are now
at that time.
But he single-handedly supported
the whole Xu family.
Did you ever see him
hesitate or frighten?
I'm useless.
I've disappointed you.
Kuan'er,
you might never
be brave and decisive as Lingyi.
But you
must not lose
the Xu family's spirit.
No matter what awaits us,
the Xu family cannot
lose its backbone.
Keep it in mind.
(Firmiana Rain
written by Bai Pu)
(The Oil Seller and the Song Girl
Volume I)
Let heaven be the witness
to my vow:
I'll never engage
in operas again.
If Lingyi is dead,
then I'll go out of my way
to protect the Xu family.
Father,
now that Xu Lingyi is dead
and the other officials
at the Ministry of Revenue
don't have much influence,
our crisis in Shandong is over.
We can
blame Xu Lingyi
for our people's
misdeeds in Shandong.
Xu Lingyi...
Is Xu Lingyi really dead?
Rest easy, Father.
My people
saw Xu Lingyi's scorched body
for confirmation.
There was no mistake.
This is the wolf tally.
Take it.
It can order
our secret followers in Shandong
and help you do things.
You've completed your task well
this time.
But don't be impatient.
You still need to act
cautiously in the future.
Thank you for trusting me, Father.
I'll keep your advice
in mind.
I won't let you down.
You may go.
Yes, Father.
Mr. Ou.
I have bad news.
Shiyi has gone missing.
Missing?
Why has she gone missing?
I just went to the Mansion of Xu
to see Shiyi.
But the servants said
Shiyi offended Great Madam.
So Great Madam
sent her away in a carriage.
I asked where she was sent.
But they knew nothing.
No.
The Xu family must have found out
that Shiyi had stabbed Marquis Yongping
after he died.
They did this to punish Shiyi.
Did you say Marquis Yongping died?
Is it true?
I heard it on the grapevine.
I didn't believe it
until I went home and verified it.
I came here
out of worry for Shiyi.
That's bad.
That means
Shiyi is really in danger
this time.
Take it easy.
Marquis Yongping is gone.
But we can protect her.
I'll gather my people
to search for her.
I'll make sure she stays safe.
Alright.
Then I'll trust you
with this matter.
Don't worry.
I won't let harm come to her.
Keep her safe, please.
Your Ladyship.
That chief steward
asserts his superior's authority
to torture you in every way.
Maybe we should quit
and leave.
No.
If I leave now,
we'll never get to return
to the Xu family.
I can't leave.
Your Ladyship.
How about you take a rest?
You've done so much work.
Don't tire yourself out.
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
I can hold on.
Let's hurry up
and get the job done.
Who is that?
Stop!
Is anyone there?
Help!
Dongqing!
Dongqing, did you hear
any sounds?
Help!
I think that's Her Ladyship's voice.
Your Ladyship?
Dongqing! Amber!
Your Ladyship!
Are you alright?
What happened?
I can't believe a thief
lurks on this shabby farm.
Oh, no.
Your Ladyship.
Nothing is lost.
He couldn't have been a thief.
A thief
would have stolen stuff.
Besides,
he pushed Her Ladyship into a well.
He obviously wanted her dead.
Your Ladyship,
did you see
the face of the person
who pushed you into the well?
He pushed me from behind.
I didn't see him clearly.
But why did he try to kill me?
Anyway, we must be more careful
from now on.
Your Ladyship, we should tell
the chief steward about this.
I don't think telling him
would change anything.
Her Ladyship is right.
The chief steward
is black-hearted.
He works for Great Madam.
Maybe
he pushed Her Ladyship into the well.
Dongqing,
we mustn't stay away
from Her Ladyship in the future.
We mustn't
let that person succeed again.
This place?
Are you sure this is the place?
How come you still haven't
finished washing these few clothes?
Chief steward,
an accident happened...
-So...
-There was no accident.
You've just been slacking off.
You can't even finish
this small amount of work in time.
No wonder Great Madam
kicked you out.
Be clear that
this is not
a place of comfort.
Chief steward,
if I'm not mistaken,
you're in charge
of the fields, hills and forests.
The assistant steward
should be in charge
of the internal affairs.
I...
I'm the chief steward.
Of course I have the right
to manage
the assistant steward's affairs.
Assistant steward,
is that true?
The chief steward is right.
Although I manage this house,
the chief steward manages
the whole farm,
including me.
You heard him.
By the way,
your punishment is to fill
all the water tanks on this farm today.
You're going too far, I'm warning you.
I'll come and check
the water tanks tomorrow.
If you fail to fill them,
I'll continue to punish you.
You...
Dongqing.
Let me do it.
We've been working for so long.
When can it be done?
You must be exhausted.
Let's get inside and rest.
Drink some water
before we come out again.
Alright.
Come on.
Your Ladyship.
I'll just have a little nap.
Your Ladyship, I'll have a little nap too.
Thank you for working so hard.
I can't go on, Young Master.
I'm exhausted.
We've never done
this kind of heavy physical work.
No.
We must finish the work
before she wakes up.
Alright.
Hurry up.
Dongqing.
Amber.
Wake up.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, look.
All the tanks are full.
This is amazing, Your Ladyship.
I just checked all the water tanks
on the farm.
All of them are full.
I got it.
The immortals in heaven
must have frowned upon them
for bullying you.
So the immortals
filled the tanks overnight for us.
That must be the thing.
I think so.
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪