♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 13=
Nanny Xu.
Yes.
Slap her!
Yes!
You are in the Xu Family
and not in your Luo Family.
You think you are strong enough
to disobey me?
Don't forget
who has lifted you,
the daughter of a concubine
to a high position.
You both got a point,
mother and Nanny Tao.
If I had showed
more solicitude for Zhun,
his illness
wouldn't have worsened so much.
Mother, please set your mind at rest.
From now on,
I will take care of Zhun
and protect him wholeheartedly
to make sure that no harm
will be done to him.
Whether you said this
sincerely or perfunctorily,
there is one thing that
you must bear in mind:
Only our Luo Family
can back you up as your root.
Let me escort you out, Mother.
Take good care of Zhun.
Amber.
Your Ladyship.
How is it?
I have searched
Zhun's abode thoroughly,
but didn't find
any exopathogen.
But, please don't worry.
I have sent men
to search the outer courtyard.
They will surely find the
source of the illness.
Those are all the things
Zhun can come into contact
with in ordinary days.
He was sound and fine previously.
But he is ill now
and the exopathogen
remains unknown.
Yu.
Come here.
Amber, go do your business.
Yes.
Mother.
I heard that Zhun relapsed again.
How is he now?
Don't worry.
With your father and grandma here,
he will be fine.
Would you like to go in to pay a visit?
I'd better leave.
Yu.
(Virtue of Modesty and Patience)
My Lord.
How is he?
He has been sleeping
since he took the medicine.
Mother.
Zhun.
-Mother.
-Zhun, you are a good boy.
You are a good boy, Zhun.
-I am here.
-Mother.
I am here. I am here.
Mother.
Zhun, are you feeling unwell?
I am with you.
-Don't cry. Don't cry.
-Mother.
Would you like me to sing you a song?
I will ask someone to
send for Imperial Physician Liu.
It doesn't matter.
Don't worry, My Lord.
Imperial Physician Liu said that
Zhun would be
like this during nighttime.
This is normal.
-Mother.
-My sweetheart Zhun.
Mother.
You are a good boy, Zhun.
I will sing you a song.
♪There is a rooster.♪
♪It can fly.♪
♪It has been bought
with three copper coins.♪
♪It has been brought here from Sichuan.♪
♪Here is a rooster. It can fly♪
♪It has been bought
with three copper coins♪
♪It has been brought here from Sichuan♪
♪Its feathers are in all colors♪
♪And they vary in length♪
♪It has been dipped in the liquor♪
♪It is really rare♪
My Lord.
I fell asleep out of carelessness.
You have been attending to
Zhun for days on end
without any rest.
You must be tired.
It's nothing.
My Lord, won't you go to court today?
I asked for leave yesterday.
Zhun.
What is wrong?
Are you feeling unwell anywhere?
Why are you sweating so much?
How come this happened suddenly?
Attendants!
My Lord.
Hurry, hurry to send for
the imperial physician.
Yes, My Lord.
-Dongqing, go fetch some water.
-Yes.
It's all right. It's all right.
Zhun.
You will be all right.
Are you feeling any better?
Handwrite...
What?
Handwriting.
Handwriting?
Are you trying to say that
you want to show your father
the handwriting you completed yesterday?
Your father has heard it.
He said he was very happy.
♪There is a rooster♪
♪It can fly♪
♪It has been bought
with three copper coins♪
♪It has brought here from Sichuan♪
♪Its feathers are in all colors♪
♪And they vary in length♪
My Lord,
here comes the imperial physician.
How is he, physician?
Your Lordship, Your Ladyship.
Zhun's illness has worsened.
I have to perform acupuncture
on him immediately
to treat him.
May I ask you to wait outside?
Please save him, physician.
Don't worry, My Lord.
Zhun is much blessed.
He will be recoverd for sure.
Zhun's handwriting is so beautiful.
It can be seen that
he has put a lot of work into it.
After he wakes up,
you must praise him decently.
It is true that
I am usually too strict with him.
Zhun can understand
why you are doing that.
He has never blamed you for that.
We all understand you, too.
Zhun is your first-born legitimate son.
He is meant to take over
great responsibility.
For this reason,
you have been
especially strict with him.
But I have forgotten that
he is only a kid
who has lost his mother.
After Zhun gets well,
you must make it up to him, My Lord.
Great Madam is here.
Greetings to you, Mother.
Shiyi.
Thank you for your hard work
all these days.
Before Zhun gets well,
you shall stay in Western Lateral Court
and shall not walk around at will.
Mrs Du.
Carry Zhun to the Fushou Court.
Mother.
Why are you doing this?
Don't ask more about it.
I will take good care of Zhun.
Mother.
I don't know what happened
to make you do this.
But, could you please
allow Zhun to stay here
till he gets well?
I am doing this
for the sake of Zhun.
Mother.
This time, you must
give me a reason.
I just came back from the Ci'an Temple.
The divination stick says that
Shiyi
is Zhun's nemesis.
The Nemesis.
So they must be separated.
Here comes the superstition again.
It is nonsense.
How can Shiyi
be blamed for this?
It is so unfair to her.
There is no such thing.
Lingyi.
The imperial physician will treat
Zhun over there.
Even if Shiyi is not with him,
it will make no difference.
Even if I am muddled-headed
and the divination is untrustworthy,
as the matron of our Xu Family,
it is reasonable for Shiyi
to make some sacrifice, isn't it?
What should I say to you?
I know
you are an atheist
and stick to impartiality
in doing things.
But you must remember that
besides being a father, a son,
an older brother and a husband,
you are also the master of our
Xu Family in the first place.
To have offspring
is the most important matter
of our Xu Family.
Remember it.
I don't agree.
To use such kind of made-up nonsense
as an excuse again
for putting Shiyi under house arrest.
Just do what mother said.
My Lord, don't worry about me.
I will take good care of myself.
(Fortune)
As for the Ci'an Temple...
Set your mind at rest, Madam.
I ensure that nothing will go wrong
and nobody will track it back to us.
(Virtue of Purity and Nobility)
You are back.
I heard that Zhun is ill.
Is his illness serious?
It is said that Physician Liu
of the Imperial Hospital
has been called over.
Since Zhun is ill,
it must be hard for Shiyi
to live in the Mansion of Xu.
I'll go visit her.
What are you looking for?
I can't go without any gift.
You are really a pedant.
Where is our available money?
What happened?
Yan Zhixiao is going to take up his
post somewhere else.
I treated him to some wine
in Chunxi Restaurant.
You dined there again?
You have visited that restaurant
many times this month.
How could we manage to live our life
if you keep doing this?
Wuniang,
I know
Zhixiao is definitely not
an average person.
When he makes his way
in the world someday,
he will surely be helpful for me.
I tried to befriend him
for the sake of our future.
We can't only think about saving money.
Wuniang, anger is not
good for your health.
I dare not do it again, OK?
Yeah, money should be spent
on some occasions.
But you have to consider
how we can live our life.
We don't have other sources of income.
If we don't live frugally,
how could we manage to make ends meet?
Wuniang, I have considered
all these things you said.
But I think that now
we should try to broaden our
sources of income
instead of reducing our expenditure.
I found that
there are few dried fruit shops
in the capital.
A storefront in the West Street
happens to be vacant.
We'd better purchase it.
Easier said than done.
We need capital to run our own shop.
How can we raise the fund?
Aren't you going to the Mansion of Xu
to visit Zhun?
You can take the chance to
mention it to Shiyi
that we are willing to
enter into partnership
with her to do business.
With the help from the Xu Family,
we will achieve success naturally.
You have a point there.
Well, if so,
it will be more improper
for me to go empty-handed.
That will be a great disgrace.
I still have the bird's nest
as part of my dowry.
Maybe I should take it
with me as a gift.
Wuniang,
you have done so much for our family.
It is fine as long as you know it.
You must work hard in your study.
When you pass the imperial exam
and obtain official rank one day,
all our efforts
will be worthwhile.
Right.
I will try my best to pass the exam
as early as possible.
By then,
I will let you live the best life
and won't allow you to bother
about anything.
As you said,
subject to the ancestral policy,
Duke Wei can't be persuaded
for the time being.
Then, how should we
deal with the current situation?
We need to bide our time.
Now Marquis Jingyuan is
in his prime of power
and the sea ban policy
is deeply-rooted.
If we are anxious for success,
we will make ourselves vulnerable
to other's attacks.
Your words made sense, My Lord.
All along, the adherents of
Marquis Jingyuan
have been engaged
in many corrupt practices.
We only need to be patient
to find their weak points.
Then we will undermine their power.
Given enough time,
I am sure we will be able
to uproot his force.
To date, the Ou Family
hasn't decided on an Heir Apparent.
Ou Lixing
is not more astute and scheming
than Marquis Jingyuan.
He is also anxious
to butter up Marquis Jingyuan.
This will give us a chance.
Rest assured, My Lord.
I will send men
to keep watching Ou Lixing.
Mother. Mother.
Yu,
did they give you a hard time
knowing you would come here?
Don't worry, Mother.
They didn't notice that
I sneaked in.
You slippery boy!
Dongqing, go fetch the pastries.
Come, Yu, be seated.
Well, Mother.
Previously, you told me
to keep an eye on Zhun, right?
Now I know
where Zhun goes secretly
for play in normal days.
Tell me.
Do you know
where Zhun usually goes for play,
especially the place he
visits secretly for play?
No, I don't know.
Since Zhun fell ill,
Concubine Qiao has been
taking care of him.
So I seldom had the chance to see him.
Yu,
could you
do me a favor?
What can I do for you, Mother?
I want you to find out
the place Zhun visited for play
in the several days before he fell ill.
But you must
keep this matter between us
and mustn't let others know
including Concubine Wen.
Could you promise me?
The garden.
The dog.
I have seen Zhun
stay in the garden alone several times.
But I didn't pay close attention
to that back then.
After you mentioned it to me,
I especially went to check the garden.
I saw that at the corner of the garden,
there is a dog raised by someone.
I saw Xiuyuan herself
feed the dog.
Xiuyuan?
Yu.
I have something to do.
You could take the pastries and leave.
OK?
Thank you, Mother.
Look after your health, Mother.
Allow me to take leave now.
OK.
Let's go.
Garden.
Give the things to me.
(Singing Orioles on the Drooping willows)
I am here to see Shiyi.
Why have you brought me here?
Now Concubine Qiao is in charge
of the family affairs.
If you want to visit Her Ladyship,
you have to ask for
Concubine Qiao's permission first.
Go inside.
Let's go.
I am here to visit Shiyi.
I am her fifth sister.
You Luo sisters
are really close.
Her Ladyship has just been grounded.
Then you came to visit her.
My sister has been grounded?
What for?
Are these for Her Ladyship?
We can hand them over to Her Ladyship.
Xiuyuan, take them.
These are for Shiyi.
How could you be qualified
to hand them over?
I want to see my sister Shiyi in person.
It is not proper for Her Ladyship
to see any outsider now.
Please leave.
I haven't seen her in person.
How could you know it is not proper?
Where is the Marquis?
I want to see and
ask him to reason things out.
How can your Xu Family
treat a guest like this?
What did you say?
Madam.
If His Lordship comes to know this,
I am afraid he will be angry.
Madam, please come with me.
That's more like it.
So, Your Ladyship,
you have asked Yu to make investigations
about where Zhun went for play.
That's because you have
got suspicious, right?
Zhun has been taken good care
of by so many people.
But he still relapsed time and again.
It is really odd.
If we had made investigations rashly,
I am afraid we would not
have been able to
find anything.
Yu actually cares a lot about Zhun.
Besides,
nobody will guard against a child.
So I have entrusted Yu
with the investigation.
Well, as expected,
Yu didn't let you down.
Now the most important thing
is to find the cause of Zhun's illness.
Then Zhun can be lifted out of danger.
But now you are grounded.
You can't go out.
What should we start our
investigation with?
Shiyi.
Wuniang.
I brought you some bird's nest.
Hurry.
Thank you, sister.
Take a seat, please.
OK.
I heard that Zhun got ill.
So I came to pay a visit.
After I arrived here,
I was told that you had been grounded.
What happened exactly?
It is a long story.
Wuniang.
Could you please do me a favor?
(Rites)
Come on.
Come on, eat more.
When was this dog
placed here?
Have you
brought Zhun here frequently?
I will go take care of Zhun.
Don't leave. Let's get this straight.
Someone, come here!
Stop!
Her Ladyship has escaped.
The Great Madam has given
the strict order
to forbid you to go out.
Take her back where she was.
Chase her!
My Lord!
Shiyi.
I have found the exopathogen
that caused Zhun to fall ill.
My Lord.
This dog also has tinea.
If Zhun
has come into contact
with this dog frequently,
the dog must have passed
the exopathogen
to him.
Great Madam,
someone with evil intentions
must have encouraged Zhun
to play with the dog.
I am to blame for being careless.
I should have paid more
attention to this.
Xiuyuan.
Tell me what happened exactly.
Great Madam, um...
Great Madam,
I gave the dog to Zhun.
It has been kept in the garden
so that Zhun could come to play with it.
But I really don't know that
it has been carrying
the exopathogen.
Now Concubine Qiao
is absolving herself from
all the responsibility.
As I see it, you have tried to
do harm to Zhun purposefully.
Then you shifted the blame for this
onto Her Ladyship.
Dongqing,
how could you behave so rudely?
It is of excellent quality
and is flawless.
Thank you, Mrs Zhou.
This is from Concubine Qiao.
Please thank her on behalf of me.
I am fond of Zhun so much.
I don't have the heart to harm him.
I saw that
Zhun lost his mother
and looked lonely,
so I gave the dog to him
to keep him company.
There is no way for me to know
it has contracted the exopathogen.
Moreover,
Xiuyuan and I also
played with and fed the dog every day.
But we are both all right.
Great Madam, My Lord,
please believe me.
Well, imperial physician,
could you find out
where the exopathogen on the dog's hair
came from?
All things in this world reinforce
and neutralize each other.
I can't give a clear explanation.
Well,
according to Imperial Physician Liu,
Zhun contracted the disease by accident.
Since you don't feel guilty,
why haven't you mentioned it?
And why have you chased
Shiyi in the mansion?
My Lord, I am wronged.
I never mentioned it
because I really didn't realize that
this matter has anything to do
with Zhun's disease.
I chased...
I chased Her Ladyship
because I was afraid that the dog
might bite her.
My Lord,
I swear that
I did all things
without any wicked intentions.
Lingyi,
I have watched Lianfang
since her childhood.
If anyone says she meant to harm Zhun,
I won't believe.
Great Madam.
My Lord.
Though
I didn't do this intentionally,
I must say that
I caused Zhun
to fall ill.
And I put Zhun through
such great suffering.
I have
committed a great sin
and I can't make amends
even if I die 100 times.
If...
If Zhun can't get well,
I won't stay alive.
Enough.
Don't say ominous words about death.
Zhun will recover from illness.
Xiuyuan, help her stand up.
Imperial Physician Liu,
since the cause of illness
has been tracked down,
Zhun can be cured, right?
Zhun has been ill for quite a while
and he has relapsed repeatedly.
So, I am not sure
whether he can tide over this crisis.
(Virtue of Modesty and Patience)
♪There is a rooster♪
♪It can fly♪
♪It has been bought
with three copper coins♪
♪It has been brought here from Sichuan♪
♪There is a rooster. It can fly♪
♪It has been bought
with three copper coins♪
♪It has been brought here from Sichuan♪
♪Its feathers are in all colors♪
♪And they vary in length♪
♪It has been dipped in the liquor♪
♪It is really rare♪
May Buddha bless Zhun with
the power to pull through!
Madam, please eat something.
Take it away.
It's all right.
I brought it in secretly.
Nobody saw me.
Even if I was seen,
it will be all right.
Her Ladyship
went out
while she was grounded.
But Great Madam and His Lordship
didn't hold her accountable.
Shut up!
This is different from that.
Why are you still not getting it?
Her Ladyship didn't resist
when she was grounded
because she wanted me to
let my guard down.
Now,
if I can't
make Great Madam and His Lordship
stop suspecting me completely,
I will have no place to put my feet on
in the Xu Family.
Take it away.
Yes, Madam.
May Buddha bless Zhun
with the power to pull through!
Auntie.
Zhun regained consciousness.
Imperial Physician Liu, Zhun came round.
Hurry!
Hurry to check upon him.
I will go notify Great Madam.
Since Zhun came around,
there is nothing serious with him now.
He will get well
as long as he rests
quietly to recuperate.
Thank you, Imperial Physician Liu.
I will prescribe some other
medication for Zhun.
Your Ladyship,
please make Zhun take it as instructed.
I will.
Dongqing, take Imperial Physician Liu
to fetch the medication.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
You are fine now, my darling Zhun.
The physician said that you got well.
Auntie.
Have you been attending to me
every night these days?
How come you know that?
I heard you singing, auntie.
It is a song that
my mother often sang to me.
Auntie, your hair is so messy
and looks so ugly.
Little brat!
You talked nonsense upon waking up.
I will go tell your father
and ask him to teach you a lesson.
Mother, I said the wrong words.
Don't tell on me in front of father.
I heard Zhun talk.
Zhun came around at last.
Handwriting.
Zhun, your handwriting
has improved a lot.
Good job!
I will find a couple of practice sheets
suitable for you.
Thank you, father.
Zhun has just come around.
His body is still weak.
We'd better not disturb him
and allow him to have a good rest.
Yizhen is right.
We...
Something bad happened, Great Madam.
Concubine Qiao passed out.
Hurry to tell me what happened.
Concubine Qiao thinks that she
committed a great sin.
So over the last few days,
she has been praying for
Zhun in the Buddha Hall.
To show her sincerity,
she has been fasting and
sleepless all these days
only hoping that the
Goddess of Mercy Guanyin
could bless Zhun.
Well, it is very thoughtful of her
to have been praying for Zhun.
Hurry to rise to your feet.
Go take care of her.
Yes, Great Madam.
Lingyi.
As you can see,
Lianfang has been praying sincerely
for Zhun's sake
and she has got her
body hurt due to fast.
Should you go visit her?
I hope that she really
deserves the love from you, Mother.
Hurry to go visit her.
The imperial physician has said that
Zhun's illness
has nothing to do with Lianfang.
Since the exopathogen has been found
and Lianfang is in bad health,
I will entrust you
to take care of Zhun.
Yes, Mother.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to eat something?
Madam.
His Lordship is here to visit you.
Hurry to help me stand up to dress up.
Greetings to you, My Lord.
You are not feeling well.
Forego these formalities.
It doesn't matter.
Thank you, My Lord.
Over the last few days,
you have been praying for Zhun.
That's really very thoughtful of you.
As long as Zhun can recover from illness
and as long as I can share your burden,
it will be worthwhile for me to do it.
If the fast and prayer can
cure a disease,
what do we need physicians for?
Are you still blaming me, My Lord?
If I had known that
the dog would cause Zhun to fall ill,
surely I would not have given it
to Zhun as a gift.
I was wrong in this matter.
I am willing to accept any punishment.
I only hope that
you can forgive me, My Lord.
Lingyi.
Since Zhun has been out of danger,
I won't carry this matter further.
I won't continue to pursue this matter.
But Mother has a lot of
trust in you all along.
For so many years,
she has been treating you
as her own daughter.
Don't make her sad again.
Do you understand?
Thank you for trusting me, My Lord.
Know your place and
conduct yourself well.
Where is Mrs Liu?
She...
She didn't do her job well
and offended Her Ladyship.
So I drove her out.
It is said that
she has returned to her home
in the countryside.
Back to the countryside?
Where does she come from?
It is said that she comes from Shandong.
About the specific location,
I have no idea.
Madam, you see now that
His Lordship loves you dearly.
Upon hearing that you passed out,
he hurried to come to check upon you.
Mrs Zhang.
His Lordship asked about
Mrs Liu suddenly.
Do you think that
he has found out something?
Madam.
Don't get yourself scared.
We have paid Mrs Liu
so much money.
She has been long gone from the capital.
Even I don't know her whereabouts.
Madam, don't worry.
Nobody will find out this matter.
Maybe I am just getting paranoid.
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪