♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 36=
(Duke Mao's Mansion)
What on earth
were you doing?
Did you really have to make
her furious
when she was already like that?
Wuniang,
a potent drug is needed
while one's seriously sick.
Alright. Let me take you back.
Let's go.
(Duke Mao's Mansion)
Very well.
No one would care about her again.
When she's dead,
the entire Wang family
will belong to me and my son.
(Unrivaled Beauty with Heavenly Aroma)
Amber.
Get someone to keep an eye
on the Wang family.
Let me know if there's anything.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Given what you just said,
I think you've known
what I'm going to do.
I don't dare
to take a guess of your thoughts.
I just thought
that when someone plays nice,
the other should use threats.
I think Your Ladyship
just wanted to provoke Lady Erniang.
With Your Ladyship's personality,
of course you won't leave her alone.
You know me so well.
Your Ladyship.
Mr. Lin is here.
Mr. Ou.
(Qifu Tea House)
Please enjoy.
I've always wanted
to apologize to you.
Because of me, you had to
withdraw from Xianling Pavilion.
Sorry I caused you the trouble.
Our business is getting busier.
I was going to quit anyway.
Madam Xu, you don't have to feel
sorry for that.
By the way,
when I was at Xianling Pavilion
and checking the account
with Master Jian,
she told me
that you seldom went there lately.
Is there anything happened at home?
Nothing happened at home.
It's just that Erniang...
Young Madam Wang?
I've also heard of it.
Speaking of that,
our Ou family
has something to do with it.
I'm really sorry.
It's not your fault.
You don't need to apologize.
Actually, ever since Wang Yu died,
Erniang has been having
a difficult life in the Wang family.
She's a strong woman
and she wouldn't accept our help.
She's also seriously ill.
Is she seriously ill?
Has she seen a physician?
Don't know what kind of
physician the Wang family found for her.
She's been taking medicine,
but her condition
hasn't got any better.
I found a physician for her,
but she refused to see him.
The other problems can be fixed.
But when it comes to treatment,
it needs her cooperation.
Don't worry about that.
As long as she takes medicine,
it can be solved.
You have an idea?
(Virtue of Modesty and Patience)
Ou Yanxing's idea is good.
If Erniang is willing to take medicine,
she will get better.
I was going to discuss it
with you first.
But I bumped into
Mr. Ou on my way home,
so I had a chat with him.
My Lord, if you think it's okay,
I'll do it.
Erniang treats you so badly,
yet you still care about her this much.
You've never blamed her?
I have.
But we are sisters after all.
And she's a poor woman.
I don't want her
to be bullied by others.
It's the luckiest thing
for Erniang
that she has
a good sister like you.
My Lord, am I good
at everything in your eyes?
I guess.
It's not bad at least.
Your Ladyship.
Lady Shiyi.
Jinlian.
I call you over today
to ask you one question.
Do you want to save your Young Madam?
I'm willing to do anything
to save her.
Luckily, Erniang has you by her side.
Jinlian.
I'm about to die.
But I'm worried about you
the most.
Just leave this troubled place.
No one can protect you anymore
after I'm dead.
I won't leave.
Young Madam,
I have medicine here.
You will get better
after taking this.
Medicine?
What medicine?
I... I met a roving physician
on the street.
He gave me a secret prescription
specially for your illness.
There's no such secret prescription.
Jinlian,
no need to bother.
At this point,
just let it be.
Young Madam,
don't you remember
how Lady Shiyi
laughed at you?
She said you were a coward
who complained all the time.
If you give up like this,
she will get her way.
Are you really
going to let her look down
upon you?
What did you say?
Young Madam.
If you gave up
like this,
you would
completely lose
to Lady Shiyi.
Do you want that to happen?
As long as you get better,
you'll still have a long way to go.
And one day,
you will make those people
who despise you
pay for what they did.
Young Madam,
please don't give up.
Young Madam.
You are right.
I can't let them look down upon me.
No matter what,
I have to give it a try.
I can't let Shiyi
laugh at me.
The medicine.
Give me the medicine.
Here, Young Madam.
(Duke Mao's Mansion)
Here.
This roving physician
is really good.
You've only taken the medicine
for a few days
and you've already
got much better.
They all want me to be dead.
But I must get better.
When I'm well again,
I'll kick
that woman out for sure.
How come
there's no one is this yard?
Young Madam,
you just got a little better.
If that Lady Wang-Liu finds it out,
she'll harm you again.
Now, hurry to lie down.
Greetings, Young Madam.
I'm just here to see
if you are getting any better.
Young Madam's condition
is worsening day by day.
And now,
she can't even speak.
Madam, please be kind
and find another
physician for Young Madam.
Young Madam's condition
keeps worsening.
Even the best physician
won't be able to save her.
Just
take good care
of her.
Here.
(Precious Breezes and Dew of the Moon)
Looks like she doesn't
have much time left.
Keep a close eye on her.
Don't make any mistakes.
Yes.
When the Superior Man eats,
he does not try to stuff himself;
at rest he does not seek perfect comfort;
he is diligent in his work
and careful in speech.
Tell me.
Have you forgotten
the things you've learned?
But Confucius also said,
food and beautiful things
are basic human desires.
Eating is a basic need for human beings.
It's just your excuse.
That's not what Confucius meant at all.
Who taught you that?
Mother.
Nonsense.
Your mother wouldn't misinterpret
Confucius' words.
Mother.
My Lord.
Why are you angry again?
I'm not angry.
Master Zhao has been waiting
for him to go to the class,
but he's messing around here.
My Lord,
Zhun is still a kid.
It's normal that he likes playing.
A kid who likes playing
is usually smart.
He skipped classes
for two and a half days
when he's supposed to study
for three days.
Does that sound smart to you?
Master Zhao is going to
leave out of anger.
What do you think we should do?
My Lord,
why don't we let Yu and Zhun
study together?
For one,
Yu is older than Zhun.
He can be a good example for him.
For two,
Yu's teacher Master Kong
hasn't been available for long
because his mother is ill.
We can't let Yu fall behind
in his study.
If they go to school together,
they can keep each other's company.
Yu,
would you like
to study together with your brother?
Yes, I would.
I will study hard
and I will encourage
my brother to do so.
Now, rise.
In the future, you two
will study together.
I will let Concubine Wen know.
Yes, Father.
I don't agree
with you two.
Although we can't let Yu
fall behind in his study,
Yu and Zhun have different status.
They should be taught separately
so that they can both learn
what they need.
Otherwise, if we put them together,
it'll cause a lot of trouble
in the future.
Think about it.
So many brothers of prominent families
fought each other
to the point that
their families got destroyed.
You should learn from those lessons.
Mother.
Cao Cao attached more importance
to Cao Zhi than Cao Pi,
that's why Cao Zhi came up with
the Seven-step Poem.
If Cao Cao had treated them equally,
Zhi and Pi would've had
a firm tie of brotherhood
and built a strong bond.
If they had worked together as a team,
the Wei Dynasty
would've had a promising future.
I understand
that because you are
an illegitimate daughter,
you think the kids
should be treated equally.
But these are the rules
set by our ancestors.
There must be a reason for that.
It's not that simple.
Mother, you are right.
But just because
I had similar experience,
I understand more
that the conflict between siblings
is not because they have
different status,
but because of
the lack of communication.
So you mean
I'm wrong,
or the rules are wrong?
Mother.
It's actually my idea.
Zhun likes to play.
Yu, on the other hand,
is diligent in study.
If they can
study together,
Yu can be a good example
for Zhun,
which will only do good to Zhun.
Since you've made
a decision,
I won't interfere anymore.
Mother,
you are the pillar
of our Xu family.
That's right, Mother.
You watched
all the children growing up.
There are so many things I don't know
and I still need to learn from you.
Shiyi,
you've done an excellent job.
You don't need
an old woman like me
to teach you anymore.
I'm still inexperienced.
The bridges you've crossed are even more
than the paths we've walked.
How can I compare to you, Mother?
Alright.
Let's start eating.
You two are echoing
each other's words,
which is even more interesting
than the play I watched.
Here.
(Virtue of Modesty and Patience)
Yu is gentle and kind.
He looks more like a scholar.
I think taking the imperial exams
will be suitable for him.
My Lord, you spent most of the time
on the battlefields.
You don't know your kids
well enough yet.
Now that you've been transferred back,
you can talk to them more
when you have time.
I think they'll surprise you.
Yu is not a little kid anymore.
I can't let him study
with Zhun all the time.
I'm going
to send him to the Jinxi Academy
in Leshan next year.
Next year?
Yu is only ten years old,
and you'll send him to such a far place
to study?
An uncut gem goes not sparkle.
Besides, Master Jiang
in the Jinxi Academy
is well-known for his wisdom
and characters
among the scholars.
Ambitious men should aim far.
Studying there will help him
open his eyes
and broaden his mind.
It'll do nothing bad but only good
to his future.
That makes sense, My Lord.
Actually,
I also have other concerns.
What concerns?
The Wen family do business
on the coast all the year round.
They must have some
sort of business connection
with the Ou family.
Concubine Wen
has been restless since she
married into our Xu family,
which makes me
a little confused.
My Lord, you still suspect
that Concubine Wen
is the informer of the Ou family?
I'm not sure.
But I can't rule
that possibility out either.
So you want to send
Yu away
in case he's used.
Madam,
Yu is such a great kid.
Although he's asked to
study together with Zhun,
everybody can see
that our Yu
is much more diligent than Zhun.
Of course.
If my Yu weren't this
outstanding,
His Lordship wouldn't
value him this much.
Our Yu
is just as good as the others.
He deserves it.
Since His Lordship
thinks so highly of Yu,
I need to seize the opportunity
and find him a wife from a noble family
so as to secure his position.
Madam,
then you should talk to Second Madam.
She's from a prominent family
and has many connections.
Most importantly,
she likes our Yu.
I'm sure she'll be willing to help.
That makes sense.
It's better to do it sooner than later.
Come on, we'll go right now.
Yu,
do you have a plan for your future?
My teacher taught me
that ambitious men should travel more,
see more and learn more.
I'm a slow learner.
I can't fight battles
and make military exploits
like father did.
But I want to create
a future of my own.
I want to study hard and strive
for scholarly honor
to win glory for our Xu family.
Good.
That's quite an aspiration.
Then
is it okay for you if I send you
to Jinxi Academy in Leshan
Sichuan province to study?
What's wrong?
You don't want to go?
I don't mean that.
Master Jiang of Jinxi Academy
was once a top scholar.
He left the court to engage himself
in teaching.
No one can compare to him
in terms of characters and knowledge.
I've admired him for a long time.
Good.
I'm very glad
that you have such ambition.
When you arrive at the Academy,
you've got
to study hard
and must not be slack.
I won't let you down.
Please rise.
Master Zhao is still waiting for you.
Go ahead.
I'll take my leave.
My Lord, Second Madam is here.
Let her in.
My Lord, sorry to bother you.
Never mind.
You seldom come to Banyuepan.
What brought you here today?
I heard that you are going to send Yu
to Jinxi Academy.
There's something
I don't know if I should tell you.
Please go ahead.
Concubine Wen came to me yesterday
and asked me to be Yu's matchmaker.
Concubine Wen
saw that I've been paying
attention to Yu recently,
so she has some other thoughts.
No matter what, Yu's marriage
should be arranged by Shiyi.
Since she came to me,
I think she knows
that you wouldn't agree.
You are indeed insightful.
Concubine Wen
is after all a businessman's daughter.
My Lord, since you've made a decision,
you'd better have Yu
get ready for his trip soon,
in case Concubine Wen
gets in the way of his study.
Okay.
Your Ladyship, Concubine Wen is here.
Your Ladyship. I'm begging you.
Please don't sent Yu to Leshan.
Please.
Get up first.
Your Ladyship.
I assure you
that Yu is a good boy
and he'll be
as filial as Zhun to you
in the future.
He's been
seeing you as his own mother.
Your Ladyship, please.
Don't send him away.
It's so inappropriate.
Amber, Dongqing.
Help Concubine Wen to get up.
Sit down and let's talk.
Why do you not want Yu
to go to Leshan?
Yu is too young.
Gan Luo became a Prime Minister
when he was 12.
Grand Secretary Chen
passed the imperial exams
when he was 11.
Yu is not young anymore.
But
Leshan is too far.
I don't want him to leave me.
Ambitious men should aim far.
They can't be kept in the room
like girls.
Otherwise,
how can he
protect you in the future?
But...
Does Yu know
that you came here?
He doesn't.
The teacher Jiang Song in Jinxi Academy
was once a top scholar.
It's a rare opportunity for Yu
to have such a famous teacher.
You should've
talked to Yu first before you came here.
My Lord.
It's my decision
to send Yu to Jinxi Academy.
My Lord.
As parents,
we should put
our children's future first.
Are you really going
to take care of him for a lifetime?
The decision has been made.
You need not to worry.
And don't bother Yizhen anymore.
Yes.
It's must be Shiyi.
She saw that His Lordship
attached importance to my Yu,
so she wants to send him away.
She thinks she won.
I won't give up easily.
Concubine Wen acted like that
because she's worried.
After all, her son will travel to
such a far place.
Parents all hope their children
can stay with them.
But Yu
is also my son.
She claimed that she cares about him.
I'm just afraid that she'd
actually ruin his future
in the name of doing right by him.
The Longjing tea harvested
before Qingming smells so good.
And it's the right temperature
to drink it
My Lord, would you like to taste it?
General Fu,
why did you ignore me?
I didn't.
What's wrong with your neck?
What are you doing?
I strained it when I trained.
Let me give you a massage.
You don't have to.
Are you mimicking me?
Does this medicine work?
His Lordship gave it to me.
Of course it works.
But I think
my method will work better.
What method?
What's the matter with you?
Did... Did it hurt that badly?
That badly?
Why don't you sit down and try it?
I'll pass.
No way.
Let... Let go of me.
You are such a bully.
My neck is not hurt anymore.
Her Ladyship was looking for you.
Where have you been?
I...
I went to collect the clothes.
Where are the clothes?
Gosh. The clothes.
Isn't it His Lordship's medicine?
(Why does Dongqing have it?)
(Honor the Ancestors
and Benefit the Offspring)
Congrats, Young Madam.
You are recovered.
Thanks
to your attentive care,
I'm finally recovered.
Lady Shiyi,
you've done so much
to help Young Madam.
Why don't you tell her what you did?
Do you think
she'll still accept it
if she knows that I'm the one
who's helping her?
Don't worry.
Just do as I said.
Erniang will be saved.
Young Madam, you've been
very nice to me.
Even when you were seriously ill,
you still cared so much about me.
It's my duty to take good care of you.
Now that I've got back on my feet,
I'll take everything
that belongs to me back.
That Lady Wang-Liu
has been waiting for
the news of my death.
Go out now and tell them
that I've got better
under your care,
and that I'll be well soon.
Yes.
I'll let everybody know
that I'm the matron of Wang family.
Madam, what do you need me for?
I still need
to take care of Young Madam.
(Honor the Ancestors
and Benefit the Offspring)
Jinlian,
you are old enough
to get married now.
We no longer need you
to take care of Young Madam.
What do you mean?
In the future,
you will belong to this man.
I'm the only one who
cares about you now.
Young Madam has just
got a little better,
and you are going to kick me out.
You can't wait
for her to die, can you?
You are just a maid.
How dare you show disrespect
to your master?
Slap her.
(Precious Breezes and Dew of the Moon)
Who said you were a master?
Mr. Huang,
this maid
will belong to you in the future.
Take her away.
Thank you, Madam.
Young Lady.
Young Lady, go home with me.
I am...
I will take good care of you.
-I...
-Stop it.
Let's go.
(Precious Breezes and Dew of the Moon)
(Honor the Ancestors
and Benefit the Offspring)
Young... Young Madam.
You've recovered?
What?
Does my recovery
disappoint you?
No.
That's not what I meant.
Lady Wang-Liu,
you are only an outsider who temporarily
helps me manage
the household when I was ill.
Yet you are blinded by your greed.
Not only have you replaced
the servants,
you've also violated the rules
and were going to sell my dowry maid
to a stranger.
Just on that alone,
I can have you punished by law.
Guards.
Send Lady Wang-Liu and this guy
to Shuntian Prefecture Office.
Yes.
Don't. Don't. Don't.
No.
Don't. Please don't.
Are you crazy?
Don't. Don't.
Have... have you forgot
who recruited you
into the Wang family,
and who paid you monthly allowance?
Lady Wang-Liu,
just save it.
They've become my people long time ago.
You...
Young Madam.
I have nothing to do with it.
I... I was deceived by her.
Mr. Huang,
what nonsense are you talking about?
Fine.
Then I'll let you go
after you write a statement.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I'll... I'll write it.
I promise.
My son.
Hurry and help me.
She will send me
to the government.
You are now the heir of Duke Mao.
You don't need to be afraid of her.
The entire Wang family
will be yours in the future.
Here,
except for Duke Mao and Madam Wang,
you are the most powerful one.
Come on.
(Precious Breezes and Dew of the Moon)
Greetings, Mother.
Mother,
please forgive my birth mother
for my sake.
Since you've been
adopted by me,
she's no longer your mother.
I can let her go,
but you have to give an order
that she
and her people
must leave here
in three days,
and they aren't allowed to enter
the Wang family without my permission.
My son,
just let her sue me.
So what
if they'll flog me?
I'm not afraid of it.
Otherwise,
I'll go to Shuntian Prefecture Office
and sue you for being unfilial.
You've become my adopted son,
yet you still cover for
your birth mother's wrongdoings
and neglect the order of
your adopted mother.
Young Madam, you don't even care
about the Wang family's name anymore?
Even if you don't care about the name
of the Wang family,
the Luo family is
a prominent clan in Jiangnan
that has served the court
for generations,
and the Xu family are also
high-ranking officials.
If you don't care
about their reputation either,
just go ahead and sue me.
Send Lady Wang-Liu
to Shuntian Prefecture Office right now.
Jinlian, get the carriage ready.
We'll go, too.
Yes.
Don't. Please don't.
(Honor the Ancestors
and Benefit the Offspring)
Young Madam.
Young Madam. I made a mistake.
I know I'm wrong.
I dare not to do that again.
I'll leave here right away.
I'm begging you.
Please forgive us.
Jinlian,
watch her
and make sure she leaves.
Also, kick those
people she brought in
out of our family.
Search everybody
who leaves our house.
If any object of our family
is found on them,
send them all to
Shuntian Prefecture Office
for the crime of theft.
Yes, Young Madam.
Young Madam.
That Lady Wang-Liu left?
Yes.
She packed her stuff the next morning
and left with her people.
Lady Erniang
even had people
search them at the gate.
That does sound like
something Erniang would do.
Everything you did for her
finally paid off.
But,
Duke Mao doesn't care about
the household affairs.
Erniang has only her adopted son,
and she has to take care
of her ill mother-in-law.
I'm worried
that some street gangsters
will make trouble for them.
Amber,
ask Steward Bai to send a letter
to the Magistrate of
Shuntian Prefecture Office.
Let them keep an eye on the Wang family
every now and then.
Amber,
give Steward Bai
20 tael of silver
and ask him to treat
those bailiffs some wine.
Yes.
Don't worry.
No one dares to make trouble for them.
My Lord, let me thank you
on Erniang's behalf.
(Account Books)
Young Madam,
these are the account books.
Please review.
(Account Books)
Finally they are back
in my hands again.
Looking back,
it was like a dream.
Congrats, Young Madam.
From now on,
you'll be the matron
of this mansion.
No one dares to look down upon
you anymore.
Although I hate Shiyi,
she is right about something.
Complaining wouldn't help with anything.
Only by making myself strong
can I hold my head up high.
(Xianling Pavilion)
Shiyi.
Teacher.
I have fantastic news.
Seeing how happy you are,
I guess
we've just received
a big order, right?
Even better than that.
You know what?
The Palace will hold
a birthday celebration for His Majesty.
The inner palace is shorthanded,
so they'll use some embroidery
from folk workshops.
Because of the excellent
embroidery skills of
our Xianling Pavilion,
we are qualified for the pre-screening.
We need to make
an embroidery work as soon as possible
and deliver it to the Palace.
If it's chosen,
our Xianling Pavilion
will become world-famous.
By then,
our embroidery skills
will be widely circulated.
That's right.
Since it's His Majesty's birthday,
we need to think of
a propitious embroidery pattern.
Oh, right.
Bring me the pattern book.
Let's figure out
what to embroider.
Let me see.
Take a look.
What should we embroider?
How about this?
How about "Magu Celebrates
The Queen Mother's Birthday"?
"Bodhisattva Lotus Sutra"
is not bad either.
Both are good,
but if we want to
make our work stand out,
we need to think of a unique idea.
Why don't we make a
"One Hundred Longevity Picture"?
I'm thinking
we can use "One Hundred
Longevity Picture" as the main pattern
and make it a centerpiece of the room.
But unlike the previous ones,
the 100 "Longevity" characters
in our picture
will be all written
in different styles
and different scripts,
including
seal, semi-cursive, regular, cursive
and such.
We can also mix them with the different
handwritings of
the famous calligraphers of all ages,
representing a long and eternal life.
Good.
It's such
a good idea.
Calligraphy embroidery
requires excellent skills.
It's a good opportunity for our girls
to show their talent.
But
we need to find someone
to talk about the writing.
Master Jian.
Mr. Ou.
-Mr. Ou.
-Master Jian.
Madam Xu, you are also here.
That's even better.
The one who's in charge of the birthday
celebration is Ou Lixing?
Yes, it is my brother.
I think
you should be aware of that.
If he knows that you are involved,
I'm afraid he'll do something
to make trouble for you.
Thank you for your reminder, Mr. Ou.
I still have
a meeting with a business partner.
I can't stay for long.
I'll take my leave now.
Let me see you out.
Okay.
Mr. Ou, take care.
This time,
we'll embroider a
"One Hundred Longevity Picture"
for His Majesty's birthday.
I heard that you are
good at calligraphy,
so I'm wondering
if I can bother you
to write the main pattern for us.
It's my pleasure to help.
Master Jian,
we are friends.
Just feel free to ask.
In that case, thank you very much.
Master Jian, I'll leave now.
Alright.
(Longevity)
This calligraphy is very good.
Though it consists of different scripts,
it doesn't look awkward at all.
Instead, it's an
impeccable and
integrated work.
My Lord.
Shiyi,
I didn't expect that you are also
well-versed in calligraphy.
Calligraphy isn't my expertise.
This work isn't mine.
It's written by Ou Yanxing.
Why did you bring
his work home?
It's an embroidery pattern.
The Palace is collecting
embroidery from
folk workshops right now.
The ones that
can produce high-quality works
will be chosen to assist
the Palace with embroidery making
for His Majesty's birthday celebration.
Xianling Pavilion will use this
to participate in the selection.
You must use his calligraphy?
Master Jian thought
that Mr. Ou is good at calligraphy,
so she asked him for help.
Otherwise, she doesn't have
enough time to find
another suitable person.
(Longevity)
This character
is dull
and was done in a rush.
It doesn't look like
a masterpiece at all.
Wouldn't it be boring
just presenting a calligraphy
to His Majesty?
My Lord, but you just said...
My Lord, do you have
a better idea?
Xianling Pavilion's matter
is up to you.
(Longevity)
My Lord.
Be careful.
Don't wet the paper.
My Lord, are you practicing calligraphy?
(Longevity)
So?
How's my writing?
My Lord, your writing
flows nicely
and looks vigorous.
Do you think Shiyi
would use mine
as the pattern?
My Lord,
you are running out of paper.
I'll go get some for you.
My Lord.
(Longevity)
Why did you get in here
without even
notifying me?
Since when am I not allowed
to enter your study anymore?
My Lord, what are you writing?
Nothing.
I was working.
What are you doing here?
The weather has been nice these days.
I want to learn archery.
General Fu told me
that you've mastered excellent
riding and shooting skills
since you were little.
My Lord,
could you please teach me?
Why do you want to learn archery?
I want to experience
what Su Dongpo wrote,
"My bow is like a full moon,
and aiming northwest,
I will shoot down
the fierce Wolf from the sky."
My Lord,
would you please be kind and teach me?
Alright.
Let's go.
My Lord, you are awesome.
I guess, on the battlefield,
it's all thanks
to your excellent shooting skills,
you defeated those barbarian pirates,
protected our people,
and made our Ming military proud.
Shiyi,
have you heard a sentence,
"When someone praises you
for no reason..."
I meant what I said.
Without heroes like you
fighting the battles
and protecting our country,
no matter how talented
those scholars
and calligraphers are,
they won't be able to enjoy the peace
and show their talent.
Just like
without a thoughtful
and understanding wife like you
helping me
with the household management,
I can't feel at ease
to fight the enemies
and protect our country
on the battlefield.
Let me teach you.
Ready.
Loose.
Bull's eye.
Nothing can
beat you, My Lord.
That's true.
Again.
Actually, about the
"One Hundred Longevity Picture,"
there's something else
I want to discuss with you.
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪