♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned Grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 15=
(Xuanya Painting and Calligraphy)
Take care.
Madam.
These are too expensive.
They are.
But as long as it can make Concubine Qiao
change her mind,
it will be worth it.
I hope that your efforts
won't be wasted.
(Xuanya Painting and Calligraphy)
(Xiangfu Vinegar Shop)
Isn't that Mrs. Zhang?
Why is she here?
(Vinegar)
(Rice Vinegar)
Hurry up.
Hurry.
(Vinegar)
Let's go.
Are you serious?
I'm very sure.
I personally saw it.
No wonder.
I knew it.
Why did she buy so much rice vinegar?
I guessed it right indeed.
If you pour enough rice vinegar
into the water used to wash rice,
it will remove the moldy smell
in the water.
Merchants
pull this trick too many times.
Those rice
was too moldy already.
Back home,
we won't even use them
to feed the pigs.
Rice vinegar
can remove the moldy smell of rice,
but it can't eliminate its toxicity.
People will die if they eat it.
Since it's that serious,
Mrs. Zhang
is too bold.
isn't bold enough.
Madam.
I'm afraid we can't
disclose this matter.
After this, this involves His Lordship.
His Lordship is still young.
He'll surely get another legal wife
in the future.
Should we let Concubine Qiao
ascend to position
making things difficult for you,
or let the wives help each other
like a tripartite balance of forces?
Which one do you think
would benefit the Wen family
and you more?
There's an opportunity
for the Wen family
to overturn the situation now.
I must think about this carefully.
How strange.
Qiuhong.
Nanny Tao.
What's the matter?
I went to the kitchen just now
to get some porridge for Concubine Wen.
Who knew that the servant in the kitchen
ran out
and even took the porridge away.
She said that she got it mixed up,
and it will be bad if we'll get
a stomachache after eating it.
Perhaps something dirty
got mixed in there.
Qiuhong.
You said something
got mixed up?
Yes.
What's the matter, Nanny Tao?
Nothing,
It's nothing.
Moldy rice?
Nanny Tao.
You're so flustered.
Where are you going?
I... I'm fine.
Oh, right.
You... Do what you have to do.
Do what you have to do.
Do what I have to do?
She's not usually this way.
This is bad.
What happened?
Don't be anxious, Madam.
It's done.
Really?
This trick
is amazing.
Next,
we just need to see what will happen.
Oh, right.
I'm just not sure what Her Ladyship
will do.
Her Ladyship has gotten ahold
of such a big mistake.
If she has the boldness
of the late Her Ladyship back then,
she'll surely use this opportunity
to defeat Concubine Qiao
and get back the authority to manage
household affairs.
Before,
the late Her Ladyship was nice
to the Wen family.
Since Her Ladyship is her younger sister,
she'll surely be easy to get along with
in the future.
So the Wen family can change
our fortunes
very soon.
Nanny Tao.
You served Yuanniang
for a long time.
Do you know that the punishment
for making a false charge against
a master
isn't just flogging?
Your Ladyship, don't worry.
If I didn't have any evidence,
how would I dare
make such groundless accusation?
By the way, Your Ladyship,
you didn't see
those bags of rice.
Only a thin layer
of good rice is on top of them.
The rest are all moldy.
It's obvious that someone
tampered with them.
I think
Concubine Qiao
has long planned
to make some money on the rice
for the porridge.
Even if she doesn't get enough money
from her usual portion,
the Qiao family is so rich.
She wouldn't lack money.
Why would she do this?
Your Ladyship, you're thinking
too highly of her.
Who isn't tempted
by money?
Yes, the Qiao family is rich indeed.
But the Qiao family
isn't just
hers alone.
Are you sure what you saw
was moldy rice?
Did you see it clearly?
I did.
If... If I'm speaking nonsense,
I'll... I'll be struck
by lightning.
By the way, I also heard
that inside the soup kitchen,
there are a lot of grain supplies.
Who else knows about this?
It seems like
aside from Mrs. Zhang's staff,
I'm the only one who knows about this.
How did you find out then?
Concubine Wen's maid Qiuhong
said that she got the wrong porridge.
So what if she did?
So I thought
the problem must be with the rice.
Then I went to the warehouse to check.
By the way,
on my way back,
I even met Mrs. Zhang's maid,
Xialing.
This is a major matter.
Don't disclose this to anyone.
Come with me to the warehouse.
Mrs. Zhang.
Bad news.
Earlier,
I met Nanny Tao,
who came very flustered
from the direction of the warehouse.
I went inside to take a look.
Who would have thought
that the door to the warehouse
was open?
I think
she must already know.
Go... Go back now
and lock the door of the warehouse.
No one can go inside again.
-Go, hurry.
-All right.
Wait.
Go, open the door of the warehouse.
The key is with Mrs. Zhang.
Where's Mrs. Zhang?
I don't know.
Your Ladyship.
Let's find someone
to break the door open.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, where are you going?
The soup kitchen
is full of moldy rice now.
If they continue investigating...
You're so bold.
How dare you use moldy rice
to make porridge?
Don't you know
how important this is to Great Madam?
If you need money, just tell me.
Why did you tamper
with the relief grains?
Madam... Madam, I am wrong.
It's all my son's fault.
He owes a huge debt.
They'll kill him.
How would I dare to tell you about this?
How long have you been using moldy rice?
Two days.
Just two days.
I waited for Great Madam
to light the incense at the temple
before I dared to use it.
I originally thought
about buying some moldy rice
to earn some money
and stop after I earn enough.
Who would have thought...
Who would have thought
that someone would find out?
Don't you know
that people will die from eating
moldy rice?
If something really happens,
and the government blames us for it,
the entire Xu family
will be dragged down.
His Lordship...
What will His Lordship think of me?
Madam.
Madam, I was wrong.
I dragged you down.
I'll go to His Lordship now.
I'll seek punishment from His Lordship
and Great Madam.
I'll tell them that it's all my fault,
it has nothing to do with you.
No.
You're working for me.
I can't evade the responsibility
for this no matter what.
Xiuyuan.
Let's go and borrow rice
from the Qiao family immediately.
We just need to replace the rice
before Luo Shiyi
finds out.
Then we can still redeem the situation.
This matter cannot be delayed.
Let's go to
the soup kitchen immediately.
Thank you, Madam.
Here, take it.
Here, this is yours.
Thank you.
Line up properly.
Your Ladyship.
If you don't guard the warehouse,
if they remove
the moldy rice,
we won't have any evidence.
(Disaster Relief)
Here, this is yours.
Thank you.
Don't push each other. You'll all get some.
You'll all get some.
Line up properly. Don't push each other.
All right, next.
Come to the front.
Thank you.
Don't push each other.
Where are the stored grains
from the soup kitchen?
Thank you.
Next.
Since I'm already here,
I already know.
You're just following instructions,
I can opt not to hold you responsible.
But if you don't tell me now,
do you know what crime
you'll be charged with?
Tell me.
Over there.
Your Ladyship.
Why are you here?
If you want to know
the situation of the refugees,
you can ask me directly.
You don't need to personally come here.
What you hear may be false,
but what you see for yourself is true.
Disaster relief is a very
important matter.
I want to see it for myself
before I can feel at ease.
Please move aside.
Next.
It's just some rice.
Why can't I see it?
Of course there's nothing
that can't be seen.
It's just that
Great Madam told me to handle
the disaster relief.
Your Ladyship.
It's better if you don't interfere.
Madam.
Great Madam told you to handle
this matter indeed.
But don't forget
your status.
You're just a concubine after all.
How dare you tell Her Ladyship
what to do?
Move aside.
Your Ladyship.
You're using your status
to overstep your authority.
Are you doubting Concubine Qiao
or Great Madam?
In front of Her Ladyship,
who allowed you to interrupt
the conversation?
Your Ladyship, if I'm overstepping,
you can punish me back at the mansion.
But if you
break the rule
that Great Madam set today
and insist on barging in,
you can do it...
over my dead body.
Mrs. Zhang.
(Xuanya Painting and Calligraphy)
(Fabric Shop)
Whose rice is this?
Don't take them.
Don't take them!
Stop taking them!
Your Ladyship.
Here is the thing.
Look at all the people here.
If you insist on doing what you want,
and it turns into a big deal,
it's not good, right?
You two
keep stopping me.
What is your intention?
Nanny Tao,
Dongqing, Amber.
Move.
Madam.
-Madam.
-What happened?
There was an accident along the way.
The rice is gone.
Madam, what should we do?
Madam.
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, take a look.
All these...
All these are bags of moldy rice.
Look.
How dare they tamper
with the relief grains.
Lianfang, you're so bold.
Well...
Mrs. Zhang.
What exactly is going on?
Your Ladyship, don't be angry.
I suddenly thought about doing that.
I was blinded by money.
The moldy rice
has nothing to do with Concubine Qiao.
It was all me.
Your Ladyship,
please investigate it clearly.
If it had nothing to do with her,
why did she stop me earlier?
Your Ladyship, please be discerning.
No eggs can remain unbroken
when the nest is overturned.
I definitely won't do anything
that will harm the Xu family.
Mrs. Zhang.
I trusted you so much.
I can't believe you committed
such a grave crime behind my back.
Your Ladyship.
I didn't discipline her well.
Your Ladyship, please punish me.
Your Ladyship, it's all my fault.
I dragged Concubine Qiao down.
I dragged down the Xu family.
This isn't the time
to listen to you admit your faults here.
This is a grave matter.
If something goes wrong,
I won't spare you.
How much rice do we still have at home?
If we bring them all here,
how many days will it last?
At the mansion,
including the villa,
we still have excess grains.
However, there are too many
refugees.
Even if we bring it all here,
it won't last for more than a few days.
Your Ladyship, since we don't have
enough grains,
after the grains are used up,
let's stop giving out porridge.
No.
If we stop giving out porridge,
the refugees must endure hunger again.
Besides,
His Majesty is already aware
that we're giving out porridge
for disaster relief.
If we stop it hastily,
I'm afraid that it might be considered
as deceiving His Majesty.
No matter what happens,
we must continue this soup kitchen.
Lianfang.
Go home immediately
and bring all the rice over.
Let's see how many days it will last.
Then let's think about
what else we can do.
Yes.
Go.
Let's go.
Amber, bring a few people
to buy rice in rice shops.
Buy as much as you can.
Remember, be careful.
Don't let others find out.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship.
What should we do
with all the moldy rice?
Mrs. Zhang suddenly brought
so much moldy rice.
I keep thinking
that there's something fishy.
Leave them here first.
We'll remove them later on.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Nanny Tao.
Tell them to throw away the porridge
in the pots.
We'll cook some more
when the new rice arrives.
Your Ladyship.
Even if this is moldy rice,
eating it one or two times
won't cause any troubles.
Nothing happened
in the past few days.
I'm afraid that if we stop
giving out porridge,
the refugees will cause trouble.
We're lucky nothing happened.
Cook more after the new rice arrives.
Yes.
What's going on?
Why aren't they giving out porridge?
Have they run out?
Don't be ridiculous.
Marquis Yongping said that he'd
give out porridge,
so he won't forget about us.
Right.
Don't be anxious.
The porridge will be ready soon.
Everyone can get some.
Wait for a while.
They're so nice.
Line up to get porridge.
The porridge is here.
Don't be impatient.
Line up.
Don't push each other.
Line up to get porridge.
Everyone can get some.
Thank you.
Hurry, make it quick.
Dongqing, come.
Everyone can get some.
Don't push each other.
Thank you.
Take care.
(Mansion of Xu)
Your Ladyship.
We found information
about the moldy rice.
Is there any problem?
It was bought from Jiang's Rice Shop.
But coincidentally,
the brother of the keeper
of Jiang's Rice Shop
works for
Marquis Jingyuan.
Marquis Jingyuan?
The Ou family?
Your Ladyship, you haven't been
in the Xu family for long.
Perhaps you're not aware.
The Xu and Ou families
have a deep feud.
Back then, the death of the late Marquis
and his second son
was related to the Ou family.
In that case,
it's very possible that the Ou family
planned the moldy rice incident.
Your Ladyship, Mrs. Zhang definitely
won't be bold enough
to collude with the Ou family.
Whether she colluded with them or not,
His Lordship will be the judge of that.
What's important now
is that if the Ou family
was really the one who did this,
if no trouble happens,
they definitely
won't just give up easily.
Now, things only seem calm
on the surface.
Perhaps
the trouble will come later.
Your Ladyship, you're right.
If the Ou family takes advantage of this
to cause trouble,
the entire Xu family
will be in chaos.
Your Ladyship.
What should we do then?
Your Ladyship, we went
to almost all the rice shops
in the entire capital.
But the rice
was almost sold out.
Rice can't be bought
at such a huge capital?
Someone is definitely playing tricks.
Which are the largest grain shops
in the capital?
Ruixing Grains,
Shengping Grains,
and Fengping Grains.
Amber.
Go to those shops to check.
It doesn't matter if the rice is
more expensive than the market price.
Yes.
Lianfang.
I'll give you a chance
to redeem yourself.
Can you borrow some rice
from the Qiao family?
Your Ladyship.
It's not that I don't want to help.
Before this,
I've already asked my family
to provide some rice.
But I didn't expect
that an accident would occur
along the way.
Currently, my family
has no extra rice
to lend to me anymore.
I'm afraid it wasn't an accident.
Could it be that the Ou family
was also behind it?
The situation is very urgent now,
and His Lordship happens to be away.
Great Madam and Second Madam
also went to Ci'an Temple.
How can we deal
with such a grave matter?
Where's Lingkuan?
Is he back?
No.
Princess Danyang said
that after His Lordship left,
he went to watch a Chinese Opera
outside the city.
I'm afraid he won't be back
in a few days.
Steward Bai.
Take care of the soup kitchen first.
Don't disclose this at home
in order to avoid panic.
I'll think of something.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, is there anything
we can help with?
Your Ladyship.
If you need my help,
please tell me.
The most important thing now
is to find new rice
to replace the moldy rice.
Otherwise, we're in big trouble.
Master Lixing.
Marquis Yongping's wife
found out about the moldy rice
and replaced them.
Replaced them?
She can replace them temporarily.
Can she replace them for long?
I want to see
if there's an endless supply of rice
in the Xu family's mansion.
As for the Marquis Yongping's wife,
you're referring to the new legal wife
Xu Lingyi just married?
Exactly.
I heard that the new legal wife
isn't well-liked in the Xu family.
A concubine
is even the one managing
the household affairs.
Why is she involved in this?
I'm not sure
about the details.
The rice in the city...
According to your instructions,
we've gotten all of them.
The roads are blocked due to the flood.
The food from outside can't be
transported here.
They won't be able
to sustain this for long.
Watch them carefully.
You're very discerning.
They're just
dragging out a feeble existence.
When they use up all their extra rice,
the Xu family
won't be able to overturn
the situation again.
Nice work with the Qiao family's
horse carriage.
Thank you.
After Marquis Jingyuan comes back
from his inspection in Fujian
and sees your great accomplishment,
he'll surely be happy.
I'm congratulating you in advance.
This smells so good.
Here.
Hey.
Are you all right?
All right.
Let him rest for a while.
Come.
Help him get some rest over there.
This way.
Here.
Give him some water.
Rest for a while.
Everyone.
Rest for a while if you feel tired.
Sit down for a while.
My Lord.
General Fu.
For the sake of the disaster relief,
you haven't rested
for many days.
Take good care of yourself.
I'm fine.
The weather is very hot.
There are many rats and insects
in the flood.
It's very dirty.
The refugees
are mostly women and children.
I'm afraid that after what happened,
they'll get sick.
When we get to the base,
tell the physician who came with us
to make some medicines
to prevent sickness
and deliver it to the refugees.
My Lord, you're very thoughtful.
Give it to me.
General Fu.
Look.
His new shoes are so wet,
and His Lordship is still smiling.
What do you know?
That's called
the drinker's mind isn't on the cup,
but on Her Ladyship.
He's probably thinking
about Her Ladyship.
So you understand?
Hurry.
You know
what to do next, right?
But...
But what?
Don't you want your son
to stay alive?
Take that
to guarantee
that nothing will go wrong.
Here, this is yours.
Here.
All right.
Thank you.
Line up properly.
Take it slow.
You evil people.
What kind of rice
did you give us?
After my dad took the porridge,
he's been foaming at the mouth.
Our stomachs are aching.
Could it be that you're giving us
moldy rice?
If you don't give us
an explanation today,
we won't leave.
Everyone.
Give us an explanation.
There's no problem with the rice.
May I ask
if you have other illnesses?
Of course not.
Did you get your porridge here?
I heard that Marquis Yongping
has always been an honest official.
We came here
because of him.
Right.
How can he give us
moldy rice?
It's true.
We ate the Xu family's rice.
That was why our stomachs
started aching.
In the past few days,
we never
left this place.
If you all don't believe us,
go inside and see
if they're using
moldy rice or not.
Calm down, everyone!
Don't believe in rumors.
Don't believe in rumors!
(Disaster Relief)
Don't panic.
Your Ladyship.
Don't be scared, everyone.
There's no problem with the rice.
Eat them without any worries.
If you still have doubts,
I can eat with you.
Who are you?
Right.
She's Marquis Yongping's wife.
So what if you're
Marquis Yongping's wife?
Who knows if what you're saying
is the truth or not?
Make my father well first.
Father.
Father, how are you feeling?
He ate your moldy rice.
If there's no problem with your rice,
do you dare to show it to us?
Yes, show us!
Show us!
Madam Xu.
Could it be that there's
really a problem
with the porridge you gave us?
Why are you still talking to them?
Turn this soup kitchen over.
We can surely find the moldy rice!
Right.
Right!
Let's go inside and find them!
Wait.
Don't panic.
Your Ladyship.
Shiliu.
Stand up first.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, it's just a scratch.
Your Ladyship, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Look, everyone. I found it.
Just take a look and see
if it's moldy rice or not.
All of this is good rice.
It is the good rice.
Yes, it is the good rice.
Did we
falsely accuse them then?
This isn't moldy rice.
This is the good rice.
Good rice.
It is the good rice.
Take a look.
This is good white rice.
We've misunderstood.
I knew it.
The Xu family
won't do such a thing.
Good rice.
All are bags of good rice.
Everyone can feel at ease now, right?
Continue lining up for porridge then.
Line up.
Come on.
Come, line up properly.
Come, one by one.
Everyone can get some.
The Ou family is unpredictably
insidious in doing things.
We must guard against them.
Dongqing.
Take this land title
to Master Jian.
Master Jian knows a lot of people.
See if she can find
someone with a lot of extra rice
to make a deal.
I'm willing to use an acre of farmland
in exchange for six kilograms of rice.
We can get 120 kilograms of rice with these.
But Your Ladyship,
these are your dowries.
We're in imminent danger.
We can't think
about those things anymore.
You must be careful.
Don't let anyone find out.
(Land Title)
Hurry.
Place that over there.
Be careful.
In that case,
they must have borrowed some rice
from somewhere else.
That's fine.
Even if they borrow from people
in the entire capital,
they won't be able to get much
for their needs.
They're just dragging out
a feeble existence.
You're right.
They won't last long.
If the Xu family stops
giving out porridge,
those refugees
surely won't just give up easily.
When that time comes,
they can't hide
their moldy rice any longer.
I can't believe Xu Lingyi's wife
lasts this long.
I've belittled her.
Tell them to watch
the soup kitchen closely.
Don't let them get any chance
to remove the moldy rice.
Yes.
If the Ou family can't
cause us trouble today,
they'll surely find another opportunity.
However,
our rice supply now
is only enough for a couple of days.
We must find
enough new rice.
But the Ou family
just wants everyone to know
about the moldy rice.
We can just move
the moldy rice away secretly.
They were even watching
the Qiao family's horse carriage
that was supposed to bring rice.
And they spent so much money
to buy all the rice in the city.
How can they let us
move the moldy rice away so smoothly?
If we really moved the moldy rice,
perhaps
they'd catch us in the act.
I wonder
what happened with Amber.
Alms.
You are so kind.
Give us some food.
It's mine.
(Wine)
Don't take what's mine.
Give it to me.
(Vinegar)
Move.
Give it to me.
Stop taking it away.
Give me some food.
After just a few years,
the capital changed so much.
There are so many refugees.
The flooding disaster this time
must be serious.
Young Master, should we go
to the shop first?
There's no rush.
Alms.
Please.
I really need it urgently.
My master really needs it.
(Fengping Grains)
I told you many times.
No matter how much
you're willing to pay,
we won't sell our rice to you.
Be nice.
Let me in.
I really need it urgently.
Can you let me in?
Are you done yet?
Young lady, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank you, sir.
(Fengping Grains)
Why do you need to buy rice
so urgently?
My master
needs rice for disaster relief.
But the keeper
won't sell me rice
no matter what.
Most likely,
the keeper is afraid
that you're buying rice
to sell them at a high price
and harm the citizens.
That's why he's not willing
to sell them to you.
Why would we do that?
My master is...
My master
won't do
such a terrible thing.
Since they're willing to buy rice
at a high price,
they're surely not people
who will pull tricks.
Come with me inside.
But...
(Grains)
(Rice)
Young lady.
You think I really won't
get physical with you,
do you?
Sir.
Sell this young lady
the rice that she wants.
Follow the market price.
You're so arrogant.
Don't you see
what kind of place this is?
Can you act so impetuously here?
(Ou)
Sir, you...
Young lady.
How much rice do you want?
We'll sell them at the market price.
Really?
Thank you, sir.
Dongqing.
Look, we're out of rice.
Right.
What should we do?
Your Ladyship.
Our good rice is all used up.
Only moldy rice is left.
If we can't give out more porridge,
we can only shut down the soup kitchen.
The Wang family's soup kitchen
might still have some extra rice.
What if
we lead the refugees
over there first?
Perhaps we can control
the chaotic situation.
No.
All the Marquis in the capital
are providing disaster relief according
to His Majesty's imperial edict.
Each family is responsible
for one soup kitchen.
Soldiers are guarding between each area.
If chaos occurs
and they investigate it,
I'm afraid we won't be able
to hide the moldy rice.
When will you give out porridge?
Give them out.
Is there rice?
Everyone, quiet down.
Let me tell you, there's no more rice.
There's no rice.
Be kind.
Give the children some porridge.
They're starving.
We want porridge.
There is so much rice.
Why won't you cook them?
Right.
There is so much rice.
Why won't you cook them?
Your Ladyship.
Once people get hungry,
they're capable of doing anything.
Based on the situation outside,
I'm afraid they'll cause trouble.
At a time like this,
your safety is the priority.
Go back to the mansion
and avoid them first.
No.
In times like these,
I can't leave all the more.
Your Ladyship.
We haven't eaten yet.
We're all waiting.
I'm apologizing
to everyone.
We didn't watch the relief grains well,
and rats got to them.
We're afraid that you'll get sick
if you eat them.
I've already sent people
to get new rice.
Please be patient and wait for a while.
How can we wait?
Right.
The children can't wait.
What should we do?
So what if the rats got to them?
Right, Madam Xu.
We're farmers,
we're not that particular.
-I want to eat.
-Right.
You can just feed the children first.
Yes, feed the children first.
Please be patient.
No.
I'll stay here
and wait together with you all.
If new rice doesn't arrive,
you can come to me.
If it doesn't arrive,
we'll starve to death then.
Everyone!
Let me say something!
Since Madam Xu
already said that,
so what if we wait
just a bit longer?
Let's wait.
-Yes.
-Right.
Master Lixing, I don't understand.
Why don't we let
the people we've arranged
charge into the soup kitchen directly
and bring the moldy rice out?
Then we'll have the evidence too.
The Xu family won't be able
to deny it any longer.
I can't incite the refugees
to go on a riot.
Even if our people
take the moldy rice out,
it's unavoidable for them
to leave a trace.
Perhaps
Xu Lingyi will even make countercharges
against us,
and say
that we've exchanged the rice
to frame him.
You're right.
I'm too impatient.
We've been fighting with the Xu family
for so many years.
We can wait a bit longer.
Yes.
Sir, it's up ahead.
Hurry.
Wait.
Sir, let's go another way.
We've been waiting for so long.
When exactly will you
give out porridge?
-Right.
-When will you give out porridge?
Everyone, listen to me.
Stop listening to her nonsense.
No new rice will arrive.
I heard
that they're keeping the rice
to sell them at a high price.
How can these rich people
really care about us?
That's nonsense.
Right.
Liars.
They're liars.
Your Ladyship.
Don't listen to gossip.
I guarantee on behalf of the Xu family
that within the disaster period,
every one of you
will have food to eat.
Where's the food?
Don't listen to her lies.
Let's fill our stomachs first.
Let's go inside to get some rice!
Let's go!
Everyone, calm down.
Move!
Your Ladyship!
Don't push.
Your Ladyship.
Don't take them!
Move.
You can't take them!
Don't push each other.
-Give it to me.
-Go away.
(Disaster Relief)
Let go!
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪