♪Wearing peach blossom makeup,
I boil tea over the stove♪
♪With a pure heart,
I embroider the brocade of time♪
♪On the short paper,
affection flows in the silent moonlight♪
♪I only wish that by my side,
is my love♪
♪Cool autumn wind blowing,
I gaze far leaning against the railing♪
♪Sunset glow over the green hill,
in formation wild geese are flying♪
♪Covering a thousand miles on horseback,
for whom is he longing♪
♪He returned home in dreams♪
♪I will never forget
that you held my hands♪
♪In your warm palms
and we braved winds and waves♪
♪Unexpectedly, after we traveled so far
and turned grey-haired♪
♪I am still by your side♪
♪Hearts burning,
we look into each other's eyes♪
♪Feelings overflowing,
they don't need to be hided♪
♪No matter how time passes
and life changes♪
♪Together, we will grow old♪
=The Sword and the Brocade=
=Episode 43=
In the final analysis, it's my fault.
If I refused to take her
as a concubine resolutely back then
and didn't put her
to the test intentionally,
she might still
be alive.
My Lord,
nobody can foretell things.
You are not to blame for this.
I was not in love with them.
But I accepted them as my concubines
for various reasons
and caused all these tragedies.
All these things
are not up to you.
You can't force yourself
to love them.
But I believe that
you have done your best
to take care of them.
The only thing I can do now
is to bury her decently.
My Lord, don't worry.
I will arrange personnel
to handle Concubine Qin's
funeral affairs properly.
She has given up her grudges in the end.
So I am sure that she can rest in peace.
My Lord,
do you think
Marquis Jingyuan will believe
the message from Concubine Qin?
Whether he believes it or not,
he will no longer trust Wang Jiubao.
We can't
keep Wang Jiubao anymore.
Though we have been
holding his wife and son as hostages,
we have been cooperating
for so many years
and have had our separate needs met.
He didn't suffer losses.
Normally, he shouldn't
have betrayed us suddenly.
If this is Xu Lingyi's stratagem
of sowing discord,
your suspicion of Wang Jiubao
will play into his hands.
The imperial court has been offering
enlistment to Wang Jiubao
since a long time ago.
Wang Jiubao is fully aware that
accepting the enlistment
by the imperial court
will lead to unpredictable risks.
Surely, he won't surrender easily.
The problem now is
that Shen Niang and her son
must have been brought to Wang Jiubao
by Xu Lingyi.
Even if this is just Xu Lingyi's
stratagem of sowing discord,
we have to be on guard.
It is better to take the initiative
to gain the upper hand
than to be at a passive disadvantage.
If Wang Jiubao wants to
save his own skin,
he will have no choice,
but to pledge allegiance
to the imperial court.
Then I guess you must have
made relevant arrangements.
I have sent personnel to Fujian
to remind Wang Jiubao
to take preventive measures.
Linbo has also been
assisting them in secret.
There is no way for Marquis Jingyuan
to accomplish his end.
(Rites)
Dongqing.
Why are you here?
Have you had the hairpin fixed?
I have told you
I want it to be
as intact as a new one, haven't I?
This hairpin has such obvious cracks.
It is clear that you are not sincere.
Dongqing.
I caused the cracks
to this hairpin.
But the cracks of my heart
were caused by you.
Why are you so cheeky
to say such cheesy words?
Dongqing.
Please stop torturing me.
I want you to marry me.
I will spend the rest of my life
to mend the cracks of this hairpin,
all right?
Do you sincerely want me to marry you?
Of course I do.
Except you,
I don't want to marry
any other woman.
If you don't marry me,
I will become a monk.
I don't want you to be a monk.
Does this mean
that you said yes to my proposal?
I didn't say that.
I didn't find
you are so thick-skinned till now.
This is nothing.
For you,
I am even willing to die.
Don't talk nonsense!
It is late now.
I will be off.
(Rites)
Give this back to me.
Your Ladyship,
I am leaving for Fujian.
Before I leave,
I want to tell you something
that has been on my mind all along.
If not, I will not be able to leave
with peaceful mind.
I want to
request you to allow me
to marry Dongqing.
Dongqing.
Are you willing to marry Linbo?
It seems that Dongqing
is not willing to.
Then I think we'd better drop it.
Your Ladyship,
I didn't say I am not willing to.
I am willing to marry him.
A grown girl can't be kept by your side.
Then I will
give my consent to your marriage.
Thank you, Your Ladyship!
From now on,
you must treat Dongqing nicely.
Linbo is leaving for Fujian.
So today I will grant you a leave.
And you should bid
farewell to him properly.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Go do your things now.
Well,
if I hadn't been forced to stay at home,
I would not have noticed
such beautiful scenery in our house.
You have watched them for quite a while.
Now go inside to have a rest.
Our baby is growing heavier
in your tummy.
So it is not good for you
to stand for long.
Let's go.
Let's go inside.
Sit down.
Come on.
Taste this bowl of
ewe's milk and Chinese yam congee.
We are not rich.
After I give birth to the baby,
we will need more money to spend.
You shouldn't have spent money
buying such luxurious stuff.
Shiyi sent someone
to bring the ewe's milk
early in the morning.
The Chinese yam didn't cost much.
If you like it,
we can afford it.
I will be right back.
Master Qian.
What is the matter?
Is it that we are running out of money?
I am afraid that our money
will be used up in a few days.
I have prepared
Her Ladyship's three meals
as you ordered.
Now Her Ladyship is going to
give birth to a baby soon.
It is inevitable that
our daily expenses have increased.
It is not time for the farm
to harvest crops.
So we are spending money
without earning any.
I didn't expect that
we would not be able to make ends meet.
Should I
go to the Xu family to borrow some money
from Madam Xu again?
You can't lift someone out
of chronic poverty.
It is not a good way in the long run
to always depend on
the Xu family and the Luo family.
I am to blame.
I am a useless scholar
who can't support his family.
Take this silver.
You mustn't
let Wuniang know this matter.
Or she will worry.
Whatever she likes to eat,
you should buy them for her.
As for the money,
I will manage to bring it home.
OK.
Come to have a look!
Qian Ming.
Zhiyuan.
Why are you here?
I am going to your house to see you.
You want to see me?
What is the matter?
It is something great!
Luck will turn in your favor.
How about this?
I will give you a treat.
Let's talk as we drink.
How do you like this idea?
After you!
You first.
A few days ago, an elder brother of mine
just returned from the south.
He said he has some old acquaintances
in the south.
They are engaged in
the embroidery business.
They need lots of embroideries.
I learned previously that
you have a relative
who runs an embroidery workshop.
So after hearing this news,
I came to see you immediately.
It is true.
My sister-in-law
is running an embroidery workshop
with a partner.
Well,
since she is such a close relative,
it will be an easy thing.
You don't know, Qian Ming.
The southerners
are very generous in business.
As long as a deal is closed,
the profits will be handsome.
If you can have
a share of them more or less,
you will have enough to spend
in the coming two years.
Really?
Of course.
Then it is really a great chance.
You can't afford to
let this chance slip.
Many people
will scramble for such a chance.
The earlier, the better.
If you can make up your mind now,
Qian Ming,
I will go back right now
to settle this matter
with my brother.
OK.
Today I will go to see my sister-in-law
to talk about this matter.
Zhiyuan.
(Xianling Pavilion)
As long as you two agree,
I will handle the other matters.
Of course, it is a great thing
to be able to expand
our Xianling Pavilion's business
to the south.
If we can really conclude this deal,
we will not only
let the name of our Xianling Pavilion
known by more people,
but also bring benefits to
more embroidery girls.
Why not go ahead with it?
The only problem is that
now our Xianling Pavilion
is not large-scaled enough.
I am afraid we are not capable of
producing as many embroideries as
specified by the order
in a short time.
We are thinking about scaling up
our Xianling Pavilion, right?
Why don't we take this chance
to set up a branch in Yuhang?
I know some embroidery girls
over there.
I can ask them to help us
to recruit highly-skilled
embroidery girls
among the folks.
In this way,
we will have no problem
closing this deal.
This is a great idea!
OK.
Let's do it this way.
We have to trouble you to work
as the middleman.
It's my pleasure, Shiyi.
This matter shouldn't be delayed.
I will go see my friend right now
to nail this matter down.
Wait for my news, you two.
Take care on your way.
Be seated, Shiyi.
These days
Wuniang is
in great need of money.
If we can succeed in this deal,
her shortage of money
will be less serious.
You are so nice
to care so much about your sister.
Nonetheless,
it is also a very good thing
for Xianling Pavilion.
Now we should
start making preparations for
opening up a branch.
We will be very busy in the coming days.
You will be happy doing things you like
no matter how busy you are.
Exactly.
I am thinking that
after we open up the branch in Yuhang
and conclude this deal,
we should set up more branches
in more places
to spread the craft of
our Xianling Pavilion.
Maybe
we will be able to help more people.
Behave yourselves!
Did you hear?
Don't move!
What are you doing?
Sit down! What are you doing?
(Transaction Documents)
Report!
In the wooden cases, we found
loads of embroideries from
Xianling Pavilion of the capital.
We also searched them and
found the transaction documents
of Xianling Pavilion.
(Transaction Documents)
Report this matter to
the imperial court immediately.
Yes!
Fujian Administration Commission
submitted a memorial
to the imperial court.
It says that
Xianling Pavilion of the capital
is found to collude with
the pirates in smuggling
and selling embroideries abroad
without permission to make profits.
Both witnesses and material evidence
have been obtained.
His Majesty got enraged
after reading the memorial
and gave the order
to have Xianling Pavilion seized.
And His Majesty has designated
the three judicial offices
to investigate this case thoroughly.
Grand Secretary,
could there be any
kind of misunderstanding?
Though I have no knowledge about
Xianling Pavilion's operation model,
I am sure that
it has never colluded with the pirates.
Grand Secretary.
Xianling Pavilion
is the property
of Marquis Yongping's wife.
I humbly think that
Marquis Yongping should
be required to stay out of this case.
Grand Secretary.
When smuggling is rampant,
the imperial court will
be short of sources of tax revenue.
It is like a human
who lacks vital energy and blood.
Such an illegal act undermining
the foundation of our state
calls for severe punishment.
Therefore, His Majesty has
issued an imperial edict
to pick up the owner
of Xianling Pavilion.
Marquis Yongping.
This matter concerns the foundation
of our state.
You mustn't bend the laws for your wife.
Go inside!
Hurry!
Who is the owner here?
Officer.
I am the owner of Xianling Pavilion.
What is this for, officer?
Xianling Pavilion
colluded with the pirates
to smuggle embroideries.
All of you
must come with us.
Whoever resists
will be killed.
Well,
could there be
any misunderstanding in this?
Do you know
this is the property
of Marquis Yongping's wife.
She can't help you.
She herself will be apprehended too.
Take them away!
You!
You can't catch people arbitrarily!
-Officer!
Master Jian.
Could there be any misunderstanding?
Officer!
Master Jian,
please go.
(Mansion of Xu)
(A fair place
produces outstanding people.)
Marquis.
-My Lord.
-Shiyi.
Please forgive us, Marquis.
We are doing our job by order.
Have they hurt you?
I am fine.
My Lord, I didn't...
I know.
Believe me.
I am with you.
I won't let you be wronged.
Listen up, all of you!
There is still no verdict on this case.
If anyone dares to hurt my wife a bit...
Marquis,
we dare not hurt Madam Xu.
Madam Xu,
please come with us.
(Mansion of Xu)
What should we do?
Wuniang! Wuniang!
Wuniang!
(Virtue of Purity and Nobility)
What's troubling you?
Why are you so panic-stricken?
Xianling Pavilion was accused of
colluding with pirates
to smuggle embroideries.
It has been seized.
What?
I went to see Qin Zhiyuan just now.
Someone said that
he had been promoted to
an official position of Fujian.
He has no scholarly honor
or official rank.
Theoretically,
this shouldn't have happened.
I am afraid,
I am afraid that Marquis Jingyuan
used me with the help of Qin Zhiyuan.
(Virtue of Purity and Nobility)
-Come!
-Hurry to go to the Xu family
to see Marquis Yongping!
Take away Qian Ming.
What is going on?
Hurry to go to the Xu family
to see Marquis Yongping!
Why are they arresting you?
Hurry to go to the Xu family
to see Marquis Yongping!
Hurry up!
Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, are you all right?
What should we do, Your Ladyship?
The Xu family.
Let's go to the Xu family.
Your Ladyship, be careful.
(Mansion of Xu)
It is true that Qian Ming acted
as the go-between
in the trade of the batch of
confiscated embroideries.
But he said that
he had fallen into
Marquis Jingyuan's trap.
And Marquis Jingyuan cheated him
with the help of
his classmate Qin Zhiyuan.
Marquis Jingyuan.
It is his scheme again!
My Lord, Duke Wei is here.
Duke.
How are things now?
I have sent personnel to check it out.
Now the evidence obtained
by the Ministry of Justice
is the embroideries of Xianling Pavilion
and the transaction documents
as well as seals.
The witnesses are the pirates
caught on the spot.
The testimony of the pirates proves that
Xianling Pavilion has really
got involved in smuggling.
The evidence is conclusive.
What is His Majesty's attitude
toward this?
I am afraid that His Majesty
has got suspicious of you.
So he ordered the three judicial offices
to try this case jointly
and make strict
investigations pursuant to laws.
But there are still a few days to go
before the joint trial of
the three judicial offices starts.
We still have a chance
to find out the truth.
Then,
then Qin Zhiyuan
will be a crucial factor.
But he is in the faraway Fujian now.
I am worried that we won't be able to
find him before the joint trial starts.
I have contacts in Fujian.
I will ask them to find Qin Zhiyuan.
I must have him brought to the capital
even if resorting to kidnapping.
My husband and I are to blame for this.
We caused Shiyi to
fall into the bad person's trap.
Marquis,
my husband did this to
feed and clothe our baby and me.
If not so, as a scholar,
he wouldn't have engaged in business.
He didn't do such a thing purposefully.
I know.
I will definitely get them out
of the prison.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Marquis!
It is the prison.
How could Shiyi
put up with
the sunless and fettered days in it?
Might she suffer corporal punishment
in it?
Thinking of this,
I feel short of breath
due to worry.
Don't worry too much, Mother.
I will manage to visit Shiyi.
With I being Shiyi's husband,
I bet they dare not act recklessly.
Our Xu family
has always been sticking to
integrity and uprightness.
How come Shiyi got framed
for smuggling inexplicably?
It is obvious that Marquis Jingyuan
tried to hurt us.
Even if we keep lying at home,
trouble will come to us.
The Ou family
has been eyeing us menacingly
and trying to
undermine our power all along.
They went too far in bullying us!
Sooner or later,
we have to settle our accounts
with the Ou family.
But I feel sad to see Shiyi suffer.
I have sent people to
investigate this case
and to look for evidence.
I believe that in a few days,
news will come.
Marquis Jingyuan is a sly fox.
Whatever it takes, I will not
allow his conspiracy to succeed.
(Prison)
You can't go in,
Marquis Yongping.
Please don't make it hard for me.
What's your motive for
forbidding my lord
to see his wife?
Marquis Yongping.
Official Li.
I want to go in to visit my wife.
Please bend the rules a bit.
I can understand your feelings,
but this case involves you,
Marquis Yongping.
Please think twice.
Such being the case,
I will not make it hard
for you, Official Li.
But I request you
to be impartial and just as usual
and distinguish
between truth and falsehood
when you try this case.
That is the working style of
our Ministry of Justice all the time.
You need not worry, Marquis Yongping.
I am wronged!
-Hurry! Hurry!
-I am wronged.
Go inside!
(Prison Guard)
Move quickly!
Hurry up!
Go inside!
I wonder where my brother-in-law
and our embroidery girls
are imprisoned.
I am sorry to have implicated you.
This is not your fault.
Don't mind it.
Something must have gone wrong.
Our Xianling Pavilion
has never done any illegal things.
As long as the truth of
this case is revealed,
we will be set free.
I am afraid that
this matter is not so simple.
As is known to all,
I am the owner of Xianling Pavilion.
If they don't have solid evidence,
how did they dare to do this to us?
Well.
You mean that...
I am afraid that this deal
is a conspiracy
against me
and our Xu family.
Could...
Teacher.
If they ask you,
you only need to say that
I handle this matter all by myself
and you know nothing about it.
(Prison Guard)
The minister will
interrogate the prisoner.
You, come out!
Remember what I said.
Shiyi!
(Prisoner)
Luo Shiyi.
Xianling Pavilion
smuggled embroideries
into overseas countries.
Who is behind this?
Did you act on Xu Lingyi's instigation?
I have told you that
I have been doing legitimate business
and haven't got involved in smuggling.
My husband
has never had a hand in
any affairs of Xianling Pavilion.
Official, I don't know
what purpose you want to achieve
by charging my husband
with such a crime.
Mind your words!
In the smuggling ship,
the embroideries of
Xianling Pavilion were found.
Also, the pirates testified that
they did business with you
with Qian Ming being the middleman.
Now we have both
witnesses and material evidence.
How dare you still resort to sophistry!
You are the wife of Marquis Yongping.
How could he
stay aloof from this?
Hurry to confess.
Someone has framed me deliberately.
Official, please judge wisely.
Total rubbish!
Marquis Jingyuan is here.
(Prison Guard)
(Prisoner)
What has brought you here?
Have you got her confession?
If you find it difficult to do this job,
no need to say any more.
I dare not.
Back then,
you ever saved my life in Fujian.
I am not an ingrate.
But...
Have you met difficulty
in handling this case?
Though I have witnesses
and material evidence,
Luo Shiyi asserted categorically that
she's been framed
and refused to admit to her crime.
In your opinion,
can a woman like her
be capable of
a major event like smuggling?
Just as your theory about
this case suggests,
if the smuggling thing is real,
it is absolutely impossible for her
to be the wirepuller.
It is very likely that
Marquis Yongping is the mastermind
behind the scenes.
I used to think
that he devoted himself to the state,
so he was kind of respectable to me.
If he has breached the laws of
the imperial court
for personal gains,
I will do all in my power
to eliminate him.
His Majesty relies heavily on Xu Lingyi.
If you can't drag a confession
out of his wife Luo Shiyi this time
and can't convict him,
nobody can ensure that
in the days to come,
His Majesty will not
show leniency towards him.
Don't worry, Marquis Jingyuan.
Whether for personal reasons
or for the sake of the state,
I will go to all lengths
to close this case.
Good!
I just want to see in you
this spirit of working selflessly
for public interests.
(Prisoner)
Bring another prisoner here.
Shiyi!
If you want to know anything,
just ask me.
Shiyi!
Master Jian has nothing to do with this.
Teacher!
(Prisoner)
Smuggling is a grave crime.
If you confess honestly,
maybe I can give you a light sentence.
I will ask you the question again.
Did Xu Lingyi direct Xianling Pavilion
to smuggle the embroideries?
I have told you that
we concluded the deal
with the businessmen engaged in
legitimate business.
About other matters,
I have no knowledge at all.
Then how can you explain
(Transaction Documents)
the transaction documents
we obtained from the pirates?
On these documents, there are clearly
the seals of Xianling Pavilion.
I handle this deal
all by myself.
Marquis Yongping
and his wife
have nothing to do with it at all.
It is apparent that you and Luo Shiyi
are business partners.
How could you say
the deal has nothing to do with them?
Moreover, as a woman,
how could you
make contact with the pirates?
Under such circumstances,
you still refuse to repent.
Official Li.
Look at her...
Drag her away.
I will interrogate her some other day.
Yes.
Teacher.
(Prisoner)
How could they torture you so cruelly?
It is my fault.
I have dragged you into this.
You should blame me.
Shiyi.
Don't say this.
I have been living my life
in a lonely and wretched way.
But you
brought me much happiness
and you also
made it possible for me
to realize
my unrealistic aspirations.
My heart is filled up with
gratitude to you.
Teacher, stop speaking.
Have a rest.
Don't worry.
I have said that
I handled the deal
by myself.
You have...
Teacher.
You have nothing to do with it.
Why did you say that?
Haven't we agreed that
you would say you know nothing about it?
Silly girl.
In my heart,
you are not only my student,
but also my family.
How can I do nothing and see you
get stuck in the prison?
You must stay alive
and pass down
our craft of embroidery.
Only in this way,
can you help more people.
I will. I will.
Teacher.
Hold on.
Xianling Pavilion needs you
and I need you.
You must hang in there.
I am fine.
Teacher.
Have you heard of it?
Xianling Pavilion has been seized.
It belongs to the wife
of Marquis Yongping.
(Bucket Rice)
Who had the guts to do that?
It is said that Xianling Pavilion
colluded with pirates in smuggling.
(Grain)
Even the wife of Marquis Yongping
has been apprehended
by the Ministry of Justice.
Really?
Yes, really.
No wonder recently,
rumors have been circulating everywhere
saying that the wife of Marquis Yongping
got into trouble.
Yes, indeed.
Let go of me!
Tell me
whether my husband
was killed by Ou Yanxing
and Xu Lingyi.
Tell me!
Young Master, something bad happened.
Your sister-in-law
has had Lady Amber caught
and brought to our mansion.
Where is she?
In the firewood room.
You still won't come clean?
If you continue remaining silent,
your beautiful face
may be scratched.
Stop him!
I know you work for Lixing.
But I suggest you make clear
who will be the master of our Ou family
in the future.
From now on, if anybody dares to
cause Amber any trouble,
I will not let him off.
Mr. Ou.
What are you doing?
Stand up quickly.
Mr. Ou.
Now Her Ladyship
is locked up in the prison.
You know her personality.
She must have been framed.
I beg you to save her.
How can I not know that
Shiyi has been framed?
I especially inquired about
this matter just now.
Now the authority has got
both witnesses and material evidence.
To get Shiyi acquitted of the crime,
we must try hard
to figure out a way.
Her Ladyship has never
made enemies in normal days.
So I think it is very possible that
your father has framed her.
Mr. Ou.
I am afraid that now
you are the only person
who can save Her Ladyship.
Impossible.
Mr. Ou.
It can't be him.
I know this is hard for you.
But be it smuggling
or colluding with pirates,
they are felonies
that can result in death penalty.
We can't do nothing
and watch Her Ladyship get killed.
Don't worry.
If my father really
did such a bad thing,
I won't sit watching.
Grand Secretary,
please be aware of this.
Someone has meticulously
orchestrated this case
to frame Xianling Pavilion purposefully.
This person's aim
is to frame our Xu family
through Xianling Pavilion.
About this case,
both witnesses and material evidence
have been obtained.
The evidence is irrefutable.
Even if what you said is true
and your wife has been framed
and wronged,
without evidence,
how could you make His Majesty
and all officials believe that?
Lingyi.
You always stay loyal
to His Majesty and care about people.
And you are always
an upright and incorruptible official.
I believe that
you are not involved in this case.
You have good judgement.
This case was elaborately orchestrated.
So it is not easy
to find the loopholes of the opponent.
But all conspiracies have flaws.
As long as His Majesty
and Grand Secretary Chen
can grant me some time,
I will surely find evidence
to prove the innocence of
Xianling Pavilion and my wife.
In the coastal regions,
the criminal activities of
pirates are rampant.
It has been disturbing
His Majesty a lot.
So His Majesty thought of
offering enlistment to them.
His Majesty entrusted you
with this matter.
Though His Majesty didn't
make his thoughts explicit,
to get rid of the trouble
caused by the pirates,
His Majesty
is more and more inclined to
lift the sea ban.
As for lifting the sea ban,
it will be the best
to have His Majesty
and your support.
But to lift the sea ban
concerns the ancestral policy.
Thus, there must be someone
who overrides all objections
to push it forward.
You are the most suitable candidate.
But now,
once your wife is convicted,
you will be implicated.
If you get into trouble,
how can you promote the lifting
of the sea ban?
So I hope you can
bear the big picture in mind
and won't let His Majesty down.
What do you mean
by saying this, Grand Secretary?
This is the memorial for you
to state you will divorce your wife.
(Divorce Agreement Memorial)
You only need to
submit it
at the joint trial
of the three judicial offices
and to state publicly that
you have nothing to do
with the smuggling
and your wife is to blame for all.
So you decide to divorce her
and drive her out of your Xu family.
Then your problem will be solved easily.
If I really submit this memorial,
I am afraid I will become
a person guilty of perfidy.
Lingyi.
I just don't want to see
your effort over all the past years
go down the drain.
Now
success is just around the corner.
You mustn't lose the greater
for the less.
This is also His Majesty's thought.
♪I trimmed the wicks,
the memory kept me awake at night♪
♪It was late into the night
I started missing you again♪
♪I closed my eyes♪
♪I thought of the old days♪
♪The past whispered in my ear
but you couldn't hear it♪
My Lord.
Warden Jiang has sent a message.
It says that Master Jian has been
put to severe torture
and got badly injured.
This is obviously
extorting confessions by torture.
How about Shiyi?
How is she?
Official Li didn't torture Her Ladyship.
Entrusted by you, My Lord.
Warden Jiang also helped
Her Ladyship in secret.
So Her Ladyship is fine and safe
for the time being.
Go ask for Warden Jiang's help
to deliver some medication
to Master Jian.
Yes, My Lord.
My Lord, there is another thing.
Our people in Fujian
have sent back a message.
Did they find him?
When they got to the place,
Qin Zhiyuan was found dead.
It suggests that Marquis Jingyuan
has prepared for this in advance.
♪In the cold darkness of midnight,
a sigh is heard♪
♪Who picked up the paintbrush
to draw loneliness♪
♪In my life, I can draw everything,
but lovesickness♪
♪The mountain city is waiting for rain♪
♪I am waiting for you
to pass in my memory♪
♪The sky is in a more lonely color
than your face♪
♪The wind rises
and the candle light flickers♪
♪The thin clothes
can't stand the cold days♪
♪Full of twists and turns,
fate is untold♪
♪I ground my thoughts into ink♪
♪But I still can't sketch your contours♪
♪How could the ink
and paper exhaust our stories♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to disturb the heart♪
♪Who visited to remind me of the past♪
♪If feelings can be kept in mind,
but cannot be confessed♪
♪I won't escape from whatever end♪
♪In the dim lantern light,
with you there is me♪
♪Who picked up the pen
to set free lonely tears♪
♪Whoever visited my life,
only you stayed all the days♪
♪If the moth doesn't fly into the fire♪
♪How can it be said to be persistent♪
♪Coming to the end of your story,
there is me♪