[English subtitles are available]
[The Ingenious One]
[Episode 13: The Hero Runs into Trouble]
This is not a place to stay.
Don't bother
going to look for more puffer fish.
It's easy to catch them.
It's just that no one other than you
dares to cut them open.
You have to prepare them yourself.
We are all looking forward to your recovery.
With you around, the Cao Sect won't fall apart.
That physician told me that in the long run,
healing yourself with the weaker poison of pufferfish
will be fighting poison with poison.
You will become impervious to poison.
That is why over the years,
I've been fighting head-on.
I'd never thought about taking it slow.
Everyone in the Cao Sect comes from poverty.
We need someone tough, like you, to lead us.
By the way,
one of our men came back this morning
saying that Tang Xiao has been looking for you all over the city.
All these years,
how much have you done for him?
How much money have you earned for him?
He didn't show any mercy when things happened.
It's precisely because I've done a lot
and I know a lot
that he's the most worried
about me being alive.
What do you mean?
Are you resorting to underhanded tactics
because beating and torturing me was useless?
I will never testify against the Sect Leader.
Even if you threaten me with my life,
I will still say robbing and killing the traveling merchants
was my idea alone.
Xie Guang.
The raw silk has entered the city
and Qi Tianfeng has been defeated.
Qi Tianfeng is ruthless.
Why are you all so loyal to him?
Is human life
worth nothing in your eyes?
Shut up and kill me!
You don't even care about your own life.
I can't sleep at night.
As soon as I close my eyes, I can...
Coward!
Yes.
How will you find the answer here?
Why haven't you been eating well
and taking care of yourself these days?
You never came when I invited you to.
My sister must have called for you this time.
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
You don't have to pretend around me.
I happened to run into your maid.
She said she had finished sewing your clothes
and was bringing them to you.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't wash the blood off,
and I accidentally ripped it.
I have been fighting to uphold righteousness
and I've traversed the martial world.
But once I see blood,
I became like this again.
You are kind and righteous.
You see people as people.
This is what I know about you.
If you could sleep well the moment you came back,
I would feel a little scared.
It's okay.
This robe is damaged.
How about I make you a new one?
No.
This is a token of our love.
It has to accompany me until I grow old.
Then I'll embroider over where it was ripped.
As for the bloodstain,
I'll dye it black.
You will definitely look good
when you wear it.
There's a dyeing workshop at home.
Let's go now.
My lady, are you relieved now?
Have you talked to the workshop?
Although we don’t have much time to make the tributary cloth,
the craftsmanship mustn’t be careless.
Don't worry.
You don't need to remind me of this.
Are you tired of me nagging too much?
I dare not.
I just meant you've been tiring yourself out over these things.
Don't worry about them anymore.
But there's another thing
I need you to do.
It won't be easy.
Can you go to the Music Office
and see if you can help get Ms. Ke's name off their register?
Are you serious about this?
What's wrong?
Ms. Ke is smart.
Although she's of lowly status,
she's a gracious person.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing.
It's a great thing.
I'm just a little surprised.
At me?
Yes.
It's your fault.
My fault?
It's your fault for being too beautiful.
Why do I feel I've heard that before?
Menglan.
Su Mingyu.
Were you lying
about my Master?
Let her go first.
Answer me!
The Cao Sect has a new leader now.
Qi Tianfeng has been defeated.
It's over.
I advise you to think this through.
Don't seek your own doom.
The Cao Sect
is really gone?
The Cao Sect has been defeated.
It was completely and utterly defeated
by the Su family.
If you want revenge, come for me.
Taking a defenseless woman hostage
isn't the Cao Sect's style.
Don’t play tricks with me!
I'll kill her!
Fine.
Let's play fair.
What are you waiting for?
How about I concede three more moves to you?
Watch who it is you're touching.
You're seeking your own doom.
Do you remember your muttering?
Let me teach you
how to get over this.
Cut off my head
and let my blood splatter on your face.
It's piping hot.
You'll be fine after getting wet.
I've killed people before.
Mingyu!
Don't listen to him. Put the knife down.
Kill me!
You'll recover if you kill me.
Do it!
Mingyu, don't listen to him. Put down the knife.
Come on.
If you had hurt her just now...
Leave.
I'm not the one
who should be repaying your debt.
Coward.
You're just a coward.
It's okay.
This is my choice.
Menglan.
Thank you.
[Zhang’s Pharmacy]
Young Master,
this medicine is supposed to act as an aide.
You must avoid spicy and oily foods.
Don't break the rules before you recover.
You broke the rule?
Willingly so.
Young Master,
the medicine for stabilizing and supplementing the essence is here.
Take care.
Count carefully.
Don't panic, got it?
Hurry up.
You're always so slow.
We're already closing, and you're still so slow.
Aren't you in a hurry to go home?
Close the door.
Look at you.
I have something important to do today.
-Wait.
-Can you work carefully?
Hurry up.
You look so energetic, Mr. Mo. You look good.
Why are you here?
I was going to go look for you.
I brought some herbs that are rare on the market.
They can stabilize and supplement your essence, and are good for relaxing your muscles.
Tell Kang Qiao to avoid oily and spicy foods
while taking them.
Do you want something from me?
Mr. Mo,
you said you had something important to tell me.
What is it?
Didn't Master tell us
to report to him once things are settled?
You disobeyed the order and let the Su family go.
Let’s go and explain as soon as possible.
You can still pretend to be sincere and frightened.
If you drag it out,
it will be hard for you to put on an act.
Not tonight.
Qi Tianfeng hasn't been apprehended yet.
This matter is not over yet.
Didn't I tell you
where he's hiding?
I'm short-handed.
Don't come to me for this.
Kang Qiao hasn't fully recovered.
We lost quite a few shadowmen too.
I don't have anyone for you.
You said
we can work together in the future.
You changed your mind?
Mr. Mo, you're not that kind of person, right?
Besides,
I only want to borrow your shadowmen
to appear more intimidating.
To subdue those stragglers,
we'll still need your eloquence.
I have to go too?
Of course.
Qi Tianfeng killed Mr. Wen.
He is the Yuntai Sect's enemy.
Subduing him
will be a greatly meritorious act.
How would I dare monopolize something like that?
Gui.
Any news?
The ship has moored at the fishing port in the east.
Really?
But there's at least ten li to go.
Why isn't it at a dock nearby?
It's a long story.
But they have promised
to send someone to help us.
We need to get ready to set out as soon as possible.
Master.
Since the pirates' fleet entered the river a few days ago,
the River Defense Office has stepped up its patrols.
Master Guan didn't want to take the risk,
so he moored the ship at the fishing port in the east.
He didn’t want to take the risk?
Wasn’t he the one who entered the river
to transport raw silk into Nandu?
He didn't deny this.
But he asked me to tell you
that he only transported the silk for money.
Now, he is desperate for talented aides
and needs someone like you,
who knows the riverways well, urgently.
Okay, you may leave.
We'll be on standby.
Master.
I have an internal injury at a time like this.
Is the Cao Sect fated to be destroyed?
The men guarding outside are skilled.
With Master Guan's help,
we can definitely get out of here.
I think there are only 15 people in the yard.
We were careless just now
and exposed ourselves.
They are already on guard.
What a good time for you to be careless.
How can we launch a sneak attack?
It doesn't matter.
We have twice as many men as they do.
Even if we attack by force, we'll still win.
Yes.
Even a wall can't stop us.
Even so,
when we guarded the relay station,
we were also heavily outnumbered.
There's only one wall,
so it might not be appropriate to force our way in.
Yun Xiang promised
we will take Qi Tianfeng down without bloodshed.
Let's just stand guard here first.
It's boring to wait.
Let's give him a hard time
by announcing our presence.
Good.
-Okay.
-Let’s go.
How many shadowmen have you brought?
You're rich
and you have strong men and sturdy horses at your disposal.
I'm envious.
Come on.
Let me ask you.
How did you know
I can contact the pirates?
You said it yourself after meeting Master last time.
You once hired hundreds of pirate ships
to rescue victims in Anqing Prefecture.
That’s when you set your eyes on me?
Of course.
Okay.
In the future, I'll be careful
when I'm talking to you.
What are you up to now?
Qi Tianfeng's hideout
is near a smuggling port.
Yes.
Smugglers collude with pirates too, right?
No matter how badly injured he is,
he can still escape by boat.
But he chose to stay
somewhere near Nandu City
to wait for backup.
Maybe we were careless.
There might be unforeseen circumstances today.
Full speed!
Boss, someone is coming.
Old dog!
You don't even dare to show your face.
You call yourself the Iron Hand Demon?
Come out and fight us!
That's right! Come out!
Come out!
Are you hungry after hiding for such a long time,
so you roasted your own balls for food?
No wonder you're all cowards.
I'll kill them all!
Ba.
Don't go out.
Don't fall into their trap.
Even if I die,
I can't let Master suffer this kind of humiliation.
Master ordered us to stand guard in the courtyard.
Brothers.
Calm down.
If they knew we had reinforcements,
they would have attacked us.
It's not too late to take revenge
after Master Guan comes.
They're Yun Xiang's reinforcements.
That's a sea bugle.
They should be pirates.
Pirates?
Will we come back from this alive
to get paid?
Brothers.
I'm afraid we've run into pirates.
If we try to escape, we'll die for sure.
Kill them with me!
Kill them! Kill them!
Don't panic. I'll check it out first.
How dare you draw your swords when I, Guan, am here?
[Pirate, Master Guan]
Everyone,
we're here to settle a score.
We won't get in your way.
I am a man of the sea.
I don't understand your nonsense.
When the people of the sea come ashore,
you must follow the rules of the land.
Master, it's Master Guan.
Since he's here, we should meet.
Open the door.
Master Guan, how have you been?
I'm good, of course.
How did you end up like this?
I made a miscalculation.
I'm afraid I'll have to rely on you in the future.
No problem.
Let's fight into the courtyard
before making any further plans.
Master Guan.
Which of the Masters of the Three Oceans and Seven Islands
do you know, Lass?
Master Liu of Baisha Island.
Five years ago, I traveled across the East Sea
and saved his ship.
Since it's a blood debt,
you may live today.
According to the rules,
I have the final say
on how this blood debt is to be repaid.
You have a temper.
Tell me then.
Master.
Should we start fighting? If this goes on—
Leave Qi Tianfeng to me
and let us go.
Are you kidding me?
This is the rule of the sea.
If you refuse to repay a blood debt, you will suffer a shipwreck.
That’s right.
But I have already killed Master Liu.
It's no one's debt now.
Do I need to pay you back?
If you don't follow the rules of the sea,
then follow the rules of the martial arts world.
Stop!
Ms. Shu.
Don't be rude to Master Guan.
Mo!
Guan.
Why are you here?
-That Lass…
-Master, it's not looking good.
Let's retreat.
How have you been?
Master Qi.
We meet again.
Brothers!
Withdraw!
Master Guan!
You're not a man who goes back on your word.
Ridiculous!
When have I ever had a good reputation?
Qi Tianfeng.
Let's settle our score
once and for all.
If you break your meridians and destroy your internal force,
I guarantee your brothers won't be hurt.
The worst is death.
How can we let Master suffer humiliation?
You are willing to die for him,
but your Master is a righteous man.
He might not be willing to let you do that.
Yun Xiang.
Don't go too far.
Master Qi,
you came to Guanghui Bank to give me pointers.
You must have expended a great deal of energy.
What? Do you want to have another duel today?
Mo Bufan.
You're a lackey to an evildoer.
You'll have it coming to you!
Yun Xiang.
Are you willing to protect my brothers in the Cao Sect?
You still care for your brothers at this juncture?
Okay, I promise you.
I believe you.
-Don’t, Master.
-Go away!
-Master!
Master!
Guan.
Not bad.
You have all of the Three Oceans and Seven Islands under your command.
Even Wang Wufeng hadn't managed to do that
at his peak.
You're amazing.
Things have changed.
There aren't many in this business now.
Anyone who has a few lousy ships
and is brazen enough calls himself a Master.
What's the point of subduing them?
Master.
Here.
How are our men?
Don't worry. They're fine.
What did Mo Bufan give you
to make you turn against me at this juncture?
To be honest,
even if they hadn't shown up,
you wouldn't have gotten to live.
Why are you looking at me?
You have yourself to blame for messing with too many people.
Someone offered me a huge sum to silence you.
I wanted to lure you onto my ship first.
Who offered you money?
Who wants to silence you? Don't you know?
Do I have to say it here?
Tang Xiao, right?
Let's go.
We have nothing to do with this place anymore.
Lean on me.
Who is that young man?
Yun Xiang, what's wrong?
This guy is interesting.
I have been to Nandu twice.
I hear people talking about him everywhere.
I am in need of a smart subordinate.
Why don't you talk to him for me?
Guan, forget it.
He's not easy to deal with.
Don't have designs on him.
Fine.
You made me come here for nothing.
How will you compensate me?
I'll prepare a big gift for you.
Okay.
I'll be off now.
Let me see you off.
Have some water.
So you've been following Tang Xiao's orders?
Ding Yi.
-Master.
-Leave us.
Master.
Go.
Yun Xiang.
You want to investigate the massacre in Luo Family's village?
Let me ask you first.
How deep will you look?
Anyone who was involved must pay the price.
Good.
Very good.
I've been
in a risky trade all my life.
At times, I have done unrighteous acts.
But to be honest,
it wasn't just to make money.
I also want to see those arrogant
and prestigious families
fall from grace
and experience how the rest of the world lives.
So you wanted to use me to deal with the Su family
to fulfill your wish?
Yes.
You can keep investigating
the Luo Family's village case.
But Nandu CIty
will be ruined by you first.
Qi Tianfeng.
You've said many useless things.
Why don't you explain what happened to my family first?
Okay.
I've already talked about your family's armed escort agency.
At this point,
you're still pinning it on Wen Cong?
You used to call him Godfather,
but now you call him by his name.
That means what I said just now...
Y- You believed me.
Ms. Shu.
Wen Cong destroyed the armed escort agency back then.
But now,
Yun Xiang has provoked
the bet between the Su family and me.
Aren't the tactics similar?
Think about it.
Of course,
I did all these.
If you kill me now,
that's right too.
Keep talking about Luo Family's village.
What was the relationship between the massacre and Tang Xiao?
It was a complicated relationship.
What about Wen Cong's imprisonment?
He moved it along.
Tang Xiao is a tyrant in Nandu City,
but he's just a puppet.
Who is behind him?
I've been investigating this for years.
But I'm not sure what is true.
Go on.
Tang Xiao laundered his dirty money using the gambling house
and then transported the money north of the Yangtze River.
Since he wants to cross the river,
he must use the Cao Sect's ships.
One of my trusted subordinates
accidentally heard their secret.
The Lingyuan Sect.
Do you have any evidence?
Where is the henchman you mentioned?
He was ordered to rob the traveling merchants
and never returned.
Since you have no evidence,
keep talking about Luo Family's village.
What did Wen Cong tell you?
He said he just wanted to buy the land.
What happened after that
was totally beyond his expectations.
He wasn't lying.
What happened after that?
What did you do after that?
What did Tang Xiao do?
It was a common way of acquiring land.
They bribed the soldiers and threatened the villagers.
But I don't usually deal with the government
and nor do I have such connections.
So Tang Xiao came to me and said
he had a deep relationship with the Government Office
and offered to mediate.
In other words,
you didn't know a single thing
about the massacre of the village?
I heard about it.
I heard about it before the incident.
But I didn't pay attention to it,
and I didn't tell Wen Cong.
Those were 313 lives.
How could you ignore them?
Yun Xiang.
I was an itinerant
who couldn't even guarantee my own survival.
How could I offend Tang Xiao
for the sake of people I hadn't even met,
much less offend
those soldiers who killed so many people?
That's all I have to say.
I've told you everything I know.
If you follow this lead,
you will find out the truth
about the massacre of Luo Family’s village.
If you manage to catch Tang Xiao,
you can gorge out my eyes
so that I can see
him being destroyed.
I've said everything I need to say.
Please keep your promise
and don't hurt my men.
Let them go.
It's time to end this.
Ms. Shu.
Go ahead.