[English subtitles are available]
[The Ingenious One]
[Episode 8: The Su Family Is in Danger]
I have nothing else I can welcome you with.
This is the mung bean cake I made this noon.
Have a taste.
Thank you.
The mung bean cake you made is different from that sold in the shop.
What special ingredient did you use?
Nothing special. Just the usual ingredients.
You have to take care of so many children.
Yet you had time to make mung cake at noon?
I have a knack for time management.
In the past two years,
how much money has Jishan Hall received?
I don't know the total number.
But every amount of money
is clearly recorded.
You've just checked the books.
Three months ago,
Jin alone sent 60 taels of silver.
Considering current prices, this amount of money
can cover one year's expenditure of an average family.
But you used all that money in one month.
The money that Jin risked his life to earn
was entrusted to the wrong person.
What are the kids?
Why are you hiding like a coward?
Come out and fight with me.
Hand over the kids.
Then I might spare your life.
You got paid. You need to do your job.
I've paid you.
Don't come any closer.
Everyone man I kill
is worth 10 taels of gold.
You are going to pay for that.
Let me guess,
every time a donator found something wrong,
you would take them to the backyard
and kill them, just like what you did to Jin.
Miss.
You are breathless.
You must be badly injured.
You are really unlucky today.
Jin is in a bad mood today.
I'm in an even worse mood.
You are talking nonsense,
waiting for the poison to take effect, right?
You...
What a hypocrite!
Why are you so nosy?
What is the poison on the blade?
It smells so bad.
You can try it yourself.
Dragon series poison. Swimming Dragon?
20 taels of gold for two people.
Little girl, don't be afraid.
We met before. Do you remember?
Why are you alone?
They... They were sold.
Sold?
Don't be afraid. I'll get you out of here.
Turn around.
You know Swimming Dragon?
You've got something.
I'm curious
how you got this poison.
There's no point asking.
As the name indicates, the poison will flow in your blood until you die.
You'll be so painful that you want to me kill you quickly.
A good rider falls off the horseback.
A good swimmer drowns in water.
Because they are careless and arrogant.
You didn't touch me just now.
Is that so?
Red Dragon.
Who are you?
Since you know a lot about Dragon series poison,
you know Red Dragon has different effects on different people.
This poison can kill people in thousands of different ways.
I think your liver will be melted
and you'll bleed to death.
The antidote.
Let's exchange.
Okay.
Don't play any tricks.
I have many ways to deal with you.
Tell me.
Who did you sell the kids to?
To do such business, the buyers are careful.
They will not reveal their names.
I care about the money.
I'm not interested in their names.
Monster.
I asked you not to kill her.
I've asked her about the information we want.
She's useless now.
Little girl.
It's my fault.
I'm too late.
Xiaoyu.
It'll hurt.
We are almost done.
It's done.
Give me your hand.
Bear with it.
Xiaoyu, look. Candied haws.
They are sweet.
These are for you.
Xiaoyu.
If it hurts, you can pinch me.
You can cry or make a scene. Don't hold it in.
Xiaoyu.
This is the last time.
No one will hurt you anymore.
It doesn't hurt.
I'm not afraid.
According to Mrs. Jia,
people go to Jishan Hall to buy children every month.
Girls are sold to be underage prostitutes,
and boys, servants.
Xiaoyu wasn't sold
probably because she hasn't fully recovered.
But where did those kids go?
I told you not to kill her.
She probably didn't know.
But since people bought kids from Jishan Hall regularly,
there must be a whole chain.
With a number of people involved.
It shouldn't be difficult to find clues.
Yun,
do you have any plans?
Not yet.
You ate them all?
You like candied haws so much?
You can ask Brother Mingyu to buy more for you.
Xiaoyu.
Uncle Jin.
Are candied haws delicious?
What else do you want?
I'll buy it for you.
It's late.
To sleep well, she shouldn't eat too much.
I'm full.
Really?
Okay, let's eat tomorrow.
Uncle Jin, your stubble is hard.
Is it?
What's wrong, Xiaoyu?
I miss my father.
Don't be afraid, Xiaoyu.
I will protect you.
My father taught me to sing a nursery rhyme.
He said I can sing it when I miss him.
I'll sing it for you.
Okay.
♫Even if it's just a humble house♫
♫We are happy with it♫
♫Clothes made of cotton♫
♫Are warmer than those made of silk♫
♫Be they long or short♫
Be good, Xiaoyu.
Stop singing.
It's late. Go to bed.
Here.
Jin.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll ask my connections in the government
to help find out where the kids are.
Remember to copy all the account booksbooks
of Jishan Hall.
I'll take a look.
Maybe I can find some clues about the human traffickers.
Thank you.
Jin looks fierce.
But it turns out that he's very gentle.
I didn't think so when we first met.
Now I've realized
Jin is a tough warrior with a tender heart.
I'm both brave and considerate.
You are the same kind of people.
[Guanghui Bank]
All cargo ships owned by Cao Sect are on hold.
A number of sects are colluding.
The Tang family even sent five large boxes of silver
to Cao Sect's headquarters.
Did you find out
who set the fire?
We've been investigating.
But we don't have a clue.
All right, you may leave.
Yes.
Wait.
The three of your subordinates took an order
to kill Jin Biao without our permission.
Do you know that?
Jin Biao?
The swordsman together with Yun Xiang?
Yes.
Jin Biao is a martial arts ace.
Only one of the three survived.
And he's seriously injured.
This is a result of my lax supervision.
It's my fault.
I'll kill him so that no one can find out.
You...
Bastard!
Those people are your men.
Just keep an eye on him.
Take care of the funeral of those two.
Also,
this matter rests here.
Don't mention it again.
Yes.
You may leave.
Master, you've tasted at least a hundred kinds of tea.
The tea tree on the hill is still your favorite.
Tell me about the raw silk.
The silk price has risen to five taels per catty.
It's estimated
the price will double tomorrow.
We spent 8,000 taels to buy in silk today.
But even so,
we still don't have enough inventory.
The 15,000 taels sent by Mr. Tang
will run out soon.
Maybe it will be used up tomorrow.
I know it clearly.
Master,
I've been with you for so many years.
You've never done such business.
Someone from Yuntai is coming.
I have no choice.
I have to take the risk.
Ding Yi,
we can't afford to miss this opportunity.
If we can defeat the Su family
and dominate the business world in Nandu,
Yuntai will be warier of us.
The Tang family will also restrain themselves.
But the Su family is illustrious, notable,
and wealthy.
It's not that easy
to deal with them.
Just wait.
Just like this tea.
Drink slowly.
Only after three brews,
can its true flavor be revealed.
The three shadowmen
didn't know
what dirty business Jishan Hall did.
Take this as a lesson
and lay down strict rules.
Of course.
But I'm worried that...
According to sect rules, we can't recruit secret soldiers without permission.
And now Master is in Nandu.
Are you worried
Yun Xiang will report us to Master?
I don't know.
After all, even you can't see through him.
You don't need to see through everyone.
You just need to remember
everyone is profit-orientated.
If he turns me in,
what benefits can he get?
Why can't the Chamber of Commerce in Nandu
be controlled by Nandu's businessmen?
Why does it have to be Wen Cong?
Uncle Jin, come and get me!
Give it to me.
Come and get me.
Give it to me!
I'm here!
Come after me!
Chase me!
Give me the pinwheel.
Give it to me.
I'm teaching her how to throw darts.
Why did you suddenly come out?
She's just a kid. How can you teach her this?
Don't go out. Play in the room.
I...
How would I know what to play with kids?
Besides, what's wrong with teaching her this?
She can learn to protect herself.
What's wrong with you?
The future of the Su family is hanging by a thread.
Su Mingyu
tackled the government
just for what happened in Jishan Hall.
That "Ten Taels of Gold" is not better.
He has no foundation in Nandu.
However, he insisted on
looking for clues single-handedly.
In addition,
ever since I bought Liansheng House,
no one has been taking good care of it.
Xiaoyu gets along well with all of us.
You are the only one she avoids.
Have you ever thought about the reason?
We are facing so many dangers now.
How can I enjoy
playing with a kid like you do?
Sure enough,
children have sharp eyes.
They can tell who has a warm heart
and who doesn't at a glance.
I don't care
how a kid thinks of me.
The price of raw silk will increase to 5 taels per catty today.
Most of the raw silk stocks in the city
has been controlled by Qi Tianfeng.
This is a life-or-death moment for the Su family.
In such a troubled situation,
it's okay if you don't want to help,
but can you leave me alone?
That ring looks ordinary to me,
but you treasure it.
You said those children had nothing to do with you,
but they are precious to "Ten Taels of Gold".
"Ten Taels of Gold" is anxious
because he doesn't know where the kids are
and what they are suffering from.
Mr. Su is trying his best to help.
What did they do wrong?
I'm trying to reason with you, but you're talking about love with me.
If there is only reason in the world,
everything will be much simpler,
but it's more boring as well.
I heard people from Yuntai
don't engage in love or hatred.
But if you don't know hatred, how can you love?
If you don't know love,
what's the meaning of living?
I don't know why Godfather saved you.
But I'm sure part of that reason is sympathy.
Dad.
Dad!
What's wrong with you, Dad?
Dad.
If you're done, please leave.
I'm not finished.
I don't believe you don't feel sorry for the kids at all.
You've been restless since last night.
You watched the iron hook for a long time.
What's the secret behind it?
It's Guanghui Bank.
Why didn't you tell Jin Biao
such an important clue?
You know his personality.
If he knows,
he will definitely storm into Guanghui Bank.
But Kang Qiao and Jin Biao
are neck and neck.
If I join hands with him against Kang Qiao,
we might have a chance of winning.
Do I have to arm wrestle you
to remind you of your condition?
Maybe I'm no match for Kang Qiao.
But I can deal with you
even if I'm not doing well.
I underestimated you.
Can't you show me some mercy?
Considering how much I don't like you,
that's not an option.
Actually, if "Ten Taels of Gold" finds out the truth,
it will give me an advantage.
If I tell him the truth now, will you think I'm cruel?
What do you mean?
Maybe Mo Bufan did it on purpose,
or maybe it's a misunderstanding.
Whatever the truth is, he must be waiting for me
to question him.
If I let "Ten Taels of Gold" confront him first,
Mo Bufan will feel in the wrong.
Then it'd be easier to make him at my disposal.
As you said,
you didn't tell Jin for his own good.
If you mean what you say,
you still have a conscience.
I just want to wait a little longer.
When everyone is in panic,
the tide will turn in favor of me.
By then, you and Jin
can smash Guanghui Bank.
Then I'll step in to mediate,
forcing Mo Bufan to join my side.
What do you think of my plan?
I touched your hand just now. It felt warm.
I guess it's my illusion.
Your heart is as cold as ice.
Have you seen Xiaoyu's injuries?
Have you ever thought about
how miserable those missing children would be?
Do you know what it means to waste one more day?
She has suffered for so long.
It won't be any worse
if she waits longer.
Yun Xiang.
You fought with your senior.
That's against sect rules.
Is that what all these years of hard cultivation taught you to do?
He took my thing.
People in Yuntai
rely on their wisdom.
Every tangible thing dies.
I want to know
what you are trapped in.
It's just an ornament.
It's just I've been wearing it for a long time.
Don't lie to me.
It's the only thing
my father left to me.
Destroy it.
Destroy it?
I won't unless I die.
If you can let go of your obsession,
you'll be at peace with yourself.
It's a taboo for people of Yuntai
to have obsessions or be trapped in emotions.
Are you going to disobey my order?
If I expelled you from the sect because of this,
your cultivation for years will be in vain.
Will you regret it?
No.
Your worry deflects you from the truth.
Your obsession
will be your Achilles' heel.
[Everlasting Honor of Ancestors]
Young Master.
Qian.
When did you come back?
I felt uneasy.
But I dare not disturb my sister.
That's very considerate of you.
Qian.
Are caravans on their way?
According to Chairman Su's order,
they were divided into 11 teams.
They would take the land route, escorted.
[Silk Escorts]
Ancestors,
bless the Su family to soldier on.
[Two days later]
Slow down.
Give it to me.
Here.
Take it.
Young Master,
are you going to sell
all the raw silk?
Yes, all of it.
This time, all 11 escorted teams
were attacked.
Less than two-tenths of the raw silk got here.
The raw silk we have now
is not enough
for our own production.
Qian,
I have my reasons.
How about this?
We should let your sister decide.
Although we don't have much raw silk,
it's enough to make tribute cloth.
That can also
solve our urgent problem.
Qian, the tribute cloth
isn't our most urgent problem now.
Our priority is to maintain our status
in the Chamber of Commerce.
Sister, are we still in touch with
Eunuch Liu of the Textile Department?
That's great.
Eunuch Liu
has always been very close to us.
If he can help us,
we can deliver
the tribute cloth later.
Eunuch Liu can help us with the tribute cloth
but he can't control the silk market in Nandu.
There are many people in the Nandu business world
coveting the position of chairman.
If we can't lower the silk price
and fail to stabilize the silk market,
sister, you are to blame.
Then, you'll lose the position of chairman
and the Su family's reputation will be greatly damaged.
Could we still be a royal supplier by then?
Sister, Qian,
you should know
what you are doing
and prioritize the problems we are facing.
Let me ask you.
How can we lower the silk price
with just more than ten carts of raw silk?
Well...
This...
Your sister will ask
how to use this small amount of raw silk
to lower the silk price.
Then your answer should be
in the name of the Chamber of Commerce...
Yes.
We can sell raw silk at a low price
in the name of the Chamber of Commerce.
In this way,
we can stop the price of raw silk from rising.
Also, people can see
you have
a strong sense of responsibility.
Anyway, making tribute cloth
is an effectual...
No.
Making tribute cloth is an ineffectual remedy.
To reduce silk prices is to move the needle.
What's wrong?
Sister,
you and Qian don't have to avoid me.
You're already deeply in love.
How can you hide it?
Life is short.
Time flies by.
You don't have to hide it.
Besides, there are only you and me in the Su family.
I consider Qian as a family member.
Did Mr. Yun
teach you this?
Sister.
Does it matter?
Do you think it makes sense too?
Rong,
invite Mr. Yun over
with the highest courtesy.
Okay, I'll do it now.
Mingyu.
Sister.
We have time today.
Why don't you talk with me
about Miss Ke?
Mr. Yun.
Han Xizai.
A masterpiece dating back to the Southern Tang.
I didn't expect it to be in the Su family.
Some people think the story behind the painting is like this.
When the Southern Tang was in decline,
Emperor Li Yun ordered the imperial painter to sneak into Han Xizai's house.
He wanted to see
if the man he intended to appoint as Prime Minister
was really prodigal
and unrestrained
as rumors said.
The painter's skills were excellent.
The painter portrayed the banquet vividly.
The emperor must have seen
Han Xizai indeed led a life of debauchery
and he was not an aspiring man.
Thus, the emperor didn't make Han Xizai an official.
But if you look carefully,
you can see that Han Xizai sat there alone
when others were singing and dancing.
He was frowning.
Maybe the emperor saw
how hedonistic Han Xizai was.
Or, he actually understood Han Xizai's true purpose but didn't point it out.
What do you think?
I think this person is quite interesting.
Han Xizai was sitting by himself at this boisterous banquet.
He was the only one with a sober mind.
Then this monk seems to have entered the secular world by mistake.
He and Han Xizai were best friends.
He knew Han Xizai was ambitious
but Han couldn't realize his aspirations.
Therefore, Han Xizai could only indulge in wine
for the rest of his life.
The sigh of the monk could be heard clearly
even after hundreds of years.
The person with the most acute observation
should be the imperial painter.
It's not difficult to draw people's posture.
But he understood what was behind the posture.
No matter how brilliant the painter was,
he wouldn't know that after dynasties,
someone would
examine his work so carefully.
In this chaotic world, it's difficult to see things clearly.
In fact, you already knew
this isn't Gu Hongzhong's original work.
But you didn't point it out.
The world is chaotic.
Why bother to distinguish the true
from the false?
Just like this painting.
It may not be useful.
It's silent
but it's far better than the noise outside.
Mr. Yun,
unlike Han Xizai,
the Su family has many friends
and we are exactly what we appear to be.
We treat our friends
sincerely.
Since I'm here,
I know it clearly.
[High Quality Raw Silk, 2 Taels per Catty]
Everybody,
the raw silk for today is sold out.
I'm really sorry.
Sold out?
Do you have more tomorrow?
Everyone,
recently the price of raw silk in Nandu
has soared to 6 taels per catty.
Six taels!
So if you want to buy
cheap raw silk,
why don't you come in
to learn what the Su family's plan is?
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming.
I'm truly grateful.
Mr. Su,
we are here today for raw silk.
Yes.
Business is business.
Just tell us how much raw silk you have
and what's the price.
To be honest,
the Su family's silk is already sold out.
Sold out?
Why are we here then?
Let's go.
Please wait.
Although we have no more inventory,
we'll keep selling the raw silk of the Chamber of Commerce
at the price of two taels per catty.
What does this mean?
He doesn't have any raw silk but he'll keep selling at the price of two taels per catty?
Let's listen to his explanation.
What's going on?
Everyone,
this is the deed endorsed by the Chamber of Commerce,
stipulating that the Su family
will sell its raw silk at 2 taels per catty.
There are 80,000 catties in total.
We'll deliver the order in 15 days.
Of course,
if we can't deliver it in 15 days,
we'll make compensation according to the silk price on that day.
[Deed]
[Two taels per catty. 80,000 catties in total. Promise to deliver in 15 days.]
[Nandu Chamber of Commerce]
It's clearly written behind the deed.