[English subtitles are available]
[The Ingenious One]
[Episode 16: A Life-and-Death Battle]
Bravo!
[Liansheng House]
Mr. Wu of Wangyue Pavilion.
A pair of golden dice.
Mr. Su.
Mr. Wu.
A little gift for the opening ceremony.
Thank you.
Come in.
Please come in.
Wish you prosperity.
Let's go in and take a look.
Mr. Liu, please come in.
Please come in.
Qian.
Where is my sister?
The deadline for tribute cloth will be due soon.
She is supervising the workers herself.
She can't make it.
She said she would come to see you
with gifts another day.
I understand. The tribute cloth thing is more important.
She's working hard lately.
Please take care of her.
Don't worry.
This will be a busy day.
Take care of yourself.
Then, suit yourself, Qian.
Mr. Liu.
You're quite like
Chairman Su now.
Mr. Liu, it's an honor
to have you here.
Are you satisfied with
the musicians
you hired from me?
Of course.
The musicians at Zhaixing House are all top-notch.
But there was a misunderstanding.
I hope you don't mind.
Misunderstanding? What is it?
Please come in.
Mr. Kang of Guanghui Bank did come to me
for the girl you mentioned just now.
I bought this girl
from the black market.
She's talented.
So, when Mr. Kang
asked to redeem her,
I didn't agree.
But this girl is the daughter of a good friend of mine
who died some time ago.
She got lost.
That's why she was sold into the black market.
I didn't expect her to end up in Zhaixing House.
A few days ago, another friend of mine went to look for her rashly.
I was afraid that he had disturbed you.
She's fine at Zhaixing House.
No one came to look for her.
My brother is a swordsman.
He went to see you with my jade pendant.
You didn't meet him?
No.
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
Miao,
change a table for customers of Table Tian.
If they don't want to change,
attend to them.
Keep things in order.
Okay.
Tianhu.
We're so busy today. You should go in and help.
Why are you sitting here and slacking off?
Miss,
I'm just taking a break.
I'll go now.
Mr. Tang.
Let me show you how it's done.
I'll make this place bankrupt
within one day.
Just wait and see. Today is the day.
The present from Mr. Tang of the Tangs' Gambling House is a sword.
Wait.
Yun Xiang.
What?
You aren't letting people in?
Why do you have Jin Biao's sword?
I don't want to talk to you.
Get me Yun Xiang.
Well,
it was I who condoned
Wen Cong opening a gambling house
in Nandu.
But after you came here,
you bought Liansheng House and refreshed it.
Now this place is even better
than Tang's House.
Impressive.
Mr. Tang, I know you are joking.
It's all for the prosperity of Nandu.
We're just doing business.
As an old saying goes,
"There is only one sun in the sky and one king in a country."
By the same logic, we can't have two leaders
in the same industry and in the same region.
Am I right?
Judging from what you said,
you want to battle it out with me?
Let's play.
What's the stake then?
You.
I'm the stake?
If you lose,
write a contract to say
that you volunteer
to become my servant.
Is that okay?
What if I win?
You can't win.
In my opinion,
you are actually a cruel person.
You knew I caught Jin Biao.
You've been chatting for so long.
But you didn't mention anything about him.
You're just like Wen Cong.
Exactly.
Poor Jin Biao.
Before we fight it out,
do you dare to hurt him?
Well, well.
You agreed to gamble with me, right?
I can't wait.
Let me tell you the truth.
The place where my family's servants live
is much more luxurious than the houses of common people.
There are plenty of girls like her.
Do you remember Qi Tianfeng?
What does he have in the end?
Don't compare him to me.
I want it to be big and exciting.
Just decide when and where.
I'm looking forward to it.
You seem to be anxious to gamble with me.
How about this?
Let's do it today.
Now and here.
That's what I think as well.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Get ready and come down soon.
Tang Xiao only brought Meizhu this time.
That means Zhong should be guarding Jin.
You must keep in mind
you are going to find out whether Jin is safe.
Don't put yourself in danger.
Have you foreseen
the capture of Ten Taels of Gold?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Don't worry. I know what to do.
Remember, don't try to
save Jin recklessly.
Protect yourself.
I already have a perfect plan.
You didn't nag when I went out in the past.
In the past? I was single back then.
All right. I can take care of it.
Tang Xiao must be
well prepared.
Don't lose.
If we want it in the bag,
we need the support of something.
What?
Don't move.
You have so many sides.
Defeat Tang Xiao first.
Excuse me.
I heard a big joke just now.
I can't wait to share it with you.
Just now,
someone
wanted to compete with me
on gambling.
Who is this?
Who else can it be?
It's the new owner of Liansheng House,
the arrogant Young Master Xiang.
He's seeking his own destruction.
Destruction?
How come you always
walk without any sound?
Tang Xiao is good at cheating.
By "he",
are you referring to Mr. Yun?
Of course not.
Tang Xiao has been pretentious for so many years.
It's time that someone taught him a lesson.
Since Mr. Yun is your friend,
then he is also a friend of the Su family.
I heard someone else say that before.
Qian,
You've been with Ms. Su for so many years.
Why haven't you learned from her
to be elegant and magnanimous?
Menglan.
It has been a long time.
Behave!
Excuse me.
The contract has been drafted.
Mr. Tang, please have a look.
Let's see.
[Contract]
I guess you all want to know the content.
So, I'll read it.
Today,
[Today, I agreed to gamble with Tang Xiao.]
[If Tang Xiao wins, I volunteer to be a servant of the Tang family.]
[Promiser: Yun Xiang]
I agreed to gamble with Tang Xiao.
If Tang Xiao wins,
I volunteer to be a servant of the Tang family.
Promiser: Yun Xiang.
He used himself as the stake.
How long has it been
since we saw such a big gamble last time?
It's really exciting, isn't it?
Yes, it's going to be interesting this time.
Tang Xiao,
what if you lose?
I've never lost in my whole life.
If you defeat me today,
I'll give you half of
the 17 gambling houses our family owns.
What do you think?
I bet half of my fortune and you bet your freedom.
Is that fair?
I'm afraid you'll lose more than that.
I'm afraid you'll be doomed.
Let's start then.
[Tangs' Gambling House]
Where are you sending the food?
Tell me.
The cellar.
The cellar?
Is a swordsman kept there?
Yes.
Go.
Hurry up.
Where is he?
Up there.
He's here again.
Open the door!
You deserve it.
There's no guard outside.
Run!
They were roofied by Master.
They've long lost their mind.
They've been tortured.
Miss.
Miss, please kill us.
We want to die but we are not able to.
Miss.
What are you talking about? Run!
We can't get out.
Master has foretold my fate.
We are destined
to be his slaves.
I've given you options. It's up to you.
Jin.
How do you want to play this round?
Since we're playing, we should play hard.
How about this? Three rounds in total.
How about two out of three?
You are the guest. You decide.
Since you've decided how many rounds there should be,
according to the rules,
we should decide what to play.
Mr. Su,
you sound like a jerk.
I'm the guest.
I use all your stuff.
I should decide what to play as well.
Menglan.
Isn't that right?
You...
It doesn't matter.
Just do as Mr. Tang said.
Learn from him.
Mr. Tang, please.
What should we play?
Cui,
how old are you?
I'm 17.
In this round,
let's bet on whether this girl
can live to 18.
Young Master.
-Young Master, please spare my life.
-Tang Xiao is too unruly.
He's always like this. There's nothing he doesn't dare to do.
Mr. Tang, you must be joking.
No.
I am
being serious.
Just make a guess.
Please spare my life.
I want to see
how Yun Xiang is going to solve the dilemma.
Please spare my life.
If we guess she can live past 18,
are you really going to kill her on the spot?
You already have Menglan,
who's such a beauty.
Don't covet my girl.
It's none of your business.
What can I do?
What can I do to her?
For a flower-like girl like her,
a disease or an accident
can destroy her easily.
What do you think?
Mr. Tang is indeed bold.
I throw in the towel in this round.
No.
That's too hasty.
You...
You're just trying to be the bigger man.
Even if you admitted defeat, you need to play by the rules.
Yun Xiang,
I'll ask you again.
And you need to answer me again.
Can she live to age 18?
I think she's haunted by evil energy.
She's been suffering.
I don't think she'll survive to 18.
Nonsense!
She works for the Tang family.
I'll treat her well.
18?
If I want her to live past 80,
she wouldn't dare to die at 70.
Look at you. I was just kidding.
Stand up.
How rude.
Here.
Thank Mr. Yun for saving my life.
Thank you, Mr. Yun.
Move aside!
Yun Xiang.
Three rounds in total.
I've won the first round.
Winning you in this way
is fair, isn't it?
It's all about flexible strategies and tactics.
Mr. Tang, you really excel at this.
I'm impressed.
Mr. Tang, you are on our turf now.
You must be worried about using our stuff.
It doesn't matter.
If you want to cheat, make sure I can't tell.
As long as you can do that, you win.
Fine.
You seem very confident.
I don't want to make things too complicated.
Let's play something easy.
Let's have a game of luck.
How about word guessing?
Word guessing?
The easier kind or the more difficult one?
Let's take the easier form.
It's the simplest
but the most interesting.
The easy-level word guessing?
What is it?
You don't know?
Even a kid can play that.
Really?
You play instead of me then.
No, no, no. Mr. Tang, it should be you.
Word guessing it is.
I think you believe no one
here in Liansheng House.
How about this?
You can write the word yourself.
Choose one from spring, summer, autumn, and winter.
If I guess right, I win.
One word out of four.
Then before this game starts,
I already have a 75% chance of winning.
Before we know the outcome,
it doesn't matter even if you have a 90% chance.
How confident you are.
Tang Xiao,
don't go too far.
Have I gone too far?
It doesn't matter, Mr. Su.
He's worried that
we would tamper with the paper and ink.
It's reasonable.
Learn from him.
I want to use the paper and ink from your accounting office.
Pretty,
please get those for me.
Tianhu.
Mr. Yun hasn't agreed.
Go ahead.
Meizhu.
Go with her.
She looks dull,
but she's very cunning.
Jin.
Drunken Dragon!
Run!
Yanan, run!
She's not poisoned?
Master wants paper.
Are these clean?
Mr. Yun doesn't want that innocent maid
to die on the spot.
So, he lost the first round.
The second round is crucial.
Why is he still so careless?
It's very likely that he'll cheat.
How can he cheat at word guessing?
He...
You don't know him well.
He looks calm,
making you anxious.
In fact, he has been fully prepared.
This scene
reminds me of the poet, Li Bai.
He once ordered senior officials
to remove his boots and prepare ink for him.
I also want to have a try.
If I take off the boots, it will be smelly.
Right?
Then just grind the inkstick for me.
What do you think, Mr. Su?
Will you
do that?
How dare you compare yourself to Li Bai?
If you don't want to,
then let the beauty do it.
I'll do it.
I must find a chance
to teach Tang Xiao a lesson.
Qian,
you've been through all kinds of hardships.
Why can't you keep calm when things involve the Su family?
Don't worry. The evil will be punished.
He'll kick Tang Xiao's ass for you.
Mr. Mo. Mr. Qian.
Which round is it?
Round two.
Yun Xiang lost the first round.
We'll see the outcome of this round soon.
Why is Mr. Su serving Tang Xiao?
Tang Xiao has always been disorderly.
He's just trying to humiliate Mr. Su.
Then,
Mr. Su is better than Tang Xiao.
What do you mean, Miss Shu?
Mr. Su has been living a luxurious life.
He doesn't know how difficult normal people's life is.
After experiencing this,
he'll know compromise and endurance are fine.
He'll be more broad-minded.
Please.
Am I that pretty?
Don't you know you should recuse?
You can't just say my word out loud
after I finish writing, can you?
You. Come here.
You're kind of chubby.
Go up and block their view.
Be quiet.
Okay.
Go away.
You can guess now.
Guess.
Mr. Tang, calm down.
Let me think about it.
You made the rule yourself.
Take your time.
Beauty, come on.
Wait there to open the box anytime.
This round is crucial.
If Young Master Xiang loses again,
he'll become a servant in the Tang family.
That's not right.
He has always been decisive.
Why is he hesitant suddenly?
He chose to play word guessing himself.
I'm worried that he would fail
if he planned poorly.
Girl.
This is the second round.
He lost the first round.
If he loses again,
he will be Tang Xiao's servant.
Don't worry.
He will surely win.
Mr. Mo,
I have a private request.
May I have a word with you?
I was just thinking about this.
Yun Xiang is betting his freedom on this
but you and Jin Biao were not here.
Jin Biao was captured. That's why.
But I was careless.
I failed to save him.
It's not your fault.
It's right to escape first in that situation.
Drunken Dragon?
You were poisoned by Drunken Dragon.
How did you manage to escape?
Why are you like Yun Xiang?
You both suspect your own people first.
You both borrow shadowmen from me when you need help.
Tang Xiao once brought people to Liansheng House to cause trouble.
I was almost injured by poisonous needles.
That's how I know he's a master of poison.
Therefore, I was fully prepared when I went to rescue Jin.
The medicine I brought couldn't detoxify the poison immediately,
but it could delay the effect of the poison
so that I could have enough energy to escape from Tang's Residence.
I'm just curious.
I didn't suspect you.
How about this?
I'll ask shadowmen to keep an eye on Tang's Residence.
If Jin Biao is transferred,
we'll know.
That's enough. Thank you, Mr. Mo.
Yun Xiang.
It's about sunset. Give your answer quickly.
Why don't you just go back to Tang's Residence with me?
I will definitely go to Tang's Residence.
But not now.
You are dragging your feet.
Yun.
I'm back. Are you more eased?
I feel more than that.
Upon your return,
I suddenly had an idea.
I've made up my mind.
Have you?
Think it through.
You only have one chance.
"Snowflakes are just like petals of pear flowers."
"In the heavy snow, I can barely see the village."
The world turns quiet when heavy snow falls.
I choose winter.
Manager Ke, please reveal the answer.
[Winter]
It's really winter.
He guessed right.
That's unexpected.
Tang Xiao was defeated.
You cheated.
Tang Xiao.
If you can tell me,
how I won,
I can make you the winner of this round.
I've seen so many eyes.
Yours are the most beautiful.
If you keep staring at me with them,
I'll take them home without you.
Did you cheat?
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Round three.
I can decide how to play this round, right?
We've finished two rounds
so quickly.
Mr. Tang, you think it's not fun enough, don't you?
What do you mean?
I'm thinking
how about making this bigger?
I'm listening. I'm afraid you can't make it big enough.
Let's see
if Liansheng House can make more revenues
than Tang's House
in the next three days.
Okay.