This is the best time for you to escape.
Teresita!
I no longer have the reason to live.
Eduardo and I are here for you, Auntie.
We’ll fight against our enemies
side by side.
I need to speak with Adelina.
Do you know where she might be?
I don't know
where Miss Chinita is right now.
Where is she?
I don’t know.
Even if you kill me right now,
my answer won't change.
PREVIOUSLY
At least I'll be with Luisa in paradise.
- Have you found Teresita?
- No.
But we've found her sister, Adelina.
I dreamt of Adelina last night, Tasyo.
I have a bad feeling.
I can feel that my sister is in danger.
- Adelina.
- Hiroshi?
The Japanese are coming.
They’re headed in our direction.
It’s Eduardo.
He's the reason you're after Adelina!
Those siblings are opposing my army.
That's why it's only right
that I have them arrested!
If you’re looking for my brother,
I don’t know where he’s hiding.
I don't need to know
because I know you won't tell me.
I'll use you in some other way.
Whatever it is your planning,
I don't give a damn.
Do what you want
if it pleases you.
That's what playing God
is all about, right?
I assure you
that this time
you won't escape death.
Thank you for bravely defending
this country with us, Minyong.
I'm sorry
if I can't take you back home
to your family.
For we too
have families and loved ones
wanting and waiting for our return.
Take all the supplies we can use.
Be quick.
We'll leave right away
and look for a new camp.
Where's the Colonel?
He's not here.
The authorities have arrested Adelina.
He must have stayed up late
because he visited her last night.
Did they catch Adelina?
What did the Colonel do to her?
Is she still alive?
Why do you ask?
And why…
are you so concerned for her?
I just want to know the details, Colonel.
As an officer, I believe
it is my right to know.
You're right.
It's also my right to know
how Teresita escaped.
There was no sign of forced entry.
I also made sure not to leave anything
inside the room
that Teresita can use to escape.
Which meant…
somebody helped her escape.
What do you think, Akio?
Colonel.
I don't know how she escaped.
With all due respect, sir.
But your wife is your responsibility.
My apologies, but I have to go.
I only came here to submit some paperwork.
Where's your pistol?
Be safe, my friend. Please.
My pistol…
I must've left it in my quarters.
What impeccable timing.
Hiroshi just used a gun against me.
Was that your gun, Akio?
Colonel.
I am not a traitor.
My loyalty and allegiance
is to the Japanese Imperial Army.
Now if you have no more questions,
may I have your permission to leave?
Shimizu.
Keep an eye on Akio.
That lad…
I don't trust him.
Yes, sir.
Nakamura, any updates?
Akio, look at this.
What's this?
The Colonel wants everyone to know
that the vaudeville star,
Adelina Dela Cruz, has been captured.
And that she will only be freed
once Eduardo Dela Cruz
or Teresita Borromeo surrenders.
Don't you think that's a smart move?
Men, distribute these to everyone!
Post these in every corner!
The Colonel wants the word out
as soon as possible.
Yes, sir!
Miss, it's me, Omar.
Please don't hurt me.
- Calm down.
- I'm sorry.
God.
How was your trip?
What's wrong? What's that?
I saw this poster at the checkpoint.
The Japanese soldiers
were giving these away.
They caught Chinita.
And they'll only release her
if Eduardo or I surrender.
That bastard Yuta.
Yuta.
Leave Adelina alone.
I know how important
she is to you, Teresita.
Release my sister at once.
I have a proposition for you, my wife
I'll do what you wish,
but you must come back home to me.
I don't trust you.
I know you won't release
my sister that easily.
I know you're a hoax and a liar, Yuta.
You'll do anything
just to get what you want.
He's just using Adelina to force Teresita
and Eduardo to surrender?
Is Teresita free from Saitoh?
I released Teresita, Hiroshi.
I helped her escape.
Saitoh is suspecting me.
He thinks I'm no longer loyal to him.
If that's the case, why did you call?
Do you think you can order me
to release Adelina?
You're a monster, Yuta.
Listen to me, my wife.
I’m giving you until tonight to come back.
Or else,
something bad will happen to Adelina.
I'll hold the gun myself…
and I will end her life.
Akio.
I know you're a good man
and a good soldier.
So, do what’s right.
Help us escape.
Get us out of here.
The fate and safety of your sister
is in your hands, Teresita.
You must decide.
Will you save her?
Or will you let her die?
Are you crazy?
I can't do that.
The Colonel is going to kill me
if he finds out.
Why do you still fear him?
How long are you going to tolerate
his evil deeds?
Until it's too late?
Until he has killed many more?
He might kill you too,
just like what he did to Colonel Arata.
Akio, you're a good man.
Do what's right.
Open the door.
Is he really going to kill Chinita
if you don't surrender?
Don't you think
he's just trying to scare you?
I know Yuta.
I've seen what he's capable of.
It's me! Teresita didn't do anything!
- Miss Dolores!
- Release Teresita.
Miss Dolores.
Take this woman outside and kill her.
When he says he'll punish anyone
who defies him,
he means it.
That's why I know
that Yuta will really kill my sister
if I don't surrender.
But if you surrender,
how can you be so sure
that he'll free your sister?
That's the problem.
I don't trust Yuta's words and promises.
How can I save my sister
when I know we'll both die
in the hands of that monster?
Colonel.
If Mrs. Saitoh does return,
are you really going to release
Adelina Dela Cruz?
Nakamura.
Do you think I'm a fool?
I will not release Adelina.
I will kill her and her brother,
Eduardo Dela Cruz.
That way,
we can finally silence
those damned guerillas!
Colonel.
I'll be heading out first.
Are you starting to be like Minyong?
How come you're smiling right now?
I was just remembering
the dream Adelina and I once had.
We wanted our own home.
When I get a good job,
I'll buy us a big house
that we can call our own.
I can't wait to live in our very own house
with just the two of us.
But look at us now, Tasyo.
We're hiding from our enemies
deep in the forest.
We're always under the scorching sun,
the chilly rain.
Waiting.
I'd rather wait here
than suffer in the hands of our enemies.
This is paradise for me.
True paradise is a place
where we can all live peacefully
with the ones we love.
I'm left with no other choice,
but to surrender and pray
that Yuta will release my sister.
But if you do that,
you'll be the Colonel's slave forever.
Is there really no other way?
That's where we'll fulfill
and achieve our dreams.
This is hell, Tasyo.
And that's because of our enemies.
In coming!
Please don't shoot.
It's just me!
Wait.
Lower your weapons.
Dad.
How did you find us here?
I know this mountain well. Why, son?
Don't you want to see me?
Are you jealous of them?
Speaking of, where's your dad?
Is he still alive?
Eduardo…
He needs to know about this.
so he can save our sister.
We need to talk, Eduardo.
That's why I'm here.
There's something you need to know.
But I don't know where Eduardo is.
I'm going to get killed,
just like Colonel Arata.
Whom are you referring to, sir?
I caught Captain Watanabe
talking to Hiroshi Tanaka.
What were they talking about?
That's a powerful poison for rats.
It can also kill humans and other animals.
Drink it.
I said drink!
That has poison.
COMING UP
I'll die honorably.
That's a promise.
This is the office of Colonel Yuta Saitoh.
I'll surrender.
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego