Hey! What are you doing?
Don't tear down my theater!
I am the true owner of this property
and that theater!
You have no right
to set foot here, so leave!
-Papa!
-I said leave!
You are disrupting our work!
Hey! Please stop!
Please! We don't want any trouble!
We apologize.
My sincere apologies, sir.
We want to apologize
for what our father did.
We are sorry.
You're only causing trouble here! Get out!
Leave!
-Papa!
-Leave!
-No, you leave!
-Papa!
-I said leave!
Papa, stop!
We don't have any right to this place.
Someone else owns this now, Papa.
Teresita is right.
Let's stop causing trouble.
I don't want you to get into a fight.
And I definitely don't want you hurt.
Dad…
I knew you would be hurt
when you found out.
Please forgive us.
Don’t worry, Papa.
Hush now.
We will buy a new land,
one where we can build the theater on.
Right?
Yeah!
Teresita's right!
We'll have a fresh start.
As long as the three of us are together,
I know there's nothing we can't do!
Isn't that right, Dad?
Dad.
Father.
So your business is still here.
Now is the right time to further expand
our businesses here in the Philippines.
But the Philippines is
still under American control.
And now that our country
is allied with their enemies,
the Americans might make it
difficult for us to do business here.
American rule is about to end.
Japan will be the next to govern here.
Open the box.
Colonel.
What a great gun!
Get these out quickly.
Yes, sir!
Watanabe.
Yes?
I will leave the rest to you.
You understand, right?
Yes, sir!
Good morning.
Here is the payment for your services.
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
No one must know what you have seen here.
Thank you very much.
Did you say that Japan will rule
the Philippines next?
Why do you think so, Father?
I cannot answer that yet.
Come, let me show you inside.
I haven't spoken to Mr. Tanaka
about Hiroshi yet.
But one of these days,
I will invite him out
to finalize our agreement.
I doubt he can refuse my Teresita.
Especially since they look
so good together!
Yes, that's right, my friend.
All right, then. Goodbye.
I've done what you asked me to do.
About?
About Eduardo and Adelina.
My friends will teach them a lesson.
Even if I am hurt,
the day is still so beautiful!
Excuse me, sir.
Are you Eduardo Dela Cruz?
Yeah, that's me.
You're coming with us!
Took you long enough. Go!
Get him out of here!
Mama.
Where have you been?
You just missed Mr. Tanaka and Hiroshi.
Hiroshi?
He's back in the Philippines?
And why is that woman here?
Do you really have no respect?
I've already made it clear.
I don't want to see you
or your damn brother ever again!
What about me?
Do you not wish
to see me as well, Carmela?
Julio?
Goodness gracious!
You're still alive?
And Papa knows
you've sold his land to Mr. Tanaka.
Let me talk to Carmela in private.
Of course, Dad.
Teresita, let's go.
No.
I'm not going anywhere.
I don't want you to fight again.
Mama, Papa.
I will go ahead.
I know this is a…
family matter.
I'll come back later.
Dad.
Why did you sell my theater?
I thought you were dead.
You that I would come back!
I wrote to you before!
And to my children.
I wrote to all of you!
But, Papa, Adelina and I
never received a single letter from you.
So that's why…
I never received a response
from any of you.
Then…
What happened to my letters?
Thank you.
Teresita must never know that
her father has been sending us letters.
If she does, you'll be the one to pay.
Yes, señora.
What do I know about your letters?
You're just making up stories
to make me look bad to our daughter!
I know when you are lying
and when you are telling the truth!
Where are my letters?
-Papa.
-What did you do with my letters?
I did not receive anything!
Enough, Papa.
Please don’t be angry, Papa!
And what can you do…
about the piece of land
I sold to Mr. Tanaka?
Nothing.
I endured for ten years!
Being away from my daughters
to save up money
and rebuild my theater.
I wasn't here to see Teresita
and Adelina grow up in those ten years!
And this is what I come home to?
You sold my land and theater?
My only legacy for my children?
You should have just killed me!
Now, Julio…
Now, you know the feeling…
of hoping and failing…
and being betrayed.
So welcome home, dear husband!
Papa!
Please stop, for heaven’s sake!
Don’t hurt her, Papa!
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Carmela.
Why are you…
still punishing me?
For my past mistakes?
I don’t want to argue with you anymore.
Good, you're finally awake.
Who are you?
What do you need from me?
Why are you doing this?
What have I done to you?
Stay away from the Borromeos!
Or we're coming after your sister next!
Don't you dare.
I will find you and have my revenge
the moment you touch my sister!
What can a nobody like you
do to someone rich and powerful?
Nothing, that's what!
I haven’t changed anything
in your office, Papa.
Adelina and I wanted you
to find it the way you left it.
You two are very good daughters.
I don’t deserve to be your father.
Papa.
Whatever mistakes you made in the past,
they don't matter to us anymore.
So, Papa, don’t mind what Mama said.
This house is still your home.
So you still have
every right to live here.
So your mother and I can keep arguing?
No more.
I don’t want to drag you two into this.
Adelina used this
when she was still living here.
But I don’t know
what she's keeping inside.
What did you say?
"When she was still living here"?
Adelina could no longer
stand Mama's treatment of her.
So she was forced to live there.
That's where her brother Eduardo lives.
That's why, Papa…
I'm begging you, please don't leave.
So we can save Adelina again
and take her back.
Papa!
Adelina!
Adelina, come out of there!
I don’t think anyone’s home, Papa.
The house is locked tight.
You allowed your sister to live
in that miserable house?
Didn’t I leave her with you,
so you could take care of her?
I’m sorry, Papa.
But what could I do against Mama?
Don’t follow me.
Just wait for Adelina and take her home.
Tasyo, where's my brother?
Huh? Well…
I don’t know. Maybe he’s still at home.
I already went there,
but the place was empty.
I thought he might be here. Isn't he?
No, he's not.
Well, maybe…
Why don't you just wait there?
He's probably on his way.
Hold on, Tasyo!
-Why?
-I want to ask you something.
What is it?
Has Hiroshi really returned?
Have you seen your boss' son?
No, not yet.
I just got here.
Where is Eduardo?
Unbelievable.
I thought I told you to leave.
I decided to live here again.
With my two daughters.
Did you hear that, Carmela?
In case you've forgotten,
I am still the head of this family.
So I am still in charge.
But I will fight for my right
and the life I want for my daughter.
I’m only here to look for my brother.
Hiroshi!
Akio!
What do you want?
Come ride with me.
Our childhood friends want to see you.
Adelina!
Is that really Hiroshi?
-It is him.
-Huh?
It really is Hiroshi.
Huh?
He's changed so much.
He's so handsome now.
I don't think so.
Ouch!
I'm more handsome than him!
He's lucky I was sitting earlier.
Don’t you have work to do, Tasyo?
Aren’t you waiting for Eduardo?
Thank you, Lord!
You made my wish come true,
Hiroshi came back.
Enjoy, my friend!
Thank you!
Thanks for the treat, Hiroshi!
This is my first time trying this.
It’s really good!
Don't wolf down your food or you might…
choke on it.
Why are you smiling?
I just remembered someone.
Who?
A childhood friend who was…
very kind to me.
It’s a girl, isn’t it?
A childhood sweetheart?
Cheers!
It’s foolishness to talk about women!
Teresita?
-Adelina.
-What are you doing?
Thank God you’re finally home.
Papa wants you to go
back to the other house.
Really?
But wouldn't this cause even more trouble?
I don't want to be the reason
our father and your mother argue again.
Why, Adelina?
Don’t you want to be with Papa?
You know that's been
my dream for the longest time.
But what about your mother?
Adelina.
Don’t worry.
Mama will never hurt you again.
Papa and I are here to protect you now.
Let's go home.
I want to wait for my brother.
I want to say goodbye to him.
Will that be all right?
All right, go ahead.
I’ll bring your belongings
to the other house, okay?
Oh, are you done packing?
-Wait.
-Just a few more things.
Here.
You don’t have to
worry about Adelina anymore, señora.
I'm sure that, once Eduardo talks to her,
they will never bother you again.
Those siblings aren't my only problem now.
Julio is back too.
How unfortunate that I was born
when men are the heads of the family.
I’ll figure out what to do
with my husband later.
What’s important is that
I save my only daughter
from the misfortune her father will bring.
So drive faster!
Yes, señora.
We caught a lot of snails again today!
I will cook delicious miso-mi for you.
Hey! Nana!
Wait, Nana!
Nana!
Hey, Nana!
Nana?
Is there a snake?
Hey, Nana.
Nana?
Are you okay? Wake up!
Wake up! Are you all right?
Yuki!
Someone is lying on the ground! Come here!
Help me!
Excuse me, miss.
Are you following me?
How delightful!
You still know how to speak Tagalog.
Adelina?
It’s me! My hunch is correct.
You are Hiroshi!
This day is truly beautiful!
I know that Teresita
will have a much better life
if we can agree to marry
your son to my daughter
as soon as possible.
Who is he?
Why did they hurt him like this?
We will find out when he wakes up.
Colonel Arata wants to give you this.
He wants you to look for connections
among the locals who are willing
to cooperate with
our Japanese Imperial Army.
I know someone we can use.
I won’t let her be married off
to a man she doesn’t love.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego