Colonel, according
to the Kempeitai's report,
the prisoners attempted to
seize weapons and escape.
Some of them didn't succeed.
Where is the corpse of Eduardo Dela Cruz?
Colonel, he got away.
My suspicions were right all along.
That's why we need to go home
and tell Adelina about this.
-Let's go.
-Wait.
You can't tell them
what you know about Colonel Yuta.
Your brother isn't here.
We don't even know
if we'll ever see him again.
We need to believe that Eduardo is alive.
I'm going home, sir.
I want to see and embrace
my mother and father.
The Kempeitai are looking for us,
and once they find us,
we will not be the only ones at risk.
Our families will suffer too,
do you understand?
Where is Eduardo now?
Why hasn't he returned?
And who wanted them arrested?
Don't ask any more questions.
What's important is that Eduardo is safe.
Those soldiers will not stop
until they find that fugitive.
Our lives will be in danger.
Our son is really not here.
He hasn't come home since he was arrested.
No! Please, don't!
PREVIOUSLY
Please, have mercy. Please.
Sorry to interrupt.
But these people are old
and cannot even fight us back.
Please show them mercy
and spare their lives.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're right, sir.
We shouldn't have come back.
I shouldn't have come home.
Your parents are safe now.
Let's go.
We need to get away from here.
But where will we go now, sir?
Let's go.
Why haven't they found him?
Nighttime has come,
how is he still missing?
Colonel, they've already searched
his home and the homes of…
Enough!
He's bound to meet up with Teresita.
The Kempeitai already checked
where the young lady is staying, Colonel.
But Dela Cruz was nowhere to be found.
When we arrived there,
they said he hadn't shown up.
And you believed them?
Are you an idiot?
You're not just a soldier.
You're also a man.
I am certain
Dela Cruz will find a way
to see his sister and Teresita again.
Teresita, forgive me.
I'm disobeying your mother
and our father as well.
I want to find Eduardo.
And I'm sure he wants to see us too.
Adelina, I want to see him too.
But how? Where is he?
Could he be hiding at your aunt's house?
Maybe he's with his biological father?
No, Teresita.
I don't think that's possible.
Auntie Amalia despises Eduardo
just as he despises his own father.
But where could he be?
I can see in your eyes
that you're hesitant to trust me, Adelina.
Yes, I am Japanese.
But I'm not your enemy.
I am a friend.
I want nothing but for Eduardo to be safe.
Adelina.
Look into my eyes.
You will see I'm telling the truth.
I give you my word.
I will never do anything to harm
my beloved's brother.
Tell us, Adelina. Where could he be?
If I'm right that Eduardo wants to see us,
I think I know where he might be.
He's probably waiting for us there.
-Where?
Sir.
Why are we here?
My mother is buried here.
You still haven't answered my question.
Sir, what are we doing here?
Are we going to hide here?
Someone is coming.
I see a Japanese soldier, sir.
-We've been followed.
-Eduardo?
Eduardo, are you here?
Eduardo?
My God.
Eduardo!
Eduardo…
Hush, my princesses, I'm here now.
There, there.
Hush now.
Mario, come here.
Don't be afraid.
Come here.
This is Adelina, my sister.
This is Teresita, the woman I love.
And this is Hiroshi.
He's our childhood friend, a Japanese.
Don't worry, he's a good person.
This is Mario. I was with him in prison.
We escaped together.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
Eduardo, we know what happened.
They said you escaped?
Earlier, the Kempeitai came
to the Tanakas looking for you.
I knew they would do that.
That's why I came here.
I knew that if you wanted to see me,
you'd know I would be here.
I hope…
you will not betray us, Hiroshi.
I'm not a traitor, Eduardo.
If I didn't value our friendship,
I would have married Teresita long ago.
But I didn't, right?
Because I know you love her.
Forgive me
if I doubted you before, Hiroshi.
Since the war began,
our hearts have been filled
with doubt and fear.
I hope that no matter what happens,
we keep valuing our friendship
and trust towards each other.
Despite our differences.
You can count on me.
All of you.
Thank you.
May I…
have a moment with Teresita?
I just want to talk to her.
Of course.
Are you hurt?
Teresita.
I'm sorry I didn't make it
to our meeting place.
What's important is you're safe.
You're alive.
That's all that matters to me, Eduardo.
I don't believe
that Eduardo Dela Cruz's sister
doesn't know where he is!
You're stupid to believe them!
But the Kempeitai
have already gone to the house,
and the Tanakas confirmed
he wasn't there--
I don't believe that neither
Teresita nor Adelina know anything.
Since you are all useless,
I will find out the truth myself.
Damn it!
Did the Japanese do this to you?
They tortured every single captive.
My God.
You need to get treated, Eduardo.
No. I'll take care of myself.
Hush now.
Teresita, forgive me.
Eduardo, I'm sorry for interrupting.
But I've been meaning to ask.
Where's Tasyo?
Why isn't he with you?
Where is our friend?
He was shot while we were escaping.
And I don't know if he's still alive…
or dead.
You're lucky to have survived, Filipino.
But I assure you…
you will experience extreme suffering
because of your
and Eduardo Dela Cruz's attempted escape.
-Why don't you just kill me?
-I can!
But I can still use you
against your friend.
My God, poor Tasyo.
I feel the same way.
He had nothing to do with this.
I'm the one they wanted to capture.
They only wanted me,
but they also arrested our friend.
My Lord.
If Tasyo is alive or dead…
God, keep him safe.
But why were you arrested?
What did you do against them?
What do they need from you?
Adelina, it's almost curfew.
We need to leave now.
We might need to leave too, sir.
The Japanese are looking for us right now.
There's still time, Mario.
Why are you in a hurry, Hiroshi?
Don't you want to know
who arrested and tortured me and Tasyo?
Why, Eduardo?
Who had you arrested?
You've met him.
Who, Eduardo?
Their heartless colonel.
Colonel Saitoh Yuta.
Where is our colonel going?
He will look for Eduardo
in the Borromeo family, sir.
I really hope Eduardo gets caught again.
I just want that traitor dead.
He kept asking me
about my father, about his location.
And when we couldn't answer,
we'd be tortured.
Enough! Please!
He was on the way to killing us.
That's why we attempted to escape.
Many of us were unlucky.
Only Mario and I survived.
I knew that colonel was up to no good.
So be careful.
Especially you, Teresita.
You cannot trust that man.
And you must not let our colonel know
you're aware of what happened.
If by chance you encounter him again,
you must pretend you know nothing
about what happened to Eduardo.
He must not know
we met with Eduardo today.
Of course, Hiroshi!
Do you think we're so stupid
that we'll reveal this to that colonel?
Adelina.
I'm just reminding you
because I don't want any of us
to be in danger,
especially since he's not
just an ordinary soldier.
He's cunning and ruthless.
Especially to his enemies.
Hiroshi is right.
Don't act any differently
in front of the Colonel,
so we can ensure your safety.
You want to ensure our safety?
Is anyone even safe in times like these?
I don't think so.
All of us can be arrested…
or killed at any moment.
Damn you, Colonel Saitoh.
Damn him and his fellow men to hell!
I apologize for what happened
and for what may still happen.
But believe me.
This is not easy for me either.
For all of us, Hiroshi.
Especially us Filipinos
who are continuously being invaded.
We need to find a place
for you to hide, Eduardo.
Mario too.
Why don't we try to
talk to Maestro Johnny?
Aren't there many rooms in his theater?
Don't bother.
I won't run or hide.
But you have no other choice, Eduardo.
Let us find a way to save you.
We can't let them arrest you again.
Just look at your wounds.
You're right, Adelina.
Mario and I have no other choice now…
but to go to the mountains.
We'll join the guerrillas
and fight the Japanese.
What did you say, Eduardo?
You will fight the Japanese?
That's right, Adelina.
That's what I want to do.
To fight the new invaders of our country.
For heaven's sake, Eduardo!
That's extremely dangerous.
Eduardo.
I'm against this too.
That's not you.
I thought you never wanted to be involved.
Especially in this war, Eduardo!
I don't want trouble. I don't like war.
But what else can I do?
I'm part of it already.
Mario and I.
What do you want?
Would you want us to hide like rats?
You wouldn't be
proud of someone like that, right?
But Eduardo, we're worried about you!
Eduardo.
I beg you.
Don't do this.
I don't know what I'd do
if anything bad happens to you.
Eduardo.
Teresita.
Adelina.
I saw my fellow prisoners die
at the camp we were imprisoned in.
Pour it on them.
I said, pour it on them!
Many died there.
Too many.
We suffered the terror together.
And now, their lives have been stolen.
Tasyo could be one of them now.
Mario and I owe our survival
to those who have died.
It would be unfair to them
if we become selfish
and not fight to gain justice
for them and our country.
Eduardo, I understand.
I understand you.
But you don't know how to fight.
What you want to do is very dangerous.
You're risking your life.
You're risking Mario's life.
Look at who you're taking with you.
He is too young, Eduardo.
What do you know
about shooting or killing?
Have you done that before?
What if you're killed too, Eduardo?
What if you get killed?
Eduardo is right.
They have no choice.
I'm sure the Kempeitai won't stop
until they are arrested again.
Eduardo.
I understand your decision
and I respect it.
You have a responsibility to your friends,
your people, and your country
to fight against your invaders.
I hope you also understand
my family's decision
to fight for our country too.
Because this is my obligation, Eduardo.
Ours.
To our country.
It's an obligation
I can never turn my back on.
I'm sure the next time we meet, Hiroshi…
we'll be enemies.
But rest assured,
I will still treat you
like a brother and a friend.
Like I told you,
I value our friendship more.
I promise you too, my friend.
That I will treat you the same way.
I see Japanese soldiers, sir.
No matter what happens,
don't be too obvious.
He's not a rightful leader, Hiroshi.
He is interested in Teresita,
but he is heartless.
How can you say that
to our colonel, Adelina?
If you send Adelina away,
I will also leave.
I came back to be with my daughters.
And if I need to talk to Colonel Saitoh
to stop pursuing Teresita, I will do it!
I'm just taking my chances, sir.
Do you know where the guerrillas are?
Are you joining them
or are you Japanese spies?
No, sir!
We are looking for them
so we can join them.
Colonel, why is this man still alive?
I thought he was executed!
I'm glad to meet you all
as our new comrades in this war.
Let me just call our leader.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego