I can't be pregnant.
I don't want to bear and give birth
to the child of a devil.
The Japanese are stricter now,
especially toward men.
The Japanese soldiers might see you
as members of the guerrilla.
Have you had breakfast?
Why? Are you going to feed us?
We have new visitors downstairs.
Sister Maria suspects
that they might be guerrillas.
Where are they? I want to see them.
Teresita!
There's no news about him anywhere.
Didn't I tell you I'd come back?
Bless the Lord Almighty.
You got away from those soldiers.
Colonel, your wife is not inside
the organizer's house.
We will search the entire Metro Manila
if that's what it takes to find her!
I'm carrying the child of the devil.
How can I be with you?
How can I bear to show you
the growing life in my womb?
So the best thing for us
is to forget each other.
PREVIOUSLY
Who killed my father?
- Tell me!
- You're looking at him.
This man is the one
who killed Julio Borromeo!
You said so yourself.
You never wanted
for any of this to happen.
Neither did I, Teresita.
I never wanted to become a guerilla.
I never desired to kill.
But I had to, so I can live.
I had to do it for our people.
I had to fight for our freedom.
I'm just like you.
You who surrendered yourself
to that devil,
so you can live
and save others.
This war may have tainted us for good.
It may have changed us for the worse.
But one thing will never change, Teresita.
And that is my love for you.
I still love you so deeply.
And whatever happens,
my love will never change.
Eduardo.
I love you with all my heart.
I love you very much.
- But I don't know if I can…
- We'll make it work.
As long as we're together, Teresita.
I'm here now.
Please don't push me away.
We'll get through this.
I'll never leave your side.
I promise.
What?
Everything I told Adelina was the truth.
You killed Julio Borromeo!
Are you all right, my love?
Who is this man?
Was he telling the truth?
Did you kill my father?
Tasyo.
Follow me.
Wait, what about them?
Don't worry, they know what to do.
Just follow me.
Hurry.
Who?
Who shot him?
Was it the Japanese?
Did they kill my father?
Monsters!
Anyone can die at war.
Anyone can end up killing
their own comrade.
I can explain.
Is it true?
Is it true or not?
No…
Adelina.
Hiroshi, behind you!
You betrayed us!
Good day to you, sir.
- What's your purpose, sir?
- We're looking for a Filipina.
My wife.
Teresita Borromeo Saitoh.
Forgive me, sir.
But your wife is not here.
Search the entire church for Teresita!
Yes, Colonel!
Eduardo, you have such a kind heart.
I don't know why God
gave me someone like you.
You're a gift, my princess.
Never look down on yourself
because your kindness will always outweigh
everything you've been through.
Dry your tears.
Eduardo.
Eduardo, Colonel Saitoh is there.
He's looking for you, Teresita.
You need to leave now.
Wait, I know a way out of here.
Take these weapons with you.
You'll need those.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Hurry.
Is that why you killed him?
To mask me away from the truth?
- Is that it?
- I killed him
because he betrayed our group.
We were in battle.
Many of us died.
The enemies were prepared.
Smoke filled the air.
It was hard to see anything.
I was terrified for my life.
I panicked, Adelina.
When I saw him,
I thought he was an enemy.
Over here!
He's not here!
Adelina, I didn't know…
I didn't know he was Mr. Borromeo.
I didn't realize that I shot…
and killed your father.
My God!
Are you sure my wife is not here?
Yes, sir. She's not here with us.
Liars!
- Men, find her this instant!
- Yes, sir!
Adelina.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry if I hid the truth.
My love.
But believe me when I say
that it was all an accident.
Why?
Why, why?
Hide, Teresita.
You had your chance, Hiroshi!
You had your chance
when you brought back my father's body!
Why didn't you tell me then?
Why, why?
I couldn't, Adelina.
Mr. Borromeo.
I don't want your daughter to hate me.
Forgive me.
Adelina, I didn't want you to hate me.
I didn't want to lose you.
Forgive me, my love.
I…
Hiroshi.
Stay away from me.
Sister, let's leave this place.
Let's leave this place.
Adelina, Adelina…
I love you.
I don't know…
I don't know
if I can ever forgive you, Hiroshi.
Maybe only time will tell.
Sister, let's go!
Adelina.
I know you're upset
now that you know the truth.
I can't imagine how angry
you must be right now,
but I hope you find it in your heart
to understand Hiroshi's side.
You want me to understand and accept
that he killed my father?
It was an accident, Adelina.
He never wanted that to happen.
But it did happen, Sister.
Just like this war, Adelina…
the unexpected will happen.
And now that we've witnessed
what it has done to our lives…
- Are you okay, Tasyo?
- I'm fine.
- I think that's all of them.
- Teresita.
Teresita?
Teresita!
Adelina, our lives have stopped.
Only time can tell if we survive or not.
Think about the guerillas,
who risk their lives every day at war.
How terrified they must've been
for their lives,
knowing that every battle ground
requires them to sacrifice.
What if you put us
or yourself in Hiroshi's shoes?
What if it was you
who unintentionally killed his father?
Would you want him to forgive you or not?
The war has been cruel to all of us.
It doesn't just bring death.
It also brings anger and dispute.
Eduardo.
She was just here.
How could she disappear?
Let's just go.
Maybe she got scared and ran away.
Teresita!
Forgive me, Eduardo.
I don't want to be a burden to you.
That was the last time
Teresita and Eduardo saw each other.
Same goes for Hiroshi and me.
Until the year 1943 ended,
and comes a new year.
The guerrillas continued fighting.
Let's go, Eduardo.
There are too many of them.
They continued to fight our enemies,
who became more ruthless than before.
It was as if there was no God.
I found an infant!
Like God had abandoned us all.
Then the Americans returned.
God finally gave in to our prayers.
At last, the Americans have came back
to help free the country
from the hands of our ruthless enemies.
They began to infiltrate
the province of Leyte,
where they started to attack
the enemy's forces.
The American general has also returned
with his promise of freedom.
This is Commander Liwayway.
She's one of the most respected
commanders of the Hukbalahap.
Forgive me for intruding.
It's just that I've never met
such a lady who fights
in such clothing…
I don't fight to entice fools like you!
I never should've let her
leave without me.
We'd probably still be together by now.
What could've happened to them?
Morena!
I mean, Sister.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego