Hiroshi asked me a favor.
Take care of my parents.
Don't abandon them.
I cannot just abandon the parents
of Teresita's husband-to-be.
The wedding is off, Mama.
Does honor mean nothing to you?
Our friendship with their family
will be ruined!
You didn't tell us your boss was rich.
You could've asked him for a loan
for your auntie and me.
You can head back home.
-I need to go somewhere.
-Where are you going?
I'm going to scrape together some money!
The Japanese couple are inside.
I'm sure we will gain a lot from this.
They're here.
Our army has arrived.
PREVIOUSLY
The war has reached our country.
I'm sure we'll be blamed
for what's happening.
Hurry!
Francisco! Come here, hurry!
Why are you looking for the driver, Julio?
The war has reached us.
We need to prepare.
-Francisco!
-Yes, señor?
Get the car ready.
We need to buy rice and food to stock up.
-Got it?
-Yes, señor.
-Hurry, before they run out.
-Dad, I'll go with you.
It's dangerous outside.
Just stay at home
and listen to the news on the radio.
No, what if something happens to you?
It's dangerous out there.
I don't want you to get hurt!
Papa, why don't you
let Francisco go alone?
Why must you leave us here?
I agree, Julio. We're all women here.
What if a burglar comes in?
Or a bomb drops on this house?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'll be quick.
-Dad!
-Papa!
-Be safe, Dad!
-Julio!
Why did this have to happen
before Christmas?
Teresita, come. Let's listen to the news.
Come, dear.
Where do you think you're going?
Who are you?
Why did you kill her?
So she can't report us to the constables.
Let's go!
I'm so scared, Chikara.
I never imagined
we'd be in a situation like this.
We'll get through this together.
We have to stay strong for each other.
God Almighty.
Please don't let
anything bad happen to us.
Save our country
from the Japanese invaders.
Please guide our soldiers.
Help them drive away the new conquerors.
Help us, please.
Give us your money and jewelry.
I mean…
-Nicanor, grab everything now!
-Okay.
Do it if you don't want us
to kill you both!
Don't come any closer…
or I'll shoot.
What's taking them so long?
They're handing them out.
-Everybody is paying, right?
-And for you?
Those who came earlier
bought everything already.
They should be used
as cannon fodders against the Japanese!
-Right!
-Calm down, friends!
Let's be patient.
I know we'll be able
to buy rice soon, right?
-Señor.
-Did you get any?
No, every store ran out of stock.
This is the only one open.
-Get in line.
-Okay.
-He's cutting in line!
-Señor, may I buy a sack of rice?
-I can pay double.
-You'll pay double?
Rice is already expensive,
now you're doubling it?
Right, the price has doubled already.
Unbelievable. We've been here all day.
Señor, I'll buy it no matter how much.
Just tell me.
Señor, the rich and the poor
are now on equal footing.
Get back in line.
-See?
-Yeah, serves him right.
-We've been here all day.
-Get back in line.
-Give it to them.
-Do they still have rice?
There's still some.
Haruka, run!
-No! I won't leave you!
-Just go!
Don't move!
Chikara!
Take everything in this house!
-What about the woman?
-I'll take care of her.
I agree with the attack on Pearl Harbor.
Those greedy Americans.
They want to rule the world.
But why the Philippines?
Why did our country invade it too?
Did our government even consider
that we'd be affected by this?
What about our Filipino friends?
They welcomed us and this country
has become our second home.
You're choosing this country over our own?
Can you stop arguing?
You. Whose side are you on?
Is it our country
or the Filipinos and Americans?
Is loyalty only measured by that?
By blindly choosing one's own country
and accepting their violence?
You are defying the Emperor!
Traitor!
You're a disgrace to your family and race!
Enough, Hiroshi.
-Such a disgrace!
-That's enough.
Stop it.
Hey!
What's happening here?
You won't succeed
with your evil plans for this country!
America will destroy you
and your demonic race!
You're all demons!
Stop!
Go away!
Help!
Help! Stop!
No! Stop! Go away!
I wonder what they're talking about.
I'm nervous, Ryo.
They look like they're plotting something.
Do we just wait here until they hurt us?
Mr. Tanaka.
What do you mean?
I don't know
what's happening to my parents.
I don't know if they've been caught.
They could be in danger.
That's why I can't stay here any longer.
But how will you get out of here, Hiroshi?
You scolded us earlier for killing,
yet you killed that Japanese woman.
-You're really something, Lauro.
-Did you see what she did to me?
Just grab their things and go,
so we can have a better Christmas.
Let's go! Hurry up!
Eduardo!
Eduardo.
The war has arrived in our country.
It's complicated.
Especially with what's about to happen
in this country.
Just leave now, Eduardo.
Go to your province.
Go somewhere far from Manila.
It's the only way to be safe.
Hiroshi was referring to the war.
-What?
-What are you saying?
He came to see me this morning.
He told us to leave.
I didn't understand him at first.
But now, I do.
He knew about the war all this time.
I should've listened to him.
But how did Hiroshi know about the war?
Why is my father's name
included on that list?
What is that for, sir?
Could it be Mr. Tanaka?
I saw some documents with him.
Maybe he knows something.
What does our boss have to do
with the war right now?
I don't know.
I need to talk to him. Stay here.
-Eduardo, I'm coming with you!
-Wait, Eduardo!
Why did the Japanese
deceive the Americans?
They even managed to enter our airspace.
MacArthur is a weak general.
He should've prepared the entire USAFFE
long before Pearl Harbor was bombed.
If they were ready,
we wouldn't have been attacked here.
Just a cup, please.
I'm sorry, madam. We're out of rice.
We ran out.
Can't I even buy a scoop?
They're no longer selling rice.
How come? You still have some sacks left.
-Exactly.
-We're not selling those anymore.
Those are reserved for my family.
-What?
You made us line up here.
We waited for so long,
and now you're telling us
we'll get nothing?
-What's your problem?
-Please pity our children, sir.
We've waited in line.
-There's more underneath.
-Every shop is closed.
Oh, no! Those are Japanese planes!
Run!
Don't run, you might get hurt!
They just keep coming.
Looks like the USAFFE
is not stopping them either.
It won't be long before our country
falls into the hands of the Japanese.
God, I hope not.
Let's go, sister.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Tanaka!
Stay there.
Teresita.
Mr. Tanaka.
He's alive.
Mr. Tanaka!
Mr. Tanaka, please wake up.
Mr. Tanaka.
Eduardo, Mrs. Tanaka…
Mr. Tanaka, please wake up.
Mr. Tanaka?
Mr. Tanaka.
It's us.
Adelina and Teresita.
Mr. Tanaka, what happened to you?
Adelina! Teresita!
Bring Mr. Tanaka here, hurry!
Haruka, wake up! Haruka! Ha…
Haruka.
Haruka!
Hey! Haruka!
Hiroshi.
You fell asleep, my friend.
Are you okay?
I had a nightmare.
I really don't feel good
about this place, Ryo.
I must go home.
MacArthur was unprepared
for the Japanese attacks.
I overheard our officials.
Based on the report they gathered,
most American warplanes are in Clark
and have been blown up by the Japanese.
Hey.
Hiroshi.
Where are you going?
So don't be surprised
if nothing is intercepting
the warplanes attacking us.
Damn it.
So that useless general
was slacking off all along.
We did nothing wrong to be detained.
Isn't there a due process
before detaining someone?
We also have the right
to get an attorney to defend us.
This is war.
Your rights are worthless now!
Get back to your place!
Sir, I am begging you.
I just want to make sure
my parents are safe.
You won't step aside?
I'm sincerely asking for forgiveness
for the ongoing Japanese attack
on your country.
But I'm also asking for your understanding
to spare the Japanese residing here.
Most of us have nothing to do
with these atrocities.
You really won't obey?
Sir, I am begging you.
Set us free.
-Let go.
-Aren't we going to help him?
Hey. I said, let go.
Don't make things worse.
We're defenseless against them now!
-Get back!
-Sir, I am begging you.
Don't treat us as enemies, but as humans!
Hiroshi!
Hiroshi! Are you all right?
Julio.
The stores have closed.
There are no more supplies left.
The others won't sell anymore.
It's the same with the neighboring towns.
We still have plenty
of food in the pantry.
Besides, we have a farm.
I'm sure we have plenty of crops.
I don't think this war will last long.
The Americans will surely defeat
and drive those Japanese out
before Christmas!
What if you're wrong?
What if this drags on?
This war won't last, Julio.
Like I said, the Americans won't let
the Japanese take us from them.
Stop worrying!
Do you also smell that stench?
I think something is rotting.
It seems to be coming from a dead animal.
Maybe that's why flies are swarming us.
What about Hiroshi?
What if he finds out about this?
He'll be hurt when he hears about
what happened to his mother.
The war has indeed reached our country.
People are slowly losing
their compassion for one another.
That's why I'm more worried
about what will happen to us
once this war conquers us.
You must be delighted
now that Teresita
is giving Hiroshi to you.
-You're a whore like your mother!
-Señora!
Watanabe, what are you doing here?
The rotten smell is coming from here,
Lieutenant Colonel.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego