If you’re looking for my brother,
I don’t know where he’s hiding.
I'll use you in some other way.
Did they catch Adelina?
What did the Colonel do to her?
Is she still alive?
Why are you so concerned for her?
They'll only release her
if Eduardo or I surrender.
Where's your pistol?
I must've left it in my quarters.
What impeccable timing.
Hiroshi just used a gun against me.
Was that your gun, Akio?
He's just using Adelina to force Teresita
and Eduardo to surrender?
Yuta, leave Adelina alone.
I'll do what you wish,
but you must come back home to me.
Saitoh is suspecting me.
He thinks I'm no longer loyal to him.
I know you're a good man
and a good soldier.
So, do what’s right.
Help us escape.
Get us out of here.
Keep an eye on Akio.
I don't trust him.
I’m giving you until tonight to come back.
Or else, something bad
will happen to Adelina.
Eduardo…
He needs to know about this.
so he can save our sister.
But I don't know where Eduardo is.
We need to talk, Eduardo.
There's something you need to know.
PREVIOUSLY
They want Teresita and I to surrender
in exchange for Adelina's freedom.
That means Teresita escaped.
I saw that poster at Plaza Sta. Cruz.
Saitoh just couldn't leave us alone,
can he?
Why would he?
You’re the face of the resistance.
I’m certain that you know they’ll do
whatever it takes to capture you
so they can weaken your group’s morale
and put an end to this opposition.
That damned Colonel.
Eduardo, does this mean
they're going to kill Adelina
if both of you don't surrender?
Comrades.
I'm sorry,
but I'm going to need your help.
I must save my sister.
I won’t force anyone,
but I'll forever be grateful.
Count me in, Commander.
Me too, Uncle.
We'll help you save your sister.
I’ll go too.
Raise your fists
if you’re willing to help Eduardo!
- Us too, Commander!
- We’re with you, Commander!
Me too, Commander!
Prepare yourselves, men.
We’ll leave as soon as possible.
Lord God.
Please give us
the courage to overcome our situation.
Please save Adelina, Hiroshi, and me.
Adelina.
Why is that soldier looking at us?
What's he going to do to us, Adelina?
My Lord.
Please don't lead us into temptation.
Sister, don’t be afraid.
I know Akio.
He's not a greedy man like Saitoh
who will do anything to get what he wants.
But we should fear him.
Our lives depend on him.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done…
Teresita.
Where are you?
What is it going to be?
Are you coming back?
Or not?
Are you going to disobey me?
As time passes,
I can’t think of any other way
to save my sister.
Be safe out there.
You too, Teresita.
Until we meet again.
- I love you very much.
- I love you very much too.
Colonel.
Why are you back so soon?
Do you have something to report?
I caught Captain Watanabe
talking to Hiroshi Tanaka.
What were they talking about?
Forgive me, Colonel.
But I couldn't hear
what they're talking about.
After their conversation,
he also checked on the nun
and Adelina Dela Cruz
in their cell.
Colonel, your suspicion could be right.
I don't think Captain Watanabe
should be trusted.
Well done.
Thank you.
Yes, sir!
Why do you still fear him?
How long are you going to tolerate
his evil deeds?
Until it's too late?
Until he has killed many more?
He might kill you too,
just like what he did to Colonel Arata.
Akio, you are a good man.
My dear Akio.
How have you been, my son?
Your siblings and I
are doing well here in Nagasaki.
We all miss you so much.
I'm waiting for your return, my son.
Please take care of yourself.
Thank you for bringing honor
to our family.
We're so proud of you.
Watanabe.
Colonel, do you need something from me?
Drink it.
Do I have to repeat myself?
I said drink!
That has poison.
It’s a prank, soldier.
You got me there, Colonel.
Why, Akio?
Is there a reason for me
to take your life away?
None at all, Colonel.
You know how loyal I am to our army.
To our army?
Of course.
But are you loyal to me?
Yes, Colonel.
I am your most loyal soldier.
- Miss!
- Sir.
Any news from your trip?
Did you see anyone
at the house of the Tanakas?
Mr. Hiroshi Tanaka wasn’t there.
The servants were also gone.
Their house looked abandoned to me.
I also asked help from my cousin
whose husband is secretly part
of the resistance.
They might know who Eduardo Dela Cruz is.
They do know him.
But they don't know where he is right now.
I'm so sorry, Miss.
I know this isn't the news
you're expecting.
I’m giving you until tonight to come back.
Or else, something bad
will happen to Adelina.
I will hold the gun myself and kill her.
Looks like I have no choice left.
Captain, you called.
Here are all the documents I have.
Take it.
I'm leaving those to you.
Whatever happens to me,
you'll be the one in charge of everything.
Whatever happens to you?
What do you mean, sir?
I'm going to get killed,
just like Colonel Arata.
Whom are you referring to, sir?
Don't worry.
I'm hard to kill.
Do you perhaps have any enemies
in our army?
You can tell me.
You may go.
Don't tell anyone what I’ve told you.
Yes, sir.
Understood.
Mother.
I'll die honorably.
That's a promise.
This is the office of Colonel Yuta Saitoh.
I'll do as you say, Yuta.
I'll surrender.
I'm glad you made the right decision.
You have nowhere else to go,
but to me.
I’m giving you until today to return.
I'll be waiting for you, Mrs. Saitoh.
Miss, what are you looking for?
I’m looking for something
I can use against that monster.
I have a dagger hidden here somewhere.
I can give it to you if you like.
I won't be able to take that
inside their camp.
If I'm going to be checked,
I need a weapon of some sort,
something that they won't suspect.
Are you sure about your decision?
You’ll be in great danger
if you surrender to the Japanese.
I'm not afraid.
This is the only way to stop Yuta
once and for all.
No, put that bottle down.
That's a powerful poison for rats.
It can also kill humans and other animals.
Especially if you inhale a lot of it.
Who's responsible for this mess?
Remove the dead bodies here!
Quickly!
Can you really die by just inhaling this?
Yes, miss.
That can kill you through your mouth,
nose, eyes, and body.
Even just by a drop.
Miss?
What are you doing?
Commander, there's a checkpoint.
Don't be too obvious.
Where are you headed?
- Did you take a wrong turn?
- I see.
You’re not Japanese, are you?
You’re Filipinos!
I'm ready to kill and die.
I'm going to kill that devil.
My wife has decided to come back
to save Adelina Dela Cruz.
As soon as she returns,
carry out my orders immediately.
- Hiroshi, follow me.
- Where are we going?
To Adelina's cell.
We will set them free.
Adelina?
Where's Adelina?
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego