PREVIOUSLY
It has come to our attention
that one of your people is a spy.
I know and believe Teresita is alive.
I'm sure we’ll find her.
Along with all the women like her.
We're going to free them
from those monsters!
She's just 12 years old.
She's far too young to endure
your disgusting soldiers.
We'll prove to you that someone here
is against us.
- What's that?
- A Makapili.
They're traitors
who report to the enemies.
Arrest him!
Traitor!
Are you really going to marry the Colonel?
Don't worry about me.
Go home to your parents.
Who are your other comrades?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm still wondering
who's the man behind the mask.
The one you call a Makapili.
I'm sure Marcel knows that man.
He was a wearing a disguise,
which meant we might know him too.
Now do you know
how we captured Sergeant Diosdado Reyes?
He was captured by our soldiers yesterday.
Don't even try to escape, you moron!
It's so easy to eliminate the guerrillas.
They confess pretty easily
once they're captured.
- Stop!
- Lift his head!
I'm so glad we met again, soldier.
I'll make you suffer even more.
Continue!
He couldn't bear the pain,
so he switched sides and pointed to you.
He claims you're the one
aiding their group,
supplying them with food and weapons.
Now,
are you still going to deny it?
If I were you,
I'd rather confess now than suffer later.
Who are your other comrades?
Tell me the names
of those treacherous snakes.
Tell me who they are.
I'm not like Dado!
I won't betray…
my people!
I'd rather die
than tell you the truth!
Colonel, why did you kill him?
He was wasting my time.
I still have to prepare for my wedding.
Wedding? You're getting married?
That's right.
So don't bother me for now.
Dispose of him.
Please be careful, Sister.
Watch out for those soldiers.
We'll stay here for now.
Marcel has been captured.
My Lord.
How long must we endure this?
When is General MacArthur coming back?
Who knows.
I think we should just prepare ourselves
for what's going to happen next.
It's time, Manuela.
Your escort is waiting outside.
All right.
Take care.
I have something for you.
I saw this poster on the street.
Isn't that Hiroshi?
What?
Are the Japanese
planning to arrest Hiroshi too?
Did you two meet recently?
Have you heard anything from Hiroshi?
No.
I don't even know where he is.
Who are you?
Thief! Catch him!
What's that noise?
- Is someone there?
- Could it be the guerrillas?
Go check over there!
Now!
Damn! A base nearby is being attacked.
What's happening? Why are there gunshots?
Please, let's take a different route!
We're going to get killed here!
No! Our men need us!
Get ready to fight!
Let's get out of here!
Adelina.
Who's that letter from?
Eduardo.
Juan gave this to me the other day.
I'm just reading it again
to reassure myself
he's still alive out there.
Your brother's alive?
Then the Japanese were lying
when they told everyone he's dead?
Eduardo's very much alive, Luis.
I just hope the same goes for my dad,
Hiroshi, and Teresita.
I hope they're all alive like my brother.
Start the car now! Let's move!
Adelina. Luis.
- Bad news.
- What is it, Nando?
Marcel's dead.
The intel came from our insiders.
The Japanese killed him.
Those bastards!
Hey, you!
Hey!
Stop right there!
- Give that back!
- Give it!
Give it!
- I'm not your enemy.
- Give that back!
- Give that to me!
- Don't fight back!
Thank you for your help, miss.
It means a lot that you came with us.
It's so nice to see you again.
You should thank Colonel Marcos Agustin.
Thank you very much, Colonel.
My name's Eduardo.
Call me Marking.
We're leaving in five minutes!
Make sure you all get the…
- Enemies are approaching.
- Let's move.
- Everyone, move!
- Move!
My Lord. Eduardo?
Eduardo!
Stay back!
- Let's move.
- Go, before they catch up.
Stay back!
Faster!
My heart is bursting
with excitement and joy.
- My Lord.
- What happened?
I saw my fiancé.
I saw Eduardo again.
Wait, isn't he dead?
That's what I thought too.
But I'm sure I wasn't mistaken.
I saw him with my own eyes.
My Lord, thank you for hearing my prayer.
Eduardo's alive.
Good for you.
As for me, I don't even know
if my husband is alive or dead.
I don't even know if he's looking for me.
Forgive me, Norma.
I haven't thought about…
your situation.
Uncle.
I'm glad you all game back alive.
We lost one comrade.
We couldn't even bury his corpse.
Get some rest!
You too, kid.
I heard there was a gunfight earlier.
I'm glad you weren't harmed.
Can you please let go of me?
It's very hot in here.
Could you step out for a bit?
I want to change my clothes.
You can change your clothes right now.
We're getting married, anyway.
Eduardo.
I'll be leaving the camp later at dawn.
I'm going to the city
in hopes of finding my daughter.
I'll go with you, Auntie.
We might get a full moon tomorrow
or the next day.
I was hoping to see my sister again.
And hopefully, Teresita will be there too.
Then you should get some rest.
We have a long journey
ahead of us tomorrow.
I'll just say goodbye to Jorge.
We can't talk to Marcel's family
when their house is surrounded by enemies.
Let's just go before anyone notices us.
We need to avenge Marcel's death.
Take me to the guerillas.
I want to talk to them.
Stop! Why are you outside?
Come with us!
Hey!
Don't shoot!
Everything's all set.
A priest will come tomorrow
to facilitate our wedding.
Tomorrow?
- Yuta, maybe we can…
- We've already talked about this.
Don't try to postpone this any longer.
It would be more favorable for you
to marry me right away.
Our wedding is tomorrow.
So get some rest.
You caught a Japanese soldier.
Not all Japanese are bad.
- You're lying!
- Don't touch him!
COMING UP
Help me. I don't want to die yet.
I'm a friend of Hiroshi.
Looks like they're hiding women
in that garrison.
- What are you going to do, sir?
- I'll get inside that garrison.
Maybe Teresita's inside.
Teresita Borromeo, do you take Yuta Saitoh
to be your lawfully wedded husband?
- Where are the other women?
- One of them is outside.
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego