Please be honest with me.
Where's Teresita?
-I don’t…
-I don’t believe you anymore.
I'm passing these onto you and Julio.
And Eduardo too.
So he can help his fellow guerillas.
Do you know a girl named "Teresita"?
Yes.
She's one of the women we met here.
-Where is she?
-I think she's in her room.
-Teresita, are you there?
-Eduardo?
I won't say goodbye to your father.
But you can't go out at this hour, señora.
I can't, I need to be somewhere.
I'll find Eduardo, Adelina.
I can't stay much longer.
Will I see you again?
Where's Carmela?
She left immediately after we spoke.
-I have a favor to ask you.
-What is it, my friend?
I need to borrow your gun.
I know now where Teresita is.
It's time we attack the Colonel's garrison
and free Teresita from his grasp.
I heard Eduardo.
I really thought he came.
Where's Hiroshi?
He abandoned his post and his men.
Traitor!
We've been betrayed
by Hiroshi and his father!
Have our men look for him.
Arrest him at once.
And if he resists, kill him.
Am I clear?
-Yes, sir!
PREVIOUSLY
Yamamoto!
Carry out my orders immediately.
Yes, sir.
Colonel, there’s one more thing.
Mrs. Borromeo has been requesting
for your presence outside.
Her again?
What does she want now?
Fine.
Just do as I instructed.
Yes, sir.
Kenji.
Hiroshi's still our childhood friend.
We’ve known his father
since we were young.
His father treated us like his sons.
You shouldn’t have reported them.
You could’ve at least told me first.
Why?
Could you have prevented them
from betraying and abandoning
our country and army?
That's her, Eduardo.
She's my Auntie Amalia.
She’s your relative?
Yes, what happened?
We thought she was a Japanese soldier.
That's why Sir Jorge shot her.
Sir!
Why are you here again, Mrs. Borromeo?
Are you really not going to let me see
or speak to my daughter?
Please, Colonel.
I’ve been good to you.
I respected you.
-Please don't deny me--
-Go home.
Auntie?
Auntie Amalia?
Don’t be afraid.
It’s me. Eduardo.
Eduardo?
Colonel, is this…
Is this how you repay me
for my loyalty to you and your army?
Is anyone else with you?
Wait there.
Thank goodness you’re safe.
I'd also like to apologize on behalf
of my comrades for hurting you.
But, Auntie, what happened?
Why are you wearing that uniform?
I escaped from the garrison
the Japanese kept us in.
Eduardo.
Every night…
Every night, they would rape us.
Where is Yoshida?
Call him for me.
I need to talk to him.
Teresita was there too.
You know her, don’t you?
-She’s the daughter…
-You came from the Colonel's garrison?
Yes.
-How did you know?
-Because I was there
and I talked to Teresita.
I just can't believe
you're a victim in this too.
Go to hell.
Sir…
This is what the Japanese soldiers
do to our women.
We can't turn our backs on them now.
I’ve ordered Minyong to gather
the other guerrillas we know.
We can't beat them alone.
We're going to need help
from the other groups.
All we have to do is wait, Eduardo.
We'll attack those bastards
as soon as our brothers get here.
Lauro!
I regret…
the day I accepted
this so-called friendship!
They were all right!
No foreigner will ever love our country!
Die!
I pray you all die!
Are you sure this is their hideout?
Yes, sir.
Why is no one here?
I think they moved elsewhere, Eduardo.
Teresita!
Colonel, good morning.
Good morning.
What happened to you? Why are you injured?
Don't ask any more questions.
Bring the women down!
Yes, sir!
Welcome to your new home, Teresita.
Why did you move us here?
Too many women have escaped.
They might report us to our enemies.
It's no longer safe for us to stay
in that garrison anymore.
Take these women inside!
-Yes, sir!
-Go!
Get inside! Inside now!
Faster!
-Let's go, Alicia.
-I have bad news to tell you, Teresita.
What is it?
Your mother is gone.
She has passed away.
How did my mother die?
What was the cause of her death?
She was killed by your people
who were angry with her
because she was my close friend.
Now do you understand?
Filipinos are not good people.
Because like mine,
your mother was killed by them too.
Yuta, where's my mother’s body?
I want to see her.
Yuta, please. Let me see my mother’s body.
I don't care
if you or your men come along.
I won't allow it.
Now get inside.
How can you be so cold?
She’s still my mother, Yuta!
I can’t believe
God created a monster like you!
Get inside right now!
Go! Get inside!
Go!
We failed to rescue Teresita.
We weren’t able to catch them
back at the garrison.
Looks like the devil outsmarted us again.
Now I don't know
if I should be happy that I survived
while my companions continue to suffer.
I will find them, Auntie.
No matter where they take them.
I'll make sure to kill Saitoh myself
for all the atrocities he has done.
As soon as I get better,
I'll look for Luisa and Lauro.
When I find them, I'll take them here.
We'll join you, Eduardo.
I want to help you search and rescue
those women they've raped.
Uncle Lauro is out of the picture.
He has sided with the enemy.
He has sold his own soul to that devil.
He already turned his back on us.
Is that true, Eduardo?
He's after me…
and all the guerrillas
that are against his master.
Your husband is no longer one of us.
If what you are saying is true…
it pains me
that my own husband has sided with the men
who raped me very single night.
I hope we finally defeat our enemies
so that women like your Auntie Amalia
can find peace.
That counts us too.
Do you still remember what you promised?
That we’d play baseball after the war?
Let’s do that, Eduardo.
Everyone can join.
Men or women, young or old,
we'll include everyone.
It'll be the end of the war.
1942 has just started,
but we've already faced
numerous painful events at the onset.
Let us through.
Adelina, there she is.
I saw them earlier when I passed by,
so I went to pick you up immediately.
WARNING, DON'T BE A TRAITOR
LIKE MRS. CARMELA BORROMEO…
These are very unfortunate events
in our family’s life
and it coincided with the war
that was happening in our country,
which only got worse
after General Douglas MacArthur
left the Philippines.
In the following months, we've suffered
even greater defeat and hardship.
On the same day Bataan fell,
the notorious Death March began.
Thousands of soldiers died
because of fatigue,
thirst, hunger, and disease.
Or they were simply killed by our enemies.
The Japanese Imperial Army
forced more or less 60,000
to 80,000 Filipino and American soldiers
to march from Mariveles, Bataan
to Camp O’Donell in Capas, Tarlac.
Then the enemy proceeded
to strengthen their attacks on Corregidor,
the country’s last defense.
The battle didn’t last long.
Corregidor also fell
to the Land of the Rising Sun.
Japan had completely defeated America.
But they haven't defeated the Filipinos
who continued to fight for our motherland.
Mario?
Eduardo…
Despite being abandoned by the Americans,
the Filipinos kept fighting.
Armies who opposed the Japanese
continued to increase in number.
For each Filipino they kill,
the enemies just keep
profaning their bodies.
Hey, look!
-I’m rich!
-Me too!
Blood and tears flooded
the Pearl of the Orient.
Starvation was rampant,
especially in Manila.
To alleviate our sorrows and fears,
vaudeville continued
to give hope to the people.
You’re from the Philippines, Tuging.
Where else?
Wrong!
I’m not from here.
Wait.
Are you…
Sir Arturo?
Have you returned from America?
That’s not me!
The theater also served as a secret office
and a hideout for spies like me
who continue to help the guerillas.
Ouch! Ouch!
Quit it, Puging! You’re hurting me!
Unbelievable.
I really don’t know where you’re from.
I'm not who you think I am.
Still don't believe me?
Look!
Well?
Are you stupid?
Can you guess now?
I know where you’re from!
From Japan!
Even if Teresita is gone,
I'm still going to fight
for our country and for our people.
If you say no, I won’t think twice
about handing her over
to my soldiers tonight.
It seems like you don’t know
your employees very well.
It has come to our attention
that one of your people is a spy.
-What's that?
-A Makapili.
They're traitors
who report to the enemies.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego