"I love Adelina"?
Really?
Ouch!
I know why he kissed you.
-Can't we just forget about…
-Hiroshi loves you too!
Why are you still here?
Aren't you suspended?
I'd like to hand over
my resignation letter.
PREVIOUSLY
Where is the colonel?
We've been looking for him.
Perhaps, he continued his plan to leave.
To monitor the situation outside.
Our air force will soon be flying here
to the Philippines, Lieutenant Colonel.
What wonderful news.
Now, I am ready to slaughter
the American and Filipino enemies.
I accept and support your marriage.
-I have no objections…
-How can I marry him when he loves you?
I'm calling off the wedding.
I will withdraw from the agreement myself.
Aren't you going to marry her?
I would rather die with honor
than die a liar.
We need to protect you.
You scared me, Chikara.
I thought you were going to shoot him.
My sister loves you.
And please don't think you will die here.
Thank you, my friend.
I know why he kissed you.
-Can't we just forget about…
-Hiroshi loves you too!
I will withdraw from the agreement myself.
But what about Dad's property?
Would you let the Tanakas take it back
and Dad get hurt again?
What about you and Hiroshi?
We both know
I'm not marrying him out of love.
Come on. I thought
we were leaving, Eduardo.
You can go if you want.
My friend.
Aren't you being too protective
of our boss?
What will you do once the constabulary
arrives and takes them away?
And didn't you say Hiroshi warned you
that someone wants to kill you?
What if they come here,
find you, and kill you?
What will you do then?
If that's the case, then so be it.
Teresita won't cry for me, anyway.
What about your sister?
Hiroshi asked me a favor.
I cannot just abandon
the parents of Teresita's husband-to-be.
I'm staying here.
Suit yourself.
Your love is something else.
Poor you.
Papa.
Aren't we going to see your friend?
I thought you said
he could help us with Hiroshi.
A constable gave this to me.
Out of pity.
Let's share it.
Here.
-Here.
-Thank you very much.
No problem.
Yuki. You should eat.
Everyone, gather round.
Let us share this bread.
Here you go.
Here you go. Go on.
Here. Please eat.
Something to fill your stomach.
Thank you.
When we get out of here,
I will take my family to Tom's Dixie.
I will order delicious food
no matter the cost.
Brother, I will cook ramen
for the two of us.
Just thinking about it
makes my mouth water.
Indeed.
And you, sir?
What will you do once we get out of here?
I will go to Adelina.
I will embrace her tightly
and never let her go again.
That's the first thing I will do.
For you and your Adelina?
General…
MacArthur.
You're so weak!
It is to our army's advantage
that General MacArthur is indecisive.
At this very moment,
our brave air force
is on its way to this country.
Forgive me for interrupting,
Lieutenant Colonel.
But let's wait for our colonel to return
before you decide.
When will he return?
Our time is running out.
Does he want the war to reach us here
and we're just standing around?
-Gather round!
-Yes, sir!
Allow me to share
our next course of action.
The Japanese are no longer in this house.
The constabulary has taken them.
-If that's true, why won't you let us in?
-Of course.
I'm the caretaker here,
so I can't just leave
my master's house unattended.
Comrades, we are fellow countrymen.
So please, leave at once
instead of causing more trouble.
Let's go, everyone.
That's right.
My Lord.
I almost peed my pants.
-Uncle.
-Eduardo.
You're still here?
Well, Eduardo wouldn't leave our boss.
I'm already so hungry, I'm going to faint.
If that's the case, then go home.
My friends and I
will take care of this place.
No need, Uncle.
We can handle it.
I don't want to bother anyone else.
He's not just anybody. He's your uncle.
Come on, I'm getting really hungry.
Son, trust me.
I won't neglect your masters.
Even if it means dying here,
I won't just surrender them.
You see?
-You better get going.
-Let's go.
Let's go. We'll be back soon.
I'm really hungry. Let's go.
Thank you.
-Take care.
-We will.
This is the house I was talking about.
The Japanese couple are inside.
I'm sure we will get a lot from this.
I'm sorry, Julio.
But I can't help you with Hiroshi.
But Hiroshi is innocent
I understand, dear.
DR. JUAN G. NOLASCO
MAYOR OF MANILA
But, mayor…
Mayor, they're in a terrible place now.
We also need medical treatment for…
my sister's fiancé.
He was hurt before he was arrested.
Give me the full name of this Hiroshi
and the camp he's in.
I will immediately send for
a doctor to treat him.
That's all I can do for now.
We will accept it, mayor.
Thank you very much.
Eduardo!
-Adelina.
-I thought you were at the Tanakas.
Uncle Lauro is there now.
He and his friends
are watching over the couple.
Have you found Hiroshi?
He's in Intramuros, Eduardo.
Inside the American camp.
I'm glad you found him.
How was he, Teresita?
Are you heading home?
Why don't you ride with us?
So we can tell you what happened.
Move over a bit, Adelina. Give them space.
No, it's okay, Uncle.
Our place is not that far.
-We'll just walk, you go ahead.
-Eduardo, get in.
I said, we're fine.
We'll be off. Take care.
Are you still upset with Teresita?
I guess she really had your hopes up, huh?
Unbelievable.
What are we going to tell the Tanakas?
That we couldn't do anything
to free Hiroshi?
Why aren't you eating? Aren't you hungry?
Then again, who can eat peacefully
at a time like this?
I know.
Teresita, get ready.
We will go to the Tanakas.
I want to know how they're doing.
The wedding's off, Mama.
I'm backing out.
What nonsense is this, my dear?
She's just joking, señora.
Teresita, I've decided, haven't I?
What decision?
Why are you deciding for her?
Adelina has nothing to do
with my decision, Mama.
I changed my mind.
I hope you and Papa can forgive me.
Come here. Talk to me!
Don't force her anymore, Carmela.
I agree with our daughter's decision.
There will be no wedding.
No child of mine will sacrifice
their happiness for me.
The theater will mean nothing
if you sacrifice yourselves for it.
Please, Carmela.
I beg you.
Don't hope for this wedding
to push through.
I won't have it.
We already had an agreement.
Are you prepared to sever
our friendship with them?
-That's what I told Teresita.
-Enough, Adelina!
Don't force Hiroshi on me!
My decision is final!
The wedding is canceled!
Does honor mean nothing to you?
Our friendship with their family
will be ruined!
Do you think I will allow this?
Carmela!
Are we really going to prioritize
our shame, all those other people,
over the happiness of my children?
I don't care about your bastard child!
I have decided!
This conversation is over!
There will be no wedding!
Our message has been sent.
Good. Thank you.
They're here.
Our army has arrived.
Adelina.
That was loud.
Where did that come from?
Dad, look!
Where is that smoke coming from?
God.
What is happening?
God Almighty.
The war has reached our country.
I'm scared, Hiroshi.
I'm sure we'll be blamed
for what's happening.
You are so evil, Uncle.
I know what you did
at the house of the Tanakas.
You and your friends.
You broke into their home and robbed them.
Perhaps, it is better
to let Adelina talk to Hiroshi.
COMING UP
Even if Adelina and Hiroshi
are really the ones in love?
Be quiet!
Our country is already at war.
Don't tell me we're at war
in this house too.
I don't care if I get beaten up or die.
I will avenge my mother.
How did you know this country
would be in danger, Hiroshi?
Is it because of your father's friends?
Or is it because of your father himself?
Would you dare betray
the people precious to you?
Hiroshi, what is the truth?
Are you really a friend,
or are you one of our enemies?
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego