Where did the two children go
and why did you let them leave?
I'm sure this is all
your bastard daughter's fault.
Now do you understand
why I don't want her here?
Enough, Carmela.
Let's not argue about this anymore.
They're back.
Adelina. Teresita.
Where did the two of you go?
We were worried sick.
My apologies, señor.
The two thought to go on a walk.
Teresita.
Next time, tell your mother
whenever you're going out.
So we won't have to worry.
But…
I'm glad.
You two seem like you're getting along.
Very well.
Go wash up.
And get changed.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Meding, get me a glass of water.
Let me.
Here you go, señorita.
Even if you wish to serve me,
I will never accept you.
Because you are…
a bastard.
Meding, take my glass of water to my room.
Tasyo!
Tasyo, what are you doing here?
I don't want to go home yet.
The constables are still there.
Why are they at your house?
They want to arrest my father.
They said my father was an insurgent
against the Americans.
Oh, no! Why is he fighting against them?
My father said that the Americans
are not really helping our country.
They're only helping
the rich and themselves.
While poor people like us are still poor.
Maybe your father is right,
especially since Sir is a bad person.
Who's "Sir"?
Hey! Look who finally decided
to come home.
Sorry, Uncle.
Merese. That's what naughty children get.
Clean the pigsty out back.
You can't sleep
until you're done with your chores.
Yes, Uncle.
When I grow up,
I want to become an insurgent too.
I will punish all our oppressors.
Why did you bring that child back here?
Mama, please don't scold me.
I didn't think
that she would come home with me.
Mr. Juanito wouldn't go home without her.
And Papa told our driver
to keep an eye on Adelina.
Your father really wants to hurt me.
But, Mama…
I feel bad for Adelina and her brother.
Why are you defending those vagrants, huh?
Just, please…
do not get too close to them.
Especially that bastard.
So she'll choose to leave on her own.
Adelina.
Don't just stand there. Come, child.
Don't be shy.
You're really amazing, Uncle.
Doesn't your sister
sing and play the piano well too?
Yes, Uncle.
She's really talented.
Teresita, my dear.
Where are you going?
I want to rest now, Papa.
Can't you stay a little longer?
I want to spend some time
with you and your sister.
Go on. Sit down.
I'm not done rehearsing yet.
Your big sister takes after me.
She is truly very talented.
Come. Sit beside me.
How about you?
I wonder what you got from me.
Why won't you answer me, my dear?
Like you, I also like dancing.
Though I'm not as good as you.
And I'm often chosen
to lead our performances in class.
Is that so?
Then there is no doubt
that you are my daughter.
But you are much more
knowledgeable than I am.
Especially since I don't know…
What do you call the dance
you were performing, Dad?
Don't worry.
Your Mama Carmela
went out to visit her friends.
She's not here.
So you can call me "Dad" all you want.
It's a good thing she's not here.
Or else, she's going to scold me again.
There's no doubt about that.
Tap dance. That's what I perform.
Tap dance?
Don't you know what tap dance is, Adelina?
To tell you the truth,
the first time I saw it
was when Dad was dancing it on stage.
In that case,
welcome to the world of tap dancing.
Come here, you two. Come.
Tap dancing is a type of dance
that combines rhythm and expression
in a symphony of sound and movement.
Watch this.
Your feet aren't just for walking.
You can also use them as an instrument,
much like playing the piano,
guitar, or drums.
Right?
Dad, I feel like my feet want to sing!
You're right, dear.
As a tap dancer,
you are not just a dancer.
You're also a musician.
Both of you, listen to me.
Feel the music in your hearts,
and let the rhythm guide you.
Mama!
Mama.
I just stepped out for a while
and you've already become…
friends with that bastard.
Mama.
I understand how you feel,
but I must admit…
I feel bad whenever I ignore Adelina.
Forgive me, but…
I don't think I can be cruel
to my own sister, Mama.
You're telling our daughter
to stay away from Adelina?
Have you no shame?
You're teaching our daughter
to be cruel to other people.
And what about you, Julio?
What do you know about decency?
You're the one who was unfaithful
and had a child with another woman!
This discussion is over!
You won't hear anything from me.
But I swear, until the day I die,
I will never speak to you
and your bastard child again.
Mom.
I feel so guilty.
They're fighting because of me.
Why did you have to leave me so soon?
Mom…
Wait, Adelina.
Why are you crying?
I was crying earlier too. Just like you.
Is it because
your mother and father fought again?
I'm sorry, Teresita.
I understand if you won't
speak to me ever again.
I won't hold anything against you.
And your mom.
Can you embrace me
just like how you embraced your brother?
I want to know how it feels
to be embraced by a sibling.
Good morning, Mama!
Let's have breakfast.
You go ahead.
I don't want to share a table
with the daughter of Satan's whore.
Teresita. Adelina.
Pack your belongings.
We won't be coming home for a while.
Papa.
Wouldn't Mama hate us even more
if we did that?
Please don't make things worse, Dad.
Just try to calm her down
until she stops hating us.
Just do what I'm telling you. Right now.
Get in the car. Now.
There are so many.
Papa! Look!
There are so many butterflies
and dragonflies.
You're right, Teresita. It's amazing!
Dad, can we catch some?
All right. I'll come with you.
Ingo, please bring our belongings inside.
-Quickly, please.
-Let's go over there.
Sure! Dad!
-Dad!
-Papa…
Long live the Filipino people!
-Papa!
-Jose!
Papa!
-Papa!
-Jose!
Papa!
Jose!
What did you do?
We're already looking into it.
We will investigate
this matter thoroughly.
I'm begging you.
Show some mercy.
I gave my whole life and heart to my art.
Have pity on me. Help me save the theater.
COMING UP
It's a hefty sum,
and I don't have that amount of money.
Hide here.
Eduardo, I think we're going to die here.
They have us surrounded.
Fortunato!
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego