Get ready.
I'll find a way for us to escape.
Do you have any cough medicine?
I'm not feeling well these days.
I think our colonel wants
to embarrass me in this camp
and put you all in danger
as your worthless leader.
Kenji, we'll all die together.
I'm ready for my first mission.
What's your mission?
Love for the Philippines.
Be careful with this.
This will be a big help
for our guerrillas.
My mother…
She was killed by my worthless father,
who is a Filipino.
-But that means you're also Filipino.
-I'm not like you!
I despise the blood of that monster.
We'll go after Adelina Dela Cruz,
and she'll be our bait
to capture her brother.
Hey, kid! Stop!
Hey, stop!
I just to see my wife and daughter again.
-That's all I want.
-It will be granted.
Adelina?
Tell others that no one
should sleep tonight.
I don't know where she is anymore!
PREVIOUSLY
Amalia, we already told the others.
I hope Teresita's plan succeeds.
Amalia.
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
I'm worried about my daughter.
Where could she be right now?
I hope
the Japanese soldiers didn't take her too.
Luisa, come.
Stay here.
Luisa, I want you to stay here for now.
This is just really important.
I'll be back.
Don't worry too much, Amalia.
The Lord protects the innocent children.
Have faith.
The moment we get out of here,
trust that you'll be
with your daughter again.
So don't lose hope.
Would you like us to pray for her?
Well done.
You've completed your mission.
This means you can now
take on bigger missions.
They're going to need
more weapons, Adelina.
Especially since the Americans,
if they're not in jail,
are probably in Bataan and Corregidor.
We need to secure weapons,
anything our guerrillas can use.
Leave it to me.
I'll handle it.
Let's go.
What about my dad?
Did you find out what happened to him?
He's safe.
Keep walking!
Hurry up!
He's currently imprisoned
at Fort Santiago.
Don't worry.
He might be in prison,
but Mr. Julio is alive.
How do you know all this?
How can I be sure
you're telling me the truth?
This is the perfect opportunity for us
to escape this hell.
What about that Devil Colonel?
We have a man inside who confirmed this.
Don't ask who.
The less you know,
the better it will be for you
and our group.
You're right.
He truly is the devil.
He's corrupted by his own thoughts
and experiences,
so we have to get out of here.
Don't worry.
The devil is sleeping soundly.
That monster won't wake easily,
and there are only a few soldiers left.
We can't miss this chance.
Come.
Move closer and I'll tell you our plan.
We have to go. Let's go, Luis.
Wait.
If there's really a man inside,
could you also ask them
to find where those bastards
took Teresita and Auntie Amalia?
Yes, both of them
were taken by those monsters.
And I know they're not in safe hands.
That's why I want to know where.
I will find them myself.
We've already asked about Teresita,
but they still don't know anything.
We'll ask again tomorrow.
Don't forget your new mission.
And be careful, Adelina.
Teresita.
Auntie Amalia.
Wherever you are right now,
I'll find you.
What are you doing here?
Go back to your room.
Scram!
I am engaged to your colonel, soldier.
Or do you want me
to report you to your colonel
for your rude behavior?
Together!
Colonel! Me!
My apologies, madam. Forgive me.
Enough.
Just fetch me some water from the well
and bring it up to the kitchen.
I'll prepare the bath for your colonel.
What?
That's a woman's job.
Are you going to do what I say
or do you want me to report you?
I'm on it.
I hope you can forgive me.
I had no other choice
but to bring you here.
I know you understand why.
I want you to write down
all your camps here, Ryo.
I can't do that, Eduardo.
My fiancée's life is at stake,
as well as the other women
who have been abducted by your soldiers!
So just cooperate and write them down!
What do you want?
Follow me.
The Colonel is calling for you.
Go to your colonel!
To the Colonel! Go!
Amalia, that's enough!
Eduardo.
You're just wasting your time.
I don't think he can be swayed.
He's right. Do you want me to beat you up?
Is this really what you want? To die here?
Write them down and we'll set you free.
Enough!
You killed him.
I regret nothing.
There are no more soldiers!
No more! Go!
Hurry! Just go!
Go.
Wait for me, Eduardo.
We'll meet again soon.
I don't believe
these are the only camps you have!
That's all I know.
I don't know where the others are.
I don't believe you!
Even if you kill me,
I really don't know anything else.
Put the gun down.
I know him, he's not lying.
I guess she was really hungry.
My dear.
Since when have you been
living on the streets?
Leave her to me, Uncle Johnny.
Get some rest. I'll take care of her.
Thank you for letting her stay here.
Women
and especially the children
are truly the most unfortunate
in this damn war.
Luisa.
I know the Lord made a way for us to meet.
However,
you bring very unfortunate news.
But nevertheless,
I'm glad the Japanese soldiers
didn't take you either.
Unlike your mother.
My mother made me run.
She saved me.
Please help me, Adelina.
Please help me find my mother.
Of course.
Of course, Luisa.
Don't worry.
I'll find a way to find her and my sister.
Dry your tears.
Hurry up.
Watch your step.
Auntie Amalia!
Damn women!
Lorena, no! Let's go!
Why did I dream that something bad
happened to Teresita?
My God.
Is this my punishment?
Am I to live alone…
and lose my family?
You know, Luisa…
I'm all alone now just like you.
The Japanese took my family one by one.
Who had you arrested?
Their heartless colonel.
Colonel Saitoh Yuta.
He almost killed us.
That's why we attempted to escape.
Please, not my sister!
-Dad!
-Take Mr. Borromeo!
Dad!
Including the love of my life.
I'm sure the only reason our colonel
wants me to become a soldier
is because he wants me to die.
Thank God I found you, Luisa.
You're my only family right now
that I can hold on to and be stronger for.
Thank you, Luisa.
I promise.
I'll do everything to keep you safe.
I won't allow our enemies to take you.
Hey.
What are you doing?
What is this, Eduardo?
Don't worry. I'm setting you free.
My comrades will drop you off.
Lucas, you and Minyong
drop him off near their camp.
Mario will go with Sir Lucas.
Mario, don't hurt him.
I won't, Eduardo.
Get up from there.
Come on.
We'll be in danger if we let him live.
Finish him off.
Yes, sir.
Come in!
Colonel, we have bad news.
-Are we being attacked?
-No, Colonel.
But the women tried to escape.
How can you be so stupid?
Where's Teresita?
-Did she escape?
-No, sir.
She's outside, along with the other women.
Whoever planned this
will pay dearly.
Call for backup!
Who goes there?
Don't worry.
We'll be together with our families
and loved ones again soon.
Wait, Sir Lucas.
-Why?
-The master's orders.
What are you going to do?
You're worse than a traitor!
Take this woman outside
and kill her there.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego