I'm worried about my daughter.
I hope the Japanese soldiers
didn't take her too.
You've completed your mission.
This means you can now
take on bigger missions.
This is the perfect opportunity for us
to escape this hell.
Teresita. Auntie Amalia.
I'll find you.
Follow me.
The Colonel is calling for you.
I want you to write down
all your camps here, Ryo.
As well as the other women
who have been abducted by your comrades!
So just cooperate
and write down what I'm asking for!
I really don't know anything else.
The women,
especially the children,
are truly the most unfortunate
in this damn war.
Please help me, Adelina.
Please help me find my mother.
Why did I dream that something bad
happened to Teresita?
Colonel, we have bad news.
-Are we being attacked?
-No, Colonel.
But the women tried to escape.
How can you be so stupid?
Where's Teresita? Did she escape?
Don't worry. I'm setting you free.
My comrades will drop you off.
We'll be in danger if we let him live.
Finish him off.
Whoever planned this will pay dearly.
PREVIOUSLY
Why did you run away?
What were you girls thinking?
You know you can't escape!
Now we're all doomed!
Why did you do this?
I have a daughter.
I don't even know if she's alive or dead.
What do you expect us to do?
Do you want us to endure
the abuse forever?
We fought for our freedom
because we're human!
We're still human beings!
Salute!
How many of them escaped?
Colonel, we killed two of them.
Two died.
-But how many escaped?
-Two of them escaped, Colonel.
They also killed two of our soldiers.
Two women managed to escape
and kill two of our soldiers.
You were bested by mere women?
And who among you…
is the idiot responsible for all of this?
No one's going to talk?
Do I have to kill each of you one by one
before someone speaks?
Who started this?
Please spare us!
It was me.
I'm the one responsible for all of this!
Liar.
I thought I could trust you.
But you're worse than a traitor!
You can take my body,
but you can never have my soul!
What did you just say?
Colonel, please forgive us.
We won't do it again.
Teresita, let's beg for forgiveness.
Please forgive us.
Please forgive us. We won't do it again!
I was wrong.
I thought you were like my mother,
but you're nothing like her.
You're a shameless liar.
Just like my father.
And just like him,
you also deserve to die.
Please spare her!
Don't kill her!
You've lost my respect for you.
You deceived me.
Take this woman outside
and kill her there.
Don't kill her!
-Teresita!
-Don't kill her!
Colonel.
Colonel, we're begging you.
If any of you survive…
We won't do it again! Please!
…go to my family.
And tell them…
I love them very much.
-Take her outside!
-Wait!
Wait!
Teresita didn't do anything!
She tried to hide the truth
because she felt sorry for me.
She thought you wouldn't hurt her,
that's why she took the blame.
But the truth is…
it was me!
I started this!
I helped these women escape!
You hear me, Yuta?
You're a worse demon than Satan!
It's me! Teresita didn't do anything!
-Miss Dolores!
-Release Teresita.
Miss Dolores.
Take this woman outside and kill her.
Yuta, I'm begging you!
I won't change my mind.
Someone must be punished for you to learn.
Don't say another word.
You can still do so much for our country.
So please don't throw away your life.
Dolores.
Take her outside.
Now!
Miss Dolores!
My dearly beloved
My soul adores you
You resemble
A fragrant flower
Pure in its cleanliness
Great in beauty
A sweet fountain
Of eternal happiness
A blissful Eden
You abode
Full of laughter
And sweet delight
You're like a radiant fairy
And upon seeing you
A fragrant flower
Immediately blooms
Papa.
Eduardo. Adelina.
Where are you?
I hope you're looking
at the moon right now,
wherever you are.
Are you also gazing
at the moon like I am, Adelina?
I guess
you've realized that the Japanese
were never truly our friends,
but our enemies.
Where are they?
Colonel, Adelina hasn't seen
her brother in a long time.
Hiroshi!
I'll come here every full moon.
Not as a member
of the Japanese Imperial Army,
but as a true and loyal friend.
Kenji.
Lieutenant.
Take your positions.
Warn the others.
There are enemies.
Watch out. Enemies.
They're ready.
Mom?
Mom!
Luisa.
Don't cry.
Don't worry.
We'll be together with our families
and loved ones again soon.
And we'll all be free.
Just a little more patience, okay?
Now, go back to sleep.
I'll be right by your side.
-What?
-We missed our chance.
Not yet.
Let's make them think we're not here,
then we'll attack.
I'm praying, Yuta. Leave me alone.
I just want to apologize
for hurting you earlier.
But it was also your fault for testing
and embarrassing me
in front of my soldiers.
I hope you won't try to escape again.
I'm expecting you not to break my trust.
You only need to love me, Teresita.
And I will do anything to make you happy.
Can you do that?
Under one condition.
You'll respect all the women here
and stop abusing us.
And what use will they be
if I give in to your request?
If not, I won't see you.
Leave me alone.
Teresita.
If you want me to love you
and if you want me to be like your mother,
don't be as cruel as your father.
Now, leave.
Colonel, we've already buried Dolores.
We have nothing else to do.
Can we have the women now?
You idiot!
-Get out!
-Yes, sir!
Teresita.
We still succeeded.
Even if they killed Miss Dolores,
Manuela and Lorena were able to escape.
And more importantly,
you were able to gain back
the devil's trust.
Be patient, Auntie Amalia.
We'll get out of here soon.
You've been staring at that for a while.
Before the sun rises tomorrow,
we'll go on a journey.
We'll check every garrison
and free those women
from the grasp of our enemies.
Forgive me, Lieutenant.
But we've been waiting for a while.
I think the enemy has fled.
Let's head back to the barracks, sir.
No. No one leaves.
I said no one!
What do you even know about war?
You're such a coward!
Let me get some rest.
Enemies nearby!
Lieutenant, we're surrounded.
Use the radio! Call for backup!
We can't do that, sir!
Our radio is broken,
and they haven't sent us a new one!
They may want me to die,
but you can't die here.
Adelina, forgive me.
I don't think I'll see you again.
The coast is clear.
Wait, Sir Lucas.
-Why?
-The master's orders.
What's happening? Why did we stop?
This is not Eduardo's order!
He's not the leader,
so why should I obey him?
Now, move!
What's happening?
What are you going to do?
Mario, out of the way!
Over there! Let's go!
Help! Somebody!
Stop!
Please stop! Spare him, please!
Let's go.
Damn you, Colonel!
This is all your fault, Colonel!
There are two women looking for you.
They said they're Teresita's friends.
They have a message for you.
You're the reason I'm in this war.
Because you don't want to give
your loyalty to our country.
Adelina Dela Cruz is the only key
to Eduardo Dela Cruz's surrender.
That's why I want her
arrested immediately!
Why did you have Ryo killed?
Do you even need to ask?
I'm making arrangements for a ship.
I'm leaving tomorrow night.
I'm going back to Japan.
Where's my daughter?
I'm sure Colonel Yuta
has already punished them all.
What does the Colonel
have to do with this?
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego