Due to our coordinated attacks yesterday,
the strength of the American Far East
Air Force was cut in half.
-Proceed with the land invasion.
-Yes, sir!
Lower the casket.
Hold on!
Hiroshi?
Where will we hide him?
Don't we have a farm?
I don't want to leave Manila.
I need to know where they took
and imprisoned my father.
-But how will you do that, Hiroshi?
-Where? How will you find him, Hiroshi?
We have many friends, mostly my father's.
I'm sure they can help me.
How did you know
this country would be in danger?
What is your connection with
your fellow Japanese invading our country?
I suspect
that Hiroshi's father is a Japanese spy.
We don't know each other, so who are you?
Hiroshi. He's the son of Chikara Tanaka,
one of our army's spies.
If Eduardo's suspicion is correct,
shouldn't you forget
about your feelings for Hiroshi?
I am Hiroshi Tanaka,
ready to offer my life and service
for the glory of Japan.
This isn't what I expected
for our first Christmas dinner
since my return.
What matters most
is that you're here with us again.
Merry Christmas, Papa, Mama.
PREVIOUSLY
For you two.
Adelina said you had nothing
prepared for Christmas Eve.
Why bother celebrating?
We're in the middle of a war.
But still, thank you for the food.
Take those upstairs, Tasyo.
No need to wait for me.
We all know you just want
some time alone with Teresita.
-Shut up.
-Okay, fine.
Don't eat it all, okay?
Leave some for Eduardo.
Sure.
You shouldn't have troubled yourselves.
If Señora finds out,
she'll probably scold or insult me again.
Don't worry, Eduardo.
She's sound asleep. She won't know.
It's actually strange,
how she could sleep so peacefully
despite everything that's happening.
Have you heard the news?
General MacArthur
and his entire force have retreated.
They've left Manila.
Rumors say they headed to Bataan,
and, any day now,
Manila might be declared an open city.
What does that mean, Eduardo?
It means they can no longer defend Manila,
and our city will be free
for enemies to take over.
Merciful Lord.
What you said might actually come true.
The Japanese might succeed in
completely taking over us.
I can't even begin to imagine the horrors
that await us once that happens.
It'll be the same.
We'll surely have to adapt to them.
Aren't we already used to
being conquered by foreigners?
But America's governance
was far more favorable.
Whether it's the Japanese
or the Americans,
what will foreign occupation bring us?
Eduardo.
You sounded like an insurgent just now.
I'm just very frustrated.
It seems our lives have come to a halt.
Not long ago,
you two were performing at the theater
and I was just starting college.
We were full of dreams, and now…
Don't worry.
Everything will be all right.
Just have faith.
Teresita is right.
The disturbance caused by the enemies
has become a common sight for everyone,
that's why our lives just went on.
Even in the world of vaudeville,
which reopened to momentarily sweep away
and calm the fears and worries
of the people.
That's my sister!
And I'm friends with that morena lady!
This was the course of our lives,
-That's my sister!
-even when the Japanese arrived
and attacked our beautiful
and prosperous city of Manila.
MANILA
DECEMBER 27, 1941
Colonel, our long-awaited
moment has finally come!
The key buildings in Manila
have been bombed.
Just as I anticipated.
We must celebrate this event,
for the whole city of Manila
will be soaked in blood.
Please don't come any closer.
-Please.
-Go home now, please!
Go home now!
Lord!
Why did you allow this cruelty to happen?
Why did you take my child?
That was the first time we truly felt
that the war had come to our land.
From that day on,
the lives of the Filipino people
will forever be changed.
Eduardo,
are we going to die too?
No. We'll survive this.
The two of you shouldn't worry.
Why are you still here?
Please, go home.
-Go home now, it's dangerous here.
-Please.
Let's go.
We already knew back then
that it was only a matter of time
before the Japanese
would completely take over Manila.
Hey, Yuki, wake up.
Where's the constabulary?
Ryo, they left in a hurry earlier.
I have no idea where they went.
Good! This is our chance
to get out of here.
He's right. Let's escape now!
Let's hurry while they're not here.
Wait a moment!
Let's not go out yet.
They might just be testing us.
If we try to escape,
they could be waiting for us outside.
That makes sense.
Comrades, let's stay here for now!
Ryo, where could the constabulary be?
Why did they leave us here?
Eduardo!
Tasyo!
What is it, Dado?
They're here.
The Japanese have taken over Manila!
Come with me.
Why? Where are we going?
We'll go to the mountains and fight!
We cannot let them rule over us!
So grab all the weapons you have,
bolos, machetes, knives. Hurry!
Wait. Dado, hold on.
Let's first wait and see
what the Japanese will do
before we decide to fight.
What else is there to wait for, Eduardo?
Do you expect them to be fair to us?
Or maybe you're just scared?
I'm not scared, Dado.
If I go to the mountains now,
what will happen
to my sister and Teresita?
Am I supposed to leave them now,
when nothing is certain?
Are you going to place them
before your country?
Admit it, you're just scared!
Wait! Hey now, wait! Calm down.
We'll gain nothing
if we just fight blindly, Dado.
And understand this, Dado,
we're not cowards
because Eduardo and I are ready to fight!
But he's right.
I want to know what they plan to do
before we fight or do anything.
Do what you want.
I just know I'm going to fight.
Wait. Where are you going?
To Adelina's.
I'm going to check on their situation.
Make sure it's secured tightly
so it doesn't fall.
Francisco, make sure it's level.
Carmela!
What are you doing?
Why is it up there?
Mama, it's embarrassing to our neighbors.
They might think
we're supporting the enemies.
Should I still care
about what others think?
America has been defeated
and they're cowards for fleeing to Bataan!
We can't rely on them anymore.
There's a new country in charge,
so we need to show the Japanese
we can cooperate with them.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You know what they call you?
A traitor.
And an opportunist.
Are you referring to yourself?
In this household,
there's only one traitor I know
and it's not me.
Do whatever you want.
My daughters, let's go inside.
Dad, just a moment.
I need to talk to Eduardo.
Get inside, Teresita.
-Eduardo.
-Adelina.
Are you aware of what's happening?
Yes.
So as much as possible,
you and Teresita shouldn't go outside.
It's better to be careful.
But Eduardo,
isn't there still something good
about what's happening now?
Hiroshi can finally come out from hiding.
We'll see our friend again, right?
Our great Japanese Imperial Army!
Hiroshi, is that you?
It's him! What happened?
Our soldiers
have successfully entered Manila.
You are all free now.
Long live the Emperor!
Long live our Japanese Imperial Army!
-Long live!
Long live!
Hiroshi.
Thank you very much
for coming back to free us.
But…
you're wearing the uniform of our army.
Have you become one of them too?
I don't want to
talk about it anymore, Ryo.
What are you waiting for?
Leave now, go home.
Thank you.
Yuki, let's go.
Hiroshi, you are a good person.
May you not be changed by anger
because of what happened to your family.
All the detained Japanese civilians
were released that same day…
including Hiroshi's father.
-Many imprisoned Japanese
-Hey!
were filled with resentment
for what happened to them,
so some of them took revenge
on those who were not their own.
How embarrassing!
Have a taste of your own medicine!
Let's go here! Come with us!
Though the war had just started,
many hearts
were already filled with hatred.
Shut up!
They caught and imprisoned
all the Americans, civilian or not,
along with their Filipino
constabularies and soldiers.
You are the enemy so it's just right
to kill all of you!
Just die!
Everything in this country
has truly changed.
May you two never forget to pray.
Eduardo, would you like to come with me
to Escolta or Sta. Cruz Plaza?
Come on, let's survey the area.
We might see some Japanese there.
Hey! Do you even hear me?
You're so deep in thought.
We don't know
when we'll die, right, Tasyo?
Do you think the Japanese
are going to hurt us too?
Do you think they're as ruthless
as the Americans who killed my father?
What do we even know?
Still…
I want to die without any secrets.
Where are you going?
Who are you?
Why are you in my house?
Don't you recognize me anymore, Father?
Hiroshi?
Father.
My God!
Eduardo.
-Sorry.
-It's you.
Sorry if I startled you
and sorry for daring to enter your room.
But this is the only way
I can talk to you, Teresita.
Is there something you need?
What is it?
Teresita, I don't want you to think
that I'm disrespectful.
But we don't know
what will happen to us, do we?
So I want you to know
that nothing has changed in me.
I still love you even now.
Here.
This rosary belonged to my mother.
I want to give it to you
so it can protect you.
Thank you very much.
But you don't have
to give this to me, Eduardo.
Take it.
Why can't you accept it, Teresita?
Is your heart no longer for me?
Has someone completely taken you away?
I already told you, didn't I?
I won't be marrying Hiroshi anymore.
So why would you think that?
But why won't you accept my gift?
Because I'm ashamed to take
the only remembrance
you have of your mother.
Perhaps your feelings for me
have disappeared completely.
Right. Who am I, anyway?
Apologies for wasting your time
with my confession, Teresita.
Just forget about this moment…
Why do you think that way, my love?
What did you say?
You love me?
I called the wedding off…
not only for Hiroshi and Adelina,
but also for you.
For the both of us.
So my love,
why are you wondering now?
You took away the fear and sorrow
in my heart, Teresita.
You've made me very happy
despite everything happening around us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Teresita.
Thank you, my love.
What are you doing, Teresita?
Manila Hotel.
The former home of
the American General MacArthur.
Who would have thought
this would fall into our hands?
I'm really glad that you want to serve now
and help our country.
I don't want to ruin what little happiness
my brother has, Tasyo.
But I also know the señora
will do everything
to break my two siblings apart.
Good thing I came here.
I had a feeling you would be here.
It is time to clean up
all the filth and corruption
that America brought to this country.
It's a good thing our flag is already
at the house of the Borromeos.
Why did you go to the Tanakas?
We had an important discussion
about you and Hiroshi.
About your upcoming wedding.
COMING UP
Subtitle translations by:
Nehemiarey Dallego