Colonel.
I found a house that we can use
as our headquarters
once we occupy this city.
Excellent!
You are truly reliable.
See you later.
Yes, sir!
The house is ours.
The beautiful woman there is mine.
Ma…
Ma, how are you?
Ma, we're at the hospital.
You lost consciousness
when you fell down the stairs earlier.
Do you see now, my dear…
what happens when you are being stubborn?
Do you want me to die?
No, Ma.
Forgive me, it's all my fault.
I'm not angry with you.
Just promise me one thing from now on.
You will never leave me again.
Promise?
I promise.
You may be a hothead.
But you're a good person, Eduardo.
Stop flattering me, Adelina.
But thank you.
We really are siblings.
How is the señora?
She is conscious now.
We are just waiting for the test results.
That's good.
All right, we'll go ahead.
Señora might see us if we stay.
Wait.
I want to thank you both.
Especially you, Eduardo.
There are not many people like you.
I know my mother treated you horribly,
but, despite everything,
her false accusations,
you still helped her.
You're welcome, Teresita.
What matters is that, you believe
I had nothing to do
with what happened to your mother.
I believe you.
Forgive me if I doubted you.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Let's go, Adelina.
Adelina.
Are we all right now?
Are you no longer angry with me?
I know the conditions my mother gave you.
Yolanda told me everything.
I don't want you two to avoid me.
Especially you.
You know I would never do that, Teresita.
All right.
You should go now.
I'm glad the señora survived that fall.
It would be a tragedy
if Teresita became an orphan.
I wish the señora would just pass away,
so no one would belittle us anymore.
Just kidding.
But, Eduardo, tell me the truth.
Do you like my sister?
Is that why you still
helped her evil mother?
Was it for Teresita's sake?
Why are you quiet all of a sudden?
I knew it!
That's the secret
you can't tell me, isn't it?
No wonder you always followed us around.
All this time, I thought
you just wanted to protect me.
If you tell Teresita,
you'll be in big trouble.
So it's true?
You like my sister Teresita?
Don't you ever tell her, okay?
Or we're going to have a problem.
Okay, Eduardo. I won't tell Teresita.
Unless you tell her first.
-I don't want it to come from me.
-That's right.
But what now?
Isn't the señora planning to marry off
Teresita to another man?
Who is she marrying her off to?
Do you know?
No.
The señora didn't mention anyone.
Even Teresita doesn't know
who she's going to marry.
Why were we born poor?
Why, right?
Let it go, Eduardo.
I'm sure you're more handsome
than the rascal
the señora wants for Teresita.
This is why I love you, Adelina.
-Eduardo, my hair!
-Really? "Rascal"?
Forgive me.
-Buy me hopia.
-Hopia?
-We have no money.
-I know which store…
My goodness!
Forgive us, sir!
Adelina.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I was just thinking about
the man in the car.
What do you think, Eduardo?
Is he Chinese or Japanese?
How would I know? Why should we care?
Nothing.
I just thought he was handsome.
What?
-"Handsome"?
-The passenger. Did you see him?
Wasn't he handsome? And he looks rich too.
What are you…
Adelina, were you ogling him?
I just said he looked handsome.
I wasn't ogling!
You better behave. No man will
respect you if you're like that.
Me? "Like that"?
Is that what you think of me?
You're the one who likes…
Your mouth, okay?
-Your mouth.
-Am I right or wrong?
Are you surprised I got out?
-Come here, let's talk.
-Eduardo, leave him alone.
There you go again.
-Liar!
-Enough!
Come on, let's go home.
Hiroshi!
Look at you, you've grown so much.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Thank you, Mother.
Father.
Welcome home, my son.
Come inside.
Good evening, señora.
Francisco.
I brought food and clothes.
Please put them there.
Forgive me for visiting this late.
I just found out what happened to you.
What did you say?
If you didn't bring me here
to the hospital, then who did?
Ma…
Eduardo brought you here.
He and Adelina helped me
get you to the hospital.
Damn it.
Ma…
Instead of getting angry at them,
let's just be thankful.
If it weren't for them,
you wouldn't have made it here on time.
Stop being angry at them.
I also hope you withdraw
your case against Eduardo
since I know you and Francisco
are making up stories against them.
Please, Ma.
I hope you don't bother
Adelina and Eduardo anymore.
I promise, Mama. I will never leave you.
Dear, I'd rather not talk about them.
You should just go to the doctor.
Ask if my test results are ready.
Okay, Mama.
I saw the siblings earlier.
I was surprised the constabulary
released Eduardo so soon.
I'm sure Adelina told Teresita about it,
which made us argue in the first place.
What do you think she said, señora?
My goodness, Francisco. Don't ask.
You're giving me a headache.
Come here.
I have something for you to do.
So that…
I can get even for what happened to me.
What's that, señora?
It's been so long since I came here.
I've really missed your cooking, Mother.
That's why you should eat a lot.
Okay.
Father.
How are my Filipino childhood friends?
Do you still see them?
Teresita, Eduardo, and Adelina?
Did you think…
I brought you here just to reunite you
with your childhood friends?
Forgive me, Father.
Honey, our son has just returned
and you're already scolding him.
Hiroshi, don't mind your father.
Go ahead and eat.
Señor Tanaka, your awaited guest is here.
Mr. Arata, Mr. Watanabe, good evening!
I want to introduce you
to my son, Hiroshi,
who has just arrived from our homeland.
Welcome back to this country, Hiroshi.
Forgive me, but do we know each other?
I'm Akio, your playmate
from when we were kids.
Do you still remember me?
Hey, Akio! Why did you hurt her?
A mere girl shouldn't have beaten us.
I can never forget you.
Let's go there.
Mother, who is Father talking to?
I don't know them.
It's my first time seeing them too.
Please sit down. Let's eat.
Does your family know who you really are?
Mr. Arata.
No, they do not.
Colonel Arata.
That's what you should call
a high-ranking officer
of the Japanese Imperial Army
established in this country.
Especially when it's just us talking.
Forgive me, Colonel Arata.
No apologies necessary.
Is that the list, then?
Yes.
Here is the list of names
of wealthy families here in Manila,
and the names of high-ranking soldiers.
This is a big deal for our mission.
Mr. Tanaka, get ready.
The attacks are about to happen.
When?
Our first attack in this country
will take place in December.
In December?
First, Pearl Harbor.
And then, the whole nation.
The defense camps of the Philippines
must be destroyed first.
So they can't do anything
once our troops enter Manila.
He still hasn't changed.
Akio is still annoying.
Let him be.
Get some rest.
Why did they come here, Father?
Who was with Akio?
What did they want from you?
And what were you talking about?
It's a good thing
you've saved up some money.
Otherwise, you'd still be in jail.
That was only temporary.
Until Teresita's mother withdraws
her complaint against me,
the constabulary
can still arrest me anytime.
What?
I'll be damned.
I thought your suffering had ended.
Guess I was wrong.
Adelina!
Teresita!
Eduardo!
I didn't know this is where you bathe!
Adelina!
Teresita is here!
Teresita!
I'm glad you got home safe.
I came alone.
-Mama won't be home until tomorrow.
-Until tomorrow?
Wait, I'll go down!
Teresita.
Tomorrow is Saturday, isn't it?
Maestro wants us back
to the theater tomorrow
because it'll be
our first performance on stage.
I know.
So by the time Mama comes home,
we're already out the door.
But what if she finds out we're together?
She'll get mad at me and Eduardo again.
The truth is, she told us
to leave here and stay away from you.
Those were her conditions.
She even threatened me
not to tell you about it.
I know that.
But don't listen to her.
Mama and I already agreed
that she won't bother you anymore.
And that she will drop
her complaint against you, Eduardo.
So you can relax now.
Thank God!
I'm glad your mother changed her mind.
You're welcome.
Well, Adelina?
Since Mama is not home,
I'll wait for you there
so we can practice.
We need to prepare
for our performance tomorrow.
That's right!
Okay, I'll be there.
All right.
I'll be going now.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
I want to watch your performance.
I'll go too. We don't have work tomorrow.
Fine!
But can you please fix yourselves first?
You both look like wet dogs.
You don't even have shirts on.
Just look at you, Tasyo.
You're not even ashamed of yourself!
You heard that, Tasyo?
People will finally watch
Adelina and Teresita tomorrow.
We can't miss it.
Yes, I heard.
That's why I'll be going with you.
Just don't be all shy tomorrow.
What if Teresita gets married
to someone else?
Can you handle that?
Can you bear seeing her
end up with someone else?
Look, Eduardo, our favorite comedians.
When do you think
it'll be Adelina's and Teresita's turn?
Don't be impatient. Just watch.
Ouch!
You are so stupid!
How dare you!
Hey, break a leg out there.
Make sure the audience won't get bored.
Especially with you, Adelina.
Because between you two,
your sister is the better singer.
You need to dance well
and make the audience laugh, okay?
That hurts.
Don't listen to him.
Daddy Johnny just talks that way.
Hey, Marcel is a great singer.
Not really.
This boy.
What are your names?
She is Chinita and she is Morena.
From now on, those are your stage names.
"Morena"?
Teresita, I don't think it's nice
to be known by those stage names.
Just follow along with it.
That way, Mama won't know
we're already performing.
I accept our new names, Maestro.
Just call me Daddy Johnny.
Listen here.
Pugo will call you
when it's your turn on stage.
Remember, the audience will decide
if I'll accept you in my company or not.
So do not fail me.
Especially since we have
an important guest
who wants to watch you two in particular.
Teresita.
I'm nervous.
Who is this special guest?
I don't know.
Hiroshi!
Where are Teresita and Adelina?
Wherever you are
Be it the city or the country
You will always bump into
The naughty clown
I will have him marry my Teresita.
My name is Juan. Remember my name, okay?
I won't forget you, Juan.
Did you buy those for Teresita?
For her and Adelina.
Don't even try to tease me.
Teresita might hear you.
I heard Teresita's father hasn't returned?
I'm no longer hoping for that, Hiroshi.
COMING UP
Subtitle translation by:
Nehemiarey Dallego