[Blind Woman]
[Episode 4: Come on, Jump Down]
Miss Lin.
Please be at ease.
I'm a doctor.
I will never cross any boundaries.
Okay.
There's no anesthetic here,
so bear with it.
Hang in there. I'm almost finished.
♫The wind and rain shake the tender branches♫
♫Dark clouds trap the sunset's glow♫
♫No one knows when the skies will clear♫
♫Even the birds have fallen silent♫
She's having a fever.
♫Darkness seems to swallow me whole♫
♫Who can purify my soul?♫
♫I'm like searching in the abyss♫
♫For a lighthouse♫
So cold.
♫The path ahead still holds uncertainties♫
♫It's hard to tell what's real from false♫
♫What I believed in was trampled at will♫
♫Dismissed as mere dreams and jokes♫
♫If you want to escape this world, wait for the rain to fall♫
♫Watch the fireworks released by the gods♫
♫Just pause for a moment♫
♫Let the nearly barren heart sprout new buds♫
♫Set forth again, and I won't be afraid♫
♫The most resilient flowers bloom on the cliffs♫
♫Let the past scars be carried away by the wind♫
♫Those who have dreams must first face♫
♫The chaos of the world♫
Young Master, we...
You go prepare the car. I'll be down shortly.
Okay.
[Yu's Mansion]
So cold.
Who's there?
Young Master, it's me.
What is it?
I just heard from Xiang
that Captain Wu has led his men
to cause trouble for Miss Lin tonight.
Wu You went after Lin Wanyue?
Is he still trying to force Miss Lin to give
a false statement accusing me of murder?
No.
I have to go there now.
Cheng Hao, get the car ready immediately.
Yes, Young Master.
Open the door!
Lin Wanyue!
You knew Yu Yanchuan was the murderer
of the Zhong Cheng couple,
yet you deliberately chose not to identify him.
Open the door!
Search this place!
Yes, sir!
Boss, she is not here.
The dog is still here.
Lin Wanyue must not have run away yet.
Keep searching.
Yes.
Miss Lin.
There you are.
What do you want?
What can we, the police, do?
Of course, we're here to have you help investigate
the Zhong Cheng couple's murder case.
Haven't I already identified that man?
You're still trying to fool me?
You knew full well Yu Yanchuan was the one who murdered
the Zhong Cheng couple,
yet you deliberately didn't identify him.
He's not the murderer.
Fine.
Still being all stubborn, huh?
Before this rope breaks,
if you say Yu Yanchuan is the murderer,
I guarantee
you'll live.
But if you don't...
you'll be taking a one-way trip to the afterlife.
You're abusing your power
to extract a statement!
Even if it's so,
what can you do about it?
Don't push me any further.
Alright.
Let's see how much longer you can hold on.
Help.
Lin Wanyue!
♫I push hard to topple the darkness♫
♫A corner of light emerges♫
♫You spread your wings♫
Wanyue, grip my arm tightly.
♫Dancing quietly♫
♫You've been through surging waves♫
♫Sending out signals♫
♫I say, in this world♫
♫There's still some beauty♫
♫The night sky is upside down, with gentle hues♫
♫If love could be the cure♫
♫I'd search for you, for what was once lost♫
♫Those playful jokes♫
♫Waiting until you're ready to touch the heartbeat of the world♫
♫It's also a sign of me rushing toward you♫
♫As the ice and snow melt away, I wait for your embrace♫
Mr. Yu, where are you taking me?
♫Waiting for the rainbow to stretch across every path♫
Miss Lin.
It's fine now.
Your place is not safe anymore.
♫And in your world, there is no more noise♫
Come stay at my place for now.
What?
♫I'm here, and you'll eventually feel it♫
Don't worry.
Only if you stay with me
will Wu You leave you alone.
Alright.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Miss, Yu Yanchuan is here.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Miss,
I've already had Xiang spread the word.
Okay.
Recently, Yu Zhenhai's butler, Lai Guangsheng,
has been watching us.
He's downstairs right now.
Let's give him something drastic
to see.
Yes, Miss.
Father!
Mother!
Master.
What should we do about Jiang Yude's daughter?
[Yu's Mansion]
Hell may have taken my sight,
but it helped me return as an avenging ghost.
This time,
it's your turn to go to hell,
my enemies.