Hello. Hello.
Mr. Yu.
There was a fire in the warehouse.
He's dead.
What?
He just wanted to teach me a lesson.
No way.
Don't worry.
I will help you
I'll help you with your father's death.
Why are you helping me?
Because I already know
He Dahai said
in He Dahai's mouth.
He killed my mother.
What?
[You deserve to die.] I'm sorry.
I deserve it.
If anything happens to you tonight,
I won't let him go.
Thank you.
Wanyue,
You've taken your revenge.
What's your plan next?
I haven't avenged.
Uncle told me in the warehouse
there was more than one person who killed my benefactor.
Then who is the other one?
He didn't tell me.
No matter who he is,
I will find him.
Wanyue.
Have you heard of fireflies?
Yes.
Is this the firefly?
What does it look like?
It's
that shines on the tail.
Then it'll be pretty at night.
That's right.
The summer night glows.
The stars in the mortal world.
Hearing what you said,
I feel so beautiful.
Any news about the opium of Zhong Cheng and his wife?
No.
Hurry up and investigate.
Okay, go ahead.
Mr. Yu.
I'm here to see you. I'm here to see you.
What's the matter?
There was a fire in the western suburbs last night.
Someone was burned to death.
According to the investigation,
we found the victim was Mr. Yu's butler to Guangsheng.
Mr. Lai is dead.
There's a possibility that he was murdered.
No.
The initial judgment is that there was an accident.
Mr. Yu,
We need you to go to the police station
to identify the body.
Okay. I'll go with you.
Father.
Father, I have something to tell you.
Let's talk when I'm back.
I've long heard that Miss Lin is living in the Yu family.
I knew it.
Wu You, I'm warning you.
Don't try to hurt Miss Lin.
Miss Lin, I'm glad you're fine.
If someone bullies you in the Yu family,
call the police.
Thank you, Officer Wu.
Don't be afraid.
Wu You thinks he's Wu Yingtian's foster father.
because Wu Ying Tian is Wu Ying Tian.
Will the police find evidence and find me?
Don't worry.
The warehouse was burnt down.
No clue is left.
Let's go.
Let's go find He Dahai
Extra edition, Xishan Warehouse
[Xishan Warehouse]
Tong Tong.
You gave me a whistle last time.
I'll give you a wave drum this time.
Do you like it?
Yes
Thank you. Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's you again.
What do you want?
Can't you stop?
Tell us who the other murderer is.
We won't get you into trouble.
What other murderer?
That's not true.
You won't tell me?
What are you doing?
Tong Tong.
You're not going to tell me?
He Dahai.
Tong Tong should be five years old this year.
Don't you dare touch her.
I'm not trying to hurt her.
I want to help her.
Help her?
How?
I can send Tong Tong to the orphanage
and let her study there.
But in exchange,
you must tell us
who the other murderer is.
What do you think?
The other murderer
is Wu Yingtian, the current director of the police station.
Tong Tong, come here.
Master! Master!
I’m innocent!
Lin Wanyue must have set me up.
She pushed me down the stairs.
Uncle, I'm blind.
You overestimated me.
When I walked to the stairs,
I saw uncle rolling down
and rolled down the stairs.
You little girl.
What are you talking about?
Let's go. Let's go.
Master
I found this in Xiang's room
Caixiang
I want to see
whether you're tough or a bullet.
Master.
Please don't kill me, Father!
What happened?
Chuan.
Look at this.
It's hallucinogenic.
hallucinogenic.
This unused hallucinogenic
was found in Xiang's room.
I asked someone to compare it
The hallucinogenic in Uncle's autopsy report.
in the autopsy report.
She's the murderer who killed Uncle Lai.
For the sake of our years,
I'll give you one last chance
Tell me, Caixiang.
Why did you do that
Master, I was forced.
Who?
It's me. It's me.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!