(10th year anniversary special,
3 Meals A Day Light)
It's that house, isn't it?
(Pyeongchang where potato flowers
bloom in July)
Yum.
Yes.
(A delicious meal made of love)
Yum.
(They are excited
because they're together)
This is well-fermented.
So delicious.
(They spend a fun time together)
(Chuja Island that gets a lot
of sunlight in August)
I got something!
(Feeling the thrill)
(and freshness from summer)
(The 3 Meals Family enjoy
their time on the island)
(September, the month when
the wind blows)
(Mount Jiri Rest Area)
I guess they are here.
(This time, they are meeting up
at the rest area)
Oh?
(Haejin arrives in glasses)
(Next is Seungwon)
(Nice to meet you)
What is he? A cowboy?
Look at his shoes.
(Cha-boy is dressed up today)
(The main highlight)
What do you know about fashion?
- What?
- How are you?
You don't mind wearing
long sleeves now.
(It's been 3 weeks
since they met)
Why...
Why are you so dandy these days?
Really?
The glasses are a dandy style.
Why is that so?
I use these often.
I guess the season has changed.
I think it is changing.
(The heat is slowly going away)
(A season of warm sunshine)
Are we going somewhere?
Where do you think we will go
on your final shooting?
(Why are they gathered at
Mount Jiri Rest Area?)
Mountain village?
We're going to Mount Jiri.
We are?
We'll go to a house that is
located in Mount Jiri
and film the last episodes
for '3 Meals A Day Light.'
(It is located between
Jeolla-do and Gyeongsang-do)
(Mount Jiri)
(This time, we are at
a green mountain)
(Walk up the beautiful mountain
and you'll see a flowing valley)
(Namwon)
(Time goes by slowly)
(That's why nature stays there)
(The story that will happen here)
This is amazing.
(Enjoy the sound of nature
during the day)
The stars are out.
Wow.
This is so beautiful.
(They can enjoy stars
in the sky at night)
(The story of 3 Meals Family
in a mountain village)
Why did you soak it in vinegar?
(As usual, there are
small sparks flying too)
(The things they will taste
in Mount Jiri)
(Chef Cha's food that is
made with love)
This is so delicious.
You collected a lot?
(This much)
(Enjoy nature)
Three-story Stone Pagoda
at Baekjangam.
First floor.
Second floor, third floor.
Must you really count?
(They also spend time
enjoying nature)
This is mind-blowing.
When else will we come here?
This is wonderful.
Longing
makes me sing
the pain in my heart.
- Tears...
- Stop it.
(They've had a unique harmony
for the past 10 years)
(Their story begins now)
You can go there now.
We need to look around
the town. It's a necessity.
- We definitely need that.
- You have everything there...
We would still look around
even if it's not necessary.
We need to buy makgeolli
in Mount Jiri too.
(Their makgeolli tour continues
from Pyeongchang)
Makgeolli is a must-have in fall.
There is a brewery in this area.
Yes.
(They will stop at the town
before going to their house)
How do we get there from here?
(Their vehicle from here
back home)
(Introducing their new car)
Why are we suddenly
using this car?
(Flustered by the luxurious SUV
after their Ferrari)
We're comfortable with
the Ferrari.
This is too much.
You're driving up the mountain.
So this is for safety.
But...
Isn't this too much?
(Unfamiliar luxurious treatment)
Okay.
(They put their bags in first)
(They head to town
to do grocery shopping)
(From Mount Jiri Rest Area
to Macheon-myeon)
What have you been up to?
Me? I've been very busy.
Why?
(Seungwon had a busy schedule)
You must've been busy
because of promotions.
(He is busy due to promotions)
What about you?
I've been at theaters.
(Theater?)
I started acting in theaters
in Cheongju.
The troupe has been active
for the past 40 years.
I thought about it
and I think it's meaningful.
So, I agreed to it and
am practicing there.
I doubt it was an easy
decision for you to make.
I will watch you.
I have to.
When is it in October?
(They matched schedules
and he actually went)
But
we came in the morning
in long sleeves
and it wasn't too bad.
There are a few places
in the south
that are still experiencing
a heat wave.
Well, a heat wave is okay
but not a heat tsunami.
What are we having for lunch?
I'm planning to cook jjajangmyeon.
- Really?
- Yes.
You will actually
make your own jjajangmyeon?
Yes.
You have the ingredients?
That's why we're going
to go shopping and buy pork.
- What about noodles?
- We have kalguksu.
We can use that.
What do we need?
Onion, pork, squash, potatoes.
- Yes.
- That's all we need.
I'm already drooling.
Sprinkle on some chili flakes.
Oh my goodness.
(Chef Cha plans his menus
even without being told to)
This must be it.
(Where will they stop by
to get groceries?)
(Macheon-myeon,
Hamyang-gun, South Gyeongsang-do)
There's Black Pork Village too.
(Mount Jiri is famous
for black pork)
(There are signboards of
black pork everywhere)
They only sell meat here.
It's very clean.
Hello. Hello.
We'd like to have pork sirloin
to make jjajang.
We'll have 400 grams of meat.
Please cut them into small pieces.
This looks good too.
(After looking at fresh meat)
(Peeking)
Anything else you need to buy?
Well, we can grill this.
(Good meat makes him
want to grill it)
My goodness.
Let's have samgyeopsal for dinner.
- That works.
- Yes, let's grill that.
- Okay.
Then eat it with kimchi.
Alright! Oh!
(They have a cauldron lid
back home too)
Great.
(He bought pork belly
for them to grill too)
We can use the lid for grilling.
Thank you.
(They have bought pork)
This is it.
I think this place
has a long history.
My goodness.
Hello.
(They need to buy makgeolli)
Since 1933.
This place will soon
be 100 years old.
How many bottles?
Maybe around 3 to 4 bottles?
Please give us 5 bottles.
(They bought 5 bottles
of makgeolli)
Why did you even ask?
(One-way communication)
(They have even bought makgeolli)
(Now, it's time to go home)
The makgeolli looks good.
(They shopped at Gyeongsang-do
and go home to Jeolla-do)
(They drive through the road
that is covered in green)
This car is very stable.
This car is not bumpy at all
even on mountainous roads.
Look at the green.
It feels good to have
lots of green around us.
I've been seeing
only buildings every day.
I used to hate nature back then.
- You like it now?
- Yes, I do.
It means you're getting younger.
Right?
Am I really getting younger?
How old was I back then?
(After laughing
and chatting away)
Is this it? Looks like it.
- Where? There?
- Yes.
This is a mountainous path.
(They go up the steep road)
We're going deep into
the mountains.
(A village where golden and ripe
paddies welcomes them)
The paddy field has turned golden.
(It is turning into
the color of fall)
- Look at that.
- The grain?
Grain!
Why does this seem
so different now?
I suddenly crave toasted bread.
(He loves it too)
(They climb up the mountain
by the paddy field)
This looks nice.
(They have arrived home)
This is the place.
The yard is spacious.
(Somewhere deep in
the foot of Mount Jiri)
(3 Meals House welcomes them
with its green gate)
(After driving through the gate)
(There is a vast yard
that Seungwon and Haejin love)
(There is a porch where
they can enjoy the view)
(When you enter the house)
(Spacious living room)
(There are small rooms that
embrace nature)
(On one side of the yard)
(Vegetable patch that grows
under the sunlight in Mount Jiri)
(If you sit on the swing
by the vegetable patch)
(You can enjoy a beautiful view)
(3 Meals House is a place
to enjoy Mount Jiri)
This place is around 400 meters
above sea level.
What about our rice?
Wouldn't it have effects
on our rice too?
(It would affect the rice to
be mushy or dry)
I was understanding back then
since it was your first time
but if you fail again, it means
something is wrong with Haejin.
We are 420 meters
above sea level.
(They are now 420 meters
above sea level)
First off,
let's check out the rooms.
(Once they enter the house)
(There is a spacious living room)
(Room 1, 2 and 3)
Which room do you want?
- Any room is fine.
- Choose one.
(Peeking)
You can have this room.
(Haejin will use the biggest room)
(Although the room Seungwon chose
is smaller in size)
(He gets a window
in the direction of Mount Jiri)
We should bring our things in.
Let's take our things.
(They take their things
from the car)
(Audio equipment)
What's the matter?
My goodness.
I thought this was my bag.
(He always jokes around)
(He found his real bag
and brings it to his room)
(Haejin starts
by unpacking his clothes)
(Seungwon who has begun
to transfer his items)
The fridge too...
- What?
- Check the fridge too.
(He stops unpacking when
he heard about the fridge)
(He checks the fridge right away)
This is amazing.
(Seungwon is happy
with the fridge)
(He starts by organizing
the refrigerator)
(Haejin who is done
changing his clothes)
Oh.
- Why?
- Your working clothes.
These are
the most comfortable clothes.
(All black shadow look)
(The first thing Haejin does)
Your instinct tells you that.
(Garlic instinctively summons him)
We always need garlic.
(He starts
by soaking garlic in water)
(He leaves it in the water
for a moment)
(He naturally goes to the bricks)
(His instinct tells him
to make a brazier)
(Looking around)
(He places the bricks
at a suitable spot)
(After moving the bricks)
(Here comes another
all black shadow look)
(3 Meals A Day mode is on)
Magical things happen
once you come here.
(Dandy Yoo and Cha-boy
disappear in a moment)
(Equipment team, cooking team)
(They know what to do right away)
(After doing
their respective work)
Hello.
(The teams seem to always
bump into one another)
Seems like you have
something to do here.
This is my usual job.
(The equipment team is always
making a brazier)
(The cooking team is always
preparing the ingredients)
What are you having
for your first meal?
- What did you ask?
- What's your first menu?
Jjajangmyeon.
(He is peeling an onion
for jjajangmyeon)
(He cuts off only
the ends of a squash)
(Peel potatoes)
(Wash the prepared vegetables)
(Put them aside)
(Equipment team which has
finished building braziers)
(He looks at the soil closely)
(Shovel?)
I should do it here.
(He flattens the soil)
(And stacks more bricks)
(Another two)
(What did he get from the porch?)
(Seasoning rack that
he made with Youngwoong)
(Measuring the height)
(Equipment team tries to create
the best cooking environment)
(Seungwon of the cooking team)
Do people add that
to jjajangmyeon?
I'm preparing the meat that
we will eat later.
(This which is now being soaked)
I bought leg bones too.
- Leg bones?
- Yes.
What for?
We can make rice cake soup
for one of our meals.
I can make the broth
and keep it for later.
(Leg bones and brisket)
(Soju)
Right now, I'm draining blood
from the meat.
(Soaking meat in soju and water
gets rid of the gamey smell)
(Haejin who is getting
the height right)
You're making that for me?
That's great.
(He is done making
the seasoning rack)
Honey.
Something refreshing.
(They are reminded of something
refreshing after doing their work)
Shouldn't we have that now?
- Don't you think so?
- It's because...
(All ingredients have been washed)
The one from earlier...
How do I say this?
- I know what you mean.
- The one that was filtered.
(They know what it is
without saying in detail)
I'm curious about its taste
here.
(While Seungwon prepares
the filtered one)
(Haejin prepares the cups)
Come here.
(They are seated on the porch)
I think it'll be delicious.
(Time to have
the refreshing filtered one)
It's refreshing.
(Gulping)
Not bad.
(They love it)
It's not bad.
(He gets seated comfortably)
I think our makgeolli tour
is a success.
This is tasty.
(After quenching their thirst)
That is Cheonwangbong Peak
of Mount Jiri.
(Now they get to enjoy the view)
Over there is Namwon.
- Where is Namwon?
- Over there.
(Our house)
(Cheonwangbong Peak is over here)
(On the right side is Jeolla-do)
(On the left side
is Gyeongsang-do)
Where is Hwagaejangteo Market?
(Hwagaejangteo Market is nearby)
But...
if we're going
to explore this area,
it will look just like
any other market.
You can find everything there.
It's amazing.
(He is flustered)
(He can't hold back his laughter)
You're going to make bone broth?
I can make lots of broth
using that.
We can use that as a welcome
drink.
(Welcome drink)
After making that,
we can have seolleongtang
for breakfast.
Gomguksi for lunch.
- And for dinner...
- We will have rice cake soup.
We'll make everything with that.
You'll use the broth
in all dishes?
Yes, we should do that.
You'll exercise, won't you?
(Haejin's thighs
caught his attention)
I've been working out too.
- Are you bragging?
- I've been exercising too.
(Bragging about his lower body
that he has worked out)
(He is bragging)
Wow...
(Clear tan lines)
Do you think I wore shoes or not?
You did!
Shall we get started?
What's the time now?
(It's currently 12:55PM)
What will you do now?
(It's time to get moving)
(He will boil the brisket and
bones that have been soaked)
We'll use one brazier
to make jjajang
and the other to boil noodles.
Do you need one or two fires?
(He needs two)
Let me wash that first.
Yeolmoa is dirty.
(Prove that it has been working
hard from Pyeongchang to Chuja)
(Mr. Yoo cleans it)
(While Mr. Yoo cleans Yeolmoa)
(Chef Cha cuts the vegetables)
(Lunch menu:
Jjajangmyeon and dumplings)
(Lots of vegetables
to be added to jjajangmyeon)
(Next is squash)
(Cut the yellow squash into cubes)
(Next is onion)
(Lots of onion, a must-have
ingredient in jjajangmyeon)
(There are lots of ingredients)
(Mr. Yoo is done cleaning Yeolmoa)
(He dries it under the sun)
(It is clean despite
looking the same)
(He gets ready for the next task)
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
(Worried about Haejin
who is under the hot sun)
(Mosquitoes whirring)
Okay.
(The first mosquito communicator
in Korea)
(Peeking)
- That's for jjajang?
- Yes.
- It uses lots of onions.
The sauce is all about
the flavor from the onion.
(After the flavor of onion)
(Add the flavor of potatoes)
(Haejin is washing the mesh
under the tap water)
(He is making JABAJO)
(Laughing)
I'm very thorough, am I not?
What is this called?
I told you that this is
called JABAJO.
What is it called?
JABAJO.
(Both are giggling)
(Hehehe)
The name is...
(Giggling away)
Isn't it very honest and innocent?
(He loves it)
(Haejin's items are given names
that are innocent and direct)
(It begins with Hyungbae
in Jukgul Island)
(It has powerful energy)
(White Pillar
is created in Pyeongchang)
(Yeolmoa which has
different names)
(And JABAJO too)
(Cube lots of potatoes too)
(All the ingredients that will be
added to jjajangmyeon are ready)
(Chef Cha's list of tasks)
(Prepare ingredients
for jjajangmyeon)
- Shall I start one fire?
- Yes.
(Haejin gets ready to start
a fire at one brazier)
(Seungwon gets ready
to cut the cabbages)
The garlic...
Is that enough?
No, we need this much.
(In shock)
(This is not the time for him
to start a fire)
I have to soak even more.
(Add more garlic to be soaked)
There's a lot to do.
(He adds vinegar to the garlic)
(He quickly starts the fire)
(The wood catches fire right away)
(He naturally uses newspaper)
(Chef Cha starts to cut
the cabbages)
(The location of the basin
makes his job more efficient)
(Cuts the Chinese cabbage
into half)
(Cuts it into big pieces)
(He is done slicing
Chinese cabbage in a jiff)
I have to peel the garlic soon.
(Garlic is needed for kimchi,
jjajangmyeon, gomtang, etc.)
(He starts peeling garlic)
(Struggling)
(Gives up)
(It is hard to peel garlic as they
haven't been soaked long enough)
(He changes the garlic)
(He peels the garlic on one side)
(On the other side is
Seungwon salting Chinese cabbage)
(Salt Chinese cabbage)
(Leave it on one side so that
it gets salted)
(Then, prepare flour paste)
(Mix water and flour well)
(After stirring it)
(The flour paste is ready)
(Prepare flour paste)
(Let the paste cool down)
(This is what Haejin is doing)
(He has been peeling garlic
for the past 10 minutes)
(He continues to peel garlic)
(He peels garlic while Seungwon
goes everywhere)
(Haejin is locked in
the torturous pit of garlic)
(When will he be free?)
(He checks the time)
(Current time is 2:30PM)
(On the other hand, Chef Cha...)
(Place the leg bone and
brisket into a cauldron)
(Pour in enough water to cover
all of it)
(Boil leg bone and brisket)
(Instead of Haejin
who is peeling garlic)
(he adds more firewood himself)
(Equipment team peels garlic and
the cooking team adds firewood)
(Natural crossover from being
together for 10 years)
(Peeking)
The fire is small?
(He leaves the garlic
for a short moment)
(He is back in
equipment team mode)
(He adds more firewood
after checking on the fire)
(He goes back to the garlic)
Hey...
My goodness.
Garlic... My gosh, the garlic.
(It's funny yet sad and
makes Seungwon feel sorry)
I have to peel them, anyway.
The fire...
Can you make the fire
just a little bigger?
I will once the flame
gets bigger.
- From now?
- Yes.
(He stands up again)
I'm confused right now.
(He is in charge of
the fire for a moment)
(And then is in charge
of garlic after that)
Listen up.
You can just prepare garlic
to make kimchi for now.
Please peel another 10.
That's all.
(They decided to peel just enough
garlic for kimchi)
(A special measure to save
Haejin from this torture)
(Flour paste that he left
to cool down)
This is perfect.
It's amazing.
(The flour paste
makes Chef Cha happy)
(He puts it in the fridge)
(He gets chunjang to make jjajang)
I'm sweating now.
I'm sweating.
(He starts to sweat as
he is moving busily)
(He prepares ingredients
to make jjajang)
(And goes to the fridge again)
(Clank)
What is that sound?
(Why is he the only one who
enjoys something cold?)
- What sound is that?
- I just got a text.
(Talking nonsense)
(Even he finds it funny)
Do you want one?
No.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Now he can drink it with ease)
Did you really get a text?
(He appears with
a refreshed voice)
No, I opened one bottle.
(After telling the truth)
(He joins Haejin
to peel the garlic)
Stop peeling now.
- This is enough?
- Yes, you can stop now.
(Only the garlic needed for kimchi
has been prepared)
(Finally, he is free from garlic)
(and he is back
in front of the fire)
I have to peel the garlic...
(And start a fire)
There are no boundaries now.
That's how the world is today.
The boundary has
to be blurry as well.
Yes!
We need to be free of boundaries.
I should not think that
I'm only part of the equipment
team.
(Explaining with
his veins popping)
That is an old way of thinking.
Don't think that way.
(Even '3 Meals A Day' has joined
the generation of melting pot)
(Both the chef and equipment team
wear gloves)
Boil it here and throw out
the water.
It's not boiling?
(The broth is boiling
when they check on it)
(Throw out the first batch
of water to get rid of impurities)
(It gets rid of the smell
and removes more blood)
(He pours in water again)
I guess you add enough water
since the meat is floating.
(You should add water that is
5 times more than the weight)
(He adds more firewood
to the brazier with a cauldron)
(He does the dishes in
the most uncomfortable posture)
Because we have JABAJO...
- It makes life easier, right?
- Yes, it does.
You know what should be done.
(JABAJO fulfills
its role perfectly)
Is the fire big?
The big one? It definitely is.
You can put it over there.
- Put what?
- Bulmoa.
(The name suddenly changed)
(He sets up the Yeolmoa,
not Bulmoa)
(He makes sure that
it is set up properly)
Not everybody can set up Yeolmoa
when it is first used.
A member of the equipment team
has to do it.
(Yoo Haejin: 3 Meals Steel's head,
developer, and creator of Yeolmoa)
(Giggling)
I think the flower pattern
has been flattened so much.
(The petals are flattened)
Yes, that's why you need
someone from the team.
(He brought the tool that is
used only by the team members)
(He forces the petals back up)
You're using a hoe?
Although it looks like a hoe,
this is a necessary tool
that we need in our team.
This might look like a hoe...
(This might look like a hoe
but it is not)
So you need
a special tool for this?
Yes, the angle
makes a big difference in
how efficient it is.
(He did nothing)
(He's trying to get
the right angle)
(Tough job of being part of
the team)
(While the headquarters worker
is setting up Yeolmoa)
(Chef Cha is still very busy)
(He is making slurry
to be added to jjajangmyeon)
(Mix a ratio of 1 starch
and 1 water to make slurry)
(Slurry is a must to make
jjajang sauce thick)
(After making slurry)
(He gets ready
to stir-fry jjajang)
(Pour canola oil on chunjang)
(Yeolmoa is ready with
the touch of the worker)
Is this chunjang?
I have to stir-fry this.
(The perfect angles have
concentrated the fire)
(It is getting hot now)
(Stir-frying chunjang gets rid
of the smell and dryness)
(of chunjang and gives it
a more savory flavor)
Yeolmoa is created just
to make Chinese cuisine.
(The headquarters worker
is proud)
(He places the fried chunjang
in a bowl)
(He gets the vegetables
that he has cut)
Is this too much?
I think I prepared too much.
(Pouring them in)
Hold on.
(A lot)
(This is more than usual)
Who are you?
We should reduce it.
Is it because of
'Yoo Quiz on the Block'?
(Many netizens have been saying
that Seungwon is not generous)
(He did say on that show that
he cooked in large amounts)
(He walks the talk)
This won't take long to cook.
(He suddenly started running)
(He quickly gets the pork)
(Nobody is running after him)
(He adds a bit more canola oil)
(Stir-fries it on strong heat)
(Staring)
Don't you think that
you need more chunjang?
No, that is enough.
I will add chunjang now.
(He hasn't added chunjang)
Here it is.
We need to add chunjang.
(The chunjang that
he stir-fried earlier)
Why? You're suspecting me
of being someone irresponsible?
Yes.
(You hurt my feelings, honey)
(He adds stir-fried chunjang)
Give me that.
In this bowl,
pour in some water and
give it to me.
It's hot.
(The color starts to change
after chunjang is added)
Just pour it in. Pour it all in.
(Add in lots of water)
(There are still a lot of
ingredients)
Just add more water.
This smells like jjajang.
(Pour in more water so that
it's covered in water)
This smells wonderful.
(The tasty smell of jjajang
has started to spread)
I think many Samsung workers near
the National Assembly eat this.
(Giggling)
You should make jokes
when things get tough.
That was a good one.
(He tastes it)
(Adds chicken bouillon powder)
(Add sugar)
(While Chef Cha gets
the next ingredient)
(Haejin naturally takes the ladle)
(A bit of MSG)
(Finally, oyster sauce)
We have to let it simmer
for a long time.
(Just let it simmer since
it has been seasoned well)
(He adds more firewood
so it can simmer well)
(They get time to themselves
while they let it simmer)
(This is what Haejin is doing)
(I am hungry)
What is the time now?
It's 3:10PM.
(A lot of time has passed)
(The jjajang is boiling)
- It is boiling well.
- Yes, it is.
(Add slurry)
(He stirs it while checking
the state of the jjajang)
(Adding it bit by bit)
There's not enough slurry.
(The jjajang is still
not thick enough)
(He puts the wok aside)
(And makes slurry)
This smells great.
(I'm hungry)
(Adding more and more slurry)
(Staggering)
(They are both
losing their energy)
(But now, it looks thick)
(Tasting it again)
This is done.
(Make jjajang)
I can just leave this here.
Okay.
This looks perfect.
(Since the jjajang sauce is ready)
(Let's cook the noodles)
First off, add water.
(I hope you boil quickly)
This and ripe kimchi?
Yes, let's have those.
While we're at it,
shall we have fried eggs too?
That sounds good.
We need to make dumplings.
Dumplings?
We should've made dumplings first.
(Both braziers are in use)
We should have made
dumplings first.
I'll just put this down.
(He puts the water to cook
noodles aside for now)
(Chef Cha quickly gets
eggs and dumplings)
(Dumplings are a must
with jjajangmyeon)
(Quickly cuts them
with a pair of scissors)
Look at this.
They use one whole shrimp!
This is the real
whole shrimp dumpling.
(He filled the pan with dumplings)
(He covers the pan with a lid
so they cook quickly)
We just have to cook noodles
after this, don't we?
Yes.
(I have to endure a bit longer)
(The dumplings have turned
golden brown)
(He pours some water in it
and covers it with a lid)
To make sure that the filling
is cooked well too,
you need to cook it using vapor.
The steam will cook the dumplings.
(Crunchy outside and moist inside)
Honey.
I'm making fried eggs.
- Don't.
- Why?
I'm hungry.
(I'm suffering right now)
- Let's just eat.
- Okay.
(So hungry)
(The dumplings are ready)
(Grill dumplings)
(The water to boil noodles
is back)
(They use kalguksu to eat
with jjajang sauce)
(Chef Cha's simple jjajangmyeon
made using kalguksu)
(He plates the fried dumplings)
This is hot.
(All that's left is to taste it)
Wow.
(Face of anticipation)
Yum! Yum! Here!
Try it.
This is tasty.
(Hungry Haejin tastes it too)
(It is still hot)
It is seasoned to perfection
even without dipping.
They have been seasoned.
This is tasty.
(After getting rid of his hunger
through dumplings)
(It's time to set up the table)
(He takes out ripe kimchi
from the fridge)
(He cuts the kimchi
into bite sizes)
(Danmuji is a must
with jjajangmyeon)
(Pour lots of vinegar
over the danmuji)
(Have you forgotten about me?)
What is this?
(They save it together)
(The water is boiling
in the blink of an eye)
(Are the noodles cooked?)
Let's eat now.
(Finally, the noodles are cooked)
(Cook noodles)
(What's left is to rinse
the noodles in cold water)
The jjajang has cooled down.
(He only rinses it slightly
as the sauce has cooled down)
(Slippery)
(His slipper broke)
My goodness.
(The spirit of being bare footed)
(We should complete the task
we're working on)
Okay, this is done.
(Chef Cha prioritizes their meal
instead of his slippers)
(Mr. Yoo realized what happened
to the slipper)
(Running)
Chef Cha.
(The prince is here to save
Cha-derella whose slipper broke)
(They are wearing
the same slippers now)
Thank you.
(Cha-derella is grateful
towards the prince)
(He hops in an elegant way
like a prince would)
(Cha-derella is excited
upon wearing new slippers)
(He is back to being Chef Cha)
Now, the bowl...
(They just have to plate
the jjajangmyeon now)
(While Chef Cha
plates the noodles)
(Haejin gets the jjajang sauce)
As expected.
(They have perfect teamwork)
(Pouring a generous amount
of jjajang sauce)
- Is this done?
- Yes, it is.
(Chef Cha's jjajangmyeon that
is in yunijjajang style)
(Crunchy yet moist
whole shrimp dumpling)
(Spicy kimchi)
(Sour danmuji)
(Their first meal
in Mount Jiri is complete)
Bon appetit.
(He takes chili powder first)
Give me some chili powder too.
(The chili powder adds
more spiciness to it)
- More?
- No, that's enough.
I need to add vinegar.
(Haejin loves to add vinegar
to his jjajangmyeon)
(Seungwon doesn't like
to add vinegar to his)
I...
(He tastes it first)
I thought kalguksu wouldn't
be suitable but it's good.
(Yes, it is)
(Kalguksu noodles suit
jjajang sauce well)
This is tasty.
This tastes like something
served in a Chinese restaurant.
Really?
You went through a lot.
You had to start the fire...
Good job.
(This tastes better
because he worked hard)
(A butterfly visits them
because of the jjajang smell)
(He tastes the crunchy
fried dumplings too)
One whole shrimp.
This is perfect.
(He re-energizes
with jjajangmyeon)
Have you made this before?
Did we eat jjajangmyeon before?
No, we didn't.
(This is their first time to make
their own jjajangmyeon together)
This requires
a lot of effort to make.
Much more than expected.
The pork is tasty too.
This pork is delicious.
It's usually tough
but this one is tasty.
Yes, it is tender.
This would've been good
with rice too.
I agree.
Nice.
Great.
The view is beautiful too.
(Let's enjoy the view together)
You just have to let it boil.
(Leg bones and brisket
have been boiling for 2 hours)
What is the brisket for?
We can tear the brisket
to make rice cake soup
or even gomtang too.
(It can be added
to a variety of dishes)
For the bones, we will add
more water and let it boil.
Add a bit more firewood
so we can let it boil.
(They continue eating after
Seungwon gives a briefing)
Honey.
(He still has a lot to say)
(The fire is weak but still there)
Let's stir-fry kimchi
over that fire.
(They will stir-fry ripe kimchi
and make new kimchi)
That was a good meal.
Finally,
- we can rest.
- I feel better now.
(They are full
and have taken a break)
We will make samgyeopsal later?
(They talk about dinner
right after having lunch)
We will grill kimchi
with samgyeopsal.
Now,
I'll take a break
and start making kimchi.
(Let's rest for now)
It will ferment anyway.
It will still ferment
even if we leave it.
Let's have baek-kimchi.
- Baek-kimchi.
- Yes.
(Let's take a break
before making kimchi)
(No, they are not resting)
(But they said they would)
(Haejin takes some firewood
despite saying he wants to rest)
(Seungwon pours more water
into the bone broth)
(Nobody is resting)
(He scoops out fat from the broth)
We are cooking this
with brisket right now.
(They have to remove the fat
continuously due to the brisket)
(The broth has been simmering
for quite some time)
(He can't leave the broth)
(After checking on the broth)
(He goes to the tap
to do the dishes)
(He doesn't know how to rest)
(Haejin who is humming)
(After choosing his
working song CD)
(He appears with a CD player)
Leave that be. I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- I can do it.
(They are arguing over who
should do the job)
You should stir-fry kimchi.
(The music starts playing
as they fight about the dishes)
('The Sound of Silence' by
Simon and Garfunkel)
(The Sound of Silence)
Just stir-fry the kimchi.
I'll do this.
(Their argument continues)
(Background music that is
not suitable for the situation)
(A silent touch)
- Okay.
- Get up.
I can't believe
you played this song.
It's Simon and Garfunkel.
(Chef Cha leaves as he can't
overcome Haejin's pestering)
Of silence...
(Finally, they have
a moment of silence)
(Seungwon is in front
of the fire again)
(Now, it's time
to add more firewood)
(Familiar fanning)
(He is in equipment team mode)
(Back to being cooking team mode)
(Chef Cha is about
to make stir-fried kimchi)
(He cuts them into smaller pieces
so it's easier to stir-fry)
(Pour in some perilla oil)
(Pour a generous amount
of sesame oil in too)
(Stir-fry on low heat)
(He slowly goes to the broth)
(It's time
to take the brisket out)
(Let the brisket cool down)
(Start stir-frying kimchi again)
(When the kimchi starts
to turn yellow)
(pour in water)
(Adding water gets rid of
the sour taste in kimchi)
(and helps it cook well
which makes it tastier)
(Add some sugar)
(Sprinkle lots of chili powder)
(Now, it's time to just
let it simmer until it boils down)
(The fire gets stronger)
This is not an easy task.
Taking care of the fire is tough.
(The equipment team
has difficult tasks)
(Fanning two braziers is tough)
- It's going well?
- Yes.
(It is stir-frying well)
Why?
(Encore)
(Full of laughter)
(Not laughing)
Did contractors come
to this house today?
What's the matter?
It felt like several people
were here.
(Endless dishes to wash today)
Maybe around 20 people?
(This time he is stuck
in the torturous pit of dishes)
It's a lot, isn't it?
A lot.
(But he is not lonely
because there is music)
('Are You Lonesome Tonight'
by Elvis Presley)
This was very common
back in those days.
They add a recital in the song.
(1960s style of ringing rap)
(The next song has the same style)
('Kiss and Say Goodbye'
by The Manhattans)
(He doesn't know the lyrics)
(Give)
(and take)
And I miss you.
(He never misses the best part)
This sounds like
Korean-style lyrics.
Yes, that's right.
(Perfect for the Korean soul)
Say goodbye.
(Ad-lib is a must)
How did we end up knowing
all these songs? Right?
(A list of nostalgic pop songs
that they know very well)
But honestly...
(These songs were played often
on radios in the 80s and 90s)
We heard these songs in
'Lee Jonghwan's Night Disco Show.'
(Copying the opening)
Then...
DJ Lee Jonghwan will make
a remark right at that moment.
(Late Lee Jonghwan was a
guest DJ on 'Night Disco Show',)
(a radio show that lasted from
1 April 1981 until 23 July 1989)
(When the opening song plays)
Hello. I am Lee Jonghwan.
'This is my first time
to have you in my life.'
When a show was on air,
we would record it on a tape
to listen to it
over and over again.
(They are immersed
in their memories for now)
We used to write down lyrics
of pop songs in Hangeul before.
Yes. 'We are the World' too.
Welcome to time.
Let me hear a certain call.
We wrote something like that.
(It's like an English listening
test with some Korean language)
(After being immersed
in their memories)
(The time when stir-fried kimchi
is complete has come)
(He transfers stir-fried kimchi
into a glass container)
(Sprinkle sesame seeds
as the final touch)
I can tell it's tasty
based on the smell.
(Stir-fried kimchi is done)
(Haejin is almost done
doing all the dishes)
Honey.
This is the last one.
(A tough pan to wash
is given to Haejin)
(After doing the dishes)
(The sky has started
to become dark)
But...
The sun has started to set
when the dishes are done.
It's time to eat dinner.
What is this?
(An unexpected door cut)
(Embarrassed)
(This mosquito net was set
to avoid mosquitoes entering)
(He was about to enter
after lowering his head)
What is this?
(We've never seen this kind
of precious scenes in 10 years)
(So we will show you the shot
from various angles)
(It was meant to block
only mosquitoes)
This...
(He damages the mosquito net
and enters the house
(He gets excited since
the dishes are almost done)
(He rinses the basin)
(Cleaning up the area)
Honey.
Have you washed
the chopping board? Where is it?
There's no chopping board here.
(Here it is)
I believe there is one here.
Here it is.
What about the knife? Knife...
- Knife.
- Don't give or search it.
(He finds things himself)
(He rinses his feet that are
dirty from doing the dishes)
(We'll leave after
filming your foot)
(Slightly embarrassed)
(You can clearly see the signs
of Chuja Island on him)
(After washing his feet clean)
(It means he is done with
doing all the dishes)
(Chef Cha who is about
to cut the brisket)
(He starts by cutting it
into big pieces)
(Then he shreds it into
small pieces with his hands)
(Peeking)
Honey.
What are you doing?
By the time I'm done with
the dishes, it's getting dark.
We will be able to rest one of
these days after doing this.
Yes, that's right.
(They work hard to rest
in the future)
Please help me with that.
Then, I can keep this
inside the refrigerator.
Are we going to make
braised meat with this?
Not this.
That is made using top round.
This is brisket. It's expensive.
I don't know since I'm dull.
(He has a way with words)
(He takes some)
This is very tender.
(Amazed)
Do we add this to
seaweed soup?
Yes, seaweed soup and such.
You know your food well.
I can taste it.
This is so tasty perhaps because
you cooked it for a long time.
(Tasty brisket that is tender and
moist when boiled for a long time)
(They will add that
to rice cake soup)
(He keeps the shredded brisket
inside the refrigerator)
(Chef Cha quickly leaves the room)
(He starts to make kimchi)
(Cut green onions into four parts)
(Slice onion thinly)
(Haejin who is in charge
of garlic)
(Blend garlic and ginger)
Add that here.
Put everything in.
(The garlic is not falling down)
Just scrape everything.
(He uses a spoon
to scrape everything)
(Scraping every single bit)
(It's time to season it)
(Fine chili powder)
(Coarse chili powder)
(Sand lance extract)
(Anchovies extract)
(Plum extract)
(Salt)
(Mix everything well)
(Mince salted shrimp finely)
(He makes a fancy turn
to make the kimchi)
(Checks to see if
something is missing)
Come here.
Please sprinkle in some salt.
Just a bit.
Salt. Yes, just a bit.
There's a spoon in it.
Yes, Give me one spoonful.
There's sand lance extract
over there.
This is sand lance extract?
Pour some in this.
That's enough.
That small amount
makes a difference?
(Fascinated)
Just add flour paste
and it's done.
(He takes the flour paste
that he kept in the fridge)
It's thick.
Let's add this much.
(Add flour paste
and mix them well)
(He keeps the kimchi
inside a container)
(Finally, sprinkle sesame seeds)
(Chef Cha's cabbage kimchi
is done)
(He cleans the dishes that
he used to make kimchi)
What are you doing?
I have to wash these.
Let me do it.
No, I'll do it.
I just have to wash these.
This is all.
(Seungwon who is done
with the dishes in a jiff)
(He takes the ladle again
to check on the broth)
(He removes the fats that
are floating on the surface)
(Haejin who has opened
the door to the storage room)
(He comes out with a metal rod)
(He takes a hammer)
(Hammering)
(Pouting)
(Unhappy)
(He puts the hammer away)
(He gets a variety of tools)
What else are you making?
(What is Mr. Yoo thinking
of making?)
(He cuts the end of the rod)
(He bends it)
I have no idea what that is.
What?
(It is impossible to tell
what he is making this time)
I'm just trying this out.
(He places the rod
on the faucet?)
What is this? Remote control?
So, when we do the dishes...
(Water gushes out of the hose)
(This is his plan)
(A product that will reduce
the usage of their waist)
(Actually, Mr. Yoo who was
doing the dishes earlier)
(felt uncomfortable reaching out
to the faucet that's far away)
(He stretches his hands to it)
(Staring)
(Twists it again)
(He got an idea
after thinking for a long time)
(He tries to reduce
the distance with a rod)
(It keeps on dropping)
(Taking a deep breath)
I hope this works.
(It will be great if
he can fasten it to the faucet)
This will be so convenient.
(In the end,
he gets the green tape)
- Honey.
- Yes.
Let's have dinner.
Already?
(They had jjajangmyeon
only 2 hours ago)
I'm done.
It's ready.
You made kimchi?
I did.
Good job.
(Feeling refreshed)
(He covers the end of the rod
with green tape)
(He places it on the faucet)
(Simulation)
We can use it easily like this.
Let's fasten it now.
I'll fasten it.
(He fastens it on the faucet)
Even I find this funny.
This is of low quality.
(He is embarrassed to show
off his creation)
Do you know what inspired me
to make this?
What?
B...
Bus. The thing that is used
to open bus doors.
(Doors are open)
(Doors are closed)
The angle is slightly raised.
Only something original
will have that kind of angle.
You need to get this
from the headquarters.
(This angle is only possible
if made by the headquarters)
Copies will not be able
to get that angle, will they?
Nobody can recreate this.
Shall I make this?
Mulmoa?
It's because we get
to save water.
That is Bulmoa and this is Mulmoa.
That is Yeolmoa.
Yeolmoa.
(Sad)
I'm confused because
I made a lot of things.
(The collaboration between
equipment team and green)
(The original's angle that
nobody can ever recreate)
(It prides itself
on its classy finishing)
(Second product from
3 Meals Steel, Mulmoa)
You can just use it like this
when doing the dishes.
(He explains how it is used)
Don't pull it too strongly.
Why not?
Then, you would need it fixed.
I will do it gently like this.
After that...
Isn't this comfortable?
That is boiling.
(He wraps it up with a joke)
Great.
(He checks on the broth)
- Let it boil longer?
- Just leave it be.
Just let it boil until
that fire dies out.
Okay.
My goodness.
It's 6:45PM?
(They never stopped working
since they arrived)
(It has started to get dark)
(The sun that was blinding)
(is hiding behind the cloud)
(It's nighttime in Mount Jiri)
Squash.
We just need squash?
(It's time to make dinner)
(He turns on some music
before he starts the fire)
(He pulls the antenna)
(He gets the antenna
to listen to the radio)
(We can clearly hear
a familiar voice)
(He places it on the wooden bench
to hear it clearly)
(He gets the items needed
to start a fire)
(Items: Newspaper)
(Chair)
(Firewood)
(Mr. Yoo's dinnertime routine
has begun)
(He starts with firewood)
(Empty)
(He gets more firewood)
(A lot)
(He takes one more)
(He adds another piece
of firewood)
(He gets ready to tear
the newspaper)
(It goes into the brazier)
(He places the lighted match
into the brazier too)
(Seungwon is standing in front
of the shelf with mushrooms)
(Oyster mushrooms)
(One mushroom)
(Two mushrooms)
(Three mushrooms)
(He takes all of them)
(He excitedly goes out)
(He can't open the door)
(He surprisingly steps out
in a cool way)
What are you doing?
- You're starting a fire?
- You're making stew, aren't you?
Yes.
(Dinner menu: Black pork belly
with squash stew)
(He places the mushrooms
inside a basket)
(Being wary of Seungwon)
No, the opposite side.
(He gets water if he twists
it in the opposite direction)
You should just use the faucet
if you're on that side.
- Really?
- Yes.
- But still...
(Next up is time to prepare
the onion)
Just...
I'm not adding meat
to the squash stew.
Okay.
(He focuses on the onion again)
(He cuts and removes the peel)
(He peels using his face)
(Struggling)
(After rinsing it under water)
(He cuts it
into bite-sized pieces)
(Cut the mushrooms)
(After cutting the squash
into half)
(Cut it vertically)
(Cut it into slightly thick pieces
to add texture to the dish)
(Slice chilies diagonally)
(All ingredients to make
squash stew are ready)
Hold on. We need lettuce,
don't we?
Lettuce and sesame leaves.
Okay.
Lettuce, sesame leaves,
chilies, garlic.
(Trudging to the vegetable patch)
(He harvests lettuce first)
(My goodness)
Lettuce.
No, I don't need crown daisy.
He doesn't want crown daisy.
(He has the courage
to be hated)
Is this Cheongyang? Or chili?
(Next is to harvest
Cheongyang or chili)
(Pushing it sideways)
I can't see any.
(He moves to the next tree)
(Only Haejin
couldn't see the chilies)
(He looks here)
(and there)
(And finally sees chilies)
(Chili bonanza)
(He takes everything)
This smells amazing.
(Finally,
he harvests sesame leaves)
(Seungwon pours water
into the wok)
(He places it on top of Yeolmoa)
(He takes a broth pan
and anchovies)
(He pours water into the pan)
(He removes the innards
of the anchovies)
(He puts them in)
The lettuce...
Let me see how much
you have harvested.
(He checks on Haejin's homework)
It's not that good?
Not bad.
(He passes)
How are the lettuce, sesame
leaves, and chilies this summer?
(This time, he changes the song
into an unknown genre)
This would taste better if
we add vinegar to it.
(Washing vegetables with vinegar
will get rid of bacteria)
(He takes both garlic and vinegar)
(And pours a generous amount
of vinegar)
(Mulmoa is used well)
This is very easy to use.
(He is bragging
about what he made)
(He washes the vegetables clean)
(He rinses the lettuce)
(He adds more vinegar)
(Pouring in lots of vinegar)
(Washing it hard)
(He is washing the vegetables
like doing the laundry?)
(While he peels the garlic)
(He soaks the vegetables
in vinegar mixed with water)
(He rinses it again)
(Chef Cha is anxious due to
the long time washing vegetables)
That's done.
(He throws away the mixture
of vinegar)
(And moves the vegetables
inside the basin again)
(Staring)
(Being wary)
Did I rinse it too much?
The water is green.
(The water is green?)
Why?
(Trying to understand
the situation)
You can't wash vegetables like how
Kwangsoo washes abalones.
(Frustrated)
I think the vegetables
have lost their color.
All of them have wilted.
(He tries to resuscitate them)
(He rinses them in water)
(He shakes the vegetables
to remove the water)
Done.
(He is about to plate up
the washed lettuce)
(Checking)
Why are they like this?
This...
Nothing looks fine.
(The lettuce and sesame leaves
look wilted)
What?
(He is quiet when
he hears Seungwon's question)
(Shocked)
Why did you soak those
in vinegar?
My goodness.
(Shock and fear)
No...
But...
Why is it like this?
You shouldn't have bullied
the vegetables like that.
This is what I did back home.
(Confused)
(How does it taste?)
(One more time)
How is it?
What?
It's okay.
(Although he said it's okay)
This is bad.
Is it okay?
Don't worry yourself about it.
(He gets rid of the evidence)
How is it? You tasted it?
These are like pickles.
(Dumbfounded)
How much vinegar did you add?
You should use only
a couple of drops.
I did that.
(It's clear that he was lying)
My goodness.
You
just added lots of it, didn't you?
Yes.
(The sin of loving vinegar)
Are you a goat or something?
What should I do?
But this...
(He has no choice but
to finish this up)
Stop eating.
Listen up.
Just now...
the water was very green.
I guess I scrubbed
the vegetables too much.
(He only realized it much later)
(Giggling)
Let me taste one.
(He tastes the pickled lettuce)
It is fresh.
It is.
The lettuce is still fresh.
But what happened?
Why are you still eating them?
Are you a goat?
Let's just have this as lettuce.
Okay? Alright?
Let's turn this into lettuce.
Stop eating.
Are you eating your wrap
beforehand?
(Chef Cha goes to the fridge)
(He uses his height
to open the doors)
(He takes out gochujang)
(He takes out other seasonings
too)
(He puts the ingredients
in the rack)
(A lot)
(Next, fan it)
- Why? The fire is out?
- No, I want it to be bigger.
I'll make it a bit bigger
so it will cook faster.
(Add more firewood too)
(After he fans it with energy)
(Add it to plain water)
(The broth is boiling)
(He removes the broth pack
and anchovies from the water)
(Add one ladle of gochujang
as the base)
(Mix it well in the broth)
(Vegetables)
(Chili powder)
(Add the vegetables
that were prepared earlier)
(Chili powder that will make
it even spicier)
(Pour in some anchovy extract
to make it more savory)
(A bit of salt)
How are you going to season it?
Salted shrimps.
Yes. We need salted shrimp
when making squash stew.
(He uses salted shrimp
to season the stew)
Wash that? Do you need me
to wash that ladle?
(Haejin is back by the faucet)
(Seungwon is in front
of the chopping board)
(Slice Welsh onion diagonally)
(He tastes it)
(He adds salt)
(Sniffing)
(He adds fish soy sauce)
(The squash stew has been
seasoned to perfection)
(Let it boil)
(He checks the fire)
(He waits behind Seungwon)
Give me that. I'll do it.
(They change spots)
I can smell something spicy.
(It's time to add tofu after
letting it simmer for some time)
(Wash tofu under running water)
(He cuts it in the box
instead of on the chopping board)
(Add tofu into the red stew)
We're going to have
samgyeopsal with this?
Yes. We can grill it here.
We'll let this boil longer.
(While waiting for the stew
to simmer)
I stacked too many things here.
(Taking things one by one)
(He organizes the plates
that they used for lunch)
(After Seungwon wipes
the table clean)
(He scoops some gochujang
into a small bowl)
(He uses another bowl
for sesame oil)
(Sprinkle some black pepper on it)
(He takes both bowls
to the seasoning rack)
(Add some salt)
(1 spoon)
(2 spoons)
(The sauces to dip samgyeopsal
into are ready)
(Next is time to prepare
the black pork samgyeopsal)
(Cut it into smaller pieces)
(Next, it's time to grill
samgyeopsal and kimchi)
(Remove the stem and
put it back inside the container)
This will be done soon.
(The simmered squash stew
looks appetizing now)
(Checks the flavor)
(Add a bit more water)
Honey, the fire...
Make it bigger?
(It's because it's now time
to grill samgyeopsal)
I think we have to move
the fire over there.
Where? The smaller brazier?
This brazier is too big
for the lid.
(After getting the lid
to grill samgyeopsal on)
Yes, it has to be like this.
(He puts it at one corner)
(He removes the broth for now)
I'll remove it now.
(He moves the firewood
to the other brazier)
(Lid)
(He covers the stew pot
with a lid)
Okay.
(He places the lid to grill
samgyeopsal over the fire)
(Wipe it clean and it's ready
to grill samgyeopsal)
Now, this... Cha!
This is getting hot now.
(Getting hot)
Already?
Yes.
Shall I place it here later?
No, you can start grilling a bit
now.
I'll get angry if
we don't start now.
Pour oil in first.
(He coats the lid with fat)
(Coat every spot)
Let me do it.
(Change of member)
(Seungwon is cutting
kimchi into smaller pieces)
The fire is too strong.
This is too strong.
I'll be quick.
(He cuts the kimchi quickly)
(He places black samgyeopsal
over the fire)
This smells amazing.
(He leaves the middle part empty)
(He places kimchi
at the empty spot)
The fire has to be bigger.
(The fire is weaker now)
This gets smaller faster.
(Don't feel stressed)
(The fire manager
will solve it right away)
(The fire is bigger now)
(Haejin helps to flip
the samgyeopsal too)
It takes time to cook
because it is quite thick.
So let them cook longer.
(Cut the thick ones into half)
Shall we mix the kimchi with meat?
No. Leave it in the middle
so it absorbs the fat.
(Kimchi tastes better after
it absorbs the fat)
Just let it cook a bit longer.
(They place the well-grilled meat
on a plate)
(He drops one by mistake)
(Such a waste)
Meat... No.
Shall I plate the kimchi?
Kimchi first.
Plate them in the middle.
(Kimchi goes in the middle)
Done.
(Their dinner is ready)
(Just looking at samgyeopsal
can make people drool)
(Beside it)
(Spicy squash stew)
(Wilted lettuce that was
soaked in vinegar)
(Their delicious dinner is ready)
The lettuce...
Is it okay for us
to eat it like this?
They are all wilted now.
What's wrong with it?
This lettuce...
(Take a few layers of lettuce
that I made)
(Dip samgyeopsal in gochujang)
(Add garlic)
(And fit everything
into his mouth)
(Yum)
(Seungwon wraps the meat
inside pickled lettuce)
This is tasty.
(Add kimchi to meat)
(and more meat)
This is good.
This is amazing.
The meat is so tasty.
(Dip the tasty meat
in the oil seasoning)
(Wrap grilled kimchi
and eat it in one mouthful)
(Hot)
(Seungwon picks two pieces
and dips them in salt)
(Grilled kimchi
in samgyeopsal fat)
Why is this so good?
This is...
There is a difference in quality.
(Dipping it in the oil sauce)
(Nodding as it's tasty)
(Next is squash stew)
I haven't had squash stew
in a long time.
(Seungwon eats squash stew too)
(Yummy)
This is tasty.
This is very good.
This is not gamey at all.
(They are still praising
the black pork)
(The pork is not gamey)
The meat tastes different.
This tastes very different.
You have to do it like this.
I don't know what this is.
I wasn't planning on eating dinner
but my goodness.
The problem with this is that
we eat it too fast.
(They are almost done
with dinner)
You're done eating?
- Huh?
- You're done?
There is some left.
(Why?)
If you're done,
please make us fried rice.
(A very confident request)
- Really? Fried rice?
- It's for us.
Only if you're done eating.
Okay. I'll do that. Hold on.
(He starts by cutting
samgyeopsal into smaller pieces)
(He adds rice to it)
Please add this at the end.
(He passes laver flakes)
It's because this is for us.
Please make it with care.
Okay. I'll do that.
(First, he fries the rice)
(Sprinkle black pepper on top)
(Salt)
(Sesame oil)
(Eggs)
(Pour sesame oil in first)
What is that?
(Special service)
(Finally, he adds laver flakes
as requested)
This looks amazing.
Done.
Okay.
Thank you.
May you live a long life.
(Proud)
(He represents all staff
and takes the first bite)
This tastes as if he fried
every single grain.
This is a masterpiece.
(All staff take one bite)
This is tasty.
Did you try this?
(Black pork samgyeopsal that
is made by Chef Cha)
This is very tasty.
(Everybody is busy eating
their delicious dinner)
Anyway, what is for breakfast?
(He adjusts his glasses)
You said no breakfast.
That's what you said.
Okay. Fine.
We can just cook rice cake soup
when our guest arrives for lunch.
Is someone coming tomorrow?
I bet someone is.
Are you joking?
(Do you think our 10 years
of experience means nothing?)
So for breakfast tomorrow,
we can just have apples.
By the time we go grocery
shopping, our guest will be here.
Then, we can make gomtang
and rice cake soup.
Then we can just think about
what to make for dinner.
Our guest would bring something.
Just in case
that person is empty-handed,
send that person back.
(This will be their first time
to refuse a gust)
If the guest is empty-handed,
we can make budae jjigae.
Yes, that works for sure.
The next morning,
we can grill clams and such.
Not sure about lunch, though.
(Super J's perfect plan)
(Haejin is on his way
to take a shower)
(He makes a sudden turn
and goes to the room)
Is this the guest's room?
(After checking out the room)
(He enters the shower room)
Cha!
Me?
(He can't hear Seungwon's voice)
(Haejin steps out after
taking a short shower)
(He attacks an insect
while drying his hair)
(Their long day has ended)
(The first night in Mount Jiri
gets deeper)
(While the house owners are away)
(Someone has arrived
while sighing?)
(The fourth guest of 3 Meals House
is Uhm Taegoo)
Taegoo!
(Stands up)
(Thankfully, Taegoo is familiar
with the house owners)
(However, this is his first time
at 3 Meals House)
(Running)
(He follows them around)
(There are times when
he looks adorable)
(Taegoo is cute)
How old are you now?
I'm 42.
(Wow)
Can you feel it?
(Taegoo doesn't feel like
he is 42)
(Request: Tear newspaper
into small pieces)
(Very tiny)
Are you joking?
(He is pounding garlic)
(He is peeling a potato)
(Taegoo is helping out
in his own unique way)
(All preparations are done!
It's Chef Cha time)
(Clean-tasting rice cake soup
in bone broth)
(Both the flavor and colors
make it perfect)
(Spicy stir-fried chicken stew)
(Chef Cha's fragrant
seasoned sesame leaves too)
(Yum)
(Yummy)
(This is tasty)
You finished your rice again.
(The best meal that reminds
them of homemade food)
For me, this year...
(He is unable to stop himself
from laughing)
The time I laughed the most...
(What caused Taegoo
to laugh the loudest?)
The time has come
for you to say something.
You watched us before,
haven't you?
What do you think?
The things that I feel...
The pagoda was created
in the 1700s
but we're in the 2020s now.
It feels like
time flies very quickly.
However, nothing has
changed dramatically.
The people
who lived here back then...
How do I explain this?
They were here just temporarily
before moving on.
Just go now.
They disappeared not long
after staying here.
(10th year anniversary special,
3 Meals A Day Light)