Can we not walk side by side?
What do we do from now?
Just as we have been doing.
- Doing well.
- Yes.
Okay, then.
I will go ahead first.
That is even weirder.
Lady Eun Woo.
Yes?
I love you.
Very much so.
Yes. Me, too.
Shall we go inside?
Dan?
They are here.
Okay. You are here?
When you are at Heuksando,
- you need to have some sashimi.
- I see.
I guess you two had a good time at the fireworks.
Why prepare sashimi this late at night?
Mother, have you been w-waiting for us all this time?
Why are you stuttering, Young Man?
Here, have a glass. It is a specialty liquor of Heuksando.
I am really sorry, but do you have anything like a smoked-plum drink?
Oh, my!
I heard you cannot drink,
but I guess it was really true.
A man who cannot drink even a sip of alcohol.
Physician Yoo, you are really
too perfect!
Aigoo, he is the rarest of the rare finds.
How is it that even your eyelashes are long and handsome?
My eyelashes are not particularly that handsome—
You are handsome everywhere.
You will find much handsomeness upon closer look.
I will make sure to look closely at you.
Young Lady, you are happy, right?
- Help yourself.
- Please let me pour you a glass.
It is too delicious!
Right? Would you like to live here, then?
Should I do that, Mother?
Gosh, we need to go back tomorrow.
- Who are you looking for?
- My goodness!
Hey, this is Mak Jin, isn't it?
Are you feeling ill somewhere?
That isn't it. I just have trouble sleeping, so...
Since Physician Yoo is good with the illness of the heart, maybe he could help me.
Aigoo, that's a problem.
Physician Yoo is far away from here right now.
What? When is he coming back?
Well, we don't know that.
What's keeping you up at night?
You need to pass out after a day's work.
I'm a little timid, so...
I finally got a job at the market a while ago,
but I had to quit because the hours did not fit with the prohibitory decree.
Since we've written the petition,
I get anxious and afraid just at the sight of an official passing by.
So I haven't slept a wink since that day.
Aigoo, is it that bad?
That makes us feel so bad.
You got sick while trying to help us out?
Hey, let's take out Mak Jin's letter from the list!
Yes, yes.
We've a mountain of petitions now,
so there won't be an issue if we take out just one.
N-No, you don't need to do that.
Jang Goon will go and bring it.
Yes, hurry up and go.
No! I said it's okay!
I'll just wait inside.
I am happy  and excited
that you are... coming with me.
My heart... is pounding.
For what reason?
Because from now on...
I don't know what will happen.
Whatever may come,
I am okay since we are together.
I wish this path were just a bit longer.
So, to play chicken fight,
straighten your leg and fold it.
Then hold it and jump.
Jump, jump, jump, jump—
Oh, my. Young Master!
Have you all been doing well?
- Physician Yoo!
- You stormed out with bravado,
but how can you come back alone?
What do you mean alone?
- We came together.
- What?
Where?
- Young Lady!
- A-Aigoo!
Oh, my goodness! I had no idea you were hiding there.
I'm so glad you came with him.
While you were gone, Father had so much trouble alone.
Yes, we even went on a break.
We sent all the patients to Birchwood Clinic.
Young Lady, please never leave again.
Okay, Jang Goon.
I will make sure to stay here from now on.
By the way, while you two were at Heuksando,
did you not have any good news?
Why wouldn't they?
They basically got married without us at her family's house.
No, we didn't, yet—
We did not do it yet.
Not yet?
When are you going to do it, then?
P-Physician Yoo, you need to hurry up and tend to the patients.
They said Physician Gye was so busy alone.
- O-Oh, t-that is right.
- Yes, yes.
- There must be many patients to see.
- You're panicking, aren't you?
What's this? Things are going well for them, right?
For sure. They got closer to each other.
Why didn't our handsome Kang Il come with them?
Why would you want that froggy senselessly interrupt when things are going well for them two?
- He needs to go on about his business.
- That mouth!
You did what?
You went down, making big promises, but you were quiet all this time.
So I thought you made that countryside your home.
How could I?
I will get rid of that book of faults for you.
How can we lose the chance to end Yoo Se Yeop just because of a few petty offenses?
How can I trust you when you failed the inspection, too?
I am the only one who can come and go to Physician Gye's house anyway.
How could they have so many grievances against you?
I got it, gosh.
I got it!
Yoo Se Yeop is His Majesty's close friend.
Even if you cannot do it personally,
we must get rid of him by telling the Left State Minister.
Do you understand?
Looking at you now,
it seems that your hate against him is greater than mine.
I am curious about why that is.
Were you that anxious about the petition?
How could your pulse be so fleeting?
The petition will not be shown to Governor Ahn.
It is for His Majesty, so do not worry too much.
I brought the petition!
Thank you.
There!
You do not need to worry anymore.
Please don't burn it.
You said it's something that can help Physician Yoo.
- It is okay.
- Yes.
There's a mountain of it in Physician Gye's room.
There are many patients who like Physician Yoo.
All right, lie back down now.
If you get needle treatment and take medicine, you will be able to sleep soundly again.
Yes. Just leave it to us.
Those who lack a sense of morals and ethics must be punished properly.
But seeing how you wrote a petition
you must be one of them as well.
Because the physicians did nothing wrong.
Also, not allowing me to go outside just because I'm a widow
- is honestly just unfair.
- Whoa.
Are the widows flocking together
and making an arrogant stand as a team?
Great, great, great.
However, make sure to remember
that you are not just a widow.
You are also a naturalized foreigner.
Did you think I would not know?
It is not something you can hide.
Especially your place of birth.
Please spare me, Governor.
Please.
Please spare me.
Aigoo, a quick change of attitude.
I thought it was a different person.
Stand up.
If you just do as I say,
you can survive this.
W-What is this?
A drug
that seduces a man.
Create a chance to be alone with Yoo Se Poong.
At that moment, you just make him consume it.
So easy, is it not?
Scorched rice. It's so delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Gosh, you should
sit next to each other.
Since you came back together from the island.
Why are you all staring so intently?
You ran off after Young Lady during the busiest time
and slacked off the entire time.
And you talk so much! Granny, take away his meal.
You go and get yourself a wife! Instead of being jealous.
Poong, eat a lot.
That's how you prepare for future affairs.
Future affairs?
Future... O-Oh!
All right, let's eat!
There.
Good times for you two.
Young Lady and Half-wit, brace yourselves now.
I'm going to Hanyang.
Man Bok, preparations?
I got our stuff and the petition all ready.
You just need to walk up there with me, Physician Gye.
I will go with you since this is about me.
Hey! Imagine delivering the petitions that sing your praises and innocence
to the Ministry of Justice in person.
How awkward would it be?
You're seriously thoughtless.
You stay here and just treat the patients.
Okay, you can go back now.
You'll get better soon.
Physician Gye.
Oh, I thought you were gone for good, but you came back.
What would be a reason for me to run away?
How should I bring myself to trust you and accept you?
I met Governor Ahn at Moohwagak for a different business.
I was Physician Yoo's colleague, but
we never knew each other personally.
Hey, Froggy. Do you think I'm a fool?
I can see everything in your eyes, the burning fever.
Whenever you see Half-wit, you hide yourself
and watch him in secret.
Why the serious face?
Your aged and jaded self-consciousness.
Use it to better yourself, like when you sharpen your knife
and left for Qing to study abroad.
Don't use it to harm yourself needlessly.
What kind of acupuncture did you give to cause her pulse to stop?
He slipped while trying to show off.
One,
two,
three.
- Whoa.
- Aigoo!
He saved her!
You almost killed this patient just now.
Don't give acupuncture if you are going to kill a person.
Don't even let an unqualified physician into the palace!
How did a guy like him come into the Royal Clinic?
He is the son of that you-know-who.
I heard it was high-handed.
A high-handed appointment in the Royal Clinic? How absurd.
How come!
How come everyone trusts and cherishes Physician Yoo regardless of what is said about him,
but no one trusts me when I am working so hard?
Not even you.
That's because there's something you hide.
You'll never gain others' trust while
holding onto an unspeakable secret.
Whether it's between lovers, a student and a teacher,
or even between a father and a son.
If you feel like there's no one around you to cherish you,
you should look into yourself to see if there's a house
built on conceit and lies.
However, Froggy,
despite being tainted by the Royal Clinic,
you are a very skilled physician.
You're good with improvisations and
you have a lot of the virtues of a good physician.
I told you before, didn't I?
A single countryside physician can save hundreds and thousands of lives.
Don't waste your time looking at others.
Save yourself first, you fool.
What is it?
I wanted to have a deeper and more
intimate relationship with you, Lady Eun Woo.
Poong Woo Journal.
When I first started writing the Illness of the Heart Journal, I wrote about meeting you
on the very first page, Lady Eun Woo.
I am on your first page?
Since you are my first person.
Poong Woo Journal.
"Since we are together now, this journal will also be written together."
That is its meaning.
Isn't it such a good idea?
Yes, it is great.
In that case...
(T/N: Means "wind" in Chinese character)
it would fit better to use "woo" for "rain".
But wouldn't that lead to too much rain and wind in our future?
You already have too many unresolved issues as it is.
(T/N: Means "rain" in Chinese character)
I will block the rain and the wind.
You cannot.
Since you named it, so we can write this journal together,
we must also block the rain and the wind together.
I didn't think that through.
Lady Eun Woo, then, together.
Together.
Poong Woo Journal.
If you don't do your job right,
I'll send you back to your country.
I'm saying I'll put you on the list of people to send back.
Understood?
- Oh, my goodness!
- Hey, it's okay.
Let it be.
I'm going to clean it up.
Hey, if you want to sleep well,
you should be taking this instead of cinnamon punch.
I heard that even though the petition was burned,
you still had trouble sleeping?
If you drink this citron tea with honey,
it'll help you sleep at night.
Try it.
Delicious, isn't it?
For folks who are tormented by walking on thin ice every day
having something nice and sweet will surely calm the soul.
Who wouldn't have a worry or two in their lives?
You better not waste a single drop before going to bed!
How is he going to carry this? Won't it break his back?
Don't even worry about this guy.
He's a lot bigger and stronger than you think.
I packed some snacks that would stun even His Majesty.
Use it as a bribery when something doesn't work out.
Aigoo, thank you, Namhaedaek.
Hey, let's hurry and leave before Half-wit begs to come along, okay?
Gosh, don't worry.
He didn't even wake up yet.
God knows what he was doing at night.
Young Lady was also deep in sleep.
Both of them were busy all night, huh.
That's right. They were both busy all night.
I saw them in the herb storage room.
- What?
- My... How can they, in front of a child?
- Why? What were they doing?
- Go on.
They didn't even sleep all night.
Oh, my. They might get sick.
What could they have been doing? It's obvious.
All night
they wrote journals for the patients.
Whoa, you're strong!
- All right, let's go now.
- Yes, let's hurry.
I made preparations to sink that physician
to the very bottom.
So you just need to sit back and relax.
Oh, I wasn't talking down to you.
Anyhow, what was it that you prepared?
An ugly rumor!
Did you not tell me to end him with an ugly rumor?
You see, I...
No, no. Forget it.
You will see when the time comes, so don't worry.
My goodness.
Why so scared?
You're going back home?
Take it.
It's nice and warm. What is it?
You'll know if you open it.
Try some.
I know your feelings all too well.
How hard it must have been to live in anxiety, trying to hide everything?
That you're a naturalized foreigner.
You're from my hometown, right?
No, who would say—
Do you think I wouldn't know?
Look at me.
It was so hard that I don't even bother to hide it anymore after trying for ages.
Come on, have some.
I really didn't do it!
Please trust me!
Since I didn't have a home, family, or friends
- I had to be good with telling the weather, at least.
- Please open it!
I had to either tell fortunes or at least
pretend to be seeing something for a bowl of rice.
Although they hated me and cursed me,
they liked my skills,
so I made sure to work on my cooking.
I worked everywhere, from festive occasions to funerals.
It's delicious, right?
Yes.
What about when you had nowhere else to turn to?
There will be at least one person to hold your hand.
If you hold that hand and get up, you somehow get on with life.
I guess you had a person like that.
Are you okay?
I did.
I was able to be myself
after taking that hand.
I'm envious.
Any hand I try to accept
only wants to cut my own off.
Do you want to hold my hand, then?
You went through a lot, huh?
Rest at ease today.
I won't tell anyone that you're from my hometown.
Go home and sleep well.
Come here when you get nostalgic.
Physician Gye!
Man Bok!
Will those petitions truly be enough to solve the annulment issue?
Isn't there anything else I can do?
It's not only the petitions we have.
While you were at Heuksando,
I did some background checks on the Chief Royal Physician and his ilk
in the Royal Clinic.
I thought about telling you before leaving,
but I didn't want to worry you.
Since we have his weak spot,
he won't be able to use the false evidence to appeal His Majesty for the cancellation.
As long as nothing else happens.
Jeon Kang Il might look for this in my room.
I left a fake copy in my room,
so please watch what he does with it.
That's how
you can play a role, Young Lady.
Yes.
I planted a spy in the clinic.
It'll explode when the time comes,
so just sit still and watch, please.
Physician Yoo!
How are you doing?
Did you get some sleep?
I'm sorry.
I think it'll be better for me to go home today.
You can do that.
It might be harder to sleep under an unfamiliar roof.
Excuse me, Physician Yoo!
Could you perhaps take me home, please?
This couldn't have been easy for you.
After Se Yeop lost his father and was left all alone,
he was always on my mind.
I am so glad because he has you.
If only I had someone I could rely on at the Royal Court too,
it would be such a great thing.
Your Majesty, that book.
Please do not read it yet.
Why do you say that?
In that book
not a single unforgivable crime exists.
Although I put that book together,
who in this world would not have a fault or two?
It is merely a useful item to bring up
when you're trying to acquit Physician Yoo,
and people continue to try to harm him with false accusations.
So I shouldn't read it right now?
Yes, Your Majesty.
If you read in detail about the petty crimes of people you need to keep by your side,
I am worried that you might be overcome
with loathing whenever you see them.
So please set it aside for now and
use it should the need arise.
Taking even my heart into consideration,
you and Se Yeop are very much alike.
Very well. I heard the petitions from the people of Sorak County
stacked as tall as a person's height.
Yes.
I safely delivered them to the Ministry of Justice before meeting you.
That's a relief.
Even as the king,
I was unable to silence the fiery appeals
to nullify his works.
Now, as long as another disaster doesn't come along,
I will be able to acquit Se Yeop, it seems.
I am deeply thankful for your trust, Your Majesty.
Please be extra careful until it becomes a complete non-issue.
Yes, Your Majesty.
P-Physician Yoo.
If you sit here for a second, I'll get ready right away.
What are you getting ready for?
Well, I really wanted to treat you to a meal.
N-No, I am fine.
Thieves come once they realize a widow is living alone here.
I can only imagine how difficult it must've been
to survive on your own.
Life is like that every day.
I also understand those feelings, at least a little.
Everyone points their swords at you,
threatens you, and harasses you, probably.
And the thought that you're completely alone
fills you with resentment.
Perhaps, do you feel like you are
standing on the edge of a cliff right now?
Nothing is really your fault,
so I hope you will not ever blame yourself.
Also, make sure to look around you.
When you're in desperate agony,
you won't even notice the hand reaching toward you.
Because someone might already be extending a warm helping hand to you right now.
Mak Jin, come here!
For folks who are tormented by walking on thin ice every day,
having something nice and sweet will surely calm the soul.
I know your feelings all too well.
How hard it must have been to live in anxiety, trying to hide everything?
Whatever is causing you to suffer and lose sleep like this,
I promise to get to the bottom of it.
Even if it takes some time,
I will not give up until the end.
Physician Yoo.
Physician Yoo, I'm sorry.
H-How did it go, huh?
Did you feed him the aphrodisiac?
The aphrodisiac.
You fed it to him, right?
Y-You must have, right?
Why the heck are you not answering me?
I cannot do it.
I won't!
What?
Gosh, damn it!
Do you really want to die?
Please don't do this.
Physician Yoo is a good person.
I'm also a good person!
A wench like you...
You will be sent right back to your country.
I'm going to write your name at the top of the list.
You cannot do that.
I'm going to tell everyone everything.
I'm going to keep living here in Sorak County!
How dare you!
Let go!
Come here.
Physician Yoo.
Have you seen Lady Eun Woo?
She has been missing since earlier.
That's what I'm saying.
We also thought it was weird.
But she's not in her room, the guest room, nor the kitchen.
She's nowhere to be seen.
Now that I think about it, Inspector Physician was also missing.
Aigoo, they must be on an urgent house call.
What's that in your hand?
Physician Yoo, I'm sorry.
It seems Mak Jin tried to drug me.
What are you talking about?
L-Let me see that.
This is an aphrodisiac, isn't it?
Are you saying she was trying to seduce you?
Seduce?
Wait, Namhaedaek, isn't she from the same place as you?
She's a naturalized foreigner.
Did she say anything while I was away?
How did you know?
She had changed her accent flawlessly.
Wait a minute.
She wasn't from Sorak County? You knew about this?
Of course, I knew.
Even if she worked hard to change her accent,
there's still a trace of her old dialect.
Aigoo, how'd you find out about our secret?
This definitely isn't right.
There must be something wrong.
Governor Ahn, that bastard, shouldn't be this quiet.
He could've tried to blackmail Mak Jin
by using the fact that she's a naturalized foreigner.
Now that you mention it, I heard another repatriation request came from Qing.
He could've used that as a threat.
Yes. That could be it!
Governor Ahn, that bastard, was trying to make
the scandal in his petition come true!
What about Lady Eun Woo?
Could that be related to why she hasn't come back?
Jeon Kang Il might look for this in my room.
I left a fake copy in my room,
so please watch what he does with it.
That's how you can play a role, Young Lady.
- Young Lady!
Young Lady!
Jang Goon, this way.
- Young Lady!
Let's go that way.
Young Lady!
Young Lady—
- Young Lady!
- Bride! Bride—
It's this way!
Bride!
- We went that way before.
- What?
- That way, that way.
- No, this is—
- Where is she?
- Young Lady.
- Jang Goon, come this way.
- Physician Gye!
Yes, yes.
She wasn't on that side, either?
She didn't come out to the market today.
Aigoo, where did she go?
Young Lady!
- Young Lady!
Where the heck did she go?
Man Bok, you go look around the market.
I am going to look around the mountainside.
Young Master, please be careful.
Go, go now.
Young Lady!
It's me.
What the hell is this?
I told you not to act rashly, didn't I?
Is she the woman?
What are you going to do now?
If I just bury this corpse,
no one will know for now.
How can a so-called governor harm a citizen?
Look who's talking!
A scandalous widow who has an affair with a physician.
How dare you lecture me?
I just need to silence you forever.
Gosh, what's wrong with you?
Everything is over now, Governor Ahn.
You are only adding to your crime!
Stop ordering me around!
Please stop it now!
Please!
You!
Physician Jeon!
Shit.
Run away! Right now!
Hurry up and go!
Go and bring people!
Having trouble breathing?
Aigoo, it's about time you're quiet!
No!
Lady Eun Woo.
Lady Eun Woo!
Please.
P-Please.
♫  I guess I was also like you  ♫
♫  Just like how you are right now  ♫
♫  Like a wandering bird  ♫
♫  who has lost their way  ♫
♫  Please tell me now  ♫
♫  All the loneliness in your heart  ♫
♫  All your painful sighs  ♫