Geez!
Gosh.
I need to seal the coffin.
For that, I need to find a decisive fault.
Dear Chil Sung, you need to do a job for me.
Oh, I'm already busy, but these two seem free.
What kind of...
What work...
Something that my dear Chil Sung will be very good at.
I'm a police officer.
Catching evil guys and protecting justice!
Write down and report everything those wicked men and women
do and say  at the clinic.
Especially focusing on lewd behaviors.
- Understood?
-  Justice, my ass.
I'm just a cowardly officer
spying on good people.
Chil Sung, looking at your complexion
you must have indigestion.
Lady Eun Woo will take care of that with acupuncture in no time.
So please come in.
No, wait.
Your lower bowel is cold, and your stomach is weak.
Chil Sung must be having worries and concerns, right?
Exactly.
What is it? What are you worried about?
Governor Ahn must be harassing you a lot.
Gosh, this Governor Ahn.
Then you can slack off here and just say you were getting treated.
How is my prescription, Physician Yoo?
I thought you read my mind.
It is the most appropriate prescription for Chil Sung.
Be at home and rest to your heart's content.
By the way,
are you two always like this?
Feel at home.
Lady Eun Woo, shall we go for a walk after work  today?
Sure, Physician Yoo.
Aigoo,
are they not making it too obvious?
If some other police officer came here,
then they will be found out right away!
No, I am not doing it!
There, there.
This is a letter from His Majesty.
Just deliver it to Physician Yoo.
It was sent to you, Physician Gye.
Right now at the Royal Court, there is a wildfire of a petition
for the cancellation of all of Physician Yoo's works.
According to an appeal from Sorak County's Governor,
Se Yeop pretended to be close to the Royal Family
to seduce a widow who was trying to be chaste.
Even if he is innocent
this foul rumor has become commonplace now,
-  which is a grave problem.
- Aigoo.
Ahn Hak Soo, this bastard.
I will try my best to stop them,
but it'll be best to not arm them with further ammunition.
I still desperately need Physician Yoo Se Yeop.
I'll protect him from here,
so I ask you to protect him there.
Gosh.
Cancellation of all his work?
Physician Gye!
There is nothing wrong, is there?
No. N-Not yet...
Physician Gye, what does it mean that all of his work
can be canceled?
Everything he has achieved so far
will be made into nothing.
Ranking first in the Byeolsi Exam Liberal Arts, in the medical exam, and being the Top Acupuncturist.
He probably has way more achievements than other people,
but all of that will be crossed out altogether.
Is it something irreversible, then?
It will be difficult.
For now, he will not be able to enter the palace anymore.
Even if he is a friend of His Majesty,
there is no way to bring in someone whose work has been canceled.
What do we do then?
If Physician Yoo really ends up like that...
It is just one appeal letter.
We need to stop it. That's all we need to do.
Aigoo, a bug.
Oh, Jang Goon.
What do you need?
Chil Sung, you!
Your face is all gloomy.
Do you have any worries?
He is just stuck in the middle, going back and forth here and there.
Poor thing.
That is why I made the extra spicy flaming chicken.
- Eat this and forget it all!
- Yes.
When you are worried about anything,
eating spicy stuff works best.
Exactly! It is a cure for illnesses of the heart.
Namhaedaek's flaming chicken is the best in the nation!
Come on. She's the best in everything she does!
Nice and spicy.
Take a leg. Here.
There.
Oh, please go ahead. I don't think I can eat.
Hey, don't worry.
Be faithful!
Do you think your superior will be your superior for life?
Even if that guy keeps getting replaced,
you will always be an officer of Sorak County.
How spicy.
So spicy.
Aigoo, come have some flaming chicken, Young Lady.
I am okay. I have no appetite.
- Young Lady.
- Here.
Is she sick or something?
It's so obvious what happened.
Governor Ahn sent an appeal letter as revenge,
because you foiled his plan with Ip Boon last time.
You will be in big trouble should you make one slip.
Is that so?
"Is that so?"
Wake up!
Nothing is more effective than attacking one's ethics in the Royal Court!
If things go wrong,
you won't be able to even work as a physician.
Why should I worry when their claims are not true?
All of this will resolve if I just explain myself.
Aigoo. This is the problem with you bookworms.
You have no idea about politics!
Breaking you down is not even a problem.
Branding you as a wretched philanderer who goes around seducing loyal widows,
it's so easy for those bastards!
And, even if you say you are okay with it,
what about Young Lady?
Are you not thinking about what Lady Eun Woo might go through?
Just as a safety measure, only look after the male patients for now.
Are you telling me to accept the shackles they threw at me?
Shackles are way better than a guillotine.
It is only for a while. Listen to me.
The Young Lady will only tend to female patients for the time being.
Oh, and don't even go to house calls together.
What about acupuncture, then?
You can just go with that Froggy!
Always stay three feet away from the Young Lady.
Do not even walk beside each other.
Don't give that bastard Governor Ahn any ammo, do you understand?
You are looking for this, right?
Oh, yes.
I thought I had lost it.
Thank you.
Physician Seo,
I know you are uneasy about Physician Yoo's matter.
How did you know, Physician Jeon?
I keep one ear open to the palace since I will be going back one day.
What do you think about staying away from this place for a while?
Such as Heuksando, where your father resides.
Rumors tend to be harsher toward women.
"A former Royal Physician philandered with a widow while living under the same roof."
It is perfect for people to gossip about.
We did not do anything that is wrong.
I know.
But from the people who were criticized and impeached by the Royal Court
following a public debate,
how many do you think truly committed wrongdoing?
Physician Jeon, are you saying that
you think Physician Yoo's works can be canceled even when he is not guilty?
No one knows.
The palace's matters are just like the weather.
It is wise to stay under the roof when there is a quick shower.
No.
I do not want to hide as if I really did something wrong.
I will not run away.
If you insist, distance yourself from Physician Yoo for a while.
If you do not, you will be suspected.
Just as a safety measure, only look after the male patients for now.
Always stay three feet away from the Young Lady.
Don't give that bastard Governor Ahn any ammo.
It will be irreversible.
Everything he has achieved so far will be made into nothing.
Distance yourself from Physician Yoo for a while.
If you do not, you will be suspected.
Where is Lady Eun Woo?
She prepared rice at dawn and went on a house call.
The Young Lady made rice?
It seemed she did not get any sleep.
I came outside at dawn, and she was still here at the time.
The handsome inspector physician went with her to the house call.
- Why would he go with her?
- What?
"It is still dark. Let me come with you."
That is what he said.
He must have followed her, since it was dark.
Does he think he is a lamp or something?
When he came down to inspect us last time,
to the Young Lady he was soft like the spring breeze.
You can just focus on your patients after eating, then.
So why the long face?
From now on, send female patients to the Young Lady,
and send male patients to him and me.
Don't even give medical records of female patients to him.
But why? What if we get too busy?
It's a matter of life and death for Half-wit! Do as I say, all of you.
Governor Ahn will be fiercely out and about to
find a fault in this guy and the Young Lady.
He is scheming something again!
Aigoo, aigoo. Your spit...
- Drink some rice water.
- Okay.
Physician Gye, Chil Sung is not able to eat anything.
Please diagnose him in detail.
No, I am okay.
Hey, you, Chil Sung!
Your mom solely relies on you.
So stop looking lethargic and get yourself together, you punk!
Yes.
Eat up.
Go on ahead and eat.
Welcome.
Please wait a moment.
You got a lot better than last time.
♫  Have you noticed the wind blowing?  ♫
Physician Yoo, please give me acupuncture quickly.
I think I will be in serious trouble soon.
Then, I will ask Physician Seo—
Please wait a little more. Physician Gye will be back soon.
- For now, I'll give you moxibustion.
- Okay.
♫  I'm happy even when it hurts  ♫
♫  Little by little, I can engrave you in my heart  ♫
♫  Don't leave my side  ♫
♫  This shouldn't be difficult  ♫
♫  There's one that I can't endure  ♫
♫  Only one thing I can't endure  ♫
♫  I wish and hope every night, when I open my eyes one day  ♫
♫  I want to embrace you as you are  ♫
Try to look happy, could you?
You were smiling ear to ear going to house calls with Physician Seo.
Your behavior is the reason why such appeals are being made.
I am innocent.
There is not one suspicious thing regarding my relationship with Lady Eun Woo,
so don't recklessly speak with that light mouth of yours.
I heard the Royal Court is already discussing whether to cancel your work or not.
And you are still as laid back as ever?
Either Physician Seo or you need to leave this place to resolve the issue.
No.
We will not run away.
You are saying the same thing.
You dared to tell Lady Eun Woo... to leave this place?
I just told her my humble opinion.
Anyone would think that way.
Stop pretending to be considerate.
If you try to meddle with my life and Lady Eun Woo's life,
I will not let you be.
Because you are the one who needs to leave.
Stop being emotional.
Let me ask you one thing in that case.
The ring on Physician Seo's finger, did you give it to her?
Before you claim your innocence, try to reflect on your behavior first, all right?
"Ate breakfast separately.
Went on house calls separately, too.
Did not even face each other.
Physician Yoo took male patients, and Physician Seo took female patients."
Whoa, how proper. Right, you idiot?
I thought you would get me some good motives, but I did not gain anything here!
Whose side are you on?
I told you to keep a watch on them, but you are defending them.
Whose side are you on, exactly?
Take the lead.
How dare he come in here?
I am sure I told you not to come around here!
All right, search the place.
What are you doing right now?
What?
Collecting evidence.
I found it!
Look here, look here!
Not even 15 minutes passed, and I got some evidence.
Do I
have to make myself come like this!
Are you allowed to search for private letters like this?
I came personally to search for private letters like this.
While you are exchanging countless love letters like this,
those higher-ups are not taking it when I am spoon-feeding them.
Hand it over, please.
This is seized.
What are you doing right now?
You came just in time.
If I just submit these affectionate love letters as evidence,
your work will be canceled and you'll be doomed, right?
So why did you have to
choose to meet a widow and go through this?
Take all of these to the municipal office building.
We are not guilty of anything.
Even if you are a governor,
you cannot wrongfully take letters.
You should just hand it over.
Let me make an irrefutable offer.
W-What now? What is it again?
Your agreement from last time.
What do you say about burning that agreement
and these letters at the same time?
What are you saying?
How are one letter and one box of letters the same?
Because trafficking in a government position, abduction, and human trafficking
are all in that one letter.
I am not sure if its weight is the same as
a bunch of ordinary letters
that exchanged greetings from a far distance.
These letters are very private,
but they are just as innocent.
How about it?
- Well, if you refuse—
- Okay, okay. Let—
I will let you do that.
You got hurt because of Governor Ahn earlier, didn't you?
No, it is not.
It is nothing.
Lady Eun Woo.
I am worried,
because it seems the situation is worsening because of me.
How can you think that?
You saved my life, Lady Eun Woo.
No, I didn't.
This time, you might have all your work canceled
and lose everything because of me, Physician Yoo.
We shouldn't be sitting here.
Go to His Majesty.
Go to His Majesty and clarify the accusations.
Yes.
I will do that if need be.
However, Lady Eun Woo,
these things are nothing to me.
Since I can straighten them out.
I will stop it, so it doesn't become an ugly rumor.
Please do not worry.
Even still,
what if everything attached to
Yoo Se Yeop disappears?
In that case, I can just
keep on living as Yoo Se Poong like now.
What is there to worry about?
Dear Chil Sung,
I am going to give you one more opportunity.
There will be a prohibitory decree.
Keep a watch on them day and night starting today.
You should not sleep.
Should you?
"Women may not go outside after the Hour of Monkey.
(T/N: 3:00 p.m. – 4:00 p.m.)
If you must travel,
you must have a pass obtained from the government."
What? The sun is not even down at that time.
Have you gone mad, Orabeoni?
Seriously. Hey!
How are we going to make a living if we cannot go outside?
Aigoo, he is totally out of it.
Wake up!
"For the edification of customs, widows may only
make a living by doing sewing jobs
and making textiles until further notice.
Especially female physicians' carefree
house calls are prohibited."
Hey, this is just too obvious.
He is just trying hard to find a fault, isn't he?
Wait a minute. Could it be
that you got sick because Governor Ahn harassed you?
He did, definitely.
Things like this
must be torn apart like this in order for your sickness to be cured.
Physician Gye!
Yes, yes.
Please come with me right now!
O-Our young lady g-got injured.
The young lady of the house by the jujube tree?
Is she badly injured that she cannot even come to the clinic?
That's not it.
Because of the prohibitory decree...
Gosh, the Hour of Monkey passed.
- Damn.
- Seriously.
You are really not letting us go outside?
Geez, Governor Ahn, that crazy bastard.
Is he telling women to die in their own rooms if they get sick?
I will go myself. Just wait.
What nonsense.
Why am I like this?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
Take a seat here.
Physician Yoo, are these things treatable as well?
I cannot sleep a wink,
I lose hair by fistfuls,
and just now my heart was racing.
I could not breathe,
and started sweating.
And shamefully, I want to cry, too.
Physician Yoo, I am sorry.
I am sorry.
It is okay.
It is fine.
Working is not so easy, is it?
Yes.
You have to do what you don't want to do.
You are right.
Usually, most people run away
when they have to do what they don't want to.
In that sense,
you are a very brave officer.
Me?
Is that true?
Of course!
What are you writing so diligently on your note?
- Could I take a look?
- No.
You can never look.
An officer needs...
Whose side are you on?
I told you to keep a watch on them, but you are defending them.
Whose side are you on, exactly?
to be brave and just, right?
However, I am timid and...
Keep a watch on them day and night starting today.
You should not sleep. Should you?
cowardly.
Anyone becomes timid
when something precious is at stake.
That is not an evil thing.
Thinking about it now,
I think I have just the right treatment for you.
What do you think? Would you like that treatment?
Is it expensive?
Forget about everything else.
Just focus on your own emotions.
You just write down what you feel.
"During today's Hour of Monkey,
the wind was nice.
There were many clouds."
And then...
It feels a little awkward.
you just
look into yourself.
However, I cannot help but miss you.
Even when you're right in front of me.
What will you write today, Physician Yoo?
Me?
I would write...
During today's Hour of Monkey,
I missed Lady Eun Woo.
I was curious whether she felt the same way or not.
Since she can do just fine
without me now,
I am happy and afraid at the same time.
What is it that I should do?
Which path do I need to walk?
Aigoo, that hurts.
Well, of course, needles hurt.
Try walking now.
Oh, my goodness! It doesn't hurt!
It doesn't hurt at all!
Aigoo, you are really awesome, Physician Gye.
Why did you sprain your ankle at night? It's such a hassle.
Aigoo, I know.
I guess I'm getting old.
What made you come in person on a house call?
Where did your other cute physicians go?
It's that darn prohibition decree!
Are courtesans also prohibited from going outside after Hours of Monkey?
What prohibition?
Gosh, this is what I am saying!
That decree from Governor Ahn works just as he pleases.
He said all women are prohibited—
What? People badmouth even His Majesty in his absence.
He is not... "not here."
He is over there in the room across from here.
- Governor Ahn is?
- Yes.
I am anxious to death.
Please say something.
You must have had a reason to give me that advice.
If I get punished for slander by His Majesty,
do you think you will be safe, Inspector Physician?
So who told you to make such foolish additions to my draft of the appeal letter?
If you had only aimed at Yoo Se Yeop according to the draft, his work would be canceled
and you would be in the same boat as the Left State Minister already.
For an appeal letter to have power,
you need to get one man at a time.
When did I tell you to bring that female physician into this?
I was just trying to
put a final end to Yoo Se Yeop, that bastard.
I heard His Majesty ordered a thorough investigation.
So we will have to wait and see.
Since you already made a choice to spread a rumor,
you may as well spread another one that's foolproof.
Physician Yoo.
Lady Eun Woo.
I missed you.
We always share the same space.
How did I
not realize it all this time?
Treating together,
going on house calls together,
giving acupuncture in my place.
I had forgotten that every second of our time spent together
was so meaningful.
If we have to be so distanced from each other,
so...
you are no longer able to be my hands.
I think I will be stifled.
I hope
you feel the same way as me, Lady Eun Woo.
Even so,
we have to overcome this crisis.
We must do so.
♫  If I can send the feelings that seep out of my heart  ♫
♫  Spending my days loving and missing you  ♫
♫  The one thing that remains constant, the one I love is you  ♫
Even if it means I will lose everything,
♫  The very words "I love you"  ♫
I will never let go of you, Lady Eun Woo.
♫  I've shouted from my heart hundreds of times  ♫
♫  But I can't say aloud,  ♫
♫  so I'll wait one more day  ♫
Where have you been? The night is getting late.
What about you, Physician Gye?
Well, I was on a house call at Moohwagak.
Chun Wol had sprained her ankle.
This late at night?
Aigoo, I should have gone.
How many lives do you think you can save by raising a physician?
Well, that would depend on the physician's capabilities.
You think it would be nice to get to
a higher position after treating some higher-ups, right?
Well, that is what everyone at the Royal Clinic wants.
However,
try living a virtuous life by saving lives in urgent care.
You cannot ever quit that.
A physician is bound to save more lives
when they are in a rural place like this.
If you destroy a single rural clinic,
it is the same as killing all the people
that clinic could have saved.
Why are you saying that to me?
I heard
you are Yoo Se Yeop's colleague from the Royal Clinic.
You probably didn't meet with Governor Ahn
to investigate someone, you weren't even close to.
What are you trying to pull off here, exactly?
"Spread a rumor that's foolproof."
Damn it!
Coming into the governor's room like it is your own.
What now? W-W-What now, huh?
You are going to draw your sword, do this and that,
make me pass out by pressing me here? As a physician?
Do not meddle with my kids anymore.
You fabricate a romance between a man and a woman
and submit an appeal letter? How petty.
Oh, that?
It will resolve on its own if your subordinate physician is truly innocent.
No need for guilt.
Using Chil Sung to find a fault at any cost!
Ordering an unnecessary decree against women.
Your intention is as clear as day.
Are you still going to deny it?
You're so cheeky in front of your own governor!
You only call yourself a governor!
But a true governor would take care of his people.
Are you saying your position as Sorak County Governor
is just a stepping stone to a better position?
Withdraw the ridiculous decree right away!
If you don't, I also will not merely sit back and watch.
Woof, woof, woof, woof!
Stop giving me dog shit and
get lost right away before I lock you up!
I will not be shaken, no matter what you say.
I will find a way to stop all of you from barking.
So brace yourselves and wait.
Hey, wait. Wait, wait.
Since you won't listen to the damn advice intending to save you
but you would rather be plotting at courtesan houses,
you will soon end up just like this.
Turn the light on before you go!
Come here, you!
You will not get away with this today!
Come here, I said! Aigoo, shit!
Please help me. Please help me.
What is this? Where does it hurt?
My mother could not birth my sister all night long.
She lost a lot of blood.
Are you saying this is your mother's blood?
Why did you come only now?
Because of the prohibitory decree.
That wretched decree.
Wait just a moment. I will get ready.
Jang Goon, please get me tranexamic acid and Buddha's Hand*.
(A medicine that helps with a woman's labor)
Okay!
Are you really going on a house call right now?
Governor Ahn is out to get us.
If it is not urgent, wait for the physicians to come.
Gosh, I cannot spare even a second because it is a difficult labor.
Where did the physicians go?
Physician Gye headed out to make rounds in the county for patients at dawn.
Other physicians went out early to get medicinal herbs.
Forget that bullshit decree.
Just go.
Two people's lives are at stake.
Granny, what if she gets caught again?
Let us go.
Please be careful!
"The sky was so nice today.
Purple is a wild chrysanthemum.
The wildflowers on the road..."
Have you gone mad?
Hey! Who are you?
Are you a poet or Chil Sung?
See, here! We have a great poet here!
Get this man a beating!
I am going to fire you and
make sure you cannot even
make a living, do you understand?
You are a very brave officer.
I am a brave officer.
You go die, you bastard!
Please cut it out!
How dare you, although I was not surprised.
How dare you do that to your superior's face? Look at your glaring eyes.
I wrote everything as you ordered.
So take a look here!
If you fire me,
I will get you fired as well.
What?
Everything is written here.
How you spied on the Gye Soo Clinic,
how you harassed poor women,
and how you interfered with treatments! All of it!
I will report to His Majesty about them.
Chil Sung, I think you are too carried away, you punk—
Try reporting me, all right?
I hope you will report me. Got it?
You are really done.
I will really go.
Shinmungo*!
(A drum of appeal that people beat to draw the King's attention)
I will go to beat it!
Lady Eun Woo went by herself?
When and where to?
Yang Sun came up from the village.
She said her mother couldn't give birth all night.
Aigoo. Young Master. Young Master!
There is a beautiful physician inside, right?
That physician is a very skillful one.
So she will save your mother and your sister for sure.
Really?
Of course.
Do you know how to boil water?
Please prepare some boiled water, then.
Okay.
Hang in there a little more.
Physician Yoo!
Lady Eun Woo, how is she?
She is a patient who had come to the clinic before.
A breech baby was expected because the fetus' position was abnormal.
I think she was not able to come to the clinic
even after her contractions because she feared the prohibitory decree.
I see.
Please finish giving acupuncture.
Yes.
Try to push one more time.
You cannot let yourself go!
We cannot give up.
If we do this right, we can save them.
R-Right.
- One...
- two...
- three!
One more time. Push one more time!
Just a little more.
Push one more time.
What about the baby?
She is safe. It is a beautiful daughter.
You lost a lot of blood, so I will prescribe you medicine.
Thank you, Physician Seo.
Thank you for saving the baby.
- Why are you about to cry?
- Where is your mother?
- Why does it matter?
- Please stay here for a second.
Where is your mother?
Stop crying!
Stop crying, you brat!
- We will take you if you cry.
- I said stop crying!
What do you think you are doing?
- You go inside and wait.
- Okay.
What is all this ruckus?
There is a patient in critical condition in there.
I do not know what the matter is, but come again next time.
I do not think we can do that.
We came to see you physicians,
not the patient.
We came to teach you what happens when you
violate the decree from the municipal office.
Did I not say it was an emergency?
Violating the noble decree
of the municipal office is the most urgent matter, Physician.
The Royal Decree comes before the municipal office's decree.
You know you will be subject to national law if you interfere with treating a dying patient, right?
National what?
Physician Yoo, what is—
Lady Eun Woo, please stay inside.
Aigoo, it is past the Hour of Monkey right now.
What do we do?
Since you violated the decree,
you need to be punished, right?
There is no law that punishes a physician for saving a patient.
Aigoo! How scary, is she not?
If someone violates the decree
we were told we could rough folks up,
so we're here for a warm up.
We are thugs, so we do not know what you are saying.
But we know how to beat a woman.
Stand back.
We are on our way after saving a person, so we do not wish to harm you.
- So make way.
- Make way?
Show him what it means to make way!
- Make way for him!
- What are you doing right now?
Stop right now!
Gosh, this little.
Physician Yoo.
Lady Eun Woo, please stand back for a moment.
I certainly
warned all of you.
- What is this?
- What is that?
Gosh, you startled me.
- What is that? Huh?
- I thought it was a knife.
Let me tell you what happens if you do not listen to a physician.
Listen carefully.
You will be blinded for life if you do not wash your eyes within an hour.
Do you want some as well?
Or will you save the others?
Let's go. A-Are you okay?
Water.
Physician Yoo.
Physician Yoo, your wound.
I didn't know because it didn't hurt at all.
Are you not hurt, Lady Eun Woo?
I'm fine.
Let's hurry back so I can treat you.
Lady Eun Woo,
if we keep on walking to the end like this,
where will we arrive?
If only I would vanish,
then everything else
would find its place again, wouldn't it?
Your wound is bigger than I thought.
It must have hurt a lot.
It did not hurt much, so I really had no clue.
This is upsetting.
It hurts.
I feel secure because you are here, Lady Eun Woo.
Even so, you got hurt because of me.
It was not because of you.
It is because of that ridiculous decree
and the thugs who are harassing the weak using the decree as an excuse.
If it was not me,
it would have been some other powerless person who got hurt.
Since I have you, who will treat me,
it is better for me to get hurt.
It is all done now.
It's because you looked so haggard
from all the trouble today.
You better have a hearty breakfast tomorrow.
Just now, something really bad happened.
If only we had continued the fate that began from those cliffs.
However, no amount of regret
can reverse what is past.
We must walk the better path
and never fall down.
All the times I spent learning medicine from you,
were full of happiness.
Remembering the moment we saved each other
and to always remain indebted to each other.
-  And for that to happen, my only choice,
- Lady Eun Woo.
is that I must leave.
♫  Have you noticed the wind blowing?  ♫
♫  Bringing this dying love along  ♫
Lady Eun Woo.
♫  As I look at you with trembling eyes  ♫
♫  I'm happy even when it hurts  ♫
I cannot let you go like this.
♫  Little by little  ♫
Please do not leave.
♫  I can engrave you in my heart  ♫
♫  Don't leave my side  ♫
♫  This shouldn't be difficult  ♫
♫  There's one that I can't endure, only one thing I can't endure  ♫
♫  I wish and hope every night, when I open my eyes one day  ♫
♫  I want to embrace you as you are  ♫
There's a time for letting go and a time for protecting.
Right now is the time to protect.
Please let me have it, Mother.
You dare call her "Mother" in this situation?
You dare come to Heuksando by secretly following Lady Eun Woo?
You are the one who should stop being clingy!
What are you trying to do in Hanyang?
Background check.
In a very thorough and complete way.
As long as you want, Physician Seo,
you can learn more about medicine in Qing Dynasty.
Physician Yoo?
You keep getting hurt like that
if you are with me, Physician Yoo.
I am not in pain.
I only loved you to death.
♫  I want to embrace you as you are  ♫