(Kang Tae Oh)
(Kim Se Jeong)
(Lee Sin Young)
(Hong Su Zu)
(Jin Goo)
(Nam Gi Ae)
(And Kim Nam Hee)
(Moon River)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
So that makes you Heungbu, the good guy,
and a swallow never abandons Heungbu.
I did not catch you.
You caught me.
You are the one who came running to my side.
So you have to save me.
Protect me with everything you have.
That is an order.
It is his.
This darn jade ring for gat.
It is His Royal Highness' ring.
We do not have time for this.
We must get this news to His Majesty at once.
The Crown Prince is alive. This complicates things.
Yeo Ri.
Where is the Chief Royal Secretary?
This is delicious!
All right. Enough eating.
- Come here! - What are you doing?
What do you think you are doing? How dare you. Do you know who I am?
Neither of us has clean hands here.
Send the court lady out.
How did you...
You killed the Crown Prince?
Would you believe it if you were me?
You are going to have to.
Because my father is looking for a scapegoat to offer up in my place.
But why me? I have done nothing.
You are Grand Prince Je Un's maternal first cousin.
And you tried to back him to replace the Crown Prince, did you not?
What is it that you want?
Put Grand Prince Je Un on the throne.
And by his side...
is where I will be.
What do you need me to do?
The Left State Councilor's daughter tried to make...
Grand Prince Je Un the Crown Prince?
Yes, Your Highness. Since the Crown Prince is alive,
she wants me to take care of the loose ends.
Your Highness, what should I do?
I see now.
That explains everything.
Pardon?
Follow the Left State Council's daughter's plan only halfway.
It seems Grand Prince Je Un is fated to die by another's hand.
Darn it.
The way I see it,
he saved my legs just to make me overwork.
There is no other explanation for it. Right?
Gosh!
Okay, let us try again.
We are almost there!
Goodness.
Wait, I do not think this man is asleep.
Huh!
Go!
Gosh, I am sorry.
You fool.
Why would you grab something so hot?
That was foolish.
Hey, I know you are not asleep. Get up. Hey.
Darn it.
She is Nolbu's wife, not the swallow.
That hurt.
(Chapter 4: A Swallow Does Not Just Repay Kindness)
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Are you feeling any better?
- I should probably see a physician. - Is it that bad?
Let me see. I mean, I did my best to treat it.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Now, please take a look at her hand as well.
- Yes, my lord. - Me?
Gosh, it is okay. I am fine.
How can you say you are fine? Your palm is covered in blisters.
I am fine.
If you do not get treated, then neither will I.
- Hey. Take this off. - Yes, my lord.
- Gosh, do not do that. - Take it off this instant.
All right.
- Here. - Okay.
So stubborn.
You should have gotten it treated sooner.
Come on, open your eyes.
My lord.
Aide Cha of Hanyang Guild is here.
Aide Cha?
His Royal Highness sent a letter?
So Gang was alive.
I definitely gave Eunuch Yoon the letter.
But I have not been able to see him since that day.
And the Royal Army has no intention of making a move.
They have even restricted my access to the palace.
Someone is keeping His Highness from returning.
All right. I will go myself.
Should you not inform His Majesty first?
We cannot trust anyone in the palace right now.
I will go quietly and bring His Highness back.
My lady!
My lady. This is bad.
Grand Prince Je Un...
What about him?
A letter from His Royal Highness was found at your residence.
What was your motive for hiding the letter?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Why would a letter I have never seen...
turn up at my home?
So you are saying you did not know His Royal Highness was alive?
I knew. That is why...
I sent men to rescue His Royal Highness.
How do we know if you sent those men to save His Royal Highness...
or to harm him?
Why would I try to harm my brother now?
You are...
the late king's legitimate eldest son.
If Queen Jangjeong had not been falsely accused of adultery...
and if the late king had not left a will forbidding you...
from ever inheriting the throne,
you would have been the one to rightfully take the throne.
I have never once entertained such a thought.
But would the Queen Dowager believe that?
That is not true!
If Grand Prince Je Un intended to harm His Royal Highness,
would he have sent Left Flank Guard,
a man who has served His Highness his entire life?
I will go quietly and bring His Highness back.
- Gosh, are you all right? - Hey.
Are you awake?
I will go.
If you make a move,
everyone in the palace will find out.
He is putting you in a compromising position.
What have I done?
When a guard who protects His Highness fails to fulfill his duty,
he must face severe punishment. You know that, do you not?
Sometimes, he must face death too.
Yet,
you just helped such a traitor escape.
If this is about Grand Prince Je Un, then go back to your room.
Nothing is going to change.
I admit defeat.
But do you know something?
Amateurs always choose...
self-destruction.
If so much as a hair of Grand Prince Je Un is injured,
I will take it straight to the Royal Investigation Office.
Do you think I would leave your legs to run on?
Break them, and I will crawl.
So if you want to stop me,
you will have to break my neck first.
Do you think I cannot?
- Is there anyone outside? - Yes, sir.
Did you look for me?
Lock up U Hui in her room...
and do not let her take a single step outside...
until the Royal Wedding.
Father.
Forgive me, my lady.
Do not lay a hand on me.
I will bite my tongue off and die.
What is it this time?
My goodness.
Let me see.
It is him.
Come on down, my lord.
Who are you?
Who sent you?
We took their money, so we must see the job through, right?
- What should we do, my lord? - Get down.
What?
It is too dangerous on the horse. Get down and just look forward.
Do not ever look back.
Okay.
Here.
What should I do now, my lord?
My lord?
What is going on?
A man trying to save his own skin.
What a pathetic, cowardly sight.
Get over here!
Scum like you is not worth the air you breathe.
I know, right? Hey, give me that axe.
Would not someone who was betrayed...
be the best at swinging it?
I should not have saved him.
The Art of War states,
"Appear weak when you are strong."
Then again, my abilities are not exactly easy to hide.
And so, my strategy is this.
What is he saying?
Tackling it head-on.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
This way!
What do we do?
I will create a diversion, so you run.
Please stay alive this time.
Please.
I am pretty tough too, okay?
Goodness!
Oh, my!
- What? - Take this!
Hey.
No!
Goodness.
My lord!
Please save me!
Shin Won.
My lord.
Please forgive us. Goodness.
You were alive.
Thank you.
Thank you for being alive.
Your Highness, more importantly, Grand Prince Je Un is in danger.
What about Grand Prince Je Un?
The Crown Prince is alive.
We will deal with Grand Prince Je Un...
after the Crown Prince returns.
And you are certain His Royal Highness can return?
They tried to assassinate His Royal Highness.
Desperate people fear nothing.
They will not hold back.
Do you really believe Grand Prince Je Un...
tried to kill the Crown Prince?
The truth does not matter.
What matters is that His Royal Highness is alive,
and that he must return safely.
The same prince you tried to protect...
by sacrificing everyone you loved, Your Majesty.
Do as you wish, Left State Councilor.
As you command, Your Majesty.
The Left State Councilor has acted.
That means he will not spare Grand Prince Je Un.
The problem is...
he is not the only one who wants Grand Prince Je Un dead.
What do you mean by that?
All the better.
Neither the Crown Prince...
nor legitimate Grand Prince Je Un is here.
If His Majesty dies now with no clear successor...
The right to name the next heir falls to the Queen Dowager.
Once Je Un is exiled...
and while the Left State Councilor's attention is on him,
she will poison my father.
Because Her Highness has never once forgotten...
the Gyesa Year incident.
Left State Councilor cannot exile Grand Prince Je Un right away...
since people are watching.
He will get rid of Je Un before I arrive.
Within the 6 to 7 days it will take...
to reach Hanyang from Yeongdeok.
When did you send the letter?
Today is the fifth day.
It will be the sixth day soon.
Even at full speed, it will take two days.
You cannot make it in your condition.
Besides...
My men are ambushing all land routes...
from Yeongdeok to Hanyang.
You will never make it back to Hanyang.
You still do not get it, do you?
Hey, the land routes may be blocked, but what about the waterways?
The shipping lanes have not closed, have they?
What do you mean? Is there a way for us to go by boat?
Follow me.
I have got a fantastic swallow hidden nearby.
- No, really. I cannot be in debt. - No, it is fine.
When did you...
Apparently, that peddler saved the life...
the supervisor of the tax grain ships.
In return, they will provide us with a tax grain ship.
We should arrive at Mapo Ferry by tomorrow morning.
Then I will bring everything I can...
I owe Dal a great debt.
Will you have her accompany us to Hanyang?
She saved the Crown Prince many times.
Naturally, she must be rewarded.
Could you not just send a reward to her in Boryeong later?
Hey. If it was not for her, would we even have this ship?
Besides, when it comes to rewards,
you cannot just send money.
Shin Won, why are you so cold?
Thank you.
As you wish, Your Royal Highness.
Were you laughing at me?
You need more beating, do you not?
No, it was not that.
I was not laughing. It is so cold that I started to cough.
It was this, and you must have misunderstood.
Hold on.
These clothes look quite fine.
Staring will not make the boat go any faster, you know.
Come on, have a seat.
Let me change your bandage.
Grand Prince Je Un was arrested for treason.
The Grand Prince? Wait, hold on.
Treason?
Does that not mean his life is in danger?
I must go to him.
I am the only one who can save him.
But...
I am scared that it might be too late.
You know there is a saying.
- The more urgent it is... - Take the long way?
Why take the long way in a hurry? The more haste, the better the plan.
As soon as we reach Mapo Ferry, you should...
tighten this bandage.
Steel your heart and go straight ahead.
Okay?
Fine. I will go straight there and come right back,
so wait at the Hanyang Merchant Guild.
Do not fly off to Gangnam.
Gangnam? What does that have to do with it?
You said you were a swallow.
A loyal swallow who does not abandon Heungbu.
Just you wait.
You will be the one getting the gourd.
An absolutely enormous one, at that.
Just do not be too shocked when you receive it.
Do not worry. I am a woman with material desires.
The moon is beautiful tonight.
It really is.
It is not even a full moon, but it is still beautiful.
My lord.
I will follow you.
Who are you looking for?
It is nothing.
Move, or I will slit my throat.
What are you all doing?
Do you not know my lady? She always follows through.
(Mapo Ferry)
I am sure those clothes looked different.
Go wait at the Hanyang Merchant Guild.
Okay.
Please be careful.
I will.
Come on, let us go.
Did you see Grand Prince Je Un being sent into exile...
at the market earlier?
They say he is being sent to an island near Yeongdeok.
Of course I saw.
What a terrible fate.
I must be at the palace before 11am.
Before 11am?
His Majesty skips his morning meal.
He eats his breakfast at 11am.
He takes medicine 30 minutes later.
Then we must go there at once.
But Grand Prince Je Un is in danger too.
If he is exiled to an island, the Left State Councilor...
will deal with him on the ship.
Because that would be the cleanest way to do it.
If we are bringing the ruffians,
we cannot split up our men.
Your Highness. You have to make a choice.
Are the preparations complete?
Yes, sir. Grand Prince Je Un's ship will encounter a storm,
and it will be wrecked.
All the better.
Neither the Crown Prince...
nor legitimate Grand Prince Je Un is here.
If His Majesty dies now...
with no clear successor...
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, the Crown Prince has returned!
Send him in at once!
Anyone can stop Father's poisoning,
but Grand Prince Je Un's exile can only be stopped by his decree.
Only I can do it.
This is the ring I sent with the letter,
so it will prove that I am alive.
You must go to the palace.
I will go to Je Un.
Gang.
Gang!
Your Majesty. Forgive me for being so late.
I have troubled your heart...
and thrown the people into chaos.
Please hold me accountable for my filial and loyal failures.
No. You came back alive. That is all that matters.
That is more than enough.
Also, the journey here was perilous and I nearly died many times,
but thanks to Grand Prince Je Un, I returned to the palace safely.
Please bestow a great reward upon Grand Prince Je Un.
Of course. It shall be done.
It was no coincidence.
The Crown Prince saw right through my desperation.
He pretended not to pay attention,
but he knew everything going on in the palace.
Right after Grand Prince Je Un was sent into exile,
he knew I would poison the king,
and when exactly he takes medicine.
He remembered it all.
The Crown Prince...
is a tiger.
The moment Left Flank Guard entered,
he instantly knew there was arsenic on this medicine bowl.
You must have told him.
Yes.
For the Queen Dowager,
today must be a day under divine favor.
What do you plan to do?
To fight the Left State Councilor,
I need the Queen Dowager's help.
But Your Majesty, they tried to poison you.
If you let this go, do you not think they will try again?
Keep it as an ace up your sleeve.
To keep power from the Queen Dowager when the Left State Councilor falls,
you need some leverage of your own.
I apologize, Gang.
Why are you taking the blame?
It was Chief Royal Secretary's fault, not yours.
Gang, do you trust me?
For all you know, I could be the one who tried to assassinate you.
I do trust you.
Because you are my family too.
I know who the real killer is.
I saw who shot me at the cliff.
- What do you mean? - Left State Councilor's daughter.
If it had not been for Dal,
I would be dead by now.
Dal?
Did you meet Dal at Sinjusa?
What?
Wait, how did you know that? That she went to Sinjusa?
I heard she would stop by before leaving.
Right, about Dal.
I told her to stay in Hanyang for a bit,
but she does not have anywhere to go.
Could she stay at your place for a while?
Dal is in Hanyang right now?
Yes, she is at the Hanyang Merchant Guild.
Why on earth would you send her there?
What if she gets spotted by the Head Merchant?
What about it?
Well, Gang.
The court ladies Queen Dowager keeps sending to your chambers.
They all come from the Head Merchant.
You said that Dal looks just like the Crown Princess, right?
If Queen Dowager finds out she also saved your life,
do you think she will just leave Dal alone?
Hey.
Hurry up and go.
Hurry up and bring Dal back.
Run! Hurry up and run!
Hey, I heard you were almost exiled. Are you okay?
As you can see.
That is a relief.
- Is the inspector doing okay? - Yes, he...
He was shot too. The journey was rough,
and he got into a few fights, so his wounds reopened.
He bled a lot.
I wonder if he ever got them treated properly.
- Well... - Oh, right.
And his meals? Is he eating properly?
He must be exhausted. He must eat well to regain strength.
He cannot be a picky eater if he wants to recover.
But he just has the face of a picky eater.
Hey, why have you not answered any of my questions?
You have been asking one question after another...
that I have not had a chance to get a word in.
- Was I? - Goodness.
It seems you have grown quite close to Gang in that short time.
I have to admit, I am a bit hurt you worry more about him...
than me.
What? Close? No way.
It is just about the money I am owed.
The inspector did promise to compensate me handsomely.
I need that money to pay you back, and everything, do I not?
If that is what you are worried about, do not be.
This will take care of everything.
All of that?
What is going to happen to me now?
The Crown Prince has returned.
Nothing will change.
Even if the Crown Prince dies again, and His Majesty dies,
still, nothing will change.
You will take the place I have designated for you.
As you said, I have no other choice but you.
But the throne is another matter.
If the king dies, I will just place another royal on the throne.
Then why is Grand Prince Je Un the only one who is not an option?
Because he is the son of the late king.
And Queen Jangjeong's son.
If you are worried about revenge, that fear is baseless.
Grand Prince Je Un was even ready to take the fall for my crime.
And the biggest reason now...
is you.
What proof do you have that Grand Prince Je Un...
will not seek revenge against me?
Is it not because you love him?
You killed the Crown Prince for Grand Prince Je Un,
and Grand Prince Je Un threw away his life for you.
See? This is how love makes people weak.
If he has you wrapped around his finger,
there is no guarantee you will not turn on me.
So, wake up...
from your foolish dreams.
What, she sent all this back?
Why?
She sent everything back...
except her travel costs to Hanyang.
Seriously, what kind of peddler does that?
She is a peddler, all right.
She only took silver.
Her math is spot on.
What do you want me to do with all these things?
Then...
prepare a gift chest with the smallest, priciest items.
Okay? Make sure it is not too ostentatious.
Yes, Your Highness.
Wait.
He asked that you please wear this outfit.
"You thought you could win my heart with just this?"
I thought you would say that.
I never dreamed you would be so moved by a mere set of clothes.
How could something this beautiful be "mere"?
Someone so lowly like me...
would be punished for wearing something like this.
You will be punished if you do not wear it.
You may not realize it, but you did something incredible.
So incredible that you will regret letting me off with just an outfit.
Wear them and come on out. I will see how it looks on you.
Again?
Why?
I am pleased you can recognize me...
by my footsteps alone.
Too much has been broken between us for such pleasantries.
That is why I am here. To put things right.
Why are you always climbing up so high?
Because my mother is in the skies.
Do you miss your mom?
Is that...
your dream?
My dream...
is to go back to the way things were.
Do not tell me.
Did you orchestrate all of this because of what I said back then?
I have never forgotten your dream.
And so it became my dream as well.
It is a dream because it can never come true.
It is time...
for you to wake up from that dream too.
I do not know if this suits me.
I cannot believe I get to wear something like this.
You must have a guest.
She is not a guest. She is my woman.
The woman who will be my family.
So, could you leave now?
As you can see, I have a prior engagement.
I have not torn up your contract.
Stop right there.
You seem to be under some sort of misunderstanding.
I am not someone you can order around.
A scholar-official's daughter cannot command a royal.
The only reason...
I ever obeyed you was because I loved you.
But now...
the man who loved you...
is dead.
I am sorry.
Are you okay?
I will manage.
You were first, were you not, my lord?
You loved her before the inspector, right?
What does it matter who came first at this point?
Why did you let her go?
To save her.
It is the only way for me and for her,
for both of us to survive.
So, will you help me?
After all, I still hold your contract.
Right.
It is not like a debtor has much of a choice.
I should obey.
Your Royal Highness, you look pleased.
Gosh. Pleased?
A man of virtue...
enjoys repaying kindness and showing benevolence.
It is something like that.
I pray that is your true heart.
You will have the Royal Wedding soon.
If they see you with a woman,
who looks exactly like the Crown Princess,
it will not just be that peddler who gets in danger.
The Left State Councilor will watch you even more closely.
I am repaying the one who saved me. Nothing more.
So this is the last time.
Today.
Today is the last day.
- It is so pretty. - It is, right?
The silver one is so pretty too.
My lord!
There she goes again.
Smiling so beautifully again.
Gosh, this hits the spot!
You seem more moved by this rice soup...
than by all the gifts I sent you.
This is not just any soup, is it? It saved my legs,
and it saved your life too.
You are right.
This soup really is something special.
Now that I have had the soup,
I guess this is goodbye, my lord.
Already?
I hear there will be fireworks later.
Why do you not you stay and watch it before you go?
- Fireworks? - Yes.
It is for the Crown Prince, who was missing but returned safely.
I heard there will be fireworks to celebrate it.
It is all right. I have seen all sorts of fireworks.
Even if you have,
it must be your first time seeing it in Hanyang, right?
Okay, fine. We will watch it together.
This hits the spot!
Hold on.
Gosh, I got a scrape.
This is what I get for being so careful with it.
You wait over there for a moment.
- Where are you going? - It will just be a minute.
Shin Won and I will be right back. Sae Dol, you stand guard here.
- Got it? - My lord!
What was that about all of a sudden?
Which of these flower shoes would suit "autumn leaf" color type?
She will probably only wear them this one time.
Just pick any pair.
This is the last pair I will give her,
so the choice must be perfect.
The prettiest ones I can find. Right?
Why are you so cold-hearted?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Why are you fidgeting? You are like a puppy needing to poo.
Gosh! Do not mention...
dogs and poop in the same breath.
All right. You startled me.
I will be right back.
What? Oh, my.
What is wrong with them?
Hold on.
That woman looks familiar.
You never forget a pretty face, do you?
Gosh, she is gorgeous. What?
Is she not the peddler?
A peddler?
Yes, my lady...
No,
she is the girl who ruined Inspector Kim's family.
- I am sure it is her. - Is that so?
It has been a while.
Do I know you?
Minister Ja Gyeong would like to see you.
You wench!
How dare a lowly peddler like you...
wear red silk, a privilege reserved for nobility?
You dare defy The Laws of Morality and get away with it?
My deepest apologies. If you will just give me a moment,
I will change out of these clothes right away.
Do you think this can be resolved...
by simply changing your clothes?
Do you? I could have you beheaded on the spot...
to make an example of you for defying The Laws of Morality.
I have committed a crime worth death. Please forgive me this once,
and I will do anything. Please just spare my life.
That is right.
You will have to do whatever it takes.
Gosh, Minister Ja Gyeong, that obnoxious man.
Your Highness!
I told you to stand guard. What are you doing here?
- What? Why? - He...
Spit it out!
He... Gosh. He...
He...
Poor that peddler.
Why did she get caught by Minister Ja Gyeong?
Why would she wear red silk? It is not fit for her status.
A peddler in red silk.
Is she not the peddler from earlier?
- How long have you followed me? - The entire time.
Now that I have caught you, go back.
I have somewhere to be.
Minister Ja Gyeong is my father's closest confidant.
Do not let yourself be a nuisance to my father any longer.
Let me go.
Are you really starting a family with a lowly peddler?
Why not? I once wanted to start a family...
with you too.
All right. Follow me.
No, not here. Let us take this home.
You crazy wench.
I have taken off all the precious silk meant for nobility.
Now, will you stoop to pick up my sin from the ground and punish me?
How can Minister of Personnel...
use The Laws of Morality to threaten a woman...
and try to take advantage of her?
Is it really appropriate for someone of your stature...
to sit in the halls of government and discuss politics?
You lunatic!
You must have a death wish, do you not?
I shall punish you now!
How dare you!
The audacity of one such as you!
My lord, you will be in trouble. Please put away your sword.
My goodness.
Your Royal Highness.
"Your Royal Highness?"
Move out of my way!
I do not even know where to begin.
When are you going to stop being so reckless?
- No, that is because I... - Why can you never wait?
When you are hurt or in any danger, you are supposed to stop and wait!
You should have called for help!
You should have waited until I could save you!
Why should I... My lord. No.
Why should I wait for Your Highness?
Why should you be the one to solve my problems?
Because it is not just about you!
Do you really think this is just about you?
I told you, you look just like my wife.
And that is why you wanted me to wear this outfit?
Is that what this was all about?
Using reward as your excuse,
Were you playing dress-up so I could look like your wife...
No.
Were you playing dress-up, using me as the Crown Princess' substitute?
What?
How dare you continue to speak so recklessly?
That is why you are so angry, is it not?
Because someone as lowly as myself...
looks like the Crown Princess.
Because I was humiliated with her face.
Are I not right?
Fine. You are right. Got it?
Since you know, do not get in danger with that face.
Do not be humiliated or stand out!
I am well aware that you are not my wife.
I will not be confused or shaken by it again.
So take this and never let me see you again.
What do you think you are doing?
It is mine now, is it not?
So I will do whatever I want with it.
Stop. That is an order!
What do you think you are doing?
You dare toss the Crown Prince's gift to the ground.
It is treason and an act of disloyalty.
Your Highness, will you let this traitor go unpunished?
Let go of the sword.
If you interfere, this will only escalate.
Please.
Please stop.
This blood is on you.
Your Highness.
I am being framed!
This was all orchestrated by the Left State Councilor.
He sent his own daughter to bring me down.
It was part of Left State Councilor's plan.
The Left State Councilor's daughter?
I see.
And what did she say?
She asked me to make her Crown Princess...
Grand Prince Je Un becomes Crown Prince.
She claimed she was the one who assassinated His Royal Highness.
And that His Royal Highness would never return.
Who else have you told this to?
I have never told anyone in such detail.
Then keep your mouth shut.
Do not speak of Grand Prince Je Un...
or the Left State Councilor's daughter again.
That is, if you want to live.
That stings.
Goodness.
My lord.
The wound on your neck does not seem too deep,
but the wound in your heart does.
I am fine.
My greed got the better of myself.
I tried to carry a burden far too heavy for myself,
so of course I buckled under the weight.
One silk dress and a pair of flower shoes...
How could that be too heavy a burden to bear?
He brought you down.
That is not true.
No wonder. I was happy, which does not suit me.
These were not suitable for me.
Flower shoes? Darn them.
They only got me scrapes.
Then...
these should be fine, right?
I can put them on myself.
I bought these straw sandals for you in a hurry on my way.
It is not that the flower shoes did not suit you.
Why did you threaten Chief Royal Secretary only?
You know the culprit, do you not?
Because I have figured out why.
That will be all for today. You are dismissed.
I am surrounded by disloyal subjects only.
I should be going as well.
It seems my lady has been injured.
With their words or their actions,
they all held the daggers back then.
Sometimes, a simple touch or a certain look...
can be the most sincere answer.
My desire for revenge also began with love.
If I trample Grand Prince Je Un's feelings just to get my own revenge,
I would only be causing him more pain.
But...
Rather than finding the source of the poison,
would it not be faster to find proof...
that the Left State Councilor's daughter tried to harm you?
It is never too late for revenge.
And the right path is more important than the fast one.
Is that not going too far?
Your Highness, please calm down first.
Let us head back to the palace.
Come on, how do you expect him to calm down that feeling so easily?
That feeling?
I am sure you feel awful. You were publicly shamed like that.
That is not what he is talking about.
No, he is right.
Se Dol, for once, you have said something sensible.
- Really? - I am absolutely livid right now.
I suppose I will never see her again.
So if I do not do it now, I will never get to settle it.
That is why I am going. To settle this anger.
Let us go. We have administered first aid,
so now we need to get you treated.
Change into these clothes.
What is this? You are still here, Your Highness?
Those clothes you have on.
That bright blue is terrible on you.
You are the "autumn leaf" color type.
Anyway, this color will suit you better.
Go on and get changed.
You followed us because of her clothes?
I did not "follow" you.
I was just passing by and saw you, so I stopped.
And then I realized something.
My feelings.
All right.
Thank you for this.
All right, I am all ears.
Okay, so tell me. What feelings are you talking about?
I feel so wronged.
As they say, the guilty party gets mad.
Fine.
So why do you feel so wronged, Your Royal Highness?
I never played dress-up, using you as Crown Princess' substitute.
I am infuriated to be misjudged...
over feelings I do not even have.
You should not be saying that.
At a time like this,
you should apologize.
You should admit you were wrong.
Are you telling me, the Crown Prince, to apologize?
Beg for forgiveness?
To a common peddler like you?
If you have done something wrong, you should apologize.
How can you not see that pride is more shameful than modesty?
There are no subjects who would love a royal family...
that does not care for its people.
Therefore, you must fear your people.
Love them first.
Do not just reign over them.
Rule them with reason and justice.
Since you have nothing more to say, I will take my leave.
The Four Pillars Letter has been sent.
In three months, you will be the new Crown Princess.
- What do you think you are doing? - And just who are you?
Who in the world are you?
I came to see you one last time,
so why do you keep me rooted?
Why are you putting down roots in my heart all over again?
When you think of it, the swallow does more than repay debts.
It rewards Heungbu...
and punishes Nolbu.
It is a shrewd merchant who never makes a loss.
That darn swallow must have made some kind of mistake.
With a heart as kind as mine,
there is no way I am the bad guy here.
Me, the oh-so-precious Crown Prince.
It is gone.
- For my body to be switched... - Where did it go?
With this lowly peddler...
This is divine punishment!
(Moon River)
Has His Highness not been really strange lately?
My name is Lee Gang Doo, Your Royal Highness.
What in the world is going on?
How about we do it again like we did that day?
You mean, a kiss?
If the Left State Councilor sees her face...
that resembles the late Crown Princess...
What is to become of her?
He would kill her.
(Moon River)