=Live or Love?=
=Live or Love=
=Episode 5=
Miss Fang.
After I finish the task,
you stay here.
Stay here forever.
(Your game mission has failed.)
(Failed to exit.)
You are now my ally.
No one can bully you.
(Miss Fang should dress more nicely.)
(After all, clothes make the man.)
Sorry.
I'd like to speak to her directly.
Don't be afraid.
At least,
you have me by your side.
If destined, we will meet again.
(Asking for help won't work.)
(To leave the game,)
(I must complete the task.)
(That means)
(one of us two)
(must stay here.)
(But...)
(I am deceiving him now.)
(Is this fair?)
Miss Fang.
How much longer do you need?
Let's talk about the contract.
The contract?
We cooperate to complete the game task
for a win-win situation.
Since we can't contact the outside,
let's follow the rules.
You help me become the CEO,
and I'll double Ju'an's profits.
This way, we can both pass the game.
(My mission is to defeat you.)
(I won't help you.)
The marriage is just for the game.
After returning to reality,
we can't interfere
with each other's work and life.
After all, once we're out,
we'll compete for agency rights.
Address ugly words openly.
After going out, we are strangers.
I won't give up any benefit.
Miss Fang, please don't
play the emotional card.
Don't worry.
About businesses,
I never play the emotional card.
That's good.
I saw how emotional you were
at the wedding yesterday.
I was afraid you'd overthink it.
Overthink?
There were so many people yesterday.
You married me with a stern face.
Don't I have any pride?
So, I could only say something
just to cheer you up.
Miss Fang,
please don't take it personally.
We're just temporary partners.
Not friends.
I was just thinking,
you comforted me so sincerely yesterday.
It seems rather unkind
to compete with you later.
Luckily, you reminded me in time.
We are always competitors.
No need to hold back.
Okay.
If you are my opponent,
I will not hold back.
Alright.
It's a deal.
I have two more conditions to add.
First.
I must be involved in
all of your company's business.
Second. I sleep on the bed
on Monday, Wednesday, and Friday.
You, on Tuesday, Thursday,
and Saturday. Strictly follow it.
Now,
hurry up and wash up,
then drive me to the company.
No problem.
Hello, Luo.
Schedule a time with Luo Yan.
Right.
For private matter.
No.
I know I'm already married.
Fang Lili.
(Men's restroom)
You've blocked me this far.
Don't you have any sense of shame?
No.
I'm not blocking you.
I...
Fang Lili.
Let me make it clear.
You've already married
the rubbish An Yushen.
Whether it's out of anger
or self-abandonment,
frankly, you two losers
are well-matched.
Please have some self-awareness.
Go back and live with that rubbish.
Don't try to hit on me again.
Seeing your face
only makes me feel disgusted.
Let me also make it clearer.
First.
I really like my face.
What exactly makes you disgusted?
Please elaborate.
Second.
An Yushen is not a rubbish.
He just needs some time
to become the CEO of Ju'an.
Don't look down on him.
You can't even compare to him.
Third.
I have no personal feelings for you.
Only for mutual interests.
What? Exchange of interests?
I will stay close to An Yushen,
helping you become the CEO.
Fang Lili.
Even if you degrade yourself like this,
I won't fall for you.
I will make you believe what I say.
What's up?
Is my face that revolting?
What?
Let's start.
Our Longxing Supermarket
has some operational issues these days
needs to be solved.
Yushen,
and Luo Yan.
Which one of you
wants to take charge of it?
Young An has just recently
shown his skills in futures investment.
I believe
that for him,
this matter
is just a piece of cake.
Longxing Supermarket
loses money for years
with complicated stuff.
It's a bit inappropriate.
Ms. Sun.
We should give young people a chance.
You beat a retreat at the beginning.
Are you doubting
Young An's ability?
Shi Yu,
why not leave the good opportunity
for Mr. Luo?
I also want to see
his abilities.
(It sounds like)
(the project is small but challenging.)
(Isn't it the perfect obstacle?)
Everyone,
I don't understand business,
but I know,
one in the high place must stand
through ability to last long.
Yushen can lead by example.
That's right.
As a member of the company,
we should rise to the challenge.
I'd like to take over
Longxing Supermarket
and turn losses into profit
within a month.
Great.
Longxing Market
will be Yushen's project.
Additionally,
let me emphasize,
from now on,
no unrelated persons can
attend the internal meetings.
Fang Lili.
Please remember it.
Right.
What she is here for?
Not knowing her position.
She dragged down the Fang Group.
Such a jinx.
Don't bring bad luck to Ju'an.
In fact, I...
Actually, Lili is my assistant.
All my future projects
will be co-managed with her.
Today, I brought her here
to formally introduce her to you.
Besides,
she is my wife.
When speaking,
please make clear your own position.
I don't want to hear any
disrespectful word about her.
((What's going on with him?)
(Why is he trying to act cool?)
(Please be colder towards me.)
(You make me really despicable.)
(Ju'an Group)
You've realized there are pitfalls
in the project,
but you still let me do it.
I was thinking...
You were thinking,
since we want to quickly
establish ourselves in Ju'an,
why not tackle a tough problem?
Only this way can we prove our strength.
Exactly.
Great minds think alike.
Did you catch a cold
from kicking the covers off last night?
Take it.
(Cold tablets)
(Hey.)
(Why do you care about me?)
(Does it have to be this way?)
(Seasonal cold tablets)
You sleep in the bed today.
I'll sleep on the couch.
(Enough!)
(Don't say anything more.)
(Ju'an Group)
That night,
you dropped something.
Thanks.
I return your things back.
Isn't there any reward?
Drink together tonight?
Boss Yin.
Your car is blocking others.
Feng Zhixing!
Such temper.
So cute.
Excuse me,
where is your person in charge?
Another goal scored!
Scored!
Scored again!
Excuse me.
The ball is in!
I told you one would go in today, right?
Yes!
Excuse me,
where is your person in charge?
Who are you?
An Yushen from the Ju'an Group.
(Longxing Supermarket)
Sorry.
Please wait.
(Bringing Joy to the City)
Hey.
Long time no see.
I can hardly recognize you.
Wow, I didn't expect
that you two got married.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Let's plan another diving day sometime.
Remember the last time?
You threw up all the way on the boat
and didn't get in the water.
Cousin,
let's chat some other day.
Today I'm here
is mainly to reorganize Longxing.
Just downstairs,
firstly,
there's no customer.
Secondly,
there's no stuff working.
Encountered any difficulties?
Each supermarket
has its own business philosophy.
Indeed, service is not
Longxing's strong suit.
But we do achieve annual sales targets.
Don't we?
So, I'm really curious.
How did you meet the sales goal?
Show me the financial report,
purchase orders,
and all the accounts.
Let me take a look.
I'll cooperate with you.
No problem at all.
But,
I'm on leave today.
My accountant and assistant
are also on leave.
How about this?
Please wait
until we return.
(Really tricky indeed.)
(It's not a waste effort.)
You're getting smarter.
This mess of Longxing
is now passed on to Yushen.
Mr. An,
it's company business.
I didn't mean that.
Is that so?
However,
if he can resurrect Longxing,
I'll really reconsider this man.
(From Lin Lu)
(Mr. Zheng, from Shanyuan Group,)
(do you want to meet and talk?)
Mr. Zheng has arrived.
Come with me.
Mr. Zheng.
I've trying to meet you for long.
I didn't expect you
available today.
Sit down.
During the previous talks,
I always felt
that you didn't seem very interested.
But this time,
you're so proactive.
I heard
that the eldest son of the Ju'an family,
An Yushen,
has been performing well recently.
Mr. Luo,
feeling some pressure, huh?
I cooperate with you
because of your capabilities.
Nothing else.
Mr. Zheng,
please have some tea.
Miss Lin.
Aren't you from the CEO's office?
Why are you so eager
to assist Mr. Luo with the project?
Could it be that you two...
Lin is helping me
under Mr. An's order.
Totally for business.
Well.
I see.
About the cooperation,
there's no need to rush.
Let's schedule
a meal the day
after tomorrow.
That day,
don't you mind bringing Miss Lin
along together?
I don't mind.
Okay.
It's a deal then.
Young An. The meal's here.
Young An?
Young An.
Time to eat.
Hasn't he returned?
He has gone on annual leave.
Won't return.
Zhang Chao is really showing his power.
A dragon can't quell the local snake.
He is determined to wear me down.
So what do we do now?
Is it a bad choice
taking over Longxing?
Let's leave now.
Okay.
Why are you so quiet?
In a small matter like this,
shouldn't you have numerous ideas
to deal with Zhang Chao?
(Living with such low customer traffic.)
(He must be making Ju'an's money.)
I don't have the authority
to see Longxing's data.
Any idea?
Speak directly.
The customer traffic is so low,
but it still operates normally.
There's only one possibility.
Zhang Chao is making money off Ju'an.
He buys low
and quotes high to the group.
He makes a profit by doing nothing.
He is a relative of the An family.
Hard to handle.
An Xiangyang sent me here
to obtain evidence.
Logically, it makes sense.
How do you plan to get the evidence?
Zhang Chao must have the real accounts.
But how to find them...
Let me think about it.
(Don't worry.)
(I will definitely remind Zhang Chao)
(to destroy the accounts today.)
Then take your time.
Anyway, I have nothing to do here.
I'll ask Yin Zhiluo about it.
Thanks.
No problem.
(Longxing Supermarket)
Hello, Zhang Chao.
I'm Fang Lili.
Hi.
Why are you here?
Miss Fang.
What can I do for you?
Get in.
Zhang Chao.
To cut to the chase.
I know we're not familiar.
But what I'm about to say,
I hope you'll listen to seriously.
Not familiar?
Lili.
Haven't you forgotten
about what happened between us?
What happened between us?
Fine.
Look.
Why doesn't Luo Yan like me?
Luo Yan doesn't like you,
but I like you.
Good.
(Oh, no).
(How dramatic is this backstory?)
Oh my, Lili.
You didn't agree last time.
But it's okay.
Even if you got married,
we can still continue our relation.
An Yushen, that loser.
Even if he finds out,
he wouldn't dare to do anything.
Aren't I
better than him?
Zhang Chao,
you bad guy.
Don't you know what self-awareness is?
Let me summarize for you.
From your looks to abilities,
your EQ to IQ,
and forehead to feet,
all can't compare
to a leg hair of An Yushen.
- You...
- Besides,
in the video,
it's clearly you are
taking advantage of me while I'm drunk.
How dare you to bring this up?
What's there to brag about?
This is your criminal record.
If I sue you for harassment,
how will you stay in Ju'an?
Fang Lili.
Don't forget who you really are
just because you're in the An Family.
(Item purchased)
(Obedience charm)
Don't cooperate when I speak nicely.
Wild pig can't stomach fine grains.
Tell me,
where are the account books?
Really cheated on the purchase price.
So much money.
(Forget it.)
(It's just a game.)
(It's not real.)
(Put it back.)
You are here too.
Found the accounts?
I...
Well done.
I had planned to see him too.
But you were faster.
As expected of Miss Fang.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I've sent materials to Mr. An.
Thanks for helping me,
Miss Fang.
Cooperation.
No need to thank me.
It's stuffy here.
I'll go up first.
Take your time.
Anyway, I have nothing to do here.
I'll ask Yin Zhiluo about it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Feng,
drive here.
Young An.
At this time,
why is meeting Zhang Chao privately?
Don't rush.
Follow her.
Young An.
Miss Fang is helping you find evidence.
She's really nice to you.
Where is Zhang Chao?
He's in the car.
Seems asleep.
Take him to the hospital for a check-up.
Avoid extra problems.
Got it.
Hello?
How's it going?
Young An.
I've had him checked.
Nothing wrong.
However,
he seems to have forgotten
what happened today.
Copy his dashcam recordings for me.
I want to know exactly what they said.
Okay.
(Ju'an Group)
Everyone must have heard
about the Longxing issue?
Zhang Chao
has been overreporting costs
and embezzling funds for years.
Now he has been expelled from the group
and will never to be rehired.
Yushen.
You've done well this time.
Since
the root has been eliminated,
now,
Longxing's business
will be left in Yushen's charge.
Work hard.
When I started out,
I also worked on supermarket business.
Gradually, I am here.
Thank you.
I won't let you down.
Mr. Sun, come here.
(Is this how you proof?)
(Let me explain.)
(Feng Zhixing)
(Young An. I've sent you the recording.)
Zhang Chao.
You bad guy.
Don't you know what self-awareness is?
Let me summarize for you.
From your looks to abilities,
your EQ to IQ, and forehead to feet,
all can't compare
to a leg hair of Yushen.
Besides,
in the video, it's clear that you...
Well.
Meeting's over.
Honey,
wait for me, let's go together.
Have me walk you down the stairs?
I don't mind the thing this morning.
Get in my car, no fuss.
Just a meal.
Mrs. Yin.
Let me ask for leave from Young An.
Okay?
What leave?
I'll tell Fang Lili.
Just wait.
Feng Zhixing!
Fine.
I like such challenging game.
See Feng Zhixing again?
Not only him,
I also look for you.
It's spread all around
that you protect your husband so well.
Other men aren't worth a hair
on your husband's leg.
How did you fall so low?
Stop it.
Want to drink?
I'll treat.
An Yushen surprisingly made a comeback.
Mr. Zheng's project
must be in my hands.
He has been contacting me
every night these days.
Okay.
I see.
You go up first.
Okay.
Mr. Zheng,
this toast is for you.
Mr. Luo.
Today,
it's just a casual meal.
No need to be so formal.
Mr. Zheng,
we should have a drink, right?
Of course, Miss Lin.
Cheers.
Miss Lin.
You're really straightforward.
You, too. Mr. Zheng.
Let's not beat around the bush.
About the cooperation,
why don't we just settle it today?
Mr. Zheng.
Well, regarding the contract,
there's no rush.
There are many details
need to be further discussed.
Mr. Zheng,
as long as you cooperate,
the details are no big deal.
All trifles.
Well then.
Let's now
have a good discussion
about these trifles.
Let's start
with
the first item.
Look,
the first item...
Here,
it's a bit...
Luo Yan!
What are you doing!
Mr. Zheng,
I don't mind bringing her to dinner.
But I mind you doing other things.
You!
Luo Yan!
You'll regret this!
Regret?
You're not worthy.
♪Whenever it starts♪
♪We both like to disguise♪
♪Even the way of hugging♪
♪Prefer gentle even more♪
♪Subconsciously want
the atmosphere right♪
♪Not falling into a deadlock♪
♪The stubbornness at a certain moment♪
♪I let go of my reason♪
♪Repeatedly wanting to try♪
♪To retain and to restrain♪
♪Passing through my world♪
What's up?
Lin Lu,
why glare at me?
Go tell on me to your parents.
You really love reporting.
Oh, wait.
I forgot you don't
have parents anymore.
You're now just a dog
adopted by the An family.
No one cares about you.
Right?
♪Want to find more problems, but♪
Luo Yan!
You just wait.
♪Perhaps I'm immature♪
♪Perhaps I'm too presumptuous♪
♪Keep still from now on♪
♪Stay in the original place, both of us♪
You've drunk?
Not asleep yet?
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Although you praised my leg hair today,
I thought about it carefully
after I got home.
Miss Fang.
Your task
is not doubling Ju'an's profit, is it?
You encouraged me
to take over this mess of Longxing,
but slacked off
on handling the project.
Although you obtained the evidence,
why use an item to make
Zhang Chao lose his memory?
Are you afraid I'll find something?
You went to see Zhang Chao
really to help me?
What else could it be?
To bring down Ju'an
and take revenge.
According to the system setting,
Fang Lili was rejected by Luo Yan.
Deceived by the An family,
she lost her dowry.
This indirectly led to her
father's death.
With such a miserable history,
how else could this story unfold,
if not for the revenge?
That's ridiculous.
You don't need to pretend.
I said today,
if you are my opponent,
I will not be lenient.
Did you listen to me?
I don't want revenge.
Is that so?
Then prove it to me.
♪I forgot the time and my promises♪
♪How far I've gone,
falling into the trap of love♪
♪In dreams, I still feel sorry for you♪
♪I can't help missing you♪
♪My life got dull without you♪
♪I want to snuggle in your tenderness♪
♪I mistakenly think that my stubbornness
can win back everything.♪
♪I don't dare to reminisce♪
♪For fear that tears fill my eyes♪
♪I can't return to the past
and embrace you♪
♪It's already in vain♪
♪I stood alone under the street light♪
♪I can't find the courage to love♪
♪I hope♪
♪to give up the freedom to escape♪
♪I hope to give up the freedom
to escape♪