=Live or Love?=
=Episode 7=
Since when do you have a sister
named Yin Zhili?
Honey,
did you lose your memory?
She's your childhood friend.
She went abroad later on.
Then why does she call An Yushen
"Yushen"?
She's secretly in love with him.
She loves him secretly?
Love me secretly?
You only told me that she would help me,
never mentioned the emotional plot.
(Plot twists)
(will be unlocked by players.)
Well...
Why does she like me secretly?
What's our character backstory?
No one dared to play with her
since she was young.
As for An Yushen,
no one wanted to play with him.
So they played together.
Later, she swore to marry no one
but An Yushen.
After she went abroad,
I guess the two of them lost contact.
Why didn't anyone dare
to play with her as a child?
(Yin Zhili.)
(Hot-tempered,)
(wayward,)
(with mild personality disorder)
(and manic depression.)
(At age eight,)
(she fought fiercely)
(with her sister)
(Yin Zhiluo,)
(causing her arm breaking on the spot)
(and staying hospital for three months.)
An eight-year-old child,
broke your arm into hospital,
and even needed eight stitches.
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
Forget it. It's partially my fault.
At a young age, a fortune-teller said
I was destined to bring ruin
while my sister would be
the hope of our family.
Since then, my dad started pushing her.
However, he pushed her so hard
that she couldn't stand.
Her personality becomes
more and more stubborn.
My task doesn't include getting her,
right?
But An Yushen
doesn't like her, right?
A romantic storyline is troublesome.
Right now, I'm seeking stability.
A wise man does not fall in love.
As the saying goes,
a wise man does not fall in love.
You try to persuade our sister,
not to waste her future
on a married man.
Does it matter
that much to you?
When I tipped you off this morning,
you say you didn't like An Yushen.
True.
But we've got married.
I don't want any trouble.
Really?
Mrs. Yin.
Madam.
Dinner is ready downstairs.
Young An invited you down.
How long have you been there?
I have to go.
When did you change your clothes?
Aren't you cold?
Today's family meal,
firstly,
to celebrate Xiaoli's
long-term cooperation
with Longxing.
Secondly, it's
to welcome her back China.
Feel free to visit us more often.
Actually, besides supplying goods,
I also want to discuss
a deeper collaboration.
If the cosmetics brand I manage abroad
could enter your stores,
I believe,
for both of our companies,
it would be beneficial.
That's great.
If Miss Yin is interested
in collaborating,
I will upgrade Longxing
to cater more
to high-end consumers.
Yushen,
why call me Miss Yin again?
Don't just talk.
Have some dessert.
I'm cutting out sugar.
Please move it away.
Xiaoli
liked following Yushen since young.
But now you've all grown up.
In the blink of an eye,
Yushen is already married.
This is Lili.
You've met, right?
She is now the daughter-in-law
of our An family.
Thank you, Miss Yin,
for your timely help.
I toast to you.
Miss Fang.
What month is it now?
Why do you dress like in summer?
Women doesn't dress
according to the season.
Miss Yin's summer dress
is also very beautiful.
Sorry.
I've just returned.
Don't notice the weather.
The humidity in Jincheng is so heavy.
Be careful of shoulder inflammation.
That's true.
If I fall ill,
I'd have to trouble Yushen
to take care of me.
Lili.
Shall I get you a coat?
Sure.
Miss Fang.
You've used this trick
on Luo Yan before, haven't you?
Have some dessert.
This is delicious.
I've said,
I'm cutting out sugar.
I'm full, I'll go first.
(What is her personality set?)
(Easy to invite, hard to get rid of.)
(That's what's happening now.)
To be honest,
is Yin Zhili prettier or am I?
I'm asking you, Aotian.
(I am just an artificial intelligence.)
(I haven't offended anyone.)
It must be me.
He must like someone like me.
Fang Li!
(Part 3 Primary Data Analysis)
After the resent adjustments,
our first goal
of stop losing money has been achieved.
With Qixi Festival approaching,
we will take this opportunity
to host an ultra-low discount
shopping festival
to attract consumers.
On that day, we aim
to achieve a 60 percent
increase in sales.
Great.
In just over ten days, Young An
has resolved the mall's chronic issues.
I believe
the event will be a success.
Sixty percent?
The best-performing store
under An's brand
only saw a 30 percent increase
this New Year's Day.
You lack management experience.
Don't talk nonsense.
Mr. Guo,
young people having ideas
is a good thing.
The young calf is not afraid of tigers.
Just for this,
we should give him a thumb-up.
However, Young An,
your approach
has been tried before
with little success.
Nowadays,
there are so many shopping festivals.
There's no innovation
to excite customers.
Mr. An,
what do you think?
Lack of innovation
can be resolved with innovation.
From a logical
and commercial perspective,
this event is worth a try.
Approve it.
Yes.
Young An.
For the Qixi Festival event,
I will prepare a proposal first.
Hello, Miss Yin?
Alright.
Then see you later.
Let's meet at the Yinxiang Mall.
No need.
I'll go find Yin Zhili.
Prepare the car.
Alright.
Wait.
I'll go by myself.
You go to Longxing
finalizing the audit report.
By the way,
me meeting Yin Zhili,
don't tell Fang Lili about it.
Young An.
Forgive my bluntness.
Honesty is crucial in a marriage.
Miss Yin is just...
Follow my lead.
Okay.
(She hasn't figured out her task.)
(My matters...)
(She'd better stay away.)
Hello, Feng.
How's everything going?
Tired, right?
I've made desserts.
I bring them to Longxing, huh?
Madam,
don't bother.
Young An...
He
went to the company for a meeting.
The company?
Grandma said he went there this morning.
Really, I'm telling the truth.
Okay.
Then I'll call him to confirm.
Madam,
he went to Yinxiang Mall
to meet Mrs. Yin.
Yin Zhili?
It's okay.
It has nothing to do with me.
I don't care.
Yushen.
I think
our collaboration will definitely
be a great success.
Hello, miss.
Can I help you?
Using the Qixi Festival event
to bring our brand into Longxing
is a good choice.
This counter
features our in-house brand,
Yin.
It emphasizes
natural organic ingredients.
All scents
are crafted by French perfumers,
nourishing yet not greasy.
I squeezed out too much.
Yushen,
give it a try too.
I'll do it myself.
Why be so formal?
Miss?
Miss!
If you keep this up,
I'll call security.
When did you arrive?
Isn't this Miss Fang?
What brings you to our Yinxiang Mall?
I'm shopping.
A coincidence.
Hello, Mrs. Yin.
Here's the thing.
This lady has been
sneaking around the counter
for long.
I see.
Go ahead with your work.
It seems Miss Fang
didn't come here for shopping.
However,
I still want to recommend
our cosmetics to you.
After all,
a woman without charm
cannot hold on to a man
just by spying.
You...
Lili.
You're late again.
I forgot to tell you.
The Qixi Festival shopping plan
is handled by Lili.
So, for details like product selection,
she wants to examine them personally.
Honey,
supporting your work
is what I should do.
The planning proposal
was made by Miss Fang?
No wonder it's so ordinary.
I think,
with Miss Fang's talent for squandering,
this collaboration
should be canceled now.
After all, a high-end brand like ours
never do causal discounts.
Please give me one day, Miss Yin.
I'll present
a plan that satisfies you.
Miss Yin, so capable a person,
you wouldn't let personal matters
affect business, right?
Alright.
Then, tomorrow,
I need your plan.
Why would I get upset
over him meeting Yin Zhili?
Even agreed
to plan the shopping festival.
It's not my task to help him.
But he just gave me a way out.
Does that mean...
What am I thinking?
Miss Fang, really impressive today.
Yin Zhili is just a code.
How could she compare to me
fighting in reality?
That's correct.
Eat a bit more.
(Wow.)
(So handsome.)
Not to your liking?
(Fang Lili,)
(stay calm.)
I'm not hungry.
You eat more.
Actually, I'm also full.
I'll be back to Longxing
to keep an eye on the auditing matters.
Where to?
I'm going back with you.
You can keep shopping here.
After all, I'm not sure if you plan
to take revenge on Ju'an.
Before that,
let's act separately.
Bye.
(Luo Yan)
Hello.
Come in.
Take a seat.
Do you drink?
No need.
Thank you.
No need to be so on guard.
The one who should be afraid is me.
After all, you tried hard to
take me down before.
Mr. Luo.
You didn't call me here
for this nonsense?
You really have changed.
More interesting.
The little girl who passed me notes
was sent by you, right?
How did you know?
You wrote me love letters for ten years.
How could I not know your handwriting?
I see.
So,
you said you'd help me defeat An Yushen.
I believe it.
(Task: Approaching Luo Yan)
(You've completed the task,)
(approaching Luo Yan.)
(Reward: 1,000 points.)
Wow.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I said that I would help you.
But you kept failing.
Given your ability,
I didn't trust you is normal.
But you're different now.
Let's cut to the chase.
In the shopping festival,
what do you want me to do?
I need you to keep assisting An Yushen.
Be a good helpmate
and help him to expand Longxing.
What?
Pigs need to be
fatten before slaughtering.
But we...
It's a directive.
No discussion.
Actually,
I don't really understand,
why you suddenly stopped
targeting An Yushen.
You know the situation of Longxing,
right?
Losing money for years,
can't even pay the salaries.
So, An Yushen mortgaged
the market land
to get cash flow.
He didn't report such a big deal
to the group.
Dad hates stuff
overstep their authority.
If this ever gets out,
do you think dad will forgive him?
By then, the store
will be back to me.
Therefore,
on the Qixi Festival event,
we don't need to do anything, do we?
Right.
Let him do his job well.
The better he manages now,
the greater my profit will be.
So,
can you take a rest on Qixi Festival?
I have other plans.
Moreover,
we'd better not meet frequently.
I understand.
(It's gotten dark.)
(She's not back.)
(No calls.)
(No replies to messages.)
(What is Fang Lili doing?)
(Could she get lost in the game?)
Young Master,
you've been here for long.
Waiting for Miss Fang?
No.
I'm admiring the moon.
Since this afternoon, Miss Fang
has locked herself in the study,
refusing distractions.
She's already back?
Are you writing a novel?
So dedicated?
I'm working on the Qixi Festival plan.
I thought you just said it casually.
Why so diligent?
(How should I put it?)
(It seems like
I'm helping Luo Yan help you.)
(It's a bit complicated.)
Don't work too hard.
Have some food.
Yin Zhili made it.
It's quite tasty.
You like her cooking?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Then you eat it all.
Take it away.
Miss Fang,
you dislike Yin Zhili that much?
Is it because...
No.
She to me...
She's my loyal partner.
You wanna revenge on Ju'an.
So,
my assistant is your enemy.
If you don't trust me, make it yourself.
Or, go find
your childhood assistant for help.
You wrote all these by yourself?
So diligent.
It's very likely a smoke bomb.
I...
I didn't say anything.
Okay, understood.
(Feng Zhixing)
Hello,
Young An.
Do I need to send your plan
to Miss Yin first?
No need.
Use Fang Lili's plan tomorrow.
It is better.
By the way, help me check
if it will rain on Qixi.
Okay, one moment.
Yes.
There will be rain.
I see.
She really made great efforts.
Young Master.
Please,
prepare some snacks to Lili.
Besides,
it's been cold lately.
Get her a blanket.
Okay. Sir.
You are so kind to madam.
By the way, sir,
she made you a cake.
Really taking hours.
It's in the kitchen.
I see.
You can go.
Feng Zhixing?
Have a seat here.
Thank you.
Hey, boy.
Mrs. Yin?
What are you doing here?
Don't take the bus.
I'll drive you home.
No, it's not necessary.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Where is your home?
I'll take you home.
Really don't need bothering.
Go ahead.
Not a big deal.
Afraid I'll memorize your address
and disturb you at night?
Mrs. Yin.
I have something to say.
I don't know why you
treat me like this.
Perhaps it's fun for you.
But,
it's caused me great trouble.
Trouble?
We're not the same kind of people.
I'm just an ordinary worker.
It's hard enough to make ends meet.
After work,
I just want to be alone.
I don't have the time to entertain you
for fun.
I'm sorry.
Let me explain.
I was just passing by.
I saw you helping the elderly,
so I offered to take you home.
If you find it offensive,
you can get off now.
I'll give you one second.
Time's up. Get out now.
(YIN Youth Edition
product stock estimate: 3,000 sets)
That's my proposal on sales.
I also prepared a little surprise.
Wait a minute.
That page.
Show me again.
A stock quantity of 3,000 sets
is a bit low.
According to our market research,
within the supermarket's reach,
less than 20,000 young people
have purchasing power.
And only 2,000 are willing to
participate in the event.
Considering the 40 percent
of conversion rate,
3,000 sets
are certainly enough.
Miss Fang.
Isn't that too idealistic?
Does the market exactly
follow your mathematical mode?
My data has never been wrong.
Miss Yin, you can rest assured.
Don't you forget
how you dragged down the Fang Group?
Yushen,
you've noticed
the problem, right?
Honey,
there's no problem, right?
Miss Yin's words make sense.
Lili lacks experience in this regard.
Miss Fang.
Learning to do business
is not that simple.
I lack experience?
All business proposals I've done
have never gone wrong.
Since it's my task,
I will certainly complete it well.
There's no problem with the stock level.
You hang out with my sister every day.
You've done business proposals?
Miss Yin, actually...
I know.
You want to save face for Miss Yin.
But I trust my judgment.
Okay.
Then let's proceed as you suggest.
Yushen,
see you tomorrow.
(Qixi Festival, Sweet Confession)
♪Sunlit windows, gaze drifting outwards♪
Make main lights brighter.
Move that standee back.
Don't block the brand.
Okay.
♪Emotions accelerating, era intertwined♪
♪A breeze buries deep love in silence♪
♪Wishing to hold your hand to confess♪
♪Stealing glances at your profile♪
♪Quietly holding your hand to confess♪
♪Gentle breeze blows, roses bloom♪
♪Waiting silently for your message♪
♪Heart beating faster in silence♪
♪Always hoping the promise remains♪
♪I forgot the time and my promises♪
♪How far I've gone,
falling into the trap of love♪
♪In dreams, I still feel sorry for you♪
♪I can't help missing you♪
♪My life got dull without you♪
♪I want to snuggle in your tenderness♪
♪I mistakenly think that my stubbornness
can win back everything.♪
♪I don't dare to reminisce♪
♪For fear that tears fill my eyes♪
♪I can't return to the past
and embrace you♪
♪It's already in vain♪
♪I stood alone under the street light♪
♪I can't find the courage to love♪
♪I hope♪
♪to give up the freedom to escape♪
♪I hope to give up the freedom
to escape♪