=Live or Love?=
=Episode 12=
I have told you not
to cause any loss of life.
What exactly do you want?
I know.
I know what to do.
And you did something like this?
If you keep doing this,
don't come back.
Luo Yan,
I am not as smart as you
or Fang Lili.
I am the most ordinary one.
But I want to help you.
The only thing that makes me better
is that I fear nothing.
Hungry, huh?
I'll leave once done.
Very soon.
Where is Feng Zhixing?
He was frightened last time.
I've granted him leave.
Your people are a bit too weak.
That is unimportant.
Character matters most.
I have to go.
After all, you're not in a hurry.
You've not yet secured the property,
so you must be quite free.
You...
How could that be?
Fang Lili said
An Yushen buried those
cultural relics himself.
The workers aren't stupid.
Just buried in,
the soil turned over.
Couldn't they tell?
I have already verified it.
Those indeed belong to An Liminghui.
At the time,
if you could be smarter,
your current troubles wouldn't exist.
My fault.
So now, this land
is in An Yushen's hands.
What should we do?
Mr. Shi,
you take a break first.
Fang Lili said she has a way.
I'll leave it to her to handle.
Fine.
I want to see Yin Zhiluo.
I'm sorry.
She is not in.
How about
you come in and sit down?
Oh?
(Fang Lili)
I heard you fainted from fear.
Let me calm your nerves.
No drinking.
I have to go to work tomorrow.
(Fang Lili)
Hello?
Hello? Lili?
It was my driver.
My home?
I came out for exercise.
Wait for me.
I'll be right back.
Honey,
how did you get here?
You exercised in this outfit?
I went to dance.
Dance?
What kind of dance?
Pole dance.
Pole dance?
With whom?
With...
No, I really went dancing.
I've been very stressed.
My sister left.
My dad tracks my performance.
I...
I dance
to relieve stress.
Alright then.
I believe whatever you say.
Want some help with KPI?
Help with KPI?
Your family got this land
a few years ago.
It's adjacent
to the former glass factory site.
Turn it into a cemetery?
No need to worry about the plan.
Your dad will like it.
Fang Lili, have you gone mad?
A cemetery is a tough task.
For obtaining land
development privileges,
all points were deducted.
Young An,
I'm sorry.
I am late.
Didn't I give you the day off today?
Did you forget?
Where to?
I will
go home.
Why do you seem so distracted?
Are you in love?
I am not.
I...
Nothing.
All good.
Young An,
a few investors want to see you
and withdraw investments.
What to do? Shall we meet?
Withdraw investments?
(Ju'an Group)
How could you keep it secret from us?
They're just scamming for money.
Even for a luxurious residential area
near a graveyard,
there won't be a single buyer.
Pay us the money back!
Let's go.
How did you come up with
building a cemetery
by the residential area?
Such a sneaky trick.
I like it.
I learned a lot
from you.
After spending so much time with you,
I've learned all kinds of tactics.
What to do now?
We're planning a housing development.
They got a cemetery nearby.
Who's so malicious?
It's Yinxiang Group's land.
Of course, it's Yin Zhiluo.
She...
It's her.
But such tactics
are beyond her.
If you ask,
you have to ask Fang Lili.
She is behind this?
Young An,
what's happening between you both?
Maybe you should go talk to her.
Don't make it such a big deal.
Business is business.
At this moment,
we need to stay rational.
(CEO Office)
When did you crave for sweets?
Miss Fang,
you learn underhanded tricks quite fast.
Well,
is that against the rules?
Building residential area is fine.
Think carefully.
Perhaps,
we'll collaborate.
Buy a house and get a free burial space.
Open the window and honor ancestors.
Thank you for being so considerate.
You're welcome.
What?
Can't I talk a bit more
with my wife?
Who's your wife?
You're quite immersed.
Is the divorce agreement finalized?
Young An,
what're you talking about?
You're not blaming others
for bad luck, right?
I discussed domestic matters with Lili.
How does it concern you?
Sorry.
Fang Lili
is now a member of our department.
I'm taking her to a meeting.
Excuse me.
This member of your department
is a member of our family.
Please wait a moment.
Be careful.
Young An.
Let me tell you this.
Even I lose all money on this project,
I'll ensure Luo Yan's total defeat
and make Fang Lili feel ashamed.
Didn't you just say
we should stay rational?
Miss,
Young An is here.
An Yushen?
What's he here for?
I...
I'm going to the restroom.
An Yushen,
why are you here now?
I'm here to discuss partnership.
Ms. Yin, I heard you have
recently taken an interest
in real estate.
So I want to ask you
if you are interested
in joining me.
About real estate,
I only do that for my dad.
I don't have much ambition.
Let's skip this.
Let's talk about you and Lili.
Are you two fighting again?
Do you want me
to help you two make up?
Luo,
I just wanted to ask for your advice.
Spouses shouldn't
harbor overnight grudges.
Lili and I had a fight.
If it leads you
to developing this good land
into a cemetery,
don't you think it's a pity?
Since you already know,
I won't beat around the bush.
The cemetery development
is something
I have considered thoroughly.
Setting that aside,
I've already promised Lili.
If you want to cooperate,
fine.
Make up with Lili.
If she is okay with it,
I'll agree.
Luo,
you are Lili's friend,
and also my friend.
And I would
do everything for my friends.
I heard Yinxiang has encountered
financial issues.
If you're willing,
I can finance the purchase of this land,
in cash,
paid in full at one time.
I won't make you wait.
Yinxiang has financial issues.
How do you know?
I heard about it.
Luo,
I'm doing this for you.
Hello.
What's happening with the bank?
When were you told?
What is the specific reason?
Risk assessment?
How did they know?
Alright.
I understand.
Hey.
Answer it.
Hello?
Where are you?
How come you vanished once we got here?
I'm downstairs.
Come down quickly.
I...
Vanished once you got here?
Are you hiding from me?
No,
I didn't.
Feng Zhixing,
what to hide from?
We're all adults.
Let's forget what happened last night.
It's not a big deal.
Just like that?
So what?
Do you
want me to take responsibility for you?
No need.
Absolutely not.
I'll leave now.
About what happened yesterday,
sorry.
No need for apologies.
No one is at a loss.
Okay.
Just go.
Still here?
To deal with me,
so hardworking.
(2. Productions and Service)
(Click and add a title)
(Cemetery Development Plan)
Data shows
today is the player Fang Li's birthday.
System rewards five hundred points.
Being trapped here so long,
I even forgot it.
Thank you, Aotian.
Wishing you a happy birthday.
(Cemetery Plan by Fang Lili)
Never mind.
The heaven wants me home.
Go home to eat.
You...
Where to?
Power's out.
I'm going home.
I just came from the front desk.
Access's dead. We can't exit.
Where are you going now?
I'll have instant noodles.
What's up?
Nothing.
You...
You're not scared, are you?
No, not at all.
I...
I want instant noodles too.
Let's go.
Should I add the spicy packet for you?
Add half of it, thank you.
You offered to make me instant noodles.
You're not drugging me, are you?
You've watched too many period dramas.
At scheming,
I'm not as good as you.
I'm simply learning from you.
Not like you, talent at full level
in plots and schemes.
Everyone has their strengths.
But what you're best at
is being
two-faced.
Otherwise,
you couldn't have been Mrs. An.
Compared to you,
I am at kindergarten level.
When you pretend to be pitiful
as An Yushen,
didn't I also get fooled by you?
It's already 12 AM.
There is no cake.
Just take instant noodles
as longevity noodles.
Happy birthday.
How do you know it's my birthday today?
I
always believe
that knowing your enemy
is the key to win.
Ever since I knew
you're competing with me
for Live or Love project,
I have investigated you.
So
you've remembered my birthday?
I remembered the two of us were
born opponents,
with incompatible
zodiac signs.
♪Photos of memories are fading♪
♪How to tell this story♪
♪Good or not♪
♪No need to dwell on it♪
Make a wish, Fang Li.
Make one, okay?
I have a kind of premonition.
You'll soon
hear the best news of the day.
(I hope)
(this dream will end soon.)
(An Hang and I)
(can both leave safely.)
♪Unloading my luggage,
I gaze alone at the vast horizon♪
What did you wish for?
I'm not telling.
♪Forgiving past loves,
cries, and laughs♪
♪The misfortune of missing you♪
Hey, Luo.
Darling.
I'm sorry.
Our group
is having some cash flow problems.
An Yushen said he can buy this land.
I really need the money right now.
I might not be able to help you.
Sorry.
I need to go.
An Hang,
this is the good news you mentioned?
The power is on.
Isn't this good news?
Fang Li,
calm down.
Eat some noodles first.
We'll continue tomorrow.
(Why are you saying sorry?)
♪Unloading my luggage,
I gaze alone at the vast horizon♪
♪Forgiving past loves,
cries, and laughs♪
♪The misfortune of missing you♪
♪Someone said that the more you invest♪
(New message to Yin Zhiluo)
♪The more bare you become♪
(Why did you say)
(just pretend it never happened?)
♪I Let go of what should be let go♪
Luo Yan,
if you want An Yushen to lose,
halt his glass factory development.
Yin Zhiluo is just short of some cash.
And Yinxiang Group has deep roots
in Jincheng.
Once they get the cash,
the money can quickly be repaid.
What's more important now is
if we can temporarily fill this gap,
Yin Zhiluo won't be forced
to sell the land to An Yushen,
and our plan can continue.
As long as the cemetery is finalized,
even if someone invests in An Yushen,
his project can only rot
in his own hands.
He'll lose all the money.
And Yin Zhiluo has already said
after the cemetery is built,
she'll surrender a share.
You will be able to get a share
of all the income.
Tell her,
I'll lend her the money
without interest.
Are you sure?
I spent the morning
investigating at the bank.
An Yushen made
a risk assessment report on Yinxiang,
urging the bank not to lend to me.
Attempting to undermine me?
I even wanted you two back together.
Awful!
Now I fully support you to divorce him.
I am determined to build this cemetery.
Calm down, Luo.
Rest assured.
I will definitely make you money.
Trust me.
Reach out to all channels
to market the cemetery.
A higher profile is best.
Three days.
Within three days,
if it can't be dealt with,
we'll all withdraw our investments.
(Mr. Li from Party A)
Young An,
how come
they can build the cemetery now?
What on earth is going on?
Feng,
in the business world,
you must remember
if there are other choices,
don't mess with women.
Make an appointment with Yin Zhiluo.
Join me to meet her later.
What?
It's nothing.
I'll make the appointment.
Ms. Yin,
Young An from Ju'an has arrived.
Hello, Ms. Yin.
Call me Ms. Yin today?
You change your tune pretty quickly.
I'm here today for business.
Ms. Yin sounds more appropriate.
I know you and Lili are good friends.
You're also a businessperson.
As long as your land is open to sell,
I have good price.
(Land Transfer Contract)
I offer two hundred million yuan
to buy this land.
Here is the drafted contract.
You can raise any concerns.
You likely won't see this price again.
You seem to be fighting with no way out.
You must stop the cemetery development
before satisfying the developers.
I'm not very good at negotiation.
But I got a friend
to discuss this with you.
You can talk it over.
I have a spa appointment.
So I'll take my leave.
Young An,
we're friends here.
You rushed to the bank
to trouble Yinxiang.
How can two hundred million yuan
mend your rift with Ms. Yin?
A flat price,
four hundred million yuan.
Fang Lili,
why don't you just rob me?
If you don't want it,
we'll convert it into a cemetery.
Then consider your real estate project
doomed.
And if you do buy,
I truly wonder
how you'll get all that money.
Young An,
doing business isn't easy.
No problem.
I can afford it.
Oh really?
One additional clause to the contract.
You must pay in full within three days.
Otherwise, pay 20 percent
of penalty for contract breach.
If you can't pay on time,
you lose.
Rest assured,
I will definitely find a way
to finish this game.
♪I forgot the time and my promises♪
♪How far I've gone,
falling into the trap of love♪
♪In dreams, I still feel sorry for you♪
♪I can't help missing you♪
♪My life got dull without you♪
♪I want to snuggle in your tenderness♪
♪I mistakenly think that my stubbornness
can win back everything.♪
♪I don't dare to reminisce♪
♪For fear that tears fill my eyes♪
♪I can't return to the past
and embrace you♪
♪It's already in vain♪
♪I stood alone under the street light♪
♪I can't find the courage to love♪
♪I hope♪
♪to give up the freedom to escape♪
♪I hope to give up the freedom
to escape♪