Our late-night delivery is here.
Sorry.
I'll go grab it.
We'll finish this later.
Promise?
You promise, right?
(It's been so long.
My heart is beating out of my chest.)
(I could never say that out loud.)
Ooh!
Omurice! Omu...
Oh my god, this looks amazing!
Hey, want some?
No, it's way too late.
Aw, come on.
It's going to be delicious.
Just one bite?
I'll feed you.
Well...
Okay, just one bite, alright?
Okay.
Here, say ah.
Stop smirking and give it to me.
Haha, alright.
Here, say ah.
Mmm.
Wow, that's delicious!
Right?
See what you would've missed?
Yeah.
Time to dig in.
Mmm! So good!
Once I finish this,
I need to get ready for work.
Do you have work tomorrow?
Yeah.
I have to leave early in the morning.
Sorry in advance if I wake you.
Take your time, no rush.
I see.
Then we should get to bed early tonight.
What?
Is that your cute way
of asking to sleep together?