Let's go.
Shiono-san.
Will you work with me?
On what?
If you break up, this will all blow over.
If a scandal breaks now, you're finished.
Whether it's Makoto
or you.
I've seen too many people ruin their own careers.
I don't want you two to follow in their footsteps.
Once you've made it, then you can...
I can't do that.
Shiono-san.
I know you're looking out for me.
I really do.
But...
Without Yuki,
I would never have been noticed.
Sigh...
Makoto needs Yuki.
The only one who can make Makoto shine...
is Yuki.
I see.
I'm sorry, Makoto.
As your manager,
maybe I didn't understand you well enough.
Shiono-san.
I'll do everything I can to support Makoto.
Please, help us.
We need your help.
Please.
(We only made it to today
because of that day...)
(Yuki made a suggestion.)
Are you ready?
(Today is our anniversary.)
(I got us cruise tickets as a gift.)
(A private cabin, of course.)
(And I have another present planned.)
Wait, how does this work?
What are you doing?
My tie...
I don't know how to tie it.
Oh, honestly...
Give it here.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hmm?
Just as I thought...
You look best in the makeup I do.
I know.
Shall we go, Princess?
Huh? I'm the princess?
We're two princes.
That's so embarrassing.
Hahaha.
To everyone watching Season 2,
thank you from the bottom of our hearts.
Thanks to you,
the team was able to come together again.
Thank you so much for making
Season 2 possible.
Wow, it's finally over.
I'm a bit sad to see it end.
Me too.
But we have some good news!
Wow!
Coming up next for Season 2...
A special episode is coming soon!
With exclusive interviews and behind-the-scenes footage,
you won't want to miss it!
Make sure to tune in!