[English subtitles are available]
[Special Lady]
[Episode 6]
The door is over there.
Don't try to escape.
-Sir.
-Take him out.
You bold pervert.
Pervert.
Stop!
I need to take a closer look at you.
Don't.
Don't. Sir.
This...
You're doomed.
I remember your face.
If you come to the academy again,
I'll report to the government.
Report to the government.
Get lost.
I...
-Get lost.
-Mr. Zhang.
-Sir.
Calm down.
Don't be angry. It's bad for your health.
I'll close the door.
Close the door.
Mr. Xiao, I suggest you
don't think too much.
After all, the Song family has its rules.
I can't marry you if you can't be admitted to Song's Academy.
If you don't want me to break off the engagement,
you'd better propose it yourself.
What do you think?
Miss Zhu.
Let's wait and see.
Mr. Xiao, we may go separate ways.
We may never see each other again.
Never see you again. Goodbye.
Yueniang, where is Mr. Xiao?
Mr. Xiao left.
I didn't leave. I'm Xiao Yu.
Is Mr. Chen looking for me?
Mr. Xiao.
My dad wants to see you.
Why did father want to see him?
How would I know that?
Mr. Song must have something important to tell me.
Important things can't be delayed.
Miss Zhu, you are hindering us.
See you, Miss Zhu.
Dad wants to see him.
What could the reason be?
That day, he accidentally broke into Women's Academy.
He is a pervert.
Why did Mr. Chen admit him to the academy?
I hired Xiao Yu as the teaching assistant of Women's Academy
because he's indeed capable.
Based on my insight into people,
Xiao Yu is a rare talented man.
Besides,
it's really tiring
for me alone to be responsible for Women's Academy.
I should find a helper.
Xiao Yu
needs to prepare for Yiyang Academy's exam next year, right?
He can study and teach at the same time.
It's an important thing.
Did you report to Dean?
I'm reporting to Dean now.
Mr. Zhang.
Any other objections?
Well.
Teaching Assistant Xiao is so young.
If he is with these female students all day,
I'm afraid people will gossip.
By that time,
how can you protect the reputation of the women in the academy?
What I see is
the female students are devoted to studying,
and Teaching Assistant Xiao is diligent.
But what Mr. Zhang sees is
Xiao Yu is a pervert,
and the reputation of the female students will be damaged.
I wonder what on earth is different.
What we see or our vision?
We both are teachers of Song's Academy.
I have the responsibility to remind you
that you should pay attention to his motivations and concerns
when using someone.
I believe Xiao Yu
will pay attention to his words and actions.
If he breaks the rules, you don't need to do anything.
I'll punish him.
In that case, it will be too late
to regret.
Let me remind you.
When you make a decision related to the students,
you should consider other teachers' opinions.
If your opinions are right,
of course I should consider them.
If they are nonsense,
there's no need to consider them.
Dean. Please make the decision.
Drink more tea in this season
to detoxify and reduce internal heat.
Dean.
Several days ago, Rongniang asked someone
to deliver some dried high-quality tea to me.
I'll ask Song Li to deliver some to you someday.
Come. Try it.
Dean. You agree to let Xiao Yu be the teaching assistant?
You should try it too.
Songzhi.
I want to hear Juntang's opinions about Women's Academy.
You go back first.
Similarly,
I will hear Songzhi's opinions
about Men's Academy.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Have a seat.
Mr. Zhang.
I wonder why Mr. Zhang
dislikes me so much.
Mr. Zhang is traditional.
Mr. Xiao, don't mind him.
I didn't expect you
to speak so highly of Xiao Yu.
I sincerely think
meeting Xiao Yu
is like finding a bosom friend.
It's easy to find a child, but hard to find a bosom friend.
Besides, with his knowledge of women's makeup,
he can help me with my makeup class.
What about his morality?
If I want to know someone's morality,
I only look at his eyes.
If his eyes are clear,
I believe he has good morality.
If his eyes are not clear,
it's hard to say.
Xiao Yu has pure eyes.
He doesn't have any evil thoughts.
I think
Xiao Yu is more than enough to be the teaching assistant of Women's Academy.
Since you're responsible for Women's Academy,
it's up to you.
Thank you. Dean.
Come in.
Father. Mr. Chen.
Mr. Xiao is here.
Okay.
Greetings, Dean.
Greetings, Mr. Chen.
I've explained to Dean.
You can continue to be the teaching assistant of Women's Academy
and help me give classes.
Okay.
Mr. Chen. Thank you for your acknowledgement of my ability.
Don't let me down.
Dean. You and Xiao Yu talk alone.
I'll take my leave then.
Okay.
Yu. How have you been?
I'm fine. Don't worry, Dean.
I asked Uncle Dai to deliver daily supplies to you.
Do you like them?
Yes.
Thank you, Dean.
I thought you would return to the capital.
I didn't expect you to stay.
More importantly, I didn't expect you to stay
with the identity of the teaching assistant of Women's Academy.
I didn't expect
to meet Mr. Chen either.
And I have gained his recognition.
It was really a coincidence.
You two are similar.
You chose each other because of a coincidence.
Also,
I'm very regretful
that I failed to be admitted this year.
I admire Song's Academy for its studying atmosphere.
I want to be the teaching assistant.
I believe with the atmosphere in Song's Academy,
I'll be admitted to Yiyang Academy next year.
Yueniang,
you went too far today.
What did I do?
Are you talking about the distraction?
You know what I'm talking about.
Why did Mr. Zhang suddenly come to Women's Academy?
Why was Mr. Xiao suddenly kicked out?
How would I know?
We grew up together.
I know very well
what kind of person you are.
Sister.
I'm not Brother Li.
It's useless to act cute in front of me.
Sister,
why are you so smart?
You're not only beautiful,
but also smart.
Other girls are no match for you.
I'm not our second brother.
It's useless to be smooth-tongued.
This time, I'll go easy on you.
If you play the same trick
with Mr. Xiao again,
I will tell our parents about everything.
I dare not do it again.
I wonder what kind of good luck he had.
You are a girl.
How can you talk so vulgarly?
Sorry.
And...
And
100 handwritten copies of Women's Moral Code.
Sister, can you take my books back to the study?
I'm going to see Dad.
Thank you. Sister.
Uncle Dai.
Who are in this room now?
Mr. Song and Young Master Li.
Uncle Dai, have a rest.
I'll deliver the tea for you.
Well. You?
Uncle Dai. It's just delivering a pot of tea.
You don't think I can do it?
But
you behave too well today.
Did something happen?
No.
I behave well every day.
Look at what you said.
Thank you, Uncle Dai. Just go.
Have a rest. Go.
-Okay.
-Go.
Yueniang.
Hush.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to deliver the tea to our father.
Then go ahead.
Brother Li, wait.
Come here.
Where are you going?
Dad asked me to do something for Xiao Yu.
Brother Li, wait.
Did Dad ask you to accompany Xiao Yu to go back to the capital?
Back to the capital?
No?
Then what did he ask you to do for Xiao Yu?
Dad agreed to let Xiao Yu be the teaching assistant of Women's Academy.
Now I'm going to prepare a room in men's dorm for him.
In men's dorm?
Yes.
Xiao Yu is the son of Dad's friend.
And he has an engagement with you.
Of course I need to prepare it carefully.
Yuniang hasn't married off.
Otherwise,
he would have been allowed to live in our house this time.
What's your plan then?
I'm trying to figure it out.
Xiao Yu has an engagement with you.
He'll be a family member in the future.
I should make arrangements carefully.
But the Song family has its rules.
No one should be an exception.
After thinking about it,
I think it's better to be impartial.
Although he'll marry you in the future,
he should follow the local customs now.
He should follow the rules of the Song family.
I won't make an exception of him.
You're right.
I'm going to the men's dorm now
to check the list
and see which room is still available.
I remember
there is a vacancy
in Zhou Ji's room.
Mr. Zhou?
Brother Li, wait.
I suddenly remember that I need to go to Teachers' Office.
I have something to do.
Help me deliver the tea.
I'm going to get the list for you.
I'm going. Wait for me. Wait for me.
Who is it?
So rude.
Hello, Mr. Zhang.
It's me.
Miss Zhu.
Women should be virtuous and decent.
You shouldn't be impatient,
mad, or ill-behaved.
Yes.
You're right.
Why are you here in such a hurry?
Brother Li asked me to help him get the list of the men's dorm.
The list of the men's dorm
is over there.
Thank you. Sir.
Li Wenshu is the son of the county magistrate.
He is wildly arrogant.
If Xiao Yu lives with him,
it's going to be interesting.
I'm not gonna make it easy for you. If you can't handle it, you'll retreat.
[No.1 Zhou Ji]
I think we came out from here this afternoon.
Mr. Xiao.
Why are you here?
Senior Song.
Dean told me this afternoon
that you'd come to me tonight.
I'm free after class.
So I've been waiting for you here.
I see.
Come.
Senior Song.
Uncle Dai led me out from the academy this afternoon.
That was when I knew
the academy and your house are connected.
My father didn't want to establish this academy back then.
Only some students came here because of his reputation.
So my father built some studies in the backyard.
But later, there were more and more students.
And the studies kept being expanded.
That was how the academy was established.
I see.
Senior Song.
Where are we going?
I'm taking you to the dorm.
Let's go.
Come.
My father always advocates thrifty.
Two students live in one room in both men's and women's dorms.
Please understand.
-Thank you
-Come.
for making arrangements for me.
I've checked the dorm list.
There is a vacancy
in Li Wenshu's room.
Live with him first.
Okay.
Come.
Mr. Xiao.
You should tidy up the room first.
Senior Song.
Are you sure this is a room for two?
I...
This
is too crowded.
Mr. Xiao.
You don't know how to make the bed?
To be honest,
when I was at home,
I barely did things like this.
Sorry.
Mr. Xiao,
let me do it.
Okay.
Senior Song.
Please make that end of the quilt at right angles.
When I sleep,
I'm used to making the quilt at right angles.
Okay.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
I'll
make myself get used to it.
By the way, Mr. Xiao,
go to the dorm supervisor later
to get a cloth,
so that you can clean the tables and chairs at ordinary times.
I should do the cleaning?
Yes.
Okay. Okay.
Senior Song.
Where...
Where is the dorm supervisor?
Turn right after you go out.
Then turn left. And you'll arrive at the destination.
Turn right after I go out. Then turn left.
Right.
Left.
Right, right, right.
Turn left after I go out. Then turn right.
Turn left.
Senior.
Junior Wenshu.
I was looking for you.
Women's Academy has a new teaching assistant.
His name is Xiao Yu.
Xiao Yu?
Teaching assistant?
Do you know each other?
No. I just heard of him.
Just now, I asked him to live in your room.
From now on, you should get along well with each other
and help each other.
My...
My room?
You are just leaving like that?
This...
Xiao Yu?
Xiao Yu.
What the hell?
Who is Xiao Yu?
Xiao Yu is from the capital.
It's not easy
to deal with someone from the capital.
So what?
Nothing to be afraid of.
I don't care at all.
Right.
How about...
How about
showing him your authority?
Okay.
-Let's go.
Young Master.
Brother, are you alright?
Mr. Xue, are you okay?
Don't you know
where the wooden basin should be put?
If anything goes wrong in my room,
it will damage my reputation if they know.
-I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I don't think Mr. Zhong and Mr. Tu did it on purpose.
I was careless.
The floor is wet.
-Let me wipe it. Otherwise, someone else will slip.
-I know there are wise people.
Like I said, it's easy to slip.
What a sweet-talker.
What's going on?
My room is a mess.
Do you remember me?
This is my room.
Mr. Xiao, why are you here?
I just became the teaching assistant of Women's Academy.
I was assigned to this room.
That's great.
What happened to your head?
I'm fine. The floor is slippery.
I fell down accidentally.
I'll wipe the floor.
Good boy.
Wait.
You don't need to wipe it.
I heard you are from the capital.
Then you should play by the rules.
That's right.
It's generous of me to share this room with you.
You should be grateful.
How about
you wipe the floor?
What did you say?
I said
you should wipe the floor.
What? Wiping the floor is not something a person from the capital should do?
You are right.
Wiping the floor is not something I should do.
Interesting.
People like you
are boring.
Calm down.
Let... Let me wipe the floor.
Mr. Xiao is not suitable for doing this kind of thing.
Get out!
You two.
Get lost!
Close the door, right?
Close the door.
Who are you
to give a command in my room?
I'm talking to you.
This is my room too.
If you don't want to live with someone from the capital,
you should get out too.
You... You're being unreasonable.
Magpies...
Magpies have built nests,
but they are occupied by turtledoves.
Well...
A woman is going to marry off, and 100 chariots will be there to welcome her.
You occupied my room.
You are shameless.
You want to have a competition of reciting poems?
I'm willing to recite one with you.
I'm a poet.
Even if you want to recite 100 poems,
it won't be a problem for me.
They agreed to have a competition of reciting poems. Why are they fighting?
That's right.
Why are they fighting?
What are they doing?
I also want to know.
What are you doing here?
Come if you dare.
Get out!
Tell me what you are thinking.
-I don't want to live with him.
I mean
how you should treat your classmates
in this academy in the future.
Shouldn't you be tolerant and united
and help each other?
Fine.
Such being the case,
now you two should work together
to tidy up this room.
From now on, if I know
you two have a fierce fight again
because of a trivial matter,
the academy
won't be partial to any of you.
Senior.
I...
want to change my room.
Mr. Xiao.
Even if you change your room, you have to share it with someone
and get along with your roommate.
Isn't there a student named Zhou Ji in the academy this year?
I want to live with him.
Zhou Ji?
Mr. Xiao.
You have been admitted to the academy too?
Mr. Zhou.
You came at the right time.
Can I live with you?
Live with me?
Zhou Ji, who's your roommate?
I'm alone.
You can let Mr. Xiao live with me.
Alone?
That's great.
This is weird.
Today, I feel so happy, even though I'm copying a book.
I wonder
what's happening between Xiao Yu and Li Wenshu.
What a pity.
I planned the show, but I can't enjoy it with my own eyes.
Wontons with fine stuffing.
Brother Li.
Why did you
bring me wontons with fine stuffing today?
Great. I'm hungry now.
-Thank you.
-Be careful.
No one is taking it from you.
If Dad sees you eating like this,
you'll be punished to copy many books.
Why are you so happy today?
Normally,
you would have given a curtsy.
Right. Brother Li.
I heard you took Xiao Yu to the dorm.
How did it go?
How are they getting along?
You were right.
After Mr. Xiao moved in,
he had a conflict with Li Wenshu.
How was the conflict?
Was it severe?
No.
I guess they have personality clashes.
But Xiao Yu
doesn't want to live with Li Wenshu anymore.
He said he wants to live with Zhou Ji.
What... What did you say?
He wants to live in Mr. Zhou's room?
Yes.
It seems they know each other.
And there happens to be
a vacancy in Junior Zhou's room.
So I let them live together.
But it seems Mr. Xiao
can't take care of himself.
He doesn't even know how to make a bed,
let alone doing the cleaning in the future.
Besides, Junior Zhou and I
helped him a lot.
Why does Xiao Yu want to live with Mr. Zhou?
If he talks about the engagement
in front of Mr. Zhou...
Let me tell you.
I'm relieved
because of Junior Zhou's help.
Xiao Yu
looks lazy,
but he's smart.
I think if he stays in the academy for a year and a half,
he'll definitely learn it.
Let me see.
Did you bite yourself badly just now?
Brother Li.
Why are there so many obstacles in life?
Like this?
Yes.
So complicated.
Put it here.
It seems it's not easy to be a servant.
Right. Mr. Xiao.
I haven't had a chance to ask you
how you came back to the academy.
Has the academy decided to recruit more students?
Or...
Well. I feel embarrassed about this.
I came back to the academy
not as a student,
but the teaching assistant of Women's Academy.
Women's Academy?
It's
a long story.
Anyway, I'm very grateful that I can
continue to stay in the academy.
Mr. Xiao.
One more thing.
I think Senior Song
seems to be very close to you.
He even said you are one of them?
No. No.
I think he was just being friendly.
I have nothing to do with the Song family.
Mr. Zhou, do you have something to say?
I know I shouldn't say too much about this.
But I'm worried that you'll be taken advantage of again in the future.
It's okay. Just say it.
Mr. Xiao.
As you know, most of the students admitted to Yiyang Academy
have a good family background,
especially Li Wenshu.
He is the son of Li Shancai, the county magistrate.
Mr. Xiao.
You must have heard a saying.
Forgive
and forget.
I can't do that.
If I forgive and forget,
I will feel uncomfortable
all over my body.
Mr. Xiao.
A gentleman does not contend with petty people.
It makes sense.
But
ignoring petty people
is something new.
Take your time.
Mr. Zhou is really tolerant.
About generosity,
I should learn more from you.
I'm flattered.
Mr. Xiao, let's read books together.
I...
I'm going to get some water.
He forgot to take the basin.
No.
Instead of being a sitting duck,
I'd better take the initiative.
I can't let that bad guy
ruin my good image in front of Mr. Zhou.
But it seems
I haven't had a chance to leave a good impression.
-Why are you here?
-Where are you going?
I'm making sure the door is firmly closed.
Well. The door just...
Brother Li, is this for me?
I'll apply it later.
You can go back first.
-I'm sleepy.
-Well.
Wait.
I left not long ago.
What happened again?
-Why are you here?
I...
Who is it?
Who's outside?
Hurry up.
Hide!
Keep quiet.
Can I make a sound?
What are you doing, you pervert?
You...
You are a pervert!
I helped you.
Helped me?
If someone sees
you are intimate with a man in the middle of the night,
it will damage your reputation
if this gets out.
Let me ask you.
Why did you climb over the wall in the middle of the night?
I... was enjoying the moon.
Enjoying the moon?
Bright moonlight wakes perched magpies.
Deep into night, breeze brings cicadas' chirping.
Such an atmosphere
is not commonly had.
Let's talk about you.
Why did you climb over the wall in the middle of the night?
This is my house.
It's none of your business.
I'm not afraid to tell you directly.
I was going to see you.
I know you live with Mr. Zhou.
Don't tell Mr. Zhou
about our engagement.
Otherwise...
Otherwise,
I'll let you know what the most vicious woman is like.
Men and women should not be too intimate.
I... What you are doing makes it look like we are very close.
If Mr. Zhou finds out about this...
How can you be so vicious?
I think I'm soft-hearted enough to you.
This is my house.
It's reasonable no matter where I am.
But you
sneaked into Song Mansion at night
with an ulterior motive.
Tell me. If I suddenly scream "Someone",
what would happen?
Someone.
Hush.
I don't care whether you think
this is a negotiation
or a threat.
Anyway,
you can't tell Mr. Zhou
about our engagement.
Fine, I promise you.
I won't tell Mr. Zhou about the engagement.
But you have to promise me
you won't pester me
and cause me trouble.
Fine.
Didn't you say
the Song family's daughters only marry the students of Song's Academy?
I'm not a student.
I'm just a teaching assistant.
Let me ask you.
Do you really not want to marry me?
When she's not speaking, she is pretty and cute.
And a little witty.
Do you think
when I'm not speaking, I'm very cute
and a little witty?
Miss Zhu. Don't worry.
I will never marry you.
Or let me put it this way.
I will never be the person who will marry you.
That's good.
You don't deserve me.
Let me ask you.
Why do you want to be admitted to Song's Academy?
I...
You what?
I admire Mr. Chen's knowledge and character.
I hope to be his teaching assistant
to learn from him,
so that I can improve myself.
When I learn well enough,
I will leave Song's Academy.
Learn from him as his teaching assistant?
That's enough.
As long as I can be with Mr. Chen
and learn from him,
it's fine even if I'm not a student of Song's Academy.
It's not a pity that I'm not a student of Song's Academy.
Really?
Yes.
Fine.
As long as you promise me
you won't be a student of Song's Academy
and you won't tell Mr. Zhou about our engagement,
I won't make things difficult for you anymore.
We'll stay out of each other's business.
Okay.
A word spoken
is past recalling.