[English subtitles are available]
[Special Lady]
[Episode 21]
Mr. Xiao.
Zhu.
M-Mr. Zhou.
What a coincidence. Are you shopping?
Junior Zhou.
What are you doing?
S-Selling gourds.
Hello, Teaching Assistant Xiao. Hello, Miss Song.
I'll leave you guys to it.
Brother, I'll go over there.
Junior Zhou…
I'm leaving then.
Junior Zhou!
What are you going to do?
Explain!
Explain what?
The more you explain, the more they'll misunderstand us.
Then can you think of a way?
Go and explain to them!
Junior Zhou.
Hurry up!
Junior Zhou, we were not frolicking
as you thought we were.
Why would Mr. Zhou misunderstand?
Lady Zhu just thought too much.
No need to explain.
Junior Zhou,
why don't you stay and paint the gourds for us?
Your paintings will sell well.
But Mr. Zhou is shopping with Lady Zhou.
Okay.
Take a look.
-Come and have a look.
-Take your time to pick.
My brother painted all of these personally.
-It's so pretty.
-Pick whatever you want.
The painting is so good.
-What is this?
-This one too.
A rabbit.
-You're so smart.
-Mother, I want this.
-I'll take this one.
-There are more down there.
There are big ones and small ones.
Okay, I want this one.
Look at this. The gourd you want.
-Thank you.
-Mother, it's so pretty.
Look, isn't this pretty?
What else do you want to see?
I want to paint too.
-Your painting is so ugly.
-Okay. One by one.
Junior Zhou is really something.
The money is so much that I can't even count it.
My brother's painting has always been lively.
It's the same even if it's on the gourd.
There's more.
I want this one.
The small one is also fun.
Junior Zhou.
Look at mine. Is it pretty?
Not as pretty as mine.
So beautiful.
Zhu
always praises Mr. Zhou whenever she sees him.
Then why did she give me the handkerchief?
Could it be a trap?
Hurry up!
Sorry.
Did you pay?
-Ma'am, I want this one.
-Thank you.
Okay.
How much is it?
Here.
You're so good at arithmetic?
It's just that you're so lousy at it.
Are you two newlyweds?
We used to be like you.
We always bickered.
-Her?
-Him?
Bah!
Look.
Newlyweds are so nice.
So romantic.
Let's go.
Junior Zhou.
Zhu,
do you want the watercolor?
You are not mad at me, are you?
I've never been mad at you.
Gourds! Gourds!
Xiao Yu, keep your voice down.
Don't you want to sell gourds?
Gourds!
Of all kinds of colors.
Welcome, Lord Zuo.
Unfortunately,
our Dean went out for something.
I'm not here
for Mr. Song.
Then what brings you here today, Lord Zuo?
A few days ago,
I accidentally got Mr. Shen Kuo's
"Brush Talks from Dream Brook" translated and annotated by you.
I like it very much.
Very much.
Lord Zuo,
I'm overwhelmed by your appraise.
It's just something
I jabbered when I was bored.
Mr. Zhang, you're too modest.
The foresight and sagacity of the book
is astonishing.
After reading your translation,
I was so enlightened.
Then I thought that it would be a loss of the world
if your valuable thoughts
are not known by everyone.
Lord Zuo, I'm flattered.
If you don't mind, Mr. Zhang,
I'll reorganize your poetry anthology
and add a compilation of scholars from our academy.
to leave your thoughts to the future generations.
What do you think, Mr. Zhang?
Lord Zuo, please don't…
Don't joke with me.
I'm not joking with you.
I'm waiting for your approval.
Then I'll do it right away.
I agree.
It's my great honor.
That's great.
But I need time to sort out the information.
If it's convenient for you,
can you lend me the information
of all the students in your academy?
I'll get it now.
Okay.
Lord Zuo.
-This way.
-Come with me.
Okay.
Don't miss it.
The last few painted gourds.
The last few good gourds.
Move aside.
Do you all have a stall?
-You guys.
-Have a look. The last…
You all have a stall.
Have you paid the tax today?
-Did you pay the tax?
-Hello, officer.
Give it to me.
-Officer.
-Have you paid the tax?
Here you are, officer.
Pay your tax.
These two are presents for you.
So nice. Thank you.
Don't make us waste our time.
Did you pay today's tax? Hurry up.
-Don't move.
-Did you pay the tax?
Did you pay your tax today?
How much is it?
Half of your income today.
They don't even know the rules.
I'm sure they didn't pay.
Come here.
I'd like to see how you'll move.
Interesting.
A gourd seller
dares to be so arrogant to us.
How dare you!
Officer,
we didn't sell gourds.
Those two people
just bought some from you.
If you don't believe me, you can ask them.
Hey, come back!
Officer.
We are not merchants.
We didn't set up a stall, either.
So we don't need
to pay any tax.
These gourds
were bought from a peasant woman.
Someone liked the gourds,
so we gave some to them.
If you like them,
we'll give them to you, too.
For you.
Here, officer.
Here you are.
Don't try to play tricks.
Did you two buy gourds here?
No, we didn't.
These were given as a present. We didn't buy it.
Look, officer.
I'm telling the truth.
Go.
Just go.
Can we leave, too?
-Let's go.
-You can't leave.
Whether you bought the gourds or gave them out,
you have to pay the tax with half of your income.
Okay.
Look, officer.
I gave you three gourds just now.
Those two took away two gourds.
There are five gourds in total, right?
Here are the tax for five gourds.
Can we go now?
Let's go.
Go away.
The tax is heavy, and the people are suffering.
Forget it. Don't be angry.
Don't be angry.
Just use a few copper coins to drive away the jinx.
Didn't you teach me
not to confront the tough with toughness?
How can you forget it when it comes to yourself?
Junior Zhou, I talked a lot today,
and I'm thirsty now.
Why don't we sit down and drink something?
We made money.
It's on me.
Do you want to go?
Don't be upset.
Drink some ice drink and cheer up.
Mr. Xiao, are you coming?
I…
Junior Zhou, let's go in first.
Let him think about it.
-Wait…
-Let's go.
Hurry up!
Let's go, brother.
I guess it doesn't matter if I go or not.
Are you coming or not?
Don't just stand there.
Coming.
Lady Zhou, help yourself.
-Junior Zhou.
-Thank you.
I'll do it.
Junior Zhou.
Thank you.
Lady Zhou.
Thank you, Miss Song.
Zhu,
thanks to your quick wit.
Otherwise,
I don't know how long those soldiers would badger us.
What quick wit?
I was just being unreasonable.
You...
were really brave.
Zhu.
Where is my money?
What money?
The money for selling gourd.
50%.
Didn't I give the money
to the soldiers?
Didn't you see it?
No.
What 50%?
Isn't it 40%?
Are you trying to be unreasonable?
Me? Unreasonable?
Zhu,
there seems to be ink on your forehead.
Really?
Let me help you.
Wipe it yourself.
Don't mind him.
By the way, Junior Zhou,
thank you for today.
Luckily, you helped me sell gourds.
That's why they sold out so fast.
Anyway,
you've made great contributions today.
You have to eat more.
And Lady Zhou, too.
Here, let me add some food for you.
You flatter me, Zhu.
We worked together to succeed.
I dare not take credit.
What are you looking at?
I'm asking you. What are you looking at?
Can't you see?
Brother.
It looks so beautiful outside.
Let's go have a look, too.
Let's go.
Slow down.
Let's go, too.
What's there to see?
Are you going or not?
If you're not, I'll go myself.
I'm not going.
I knew you wanted to go.
Let's go.
Brother, this way.
Feiniang, slow down.
What kind of music is this?
It's beautiful.
This is dance music from the Western Region.
How did you know?
I...
Someone in my family does business,
and they've dealt with people from the Western Region.
Aren't your family all officials?
Can't someone do business?
Mr. Xiao,
what kind of products
do your family buy and sell?
Mr. Zhou, why do you ask so suddenly?
I'm sorry for being rude.
I heard that you had had touch with people from the Western Region,
so I got curious.
After all, it's not common to see an aristocratic family that trades with the businessmen from the Western Regions.
I'm interested in the western language,
but I don't know where to start.
My family don't understand the western language either.
When they come here,
they bring an interpreter.
Then...
It's okay. I'll go home and ask about it.
If you are interested,
I'll tell you how to learn it later.
Thank you, Mr. Xiao.
The exotic dance
is indeed much bolder and more unstrained
than the elegant and reserved style of our country.
I think we are too pedantic.
Since ancient times,
the cultivation and breeding have made women
unable to do what they like,
to wear the clothes they like,
to wear the makeup they like,
or to dance the dances they like.
It actually doesn't matter what is the right thing to do.
You can write poems and articles as you like,
but if we're talking about the outfit,
I don't think I can accept it.
When everyone
is used to it,
there's nothing that you can't accept.
What other exotic anecdotes do you know?
Tell me more.
You want to hear it?
After you said it,
I really think it's no big deal.
Besides, it's really beautiful.
In fact, many places other than the Central Plain
are not as scary as described in the books.
They have
many features that we can appreciate.
For example?
For example, their attitudes towards food
and towards people both differ from ours.
There are many more.
-Brother.
-What else?
What are you thinking?
Tell me more.
It's okay. Let's go.
He is Xiao Yu?
Yes, he is Xiao Yu.
Mr. Zhang from Yiyang Academy gave me this portrait.
It must be Xiao Yu.
This Xiao Yu is not that Xiao Yu.
Maybe they have the same name?
Dare this person
make such a big scene in Yiyang Academy?
My Lord, perhaps we thought in the wrong direction.
It's not that this Xiao Yu was so powerful,
but that Mr. Li was too weak.
Something is wrong.
Keep investigating.
Yes, My Lord.
A fatty?
While Mr. Zhang and Lord Zuo were chatting,
I peeked at the information.
Not only your portrait shows a fatty,
but you also have an ordinary family.
Who on earth is helping me in secret?
We don't know whether he's a friend or foe.
But the fact that your identity is fake
has already been known by three people.
Young Master, we have to hurry.
I'm afraid things will get more complicated later.
I didn't expect Mr. Zhou to have such a varied style of painting.
Apart from ink painting,
he could even draw such an exquisite and cute person.
This...
This wasn't painted by Mr. Zhou?
No wonder it's so ugly.
Miss Fei, you're indeed Junior Zhou's sister.
You even look like him so much when you're studying.
Miss Yan,
it sounds like you know my brother well.
We studied together before.
Seeing you like this,
I'm reminded of him.
Miss Yan, you've studied with my brother before?
I've never heard my brother mention it before.
Did you go out alone?
What are you thinking?
Of course not.
By the way, Feiniang,
did you go downtown
to take a walk this weekend?
Yes.
But Yiyang is a really complicated place.
What happened?
Last night,
my brother, Lady Zhu,
Teaching Assistant Xiao, and I
saw a group of people dancing the Western style dance
near the beverage shop.
Yueniang and Mr. Xiao were there too?
We even sold gourds all afternoon.
Miss Song Zhu also bought us beverage.
It was really delicious.
I've never had it at home before.
Humph.
You made an appointment to have a drink, but you didn't even invite me.
No, we didn't make an appointment beforehand.
We just ran into each other.
They were already selling gourds when we arrived.
So it was like when you were shopping with Yueniang,
you ran into Junior Zhou and Mr. Xiao?
No, I went shopping with my brother.
You mean
you went shopping with Mr. Zhou,
and then you met Mr. Xiao and Yueniang on the way?
Not really.
We met them
when my brother took me to buy some cake before that.
But at that time they were being chased.
They were being chased?
I don't know who was chasing Miss Song Zhu.
Luckily, Teaching Assistant Xiao was there to protect her.
Did they get hurt?
I assume they did not.
When they were selling gourds,
I saw that they were both fine.
That's good.
I was scared.
Miss Yan, do you know
what's the relationship between Teaching Assistant Xiao and Miss Song?
Why do you ask?
Yesterday,
I saw them fleeing from the chase.
At that time,
I saw Teaching Assistant Xiao holding Miss Song's hand.
Lady Zhou, you can't make a casual comment like that.
You said it yourself.
It was an urgent situation.
And even if it's true,
there's a reason for it.
You can tell me this.
If you keep telling this to others,
not only will you tarnish the reputation of Yueniang and Mr. Xiao,
but also it's not good for you either.
Like this.
It's a trick. Look.
Turn like this.
-Got it?
-Let me think about it.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
Did you quarrel with Lady Zhou?
Well then...
What's wrong? You're acting weird.
Yueniang.
I heard you were in danger yesterday.
You didn't even tell me.
You stared at me
just because of this?
Anyway, I was stalked yesterday.
Luckily, nothing happened.
I didn't want you to worry,
so I didn't tell you.
I'm glad you're fine.
The mere thought of it makes me scared.
Alright.
I'm blessed and protected by the gods.
Look, I'm fine.
Well,
did anything else happen yesterday?
Anything else?
I heard
you and Mr. Xiao hold hands.
Go back to our seats.
Qinruo.
It was urgent.
It was an accident.
Bo Ya, the guqin performer in the pre-Qin period
once played the guqin in the wilderness.
The woodcutter Zhong Ziqi
could comprehend that the tune of the guqin
was depicting something as majestic as Mount Tai
and as vast as Yangtze River and Yellow River.
Bo Ya was amazed and said,
"Great.
Our hearts strike the same chord."
After Zhong Ziqi died,
Bo Ya was so sad about losing his soulmate
that he smashed his guqin and cut the strings.
That's the story behind the Melody of High Mountains and Flowing Rivers.
You'll be confused if you just learn but not think.
You'll be tired and lost if you just think but not learn.
If a gentleman wants to achieve something,
he must first…
Mr. Xue. Mr. Xue.
judge
and analyze the situation.
He must make a through plan before taking any action.
Come on, let me tell you some news.
I promise you'll be energetic immediately.
What is it?
Mr. Xiao got a handkerchief as a gift.
It is quite normal
to get a handkerchief as a gift.
Who doesn't have one?
I don't.
Don't interrupt.
But on the handkerchief
was embroidered a mandarin duck.
It's so romantic.
However, Mr. Xiao said that someone was troubled.
He just mediated in the middle.
He said he would return it for his friend in a few days.
Luckily, I was quick-witted.
Actually, I knew everything.
I just didn't make it clear.
So it was from you?
You nerd.
Why would I give him a handkerchief with a mandarin duck?
How about I give you one with Zhong Kui, the ghostbuster on it?
Go on. Go on.
Do you know that Mr. Xiao's family don't live in Yiyang?
He came to Yiyang to study.
Besides the people in our academy,
he has no other relatives or friends.
So the handkerchief must be a token of love
given by someone in our academy.
Who could it be?
Let's just watch the show.
Ding Miao,
I see you're so happy
to learn things.
I want to know
what you think about what I just taught.
High mountains and flowing rivers.
Sit down.
Bo Ya and Ziqi hadn't been together for long,
but they became bosom friends.
They sincerely treated each other
as soulmates.
Bo Ya cut the strings
only because there was only the tune left,
but no one could understand it.
Others may think he made a fuss about nothing.
However, for Bo Ya,
losing his soulmate
doesn't only mean there was no one in this world who understood his music,
but also that no one understood his mind.
In today's lesson,
I hope you can learn a piece of life philosophy,
beside learning the tune,
that it's easy to get a thousand teals of gold,
but hard to find a bosom friend.
You students
can't even stand
or sit properly.
In every class,
your thoughts float away.
You are not interested in reading or learning,
but are so passionate about dirty things.
Indeed, each generation is getting worse.
Zhou Ji,
stand up.
Look at
what a role model is like.
When you looked at
and laughed at Ding Miao and Xue Hanfu,
Zhou Ji was the only one
who was thinking.
Class,
thinking is very important.
We need to reflect on ourselves all the time.
Qinruo.
Let's go.
Qinruo, I...
Go away!
Qinruo.
Did you have a quarrel with Lady Yan?
You're such a troublemaker.
Qin…
Lady Zhou, hurry up.
Okay.
Qinruo.
Where are you going?
Mind your own business. Just stop causing me trouble!
You caused me trouble.
-Let me ask you.
-I don't understand what you're talking about.
Can't you see such a big pit?
You scared me.
I can't see it. I'm blind.
Sir, can you stop blocking my way?
You...
Do you know it's just because Qinruo got to know that yesterday you asked me out
and held my hand
that she's mad at me now?
But even if you talk to Lady Yan now,
you can't really make it clear.
Leave her alone to calm down.
Don't interfere with girls' affairs.
I have something to tell you.
Wait until this is over.
No, I have to say it now.
Go away!
Qinruo!
Song Zhu, are you even a woman?
This is a gift from Zhu to Mr. Xiao.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Xiao.
What are you doing?
I was tidying up for you.
No.
I saw this handkerchief dropped on the ground.
It must be something important to you,
so I wanted to return it to you personally.
But shouldn't the handkerchief be in the box?
Really?
I found it on the ground just now.
Maybe I forgot to put it back after taking it out.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
You're welcome.
Mr. Xiao,
I saw the handkerchief is exquisite,
delicate,
and full of love.
Could it be that
some girl admired you secretly?
It's from Miss Song Zhu.
Mr. Zhou, what do you think?
What?
I said this handkerchief was from Miss Song Zhu.
Mr. Zhou, do you have anything to say?
It's a gift from Zhu to you.
I didn't scrutinize it,
so I can't really comment on it.
I have to go study,
so please excuse me.
How much of what you said is true
and how much is fake?
Let me see.
Yueniang.
The needlework
gets really chilling after your modification.
People might think
my sister
is embroidering some exotic herbs.
Second Sister, you don't understand.
I'm embroidering something magnificent and mighty.
Indeed I don't understand.
Second Sister, stop laughing at me.
Do you think everyone is
so ingenious on needlework like you?
What's wrong?
I'm quitting embroidering.
Let it grow on its own.
Yueniang,
the needlework is actually the same as painting.
Make your mind follow your heart.
Think about the beauty of what you painted.
Every stitch is like a stroke.
You can't be impatient.
Second Sister, you're right.
I can't be impatient.
Besides, this is what I wanted
to use to apologize.
I should embroider it myself.
Second Sister, let me do it.
If you put your true heart
in your gift,
the person who receives it will naturally appreciate your kindness.
In that case,
I'll be here for you.
When you need me,
I'll teach you stitch by stitch.
Zhen, how have you been?
I heard that in your Women's Academy, there is a teaching assistant
named Xiao Yu.
Seeing this name, I was wondering
who he was.
If you have time,
send his portrait back to me.
Remember, it's important.
That's strange.
This is not Teaching Assistant Xiao.
It's not Teaching Assistant Xiao on this portrait.
Xiao Yu.
The son of Xiao Chuanzhong.
Guards!
Master.
Send someone
to send this letter to Lord Zuo immediately.
Yes.
Instructor Shen.
You're good, Instructor Shen.
You walk silently and land without a trace.
Good eyesight.
Teaching Assistant Xiao, what brings you here?
I'm here to see the Dean,
but he seems to be talking to someone else.
So I'm waiting here.
No need to wait.
I'll take you in.
Dean.
It's okay. Just stand here for a while.
I... No.
Dean.
Why don't you get back to work?
Yes.
Brother, where is Teaching Assistant Xiao?
He must be out for business.
Brother.
I think I did something wrong.
What is it?
Miss Yan chatted with me yesterday.
I accidentally told her
that we saw Teaching Assistant Xiao and Miss Song
together in the street.
And she…
she seems to be mad at Miss Song Zhu.
Brother,
did I say something wrong?
Did you tell her
that Mr. Xiao and Zhu held hands?
Yes.
Then,
should I explain it to the two ladies?
Today, I read
a line in Volume 9
of "Exoteric traditions of the Han version of the Songs" by Han Ying from Han Dynasty.
The luke mind
could harm your mind and body.
The lust
will draw disasters for you.
What do you think of this sentence, Dean?
Take a look.
What did I paint on this paper?
If a person who has no fluke mind
doesn't control their desire
and does whatever they want,
they will no longer be the same old person they used to be.
Just like the white paper won't be white anymore with only one drop of ink on it.