[English subtitles are available]
[Special Lady]
[Episode 20]
Is Zhou Ji that good?
I...
It's none of your business.
I just don't want this marriage.
Besides, no matter how bad he is,
he is better than you.
Fine.
Since he's so good,
I'll leave.
Liar. You promised me.
Yueniang.
Mother.
You went to see Mr. Xiao off?
I didn't send him off.
Yueniang.
Although you're not young anymore,
to me and you father,
you are always a child.
So,
if there's anything,
just tell us.
Don't keep it to yourself.
Mother.
What do you mean?
I can tell
you don't want to marry Mr. Xiao.
Of course, I do.
I do.
Yueniang.
If you have something to tell,
you can tell us directly.
You don't need to let others pass the message.
We are a family.
We can talk about anything.
What do you mean by "others"?
Who else could it be other than Mr. Xiao?
Xiao Yu?
Did he tell you?
You two
put on a drama so seriously today.
Didn't you want to tell us
you don't want to get married?
Oh no.
I wronged him.
Your father and I won't blame you.
And your father agreed to suspend the engagement.
If you fall in love with each other in the future,
we can discuss it again.
How could we fall in love with each other?
Who can predict the future?
I'm very certain about this matter.
All right.
It's getting late.
Go back and rest.
Mother.
All right.
Mother, rest early.
The engagement has finally been broken off.
Great!
I finally broke off the engagement.
But I wronged him.
What should I do?
No.
He lied to me.
He deserves it.
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Xiao.
I'm back.
By the way,
Mr Zhou,
has your sister settled down?
Yes.
Thank you for asking, Mr. Xiao.
That's great.
You can see your sister every day in the future.
I envy people who have siblings.
Your family must be lively.
By the way,
how many siblings do you have?
I also have...
An elder brother.
I shouldn't have asked.
It's fine.
My brother was First Madam's child.
Zhou Fei and I share the same mother.
Mr. Xiao. Why are you back so late today?
We had a relative over at home
and had dinner together.
Did you memorize the passage starting with "The Master was diligent in teaching..."?
Yes, I did.
Look.
I haven't finished embroidering the handkerchief last night.
Who is this?
I don't know.
Really?
Come here.
That was so pretty.
Yes, I think so too.
Look, this is Zhou Ji’s younger sister.
Really?
Yes, she is.
Is the Women's Academy recruiting new students?
Yes.
Are you transferring to our academy?
What's your name?
-You can...
-Lady Qi.
Don't scare her.
You must be Junior Zhou's sister.
Don’t be afraid. What’s your name?
My name is Zhou Fei.
I didn’t hear you clearly.
Zhou what?
What Fei?
Her name is Zhou Fei.
Yes, Zhou Fei.
Feiniang.
Miss Yan.
What are you doing?
Are you bullying Feiniang?
Lady Yan, you misunderstood.
It's the first time we've seen Feiniang.
We're curious.
I asked her which family she was from.
Feiniang is Zhou Ji's sister.
-What's happening?
-She'll be our classmate from now on.
A newcomer?
My name is Qi Xi.
If you need any help,
just let me know.
Yes.
We will take good care of you for Mr. Zhou.
That's right.
All right.
If you keep talking,
Feiniang will be shy.
Lady Zhou.
Follow me.
Don't worry.
They are not bad people.
Just study hard.
If anyone bullies you,
just tell me. I'm Jin Xiaoyue.
Sit here.
It's close to me.
Come on.
Thank you, Miss Jin.
Great.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Come on.
Suspect not things, but be straightforward without arrogance.
When sitting, be as if in meditation. when standing, be dignified.
Let rituals follow appropriateness, customs follow utility.
Do not overdo rituals,
do not intrude or offend, and do not indulge in frivolity.
Suspect not things, but be straightforward without arrogance.
When sitting, be as if in meditation...
Looks like he's really angry.
Let rituals follow appropriateness, customs follow utility.
Do not overdo rituals,
do not intrude or offend, and do not indulge in frivolity.
Okay, that's all for today.
Go back and memorize this article.
I will test you
during class tomorrow.
Yes.
Teaching Assistant Xiao.
About what happened last night...
What happened last night?
You're not done yet?
Well, I...
Qinruo.
Yueniang.
Is there anything between you and Mr. Xiao?
Nothing.
Mr. Xiao acted strangely.
What's the matter?
Yueniang, come here.
Mr. Xiao has returned to the academy.
So I thought
to buy him a gift.
First,
to celebrate his return to the academy.
Second, I want to use it to express my feelings.
What do you think?
Why don't you just express your feelings?
That won't do.
I'm the daughter of Duke Yue.
It's not appropriate for me
to confess my feelings to someone.
Didn't you say that
Mr. Xiao is so dignified?
If I say it out loud,
it would be an affront to his dignity.
That makes sense.
Yueniang, go with me.
You and Mr. Xiao are friends.
You know him well.
I don't know him well.
You can decide your own business.
Yueniang,
you must know Mr. Xiao better than I do.
Go with me.
I don't know him...
You know him well.
I don't.
How could I know him well?
You know him best.
Ladies. What do you need?
Boss.
Do you have any beautiful handkerchiefs
or pouch?
Take a look here.
This way.
Boss.
Coming.
Yueniang.
Do you think it's beautiful?
Mandarin ducks?
Isn't this too straightforward?
I'm afraid if I don't be straightforward,
Mr. Xiao may not know what I mean.
Actually,
I hinted at him many times.
But he didn't seem to understand.
So I want to be straightforward this time.
Then you decide.
I wronged Xiao Yu last night.
Giving him a gift
would also be a way to show my sincerity, wouldn't it?
This wolf-hair brush is quite delicate.
It is.
Right?
Yueniang.
Do you want to send it to Junior Zhou?
Zhou...
What?
It’s not for Junior Zhou?
It is.
How about this, Yueniang?
You send this one
and I'll send this one.
Let's send them together, okay?
Boss.
Coming.
Help me pack these two.
I want this.
How about
a rosewood box?
It matches your handkerchief.
Then I'll take the rosewood box.
Okay.
This lady.
What box do you want for your wolf-hair brush?
I want a red lacquered wooden box.
Okay.
Which one is supposed to be placed in the rosewood box?
The wolf-hair brush should be for the scholar.
It should be placed in the rosewood box.
[Duobao Hall]
Take care, Ladies.
Come again.
Yueniang.
Tell me. When Mr. Xiao
sees the Mandarin ducks on the handkerchief,
would he know how I feel?
If he still doesn't understand,
he must be a nerd.
Then I'm relieved.
Yueniang.
How should I give it to him?
Of course, you should give it to him face-to-face.
Can you go with me later?
In this way,
you can also give your gift to Junior Zhou.
Well...
I don't think it's a good idea.
How can you get a lot of people to be present?
Ask him out yourself.
I'll ask Junior Zhou out myself.
Let's send the gifts to them separately.
Yueniang.
Why are you more shy than me now?
You're not usually like this.
How can it be as usual?
After all,
this isn't about creating a scene.
That's true.
Then once I go back,
I'll go ask Teaching Assistant Xiao out.
Let's hurry up and go back.
Okay.
Is anyone here?
No one is here.
Since Qinruo asked him out,
I won't feel awkward.
Why am I so smart?
Xiao Yu. This will be considered my apology to you.
Don't be angry anymore.
Miss...
Miss Zhu?
It's none of my business.
[I'm sorry about last night. A gift for you to apologize. From Song Zhu]
Mr. Xiao, you're back.
I just came back.
Mr. Xiao.
-You’re back.
-Mr. Zhou.
They are...
Mandarin ducks?
Mr. Zhou.
Was anyone here?
No.
I just came back.
I see.
What's the matter, Mr. Xiao?
Nothing. I'm just asking.
I'll go ask Ding Miao.
Mr. Ding.
Mr. Xiao.
Do you know
that pet is forbidden in our academy?
Mr. Xiao.
Both you and I will keep the secret.
Who else will ever know?
Then I...
That makes sense.
What's up?
Yes.
I need to talk to you.
Mr. Ding.
Do you understand
a girl's thoughts?
A little.
What if
a girl gives you a handkerchief with Mandarin duck embroidery, what does it mean?
Mandarin ducks?
I have Mandarin ducks in my house.
Do you want to keep them?
We'll talk about that later.
Later.
Keep your voice down.
Look at you.
So you received a handkerchief
embroidered with Mandarin ducks from a girl?
Not me.
It doesn't matter who it is.
What does it mean?
Either she wants to pair up with you
or when she bought it,
she didn't know they were Mandarin ducks.
Right.
With her intelligence,
she would think they're ducks.
Mr. Xiao,
who gave you the handkerchief?
How about I do some divination for you?
No need.
Mr. Xiao, you are so bad.
You didn't even tell me who it was.
Forget it. I'm leaving.
Mr. Xiao, don't you talk about Mandarin ducks?
No.
We'll talk about it later.
Don't tell anyone.
Does she really not know that they are Mandarin ducks?
It's good if she doesn't know.
What if she wasn't being unintentional?
How could it be?
She can’t like me.
She likes Zhou Ji.
Mr. Xiao.
Are you going to sleep?
If you are, I'll turn off the lights.
Yes, I am.
Son.
Play crickets with me.
Come on.
Well, you...
You father is here.
Why are you so quiet when I'm talking to you?
It's your favorite. It smells good.
Look.
You...
Play a few rounds with me.
Ten taels for one round.
You can have the money if you win.
If you lose,
you...
eat this.
I don't want to play.
I feel annoyed.
You're annoyed?
Well.
What's bothering you?
Tell me.
Don't you know
what's bothering me?
Didn't you see how Xiao Yu stole my thunder?
He's just a villain. Don't care about him.
How good can he be?
He's just a teaching assistant.
Even though, he's better than me.
Father.
Am I a loser?
What are you talking about?
Of course not.
You will
become a high official when you grow up.
He's a villain, yet he's better than me.
How can I be a high official?
I'm doomed.
Well.
I need to teach that guy a lesson.
I'm doomed.
Waiter.
Coming.
Mr. Xiao.
Are you here to see Yueniang?
No.
Please tell her
I have something to say.
I'll wait for her at the riverbank.
Okay.
I'll go tell her now.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Zhu.
Do you know there are many types of birds?
You must have bought the wrong gift.
Zhu.
If you have no feelings for me,
why did you buy me such a gift...
Why are you here?
Lower down.
Zhu.
I saw some people
watching you sneakily.
No.
Don't look back.
They are still watching you.
Let's go.
Master, they've changed direction.
Should we follow them?
Go after them! Go!
Hurry up!
Stop walking! Run!
Raise the sedan chair.
Who will carry me?
Brother.
You may not know
that all the sisters in the academy are nice to me.
Especially Miss Yan.
She protected me on the day of admission.
Brother.
It would be great
if someone as beautiful and kind as Miss Yan
could become my sister-in-law.
Feiniang.
Don't talk nonsense.
Lady Yan is the only daughter of Duke Yue.
Her status is unique and noble.
Mother
didn't ask you to go to the academy
to think about these things.
You should learn from Mr. Chen and study hard.
Got it.
Who is your favorite
among the girls at the Women's Academy?
I don't favor anyone.
Hurry up.
Miss Song Zhu.
Brother.
Was that Miss Song Zhu?
Miss Zhu.
Mr. Xiao.
It was really Miss Song and Teaching Assistant Xiao.
But why were they so anxious
and holding hands?
They didn't avoid it.
Go after them!
Hey, man!
You bumped into her.
So annoying.
Go away.
You...
Brother.
Calm down.
They are so fierce.
Feiniang, wait for me here.
I’ll be back soon.
Be careful. Brother.
Who asked you to come?
It's him.
He's Mr. Xiao's servant.
Why did he suddenly appear here?
He has such great martial arts.
Despite having such martial skills, he's willing to be a household servant.
This is unusual.
Is Mr. Xiao hiding something?
-Let go.
You let go first.
You're holding me.
How can I let go?
Don't use so much strength.
You...
See, you're still using your strength.
Why did those people chase you?
Did you get into trouble?
Chasing me? Didn't they chase you?
What did you do this time?
They were obviously chasing you.
I don't know them.
Maybe we both made a mistake.
We misunderstood.
They were not after us at all.
A new notice.
Take a look.
This...
With immediate effect,
stallholders within Yiyang county
face a twofold increase in taxes.
What?
How are we going to live?
The officials are so greedy
and disregard the people.
I have to argue with them.
What're you doing?
What are you doing?
Don't go.
Let's leave here.
I want to argue with them.
That's too much!
-Don’t make trouble. Let's leave.
-They’ve gone too far!
Brother!
Did you catch up with them?
Brother.
Don't worry.
We'll know when we go back and ask them.
Feiniang.
Don't tell anyone in the academy about this.
Are you talking about them holding hands
or being chased?
Both.
Brother.
I think you treat Miss Song differently.
Don't think too much.
Both of them are my friends.
I just don't want any rumors circulating about them.
But I also think
the relationship between Teaching Assistant Xiao and Miss Song is a bit special.
You little smart girl.
Everything you see is special.
Brother.
I've been in Yiyang for so long.
I haven't taken a good look.
How about you accompany me for a stroll today?
Okay, let's go for a good stroll.
Okay.
I didn't know
when you became so timid.
Coward.
I'm not timid.
It's just that this isn't how you should solve it.
Then tell me how to solve it.
You're not an official.
Let alone you,
even Dean Song was there,
it wouldn't be helpful.
If you rashly confront people like that,
what else will it bring besides trouble?
You said everything.
Then tell me
why you asked me out.
Tell me.
Can't I
just hang out with you without any particular reason?
Are you kidding me?
If there's nothing else, let's each go home.
Wait, wait.
That day, you gave me the...
Can't you just...
I don't even have money to save our child.
Let's just die.
Calm down.
You can’t kill yourself.
I wanted to sell these gourds in the city
in exchange for money to treat my child.
But I ran into those tax collectors.
I didn't have money.
It was useless no matter what I said.
They even ruined my gourds.
Calm down.
How about this?
I'll buy all your gourds, okay?
Here.
Take the child to see a doctor.
Thank you. Miss.
Ma'am.
You're older than me. You can't kneel to me.
Hurry and take the money
to see a doctor.
Go see a doctor.
Hurry up.
Thank you, Young Master.
Don't try to kill yourself again.
Thank you, Miss.
Go now.
Don't cry.
We have money for treatment.
Damn the government!
Zhu.
What are you going to do with all these gourds?
I'll think about it.
There will be a solution.
There is always a way out.
Be careful.
Wait for me.
I'm exhausted.
You bought so many gourds at once.
I have to carry them back for you.
You did a good deed,
yet I'm the one left to do the work.
You can't do physical work.
And you don't study hard.
Slow down, mind my gourds.
Xiao, slow down!
Our Xiao family is big.
There's no such work in my family.
I don't need to do this either.
Thank you
for being considerate of us common people.
You're sweating. Let me wipe it for you.
No.
Stay away from me.
You...
Stop!
Slow down!
Wait.
Put it down.
Have you figured it out?
Yes.
That's why you need to do some work for me.
You want me to do more work for you?
You're a man.
Why do you keep
picking on me, a frail girl, all the time?
Find your own way back if you can.
Fine.
Vegetables.
Sir, may I borrow your bench?
Okay.
Do you remember the way back?
Oh no.
I got lost again.
By the way,
you still have money on you, right?
Go buy some paint.
Let's work on the gourds.
Otherwise,
I'll leave you alone.
Ridiculous.
Do I look like someone who can't find the way back?
Young Master. What else do you need?
Nothing.
That's all.
Okay.
Take them.
Fresh gourds.
Come and take a look.
Take a look.
You...
You should be in charge of calling out the sales.
I...
What did you ask me to do?
Call out the sales.
I won't.
Do it yourself if you want.
You were so obedient just now.
I wanted to give you 30% of the profit.
Even though, I won't do it.
You're useless being here.
Leave.
Who said I'm useless?
I can help you pass something.
Stand still.
Raise your right hand.
Higher.
Raise this hand, too.
Towards that way.
Smile.
Hold it up.
What are you doing?
Turn your face.
Smile.
Gourds!
What are you doing?
I'm selling the gourds.
Selling gourds?
Look.
They saw it.
Who saw it?
Look, he saw it.
Look.
Didn't you see it?
Why are you here?
Mother, I want this.
I just bought you candied haws.
Let's go.
Look.
They saw it.
50%.
Go now.
If you keep talking, I won't share any profit with you.
Go.
Gourds.
40%.
Gourds!
Don't miss it.
Both adults and children like them.
Little items made of gourds.
Come and have a look.
There are all shapes of them.
The price is negotiable.
Don't miss it.
Take a look at our gourds.
Do you want a gourd?
Take a look.
Is she peeping at me?
What...
Are you drawing?
Look.
How lively is the little figure I've drawn!
It will sell at a good price later.
Who did you draw? It's so ugly.
Doesn't it look like you?
I think it looks like you very much.
So pretty.
Are you drawing the handsome me?
Yes.
It's the handsome you.
Look.
He looks like you so much.
Hode it tightly.
Don't ruin it.
Are you done?
Put it back if you're done.
I'm selling it.
No.
It's too ugly to sell.
I...
I drew a chubby little figure.
It's so cute.
I want to sell it.
Gourds!
No.
It's too ugly.
It'll be a laughing stock.
How cute.
I must sell it.
No.
-Give it to me.
-No.
Give it to me.
No, no.
I must sell it.
-I said no.
-Just give it to me.
This is not for sale.
Fine.
You don't have to sell it.
I tried so hard to draw this.
I will give it to you as a reward.
It's included in the 40% profit.
By the way.
Take it back to the dorm and take care of it.
Don’t break it, okay?
I've lost my cash and I've got to keep it for you.
If it weren't for the fear of losing face over these items,
I wouldn't keep them for you.
Well.
Your drawing skill is so bad.
Why don't you stop drawing?
No one will buy it anyway.
Do it if you can.
I can draw better than you.
Go ahead.
I can draw it now.
But I just don't want to.
Draw it. Don't just say it.
I don't want to draw now.
I'm not in the mood now.
Draw now.
I don't want to draw now.
Then stop talking.
Master.
That man defeated us
effortlessly.
I was very scared.
So I told him.
Useless!
Guards!
Beat him and the one kneeling outside
fifty strokes each.
Master. Please spare my life.
I know I was wrong.
-Hit him harder!
-Master!
Useless!
Master, please come in.
Get out.
How did it go?
My Lord. You may not know
that Xiao Yu is a teaching assistant in the Women's Academy.
Well,
we can't investigate the Women's Academy.
But don't worry.
I have taught him a lesson in another way.
Tell me.
I asked someone to beat him up.
You loser!
Loser!
Well.
Lord Zuo.
Take a look here.
The dried gourds I just painted.
-Ma'am. Come and take a look.
-Sir. Do you want a gourd?
No.
Look.
Take a look at the gourds.
Have a look at gourds.
Sir, look at the gourds.
The dried gourds I just painted.
Take a look.
Do you want a gourd?
Don't miss it.
Freshly painted gourds.
I told you.
You can't sell them.
What else can you do
apart from making sarcastic remarks?
It's fine if you can't sell them.
You've dirtied your face.
Why are you so annoying?
Don't move.
-Let me see.
-What’s wrong?
There seems to be something dirty here.
Look.
Really?
Go take a look.
Childish.
Come here.
Don't come over.
Childish, come here.
My clothes are new.
So what?
Why did you poke me?
Come here.
Don't get my clothes dirty.
Brother.
Teaching Assistant Xiao and Miss Song.
I just want to poke you.
Mr. Xiao.
Miss Zhu.