[English subtitles are available]
[Special Lady]
[Episode 36]
[Prince Fu's Mansion]
What if he is determined to marry Song Zhu?
How dare he!
If he is really that disobedient,
I won't see him as my son anymore.
And I won't let him be a viscount.
You can have these.
I wanted to say goodbye to His Highness and Her Highness in person,
but I saw them having a discussion
so I don't want to interrupt them.
Guard Yu, when it's convenient for you,
please tell His Highness and Her Highness that I've left.
Father.
Let me help you.
Why are you being so good today?
Father.
You did a great thing for the people
in the court today.
That's why you're pleasing me here?
No.
I admire you.
Good.
Father.
Thank you.
Let me thank you on behalf of the crown prince.
You've fulfilled his last wish.
Thank you, Father.
Lunch is ready.
Let's have lunch.
Let me ask Yueniang to come.
Yan.
No need to do that.
She has left.
She has left?
When?
She said she would wait for me and we would pick up Mr. Song
and go back to Yiyang together.
Yan.
You haven't eaten yet. Where are you going?
I'm not eating.
It's no use sighing.
Well...
Don't I need to have lunch?
Why did she leave suddenly?
She said she would wait for me to come back.
Did my parents say anything to her?
I have no idea.
I only saw Miss Song Zhu
get out of the side hall with the farewell gifts
and go back to the room after a while.
She didn't give the gifts to His Highness and Her Highness.
-Get me a carriage.
-Yes.
Yuniang, let's hang the lanterns together.
Okay.
Rongniang, Yuniang.
-Mother.
-Go with me to worship our ancestors.
Thanks to God's blessing,
your father, Li, Yang, and the teachers
are all safe.
Yes.
It's all thanks to our Third Sister.
Why did Mother say it was thanks to God's blessing?
Just listen to her.
What are you two murmuring?
Nothing.
Let me tell you.
You should be in awe of the gods.
You should do...
Do...
Pilot acts.
Pilot acts?
According to what I know
about Mother's vocabulary,
I think she meant pious acts.
Darling.
Honey.
Please stride the brazier
to get rid of bad luck.
Honey.
Darling.
Just do it.
Okay.
Here.
Yan.
I know you're angry with your father but you should eat.
♫No trace of falling leaves♫
♫Long years away, old friends waiting♫
♫The cool wind blows, leaving marks on memories♫
♫Quietly rooted in the sorrow of parting♫
♫Locking the heart in its door♫
♫Yearning with such sincerity♫
♫Waiting for flowers to bloom, the moon to be full, and roots to take hold♫
♫Waiting for someone to return♫
♫I care about you until the end of the world♫
♫I miss you only♫
♫As the rain falls, my tears flow♫
♫The flowers fall in the lonely city and no one enters the painting♫
♫The oaths are broken♫
Young Master
♫After letting go of worries, the world seems wider♫
♫Close at hand, yet far away♫
Xue Zicai, hurry.
Pan Yunlang.
Don't rush me. Wait a moment.
Let's do it again.
I won.
Pan Yunlang, I won.
♫Locking the heart in its door♫
I won. I won.
I won.
♫Yearning with such sincerity♫
Xiao.
Is this for me?
♫Waiting for flowers to bloom, the moon to be full, and roots to take hold♫
Yes.
These are all
from that foodie guy.
♫Waiting for someone to return♫
When will that foodie guy come?
♫I care about you until the end of the world♫
Go.
♫I miss you only♫
♫As the rain falls, my tears flow♫
♫The flowers fall in the lonely city and no one enters the painting♫
♫The oaths are broken♫
♫After letting go of worries, the world seems wider♫
♫I care about you until the end of the world♫
♫I miss you only♫
♫As the rain falls, my tears flow♫
♫The flowers fall in the lonely city and no one enters the painting♫
♫The oaths are broken♫
♫After letting go of worries, the world seems wider♫
♫I care about you until the end of the world♫
♫I miss you only♫
♫Hoping for a return, but no one answers♫
♫The tired bird has left the fence for several years♫
♫Radiant youth♫
♫The wind and sand that cannot be held♫
♫Close at hand, yet far away♫
Why are you here?
Are you angry?
Did my parents say anything to you?
Does your parents know you are here?
I don't care if they know or not.
Are you mad at me?
I...
No matter what they said,
my feelings for you won't change.
Don't ignore me
because of what they said.
I'm not angry.
Yueniang.
I missed you.
Stop.
You're making me blush.
You look cute when you blush.
Are you still angry?
I'm not angry.
I'm not angry about what they said.
I just wanted to see my father as soon as possible.
Okay.
But what your parents said
still made me feel a little unhappy.
I'm sorry that what they said made you feel bad.
I felt bad.
But
I won't back down.
Besides,
I believe you can handle it well.
Look, you're here.
Yueniang, you may rest assured.
I will treat you well.
And your parents may also rest assured.
In my life,
I will only marry you.
How do you know
my parents will let us get married?
I'm confident of it.
Dean Song has always thought highly of me.
Mother.
What brings you here?
Greetings, Your Highness.
I forgot to introduce her to you just now.
This is Lin Qing'er, daughter of the incumbent Imperial Preceptor.
Your father and I have decided on her as your fiancée.
This is unacceptable.
I will never marry any other woman.
It's not up to you.
Mrs. Song.
Can I talk to my mother alone?
Let's leave.
Princess Fu, Viscount.
I'll take my leave.
Mother.
Yueniang.
I don't want life to be hard for you in the future.
How about...
Mother.
This is my business.
Let me take care of it.
Okay.
I'll let you handle it.
Yueniang.
I support you and you can pursue your happiness.
But I also don't want life to be hard for you in the future.
I'll always support you.
I'm always on your side.
Mother, let me talk to her.
Your name is Lin Qing'er?
You are Song Zhu?
Yes, you can also call me Zhu.
Zhu?
You can also call me Qing'er.
Qing'er, let's go out for a walk.
Let's go. I'll show you around the academy.
Okay.
Don't worry, Mother.
Mother.
You know my feelings for Yueniang.
Don't force me to marry any other woman.
How about this?
Yan.
How about we both make a concession?
I can let you marry Song Zhu,
but she can only be your concubine.
Only a girl of noble birth like Lin Qing'er
can be your wife.
No.
I told you that my wife could only be Song Zhu.
If you force me to marry any other woman,
I'll marry into the Song family
and be a son-in-law that lives with the Song family.
And my name will be changed into Song Yan.
What?
You're a viscount.
How can you marry into her family?
If you do that,
you'll never be allowed to come back home
and you're not my son anymore.
This place is called Luwen Hall
where Chen Yan and I had the first battle.
I hated him so much at that time.
Take a seat.
This is the place
where Chen Yan and I
watched fireworks together for the first time.
There.
This is the place
where Chen Yan and I told each other our feelings for each other.
Mother.
You don't know what to do now?
Are you testing me?
You're silly.
Your acting was so good.
You're Prince Fu's son, a viscount.
You're so in love with that girl.
I have to come and see
how much you love each other.
So you'll allow me to marry her.
That's because she didn't back down.
She has won my trust.
She
is really like me when I was young.
I think
it won't be bad
if I let her take care of everything in the mansion.
She is the girl that I love.
Of course she's a wonderful girl.
What about
Lin Qing'er?
She didn't want to marry you in the first place.
Anything else?
Are there any more interesting stories between you and him?
You seem to enjoy those stories very much.
Because they're interesting.
Actually,
I didn't mean to make you break up.
I was curious.
Curious?
I was curious about the girl
who the viscount loves so much
that he would give up everything for her.
You're just an ordinary girl.
Yes.
I'm an ordinary girl.
Your Highness.
Qing'er, see you.
See you.
It seems you two get along well.
Looks like you've persuaded your mother.
Anyway,
we've finally overcome all the difficulties.
Not really.
Don't you know the family rules of the Song family?
What family rules?
Have a guess.
I don't remember your family has family rules.
Wait.
Don't come over.
How can you throw it at me?
How dare you!
Stop!
Don't run.
Catch me.
Uncle Dai, where is my father?
Mr. Song has gone to the Dean's Room.
My father is not here.
Let's go see your mother first.
Mrs. Song has gone to the academy.
Why is my mother in the academy?
She said she wanted to take a walk around the Women's Academy.
Thank you, Uncle Dai.
My mother never went to the academy before.
It's okay. Let's split up and find them.
Brother, where's Mother?
She just left.
Just left?
Where did he go?
I don't know.
It's strange.
My parents won't be away from home for long.
They're neither in the hall nor at the study.
I didn't see them in the bedroom, either.
Where else can they go?
There's one place we haven't been to.
Family Instructions of the Songs
Honey.
Thank you for helping me do it.
I know what Juntang meant to you.
He had no any family members.
You two grew up together.
We always saw him as a member of our family.
Darling, let's eat.
Okay.
Yueniang.
Father, Mother.
What are you doing here?
What? Can't we be here?
Why are you avoiding us?
We're not.
Your father and I are eating here
because it's quiet here.
Eating here
can bring us please.
Right, Darling?
It's peace. It can bring us peace.
The two words mean the same thing.
Mr. Song.
Mrs. Song.
I know
you are testing me.
Your Highness.
Since you know it,
let's be frank.
You are from the royal family while the Songs are ordinary people.
We're from different social classes.
Yueniang is not one of the very ladylike girls.
If she marries into your family,
I don't think it'll be good for her.
If in your family,
she is always unhappy and restricted,
I'd let her stay in the Song family for the rest of her life
rather than let her be your wife.
Your Highness.
I know you're a wonderful man.
But you're from the royal family so you can't do everything you want to do.
If I let you two get married, it may cause you two big trouble.
Mr. Song, Mrs. Song.
Listen to me.
I'm willing to give up my title as viscount
for Yueniang.
Really?
Yes.
I will be with Yueniang forever
and work as a teaching assistant in Yiyang Academy for the rest of my life.
Mr. Song, Mrs. Song, you may rest assured.
As long as you agree to marry Yueniang to me,
I will treat her well.
I'll only marry her in my life.
We'll be together forever
until death do us part.
Your Highness.
This is serious.
You have to honor your promise.
Let me vow in front of the memorial tablets of the ancestors
of the Song family and Mr. Chen.
I, Chen Yan,
will only marry Song Zhu in my life
and I won’t let her suffer any injustice.
I'll let her live happily.
If I break my promise,
let me be struck by lightning and die.
That's too much.
Get up.
Mr. Song, Mrs. Song.
Can you
trust me now?
Try this.
Is it good?
Yes.
This is for you.
You made it?
You know I'm not good at my embroidery.
I bought it.
Whether it's made by you or bought,
I'll take it and like it
even if it's poison.
Can I refuse to take it?
No.
Put it on.
Wait.
Can I refuse to put it on?
No. Come back.
I don't want to put it on.
Come back.
I won't put it on.
Yan.
Turn around.
Smile.
Look, how handsome you are.
Do you like it?
No?
You said you would take it even if it's poison.
You're a liar.
Well.
I...
I don't like its color.
Yan.
I have something to discuss with you.
I'd like to
visit the Xiao family some day.
I think we need to do that.
Let's go tomorrow.
What did you eat?
Yueniang.
Nothing.
An important guest is here.
Father wants you to go to the study.
Can't you keep the guest company?
Why do I have to be there?
You'd better go to the study now.
Yan, go with me.
Let's go.
Father.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is Uncle Xiao's son,
Xiao Yu.
Mr. Xiao.
This is my daughter, Song Zhu.
Father, is he here to...
This is your business.
Take care of it yourselves.
Yan, it's inappropriate for you to go in.
Why?
I'm still engaged to him.
It is between me and Mr. Xiao.
It has nothing to do with you.
Even without you,
I would also break off the engagement.
So I want to handle it myself.
Fine.
I'll wait for you at the door.
Hello, Mr. Xiao.
Now I see you.
You don't look like the real Xiao Yu.
What?
Nothing.
Actually,
I have something to discuss with you.
Please go ahead.
Do you remember
our engagement made in our childhood?
I came today
to discuss with you about the marriage certificate.
My father and mother will come in a few days.
No.
I...
I didn't mean that.
Lady Zhu, what are you doing this for?
I was so lucky
to be born into the Song family.
In the Song family, we respect the elderly
and men and women are equal.
My father opened the Women's Academy
because
he believes in gender equality.
He has also proven
that men and women are truly equal.
Although I don't like reading the Four Books and the Five Classics,
I love reading romantic novels.
Those novels
are stories about freedom.
And the freedom to love whomever one wants to love
is the most important kind of freedom.
However, a marriage certificate
will make two people lose that freedom
and make them stuck
in the marriage forever.
When one mistake is made,
it will lead to another mistake.
Then the couple will be miserable.
So?
So I think
if two people have never met each other before,
their engagement made by others
should be made invalid.
Otherwise,
both of them
will lose their freedom
and their lives will be ruined.
So you want to break off the engagement?
Mr. Xiao.
[To Xiao Chuanzhong]
This is a letter my father wrote to Uncle Xiao.
It’s about our decision to break off the engagement.
My parents told me
you were different from other girls.
I didn't expect you to be so special.
I hope you can understand my decision.
Do you remember what it was like
when we met here for the first time?
Why are you here?
At that time, I was still Xiao Yu.
If Xiao Yu
doesn't agree to break off the engagement,
what should we do?
We'll go see him tomorrow.
What if he still refuses to break off the engagement?
Then let's elope.
Elope?
Yes.
We'll tell him
no matter what happens,
we will never break up.
Okay.
Don't go back on your word.
♫In the ancient road♫
♫Parting is hidden in the fields♫
♫There's no green grass through this journey of 10 miles♫
♫The breeze♫
♫Is so gentle while I'm drinking wine♫
Mr. Xiao.
♫The setting sun♫
♫Seems slightly burnt while I'm thinking about the past♫
Mr. Xiao.
♫I got rid of the sorrows that had made me frown♫
♫Why not♫
♫Just ride a horse to travel around the world and laugh happily?♫
♫I sang in the fields and knew that the journey was long and the mountains were high♫
Miss Song Zhu.
♫I could only watch you leave and listen to the neighing of horses and roaring of tigers♫
I hope this letter finds you well.
It's an honor for me that we used to be engaged.
♫I've had a few happy moments with you♫
You brothers told me
♫But there were also many sad moments for parting♫
the stories between you and Chen Yan.
♫I sang in the fields and had endured many hardships♫
I'm so envious of you two.
Knowing you're in love with someone else,
♫I don't know when we'll meet again, and maybe we'll no longer be young by then♫
I'd like to quit.
As a bystander,
♫Get a pot of sweet tea to comfort my confidant in the journey♫
I wish you all the best.
♫It's just perfect♫
From Xiao Yu.
I'm finally free from that engagement.
I'm free!
♫In the ancient road♫
♫Parting is hidden in the fields♫
♫There's no green grass through this journey of 10 miles♫
♫The breeze♫
♫Is so gentle while I'm drinking wine♫
Close your eyes.
♫The setting sun♫
♫Seems slightly burnt while I'm thinking about the past♫
♫I got rid of the sorrows that had made me frown♫
♫Why not♫
♫Just ride a horse to travel around the world and laugh happily?♫
♫I sang in the fields and knew that the journey was long and the mountains were high♫
The new semester in the Yiyang Academy has started!
♫I could only watch you leave and listen to the neighing of horses and roaring of tigers♫
♫I've had a few happy moments with you♫
The new semester in the Yiyang Academy has started!
♫But there were also many sad moments for parting♫
♫I sang in the fields and had endured many hardships♫
♫I don't know when we'll meet again, and maybe we'll no longer be young by then♫
♫Get a pot of sweet tea to comfort my confidant in the journey♫
♫It's just perfect♫
Who is this gentleman?
♫I look back and my dream has come true today♫
I'm your Chen Yan.
♫It has nothing to do with the wind or the moon or anything else♫
I'm here to marry you.
♫The delightful noise♫
♫On the road cannot make me remember the past♫
What are you doing?
This is my wife.
♫Let's take a look at the banana trees in the rain♫
When you're in Song's Academy,
don't try to hit on her.
♫Hope we can meet again and laugh heartily♫
You're so annoying.
♫Is it good?♫
Great.
Yeah! We're married!