I KILL U
EPISODE FIVE
ROADKILL
Hey, my lovely sister
is struggling too much.
Instead of many hotel doors,
why do you come here?
Hey, you crazy bastard!
I'm not Jiyeon Han!
Your multiple personality
symptoms are getting worse.
I will treat you quickly, so come up.
You, son of a bitch!
How pathetic you are!
Have you caught her yet?
I am sorry.
Because Mr. Han came in
and stirred things up...
This is a power of attorney
for stock transfer.
Read it.
If you go to jail this time...
...It'll take some time to come out.
Until then, I will be running
our company well.
While you diligently pay for your sins,
I become a president.
It's good for each other.
It's good for you to
fulfill your sentence...
...and good for me to save
the company you ruined.
How is it?
I got it.
I'll give it all up.
Really?
If you take me directly
to the prosecution instead,
I'll sign it in front of you.
Hey, why do you sign it there?
Just end it now.
If you sign here now,
I will carry you out on my back.
Uh?
How is it?
It's good?
Deputy manager Han!
Oh, Director Yoon?
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
Because you don't let me meet my sister,
I've come to finish it by myself.
But why are you here?
Deputy manager Han!
I told you to get some air
and go up quietly.
This young bastard
really doesn't listen to me.
What?
What a fucking bastard...
Ouch!
You bastard!
Shit.
Hold him.
Piece of shit!
You bastard!
Holy shit!
Do not come!
Don't come, motherfucker!
Go away!
You, motherfucker!
Damn it.
Oh, damn it!
What the fuck!
Don't come, you bastard!
Shit!
Don't come, you fucking shit!
Don't come...
Fuck you!
Shit.
Son of a bitch!
Hey, Mr. Han!
You fucking bastard!
You need a reality check first.
You can't change your bloodline
no matter what.
There is no way the Chairman
would hand over the company...
...to nobody like you.
No! No!
What is this?
That is...
Stake! It's a stake.
Jiyeon decided to hand it over to me.
Jiyeon...
Oh my, why did the young lady
make such an empty promise...
...to make your heart flutter?
No!
Hey!
You are the one...
...who filmed it with a hidden camera...
...and handed it over
to the prosecution, right?
Since the response was lukewarm,
you sent it to an influencer, right?
Hey! Hey, slow down!
No, it's just a beast!
What a bullshit, they are human!
Hey, stop!
Go go go! Let's do roadkill!
Hey, you idiot!
Do you know how serious
things have become...
...because of your pranks?
Because you made many people difficult,
you have to pay the price too, right?
Director Yoon, please!
If you listened to me earlier,
you wouldn't die.
Director Yoon! No, no, no! Sir!
It's my fault.
I think I did something wrong.
I made a big mistake, huh?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Motherfucker,
you have no sincerity to the end.
Ugh, these damn bastards.
Hey Miranda!
Did you drag this bastard in?
No!
Did you think he would take over
the company in the future?
So you tested the water?
No.
It's unfair that you think that way.
How could I betray you?
Hey!
Get this bitch and
these bodies out of here.
Director Yoon!
It's not me! It's so unfair!
Save me! Please!
Pull this bitch out and bring it quick.
Yes.
Director Yoon, I didn't!
Please save me! I feel so unfair!
- Come on!
- Let go!
- Director Yoon, please save me!
- Come on!
No, Director Yoon! Help me!
Hey Ms. Kang!
If you had gotten there on time,
we wouldn't have suffered like this.
You crazy bastard.
However you killed many like this,
do you think your plan will work?
Release this quickly.
You still don't understand the situation.
What?
Yes.
What happened?
Are you done?
It's in progress now.
Still?
Why is it taking so long
to deal with that bitch?
It's over soon.
The ice must be made
with Blue Lagoon from Laos...
...because that's my favorite.
All right.
Put her on.
Jiyeon Han!
Was this all planned with this guy?
Why?
How naive you are.
What?
Well, that's why you live like a beggar.
You were fooled by what I said...
...and be a volunteer to
be Jiyeon and go to die.
Was my acting realistic?
It was so fucking hard
to pretend to be nice.
Jiyeon Han!
What on earth do you want?
Why do I have to become you and die?
Hey Sunwoo!
I've been unlucky since
the first time I saw you.
If you have brains, think about it.
I feel dirty even seeing someone
wearing the same clothes.
How would you feel seeing
someone looking the same?
Have you ever heard of Doppelgangers?
There must be at least one
looking just like me in this world.
But when those two meet,
one of the two is said to die.
So how uncomfortable do I feel?
If one of them has to die,
of course, it's you, not me.
You gonna die, so I'll tell you one more.
When you came to the villa,
do you know why we did that
instead of killing you right away?
Even I changed my clothes too.
It's a kind of spiritual ritual.
Only by doing so, I can avoid the curse
of the person who dies instead.
A certain monk once told me before.
Isn't it funny?
Jiyeon Han!
You're such a psychopath.
Was that the only reason I need die?
You are going die,
so don't try to know more.
Hey, Director Yoon!
I'm listening.
It was a short time but
I've become attached to her.
Otherwise, we could have been best friends.
So send her off in ecstasy.
Ah!
When this is over,
bring my bracelet from her.
That's expensive.
It's a limited edition.
All right.
You just leave this to me...
...and prepare for departure, please.
OKay! See you later.
Sir!
Here is the drug.
Go far away and bury the bodies cleanly.
Yes, I will take care of it.
I should have finished this earlier.
Do you understand the situation now?
I'm telling you this because
you are going to die soon.
Ms. Han is a real crazy bitch.
There's nothing she can't do
when she's on the drug.
She even hunts people for fun.
Hey, you're driving
like a maniac after drugs.
Speed up!
It's like fucking 4D!
I'm excited and running!
What the fuck is that?
Huh?
Isn't that a person?
Hey, that's not a person.
Hey, slow down!
No! It's just a beast!
What a bullshit, they are human!
- Hey! Stop!
- Brake! Brake!
Stop!
Go! Go! Go! Let's go roadkill!
Are you crazy?
Fuck you, they're human!
You hit people, Jiyeon!
You fucking shit! Shut up!
I've been in a good mood for a long time,
but you ruined it.
Damn unlucky.
Grandpa!
I can't go to jail until the end.
I would rather die here than go to jail.
Oh my princess, don't worry.
Your grandpa
would never let you go to jail.
I'll take care of everything.
Really? Uh?
Grandpa! You won't abandon me, right?
Hey, why would I abandon my pretty puppy?
Two people died.
This time it would be
at least 10 years no matter how.
So I called you.
How can I let her go to jail?
I'm 70 and if she goes to jail,
our business is over.
Seokhyun...
Yes, sir!
Why don't you think of a way?
If you just figure it out,
10 million is yours.
Are you going to kill me with that?
Was it your plan to kill me with drugs?
You were unlucky.
While looking for a way,
I happened to see something surprising.
Get on and be careful!
Get on board.
At first, I doubted my eyes.
Sunwoo Kang, a real doppelganger appeared.
So I came up with an idea.
This is Jiyeon, would you say hello?
Killing Sunwoo Kang
on behalf of Jiyeon Han.
I am sorry.
How?
Because Jiyeon is a druggie
that the whole world knows about,
dying from a drug
overdose seems quite natural...
...even in her hotel's secret club.
WHY IS EVERYONE JUDGING ME?
JUST OPENING MY EYES IS EXHAUSTING NOW
Just like that,
Jiyeon disappears from the world...
...and...
...Jiyeon is reborn
into Sunwoo Kang's life.
It's kind of like a fairy tale.
A cruel fairy tale.
You are crazy!
What will you do about
her being reborn as me?
Would I have done something without a plan?
You never know how much
Chairman Han's slush fund is.
A huge amount of gold
has all been laundered...
...and is heading to Boracay beach by now.
It is good for the company
that was going bankrupt.
In any case, all the assets
will go to Jiyeon as is.
Nonsense!
However...
...there's one thing I missed.
I never dreamed...
...you are good at fighting.
How much money do you get paid...
...to be a servant of that immature kid?
Servant?
Money does matter, why not?
My cell phone!
What kind of contact are you getting?
Hey!
What shall you do?
Your mother has just passed away.
That's good.
You can see her soon.
Sister, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Let's go out.
Sister!
Your cell phone is here.
I found it.
Thank you.
Sister!
Where are you going?
We need to go out.
I have work to do first.
What to do?
Where are you going, sister?
This isn't the exit, but the club.
This is not the way out...
You wait here.
Jiyeon Han!
Why are you showing up now?
What the fuck?
It's so fucking hard to see you.
Long time no see.
How was Blue Lagoon?
Was it good?
The ice quality is killing me.
Killing you?
Ah! I was almost killed, fuck!
You crazy bitch.
Hey, give me your cell phone!
Why?
Give it to me.
It's been a while since we met,
I'll give you a video to commemorate.
Hey.
Hey, wake up!
Hello, influencer!
Sunwoo! How did you get out?
Jiyeon Han!
You should get scolded by me.
I KILL U
Han Ji-yeon!
You should get scolded by me.
You piece of trash!
Villa?
Damn it!
Don't be too surprised.
You brought this on yourself.
You said doppelganger, right?
One of them must die.
But why...
...does it have to be me?
It is better for me to be a devil...
...than to die as an innocent sinner.
Shit.
Die, you bastard!
Ms. Han!
Director Yoon!
Director Yoon, shoot quickly!
- Director Yoon!
- Kill her quickly!
Kill her quickly!
Dramaday.me