♪Count down three two one♪
♪Sing you a song Do Re Me♪
♪Youth is my accelerator♪
♪With you, it works even better♪
♪Welcome you with my full armor♪
♪I can protect you forever♪
♪If you find out my secret♪
♪Will it be a shock or suprise♪
♪Smile drives away silence♪
♪Carefully measure our distance♪
♪My worries are gone because of you♪
♪And love comes very easily♪
♪When I get close to you♪
♪When I touch you♪
♪Two people make one♪
♪I have a magic power♪
♪When you are in my heart♪
♪I feel more powerful than ever♪
♪Me and you, you and me♪
♪We are natural attraction♪
♪We fall into wind and kiss the land♪
♪I have some questions♪
♪You are like a blind box♪
♪And you always give me suprises♪
♪Because it's you♪
=Cute Bodyguard=
=Episode 24=
(Will you marry me?)
(Su's Martial Club)
Mister.
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
If there's a secret
to live with your wife?
I understand.
Gu.
This is the right time for you
to learn some life saving tips.
When I was pursuing her,
as a typical guy,
I made so many mistakes.
Then how did you two
become a happy couple?
Well.
The secret is
I turned from a lone wolf
into her puppy.
I didn't know you are so wild.
Yeah. As long as she's happy,
then I'm happy.
How can I be happy?
Just spoil her.
That's the secret.
Well...
Guess I'll try.
Just do it.
It'll work.
Okay.
A man can't go onto
the battlefield untrained.
The anniversary was so successful.
We didn't even get a rest.
How about a drink?
Okay.
Let's do a cross cup.
The wine made me so hot.
Gu Rong, I'm a bit sleepy.
I'll go back to my room now.
And,
wear your clothes properly at home.
You might catch a cold.
Good night.
I even did that.
Am I not tempting enough?
Is it my problem
or hers?
You just made the posture.
But there wasn't any practical effort.
It wasn't working.
What practical effort can I make?
Do you know what I was like?
Be confident, Mr. Gu.
Girls love guys
who are initiative.
It won't work
if you are indecisive.
Xie Te. Listen.
If Jingjing doesn't agree to marry me,
you have to postpone your wedding.
What? Why?
I mean,
even if she doesn't say yes,
you still can't ruin
our happiness.
We've bought the wedding dress,
booked the hotel,
and sent out the invitations.
I don't care.
Our wedding
has to be earlier than yours.
What?
Marriage is between the two of you.
You need to ask
Su Jingjing about her will.
I can't make the decision for her.
It's settled then.
How is it settled?
How do I know what she's thinking?
All I can think of
is to be sincere.
Sincere?
Am I not sincere enough to her?
That's true.
Where is Xie Te?
Mr. Gu has a business event.
Xie Te will come later.
I'll talk to Gu Rong about
this when I'm home.
How can he call Xie Te away
from something so important?
It's okay.
I'm just here to collect the dress
and try on the makeup.
You can have a look
and see if there's
anything else we need.
Leave it to me.
I'll make sure you're
the most beautiful bride.
The prettiest.
Ai Mi.
That dress you just tried on
is beautiful.
Xie Te picked it for me.
It took us a long time
to find this shop.
Look around.
They have many beautiful dresses here.
I see.
These dresses suit you well.
Maybe you should have a try.
I think I'll pass.
Just have a try. We came all the way.
The dress would look different
when you have it on.
This one just came in.
You can try it on.
Yeah. Then we'll know what kind of dress
suits you best when you get married.
You're sure it's not too much trouble?
No.
Come on.
Okay.
Ai Mi. Why is the light off?
Ai Mi? Ai...
♪When I see you♪
♪Warm wind suddenly becomes gentle♪
♪After sunset, the sky is full of stars♪
♪I lose to your smile♪
♪Love is tender and stubborn♪
♪You'll get it when you fall into it♪
♪Even if there are bumps along the way♪
♪I'll never step back♪
♪In my eyes, no matter how crowded♪
♪Only your face is in my heart♪
♪Be part of your life♪
♪With love, there's no ordinary♪
♪I'll accompany you along the way♪
♪Dreams will never fail♪
♪I just want to hold you in my arms♪
♪Even for a second and a minute♪
♪Common fireworks in the world♪
♪Make a difference because of you♪
♪If love is not deep enough♪
♪I will wait♪
♪To let you know♪
(You can't hear me.)
(But can't you even see?)
You caught on my clothes.
Miss.
This is not a smart way
to get my attention.
Your attention?
Do you think I'd want to talk to you
if you didn't tear my clothes?
Su Jingjing.
Wash the teacups, too.
(You've never played this before?)
(I know how I feel about her.)
(I don't have to worry about anything)
(when I'm with her.)
(I don't have to play the role
as Gu Zhenhua's grandson.)
(I don't have to play the role)
(as the only successor of the Gu Group.)
(I can just be myself,)
(as Gu Rong.)
(A compensation for you. You're welcome.)
(You are right, mister.)
(I'm his bodyguard.)
If you go hard on him,
I'll have to protect him.
♪In my eyes, no matter how crowded♪
♪Only your face is in my heart♪
♪Be part of your life♪
♪With love, there's no ordinary♪
♪I'll accompany you along the way♪
♪Dreams will never fail♪
♪I just want to hold you in my arms♪
♪Even for a second and a minute♪
♪Common fireworks in the world♪
♪Make a difference because of you♪
♪If love is not deep enough♪
(I'm pursuing Ms. Su.)
♪To let you know♪
Do you know who I am?
Yeah. You are Gu Rong.
♪When I see you♪
♪Warm wind suddenly becomes gentle♪
♪After sunset, the sky is full of stars♪
(You kissed me.)
But Gu Rong made his efforts
to let me see a different
version of him.
(He would go jogging
with my dad in the morning.)
(He would practice
martial arts with my dad.)
(He would eat buns for only 1.5 yuan each)
(with my dad.)
(He enrolled members for my mom.)
(Sometimes,)
(he would also help
Uncle Li next door to walk the dog.)
(He no longer shows off his money,)
(or holds his head high.)
He takes care of other's feeling,
and loves everyone around him.
This version of him.
Why can't he stay with me?
(From today,)
(you, Su Jingjing,)
(are my girlfriend.)
♪To let you know♪
The lipstick package.
(First prize)
The purchase for free for one day.
And the vending machine
which is full of secret figures.
They are all made by Mr. Gu, right?
Don't be angry.
Because I think
you didn't pass the application.
♪I'll accompany you along the way♪
♪Dreams will never fail♪
You are not mad?
No.
Thank you, Gu Rong.
I extremely love all you have done.
I should thank you.
For what?
Thank you
for giving me my grand prize.
Jingjing.
You are the surprise of my life.
Marry me.
- Say yes.
Sometimes you are not very funny,
or very cute.
But I don't know when it started.
All I can see is you.
All I can think of is you.
Yes.
♪Nothing else matters♪
♪Pretend to be arrogant to others♪
♪But I just want the coquetry to you♪
♪The heartbeat of both of us♪
♪The emotional page of the manuscript♪
♪I will treasure it forever♪
♪It is nice as long as I have you♪
♪Nothing else matters♪
♪Pretend to be arrogant to others♪
Why are you so nervous?
This is once in a lifetime.
Of course I'm nervous.
♪The emotional page of the manuscript♪
♪I will treasure it forever♪
Why are you two crying so hard?
Mr. Gu said we could only get married
after you two.
You said yes to him.
There's hope for us now.
Why did you say that? Childish.
Jingjing.
We are getting married
on the sixth of next month.
What about you?
Next Monday then.
What's the rush?
How is that a rush?
I have to get it done
as soon as possible.
What if you change your mind?
Okay then.
Su Jingjing.
I'll be good to you forever.
Okay.
One more.
(Not to be loved by all people,
but to be your special)
Look at my ideas.
Look at the theme.
So romantic.
The blue starry sky.
I even got the couple's name ready.
We'll be called Ai Te.
Show me.
I designed this for Ai Mi.
Please don't copy my ideas.
Give it here.
So this is what you got
(Wedding of Xie Te and Ai Mi)
after all these days?
It's not any good?
I tried my very best.
Mr. Gu,
a wedding is a very personal thing.
What Ai Mi likes
is probably not
Su Jingjing's cup of tea.
That's why I have reached out
to the best wedding
design team in Ninghai.
I told them
Jingjing's preferences.
They'll design the wedding
in the auditorium,
the banquet in the hotel,
the fireworks show and the band
based on your needs.
I even hired
the most popular
makeup artist for celebrities.
They'll realize every dream
a girl has for her wedding.
Good.
Xie Te, you are getting
better at your job.
I'm honored.
But
I need to keep an eye on everything
and make sure nothing goes wrong.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sweet Su.
Did you put the sticker
(Happiness)
on the door?
Yeah.
And the red strings.
Did you tie them on the tree?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
Is there anything else?
The lamps. One, two, three, four, five.
Nothing wrong with that.
Right.
And at the entrance.
There are five more
outside the door, right?
Yeah. Don't worry.
That's right.
Another thing.
When is the makeup artist coming?
And the full dress.
When are they bringing
the full dress and wedding dress?
When are we going to the hotel?
Did you arrange that?
Yeah, yeah.
You've asked me so many times.
It's all arranged. Don't worry.
Really?
Yes.
My feeling is so complicated now.
There're so many things to do.
But I still feel so empty inside.
Dad, mom.
Jingjing.
You don't have to do this.
Just go upstairs.
Put on a facial mask.
I'll come up later
to give you a massage.
Have a bath.
Get a night of good sleep.
Go to the wedding tomorrow
with your best self.
You are crying.
Don't cry.
She's moved.
You know what?
Everybody says
a woman is most beautiful
on her wedding day.
That's a memory of your life.
Just be a beautiful bride
tomorrow.
Make sure everything goes as planned.
Jingjing, don't listen to your mom.
Let me tell you.
A woman is always beautiful
as long as she married the right person.
Look at your mom.
I think she's more beautiful
than yesterday.
I think mom is beautiful
every day.
My baby girl.
Hurry up.
Go put on a facial mask.
I'll come up later.
Just go.
Do it.
Okay.
Sweet Su.
Our daughter is getting married.
(Happiness)
Is it real?
I feel like I'm dreaming.
For me,
she's still like a child.
She said to me every night,
"mommy, mommy,"
"you'll take my hand"
"and sing for me,"
"so I can fall asleep."
She was so cute.
How did she grow up so fast?
She's getting married.
I don't know if she knows this or not.
My biggest wish
is for her
to be happy
all her life.
This is the most important.
She will, right?
Yes.
She will.
Dear.
Thank you.
Thank you for giving me
such a good daughter.
Thank you.
(Names for great-grandchildren)
The groom is nervous?
I'm not.
I just came down to see
what you are doing.
I watched you grow up, remember?
You can't hide it from me.
You are practicing calligraphy
in the middle of the night?
I'm not practicing.
I'm thinking of names
for my great-grandchildren.
Grandpa, the wedding is tomorrow.
Isn't it too early to give names?
No.
The earlier, the better.
Okay then.
I'm going to bed.
Wait.
I haven't finished yet.
We are the only two people
in this family.
I've always wanted you to get married.
It'd look magnificent.
You're getting married tomorrow.
I'm so happy.
Grandpa,
thank you for all those years.
I don't have any other expectations
of you.
I just hope you can
make our family bigger.
Tell Jingjing to have many children.
I can't do that, grandpa.
Why not?
You're going to be a husband.
Why are you blushing?
I'm not.
I already got five names.
Look.
Here.
Gu Nianan.
Gu Zhaoyan.
Gu Jiming.
Have some sympathy for Gu Rong.
Five here.
Have many children.
Please.
Thank you.
Five might be too many.
Put it here.
Okay.
This way.
(Su's Martial Club)
Hurry up.
Here it comes.
It's ready.
Here.
Have some wedding candies.
Wedding candies are here.
Aunt, you are here.
Careful.
So beautiful.
Isn't it pretty?
Yeah.
Gu.
Today,
I'm handing my daughter to you.
Be good to her.
Rest assured, Mister, Ma'am.
I'll take care of her.
Well.
Why do I feel like crying
on a happy day like this?
Sweet Su.
Today is our daughter's wedding day.
You can't cry.
Don't cry.
Dad and mom won't cry.
We won't.
Don't cry.
Mister, Ma'am.
We're going to the auditorium.
We'll see you later in the hotel, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Be good.
See you later, mom and dad.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
Don't hurry.
Here.
Take care of her.
Don't worry, Ma'am.
Take care.
Master.
Just go. I'll handle it here.
I'm nervous.
Why nervous?
I'm nervous too.
This is once in a lifetime.
My parents were crying.
Our parents.
Fine, Mr. Sweet words.
Don't worry.
I won't let them down.
I'll be good to you forever.
Let me check your makeup.
What happened?
What's wrong?
I'll have a look, Mr. Gu.
What happened?
Mr. Gu, we have a flat tire.
How can that happen?
We won't make it to the auditorium.
Why does something go wrong
on the first day of our marriage?
Don't say that.
Nothing will go wrong.
What now?
I have an idea.
What is it?
We're not going to the auditorium.
We just got on the road.
And compared to the auditorium,
I think Su's Martial Club
means more for us.
Think about it.
We have so many memories there,
whether it's good or bad.
I think it's more meaningful
to have the wedding
in the martial club than the auditorium.
Right?
How do we get back?
This way, please.
Hurry up, Chief He.
We're running out of time.
In a second.
You're here.
Welcome.
If you think
it's not lively enough there,
I can play
The Moon Mirrored in the Pool.
I can guarantee
it'll be touching.
Touching?
Spare us.
The bride and groom are here.
They are here.
Here they come.
Here.
They are coming.
That's their bike.
Look at them two.
Good.
(Su's Martial Club)
(Yes. This is my wedding.)
(There is no banquet.)
(No auditorium.)
(No band.)
(But there are my neighbors.)
(And there is Su's Martial Club)
(that witnessed my life and my love.)
(Su's Martial Club)
It's so beautiful.
Let's begin.
Okay. Mr. Gu Rong. Ms. Su Jingjing.
The wedding begins now.
Yeah.
The first bow for heaven and earth.
First, for heaven.
May it grant you conjugal bliss.
Yeah.
Second, for the earth.
May it give you good fortune.
Yeah.
Third, for heaven and earth.
May it bind you two together.
The second bow for parents.
First, for their nurture.
Yeah.
Second, for their love and care.
Third, for the parents.
May the grace live on forever.
Yeah.
The third bow for each other.
First, for harmony.
Yeah.
♪You are my good mood♪
Second, for offspring.
Yeah.
Third, for everlasting.
The ceremony is finished. Serve the tea.
The tea is here.
Time to serve the tea.
Here.
Grandpa, your tea.
Take this.
Time for tea.
Grandpa,
your tea.
Yeah.
Don't forget your mission.
Okay. Good boy.
Okay.
Dad, mom, your tea.
Mom, your tea.
Your red envelope.
Take this.
A daughter is the
sweetest gift for her dad.
Don't cry, my girl.
Kid, if Jingjing does anything wrong
in the future,
don't treat her badly.
Take her back to me,
I'll tell her, okay?
Okay.
He wouldn't dare.
If he treats her badly,
I'll be the first to give him a lesson.
Come on. Hurry up.
Now you may enter the bridal chamber.
There's someone making trouble.
Someone objects.
The brother.
Brother, your tea.
He's nervous.
That's more like it.
You have to give him a red envelope.
That's for sure.
But, as your brother,
I need to tell you one thing.
If you dare bully Jingjing,
I won't go easy on you.
Don't worry.
She's way stronger.
Funny guy.
Time is gold.
Hurry up.
Jingjing, Gu Rong agreed
to give me five great-grandchildren.
You got to complete the mission.
Please.
I didn't say that.
Grandpa got the names ready.
Hurry up.
Just go.
To the bridal chamber.
In-law.
Grandpa of Gu.
No, no.
Bridal chamber in broad daylight?
Is that proper?
I just heard someone
promised grandpa with five children.
Won't that tire you out?
It's kind of hot here.
You are hot?
♪It is nice as long as I have you♪
It hurts!
Don't move.
Come in here.
Ouch!
♪I will treasure it forever♪
♪Keep it forever♪
♪True love takes
a little bit of cooking♪
♪To give it a sweet taste♪
♪Your gentle smile♪
♪Is the best ingredient♪
♪Happiness is tangible♪
♪When you take my hand
and walk through the crowd♪
♪I want to use adhesive strips♪
♪to firmly stick each other's love♪
♪I'm the inaccessible exception♪
♪You're the only accident♪
♪I love you so much♪
♪I want to go anywhere with you♪
♪Believe me it's true♪
♪I feel the most myself before you♪
♪I don't need to hide anything♪
♪I'm always anticipating♪
♪In a future with you♪
♪It is our fairy tale♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪Let's look foward to♪
♪The view on the journey♪
♪And every little detail♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪Carefully♪
♪Sew you into my life♪
♪I love you♪