♪Count down three two one♪
♪Sing you a song Do Re Me♪
♪Youth is my accelerator♪
♪With you, it works even better♪
♪Welcome you with my full armor♪
♪I can protect you forever♪
♪If you find out my secret♪
♪Will it be a shock or suprise♪
♪Smile drives away silence♪
♪Carefully measure our distance♪
♪My worries are gone because of you♪
♪And love comes very easily♪
♪When I get close to you♪
♪When I touch you♪
♪Two people make one♪
♪I have a magic power♪
♪When you are in my heart♪
♪I feel more powerful than ever♪
♪Me and you, you and me♪
♪We are natural attraction♪
♪We fall into wind and kiss the land♪
♪I have some questions♪
♪You are like a blind box♪
♪And you always give me suprises♪
♪Because it's you♪
=Cute Bodyguard=
=Episode 8=
(What did we do last night?)
(Su's Martial Club)
Mom, I'm back.
Jingjing.
Mom.
Our house is cramped enough.
Why is there
a huge telescope here?
Someone sent it here.
Said that he brought it back
from the park for Gu Rong.
(Is that all you want?)
(What's wrong with it?)
(I just want to see it with him.)
(In the park.)
(On the stone stairs.)
(How romantic will it be)
(if I can sit there with him)
(watching the meteor shower?)
(If only we had a telescope.)
(That'd be even greater.)
No matter what,
thank you.
Don't flatter yourself.
I just changed my schedule
and wanted to go to the park.
It's got nothing to do with you.
(Since when has he)
(become so strange?)
(He clearly wanted to
watch the meteor shower with me.)
(He just wouldn't admit it.)
(What's wrong with me?)
(Why would I care about)
(this annoying guy so much?)
Thank you for the medicine.
You're welcome.
Why are you putting that on your face?
What do you know?
This is an emergency trick.
So I can be all pretty
at the dinner party.
Only plastic surgery
can save your face.
I think you should just give up.
Whatever you say.
I won't let someone like you
ruin my mood.
Bright red.
Cherry pink.
Cameo brown.
Which will he like?
He will like none.
Did I ask you?
How would you know what he likes?
I'll dress up all pretty.
When I show up at the dinner party,
everyone will know
that I'm his girlfriend.
And all the other clueless women
will stay away from him.
I'm afraid you are the only one
who's clueless.
Stop smiling.
You got the mask in your mouth.
Calm down.
Don't get mad with him.
It only gives you wrinkles.
(Xie Te)
Xie Te.
Whatever you do,
get me an invitation
of the dinner party
of Han Ran's publishing company
before tonight.
The invitation
of his dinner party?
Mr. Gu.
What if the chairman notices
what you're doing?
No questions.
I'm your boss.
Get it straight.
Miss Bai.
Thank God it's you.
It'd be over for me if it was Chief He.
Mr. Gu is going to the dinner party
of a publishing company?
That's news.
I know he likes sculpture.
Since when has he
got interested in literature?
I don't really know.
Okay. You can go.
I'll get the invitation.
But what am I supposed to tell Mr. Gu?
Don't worry.
I know what to say.
Thank you, Miss Bai.
(Dinner party?)
Didn't you come too early?
When will Mr. Zhang be here?
Just wait for a while.
Are you in a hurry?
Don't worry. I'm here.
Gu Rong.
Anrou, why are you here?
Xie said you'll be here.
I'm afraid that something will go wrong
in a place like this.
So I'm here to accompany you.
It's about time. Let's go.
Have you thought about the trip?
You said you wanted to go to Iceland.
Now is the best time to go.
You can check this out if you have time.
Let's go.
Thank you. Change of plan.
I'm not going there.
Cheers.
Yeah? I think it's pretty interesting.
Long time no see, Mr. Li.
Mr. Wang.
Try this, Jingjing.
You might like this.
Okay.
Is it good?
Han.
Is this your girlfriend?
Nice girl you got there.
You two caught my eye
as soon as I got in.
Such a perfect pair.
Mr. Zhang, you misunderstood.
This girl can't be my girlfriend.
So she is...
She's my junior sister.
We grew up together.
She's more important than
a girlfriend. She's family.
Family?
Family...
Of course she can't be
Han Ran's girlfriend.
Because I'm pursuing Miss Su.
♪A breeze blew over that night♪
♪Created sweetness♪
♪Listen silently to your heartbeat♪
♪Gentle breath♪
♪Time flies♪
♪Time stops. I look at you in the eye♪
She's not Han Ran's girlfriend?
What are you doing?
Asking you for a dance.
Stop it. I don't know how.
You are the only one who can touch me.
So you have to dance with me. Come.
♪Listen through the ends of your hair♪
♪Every cell of mine♪
♪Says to love you♪
♪I'm sure and confirm♪
♪How firm I love you♪
Can I ask you for a dance?
My honor.
Sorry.
It's okay.
You are my lady companion today.
You only need to look at me.
Miss Bai, is Mr. Gu serious?
I don't know.
Jingjing is very innocent.
I'm worried about her.
Mr. Han, even I can see
she doesn't just want to be your sister.
Since you chose to play dumb
from the start,
why would you pretend
that you care about her now?
Do you know how cruel it is
to give someone hope and then break it?
Miss Bai, Mr. Gu...
I must look like a fool today.
Why?
You look
captivating today.
I picked the dress for you, remember?
What good does it do?
I was doing everything in vain.
I have to use the bathroom.
If you really mean what you said,
I hope you can be good to her.
If you were only joking,
you should tell her immediately.
I don't want to see her getting hurt.
Is it?
But it's you who's hurting her.
Yeah, it's me.
It's my fault
for not telling her directly.
But now I have told her.
It's too late. You let it happen.
And you embarrassed her today.
Is that how
you don't want her getting hurt?
I see Jingjing as my family,
and nothing else.
That's good.
As for me, you don't
have to worry about it.
You don't want her getting hurt.
But I won't allow anyone to hurt her.
Okay. I hope you can remember
what you said today.
She's coming out soon.
She'll feel awkward seeing you.
I'll send her home tonight.
You should go.
Do you need help?
I hate these parties.
You can never eat and drink
as you want in there.
Come with me to grab something to eat.
Thank you for saving me back there.
I'm not hungry. Just go alone.
How can you not be?
You've barely eaten anything
since this morning.
I really don't want to go.
I just want to walk alone.
I can come with you.
No.
I don't want other people
to see me like this.
Nonsense.
What is there I haven't seen?
Turn right there and it's my home.
Okay.
I was rude at the party.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Maybe you are right.
If you really don't want Miss Su
to get hurt,
there's something I need to tell you.
What is it?
Gu Rong's grandpa,
the chairman of Gu Group,
he set the standards and choice
for his granddaughter-in-law long ago.
And Miss Su doesn't really
meet the standards.
Miss Bai.
I guess you are his choice, right?
Mr. Han.
Thank you for driving me home. Goodbye.
Miss Bai.
Wait a second.
I don't think Jingjing has to
worry about what you just said.
Mr. Gu is pursuing Jingjing now.
What kind of standards he has
and gets to have,
that's his business.
Miss Bai is so smart.
You should know what I mean.
Mr. Han.
Can I have your phone for a second?
Okay. Now we are even.
(100 yuan RMB)
(Nickname of Bai Anrou)
(Jingjing, about tonight, I...)
(Do you know how cruel it is)
(to give someone hope
and then break it?)
(But it's you who's hurting her.)
(It's them.)
(I have to find a way to lose them.)
I want to have barbecue.
Let's go.
Didn't you say it causes cancer?
Why would you want that now?
Let's cut them off in the front, Chief.
Let's go.
That's all.
- Thank you.
- I'll bring it soon.
Chief He would never know
that we went back here.
Do you want some drinks?
Do you know what this is?
Bomb shot?
Wrong.
Lover's tear.
Easy.
(Jingjing, I'm sorry.)
Slow down.
That's enough.
Eat something.
Hurry up.
Just like this chicken heart.
I'll cut him off
and never turn back.
Slow down.
(Senior, you bought a new car.)
(I'll stick these toys on it.)
(So they can be with you)
(when I'm not.)
(And they'll smile at you)
(when you are sad.)
I'll just drink this.
What? You brought me here to drink.
Trying to stop me is one thing.
How can you be so hesitant about this?
Drink it.
I never asked you to drink.
Just this one.
That's it. That's more like a man.
What is that?
That's it. Stop.
That's enough.
Have another go!
What?
Go where?
Okay.
That's enough.
That's enough?
That's enough happiness for today?
You are not happy.
Of course I am.
Since I got up this morning,
I exfoliated, I picked my lipstick...
I did everything within my power.
Why am I not happy?
I starved myself all day
to get into this dress.
It's so tight.
What are you doing?
This is public space.
Tell me.
Do you think I'm pretty?
Say it.
I only found out today
that I'm his family.
I'm just his family.
I don't want it.
I'm just happy. I'm not crying.
I'm happy.
Su Jingjing.
Why taking pictures of me?
Give it to me.
No.
Your senior definitely
never saw you like this.
This is who you really are.
I'm so ugly. Delete it.
No. I'll show him.
Why am I so ugly?
Senior would never like me.
That's enough.
You've had enough drink.
Let's go.
Geez. Su Jingjing!
Why are you so heavy?
Don't say that.
Okay.
We'll wait for a taxi.
I don't want a taxi. I feel sick.
Well...
Let's walk back then.
Walk?
Okay.
The other way.
Lift your feet.
Hold on to me.
These shoes don't suit you.
The other one.
We'll throw them away
and get a new pair.
♪When I see you♪
♪Warm wind suddenly becomes gentle♪
♪After sunset, the sky is full of stars♪
♪I lose to your smile♪
♪Love is tender and stubborn♪
♪You'll get it when you fall into it♪
♪Even if there are bumps along the way♪
♪I'll never step back♪
♪In my eyes, no matter how crowded♪
♪Only your face is in my heart♪
♪Be part of your life♪
♪With love, there's no ordinary♪
♪I'll accompany you along the way♪
♪Dreams will never fail♪
♪I just want to hold you in my arms♪
Why are you so heavy, Su Jingjing?
I want to ride that.
Okay.
Seesaw.
Put me down.
Okay, okay.
Seesaw.
Careful.
Mr. Li's shop is still open.
Put these on.
Go sit there.
Go.
Okay, okay.
Up. Up.
I used to love playing this.
Every day after school,
senior would bring me here
to play seesaw.
I practiced martial arts every day.
None of the kids liked me.
Only he would play with me,
and study with me.
Senior.
It's getting harder and harder
to see you.
I want to go back to when we were kids.
Senior.
Su Jingjing.
Wake up.
I'm Gu Rong, not your senior.
Why can't you understand?
He only sees you as his sister,
his family.
Liar.
I'm not his real sister.
We'll go our own ways in the future.
What else can I do
except becoming his girlfriend?
I see.
You call this love?
Are you three?
You are yelling at me.
Okay. Stop crying.
Let's go home. Okay?
Don't bully me.
Alright.
Okay. Stop crying.
Let's go home.
Don't yell at me then.
As if you were always nice to me.
I did my research.
I don't need
Thermage at all.
Thermage.
Look at you.
Can't let you drink anymore.
Let's go home.
Cheers.
No one's drinking.
Keep it down.
You are waking people up.
Keep your voice down.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
♪Life♪
- ♪is so short♪
- Keep it down.
Keep it down.
I want to drink.
Enough.
We're home.
You drank enough.
Drink.
Keep it down.
They are sleeping.
Let's go.
What now?
What do you want now?
Open up! I want plum juice.
Let's just go home.
Let's go.
Puppy.
What is it now?
My heels are gone.
Jingjing. It's not the heels.
Your high heel shoes are gone.
My shoes.
My shoes are expensive.
I need to find them.
Leave them. I'll buy you a new pair.
Buy?
Buy.
Let's go.
Jingjing. Go home.
Jingjing.
Just go home.
She's fine.
Hurry up.
She's okay.
Let's go home.
Okay. Sorry.
Sorry for the noise.
Good night, everyone.
I'm sorry.
That's enough.
Just go home.
Su Jingjing.
I can't carry you anymore.
You are so heavy.
Okay. Stop screaming.
Stop it.
What happened?
Ma'am.
She fell?
No. She had a little drink.
Drink?
How can she drink so much?
She's just like her dad.
A terrible drinker.
I...
What is it?
I need to pee.
Mom will take you there.
Jingjing. I'm mom.
Do you recognize me?
Mom.
Easy. Easy.
Okay.
Careful.
Is she okay, ma'am?
She's all settled.
You should go sleep too.
Good night.
What is it?
Senior gave me
so many blind boxes.
But I didn't get any secret figure.
Not even one.
Don't cry.
You're gonna wake up your dad.
I'll get you new ones, okay?
Stop crying.
Xie Te. Pick up.
Xie Te.
(Mr. Gu.)
Order a new batch of
blind boxes to the martial club.
To help with Ai Mi's business,
and also with the club's recruitment.
(Not to cheer Jingjing up?)
That's part of the reason.
(Okay. Thank you on behalf of Ai Mi.)
That's all.
Blind box...
Su Jingjing?
Where am I?
I...
Why am I here?
What happened last night?
I can't remember a thing.
Gu.
I'm so sorry
for the trouble last night.
It's alright.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'll wash
your shirt too.
Don't worry about it.
You don't have to do this, ma'am.
No.
You finally got up?
What did you do last night?
I...
The color of this lipstick
looks familiar.
I'm asking you a question.
I had a little drink.
♪It is nice as long as I have you♪
♪Nothing else matters♪
♪Pretend to be arrogant to others♪
♪But I just want the coquetry to you♪
♪The heartbeat of both of us♪
♪The emotional page of the manuscript♪
♪I will treasure it forever♪
♪Keep it forever♪
♪I'm the inaccessible exception♪
♪You're the only accident♪
♪I love you so much♪
♪I want to go anywhere with you♪
♪Believe me it's true♪
♪I feel the most myself before you♪
♪I don't need to hide anything♪
♪I'm always anticipating♪
♪In a future with you♪
♪It is our fairy tale♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪Let's look foward to♪
♪The view on the journey♪
♪And every little detail♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪Carefully♪
♪Sew you into my life♪
♪I love you♪