♪Count down three two one♪
♪Sing you a song Do Re Me♪
♪Youth is my accelerator♪
♪With you, it works even better♪
♪Welcome you with my full armor♪
♪I can protect you forever♪
♪If you find out my secret♪
♪Will it be a shock or suprise♪
♪Smile drives away silence♪
♪Carefully measure our distance♪
♪My worries are gone because of you♪
♪And love comes very easily♪
♪When I get close to you♪
♪When I touch you♪
♪Two people make one♪
♪I have a magic power♪
♪When you are in my heart♪
♪I feel more powerful than ever♪
♪Me and you, you and me♪
♪We are natural attraction♪
♪We fall into wind and kiss the land♪
♪I have some questions♪
♪You are like a blind box♪
♪And you always give me suprises♪
♪Because it's you♪
=Cute Bodyguard=
=Episode 20=
(Take care of both love and career)
Su Jingjing.
Where do I go
if you don't open the door?
It's locked.
What are you saying?
Get away.
My phone is on the desk.
Where's your phone?
Call someone to let us come out.
I wanted to do that. But I don't
keep my phone with me either.
(Su's Martial Club)
Gu!
The preparation
is the most difficult part.
I'll help you.
No way, mister.
Today is my one-month anniversary
with Jingjing.
I have to make this dish by myself.
Besides,
you can check it out.
This integrated cooking center
is so efficient.
It can stew, stir-fry
and steam at the same time.
It can make six dishes
and one soup in only 30 minutes.
Look.
Have a try.
That's good.
Today,
I'll give you a hand.
Just tell me what to do,
I'll do it.
You don't even know how to use a knife.
Slow down.
Parboil the ribs in the pot.
Who shouts out?
[*Similar pronunciation. Heard it wrong]
No one shouts out. Just parboil the ribs.
Put the ribs in the pot.
Yeah, push the pot and cover it.
Okay.
Nice.
Someone's locked in here.
(This is the design of SC Group.)
Are you not worried, Director Du?
Shout with me.
What does flow feel like?
The flow.
Is this the wall painting of SC Group?
I want to feel that flow.
But what does flow feel like?
The flow.
Take it.
What now?
I'll show you the flow of arts.
How did you come up with that?
Director Du, you should
tidy up the warehouse occasionally.
Maybe in the process
of tidying up this warehouse,
you'll have an idea.
How's it?
I guess I underestimated you.
Then why are you still standing there?
Let's do it together!
Come on.
Two cages of steamed buns.
Okay.
Takeout.
I'd like two vegetable buns.
Here it comes.
That's not going to work.
You can't just pour it all on the plate.
You have to lay out the pieces for it.
Pour the juice on it in the end.
That's perfect.
Okay.
Is it okay?
Nice. In just a few minutes,
you did a nice job. It smells good.
Nice, I think it's okay.
Our Jingjing has good luck.
I'll take it out then.
(Come home quickly. Emergency.)
Gu, don't worry.
Maybe Jingjing is working overtime.
Gu,
maybe let's eat and wait.
Mister, ma'am, you'll eat first.
I'll call Jingjing.
We can't eat first.
It's alright.
We'd wait for you.
(Gu Rong)
What's wrong?
No one picked up.
I am afraid something happened.
I don't think so.
Well, I'll just call again.
Don't worry.
I've never seen
anyone as crazy as you.
You tried on colors on your own clothes.
But the results are good.
Done!
Are you okay?
My ankle is twisted.
Then don't move. Don't move.
You can't move if you twist.
What should we do?
We're still locked in here.
Don't move.
If that's the price of feeling the flow,
I'm willing to take it.
What do you say?
Don't say that. Wait here.
I'm going to shout for someone.
I heard a noise right here.
I didn't realize there are people.
Director Du.
You two are having quite fun.
Indeed.
Stop chatting.
Please come and help us.
Okay.
I...
I-I wouldn't dare to touch you.
No way. My feet...
I got this. I hold it for you.
Be careful. I have broken my hand too.
Slow down.
Don't ever use your feet again.
Hurry up.
Come on, it's not a skateboard.
Be careful.
You're injured.
It's alright.
Is it painful?
Hang in there.
We'll be at the hospital in a minute.
It's alright.
Senior.
Han Ran.
What are you doing together?
(Outpatient)
How do you know senior?
We've known each other for years.
But I was out of the country
for a few years.
So I lost contact with him.
By the way,
the nurse just said
your hand is fine,
and you can leave after the transfusion.
Don't worry.
Do you want some water?
Okay.
I'll help you.
Look at me.
I don't have a third hand.
I'll help you.
Is it hot?
No.
Okay.
Have more.
What are you doing here?
I will take you home.
But senior isn't back yet.
Now that you're hurt,
you should have a good rest.
You'll have a long holiday
starting tomorrow.
Senior is here.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Will you eat it now or later?
You feed me.
You keep hungry then.
Gu Rong.
He was injured,
and I can't keep him
alone there.
I really just sent him to the hospital.
Don't get mad, okay?
Why didn't you answer the phone?
My phone is on the desk.
Then you should tell me
that you worked overtime.
By the time I knew what I was doing,
I was locked in the warehouse.
I told you it was an accident. Gu Rong.
Just listen to me. I...
Gu Rong, you...
What day is it today?
Why did my parents
make so many delicious dishes?
I don't know.
Don't be mad.
I was in the office
painting and working overtime all day,
and I was locked in the warehouse.
I didn't even eat properly.
Why don't you eat with me?
Don't you remember what day it is?
It's not your birthday.
Today is our one-month anniversary.
I forgot it.
So did you make all of these dishes?
No.
You made the dishes, right?
These are so delicious.
I did not expect that Mr. Gu
can not only work but also cook.
It's my favorite flavor.
Mr. Gu is so amazing.
Just like a Cooking Master Boy.
All right, don't get mad.
I swear.
I'll keep my phone with me at all times.
I'll never let you lose contact to me.
Look at you. You're smiling.
I'll be sure to keep contact.
Okay?
And...
Are my dishes really that good?
Very tasty.
That's the taste I will remember
even when I sleep.
The dishes taste better than those
made by my dad.
Then let me try.
Have a try.
The enrollment
of the winter vacation classes
is excellent this year.
But we don't have many rooms
left in this house.
How do we deal with
the accommodation for children?
Sweet Su, it's fine.
We can work it out.
Well...
Jingjing.
You're off work, right?
Well...
I'm back.
Look at you.
You didn't tell us
about working overtime.
Gu called you just now.
Right.
You didn't pick up the calls.
I...
He made you a table of delicious dishes.
Right.
I know.
So I came back right after work.
Let's eat.
I'll get you some rice.
Great.
What are you doing?
That's enough.
Have more.
You two go back to your rooms and rest.
Go back to your own rooms.
Be gentle.
Did they go to their own rooms?
Alright, let's go to bed.
No, why are you dragging me?
Go to bed!
This is way over the top.
It's like we are having
a secret relationship at home.
If it goes on,
it's really not good.
I've never left the martial club
or my parents since I was a kid.
When can I be independent
and have my own space?
Jingjing.
My apartment is next to the company.
Let's move out.
That's a very dangerous idea.
My dad will never agree.
Your dad...
Why does your dad have to agree?
It is okay as long as you agree.
Anyway, I'm not going to return
my secret figure.
Besides,
we each have a room.
Why don't I agree?
Mr. Gu, right?
You can rest assured.
There are plenty of rooms.
And I already have a plan.
What is it?
Why can't you understand?
Didn't mister just say
that the martial club
will be out of rooms
when the children
of winter vacation classes come?
By then,
let's try to tell mister about it.
Will it work?
We'll never know unless we try.
Okay.
Okay?
Great.
Caixia!
(Su's Martial Club)
I turned off my alarm clock again.
I'm going to be late again.
Right, mom and dad.
I have to work overtime tonight,
so I'm not going to be back for dinner.
Mister, ma'am.
And I'm not coming
back for dinner either.
I have other plans.
Jingjing.
What are you busy at lately?
Right.
I have to work overtime.
I have to work late every day.
Besides,
the street lamp at our intersection
is broken.
It's so dark every time I go home.
I almost
got hit by the scooter last time.
Right.
Do you have to work overtime?
It's not safe to come back
so late every day.
Yeah,
I just got in the design department.
I have to perform well,
so I need to work late.
And I think
our house is too far from where I work.
Right.
My girl is right.
Well... Indeed.
Then keep going.
Gu, if you are busy,
then I'll pick Jingjing up by taxi.
Jingjing, let's go.
Okay.
It's difficult
to take a taxi at this hour.
Gu.
Don't you have your own car?
My grandpa borrowed my car.
I don't know when I can get it back.
Company cars have been fully booked.
I don't have a car these days.
What should I do then?
Our house is so far from the company.
Then I have less sleep time
to take the taxi every day.
Right.
Sweet Su.
Jingjing's company
is quite far from home.
Well... what should we do about it?
Yeah.
How about this?
Maybe you
just get over it, okay?
Just get over it.
Young people have to take
more challenges.
You should take hard work.
Cheer up for both of you.
Cheer up!
I'm on your side.
Okay.
Let's go then.
Then we'll hurry up for the taxi.
All right, just be careful.
Be careful.
Okay.
Two meat and two vegetable buns.
Take a cup of soy milk.
Okay.
That was really the best
I could do. So many hints.
I have never thought
my dad wouldn't take any of them.
I hope he's not really
picking me up tonight.
Your trick does not work.
What should we do then?
Let's get in the car first.
We haven't had the breakfast.
Let's go and buy some buns.
Okay.
Over there.
Which one do you like?
Take a look.
This is not a bun.
Finally, it is about
(Thanks)
material design and offline extension.
The above is the design
for 10th anniversary celebration
of Fanfun Mall.
Mr. Gu, director.
Just tell me
if anything needs to be improved.
Jingjing.
What do you think of the proposal?
This proposal has worked hard
to highlight the concept of fun.
But I think in general,
it's not straightforward enough.
Exactly.
We should notice the people we target.
It will work for young people.
But older people
are naturally resistant
to these new ideas.
How dare you
play tricks to me?
Yes.
If we directly use some
novel or trendy sculptures
and posters,
the customers probably
don't even know
what points we're trying to make.
We might as well just tell them
it's fun and you're welcome.
This is a good idea.
Sounds good.
A straightforward way
is really the best way.
The Group pays great attention
to this anniversary
celebration of Fanfun.
The design department's proposal
would make a great deal to it.
I hope next time I see
a real solution that works and is fun.
Jingjing.
I want you to stop by my office
after the meeting.
Okay.
Go ahead to discuss it.
Okay. From now on,
Su Jingjing will be
in charge of the whole project.
Director.
Su Jingjing has only been
in the design department for a few days.
Don't you think it's a little hasty
to give her such an important project?
Is it hasty?
Just because
this project is so important,
I gave it to Su Jingjing.
You all have other projects
on your hands,
only she can devote herself to it.
But she's new to the company
and has no experience on projects.
Even she devotes herself to it,
I'm afraid she can't handle it.
It's none of your business.
I...
I will follow up
the whole process of this project.
That's all for today's meeting.
Let's go.
It's okay.
I've already announced it.
Don't fail me.
But...
Stop saying that. Don't think so much.
I believe you. Cheer up!
Okay, I won't fail you.
Just go to work.
Come in.
I have a good news.
Du Yuchuan puts me in charge
of the proposal
for this anniversary celebration.
I always believe you.
But, designer Su,
I wonder if you can
think about our relationship
other than career?
Do you have any idea?
Right, let's make it straightforward.
Gu.
I heard you can help me
solve the accommodation problem
for these children.
Well, let's
check the house then.
Awesome.
You're so helpful, Gu.
Right.
I'm worrying about it.
Gu, Jingjing
has been so busy lately.
She's working overtime every day.
She's still working at this hour.
Right, Jingjing
recently took on a big project.
She might keep doing so
for the next months.
Mister and ma'am, don't worry.
I'll pick her up in a minute.
Okay.
Is the company not far from here?
Right, it's just next to this place.
Great. Look at the environment.
So beautiful.
Honey, look at the painting.
Abstractionism.
You know it?
Yeah, I do.
Nice.
Good, the underfloor heating is nice.
It's ventilated and big. Nice!
This house
is so good and trendy.
Right, the house appliances
are all brand new.
We can even hire a housekeeper
to clean and cook.
Good.
The food safety is the most important.
I like the elegant decoration.
So many rooms!
We won't be so crowded.
Right. There are enough rooms.
We can live separately.
Good, Gu.
Is this nice house yours?
Yes.
Because I think...
Mister, ma'am.
If you're willing
to give me someone that is so important,
I think the house
is the most basic thing.
Nice boy.
Good.
The house is nice,
but with only one disadvantage.
It's too far from the Martial Club.
It's not convenient
for the children to come.
Mister, ma'am.
Let's sit and talk.
We can talk in a comfortable way.
Okay, have a seat.
Have a seat, please.
Okay.
Have some water.
Large table.
Mister, ma'am.
Actually, I'm not planning
on letting the children move in here.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Let's spare the rooms
in the Martial Club
for the kids.
And then,
I'll move in here with Jingjing.
He'll live with Jingjing...
Right.
Are you crazy? Do you want to die?
I'll cut you to death with my falchion
and make your birthday
into your death day.
Do you believe it?
How can you talk like that?
Don't be mad at him.
No.
Su, listen to me.
Nothing to be discussed.
Go home with me.
I'm telling you. You are not kind.
Stop talking like that.
Your bag.
Gu, that's a great idea.
Let's go! Don't talk to him.
Just too soon.
Be careful, ma'am.
Let's go.
You're lucky that Master didn't cut you
with his falchion.
I'm not asking you
to make sarcastic remarks.
Brother-in-law,
Master is a martial artist.
You did it straightforwardly to him.
Will it end well for you?
So?
So on this matter,
you have to conquer
the unyielding with the yielding.
You must show Master
your utmost sincerity.
(Clock)
I have to go pick up Jingjing.
I see now.
You just used me.
I'm leaving.
Make yourself at home
and do whatever you want.
Bye.
So serious?
Why are you here?
I didn't hear you coming.
I am here to pick you up from work.
What did my dad say?
How about the proposal?
It is said
if one is frustrated in love,
then he'd be proud in work.
But now
my dad didn't let me move out.
God didn't
help me with my work either.
I beg for just a little inspiration.
Let's go home first.
I prepared you something.
That might give you an idea.
What is it?
You'll find out when you get back.
Alright.
Let's go.
(Su's Martial Club)
This is the new forest series.
Look.
This is sure to help you
find inspiration.
You can focus on your career.
I'm looking forward to your works.
I'm just going to focus on
us living together.
Who's living with you?
You.
Right. Blind box.
I got the inspiration. You know me.
(Famous designer Lin Yaozhong)
For this anniversary celebration,
we want to cooperate
with Mr. Lin Yaozhong,
a famous artist in Singapore,
to co-brand
and produce relevant blind boxes.
We will carry out
an immersive distribution
exhibition in the mall
and set up blind box machines
in every corner of the mall
to sell the new products
in the way of letting
customers treasure hunt,
so as to improve the interaction.
Now the Internet is so developed
that many players
will choose to shop online.
So what kind of advantage
can we have in this anniversary
to attract those customers
to come and buy?
In fact, for the true blind box fans,
the purchase experience between
online stores and physical stores
is totally different.
And for this anniversary,
we'll have
an extreme attraction for fans,
which is the blind boxes
of secret figure
that Mr. Lin Yaozhong
specially designed for the anniversary.
This secret figure
can only be obtained
from the anniversary blind box machines.
So I believe this collaboration
can let our mall
transform into
a way of more youthful fashion.
Conquer
the unyielding with the yielding.
(I'm going to go home
and prepare food and wine)
(to celebrate your plan's approval.)
(Xie Te will come to pick you up.)
Ask me to drink?
What? Does he want to get me drunk
and take my daughter from me?
Tell him it's impossible.
What are you talking about?
Wine tastes man.
Gu just wants to have a few more drinks.
If he gets drunk,
it'll give you a chance
to test him, right?
The boy gets himself drunk.
What does he think about all day?
Honey.
Can he be the president
of such a big group?
I don't think
there's anything wrong with this kid.
Su.
Let me be honest with you.
I quite like
Gu.
Look at you.
Hold it back.
He's kind of cute, right?
Right.
I'll take advantage of it
with these eyes of mine,
and take a good look at him.
(You'd better tidy up the martial club,)
(especially master's falchion.)
(In case he gets drunk
and actually fights you.)
It smells so good.
Gu.
A lot of dishes.
Yes.
Well, I'll go change my clothes.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Jingjing said she has to work overtime,
so she won't come back for dinner.
Here I come.
What a table of dishes!
When will Jingjing be back?
Did she message you?
Ma'am, please take a seat.
Jingjing said she has to work overtime,
so she won't come back for dinner.
Then let's eat first.
There's no need to wait for her.
No way.
These dishes are
all Jingjing's favorites.
I wanted to make her a treat.
She has had a hard time recently.
It's okay, mister and ma'am.
You two eat first.
I left some food for Jingjing.
I'll send them to her later.
You'll send them to her?
You haven't eaten either.
It doesn't matter.
Jingjing is not here. I...
Alright.
Then you'd go stay with Jingjing.
Right, ma'am.
Do you have
brown sugar and warm paste?
Jingjing said she doesn't feel well.
Yes!
I'll go get it.
You see?
Gu cares about Jingjing so much.
Gu.
Here, brown sugar and warm paste.
Here.
Thank you, ma'am.
Then I'll go stay with Jingjing.
Goodbye, mister and ma'am.
Be careful.
Okay.
You should have some.
Such a nice boy.
You can't have a long face all the time.
Gu is very concerned about Jingjing.
(Han Ran)
(Brother-in-law, how is it going?)
(Does it work?)
(It was over before I even started.)
(You might think of some other ways.)
Our house is
far away from their company.
Will the dishes get cold
when Gu arrives?
The quality of the crisper
I bought is very good.
Even if he takes a little time more,
the dishes won't get cold.
I wonder if you're really stupid
or just playing dumb.
Don't you know what I mean?
I get it. You just want me
to allow two of them to move out.
♪I'm the inaccessible exception♪
♪You're the only accident♪
♪I love you so much♪
♪I want to go anywhere with you♪
♪Believe me it's true♪
♪I feel the most myself before you♪
♪I don't need to hide anything♪
♪I'm always anticipating♪
♪In a future with you♪
♪It is our fairy tale♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪I'm home when I'm with you♪
♪No matter how much hardship♪
♪You are the one for me♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪I think of you♪
♪Eveything about you♪
♪Without realizing♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪You are the one♪
♪In my life♪
♪I love you♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪This is our own sweetness♪
♪Let's look foward to♪
♪The view on the journey♪
♪And every little detail♪
♪This is our exclusive memory♪
♪I realize the point of persistance♪
♪Everything becomes clear♪
♪Carefully♪
♪Sew you into my life♪
♪I love you♪