=Afterlife of Love and Revenge=
=Episode 11=
Miss Zhao, are you
going home for a meal?
Don't come near. Help!
Miss Zhao!
Why is the rain getting heavier?
What's wrong? Why are they running?
You need to give us
an explanation today!
That's right!
Master Zhang from Puning Temple
said that
Pang Longyue's possessed by evil spirit.
Master Zhang has left Puning Temple.
It must be a rumour.
If we don't kill the devil,
the whole village will
be killed instead.
How do you want to deal with her?
Divorce her
and chase her out.
Some experts will kill her.
Chase her out!
Qingmu.
Our yang qi will be sucked away
when one's being possessed.
I'm not young anymore.
I don't want to see you die.
Okay.
I'll invite everyone here
to see how I kill the devil.
Okay.
Someone's killed!
I didn't get it wrong.
She's Pang Longyue.
This is bad luck. Chase her away.
Why should I? You go.
You go.
When is the rain going to stop?
It's so late now.
Why isn't Longyue home?
Didn't she hear anything
and dare not come home?
After all, Master Zhang is famous.
Yes.
Where are you going?
I'll go pick her up.
No.
Who knows
if you're going to tip her off?
Madam Cui.
I sleep with her every day.
Maybe I got some back luck from her.
Don't blame me
if you're infected.
You...
Don't come near.
Don't leave!
Where are you going?
Is that Longyue?
Aunt!
Ghost!
Hu, don't be afraid. Come to me.
Dear, I'm home.
Dear, why are they running?
Qingmu.
Them?
They're competing.
Look at the blood.
The evil spirit has manifested.
Blood?
The dress' colour is fading.
Look.
Stop giving reasons.
If we don't kill you,
the whole village will be killed.
Come here! Kill her!
Kill her!
Move aside!
You said the devil will
suck your yang qi.
If she can't suck my yang qi,
does that prove that she's not devil?
How do you prove that?
Of course I can prove it.
♪You're the fated love coming
from the immortal world♪
♪You tie the red strings on
the tips of my fingers♪
♪My heart won't change
even if time passes♪
♪I'll wait for the love
in the old place as promised♪