Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
If I had shown up there,
you would've just given people
something else to gossip about.
I asked your friend
to create a diversion.
This is so thrilling.
It's like we're playing hide-and-seek.
And...
our hands...
are still intertwined.
How cute.
Sami.
How do you know
my name?
Take a guess.
Why... are you helping me?
Because I find you interesting.
What is that...
supposed to mean?
I hope you'll figure it out.
No.
I'm not letting you get away now.
Just hide in here for now.
I'll stay with you.
I have absolutely no idea
what this guy is thinking.
Oh.
Right.
Ta-da!
I like this one too.
But there's one thing
I know for sure.
Which toy do you want?
Me?
I've always wanted
the toy ring.
But I can never seem to get it.
I really don't like this guy.