Hey, look, look, look!
Huh?
Look at this.
This is insane.
Sensei.
It's this...
These comments on Vinsta.
(New menu? What's new? It's all ripped off from other recipes.)
(And she has the nerve to teach cooking? What a joke.)
(All plagiarized recipes. Zero originality.)
I...
I'll take whatever revenge
Reika-san dishes out.
If it helps appease Reika-san,
even just a little...
I'm willing to endure anything,
no matter how cruel.
I have to be open
to differing opinions.
But...
Reika-san, I'm sorry.
If your revenge against me
goes too far...
...my dad might find out.
And you'll be in danger.
So I'll do my best to minimize
any trouble that comes my way.
My recipes are a culmination
of my own experiences
and original ideas.
They're all original.
I can say that with a clear conscience.
One look
at this recipe notebook
should make that clear.
Everyone...
...is asking for a refund.
That's their decision to make,
and there's nothing I can do about it.
Also...
The TV appearance
that was already booked...
They contacted us
and asked us to cancel...
If this is the extent of it,
it's nothing I can't handle.
Ah!
I don't care what happens to me.
But if this escalates...
...and my father finds out
Reika-san is behind this...
I...
I want to let her get her revenge.
But...