No matter how much
you hate me,
I'm still crazy about you.
Just get on your knees,
and this will all be over.
That's a pretty good deal, isn't it?
Yes.
You've been embezzling company funds.
You wouldn't want that to get out, would you?
Spending a fortune
on male escorts and all that.
What should I do?
I need you to
make a big scene.
Get on your knees, now!
What are you spacing out for?
Hurry up!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hurry up!!
This... Did you
put something in here?
This is...
Huh? What?
What is going on?
Who would put something like this...
No, I didn't do this.
Ma'am, I've had enough.
Just kidding.
Everyone, this was just part of the entertainment.
It was just for entertainment.
Ma'am.
Please, help me.
Everyone, I apologize for the disturbance.
I'm truly sorry.
Part of the entertainment...
That's not what this was at all.
I don't know
what her reasons were,
but she staged this whole thing herself.
That's not true.
I would never do something like this...
My hand slipped.