Handsome, yet fragile.
Beautiful, but timid.
You act tough to hide
your vulnerable side.
I'm okay.
Thank you.
There's something inside.
You gave me a snack last time.
This is a little something in return.
For me?
If you just give me
the same thing back,
it kind of defeats the purpose
of my gift, don't you think?
If you don't want it, forget it.
Too bad, I'm keeping it.
No take-backs.
Okay.
From the one I got...
I got this!
A ring!
Nice!
I wonder if I'll get it in this one.
It's the secret one.
There's no way you'd get it that easily.
I got it!
Such long, beautiful eyelashes.
You were just thinking about
how long my eyelashes are, weren't you?
When you start to fall for someone,
you notice things like the length of their eyelashes.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't help myself.
Don't stop.
You're so cute.
Honestly...
Iijima-san.
The police would like a word with you.
Huh?
For goodness' sake...
Didn't I tell you to stay put?