[English subtitles are available]
[Flight to you]
[Episode 10]
[Police]
Hello.
Is the female ground staff who had a dispute
at the departure hall in the afternoon still here?
Her name is Cheng Xiao.
She left after finishing the statement.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hello.
The number you dialed is busy now.
Please try again later.
[Cheng Xiao]
♫The broken shaft of a dream♫
♫Holding on tight and not letting go♫
♫After the world has collapsed♫
♫I fantasize about finding an exit♫
♫Little me♫
♫Holding on till the end♫
♫Hating myself for not being able to fight back♫
♫Fate was always out of my reach♫
♫Watching time slip away♫
♫Let the dream♫
♫Leave me alone and fly away♫
♫Don't join me♫
♫Into this flood together♫
♫Leave my world♫
♫To be free again♫
♫Look at the end of beauty for me♫
♫Let the dream♫
♫Leave me behind and go on♫
Are you home?
♫Don't look back♫
♫Let me be left alone♫
♫I can't change anything♫
♫Like a silent trapped beast♫
I just finished signing in.
♫Sending dreams away♫
Today we'll fly overnight.
What's wrong?
♫It's all I've ever had♫
Nothing.
♫I can't change anything♫
♫Like a silent trapped beast♫
♫Sending dreams away♫
♫It's all I've ever had♫
[Personnel Information]
[Current address]
[Cheng Xiao]
Hello.
The number you dialed is busy now.
Please try again later.
How can I not be anxious?
Where did you fall? Are you okay?
Which hospital are you in?
I'll be right there.
Okay, I got it. Okay.
What's wrong?
My mum fell.
You should go to the hospital now.
Take my umbrella.
What about you, Yuheng?
I'll leave after the rain stops.
Go ahead.
Okay, thank you.
Go quickly.
Didn't you bring an umbrella?
I lent it to my colleague. Something urgent came up to her.
Get in.
It's okay, Brother Nanting. I'll take a taxi.
You may go first.
It's not easy to take a taxi now.
Get in.
Let's go.
OK.
Brother Nanting.
Do you always work until this late?
It's too hard.
I'm used to it.
Hello, ARCFOX.
Hi, I'm here.
Raise the temperature in the passenger seat.
Okay.
The passenger seat's temperature has increased by two degrees.
Do you know
where Cheng Xiao lives?
Cheng Xiao?
I don't know.
My roommate, Xiazhi,
used to live with Cheng Xiao.
Xiazhi is on the flight now.
How about
I ask her after she lands?
No need.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Brother Nanting,
why do you care about where Ms. Cheng lives?
It’s about a misfiling document.
Thank you.
Hu.
That's all for today's volunteer work.
Come on.
You used my venue
to satisfy your hobby.
It’s good that I didn’t charge you the venue fee.
Go back.
Take care, Mr. Xie.
OK.
What?
Do you know him?
Wait.
Let me do it.
It's okay.
Thank you, Brother Nanting.
Since we are here,
how about you go upstairs and have some tea?
Sorry.
I have to go.
Rest early.
Now that you mention it,
it's not easy for this little female pilot.
When I retired,
I stayed at home for a month.
Do you want to give her psychological counseling?
There will be a savior for her.
Send it to No. 4.
Okay.
Shen, let's go.
Master.
What happened this time?
She had a dispute with a passenger.
She did nothing wrong this time.
This girl has gone through hardships
in our Passenger Transport Department.
I'm relieved that you're here.
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
I'm leaving.
Thank you, master. Rest early.
Be gentle.
Don't.
Sleeping makes her feel better.
If you wake her up now,
she will definitely have insomnia.
I can't delay your closing.
I have waiters sleeping at the back.
It doesn't matter.
I’ll tell them.
Captain Gu,
don’t stay here anymore.
I've told the waiters behind.
They will take turns looking after her.
Otherwise, when she wakes up
and sees there's an acquaintance here,
it'll backfire.
Let's go.
You're awake.
Have you been guarding here?
My boss told me to.
But we took turns.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Well,
this is…
This is Captain Gu’s.
Gu Nanting?
Yes.
She's gone.
When did she wake up?
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Staff room]
Cheng.
Brother Qiao.
Why are you here so early?
I'm sorry.
I left early yesterday.
Don't say that.
Everyone feels upset
when encountering such a situation.
Are you okay?
You didn't reply my message.
I'm fine. Thank you.
I've arranged a half-day schedule for you today.
Go back and have a rest.
No, I'm fine.
It's all set. No big deal.
Thank you, Brother Qiao.
Cheng.
Can you stop calling me that?
I am a 95s child.
It's just for respect.
OK.
You haven't had breakfast, have you?
Try it. My dad made it himself.
Did he make it himself?
My dad has a breakfast shop
near the airport.
My whole family moved near the airport
just to let me go to work more conveniently.
Tell me if you don't like it.
My dad has made buns for half his life.
He's still afraid that his buns are not delicious.
But if there are any returned customers,
he will be very happy.
He thinks his hard work pays off.
Try it.
It's delicious.
It's good, right?
Where is the shop?
Turn left after going out from the company.
Then cross the road, it's next to the supermarket.
Is that your dad?
Have you been there?
No.
There was once I passed by,
and my colleague bought it,
I didn't.
I should have bought
thousands of them.
This is today's flight record.
Okay, give it to me.
I’m leaving, Cheng.
See you tomorrow.
What a coincidence.
We meet each other on every business trip.
Hello, Mr. Ni.
Are you off work?
I don't have much work today.
I'll board in half an hour.
If there's nothing else,
I'll buy you a cup of coffee.
You seem different
from the last few times.
I remember when you were in Australia aviation school,
even if you were sick,
you were still lively and energetic.
Since I was 19,
for ten years,
I've been on a plane.
I thought
it's bad enough that I can't touch the control rod.
Who knows?
I can't even get on the plane now.
Actually, when I was in high school,
I also wished to learn to fly.
My family was poor back then.
I took a great effort to borrowed money
to do laser surgery with hard effort.
But I was rejected
during the enrollment.
It comes out that you can't pass the physical examination
after you have done the laser surgery.
So,
I had to study maintenance.
I used to think
life is unfair.
All roads lead to Rome.
But some people are born in Rome.
When I first started working,
I couldn't go home for a year
with a monthly salary of 3,000 to 5,000 yuan.
The apron is my living room.
The garage is my bedroom.
I remember once
we needed to replace the heat exchanger of
the air-conditioner compartments after the flight.
It was 50 degrees Celsius at the apron.
I was so thirsty.
When I saw there was some water left by the passengers,
I drank it.
In the end,
I was punished for taking the aircraft supplies.
Three months
turned into vain.
The scar on your hand...
One time, I was repairing the engine.
My colleague was too sleepy
and ran into the power.
It's not easy
in any position in civil aviation.
Luckily, God didn't give you the chance.
Otherwise,
the world will lose
such a great engineer.
So,
from another perspective,
maybe it's a good thing.
Thank you, Mr. Ni.
Don’t worry.
Cheng Xiao has 100 lives.
A life without a storm
is incomplete.
This is the Cheng Xiao I know.
Here.
No matter how Gu Nanting oppresses me,
I will find a chance to turn the tide.
Do you really treat him
as your imaginary enemy?
He doesn't deserve it.
I'm the only enemy I have.
It was not his idea
to let you become a ground staff.
It was Mr. Jiang’s idea.
Mr. Jiang.
Well,
why didn't Gu Nanting explain to me?
I've known him for more than ten years.
That's how he is.
He never speaks too much.
By the way,
are you going to serve
a flight to Beijing tomorrow?
How did you know?
Because I'll take that flight.
The same goes for the company's leader.
I asked Mr Dai
to arrange you for the reception.
I have to go to the boarding gate now.
See you tomorrow.
Do your best.
Thank you, Mr. Ni.
Come in.
I'll return your clothes after I wash them.
No need.
Don't worry. I'll use the dry cleaning. It won't spoil your clothes.
I only go to a fixed dry cleaner.
Well...
I misunderstood you.
I knew it all.
It was Mr. Jiang’s idea
to let me transfer to the Ground Handling Department.
Whatever the reason he believes,
I’ll keep working hard.
Expecting me to give up?
Impossible.
Why didn't you fill in your home address
in the staff records?
I was planning to move
when I was transferred to the Passenger Transport Department.
I thought I could
fill in the address after moving out.
Why are you checking my address?
I'm organizing the basic information.
I'll make it up later.
Well,
I'll leave you alone.
Attention, passengers of flight XD8306
to Shenzhen.
Your flight is about to take off.
Please board at Gate 73 as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Two more are left.
Let's broadcast it.
Passengers of Luzhou Airlines
flight XD8306
to Shenzhen,
namely Zhang Jingya and Hu Guoping, please pay attention.
The boarding gate
is closing.
Please go to Gate 73 as soon as possible.
Thank you.
I'm not on this flight.
I'm on the same flight as Mr. Xu.
At that boarding gate.
Then, you're for...
There is still plenty of time
so I came to see you.
Mr. Gu.
Cheng has improved a lot.
In our team, she is the first to arrive
and the last to leave.
I think I have to learn from her.
Brother Qiao.
Two more passengers haven't arrived.
But the time is up.
Should we inform the captain about the shortage?
I will do it.
See you later.
Wait.
Let the plane wait a little longer, okay?
Wait for a while.
Are you Mr. Hu Guoping?
Yes.
I... I can't find my wife.
What happened?
After the security check,
we just kept walking ahead.
Later,
when I turned around, my wife suddenly disappeared.
Can you wait for us?
We'll help you find her.
But
the cabin door is closing soon.
The plane can't wait.
Young man, young lady.
Just wait for a moment, okay?
We won't delay you.
Just wait for a moment.
Please. Please.
Please!
Sir, I'm really sorry.
All the flights have their estimated take-off time.
Once we miss it, we'll need to wait for a long time.
It will also cause
a series of flight delays later.
Please understand that.
Cheng.
This old man is quite pitiful.
Do you know the captain on duty?
Should you discuss it with him?
But we can't waste everyone's time
because of a passenger.
What matters is we should find the person
and let them change the tickets as soon as possible.
OK.
Sir.
Is your wife Zhang Jingya?
Yes.
Okay, I'll broadcast it for you again.
Okay, thank you.
Miss.
Forget it.
My wife
doesn't know her name.
What color are the clothes
she wears today?
This is my wife.
A purple shirt,
with purple shoes
and a basket of grapes in her hands.
Okay.
Sir.
Let me see.
Calm down.
I’ll find her at the airport.
Don't you have a plane to catch?
It's okay. Give me a walkie-talkie.
Keep in touch.
OK.
I'll look for her too.
Cheng.
Gate 72 in 20 minutes.
Don't forget the time.
Got it.
Please wait a moment, sir.
Thank you.
This is a broadcast looking for someone.
Ms. Zhang Jingya.
Your husband, Hu Guoping is looking for you.
Please go to Gate 73 immediately
after this broadcast.
Dear passengers,
if you see a woman in her sixties
wearing a purple shirt and purple shoes,
also holding grapes in her hands,
please contact the staff nearby.
Thank you for your help.
This is a broadcast looking for someone.
Ms. Zhang Jingya.
Your husband, Hu Guoping is looking for you.
Please go to Gate 73 immediately
after this broadcast.
Manman.
Are you mad at me again?
Well.
I found her.
She's in the amusement arcade of Zone C.
Take it.
Auntie,
I've told you many times.
I don't even know you.
You are my Manman.
I'm not.
Why not?
Ms. Zhang.
Hello, do you know this lady?
Can you take her away?
I have a flight to catch.
Sorry to bother you.
Manman, my son.
Auntie Zhang, he's not your son.
He is not your son.
He is my son.
He's my son, Manman.
Auntie Zhang.
He's really not your son.
Please help me find him.
-Help me get him back.
-Auntie Zhang.
Get up.
Jingya!
Look.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Jingya.
How many times have I told you?
Our son is not there.
He's in Shenzhen.
Did you forget again?
Didn't we agree
to visit him in Shenzhen today?
I didn't bring any tissues.
Your clothes.
Nothing.
Uncle, please wipe it for her.
Here, wipe it.
Where are my grapes?
Your hands.
I...
Auntie.
It's rotten.
Our grapes are all rotten.
We don't want them anymore, okay?
We don't want them anymore.
We are going to celebrate Manman's birthday.
Yeah.
My son loves grapes.
I want to bring them to him.
Okay.
I'll pick one.
Go ahead.
Here.
Slowly.
Sir.
You've found your wife.
Moreover, you're going to celebrate your son's birthday soon.
You should be happy.
Miss.
What birthday?
It's his death anniversary.
We only have one son.
When he was 18,
he left us
to work in Shenzhen
and never came back.
In the house he rented,
he got gas poisoning
and left.
In a blink of an eye,
20 years have passed.
After my son left,
my wife couldn't accept the fact.
Especially in the past two years,
her brain
was getting worse.
She couldn't remember things.
She still thought our son was working in Shenzhen
and insisted on a visit to Shenzhen
to celebrate our son's birthday.
I'm sorry.
Have you decided?
Wipe your hands. Come on.
The next flight is boarding soon.
I'll take them
to change their tickets.
Go back to work.
Your clothes...
It's okay.
I'll leave him to you.
Let me take you two to change your tickets.
He said he'll take us to the plane. Let's go.
I'll start the broadcast.
Hello, passengers.
Passengers of Luzhou Airlines
flight XD8155
to Beijing, please pay attention.
The flight you're taking is now boarding.
Please take your belongings
and line up at Gate 72.
I've read the report.
Your Maintenance Department
did a good job
in assuring the safety target last year.
I didn't do it alone.
It's the effort of all engineers.
-Welcome aboard.
-Thank you.
Welcome aboard.
I'm going to discuss Civil Aviation Maintenance
under Internet and Big Data
in the next Civil Aviation Forum.
We can discuss this with our peers by then.
OK.
Welcome aboard.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
Hello.
Welcome aboard.
Hello, Mr. Ni.
The girl who just said hello to you
is the female pilot transferred from the Freight Department to the Passenger Transport Department.
Are you talking about the female pilot, Cheng Xiao?
Yes.
Why is she here?
I heard Mr. Jiang
transferred her to the Ground Handling Department.
What can a pilot
learn in the Ground Handling Department?
[Baggage Check-in]
I'm at counter D11,
wearing a grey suit.
Thank you.
Sir, your tickets.
OK.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Take it.
Uncle, auntie.
I chose the first row of economy class for you.
It is more spacious and less noisy.
Look at it, the first row. How nice.
Young man, thank you for your hard work.
You’re welcome.
Mr. Gu, right?
Yes.
These are the grapes and the shirt you ordered.
Okay.
This is a free gift.
Thank you. Thank you.
That's not ours.
Here you are.
I bought it for you.
Take it.
Look at my wife.
Give it to me.
-Let go! Let go!
-No.
Young man, this is for you.
No.
Take it.
I can't take this. I really can't take it.
If you don't take it,
we won't dare to take the grapes.
Here, take it.
You're welcome.
How about this?
I'll take the grapes. I can't take the money.
Young man,
if my son were still alive,
he would be your age.
Here.
Come on.
Auntie, let me help you.
No need.
Come on. Lead the way. Lead the way.
This way.
Okay.
Passengers of Luzhou Airlines
flight XD8155
to Beijing, please pay attention.
Your flight is about to take off.
Please board at Gate 72 as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Welcome aboard.
Done.
The old man
asked me to give you this
as a token of appreciation to the ground staff.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Welcome aboard.
Bye.
Cheng.
How is it? Is it okay here?
Have you got used to it?
I'm very fine.
I've learned a lot.
Good mindset.
Then continue to study here.
Okay.
I won’t let you down.
Mr. Jiang.
Let me ask you something.
Why is the female pilot in your department
working at the Ground Handling Department?
It's Cheng Xiao.
A while ago,
three complaints letters
were all related to her.
It doesn't make sense.
So I sent her to the Ground Handling Department
and let her study for a while
so that she could fully realize
the mistakes she had made.
But what can a pilot
learn from the Ground Handling Department?
Mr. Jiang.
We can’t assign pilots
who the company pays a high price to train at will.
My arrangement is a bit inappropriate.
I'll send her back in two days.
Okay, get it done as soon as possible.
Xiaoxiao.
Dad.
I have a morning shift today.
I can get off work around five.
Sure.
What do you want to eat? I'll buy some groceries.
Stop buying.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Ask mum to come along.
Can your mum come along?
It's been a long time
since we had a meal together.
Let's eat together.
Great!
You pack up first.
I'll pick you up after work.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Bye.