[English subtitles are available]
[Flight to You]
[Episode 39]
There are no passengers on the plane today.
I'll make a heavy landing later
to check the condition of the landing gear and tires.
Instructor Shang Fei said
as long as it doesn’t exceed the limit, it’ll be fine.
There's something wrong with the monitor.
What?
What's the problem?
The attitude indicator is not clear.
It's fine on my end.
I'll operate it.
It's okay. I can see the runway.
I'll switch to visual flight.
Luckily, we found the problem during the test flight.
It would be troublesome if this were the first flight.
What's wrong with the monitor?
If there is really something wrong,
ask the Maintenance department to inform Shang Fei.
Check all the monitors
from the same batch.
Captain Gu.
What’s wrong with the monitor?
There's no problem.
The monitor is fine.
The plane is great.
What's wrong?
Get off the plane first.
I'll write the flight record.
I'll be right there.
Mr. Gu. Mr. Gu.
The macular degeneration
in your left eye has worsened.
That's why
your vision is blurry
in the center of your field of vision.
Then...
Do I need surgery?
Yes.
Injection surgery.
This disease
will affect
your work and life to a certain extent.
What do you do?
I’m a pilot.
What are you doing?
I've decided to do something very meaningful.
This has something to do with you.
You ignored me.
Gu Nanting.
You haven't replied my messages all afternoon.
I'll tell you anyway.
I wrote a unique
captain's announcement for the maiden flight for you.
Take a look when you're done.
By the way, President Xu wants to see me.
I'm at the company.
What is it?
What do you think?
Why did President Xu tell me
I am now the captain for D191's maiden flight?
President Xu has talked to me.
As a leader of the Flight department,
my duties in management are more important.
So from now on,
I'll focus on management.
No.
Even so,
can't we wait until after the maiden flight?
On the day of the maiden flight,
I have to attend an important meeting
as a representative of the company.
What meeting could be more important than the maiden flight?
Is it because President Xu found out about our relationship
and wants you to remove yourself from your position?
Fine, I can quit.
Cheng Xiao, calm down.
This has nothing to do with our relationship.
This is work,
and more importantly, my responsibility.
You know it's your responsibility?
President Xu said
if you're the captain in charge,
it’ll be more helpful for the publicity of domestic planes.
Of course,
I’ll assign
an experienced secondary captain to you.
Don’t worry.
I'm not worried about that.
It's you.
What happened?
We agreed
we will take the maiden flight together.
I have something more important to do.
Why didn't you talk to me
before you made such an important decision?
Do you consider me the person who is closest to you?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it through.
But since the maiden flight's details have been decided,
I hope you can go on without distraction.
I don't know what
made you change so suddenly.
Mr. Gu,
have you decided to focus on career progression?
But you once said
you were first and foremost a pilot.
No matter how I think about it, I don’t think it’s possible.
Mr. Gu gave up flying
to focus on career progression.
This is so weird.
Do you have any better explanations?
If I did,
I wouldn't have
spent an hour here with you.
Come on.
You're just waiting for Song to land
so you can go to see the wedding planner together.
Don’t be angry with Mr. Gu.
At least both of you qualified
to fly the maiden flight.
Look at me.
I postponed the wedding
for this maiden flight.
I dragged Song with me
to sign up.
In the end,
the bride wasn't lucky enough to be picked,
but the bridesmaid was.
Yuheng is also flying on the maiden flight.
I'm so jealous.
The fates are so cruel to me.
You've already passed the transition training.
Sooner or later,
you will make it onto a domestic plane.
Luckily, Song Xiaoni didn't make it either.
Otherwise,
my status at home in the future
will be doomed.
Here.
Coming.
Xiao is here too?
She has something to ask you.
What's wrong?
These past two days, you've been working with Gu Nanting
the whole time you haven't been flying, right?
Yes.
We're amending the safety manual for domestic planes.
Has there been anything strange
about him recently?
Strange?
Did you two fight?
No.
You didn't know Mr. Gu
suddenly quit the maiden flight of D191?
Now I know.
Who is flying it then?
Xiao?
Congratulations!
Why did Brother Nanting quit?
Song,
please keep an eye on Gu Nanting for me
in the coming days.
Don't miss
any details.
If you notice anything strange about him,
let me know immediately.
Okay.
I know this job best.
I'll get a glass of water.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
Bye, Yang.
I've sent your medical records
to Director Yang of the Central Hospital.
He said the probability of a complete recovery is very high.
Mr Yang is my childhood friend.
He's the best ophthalmic surgeon in Luzhou.
He said the surgery is not difficult.
He only has to
inject some medicine into your eyes.
When he comes back from Shanghai next week,
he'll operate on you as soon as he can.
Thank you.
Have you told Cheng Xiao?
No.
I can't make the flight with her,
I've already made her sad.
I don't want this to
affect her performance on the maiden flight.
I thought
I could keep flying until I retired.
A while ago,
my master withdrew early because of his health.
I didn't expect
it would be my turn so soon.
To be honest,
I'm scared.
Nanting.
Cheng Xiao,
Song, Xiazhi, Yuheng, and I
are all here.
We'll help you.
And the doctor said
there's a good chance of recovery.
Let's not think about such things.
Look at you now.
The Gu Nanting
who was resolute
about improving the systems for aviation safety in China,
the Gu Nanting who was steadfast
and ready to take on the challenges of the future,
where did he go?
Help me find him.
You're different now that you're the Vice President.
You're getting more eloquent.
Are you jealous of my position?
No way.
[The day before D191's maiden flight]
[Maiden Flight Announcement Script For Gu]
Cheng Xiao,
you're leaving tomorrow.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
[Ni Zhan]
Nanting.
Director Yang is back.
You can make an appointment for 8 a.m. tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Yes, Director Yang is very busy.
He had to make time especially for you.
You don't know how many people are on the waiting list.
Tomorrow,
I want to watch Cheng Xiao take off
at the airport.
I know.
But I'm afraid your condition will get worse if you drag this out.
The doctor said
the sooner the disease is treated, the higher the chances of recovery.
Think about it.
I'll come find you after work.
Brother Nanting.
I have completed
the revision of the safety manual for domestic planes.
Look it over.
Xiao,
I really found
something wrong with Brother Nanting.
I think
his eyes haven't been well recently.
I showed him an article on an official account
the day before yesterday.
He listened to it using the screen reader function.
All the messages he's been sending me lately
have been voice messages.
But he used to send texts.
By the way,
just now,
he couldn't see the words on a document.
There's something wrong with the monitor.
What?
What's the problem?
The attitude indicator is not clear.
The maiden flight tomorrow
is very important to Luzhou Airlines,
and it is also a source of honor for us.
Actually,
I've been to the assembly workshop.
I'm very confident.
Thank you for your hard work these days.
You're welcome.
You must do a thorough check
for the maiden flight tomorrow.
Make sure nothing goes wrong.
Got it.
Zhan, don't worry.
Shang Fei's friends are helping us.
Thank you, Mr. Sun.
Thank you for your work.
You're welcome.
Xiao?
I have listed the points of consideration for the maiden flight
on the list.
Tomorrow,
of the 170 seats on the plane,
other than invited media personnel and guests of honor,
two thirds of them will be regular passengers.
I hope everyone
will put their best foot forward
to show them the strength of domestic planes,
and the ability of our pilots.
I will complete the mission.
In addition,
due to work arrangements,
I will not be able to attend the maiden flight ceremony
after the landing tomorrow.
I wish you all
a successful maiden flight.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Dismissed.
Mr. Gu,
look at me now.
Did my face turn black
or misshapen?
[Luzhou Airlines]
I finally understand
what having clouded vision is like.
I think I can see,
but I also think I cannot.
I'll accompany you to the operation tomorrow.
You have to take the maiden flight tomorrow.
You can arrange for another pilot to do it.
Cheng Xiao.
We've been waiting for the maiden flight for so long.
I know better than anyone
how much it matters to you.
Even if I don't take the maiden flight,
I can take subsequent ones.
I just don't want you to go into the operation alone.
The nature of our job as a pilot necessitates that
we will make many sacrifices.
Often, we cannot keep our families or our lovers
company.
You should be used to it by now.
But this time is different.
When I first found out I was sick,
I was very sad
and scared.
I was afraid that I would have to stop flying.
I was even more afraid that it might affect you.
Ni Zhan talked to me a lot.
I thought about it a lot too.
So, for tomorrow's surgery,
even though the doctor told me
the chance of recovery is not 100%,
I'm able to face it bravely.
Do you know why?
Because I thought about
how you're doing the thing I want to do the most
on my behalf.
Domestic planes are what generations of Chinese aviation professionals have hoped for.
They have devoted their whole lives
to this one thing.
All their efforts
have been poured into
those 80 tons of metal.
At first,
I thought I could
turn this blueprint into reality as soon as possible.
But I no longer have the chance.
So,
I'm passing it on to you.
You are doing this not only for me, for Luzhou Airlines,
but also to fulfill the wishes
of several generations of Chinese aviation professionals.
Cheng Xiao,
you have always been my pride and joy.
Promise me.
Fly well tomorrow.
I'll complete the mission.
[The day of D191's maiden flight]
[7 a.m.]
[9 a.m.]
[Luzhou Airlines]
Welcome aboard.
[Hall 4]
[First date]
[10 a.m.]
Hello, welcome aboard.
Good morning. Welcome aboard.
That's so cool. You must come and take a look.
Hello, welcome aboard.
It's a domestic plane. It's its first flight today.
Take a look.
Chinese aviation is so awesome.
Do you think
Xiao can come out later?
I don't think so.
We'll have to wait for the plane to land.
It'll be nice to give her a surprise
after we land, right?
Hello, babes. Hello.
Hello.
We have already
boarded this plane.
And
this is a small gift for the maiden flight.
It's a souvenir.
It's very beautiful.
Hello, everyone.
Well,
is this a domestic plane?
What was our company thinking,
making us take this flight?
Listen.
Fasten your seat belt properly.
I'll see if we have enough time
to get insurance.
Don't jinx it.
I heard
the engines of domestic planes are imported.
Only the assembly was done in China.
You don't understand.
The assembly is different from the original. You...
I can't explain it to you.
Although the engines
and auxiliary power units were imported,
China has full independent intellectual property rights
over our domestic planes.
From the outer appearance to the internal structure,
from research to manufacturing,
everything was completed domestically.
This plane
definitely has China's DNA.
Auntie, you know a lot.
Whether it's safe or not,
whether it's comfortable or not,
I'll decide after I've experienced it.
Have a good trip.
Thank you.
You too.
[10:30 a.m.]
The doctor said it's fine.
He'll give me another shot in a month,
three months in a row.
Then, I'll essentially be recovered.
That's good.
Are you going back
or...
Request to taxi out.
Ground, Luzhou 8155 is ready,
and requesting to taxi out.
Luzhou 8155, you may taxi out.
Taxi out along F.
Wait outside M.
Taxi out along F and wait outside M,
Luzhou 8155.
Luzhou 8155, ready for take off.
Runway 34 Left.
The surface wind is 010, 4 meters.
34 Left available for take off, Luzhou 8155.
We're taking off in the direction of the wind.
We're lucky today.
Prepare for take off.
Fly towards the wind.
[Three months later]
Later, when you're free,
take Polly to the veterinarian.
What's wrong with Polly?
It hasn't eaten in three days.
It ignores me when I feed it.
Did you change the feed?
How did you know?
Yes, I changed it to a better type.
What's wrong?
Feed needs to be changed gradually,
increasing the amount of new feed
by 10 to 20 percent every day.
A gradual change
gives it time to get used to it.
How do you know so much?
My girlfriend is so excellent.
Of course I need to do better
to be worthy of you.
Okay, my excellent boyfriend.
I'll leave Polly to you.
I have a flight.
Did you forget something?
I forgot to tell you
to take a good rest.
Your eyes have just recovered.
What else?
I'm running out of time.
By the way,
you haven't answered
my question from yesterday.
When
will we move in together?
That depends on your performance.
Slow down.
I'm going to be late.
Hello.
Are you Mr. Gu?
Yes.
You have a package. Are you home now?
What package?
There are eight boxes.
What are they? Who sent them?
Hold on. Let me see.
They're marked as clothes and daily necessities.
The sender is...
Miss Cheng.
I see.
Thank you.
Hello, Polly.
Hello.
[Beihai]
Attention, passengers.
Your flight will be taking off soon.
[Economy Class]
The handover is done.
Let's prepare for the next shift.
Okay, I'm going now.
[Waiting Area, Please queue up]
We're returning from Sanya.
I'll wait for you for dinner.
♫ I wave at the sea ♫
♫ Is it rising or retreating ♫
Hello, welcome aboard.
♫ The signal is shining at me ♫
Hello, welcome aboard. This way, please.
♫ Putting aside the chaotic thoughts ♫
Hello, welcome aboard.
Hello, welcome aboard. This way, please.
♫ Welcoming the current ♫
You're a chief attendant now.
Good luck.
Thank you.
♫ Wings trembling excitedly ♫
Hello, welcome aboard. This way, please.
♫ Unruly soul ♫
Xia.
♫ Around the earth ♫
Long time no see.
♫ Unruly soul ♫
Mr. Jiang.
Jiang.
♫ Around the earth ♫
This way, please.
♫ Break through the clouds and chase the light ♫
Your seat is here.
Look in the direction your fingers are pointing towards.
♫ Wings swing against the wind ♫
♫ The silver meteor shines brightly ♫
Let's review
♫ So what if we are at a loss ♫
how we greet passengers when they board the plane.
♫ Even if there's a storm ahead ♫
Two purlicues overlapping,
fingers together, with a natural downward slant.
♫ That's the moment when courage rises ♫
♫ That's the moment when courage rises. ♫
Head and chest up, bow down 15 degrees.
♫ That's the moment when courage rises ♫
Hello, welcome aboard.
That's it, a standard pose.
♫ Heart beating heavily ♫
While showing the way, your five fingers should be together,
with your thumb up
and fingers pointing forward.
We predict that in the next 20 years,
♫ Contrail slashes across the sky ♫
Chinese airline companies
will be acquiring about 6000 to 7000 new planes.
♫ Even if there's no wind here ♫
That means
pilots will be in short supply.
♫ Running to the sky with all my might ♫
Among the list of professionals in short supply
according to the Civil Aviation Administration of China,
pilots are ranked first.
♫ Chasing the flow of the air ♫
As of 2021,
the shortage in pilots has reached
♫ The weight of unnecessary reality ♫
210,000.
Okay, fly in the air
♫ Don't dream tonight ♫
like a bird.
Crossing the ocean.
♫ I roll up thunder ♫
We will be landing soon.
♫ In the troposphere ♫
We need to descend stably
♫  Fly towards the dawn ♫
and land safely.
♫ In the stratosphere ♫
♫ Fly towards the dawn ♫
♫ Heart beating heavily ♫
Good afternoon, Luzhou control tower.
Luzhou 8308,
36 Right, runway established.
♫ Contrail slashing across the sky ♫
Got it, Luzhou 8308.
You may approach Runway 36 Right.
♫ Who says it's cold up there ♫
Approaching Runway 36,
Luzhou 8308.
♫ I want the sun to shine brighter ♫
♫ Ignite the courage in my heart ♫
♫ Overlook the world ♫
♫ Like a free monsoon ♫
♫ Over the highest peak ♫
♫ In the troposphere ♫
♫ Fly towards the dawn ♫
♫ In the stratosphere ♫
[Diagram of the landing position of the domestic plane D191]
♫ Heart beating heavily ♫
♫ Contrail slashing across the sky ♫
[Flight to You]
[The End]