[English subtitles are available]
[Flight to you]
[Episode 2]
[Luzhou Airlines]
Mr. Xu,
for the arrangement to transfer pilots from the Freight Department
to our Passenger Transport Department,
we still want to talk with you about it.
Is there any problem?
I admit that Cai from the Freight Department
is very
skilled in the techniques.
But this man looks carefree.
The pilots who work under him
all learn from him.
Now such a group of people
will be transferred to our Passenger Transport Department.
I'm afraid it will affect
the image of our Passenger Transport Department.
Nanting.
I want to hear your opinion.
The Passenger Transport Department
is applying for new air routes.
There won't be enough pilots.
The pilots in the Freight Department
were also trained by the Luzhou Airlines with great efforts.
They're skilled enough in the techniques.
I think
we should give them a chance.
Of course, we must be strict in other aspects.
I agree with Nanting.
Okay.
Let's check their performance strictly.
But even so,
let's not accept that girl
from the Freight Department.
We can recommend her to the Freight Department of other airline company.
Why?
She hasn't got married or given birth to a child yet.
Mr. Jiang,
let's stop talking about this topic.
It might cause a problem.
We're talking about it behind closed doors, aren't we?
Besides,
the ability of a female pilot
is not good enough.
Flight ability has nothing to do with gender.
It only has something to do with individuals.
What about the usage rate?
The usage rate of female pilots is low.
Isn't that a consensus?
According to the statistics of our entire industry,
for the female pilots recruited by other companies,
when it comes to the flight time,
safety record and normal rate,
their performance isn't worse than that of male pilots'.
-Mr. Jiang. -But...
I remember the Flight Department has not recruited
any female pilots
for five years. Right?
Last year,
I made a report about the feasibility
of recruiting female pilots for the Passenger Transport Department,
but I didn't get permission to proceed with it all the time.
I've long wanted to
discuss about it with Mr. Jiang.
Whether it's a male pilot or a female pilot,
they are both pilots.
We should treat them equally.
Well, for this matter,
let's do it as planned.
The plan remains the same.
However, during the interview,
you have to evaluate their performance strictly.
Okay?
Okay.
[Cabin of Luzhou Airlines]
-Miss Cheng. -Miss Cheng.
Hello.
-Xiao. -Xiao.
Fan.
Xiao.
Are you here to see the plane again?
Yes, I'm here to see my Little Seven.
After the renovation this week,
This 737 will be handed over there.
So soon?
Little Seven.
The first time when we worked together,
we went to Alaska.
Then we went to Rico and Armstrodan together.
We once transported industrial chemicals
and luxury yachts together.
Although you're old,
the feeling of operating on you isn't as good as before,
and your performance is so weak,
I still can't bear to part with you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Everything else is fine.
I have to go.
Cheng Xiao.
[8 a.m.]
[Interview Meeting of the Passenger Transport Department of Luzhou Airlines]
Be confident. Relax.
Be professional.
Cheng Xiao, go, go, go!
Mr. Gu.
For my operation on that day,
I thought about it afterwards.
I fully complied with the rules of the company's manual.
Besides, my skills
were good enough to assist me in completing the operation.
I thought about it, too.
You didn't break the rules.
But unless it's necessary,
pilots
shouldn't do extreme operations.
I'll make a new safety manual.
Your behavior will be forbidden.
They're coming out.
How was it? What did they ask?
Nothing. They only asked us a few simple questions. It's just a procedure.
I just saw
Big Devil was also inside.
Who?
Gu Nanting.
I heard from the Passenger Transport Department that
he's a nightmare for those pilots who want to get promoted.
The name "Big Devil" suits him so well.
Mr. Gu's flight skills are very good.
He is one of the best pilots
in our company.
No wonder he doesn't like anyone.
He's one of the best pilots?
After I go there, it might not be true.
Of course.
Captain Cheng is definitely the best
in the Freight Department.
Just see how I'll deal with him later.
Next two candidates, Cheng Xiao and Song Song.
Come on!
Let's wait and see.
Hello, leaders.
Sit down.
Mr. Gu.
This is my resume.
Please have a look.
If you have any questions,
please ask me.
Cheng Xiao, right?
Don't be so serious.
We're just chatting.
Have a seat.
Mr. Gu,
she mentioned you just now.
You should ask her questions.
Why did you choose
the career as a pilot?
Because of freedom.
Flying can make us get rid of gravity.
I can be so free on the surface of the Earth,
and sit in an office where I can see the most beautiful sceneries in the world,
chasing the sun and having stars' company.
Of course,
there is another important and pracitcal reason.
The income is high.
The career as a pilot can give me economic freedom
so that I can follow my heart
and live more freely.
So,
this is your attitude with which you fly a plane?
Flight work is about rules and discipline.
You have to pay the price of freedom
to fulfill your duty.
Do you know how serious this job is?
I joined this company in 2013.
My flight time is up to 3,500 hours.
My flight experience time is as long as 2,700 hours.
There is no error record.
All the evaluations have been passed excellently.
Besides,
I also have the certificate of Aviation English Level Five,
and the qualification of English communication for international flights.
This is my answer to serious work.
[Xie Zetian, Luzhou Airlines]
[Director of the Security Department of Luzhou Airlines]
For your recent performance,
you landed at the extreme wind speed.
No matter how stable the landing was,
there should be a comment on it.
The weather was so bad that day.
With my good skills, I managed to
land the plane safely.
Is there a problem?
Did we have to divert the plane to land it elsewhere,
and make the company lose hundreds of thousands of yuan?
Flight safety is not measured by money.
I'll say it again.
There wasn't any problem with my landing operation.
Nor did I violate
the current flight safety manual.
Since you're in the Passenger Transport Department,
let's wait till the interview is finished,
and then have further communication about
the landing operation on that day.
What do you think?
I think we still need to discuss
whether Cheng Xiao can join the Passenger Transport Department.
Mr. Gu,
the pilots of the Freight Department are transferred to the Passenger Transport Department.
This is the company's arrangement.
Well,
leaders,
we've just been transferred from the Freight Department to here.
Our working state in ordinary times
may be different from that in the Passenger Transport Department.
We will learn more
and get used to it as soon as possible.
A pilot is the soul of a plane.
Our job
relates to the safety of passengers
and the company's property.
We can't be careless whenever it is.
I agree with that.
However,
I came back from Hokkaido after my vacation last month.
I took the flight XD884 of our company.
For the Captain's Public Address,
I only heard it once while the plane was landing.
Mr. Gu,
is this rigorous enough?
Lin Yicheng.
Mr. Gu.
What was wrong with
the Captain's Public Address during the cruise?
Yes, I was the copilot that day.
Captain Zhang authorized me to do
the Captain's Public Address.
That's Mr. Jiang's brother-in-law.
There was a lack of one public address indeed.
I was not feeling well that day.
I had a cold.
If you fly a plane while having a cold,
your eardrums might be perforated.
You should've taken a day off that day.
Yes, yes.
I think Cheng Xiao's suggestion
is very good.
Lin Yicheng,
in the future, you must have higher standard
on the details of your work.
Okay.
Don't do it again.
Cheng Xiao,
the problem you pointed out
is correct.
Lin Yicheng,
Go back and study the operational manual.
Write a self-criticism report with Captain Zhang.
Okay, Mr. Gu.
So, Mr. Gu,
please don't look at me with colored glasses.
And don't doubt my ability in my job.
Ability is the combination of skills and attitude.
Without a serious and modest attitude,
no matter how good your skills are,
you can't guarantee the safety of flight for 100 percent.
Based on your current understanding of this profession,
even if the company lets you to join the Passenger Transport Department,
you must start from working as
an observer.
Observer?
Leaders,
isn't this too unfair?
Do you have any objections
to Mr. Gu's conclusion?
According to Cheng's credentials,
she is qualified to get promoted to captain.
It seems a bit inappropriate
to demote her to an observer suddenly.
How about
letting her fly a plane again before we decide?
How about this?
I'll arrange you two to fly a plane again tomorrow.
You think Mr. Gu's arrangement like this
is unfair, don't you?
Then fly the plane well,
show your true level of skills,
and prove it to him.
Then we'll decide
whether you can
keep your position as First Copilot.
Are you confident?
[Luzhou Airlines—Flight Training Department]
[Simulator Training Center]
It's a test for me today.
You took the advantage and became the main pilot.
I'm not the main pilot.
I was replaced.
Who will be the main pilot instead?
Mr. Gu will personally lead the flight.
Xiao, be careful.
Don't let anything go wrong.
What could go wrong?
The copilot is supposed to assist the captain anyway.
Besides, Gu Nanting is the best pilot.
With his level and my ability,
for a test like this,
I can pass it without much effort.
Let's go, Xiao.
Go.
Luzhou is flying to Hongqiao, Shanghai.
The flight time will last for 1 hour and 30 minutes.
Take off with Flap Five.
The decision speed of taking off is 135.
May the weather be fine throughout the trip.
Wait.
Take off your jewelry.
It won't affect my operation even if I'm wearing jewelry.
Besides, the company doesn't forbid wearing jewelry.
It's my rule.
Please take them off.
Don't you have a pocket?
Luzhou 8513.
Runway 34L.
Ready to take off.
The parameters are stable.
Adjust and determine the takeoff thrust.
The takeoff thrust set, 80 nautical miles.
Check.
Decision speed of taking off.
Lift the front wheels up.
They're going up.
Retract the wheels.
Instruction mode.
Raise the rotation speed to 15.
Flap One.
Flap One. Green light.
Flap Zero.
Flap Zero. Lights out.
Pressure boost is normal.
Post-take-off Checklist.
Engine bleed. Open.
Air conditioning unit. Automatic.
Landing gear. Retracted. Turned off.
Flap. Retracted. Lights out.
The Post-take-off Checklist is finished.
The weather is so nice today.
A flock of birds.
The left engine failed.
The captain has an acute brain infarction and loses his capability.
The copilot will take over the captain's work.
What?
You...
PANPANPAN.
[A special phrase to call for help]
Luzhou 8513.The left engine failed.
Requesting emergency return.
Got the signal for help.
Luzhou 8513.
Turn right to 113.
Runway 34L, available for landing.
Turn right to 113. Runway 34L.
Luzhou 8513.
Automatic driving is connected.
Do you smell it?
What smell is it?
Be serious.
Didn't the birds get caught up into the engine?
Can't you smell the burning of them?
Let me treat you to barbecue tonight.
The right engine has also stopped.
The automatic driving is closed, too.
Both engines failed.
The plane is completely out of power.
Sink rate.
Observer, drag the captain out.
You take the left pilot seat.
Do it.
Ready to reboot. Right engine.
Reboot failed.
Luzhou 8513.
Report your flight intention.
You can choose any runway to land.
The plane can't fly to the airport now.
Prepare for off-site forced landing.
We must turn the plane into a glider.
Lower the head of the plane a bit.
Luzhou 8513.
Please confirm where you are going to land.
The grassland which is 20 kilometers away
from my 040 direction.
Grassland? Are you sure?
At your 9 o'clock direction
there's the 400-meter-wide Dongpu River.
It's better than the grassland.
We can't go to the Dongpu River now.
The speed of surface wind is 8m per second.
The wind speed will be higher on the river.
The wind direction is unstable, too.
It's easy to make the plane overturn.
It's safer to land on the grassland.
Captain's Public Address.
Me?
Right now!
Cabin, attention.
It's the Captain's Public Address now.
Something's wrong with the plane. We are making an emergency landing now.
Cabin, please make anti-collision preparations.
Flap One.
Flap One. Green light.
Flap Five.
Flap Five. Green light.
Flap 15.
Flap 15. Green light.
Shall we release the wheels？
No.
Flap 30.
Too low. Gear.
Prepare for forced landing.
500 feet.
Make anti-collision preparations.
Too low. Pay attention to the terrain.
Be careful with the terrain. Pull it up.
300 feet.
It's close to the decision height.
Decision height.
50 feet.
The anti-collision operation begins.
Sink rate.
40 feet.
Pull up.
30 feet.
20 feet.
10 feet.
Crew of the cabin, get into your positions.
Evacuation checklist.
Evacuation checklist!
Alright.
Let's stop here.
Song Song,
we created a miracle.
Gather in the lecture room.
[Lecture Room 9]
Thank you.
You're welcome
Mr. Nanting, thanks for your hard work. Have some water.
I don't like soft drinks. Thanks.
What do you think of
your own performance today?
Under the extreme circumstance that
the captain lost his capability and both engine failed,
I managed to land the plane safely
and there was basically no damage to the plane.
I'm very satisfied with my operation.
What do you mean?
According to the procedures,
if the engine is broken,
it's impossible to reboot it successfully.
Asking Song Song to drag the unconscious captain out
was a waste of time.
Constantly restarting the engines was a waste of time.
According to the procedures,
asking him to help you monitor
each parameter of the plane
could better increase the success rate of forced landing.
The procedures are not inflexible.
Procedures
are the summary of experience and lesson.
They're made with blood.
Captain Sullenberger from the US Airways
also encountered the problem of both engines failing,
and he did the forced landing successfully.
Captain Sullenberger
didn't follow the procedure.
His first reaction
was asking the copilot to activate the auxiliary power unit.
Captain Sullenberger
has a profound understanding about flying a plane.
That's why
he ventured to adjust the order of the procedure.
As an ordinary pilot,
strictly following the procedures
is the best guarantee for safety.
I surely follow the procedures
and respect the rules.
But rules and procedures are not dead.
They are constantly changing and improving.
If you really care about the rules,
when the engines stopped,
you wouldn't have thought about barbeque.
We have to get trained like flying a real plane
and fly a plane like getting trained. This is the rule.
I agree with you.
Any flight operation must be done seriously.
I've always been doing it like that.
But we still need to relax mentally.
If you keep being tense,
it'll be easy for you to make mistakes.
When you were relaxed,
you had a colleague by your side
who needed emergency treatment.
There's the best treatment period for acute cerebral infarction.
But it wasn't true.
It was a simulation.
Based on what you said,
I'm 100% sure that
you have to start over in the training.
You...
Alright. Alright.
About this,
I'll think it over with Mr. Gu.
Come to my office
in ten minutes.
Don't be angry, Xiao.
You made me confused.
At first,
I was a bit worried about these female pilots.
You insisted on giving them another chance.
Why are you hold an attitude like this now?
I strived for a chance for all the female pilots.
There shouldn't be any difference in treatment because of gender.
Tell me what you think of
Cheng Xiao now.
Today,
it was supposed to be a test for her as a copilot.
When she saw that the captain was me,
she tended to think rashly in the beginning.
I set up the situation of both engines failing
because I wanted to take the edge off her spirit.
I didn't expect her to land the plane safely.
She is indeed excellent.
However,
her attitude in the evaluation
was not good enough
to meet the standard for a passenger flight pilot.
Look.
I told you so.
The pilots from the Freight Department
developed a habit like that long ago.
It's hard to change it.
Especially Cheng Xiao.
If she really comes here,
there will be a lot of trouble.
After the interview finished yesterday,
I asked each department
and learned about the pilots from the Freight Department in details.
At work, Cheng Xiao
can endure hardships and likes studying challenging problems.
She has outstanding strengths.
So,
I take back my opinion that Cheng Xiao
is not suitable for the Passenger Transport Department.
Let her participate in
the transition training for the 787 plane.
Let her go to Australia?
She will have to stay in Australia for two months.
What if she is still unqualified in the end?
Then the company's resources will be wasted.
Any potential talent
deserves the company's resources.
Come in.
Mr. Jiang.
Let Mr. Gu tell you.
Cheng Xiao,
from now on,
you are going to prepare for the transition training of 787.
After the training, your post will be determined
according to your performance.
You will give me another test?
What kind of attitude is that?
It's about the company's rules and regulations.
It's not a difficulty created to you deliberately.
It's settled then.
Mr. Gu will be
the full-time instructor for the pilots of your group.
Mr. Jiang,
can we change the instructor?
Why?
Mr. Gu looks young,
but we all know his ability.
However,
we have to thank Nanting fo his coming hard work.
I can only rest assured by handing this group of pilots
to your hands.
Okay.
Sorry.
I have something to do.
So...
Go ahead with your work.
I'll wait for the next one.
I won't give you another chance to get something on me.
See you at the training ground.
You have to keep all the promises
you've made.
Not only will I achieve them all,
I'll also do better than you.
Who is this?
You're back.
How long have you been waiting?
If you didn't show up in 30 minutes, I would leave.
It's worth if if I could make Mr. Gu, who cherishes time
so much, wait for 30 minutes.
Why are you here?
I went to Seattle to study for half a month and I've just been back.
I'm going to make a report to the leaders.
Have you learnt anything from the Boyin headquarters?
I've learnt a lot.
I even went into the general assembly shop of 787.
Recently, to pilot 787, I've always felt that
the automatic push of the engine has changed rapidly.
The stability of the five sides's pitching is low.
I can solve your problem this time.
I'll go back to the cabin to sort out the information,
and send it to your email box tomorrow.
When you're free, let's play basketball.
I'm going to Australia next week. Two months.
Let's make an appointment next time. It's too difficult.
Next time.
Xia Zhi.
What's wrong? You lost your key of the house again?
This time,
it's not about losing the key.
You have no money to pay the rent?
Tell me how much you want to borrow this time.
Xiao,
I'm not borrowing money this time.
I want to live here.
Xiao,
you must save me this time.
I saved you every time.
Just live here.
But maybe you won't live here for so long.
Are you moving elsewhere?
It's a secret for now.
But it should be fine for you to live here
until you get your salary.
Polly. You must be hungry.
Actually,
I think I've lost my job.
You lost your job again?
It's been two years since I graduated,
and I've done seven jobs.
Why didn't I get a stable job?
It's only been two years since you graduated.
It's normal to feel lost.
Then why do you want to be a pilot?
Maybe I think by being a pilot, I can have no constraint
and have so much freedom.
Who are you fooling?
How can you say such a vulgar excuse?
With your temper,
who can constrain you?
You have to keep all the promises you've made.
When I viewed the recruitment website today,
I've found that your company is conducting a social recruitment.
Yes. The company has been reorganizing all the departments recently.
I've been suffering from it.
What do you think
if I apply for a job in your company?
You want to learn flying planes?
I'm not that stupid.
I mean
I saw that how you were badly tortured
while you were learning to fly planes.
I won't learn it.
So you are...
Actually,
I want to be a stewardess.
Stewardess?
They travel around the world for free,
and check out all kinds of delicious food in the world.
Enough, Ms. Xia Zhi.
Don't cause trouble to the career of stewardess.
What are you talking about?
Is there
any hope for me?
Will you believe me if I tell you there's no hope?
Okay, okay, okay.
Alright. Give it a try if you want to do it.
If it doesn't work, I'll support you economically.
Alright. I'm going to send my resume.
Mr. Nanting.
We'll work under you from now on.
I look forward to working with you.
You're flattering him too early.
He's talking still on the phone outside.
He can't hear you.
I'm just practising in advance.
He has collected more models than me.
Tomorrow, we'll arrange a trip to Luzhou Airlines' base in Australia
to start the modification training of 787.
Tomorrow?
So soon?
I've sent the specifications
of the modification to your email boxes.
You must memorize them all.
Go back and get ready.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
Mr. Nanting,
I look forward to working with you
The door is still open.
No need to close the door.
[Middle Conference Room]
[Interview for Flight Attendants]
Please confirm your resumes again.
Tidy up your appearances.
Put away the shattered hair on the sides.
Don't be nervous when you go in.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I'll be my turn soon.
Be careful.
45 degrees to the right.
[Liang Yueru, Luzhou Airlines]
[Chief of the Cabin Department of Luzhou Airlines]
Smile.
Grin.
45 degrees to the right.
Turn right.
[Ai Jia, Luzhou Airlines]
[Cabin Department, Manager of Division One]
[Director of the Cabin, Class A Instructor]
Turn back.
Li Yuheng.
You graduated with a master's degree.
You're very highly educated.
Why do you want to be a flight attendant?
I like taking plane.
Every time I see flight attendants, I admire them.
A flight attendant's smile
can make the travelers, who have got tired from the journey,
feel warm.
So I want to be an excellent flight attendant,
and pass out the warmth.
As a flight attendant,
if a passenger chats with you
and invites you
to travel with him after landing.
What will you say?
Thank you for your kindness.
After landing,
we have uniform arrangements for the work.
It may not be convenient.
Do you need other services
or tea and drinks?
Okay. Thank you.
Next.
Xia Zhi.