[English subtitles are available]
[Flight to you]
[Episode 4]
Speak it.
Actually,
they asked me to come over
and give you a suggestion.
Suggestion?
What suggestion?
You've been practicing too hard lately.
It's already not easy for us to catch up.
Moreover, you applied for extra training.
Even Da Peng who is tall and well-built
has been overwhelmed.
Who asked you to catch me up?
We have no choice because
what Brother Nanting requires
are all Cheng Xiao's standards now.
Thank him so much.
He treats me
as a tool.
He can pick on me whenever he dislikes me.
How dare I make a mistake?
You are different.
You can pass normal training.
Brother Nanting is not as evil as you said.
That's because you didn't see his behaviour
when he was with me alone.
You two are alone together.
Listen to the point.
Let me ask you.
From the Freight Department to the Passenger Transport Department,
normally, as long as we pass the pilot transition training assessment,
the position can't be demoted, right?
Of course.
How did Gu Congxin treat me?
I’m already qualified to be a captain.
He insisted
to demote me from the first officer to an observer.
I slapped him in the face with the simulator test result,
but he didn't accept it.
He even gave me the last-place elimination.
The last one is demoted.
Who do you think he is targeting?
He does have something against you.
That's why I'm saying he is sinister.
He is clearly a scheming boy,
but he still pretends like a very upright, trustworthy man.
He's an undercover
and hard to deal with.
Do you think the foreigner
is the same species as us?
The water is so cold.
There are only cold water and cold water with ice here.
Excuse me.
I'd like some warm water.
Sorry, we don't serve warm water here.
Okay, thank you.
Warm water.
Is it for taking a shower?
I can't refute it.
You have to endure it.
We are not taking the blame for Gu Congxin.
I feel wronged.
Who knows us after the training?
Hold it.
Can you guys even understand all the English in the control room?
Can you understand English instructions?
They don't even understand what we're talking about.
Like this.
Tower. Tower. I do not speak English.
I hear that Chinese girls
don't have their minds.
Really?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you see their instructor?
What can you learn from him?
How to be weak and timid?
Ridiculous.
It's not about being weak or timid.
It's about incapability.
He’s just an instructor who is tough on the surface.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
What does she want?
What are you doing?
You must make a formal apology for your remarks.
Apologize, now.
You apologize first.
Why should we apologize first?
You started it.
You started it when you came here.
We've been putting up with you.
What are you talking about?
We speak English in Australia.
You speak Mandarin. You speak Mandarin.
Stop, stop, stop.
How about this?
We are pilots.
We solve the problems in the pilots’ way.
What do you mean?
The flight simulator test.
If I do better than you,
you say sorry
to all the Chinese trainees
in the same way your teacher did.
The flight simulator test.
Sounds funny.
But you'd better think about
what happens if you lose.
There is a strong possibility that it could happen.
I will apologize in the same way
and double the punishment.
Sounds simple.
Double?
Yes.
Deal.
Alright.
I got you, man.
Xiao,
you tell us to endure.
Why did you go first?
I've been putting up with it.
There's a limit to my tolerance.
[Luzhou Airlines]
Do you know why I recruited you?
Your height and weight are merely over the acceptance boundary
and you're not behaving properly.
I persuaded Ms. Liang from Flight Attendant Department
to hire you.
Because I saw
affability and flexibility on you.
I thought that was a good virtue
to bring you and the passengers closer.
But now I'm worried.
I think it might backfire.
No.
I didn't do it well.
Ms. Ai.
In the future,
I will study hard and practice hard.
I promise.
Are you sure you want to compete against the female trainee from Gu's team?
Yes, sir.
I'm confident I can beat her.
It sounds a bit like looking down on them,
but sir,
Eric just simply has
more than 200 hours on
a 787 simulator.
I guess that Chinese girl
has never seen one of those simulators.
It's gonna be so much fun.
And it's gonna be easy.
It will be very good too to see her with buckets of ice on her head.
Yes, I can't wait to see Gu's face.
Wind shear recovery.
It's really comfortable.
So,
besides
working,
studying and running,
it's great to waste some time
and take a walk like what we are doing now.
There's a lot of fun in life.
Finishing every flight safely
is my pleasure.
You haven't let it go yet.
What?
You know what I'm talking about.
The female pilot who works so hard.
I can tell from your attitude towards her.
You still couldn't let it go.
I'm doing my job.
It has nothing to do with other things.
Nanting,
have you ever thought about
not only one mode is allowed
in your life?
Pilots
also have different personalities other than yours.
[Gu is Recalling]
[I miss summer the most.]
I haven't talked to you for a long time.
I've been busy with work lately.
Ni Zhan is busy too.
We're all good.
RA descends.
Disengage the autopilot.
Disengage the autothrottle.
RA descends.
Take off...
Disengage the autopilot.
Disengage the autothrottle.
Next group.
You and Cheng Xiao work together
to complete the simulation project
with unreliable air speed.
Okay.
Where is your Wonder Woman?
What do you mean?
I don’t know.
I'll call Xiao.
No one answered.
I saw
Xiao posted something on Moments
in the middle of the night.
I must be staying up in the classroom
if not at the bar.
Cheng Xiao.
Cheng Xiao!
What's wrong?
Has she been up all night?
Yes.
She has this on her belly.
She must be on her period.
I gave her a glucose transfusion.
Let's wait for her to wake up.
She was overworked
and overtired.
Thanks. We will take good care of her.
I found out yesterday.
I didn't take it seriously.
It's not your fault.
This question is beyond the outline for you.
I'm an instructor.
I can't make any excuses.
Female pilots
have their own unique characteristics.
It’s not easy for a female pilot.
Especially Cheng Xiao.
She is too hard-working.
But as
a qualified passenger pilot,
she needs to be self-disciplined.
Actually, I understand you.
Punish her. It doesn't make sense.
But if you just let her go,
she will do that again.
How is it?
You can't do anything when you meet a female pilot like her, right?
She is reckless and lacks self-discipline.
These are all fundamental defects.
The point is she doesn't know these.
Go back to work.
I'm free today.
I can stay here.
I have to be responsible for my trainee.
There are more trainees
waiting for you outside.
Fine.
Tell me if you have any problems.
No worries.
By the way,
there's something wrong with you today.
What?
I haven't seen you
panicking like this for years.
It's out of control.
I'm not used to it.
Thanks.
Song,
I was a little late accidentally yesterday.
Then I might have fainted.
Thank you for sending me to the infirmary
and preparing sandwiches for me.
Help me to apply for sick leave from Gu Nanting.
You're awake.
It's difficult to find a cup of
ginger tea with brown sugar.
Here.
It's hot.
Don't you recognize me?
A car driver.
Mr. Ni.
Thank you.
It's hot.
Why are you here?
You fainted in the classroom.
You found me.
It was Mr. Gu.
What?
Are you embarrassed to be a pacesetter
or are you afraid of being criticized?
Mr. Gu is...
What’s his attitude?
He wanted to stay and take care of you,
but I persuaded him to leave.
Why don't I believe it?
Mr. Ni.
Are you here for training?
This is Mr. Gu’s territory.
I dare not interfere.
I'm here for a meeting
and also an aviation exhibition.
Is it the Silong Aviation Exhibition?
Yes.
I heard that the most advanced fighter aircraft will attend.
And the pilots who do the performance
are one in a million.
I am going to watch it this afternoon.
Can you
cover me?
I want to go too.
Can you stand it?
Have a good rest.
As long as I take a look,
I'll have the best rest.
Please.
I'm looking forward to this aviation exhibition so much.
I've been looking forward to it, please.
No, no, no.
If I take you there,
Nanting will strangle me to death.
The sun is rising from the west today.
I made a mistake twice.
Mr. Gu didn’t reprimand me.
The same goes for me.
I think
Mr. Gu probably thinks highly of my potential.
Enough, both of you. Enough.
Mr. Ni.
You're handsome.
You must be kind-hearted as well.
Please help me.
Please.
Listen.
I'm quitting sugar recently.
Your sugar-coated bullets are useless.
You...
But I...
[Gu Nanting]
Speak of the devil.
Don't expose yourself.
Just tell him
that I need to stay for observation.
Please.
How is Cheng Xiao?
She just woke up.
I need to be observed.
She's still weak.
The doctor said
she needs to stay here for a while.
Tonight.
I'll send her back later.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Just treat me to a meal later.
Mr. Ni.
You're a good person.
Nanting owes me a meal.
No problem. A big meal.
And my meal is definitely bigger than his.
Drink the ginger soup first.
Brother Nanting, Xiao...
Sick leave.
You knew it.
Is she okay?
Just a minor illness.
Brother Nanting,
you just met Xiao.
Xiao is very diligent and serious.
Technically,
she is the best pilot
in our Freight Department.
Did she often practice overnight before this?
Of course.
In terms of training,
Xiao is invincible.
Flying is more important than her life.
Sorry.
[Ni Zhan]
You, go down.
I...
Thank you for sending me to the infirmary.
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
I bought some fruits downstairs today.
The price has risen.
Did the price of apples rise?
For me?
Thank you for your concern.
Have a good rest.
[Luzhou Airlines, In-Flight Service Training Department]
The core of our training today
is safety awareness.
Many people have misunderstandings
towards flight attendants.
They think we are just waiters in the air.
But in fact,
our first job is to be a cabin expert.
The priority of the flight attendant
is to ensure the safety of the flight
and the safety of passengers.
So for the next 90 percent of the time,
we are training for some safety skills.
Today we are training for
the emergency treatment when the cabin caught fire.
Team One, get ready.
Sir.
There's a fire signal from the restroom.
Rescue immediately.
I'll put out the fire.
Is anyone there?
I'm running out of fire extinguishers.
Who will help me?
I'll help you.
Chief flight attendant.
The fire is under control.
Next team, get ready.
During emergency,
every flight attendant
should put on the life jacket
before helping the passengers.
Never pump air into the life jacket
when in the cabin.
Does anyone know why?
Xiazhi.
It is because
the plane has to make a forced landing
on the water surface during an emergency.
If the plane is damaged and the cabin is flooded,
the passengers in the life jacket
may be on the top of this cabin.
But the emergency exit is at the bottom of the cabin.
So it may cause
the passengers can't evacuate.
Good.
I'm still thinking about how to treat it.
I have some ideas.
I'll wait and see.
Here's a gift for you.
Su 57.
This is the limited edition of the aviation exhibition. You can't find it in China.
Did you shoot the formation performance?
You told me so many times.
Of course I did.
Let me show you.
Warrior and Yuyan were there.
They also had a tight-formation collision
and Pugachev's Cobra.
Anyway, they played it all.
So bad that I can't get out.
I can't even go to the scene although it's so near.
I'll send it to you later.
There's also a hand-painted
Spitfire Fighter.
The price is too high.
I couldn't bear to buy it.
How can you not buy it?
I'll pay for it.
Look what this is.
I really didn't plan to buy it.
If someone hadn't reminded me.
You really like it.
How much is it? I'll transfer the amount to you.
That's all.
Is this the bag in the aviation exhibition?
Yes.
Take it with you.
Mr. Gu,
I want to talk to you.
What is it?
[Letter of Resolution]
You want to persuade me to quit.
I am not representing the company.
It's just my personal suggestion.
This is too much.
What do you mean?
The reasons, along with the suggestions,
are very detailed there.
If you don't like me,
you can do whatever you want,
all your means.
It's just an observer.
Even if I were an observer for another ten years,
I won't be a deserter.
You don’t know yourself.
You are not suitable to be a passenger pilot.
How can you say that?
A qualified passenger pilot
will not train all night until her health is damaged,
nor
leave the school breaking the rules
before recovering.
You are excellent and diligent in flying.
But what you lack
can’t be made up by hard work.
You love flying.
You can change it another way.
I can recommend some
flight fans clubs for you.
They welcome
a skilled retired pilot to teach there.
Retired pilot?
I haven’t officially served,
yet you want me to retire?
Gu Nanting, don't think too highly of yourself.
You can't control my life.
I hope you can
think calmly about my advice.
I don't need it.
I don't accept your advice either.
[Luzhou]
[Emergency Water Landing Evacuation Training]
Today we're having
a survival training when having a forced landing on the water surface.
Two people in a group.
One of them will play the role of a passenger.
Go get ready.
Team One, get ready.
Team Two, get ready.
What's wrong, Li Yuheng?
Ms. Ai, I...
I can't swim.
It's okay. You have a life jacket.
Yuheng.
You've been doing well.
It'll be fine too this time.
Believe in yourself.
Come on.
Go, Yuheng!
Are you okay?
Xia,
your hair.
I wanted to praise you for being
flexible and team-spirited for the first time.
Is that what you return to me?
I'm sorry, Ms. Ai.
I was wrong.
Why on earth did you want to be a flight attendant, Xiazhi?
I...
Some people take this job
as a stepping stone to success.
Once they marry a rich husband, they will change their professions.
Some people
have a real blue sky dream.
But in my perspective,
this is only an ordinary job.
Meet different passengers every day
and send them to their destinations safely.
This is my sense of accomplishment.
Do you know what my biggest reward is
when I feel so tired from working every day?
It is when every time the passengers
give me a sincere smile
and say thank you to me.
I think
the effort is worth it.
The flight attendant is never a cushy job.
Suffering.
Tiring.
Not to mention the stress,
it may lead to occupational diseases.
So if it's just a whim,
I suggest you
quit early
and stop the loss.
I admit that
I just wanted to give it a try
during the interview.
I didn't take this job seriously.
But after half a month of training,
I realized that
this job is not easy.
To be honest,
I've done many jobs before.
I've given up many times too.
But if I give up again this time,
I'm afraid that
I won't trust myself anymore.
If you pass the training assessment,
you'll be on the flight in about two months.
There is still time
for your hair to grow longer.
Instructor Gu,
I’ve thought about it.
I have my persistence.
Also, I'm not afraid of your revenge.
My personal advice
won’t affect your evaluation.
Every pilot the company dedicated to train
wants to stay.
But only if you pass.
I'll prove that I'm qualified.
But I want a fair witness.
No need.
You are the best witness.
I hope you can be fair to yourself.
[Top 1 in the theoretical exam, Third place in the fitness assessment]
[Scored perfect in the simulator test, The best performer in the field training program]
♫I always hope to see you♫
♫And tomorrow♫
Being unreasoning and impulsive
is the taboo of pilots.
♫I want to escape from the little things♫
Self-discipline and self-control
♫The origin of dilemma♫
are the cornerstone of pilots.
Always respect for flying.
Being strict with the rules and regulations
♫Even covered in mud♫
is the most reliable guarantee.
♫I have to wear a smile too♫
♫I look up♫
♫At the beginning of the shining light♫
♪ Can't wait ♪
♫Start a new transformation♫
♫Like a shining star♫
♫Just cross this over♫
Recover from the stall.
Disengage the autopilot.
Disengage the autothrottle.
♫Dream travels♫
♫Between the thorns♫
Recover from the stall.
♫Like a shining star♫
Disengage the autopilot.
Disengage the autothrottle.
♫Just cross this over♫
Push!
♫See you after the storm♫
♫I always want to say goodbye♫
♫To yesterday♫
♫I want to forget all those upset♫
♫The fragments of emotions♫
Place your bets.
♫I always hope to see you♫
A pair of Kings. I have a pair of Aces.
Ace is bigger.
♫And tomorrow♫
Come on.
Xiao,
♫I want to escape from the little things♫
♫The origin of dilemma♫
♫Even covered in mud♫
♫I have to wear a smile too♫
♫I don't want to be seen♫
♫The fragile side♫
♫I look up♫
♫At the beginning of the shining light♫
♪ Can't wait ♪
♫Start a new transformation♫
Ram air turbine switch.
♫Like a shining star♫
Auxiliary power unit selector.
♫Just cross this over♫
Sir, please open the window shade.
♫Dream travels♫
Thank you.
♫Between the thorns♫
Please make sure your seat back is straight up.
Thank you.
♫Like a shining star♫
♫Just cross this over♫
Sir, what would you like to drink?
♫Fly bravely♫
Welcome aboard.
♫See you after the storm♫
Mr. Polly.
What would you like to drink?