=Best Choice Ever=
=Episode 2=
So today you want to know about
Deshan Home Furnishings'
recent production
- and the supply situation.
- You, come here.
Let me introduce you.
This is Miss Mai,
the secretary of Mr. Yao.
This is my son, Xin Jialiang.
Jialiang?
Do you two know each other?
Dad.
This is my girlfriend.
Sorry, Mr. Xin.
I'm here for work today.
Let's just talk about business first.
I...
don't quite understand.
Is Mr. Yao
too busy
to see me?
Or is he using you
to deal with me?
Mr. Xin.
I didn't know about
your relationship with Jialiang.
I just found it out.
So it's impossible
that Mr. Yao knows it.
He asked me to come today
to have an initial contact with you,
so that Yueda and Deshan
could make a close partnership.
We are very sincere.
I see. It's our fault.
It must be that our relevant person
did not make good contact with Mr. Yao.
It's our fault.
Well, from today on,
I'll handle all the work
between Deshan and you.
I'll tell
whatever Mr. Yao
wants to know.
Is it okay?
I will tell Mr. Yao about it.
Good. Well,
since Mr. Yao is busy with work today,
we can make an appointment another day.
Is it okay?
Then I'll see you out.
Thank you.
- This way, Mr. Xin.
- Okay.
Mr. Xin, take care.
Mr. Yao said he will visit you some day
to express his apologies.
Okay, I'll wait for him.
Take care, Mr. Xin.
Dad, you go ahead.
Goodbye.
Huan, Huan.
Huan, Huan...
Please listen to me, okay?
Actually, my dad just runs
an ordinary company,
and he's an ordinary
small business owner.
I...
That's it.
Xin Jialiang.
How long have we been together?
Of course, I know it.
Yesterday was our third anniversary.
Over these one thousand days,
your act like a Shanghai drifter
and a home designer.
Your parents are nearing retirement
back in hometown.
Get off me.
I want to ask you.
Which of these is real?
You said
you weren't used to Shanghai food,
so I learned to make dishes
from your hometown for you.
I stayed up all night saving up
for any pair of shoes you like.
You said the company wanted to fire you,
I made plans
and career summaries for you.
I helped you with interviews,
and asked my classmates to refer you.
I couldn't sleep all night
because of your future.
And now you're telling me,
you are a rich kid
and don't need to work hard.
Xin Jialiang.
You take me for a fool, right?
No, no.
Are you happy
fooling me around?
Huan.
I am really sorry about this.
I did have a bit of a cover-up
in the beginning.
But later I realized this mistake.
I've been looking for
a chance to tell you.
But I was afraid you'd be mad.
You don't have to tell me anymore.
Because I'm not going to believe
every word you say.
No, no.
You have to believe
what I'm about to say.
I really love you.
I swear I do love you.
Well, you go to work now.
Wait until dinner time at your house,
I will apologize to you
and explain properly.
Don't come over tonight.
Because I don't want to see you.
Huan, Huan.
It's just that simple
and especially clear.
Xin Jialiang is playing
the role of a poor person
to find his true love.
Honestly, if I were Mai Chenghuan,
I would be very mad. Let alone her.
How do you know Mai Chenghuan
isn't just playing along?
Mr. Yao, if you think so,
that's really cynical.
Go get her here.
Now?
I mean,
if Mai Chenghuan really
knows nothing about it,
then what?
It's none of my business.
As long as she has a relationship
with Xin Jialiang,
she's useful.
Impressive.
The two of them...
I'll go get her.
Chenghuan.
Come in.
Mr. Yao.
I just met Mr. Xin.
How's it?
This matter is somewhat weird.
Mr. Xin...
Mr. Xin is my boyfriend's father.
I just found it out today.
So did he.
So he thought
I'm using this relationship
to get the trust
of Deshan Home Furnishings,
and was somewhat wary of me.
Mr. Yao, I'm sorry to fail you.
It's not that serious.
Love relationship is a personal affair.
And you're only filling in today.
Don't overthink it.
About your job,
I will consider it.
Huan, where are you and Xin Jialiang?
I've shown my respect
and made six dishes and one soup.
Remind him
he owes me an explanation.
Huan, this time it's going to be tough.
Ask Jialiang to perform well.
It's better to come up with a plan
to put your mom
at ease.
Got it?
Okay, Dad. I got it.
You are back.
I'm back.
I'll do it.
Ms. Wang, pour me a glass of water.
Thank you.
Okay.
Today didn't go well?
He got a crush on the secretary
and made a mess.
Dad.
Don't call her the secretary.
She has a name,
Mai Chenghuan.
She's my girlfriend.
Water.
Jialiang.
Give me a day next week.
I'll take you to meet
the daughter of Ms. Zhang.
What are you going to do?
Jialiang.
You're going to take over from your dad.
Wouldn't it be better to find a wife
who could assist you?
Besides,
I'm not asking you
to break up with her right now.
You can be flexible.
Mom.
Be normal, okay?
Don't cause me troubles, okay?
I am concerned about you.
I love Mai Chenghuan,
and Mai Chenghuan loves me.
The two of us are so much in love
that no one can separate us.
Don't mention such things anymore.
Okay, Mom?
How can you talk to your mom like that?
So rude.
I'm not eating here tonight.
I have something to do.
It's urgent.
Whatever.
He is becoming more and more reckless.
That's because you spoiled him.
He's already 30 and still so rude.
Childish.
I'm back.
You are back.
Where is Xin Jialiang?
He has to work overtime today,
so he won't come.
He bought this for you
and asked me to bring it back.
I'll put it here.
See? I told you
that guy is not reliable.
I asked him to be reliable,
and he dares not come now.
He has to work overtime.
Didn't you say
young people should be ambitious?
The man who often works overtime
must be ambitious.
Alright, you ask him
why he has to work overtime.
Why today?
He's just fooling us around.
Alright. If he's not coming,
we can eat by ourselves.
All you know is eat.
Do you know what that means?
What do you know? Alright.
You're a peacemaker.
It's so obvious...
Let me tell you the truth.
He doesn't work overtime.
We had a fight,
so he's not coming.
Had a fight?
Is it serious?
Nothing.
We'll be fine in a couple of days.
Good. Very well.
The fiercer the fight, the better.
You could just break up.
It's perfect.
He showed his true colors
through the meal.
What do you like about him?
He has neither money nor a house.
Alright, enough.
You don't know anything.
Why do you keep telling her to break up?
Break up.
I've seen him through.
He is silly.
He is so poor,
and yet he acts like this.
He's ruined three years of my daughter.
Three years.
It's so long.
Oh my. I can't even think about it.
When I think about it, I'll get mad.
It makes my heart hurt.
Okay, come on.
Don't be mad.
Mom.
Actually...
Huan, I was wrong.
Huan.
Can you give me a chance to explain?
Xin Jialiang, what are you doing?
Huan.
I was wrong, really.
It's all my fault.
I'll be honest with you.
My family
runs a home furnishings company
worth about a billion.
I live in the Cuihu villa community.
I have four properties in the city.
I have five more in my hometown.
Xin Jialiang, stop.
Worth billion?
You might make it go public.
Hello, Mrs. Mai. Hello, Mr. Mai.
Mrs. Mai.
Going public is very difficult.
I will
tell my dad about it.
And we'll both work hard.
- Huan.
- I will make it one day.
Is he telling the truth?
Of course not.
Huan, he is lying.
I have seen this online.
It's called
romance scam.
Inferior men pretend to be rich
and get the city girls.
Huan, sorry that I lied to you.
My bad.
Look, hear that?
He lied to you. Did you hear that?
Mom, he did lie to me.
But he didn't lie to me on this.
You rascal!
How dare you lie to us!
Do you want to die? Just wait.
Wait, mom.
Mom, what he said is true.
True? What?
Everything he just said is true.
He's indeed rich?
He's been with me so long
and lying to me.
He told me
he borrowed his car
and found it hard to get a job.
It all turned out to be a lie.
Mom, you are right.
He is just a liar.
Huan, don't be silly.
You have to get the point.
The point is he's been lying
to me for the past three years.
If I hadn't run into him at work today,
I would still be kept in the dark.
Mom, you are right.
I'm going down now
to make things clear with him.
Huan, listen to me.
Well...
I think...
T-Today...
H-He must have lied to you for a reason.
He is here to apologize now.
Right? You...
Kid, marriage is a serious matter.
You must be very careful.
- Don't do stupid thing.
- No, mom.
Wait, you...
I really love you.
- Really.
- Xin Jialiang.
Can you stop shouting?
Now you're disturbing others.
Leave now.
Don't listen to her. Don't leave.
Huan, listen to me.
Look how sincere he is.
With so many people around him,
he even doesn't care.
What does it mean?
He seems so pleasant to me today.
Look at him,
he's tall and pretty.
I really know I was wrong.
Listen to his explanation.
He's explaining.
Even though I lied to you,
I really love you.
Shut up!
Mom.
He's been pretending
to be poor all along,
asked me to top up
the game cards for him,
and repay the money for his loan.
He's been lying to me.
Wait, he's so rich,
but asking you to help him repay a loan?
Yes.
Did he pay you back?
He did pay back.
- Then it's nice.
- He couldn't do so.
Wait, Mom.
Get it straight.
Why did he lie to me?
He was afraid
that I would take his money.
Anyway,
let's get him in here today.
We can't let him
keep shouting down there.
Jialiang, come up.
I will help you.
No one can help him today.
If anyone does,
I'll get mad.
Huan.
I'll convince her.
Alright.
What are you doing?
Huan.
I feel like
I'm going to die.
During this period,
I can't eat
or sleep well.
I really love you.
I really do.
- Excuse me.
- Zao, you are back.
Everyone, sorry.
Sorry for disturbing you.
It's okay now. Just go back.
Go back.
Sorry, sorry.
Zao.
Wait, Jialiang. What's wrong?
You made such a big fuss.
Zao, help me convince your sister.
Hurry up.
Wait.
You had a fight with her?
Just a little misunderstanding.
Please. Just go.
Wait.
My sister has such a good temper.
If she ignores you,
you must have done something wrong.
Oh my.
You two are really
a family.
Huan!
Huan, I was wrong.
Can you be sincere?
You're causing a loud ruckus
in a public place, harassing women.
At the least,
it constitutes public disturbance,
with administrative fine.
At worst, you could be sued
for insulting women.
Do you have water?
I...
Hello.
Zao.
Just leave him and come up
for dinner.
Huan, I was wrong.
It's okay. I'm telling him the law.
Can you forgive me?
Hurry up. Just leave him.
I really know I was wrong.
Alright, Jialiang. I'm going up to eat.
Zao, Zao.
Don't leave me, Zao.
Zao.
Who hit me?
What's wrong with you?
You are so annoying.
You keep shouting.
Sorry, auntie.
Don't be mad.
But you do have a strong grip.
I can tell you're in good health.
I'm sorry.
Xin Jialiang, come with me.
What a mess.
I hope Jialiang can come up.
Otherwise, this meal
will be wasted.
Baby.
Here is the thing.
I didn't mean to do it
at first.
But my parents
were afraid
that I would be fooled,
so they asked me to do so.
Then do you mean
I would fool you?
No, no.
I feel bad
that I've been keeping it a secret.
I wanted to tell you
a million times in between.
Baby, don't be mad anymore.
I really,
really, really regret it now.
Xin Jialiang.
You have to promise me a few things.
No problem.
First,
I understand your concerns.
But since you can lie to me about it,
you might have lied to your family.
So I want you to tell your family
about me and my family,
so that they can
have a real understanding of me.
Okay.
I've told my parents about you honestly.
My parents, my dad in particular.
He really admires you,
thinking you're really nice,
indeed.
You did it again.
Second,
although you come from a wealthy family,
I hope that in the future,
we will work hard
to make money together,
not too dependent on your family.
Once you accept your parents' help,
they are bound to interfere in our life.
Understand?
Okay.
Third,
it's the most important one.
I hope there will be no lies
between us in the future.
You have to tell me everything.
We need to be honest with each other.
Can you do this?
Yes.
I will never lie to you again.
Later...
I-I'll draft an agreement.
Then the two of us will sign it.
I'll sign my name
and put a seal on it.
Get off me.
You are really a fool.
When Ms. Zhou hit you,
why didn't you dodge?
Is your head hurt? Let me see.
I just knew it.
You still care about me.
Xin Jialiang.
Forgive me.
Move.
(Yao Zhiming)
It's you mom again?
It's Mr. Yao.
Why is this guy calling you after work?
Keep silence.
I haven't secured my job yet.
Mr. Yao, hello.
Mai Chenghuan.
Regarding your job,
I have decided.
Given your professional attitude
and not showing favoritism,
you can come back to work.
Really? Mr. Yao?
But you did make some mistakes.
So just as you said,
your bonus for this quarter
will be deducted.
I see. I accept it.
Thank you, Mr. Yao.
Good news?
Jialiang.
I've secured my job.
Be careful.
I told you
that guy won't fire you.
What are you doing?
Xin Jialiang, put me down.
Stop.
My baby has secured her job.
Let go of me. Put me down.
My baby has also forgiven me.
Dad, Zao.
What are you doing here?
I came down to throw out the trash.
I came out for some fresh air.
Is that so?
Alright then, let's go home.
Wait.
Well,
it's been a while
since I bought you ice cream.
Come on, I'll treat you to an ice cream.
Let's go.
Dad's treating us to ice cream.
(Wanjiayan Store)
I've paid.
Here, take it.
I still remember, when we were little,
you would buy us ice cream,
without letting our mom know.
This is so hard.
Fresh out of the fridge.
Sis,
did that Xin Jialiang bully you?
Of course not.
He doesn't dare to.
Besides, even if he did,
would you really sue him?
No. I would avenge for you.
Don't worry.
We had a good talk.
And he explained and assured me.
We are fine now.
Huan.
Tell me more about this Jialiang.
Though you two have been dating
for three years,
he has never visited us.
I really don't know him.
Dad.
Actually, Jialiang
is really lovely,
completely different from me.
My life is boring.
While he has a wide range of hobbies.
He is good at designing
and photography.
He can be the leader in the game.
I remember one time,
he woke me up in the middle of the night
and said to take me to see the sunrise.
And then he picked me up
and drove me to see the sunrise.
I also have a wide range of hobbies.
I also have a lot of new things.
Are you jealous about it?
Fine.
I'll never get married
and stay home with you.
That's not necessary.
Well,
listen to me.
Talk about getting along with people,
you need time
to get to know
a person well.
As a saying goes,
time reveals a man's heart.
Don't worry, Dad.
We have already talked it over today.
He promised me
that he will never lie to me again.
We want to be happy together.
I just don't want to have regrets.
The same goes for my work.
And the same goes for love.
I know.
Your mom is calling.
Hello.
Yu.
Have you seen our daughter?
Yes.
Has she made up with Jialiang?
Yes. Don't worry.
Yu, let me tell you.
I just saw
something I shouldn't have seen.
Do you think I will
get a stye tomorrow?
Hey, I...
She hung up.
Dad, this is how you deal with our mom?
I...
I shiver when I see her.
Deshan?
Why can't I click it?
Right.
This is a pretty big business.
Mom might be asleep. Keep it down.
Okay.
Mom.
Why are you peeking at my computer?
No, no. I didn't...
I checked it for you.
Jialiang didn't lie to you.
His family is so wealthy.
Indeed.
Time to sleep.
- And you peek at my WeChat?
- Time to sleep.
No, no.
Time to sleep. Hurry up.
Huan.
Don't be mad.
I'll tell her
not to do so again.
(Sales Department)
- Morning.
Chenghuan.
Are you alright now?
Mr. Yao asked me to come back.
That's great, impressive.
Don't worry about me. Let's go.
Okay.
Everyone, get ready.
We'll have a meeting
in the conference room in 15 minutes
to discuss this year's
May 20th event schedule.
You are still here?
Yes, I'm still here.
Alright, let's have the meeting.
Sure.
Two matters.
First, the disciplinary action
against Mai Chenghuan is revoked.
And she'll keep her position,
but her bonus
for this quarter will be deducted.
Second, it's April now.
The wedding season is coming up soon.
May 20th event
is important for Botticelli,
also the kickoff
for the wedding peak season.
Mr. Yao, then
Sales and Marketing Department
will prepare the proposal right away.
No rush.
I'll give you one week.
Everyone has to come up with a proposal.
I'll get all the hotel departments
to vote on it.
Mr. Yao.
This is always a matter
of the Marketing Department.
There's no need to make the vote.
I hope Botticelli
can have more talents.
I
select the superior
and eliminate the inferior.
Mr. Zhu, are
your men incompetent?
Of course not.
Our department has talents
like Mai Chenghuan and Wu You.
They are our best people.
Very good.
The winner will
receive a special bonus
and two nights in an executive suite.
I look forward to your proposals.
You heard what Mr. Yao just said.
Open vote for proposals.
Everyone,
can our Marketing and Sales Department
keep the reputation?
As your leader,
can I keep my position?
It all depends on you.
Hurry up and go prepare the proposals.
It's good.
You all danced really well.
Well done.
Go have some water and take a rest.
Okay.
Ms. Liu, you really danced so well.
- Great, right?
- I was mesmerized.
Ms. Liu, there is something
I'd like to discuss with you.
Say it.
In next week's performance,
we have only one spot
for the lead dancer.
I know it.
We finally decided on Ms. Zhou.
Why?
I choreographed this dance,
and organized the rehearsals.
Why did you decide on her?
Ms. Liu, calm down.
To be honest,
the costumes are
all sponsored
by Ms. Zhou's future son-in-law.
The costumes are really beautiful.
That alone,
we've beaten the other community.
We're a big team.
Ms. Liu, please be generous
and think big.
Future son-in-law?
Nothing is set in stone yet.
Thank you, Ms. Liu.
Ms. Zhou, you danced wonderfully.
I really thank you.
No need.
His family runs a clothing store.
You'll get a discount
if you go there.
Okay, we'll definitely go.
Then have a good rest.
(Moments)
I can't
unfold my fan well.
Yes. See.
See.
When you are free,
don't just check the Moments.
The Moments
is attractive,
but always looking down
is bad for your cervical spine.
It's not good.
Liu, in the Moments you just post,
is that your future son-in-law?
You are fast. I just posted it.
The two of them make a good match.
A good match, right?
A good match.
What does he do?
A designer.
A designer?
His family also runs
a home furnishing company.
Amazing.
He's tall, rich, and handsome.
You're really blessed.
Not really.
Yesterday,
I saw it in an official account.
It's said really well.
The successful parents
are not just about
how successful their children are.
The key is,
when you get old,
they can accompany and take care of you.
Nothing is set in stone yet.
They are just dating.
What if they break up?
So you have something set in stone?
Don't be mad.
Let me see your future son-in-law.
I'll show you the photo.
(Sales Department)
Chenghuan, don't you leave?
I almost got fired,
so I need to work harder.
Chenghuan, you're working so hard.
Then we are leaving.
Goodbye.
- Bye.
Bye.
(Concern factors of Chinese non-single group
for booking 520 love hotel/homestay in 2023)
Mom.
Huan, what are you doing?
I'm going to make
pork trotter soup for you.
Mom, I have to work overtime today,
so I can't go back for dinner.
Again?
Don't burn yourself out.
I know.
You're almost 30.
The face is starting to lose collagen.
You're going to get wrinkles.
Mom, I just took on a big project.
The leaders are all watching.
Leaders?
Your leaders are so mean.
It's not working hour now.
What time is it now?
Your marriage matters.
Let me tell you.
Your main task now
is to make more contact with Jialiang.
Got it?
Mom.
I should count on my own abilities,
not on marrying someone.
How is it possible
to depend on others in life
and expect respect from others?
I know that, too.
I agree with you.
But for a girl,
marriage is very important.
After you marry Jialiang,
his family will surely want you
to have children, right?
So you have to take good care
of your health.
Don't burn yourself out.
Alright, Mom. The leader is calling me.
I have to go.
I'm hanging up.
- Mr. Mai.
- Coming.
Come help.
Coming.
I can't see it clearly.
I told you to buy reading glasses,
but you refused.
You regret it now?
I'm not wearing them.
They make me look old.
Hurry up.
Alright.
(Baby Liang)
(Baby, I've been waiting for you for 2.5 hours.)
(Are you still working?)
I've been waiting in line
for you all afternoon.
Have a taste.
What's it?
Be careful not to spill it.
Here.
Delicious.
Huan, your mom doesn't
hate me anymore, right?
Jialiang.
Actually, my mom
just wants the best for me.
So please stop judging her.
She is nice.
What? Why would I
judge her?
I know.
If I want to be
Mai Chenghuan's good boyfriend,
I must be good to her family.
But you are also very important.
Here you go again.
I have a call.
Take this.
It's my mom. Keep silence.
Mom.
It's so late now
and you're still out.
Oh my. I've made
the pig's trotter soup for you.
Auntie, hello.
J-Jialiang, you're there.
Huan
didn't even tell me.
Auntie.
Can I have dinner
at your house this weekend?
Of course.
Come anytime,
I always welcome you.
Well.
Jialiang, what do you want to eat?
Just tell me.
What do you like to eat?
Mom, Mom.
Well, I'm coming home right away.
Let's talk at home.
No, no. Don't rush. Take your time.
Take your time.
- I'm here...
- Got to go.
Are you really going?
You told me
to take this matter seriously.
Then, what do you suggest
I buy for your mom?
Maybe I buy her a bag.
My mom and my sister
just love buying bags.
No need.
Don't buy something that expensive.
Just buy
something that can show your sincerity.
Mr. Mai.
- Dinner.
- You scared me.
Dinner.
What?
W-Why did you turn off the TV?
Jialiang is coming to our house
for dinner tomorrow.
Jialiang is coming for dinner?
So what?
What should we do?
Right.
Put all these messy things
in the drawer
to make the house look cleaner.
Right.
We need to put this camp bed away
to make the house seem spacious
and cleaner.
It's so late to do so.
Zao will be back tomorrow.
He's going to be upset
when he finds the bed put away.
He's a boy, not that sensitive.
Besides,
her sister's marriage is a big deal.
He will understand.
It doesn't matter.
Let me tell you,
Jialiang is still Jialiang,
but he's not the old Jialiang.
We have to tidy up the house,
and make it clean and presentable.
Got it?
Come on, honey. Come on, have a seat.
No. Just say it.
Look, Jialiang and Huan
have been dating for years.
He knows our family well.
Do you think
just tidying up and cleaning
will turn this dump into a villa?
Do it or not?
Yes.
Call Zao
to come back early tomorrow morning.
Okay, got it.
Sweep the floor now.
Sweep it.
Be gentle.
Our house is in a mess.
If you don't clean it,
you never know what's inside.
Mr. Mai, what are you doing again?
What?
Hurry up and clean.
My sweetie
I don't know if I'm a good mother
It's my first time being a mother
Though the years
have turned my hair white
I'm too busy to have meals on time,
but that's not my fault
It will make me feel guilty
to let you know about it
I know you care about me
But it makes me feel like
I've never been trusted
Those carefree people can't be mothers
I know it all, but it breaks my heart
Please let me pursue the life
that belongs to me
I'm as brave and kind as you,
so I'm not afraid
One day, you will also become a mother
Will we embrace each other on that day
Like a stream traveling
around the world
And returning to where it came from
I hope you are loved
I hope you find happiness
I hope I can shelter you
from the storms
I know that we argue sometimes
I know that people will grow old
So we must say I love you out loud
- My mother watched me out of sight
- Are you nearly home
- My memories became so intense
- The door is open
Through the gentle times
Wherever you are is my home
Come back home
My sweetie
Please believe in yourself