(Stage Fighter)
One movement. One facial expression.
One breath. And one finger gesture.
Dancers express with their bodies.
Dance is a visual art,
so I believe that you must be born...
with the right length of your neck, size of your face,
length of your limbs, and height.
If your body looks beautiful,
just a stretch of your arm can get you the win.
I believe that physique is absolute in dance.
It's such an unfair type of art.
People tend to look away...
when the dancer is chubby or short.
I think he's chubbier than others.
If only he had lost about 3kg...
You don't even get an opportunity if you're not qualified.
It's unfair.
I realized that my existence itself deducted points.
I was devastated.
(The world of dancers is cruel and harsh, and one despairs...)
(over the limitations of their natural physique.)
That was all I had in my mind.
"You think I can't make it?"
A dancer is supposed to...
overcome the limits of their body with their body.
Being the crazy one is my last resort.
Being crazy about dance.
Even when I'm out of my breath,
I must keep trying since it can't kill me.
He has flat feet.
He should be bad at dancing, but he's good.
He must have overcome it with his hard work.
It's not so easy to overcome that.
Isn't this a miracle?
He surprised me today.
Maybe, it's unfair in the beginning,
but I believe it's the dancer's job...
to level the playing field.
You must fiercely complete your dance...
to survive in this battle.
A brutal dance battle unfolds,
where male dancers fight with nothing but their bare bodies.
This is Stage Fighter.
There are strict classes in Stage Fighter,
and all these dancers must fight...
to be recognized for their skills.
Under.
No class is lower than Under.
This is a nightmare.
I didn't know I deserved this class.
It feels like a nail on my chest.
I felt small.
I feel like a total loser.
I had hit rock bottom.
I'm definitely going up from Under.
I'm going to go up with my grit.
Second.
They're coming up from below,
and they're blocking us from above.
The Second class is the fiercest.
Who cares about who's senior here?
That wasn't an irreplaceable dance.
I'm better than him.
How dare he talk about dance?
Who cares?
It's too horrible to imagine being degraded.
I should take his First Class.
I'm going to beat them all.
Only the dancer...
who wins against himself and everyone else...
may stand at the top.
First.
This is the grace of First.
We're top-tier within this program.
I'm sure that you won't be so offended...
by the fact that I'm above you.
I'm in the First Class.
So that means I can either keep my place...
or go down.
But I don't think I'll let them take away my First spot.
Never.
The three genres participating in this class war are...
contemporary dance,
ballet,
and Korean dance.
A dance that pursues freedom, performed barefoot onstage.
A dance that embraces gravity and flows with the ground.
Contemporary dance.
There's no correct answer in contemporary dance.
It's a genre...
where individual uniqueness stands out even more.
It's a language that's infinitely free.
Ballet.
A dance that defies gravity,
pushing off the ground...
to soar even higher into the sky.
I reckon that ballet is an art of beauty.
There is a correct answer to it.
Your jumps must be high,
and you must meet the physical conditions.
It's one of the cruellest genres.
A dance of graceful lines and breath, full of elegant curves.
Korean dance.
In Korean dance, each dancer has...
their own distinct rhythm and breath.
The atmosphere and aura that emerge from their rhythm.
It's a genre that can show a variety of colours...
while being rooted in the essence of the Korean sentiment.
(An elegant dance filled with the spirit and rhythm of Korea,)
(Korean dance)
The best dancer to survive in this class war...
will be given a chance to join a global dance company.
Once you join, you will go on a world tour...
and become a star dancer.
I present you the Dance Company of Stage Fighter.
This is a place that will help...
the dancers get into their peak conditions...
by building the best physique.
Okay. Keep going.
- Up. - One, two...
This dance studio will be filled with their passion and sweat...
- for the perfect dance performance. - Five,
six, seven, eight, and one, two...
Whose sweat will be remembered as the best one?
The dancers of three different genres...
must prove themselves and soar higher...
only with their bodies.
That's why our first audition...
will begin with a story about bodies.
Physical and Technique Audition.
How well they manage their physique,
and how technically they use that physique,
are fundamental virtues for all dancers.
The audition will proceed in groups,
chosen by the dancers themselves.
In the end, only one person who survives to the very last...
will claim the title of the First Class.
We need to see whose physique is better.
He has a good physique,
- but he can't seem to use it well. - Not yet.
Physique, technique,
energy, and basic skills are the most important.
(You must have all the abilities as a dancer to survive.)
He's got an excellent physique.
Jump. There's a trick.
- They're wild. - Yes.
They've got great technique.
(The first act of a class war to aim for a higher class)
Gosh.
- Isn't it suffocating? - So suffocating.
A class war of dance among male dancers,
Stage Fighter.
The first class war, Physical and Technique Audition,
begins now.
First position.
Music, start.
(Stage Fighter)
(STF Dance Company in Gangnam)
(Which genres are entering STF Dance Company?)
(A room of red lockers for ballet dancers)
(There are makeup products for men as well.)
(Who's the first dancer to enter the Ballet Locker Room?)
- I think this is it. - I guess so.
Yes.
(Two ballet dancers who seem acquainted enter.)
- What's this? - No way.
It's like a locker room for basketball players.
I guess it's only for ballet dancers.
(Their profiles are displayed.)
What's this?
"The face of Korea National University of Arts."
"Ballerino Prince."
Do you think I'm the face of my school?
Everyone agrees that you're the best-looking one at school.
Hello. I currently go to Korea National University of Arts.
I'm a 25-year-old ballet dancer, Shin Min Kwon.
It's been about nine years since I started dancing.
I won the Gold Prize at a competition,
held by the Korea Ballet Association two years in a row.
I won the grand award at Sejong Dance Competition...
two years in a row.
I think that Min Kwon is...
a visually beautiful dancer.
His legs are a work of art.
And he's handsome.
His arms and legs are long.
He's got the appearance of a prince.
- We're the first ones here. - Yes.
Gyeong Ho and I go to the same college,
so we're pretty close.
I'm a 23-year-old ballet dancer, Kang Gyeong Ho.
I won second place in the senior division...
of the Valentina Kozlova International Ballet Competition.
And I won second place in the senior division...
of the Seoul International Dance Competition.
I've been doing ballet for about ten years now.
- "Incredible immersion." - "The leading role hunter."
I get into character as soon as I step on that stage.
When I'm immersed in the performance and pour my heart out...
I mostly get the parts that I want.
What? "Physical check?"
- We're tied in first place. - I thought you'd get a full score.
I wanted to get a full score.
You could have gotten a higher score for your technique.
I have pretty good technique.
Ballet is insanely technical.
You need to stretch, turn, and jump.
It's a movement where you split your legs and cross them mid-air.
I'm confident doing the ciseaux.
Maybe, I should have chosen B.
Physical and Technique Audition, the judging groups.
To determine their class in Stage Fighter,
the contemporary dancers,
Korean dancers...
And ballerinos...
Will go through their first audition.
The Physical and Technique Audition begins now.
The auditions will be held in groups...
that you have chosen.
Only the last survivor will be...
a First Class.
Physical and Technique Audition.
Four groups of four.
So, there are 16 people.
I want to compete with him.
- I prefer getting the whip first. - I have to watch this.
Okay. This should be fun!
(Which ballerino will be a First Class?)
- We've arrived. - Okay. Let's head in.
All right.
It's fancy.
(New members' profiles are displayed in the locker room.)
What?
See? It's him.
From the Korean National Ballet.
(A professional ballerino is here.)
There aren't too many people yet.
Hello, I'm a 34-year-old...
ballet dancer, Kim Tae Seok.
I've been in the Korean National Ballet for eight years now.
I used to be a demi-soloist.
All ballerinos have skills that they're confident in.
Mine is called double saut de basque.
You spin twice in the air while your body is tilted and land.
It's not such an easy movement.
I can't do the double saut de basque.
(It's tough for me too.)
(Another profile is displayed.)
Gosh. He's currently a member of the Universal Ballet.
- Is that what it says? - Yes.
I'm a 33-year-old ballet dancer, Kim Kyung Won.
I was in the Korean National Ballet for a year...
and in the Universal Ballet for about five years.
The Korean National Ballet and the Universal Ballet...
are the two best ballet companies...
in Korea.
He has so many techniques that he's confident in.
My favourite is the ciseaux.
Maybe it's because I'm flexible,
but I find it easier to do a split after I jump.
I am worried.
Yes. We should be.
You can't overlook one's experience.
You get better at techniques as the years go by.
Those parts got me worried.
- Let's cheer up. - Okay.
I think someone's here.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Standing up)
(Hello.)
I jumped up before I even knew it.
(Scanning and closing the door)
You guys are ballet dancers.
- Yes. - Yes.
(He doesn't know where to look.)
What's this?
(He flinches at every word.)
This is my favourite brand.
It was a lot of pressure.
They're big seniors, so...
It's a survival, and they're my competitors.
But I was intimidated.
- Can I ask you how old you are? - I'm 24.
- You're 24? - Yes.
- I'm 25. - Oh, you're 25.
How old are you?
Shush.
I feel like their uncle.
(Holding his laughter)
Shouldn't we call him our senior?
(From an uncle to a senior)
- Or "brother?" - That sounds better.
"Senior" sounds a bit...
- Let's call each other brothers. - Brothers.
(I like that.)
You both look like good jumpers.
- I'm not. - I'm not.
I've been in peak condition these days.
(Flustered)
(He makes a declaration, and the air gets tense.)
I hate losing. I'm very competitive.
I think the younger ones should be worried.
I was wondering which group he chose.
I want to compete with him.
- You want to go with him? - Yes.
I like Group A.
Please don't put it next to mine.
(Gyeong Ho chose Group A.)
Oh, my name's up there.
(The name tags are in 1 line.)
(Gyeong Ho, Tae Seok, Min Kwon, Kyung Won)
- We're all in different groups. - We are.
I was glad that we were in different groups.
(The next dancers will be competitors in the same group.)
(The next ballerino's profile, is revealed.)
Who is it?
He has 2.5 years of experience?
He is a joint winner for the physical score.
He is a joint winner with you.
He is.
He must be a genius.
(The genius arrives at the Judging Groups Register.)
Who is it?
I am Ballerino Moon Jun On.
When I was in my first year in high school,
I learned ballet for the first time.
I had the honour of getting a certificate...
from Russia's Bolshoi Ballet Academy and Vaganova Ballet Academy.
I believe technique is my strength.
Instead of focusing on showing my body,
I am specialized in techniques, and I dance powerfully.
I have a good physique and am good at ballet.
People occasionally said I was a genius.
(Surprised)
(His group is revealed.)
They're all in Min Kwon's group.
Since he hasn't done ballet for that long,
I don't think he'll be that good.
(Exclaiming)
Okay.
(He enters.)
Nice to meet you.
(Turning his head)
(Eyes fixed on him)
(Taking a seat far away)
"What is this?"
(Staring)
He kept staring at me.
It felt unnerving.
Why did you choose Group C?
Kang Gyeong Ho in Group A.
(Suddenly Kang Gyeong Ho?)
(Me?)
- Kang Gyeong Ho. - Yes.
I saw him dance, and he was incredible.
I didn't expect to see him here.
He is a rising star on a roll.
So I wanted to avoid Group A.
Hold on.
(Sucking in his breath)
(Glancing)
I was a bit annoyed.
He came to my group because of that?
Does he want to have a go at it with me?
I didn't really know who Shin Min Kwon was.
I didn't really give it much thought.
(Two ballerinos enter STF Dance Company, smiling brightly.)
Hello.
(The next dancer arrives at the Judging Groups Register.)
He is very tall.
Isn't it hard to do a revoltade with that height?
It'll look amazing if you can do a revoltade with that height.
It'll look very cool.
"Kang Daniel."
- They look alike. - He's handsome.
He does look a bit like Kang Daniel.
Hello. I'm a 22-year-old ballerino, Kim Sang Young,
studying at Hanyang University.
I have long arms and legs, and I have a neat dancing style.
There's a move called revoltade.
I practised it really hard,
so I'm most confident in it.
He is "Wink Boy."
Will he wink at us too?
(Singing)
And I wink.
Bang.
(He suddenly feels embarrassed.)
Join Group B with me.
Shall we join together?
We can compete with each other.
(This ballerino looks young and confident.)
He's the youngest, 19 years old.
Gosh, 19?
He'll jump in his sleep.
Hello. I am Ballerino Jeon Tae Hu,
nineteen years old.
I come from Taebaek, Gangwon Province.
It has fresh, clean air.
It is quiet and nice.
(But...)
To focus solely on dance, I quit middle school.
I came to Seoul and only thought about dancing.
I loved dancing so much.
He is most confident in grand jete.
He must be very flexible.
When I jump,
I tend to stay longer in the air.
So I'm most confident in grand jete.
(Grand jete: Stretching one's leg wide mid-air)
I hope he doesn't join Group B.
(I hope the young boy doesn't join Group B!)
- I'm thinking either Group A or B. - Really?
(He is 19, so he has no worries.)
(This is how you're going to choose?)
(Come at me, fate.)
I'll join Group B.
(He chooses without hesitation!)
Actually, I don't know the other dancers' names.
I just have a feeling I can win.
(Innocent)
I'll join Group D.
(Ballet Physical and Technique Audition Judging Groups)
He joined Group B.
I can't lose to him.
(Gulping)
- Hello. - Hello.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kim Tae Seok.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
- I am... - I'm Kim Tae Seok.
Ballerino Jeon Tae Hu is 15 years younger than me.
(The age difference between Tae Hu and Tae Seok is 15 years.)
The younger you are, the bolder and more fearless...
you become when trying out techniques.
I might be stuck on the ground...
while he jumps lightly.
It made me a bit worried.
I want to see the others too.
That startled me.
(Surprised)
(The next ballerino's profile is revealed.)
He is an elite who studied overseas.
He graduated with first class honours from Kirov Academy.
Isn't he another young and famous ballerino?
He was in the Joffrey Ballet.
A lot of legendary dancers are here.
(What?)
I knew who Kim Yu Chan was.
I first met him in a competition.
I lost to him badly.
That was my first meeting with Kim Yu Chan,
so I am worried about him even now.
(Kim Yu Chan who studied overseas...)
(and beat the rising star Kang Gyeong Ho enters.)
Hello. I'm a 23-year-old ballerino, Kim Yu Chan.
In the Youth America Grand Prix final in 2021,
I placed first in the senior group.
The Joffrey Ballet I was in...
is a famous ballet company that ranks in the top ten...
in the US.
I have very good mobility,
flexibility, and core strength.
I always dance thinking, "I am the best."
The quality of my dance is top-notch.
I am very confident in my dance.
If he joins Group A,
Group A will be on fire.
I don't want to be in the same group as him.
- Why not? - Why not?
- I... - He's the opposite of me...
in various ways.
In what way?
Yu Chan dances with attention to detail...
and is very flexible.
But my dance is powerful and masculine.
Our dancing styles are the completely opposite.
I need to keep him in check in that regard.
I'm thinking of joining Group A.
I saw the name "Kang Gyeong Ho."
It looks fun.
Okay. I'll go head-first into it.
I beat him once,
so I can beat him again.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Glancing)
(Kim Yu Chan smiles as he sees Kang Gyeong Ho.)
Hello.
I had all sorts of thoughts, and I was very nervous.
(Ta-da)
Group D.
He went to Group D.
This is the Physical and Technique Audition,
and I think Kang Gyeong Ho...
is better suited for masculine techniques than me.
So I decided to change my group.
I'll go to Group D, then.
I don't start fights that I know I'm going to lose.
I was glad to find out.
(Relieved)
(Now, the only slot left for the judging groups is Group A.)
I can't wait to find out who will fill up the remaining slot.
It might be a really famous dancer.
But everyone is already so competent.
It looks modern and nice.
(Who is the final ballerino that everyone is curious about?)
(The 16th and final ballerino's profile is revealed.)
(Staring intensely)
- He got a full score for technique. - He is in the Georgia Ballet.
That's crazy.
Has anyone met him?
- Yes, we know him. - Really?
(He is acquainted with the Korea National University of Arts duo.)
We know each other.
He was in his senior year when I was a freshman.
I respected him so much, of course.
He was famous.
He is a really skilled ballerino that everyone in our age knows.
Hello. I'm a 25-year-old ballerino, Jung Sung Wook.
I took part in the Valentina Kozlova International Ballet Competition...
in the US...
and was offered a place, so I went to the Georgia Ballet.
Generally, you can divide ballet techniques into two categories.
There are jumps and turns.
I'm confident in both jumps and turns.
He jumps well...
and performs his techniques neatly from what I can remember.
(Everyone acknowledges his skills.)
I think he is an ideal dancer.
First, he has the perfect body for ballet.
You know, the "prince" they always talk about in ballet?
Ballerino Jung Sung Wook is a typical prince.
There's only one slot left, but...
(Ballet Prince Jung Sung Wook chooses his group.)
If I need to compete to survive,
I should trample on them on the stage.
(The 16 people's Physical and Technique Audition judging groups)
(The prince enters.)
(30 eyeballs turn to look at him.)
(The room suddenly becomes silent.)
(Covering his mouth)
He's the prince.
He is so charismatic.
His posture, his facial expression, and the aura he emits...
scream that he is a true ballerino.
Group A looks like fun.
(Jung Min Chan, a ballerino in Group A)
I'm seriously...
(Park Min Woo, a ballerino in Group A)
in trouble.
To beat someone like him, you must become crazy yourself.
If you had the choice, which group would you have chosen?
I would've joined whichever group had a slot left.
(He is so confident.)
Group A looks the toughest.
Group A looked really intense.
Group A is the group of death.
I thought, "If I had joined that group,"
"I wouldn't have been able to become First Class immediately."
(Who is the only First Class in the intense Group A?)
(Physical and Technique Audition will start now.)
Everyone, take off your shirts.
(The ballerinos get changed for the Physical and Technique Audition.)
He is amazing.
He had such a beautiful body shape.
A hidden ace with a firm body.
(They wear their name tags as if preparing for a war.)
It looks like a preliminary round of a competition.
(Nervous)
(A typical ballet competition waiting room)
(Stretching)
(Glancing)
(A silent competition in the disguise of warming up)
(Pasting)
Let's do this.
(Physical and Technique Audition Room for ballet)
(The princes enter.)
(The ballerinos enter the audition room.)
(Surprised)
(Ballet barres for the audition)
I saw the room full of ballet barres.
I was overwhelmed by the room's atmosphere.
(Stretching)
They're really doing this like an actual audition.
I went back to how I used to attend auditions.
(A perfect straight line)
- Was his name Yu Chan? - Yes.
I won't stand next to him.
He is really good.
He has such a pretty physique.
(Jaw-dropping)
(Gulping)
Flexibility and detailed movements that men don't usually have.
I thought I could lose to him.
(Choi Kyu Tae in Group D with him cannot smile.)
(Solemn and serious)
Ballerino Kim Tae Seok in the same group.
He has a good physique.
From what I know, he is from the Korean National Ballet.
As expected, he was good.
(Another person that catches the ballerinos' eyes)
Yun Gu in my group.
I think he has the best physique on the show.
He has the leg shape not everyone has.
Min Kwon is handsome like a prince.
He is flexible and has a good physique.
I thought, "Do I stand a chance against him?"
(Kang Gyeong Ho of Group A's neat pirouette)
(All eyes on him)
I'm getting intimidated from the warm-ups.
(Glancing)
Gyeong Ho, why did you join this group?
Gyeong Ho is powerful and charismatic.
He is on the rise nowadays too.
(Rising star Kang Gyeong Ho's eyes are fixed on...)
Sung Wook studied abroad...
and has a wonderful physique.
He is very good.
I keep checking on him, obviously.
(The warm-up continues for a long time.)
Are they going to announce the order?
I think they would have...
a ballet master or someone like that.
We were curious too.
"Who will judge us and lead us?"
(The 16 ballerinos finish warming up...)
(and are waiting for the audition to start.)
(Nervous)
Who will it be?
(The ballet coaches enter with the dancers' cheer.)
(Charismatic)
(Wait, he is...)
"He is here?"
He is very famous.
A choreographer and a producer. He is an all-rounder.
He is very cool. He is my lecturer.
Even in school, he criticizes a lot.
I was very worried.
(Intimidated)
Bravo!
- Bravo! - Bravo.
This is crazy.
(Ballet Coach Han Seong Woo)
He is a world-famous ballerino.
He is in the American Ballet Theatre.
Not anyone can join it.
(The wannabe of ballerinos)
Where else can I go and be personally taught...
by a current dancer of the American Ballet Theatre?
How did he make time for this?
(Excited)
(Next, Stage Fighter Master enters with a graceful smile.)
(He can't believe what he's seeing.)
Bravo.
(Master Kim Joo Won)
(Korea's representative prima ballerina...)
She was the principal dancer of the Korean National Ballet.
(who was the principal dancer of the Korean National Ballet)
She is a very famous ballerina.
I had no idea she would join the show.
She's an absolutely amazing figure in the field of ballet.
She is one of the top Korean ballerinas.
I looked at her with lots of affection as her fan.
(His fan mode turns on.)
(And Stage Fighter's rehearsal director)
(Rehearsal Director Matthew Rich)
(He was a senior rehearsal director of the Rambert Dance Company.)
(The dance company has 100 years of history.)
(Stage Fighter's rehearsal director who adds details to the dance...)
(with his attention to detail.)
He was very charismatic.
I could feel his aura.
(A master, coaches, and a rehearsal director)
They know ballet inside and out.
They're legendary figures that I cannot even come close to.
It will be tough.
They are really serious about this.
It made me feel more nervous.
(Closing his mouth tight)
The class battle of dancers where they fight with their bodies.
On Stage Fighter, to become the best dancer,
you will fight intense dance class battles.
It is very cruel.
Can I survive?
It can't be helped that ballet itself is in a hierarchy.
Not everyone can play the same role.
You are given a role based on your performance.
We grew up in that kind of environment.
The classes will be decided based on the dancer's ability.
First Class...
will play the lead role that has a solo part.
Second Class...
will play the supporting role that dances in a duo or a trio.
Under Class will dance in a group.
I want to become First Class...
and perform onstage as the lead role.
I am aiming for the lead role.
It was my last bit of pride.
I couldn't dance in a group.
How well you managed your body...
and how well you use that body for various techniques...
are basic virtues for all dancers.
(Nodding)
(Agreeing)
Ballet especially has fixed forms and rules.
(Ballet has fixed forms from one's toes to one's fingertips.)
More than any other dance genre,
your physique matters a lot.
The physique you're born with is important too, but...
Keeping your body in shape is a must.
You change the shapes of your joints and muscles.
You craft a body that is fit for ballet.
That's how important it is.
We'll start the Physical and Technique Audition...
to evaluate this.
(Ballet Physical and Technique Audition)
The audition will be conducted...
in groups that you chose yourselves.
(Ballet Physical and Technique Audition Judging Groups)
It will be a relay of three rounds.
It will continue until one person remains.
It's a fight of stamina.
I thought it would be tough.
This is a war.
Round One is the Barre Technique.
Barre and Center Technique.
(Sighing)
Actually, the barre technique is a basic skill in ballet.
I didn't expect them to judge us on the classic barre technique.
(Kim Tae Yeon looks more nervous than the others.)
Barre technique is something that ballerinos do the most.
Those that did ballet for a long time...
obviously have a strong foundation.
The score difference could grow from the start.
It may look easy.
You just fold and unfold your legs.
But that's not all there is to it.
You need to use your inner muscles too.
Doing it consecutively is very tough.
I should grit my teeth and do it.
I'll give it my all.
Round Two is the Center Technique.
I was very worried about Center Technique.
What kind of male center techniques will they make us do?
Nobody could copy my foundation or technique...
that I honed with a lot of effort.
Round 3 is the 1-on-1 Fixed Technique.
When each round ends,
those that lack the technique will be cut out.
As soon as you're cut out, your class will be decided.
It's the first mission, and they are going all out.
We really are starting a survival show.
There are three rounds.
It won't be easy to pace myself in terms of stamina too.
Who will be the best in physical techniques...
and become First Class?
(Which ballerino will become First Class?)
(Round 1 of Ballet, Barre Technique audition...)
(to decide the First, Second, and Under Classes)
Ballet barres...
warm up a dancer's body and relax the muscles.
It is an important step to avoid an injury.
From the barre technique,
we can evaluate your physique, stamina, flexibility,
balance, technique, and expression.
Round 1, Barre Technique, has 4 levels.
From each group, the worst dancer...
will be cut out, which makes it four dancers in total.
They will become Under Class.
(Immediately, those 4 will become Under Class.)
Barre Technique shows your natural physique very clearly...
to the point that it becomes an evaluation criterion.
My pride won't be able to take it...
if I get eliminated in Barre Technique.
I was confident in my physique.
Ballet actually is an unfair art.
I played a lot of lead roles.
If you don't have the right height or leg shape,
no matter how well you spin and jump,
you can't get the lead role.
You have amazing legs.
- No. - They have the perfect shape.
I'm most worried about myself.
I wasn't born with the leg shape.
Everyone else is very tall, but I'm not.
So I kept getting more worried.
(Stretching)
(Meanwhile, Ballerino Kim Yu Chan is stretching comfortably.)
(Looking intensely)
He has a beautiful back.
I fall behind in terms of the physique I was born with.
If I don't work twice as hard,
I won't be seen by them.
Ballet is a very cruel form of art.
We cannot hide.
Not in white tights.
Physique isn't something you can ignore.
You can tell at once how they use their bodies.
In ballet, it's so obvious when you're bad at something.
Let's start the ballet Physical and Technique Audition.
First position.
(First position: Putting the heels of your feet together...)
(while maintaining the turn-out, both feet pointing outward)
Music, start.
If I make a mistake here, I'll become Under Class immediately.
I didn't want to end the audition...
at Barre Technique without showing them my other techniques.
I was confident in barre techniques.
I wanted to be the best out of the four.
Two, one.
Go.
(Ballet Round 1, Barre Technique Audition starts.)
The first preparation is very important.
There are some who express emotions with their fingertips.
(Elegant)
(Focused)
You can more or less tell from just the plie.
(Kang Gyeong Ho continues with the plie with ease.)
I like the first dancer. Gyeong Ho.
He looks sturdy.
It shows that he has good core and muscle strengths.
(Stretching)
The third dancer, Min Woo, dances really well.
He is flexible too.
But his weight...
(His weight)
Actually, I was a bit intimidated.
I would look very short and fat.
Sung Wook beside him has a nice body shape.
He has a nice figure.
- His standing leg is very strong. - Yes.
Ballerino Jung Sung Wook next to me is tall.
He has nicely shaped legs,
so he definitely attracts more attention than others.
Three, two, one.
Two, one.
Change.
(With the change of music, Barre Technique Level 2 starts.)
(A throwing movement of the leg in every direction...)
(while keeping it stretched out completely)
It's important to pay attention to the toes as much as possible.
(Pointing the feet while keeping the turn-out is key.)
Tae Seok.
How about him?
It's clean.
To me, his position, looks, and body shape...
- are ideal for ballet. - And...
Jeon Tae Hu has...
a good body shape. He's flexible and light.
(Losing his balance)
(Dancer Lee Ha Nel loses his control and balance.)
(Observing closely)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
I was running out of strength.
Lee Ha Nel's movements...
aren't precise.
He doesn't look confident. It's unfortunate.
Shall we look at their bodies in profile?
I was startled.
When they suddenly came up to us, I thought, "This is crazy."
(Stealthy)
The dance masters and coaches are bleeding me dry.
(Masters and coaches evaluate them on the floor for more precision.)
When they're near, I must catch their attention.
We can see their bodies in profile from here.
We can see if they're turned out, if their bottoms are sticking out,
or if their ribs are open.
- Did you see someone? - Who is he?
We have to watch this accurately.
Someone was getting closer to me.
(Close-up evaluation continues for accuracy.)
I really should do my best.
Suffocating tension.
Goodness, I hope that they won't come near me.
(They're heading toward Ballet Dancer Kim Tae Yeon.)
Suddenly, I could feel their eyes on me.
I always thought that I had a weak foundation,
so I was scared.
He's very weak.
(His lips are dry.)
His standing leg is weak.
He must be strong to dance well in the center.
Shin Min Kwon has good technique.
I prefer his proportions.
Visually, it's more pleasing to my eyes.
- It feels like he's a prince. - A prince.
Yun Gu looks strong.
So I like his edgy energy.
(Just then)
Do you see Jun On?
The coaches stayed in front of me.
Compared to Yu Chan...
(Startled)
I heard names like Kim Yu Chan.
It must be easy to compare him to me.
- His feet and everything are sharp. - I agree.
His feet, legs, and turn-out are beautiful.
But for Jun On,
I don't see any accent on his feet.
(In terms of strength and details, Yu Chan and Jun On are different.)
I couldn't help but feel anxious.
I should do my best until the end.
Isn't it much better to look at them from the side?
You can see their heels and arches of their feet.
This is what we have to look at.
(The Barre Technique Audition continues.)
Three, two, one.
Change.
Even if it's hard, hold yourself together.
(Level 3: Rond de Jambe a Terre)
(A movement where the moving leg draws a circle on the floor)
Based on their standing legs, the two of them are...
The turn-out...
(Turn-out: When the legs are turned outward,)
(including the feet and the knees)
Kim Kyung Won has an amazing turn-out.
(Kim Kyung Won's foot, Choi Kyu Tae's foot)
He can't turn out.
It was like hanging off a cliff.
To me, the barre felt like a cliff.
When you're standing in the first position in ballet,
- First position. - your knees should touch.
That's when the evaluation of your dance starts.
I'm naturally bow-legged,
so it's hard to put my knees together.
For the turn-out,
I knew that I'd get points deducted.
I started to get very worried.
(Kim Sang Young keeps dancing while sweating profusely.)
(Panting)
(Drenched in sweat)
Next to me,
Kim Yu Chan stretched out his legs extremely high.
(It's hard not to compare them in the Barre Technique Audition.)
Yu Chan has a beautiful figure.
He knows how to use his feet.
(Satisfied)
(Concentrating)
(Leg stretched in a clean, straight line)
It's bad to get compared to others. How did this happen?
(The angles are clearly different as they stand next to each other.)
Lovely.
What if I get eliminated?
Three, two, one.
(A little more)
(Their strength and concentration become more important now.)
(The audition room is filled with sweating and panting dancers)
(The dancers are hitting their physical limits.)
- It must be very hard. - It's extremely hard.
I felt like my thighs were going to burst.
My legs and feet were getting cramped.
Physically, it was very difficult.
- It's about having the technique. - Yes, and strong mentality.
For the last 19 years,
I practised ballet every day at the barre until late at night.
I practised ballet all day.
I trusted my muscle memory.
Energy and mentality.
Let's endure it no matter what.
Until the end.
(Panting)
As a professional, you must keep it up until the end.
(Masters and coaches keep evaluating them objectively.)
(Level 4: Grand Battement)
(Kicking of the leg above the head)
For me, Sung Wook and Gyeong Ho are my favourites.
He definitely moves with stability and perfection.
I don't want to join Under, no matter what.
I shouldn't relax. Let's do it as much as I can.
I earnestly wanted to last until the end.
(Shaking)
I tried to make it while gritting my teeth.
Three, two, one.
Stop.
(Ballet Round 1, Barre Technique Audition is over.)
(The audition room is filled with sounds of short breaths.)
(Panting)
It's so hot.
Gosh, this is...
(Dripping sweat)
Everyone is sweating so much.
(Sweating profusely as they tried their best)
(Sighing with disappointment)
(Flopping)
It was hard to have enough stamina to move with one breath.
There was a lot of pressure to make it.
(Exhaling)
What did you think of the barre difficulty?
The sequences were easy to follow, but they were hard.
- It was harder than an exam. - It was just as advanced.
In the end, I couldn't even do the up.
(Closing his eyes tightly)
(Which dancer will be sent to Under, the lowest class?)
I will announce the dancers...
in Under Class from Round One.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
(4 out of 16 ballet dancers will join Under Class.)
(Trying to stay calm)
Coach Han Seong Woo, please announce Group A's Under Class.
(Striding)
(Group A's ballet dancers wait for the result.)
I felt confident that I'd pass.
(Exhaling)
(Turning)
(All their eyes are on him.)
(Coach Han Seong Woo passes through two dancers.)
(Closing his eyes)
To be honest, I was surprised.
(That startled me.)
Group A's dancer to join Under Class is...
He was standing behind me.
It made me very nervous.
I wanted to join Second Class because I worked very hard.
(Which ballet dancer will be the first to join Under Class?)
(What?)
(Gaping)
It's Dancer Park Min Woo. Thank you.
(Group A's Under Class, Park Min Woo)
Gosh, it fell off.
(Even the tag fell off.)
(He puts his Under Class tag back on.)
I don't believe this.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
I felt bad to be the first to join Under Class,
but I had expected it.
(Under Class from Group A)
(Park Min Woo?)
(He doesn't have the right physique.)
In ballet,
the evaluation starts with your body.
You sure can't change what you were born with.
I'll announce...
the Under Class dancer from Group B.
(I don't want to see it.)
(Everyone is nervous.)
I was quite confident about myself.
In general, my performance was disappointing. I was worried.
Honestly, I was somewhat nervous.
Group B's dancer to join Under Class is...
Lee Ha Nel.
(Group B's Under Class, Lee Ha Nel)
(Sighing)
(In Group B...)
(Lee Ha Nel?)
(His positions weren't accurate.)
(Stumbling)
(He doesn't look confident. It's unfortunate.)
(His lips are dry.)
I felt uncomfortable and frustrated to join Under Class.
(The class announcement continues.)
Now, I will announce...
the dancer from Group C to join Under Class.
(Please stay away from me.)
Matthew, please announce the Under Class dancer.
(To whom is Matthew headed among Group C dancers?)
(Group D also feels nervous by the announcement.)
Group C's dancer to join Under Class is...
I felt quite confident about myself.
I didn't think I'd get eliminated after the barre.
(Matthew stops and fixes his eyes on Moon Jun On.)
(Turning)
(Moon Jun On)
(Could it be him?)
My legs were shaking.
(He's fidgeting his sweaty hands from nervousness.)
(Matthew passes Moon Jun On.)
(Which Group C dancer will be sent to Under Class?)
Unfortunately, you've been rated Under.
It's Kim Tae Yeon.
(Under Class of Group C, Kim Tae Yeon)
(Having mixed feelings)
(The dancers applaud to cheer him up and comfort him.)
(Kim Tae Yeon clearly looks disappointed.)
(Sighing)
From Group C?
I wonder if...
Tae Yeon will be able to do well in the Center Technique.
He doesn't seem to have enough stamina.
I kept feeling dejected.
I've never felt so small...
in my life.
(Exhaling)
I'll announce the Under Class dancer from Group D.
(Which Group D dancer will join Under Class?)
Group D's dancer to join Under Class is...
I didn't think that I'd get eliminated.
(Director Matthew passes by Kim Yu Chan.)
(Nervous)
Director Matthew was lingering around me.
(Director Matthew prepares the Under Class tag in front of Sang Young.)
My heart was beating fast.
I wanted to avoid Under Class no matter what.
(Which ballerino from Group D will be sent to Under Class?)
Unfortunately, you've rated Under.
- It's Choi Kyu Tae. - Thank you.
(Under Class of Group D, Choi Kyu Tae)
(Choi Kyu Tae is sent to Under Class from the Barre Technique Audition.)
(He has many thoughts after being sent to Under Class.)
(Glancing)
(Lowering his head)
(Ballet Barre Technique Audition is over.)
He's having a mental breakdown.
- Where is he? - Tell him that it's okay.
The other dancers accepted it without getting emotional,
but it looks like he's having a mental breakdown.
Mentally, it was very hard.
When I turned out, the judges passed by me.
And I felt them looking at my knees.
He doesn't have a turn-out.
This has always been the case for me.
Always...
I want to become a ballerino and join a ballet company,
but it gets revealed as soon as I stand onstage.
So I either cross my legs while standing...
or jump and move my legs a lot.
I've had a hard time trying to hide my physical flaw.
It's just...
From the beginning, I felt that I'd get eliminated.
- I'm sorry. - Oh, no.
I hate...
my natural body type.
It's sad not to have a body that isn't appropriate...
for classical ballet.
Some of the dancers had less experience than me.
I saw that they had beautiful figures in their leotards.
I have no strength at all...
in the basics.
I felt terrible about myself.
When you aren't qualified, you don't even get a chance.
The ballet world is so cold-hearted.
(Ballet Under Class: Park Min Woo, Lee Ha Nel,)
(Kim Tae Yeon, Choi Kyu Tae)
(Only 12 ballerinos moved up to Round 2.)
Under Class dancers...
no longer have a chance to audition.
It was cruel.
I felt compassion for them.
The upcoming Rounds 2 and 3 will be...
technique in the center.
Center technique is the basis of ballet.
There are set techniques in ballet.
Pirouette is spinning like a top with one leg as an axis.
Saut de basque is jumping while turning with one foot on the knee.
Tour en l'air is spinning the entire body in the air.
Cabriole is hitting the legs in the air.
Entrechat six is crossing the thighs in the air.
Manege is jumping across the stage in circles.
Ciseaux is splitting the legs after crossing them in the air.
I kept wondering what techniques would come up.
I exhausted myself so much at the barre,
so I was worried.
As we're male dancers,
they'll probably give us movements that require advanced techniques.
I'm not good at jumps.
I was worried about getting difficult jumps.
Here is...
the center technique video for Rounds 2 and 3.
Five, four, three, two, one. Go.
(Round 2 Center Technique video starts.)
We have to begin with the start position.
(Scanning)
(Demonstration video for Round 2)
- Do a pirouette. - Pirouette?
I can do this well.
(Nodding)
Ballet is about aesthetics,
so you must turn beautifully in the standard position.
I got it.
Cabriole.
It's a double cabriole, not single.
Cabriole?
Since my knee operation, I've been avoiding that movement.
It looks easy enough. It's worth trying.
I'm confident about jumps.
They're basic techniques.
This is worth trying.
Ciseaux.
I'm doomed.
Ciseaux is technically very difficult.
- It's a feast of techniques. - I know.
I didn't know that they'd include something like this.
You can do it only when you have good jumping skills.
There are professional dancers who can't do the ciseaux.
However, I felt confident about it.
I should do it well.
I know how good Gyeong Ho is,
so I felt worried.
I was very confident.
It's a piece of cake.
(Wary)
Let's think about the shape of the next movement.
Next is entrechat six.
Here?
Opening the legs wider would be better.
It's a test of your thigh strength.
Their thighs will burst.
Entrechat six is about strength.
It's very exhausting for...
the outer and inner thighs.
The combination looked physically demanding.
- Three, two, one. - Passe tour en l'air.
Stop.
(Round 2 Center Technique video ends.)
(The back of his head looks flustered.)
This is insane.
It won't be easy.
Seong Woo, isn't the combination too difficult?
They should be able to pull it off.
It will allow us to see many things.
It's worth a try.
Let's make it to First Class.
It involves all the basic techniques.
I thought, "I'll finish it with..."
"an amazing passe tour en l'air."
Both entrechat six and ciseaux are...
movements I can do in my sleep.
I knew that Kim Kyung Won would definitely do the ciseaux.
It had many movements like ciseaux that I wasn't confident about.
I was worried.
Here is the video for Round Three.
Each dancer will perform the assigned techniques.
Two, one. Go.
(Demonstration video for Round 3)
- Double tour en l'air. - Double tour en l'air is...
about keeping the balance...
with your feet off the floor.
I wasn't so worried about double tour en l'air.
Next is manege.
(Jumping around in huge circles)
I was very flustered by the manege.
You have to show a straight line in the air to look good.
As I was already exhausted,
I couldn't show my full potential.
Having control over your body is key in manege.
You have to overcome the air resistance and move in circles.
Strength is also an important part...
of your skills.
Two, one. Stop.
This won't be easy.
It looked very difficult.
- Five, four, - What?
- three, two, one. Go. - No way.
This is very demanding.
Two of you will come out and do grand pirouettes.
Usually, grand pirouettes are done for 16 counts.
But to make it special, it will be for 32 counts.
I thought that I misheard it.
Usually, you do grand pirouettes for 16 counts.
We had to do them for 32 counts, which was twice as long.
No one does grand pirouettes...
for 32 counts.
They want to evaluate the dancers thoroughly.
I resented them a lot.
How...
I told myself to do it no matter what.
Do single pirouettes during the 1st 16 counts.
During the 2nd 16 counts,
show us your best turning technique.
(Nodding)
Grand pirouettes for 32 counts, which is unusual.
I should draw their attention.
I thought that it could be an advantage for me.
I have to distribute my stamina.
As long as I'm willing,
I can do it better than anyone else.
I'll make it with force and tenacity.
I was determined to work hard because I didn't want to lose.
I'll go for First Class.
Let's try it.
(Which dancer will join First Class from each group?)
Ballet Physical and Technique Audition,
Round Two, Center Technique, will start.
Let's begin with Group A.
Kang Gyeong Ho.
(Kang Gyeong Ho, Group A)
Jung Min Chan.
- And Jung Sung Wook. - Yes.
Let's take our first position.
The three people from Group A are some of the best dancers.
You can tell by their standing positions.
Nice.
I think Group A is really good.
They went to Korea National University of Arts.
They all went to Korea National University of Arts.
I know Gyeong Ho.
I know how good he is.
Gyeong Ho...
(Only Group A has an available spot.)
Gyeong Ho is a tough opponent.
He has everything I lack.
That's why I felt rivalry against him.
Against Gyeong Ho only.
I really like him,
but we need to compete.
I really wanted to win.
I really wanted to win and felt rivalry against him.
- I thought Sung Wook and I... - Pose?
would be competing to be in First Class.
So I feel the most competitive against him.
Gyeong Ho.
We should become the first scene-stealers.
- I don't think I can do it. - Me neither.
I was like, "What was that?" I stared at them for a long time.
They didn't feel the need to keep me in check.
They felt competitive against each other, excluding me.
It actually didn't feel great.
They're my college juniors.
(2006 Korea National University of Arts)
He entered the university in 2006.
You weren't the oldest.
Min Chan is my senior.
Classical ballet has a short lifespan,
with the prime years...
often considered to be in the early 20s.
He's quite old, so...
So you think you can step on me?
(He's just smiling.)
As my juniors excluded me like that,
I wanted to show I'm doing just as good...
as an active ballerino.
I wanted to win against those younger guys.
I thought I could be in First Class.
I was confident.
I think I'll be in First Class.
I'll do my best. It's mine.
Music,
start.
(Group A, Round 2, Center Technique)
(Allonge: A movement that involves the extension of arms.)
His leg shape is pretty.
(Impressed)
Min Chan especially looks good when he extends his leg.
I like his pointed toes.
When he does en tournant, he puts his legs together.
I like his turn-out.
- Nice. - I like Gyeong Ho.
"I'll end it with my pirouette."
(Pirouette: A movement where you spin on one leg like a top.)
- Oh, my. - Good techniques.
They turned four times perfectly.
It was clean.
He made a mistake.
And...
- Gyeong Ho. - Good.
They did double cabrioles very nicely.
But Sung Wook just tapped his feet.
It means Gyeong Ho has a better technique.
Min Chan did a single cabriole, which is unfortunate.
There is a significant difference in their skills.
It won't be difficult to make a decision for Round Two.
I was like, "Oh, no."
Gyeong Ho and Sung Wook were amazing.
I thought I should appeal to them when I do the ciseaux.
Ciseaux. I should kill it.
(Ciseaux: A jump where the legs are stretched in the air.)
- Gosh. - That's crazy.
Both extended their legs very well, making a straight line.
The jumps are so good.
- Gyeong Ho's jumps are great. - That's amazing.
I think he's one of the best in Korea.
(Meanwhile, Sung Wook couldn't do a ciseaux.)
- Oh, my. - Why did he do an assemble?
(Frowning)
Sung Wook didn't do a ciseaux.
(Oh, no)
"This is not it."
"He's perplexed."
I thought it was an opportunity for me.
Gyeong Ho is indeed great. Min Chan...
His moves are clean, though.
I think we should keep watching.
Even though Min Chan isn't so young,
I can tell he's experienced. Don't you think so?
(It's the same move,)
(but they're showing ballet techniques in different styles.)
Both have personalities...
- Yes. - in their dance.
It's pretty.
Yes. He catches your eye.
Yes.
I thought I would pass this round if I kept going like this.
"Let's not waver and finish it neatly until the end."
"Let's finish the last position well to survive."
Chaines.
Passe tour en l'air.
Yes.
Everyone did the passe tour en l'air very well at the end.
(Ballet Physical and Technique Audition)
(Center Technique, Round 2 for Group A has ended.)
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
It's definitely Gyeong Ho, right?
Yes. The quality was different.
He was great.
- But this guy wasn't bad either. - Right.
Sung Wook. He's got some character.
- He's charismatic. Right? - Yes.
So, for me, these are my two favourites.
- Sung Wook and Gyeong Ho. - Yes.
- Gyeong Ho. - Is it okay...
to do a different move, though?
(Sung Wook replaced ciseaux, a fixed technique, with another move.)
(Disappointed)
Who do you think will be eliminated?
Sung Wook did the moves in the wrong order.
So...
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a left-footer.
So I always did a ciseaux in the other direction.
I've never done it on my right side.
So I tried to change the direction.
But if I change the direction,
I can't do the following steps properly.
So it is a disadvantage.
But it was me who made a mistake.
I thought I might be eliminated if it didn't go well.
First of all, I really enjoyed it.
Min Chan,
I liked how you enjoyed it while dancing.
I loved your shapes, expressions,
and energy.
But technically,
you weren't very accurate,
which is a little disappointing.
Sung Wook is a left-footer,
so I understand it wasn't easy in many ways.
But you did the moves in the wrong order,
which is a little disappointing.
Your turn-out, shapes, and jumps...
were very good.
- Thank you. - Gyeong Ho,
your techniques were great.
But you could make better facial expressions.
(Gyeong Ho had a straight face while dancing.)
(Looking closely)
- Gyeong Ho... - His thighs.
- has great techniques, - Yes.
- but his facial expression is... - He looks nervous.
I'm not sure if he's just nervous, or...
- Sung Wook smiles sometimes. - Right.
He looks charismatic.
Compared to your technique,
you lack artistic expression.
I hope you can work on it a little more.
We'll now reveal the dancer who got cut out...
and joined the Second Class.
They cut them out right away.
I was nervous.
Sung Wook made a big mistake.
So I thought I could make it if things went well.
The Second Class is...
(Matthew stands in front of the dancers from Group A.)
(Nervous)
(Matthew is looking at Sung Wook.)
(Approaching)
Unfortunately, you've ranked Second.
Please leave the floor.
(Second Class of Group A, Jung Min Chan)
(Disappointed)
It's disappointing. Sung Wook made a mistake.
Of course, he's a great dancer.
But I wish I could've done...
- better. - You did well.
But...
I did very well for someone who was born in 1988.
Fortunately, I made it.
I'm getting ready to make up for it properly.
(Glancing)
He's still my rival, of course.
Sung Wook is a dancer with great techniques.
If I make a mistake, I might be eliminated.
I should do better.
Gyeong Ho is good.
But it's okay if I do better.
- I'm confident. - I'm confident.
But the fact that those two are competing here is...
I know. Those two...
(The big match makes even the master and the coaches nervous.)
It's going to be interesting.
Round 3. Ballerino Kang Gyeong Ho will go 1st.
- I really want to win. - Five,
- I'm going to win. - four, three,
two, one.
Go.
(Fixed Technique for Round 3: Tour en l'air, 3 times)
(Exclaiming automatically)
His jump is great.
He was good, indeed.
(Tour en l'air, 1st time)
Nice.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
Good. His jumps are great, indeed.
It's clean.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
Gyeong Ho's rotation in the air is amazing.
(Gyeong Ho's moves draw attention.)
He's good.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
He's so bouncy.
(Tour en l'air, 3rd time)
It was clean.
"Let's not make a mistake. Let's rotate neatly."
"Let's follow the movements my body remembers."
Let's look at his manege.
(Manege)
- Oh, my. - Gosh.
It's a low and long jump.
His legs make a straight line...
while he jumps forward.
It's good.
Five...
(Chaines)
- Finish up. - Two,
- one. Go. - It was very stable.
(The other dancers can't help but acknowledge his moves.)
- Okay. - Go.
But he definitely lacks personality.
I don't think I made a mistake.
I was confident.
- I think his moves were clean, - Five,
- but I think I can win if I show... - four, three, two,
- one. Go. - my artistry and elegance.
(Tour en l'air, 3 times)
To the left.
Oh, my.
- Good. - A nice spin.
Sung Wook is also good. I love it.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
- Nice. - It was neat.
Look at how he raised his chin.
Look. Sung Wook's facial expression is great.
I like him very much.
He's cool and charismatic.
I was a little nervous.
(Sung Wook shows his techniques with confidence.)
(Tour en l'air, 3rd time)
(Eyes widening)
He made a nice shape. His spins in the air are impressive.
He has better basic techniques and coordination.
I thought, "I'll make it if I keep going like this."
The manege.
He's flexible.
(Panting)
- He looks very tired. - Kick with your rear leg.
(Tilting his head)
He was tired when doing the manege.
His rear leg wasn't as high as Gyeong Ho's.
He looked very tired.
I thought I'd be in First Class.
That's what I felt.
"This is not it."
I thought I'd keep going until the end even if it wasn't going well.
- Yes. Do it quickly. - Three,
- Go up. - two, one.
(Ending pose)
(Hawk eyes)
- Stop. - Okay.
He tried until the end.
He tried.
(Sung Wook is breathing heavily.)
- He must be so tired. - This is crazy.
And he must do 32 grand pirouettes?
I know. Why 32?
- It's exhausting. - Right.
Skills are important,
- but endurance is also important. - Right.
You need good stamina.
The ballet battle is so scary.
- I'm so scared. - Yes.
It lays bare your true abilities.
Is this a fight against yourself or what?
(They can't catch their breath easily.)
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm good. How about you?
It was really tiring.
Thinking I would be in First Class...
if I finished it well,
I tried my utmost best.
I wanted to be in the First Class.
I was like, "I don't want him to take it away from me. It's mine."
(They are getting ready for the 1-on-1 Fixed Technique in Round 3.)
I'm so nervous. Oh, my gosh. I'm so anxious.
I'm just watching, but my hands are sweaty.
(Their last match will decide on who will be in the First Class...)
(in Group A.)
Five, four, three...
(Wearing a smile)
His facial expression is good, right?
- He looks like a prince. - Two.
Three, two, one.
Go.
- Both are so good. - Nice.
I like their spins.
They're not slow. They're on the beat.
A nice leg position, a good upper body position.
Their spins are great. Both are doing great.
Their turns are so good that I can't say which one is better.
This is cruel.
It's so cruel.
It's about who holds out...
- until the end. - I know. It's so cruel.
(Impressed)
They're good.
You got this.
It has started now.
Show us your skills.
Do a double.
Keep trying until the end.
Look at the speed. It's so good.
As he was trying to show another technique here, he was pushed back.
How can you show another move while doing that?
- I know. - It's impossible.
"I'm doomed."
But showing everything I can show...
How can he do that there?
That would be best.
(Sung Wook made a bold attempt, but he faltered again.)
(Meanwhile, Gyeong Ho keeps turning without showing another move.)
I thought, "Sung Wook is tired."
"I'm going to be in the First Class."
It's not over.
(Gyeong Ho stopped turning before the music ended.)
(He made a safe choice by doing single turns before he stopped.)
"Oh, it's not over."
- "He's turning." - Three, two,
- "This is embarrassing." - one.
I thought I might win, so I kept trying until the end.
- Three, two, one. - How can he turn so much?
Three, two, one.
Stop.
Oh, no.
(Their mistakes upset people who were watching.)
It takes a very long time to count to 32.
But he tried until the end.
After it was over,
I wasn't in my right mind. I was so tired.
I'm not sure if it's because I tried too hard,
but I made a few mistakes.
It was very disappointing.
Let me guide you.
I thought the music stopped there.
It's so embarrassing.
A ballet dancer counted incorrectly.
I felt so small and was ashamed of myself.
- I wish he'd finished. - That's what I said.
You know, here's what I'm afraid of.
If he can't get through 30 seconds,
how is he going to get through three minutes?
But we should consider the moves they did before this.
- Their solo techniques. - Right.
(They should consider the techniques they showed prior to this.)
Gyeong Ho has great techniques.
His moves are clean, but he lacks artistry.
(Gyeong Ho lacks artistry.)
Sung Wook's moves aren't as clean as Gyeong Ho's,
but he has charisma.
I wonder which of them will move people's hearts more.
I'm conflicted.
So difficult.
(Which one will be in the First Class?)
Both of you did a great job.
Good work.
One of you will be in the First Class.
And the other will be in the Second Class.
Gyeong Ho was clearly better than Sung Wook...
in terms of the movement quality.
I think it would've been better if you had tried until the end.
It was a little disappointing.
Sung Wook, you were tired,
and it wasn't your best.
But I think highly of you...
as you tried until the end.
I wish you had better stamina.
Doing 32 turns is extremely challenging,
especially right after the tour en l'air and manege...
with no rest.
It was very difficult, but you did your best.
We took into account your determination to try...
until the end of our evaluation.
I will announce the result.
Ballerino Kang Gyeong Ho and Ballerino Jung Sung Wook.
The First Class is...
I really want to win,
but I can't say I'm confident.
It's not easy.
But I thought it wasn't impossible.
(They're also nervous.)
(Which one will be in the First Class?)
(First Class of Group A, Kang Gyeong Ho)
It's Ballerino Kang Gyeong Ho. Congratulations.
It felt good, but I wasn't really sure about it.
I should do well to show that I deserve the position.
- Thank you. - You've achieved the highest rank.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
(Everyone was holding their breath while watching their match.)
(They end up in different ranks by a narrow margin.)
I think I'm going to pass out.
I'm upset.
I'm in the Second Class today,
but this is not what I truly am.
I'll show you.
(Ballet Physical and Technique Audition)
So next, we have Group C.
Moon Jun On.
(Ballerino Moon Jun On)
Shin Min Kwon.
(Ballerino Shin Min Kwon)
And Kang Yun Gu.
(Ballerino Kang Yun Gu)
Kang Yun Gu is so cool.
I think the dancer from Hamburg Ballet...
will be in the First Class.
- An elite dancer from abroad. - I'm so curious.
(The first Korean ballerino in Hamburg Ballet)
He's the first Korean ballerino in Hamburg Ballet.
When I say, "I'm from Hamburg Ballet,"
people think I'm a good dancer. It's a famous ballet company.
The physical ranking. My goodness.
How can you get 18 points?
But I can tell he has a great body just by looking at the picture.
He's confident in pirouette.
Looking at his body, I think his turns will be great.
(Technique I'm confident in: Pirouette)
I was born with a nice body.
People in the ballet company said...
my pirouette was clean.
Many people said my mid-air positions...
were nice.
I'm confident...
that I'll do better than any other dancer here.
Ballerino Moon Jun On. He's so brave...
because he's not intimidated only with 2.5 years of experience.
He has a great potential.
(Clean and upright)
Min Kwon is a good-looking guy.
- He's handsome. - Yes.
He looks like a ballet prince.
Min Kwon has beautiful legs.
I think Min Kwon is an ideal dancer in terms of his physical appearance.
From what I know, he went to Korea National University of Arts.
I think he'll be in the First Class.
I was a little mad.
I thought I should show them properly.
(When the ballet judging groups were revealed)
- What? - What?
Jun On has 2.5 years of experience.
I wanted to avoid Kang Gyeong Ho. It was a little annoying.
He came to my group because of that?
"What's this guy?"
Min Kwon.
As for Min Kwon, I remember him...
as someone whose looks shined more than his skills.
He wasn't anything more than that.
(Kang Yun Gu)
(Group C)
I'm sure he knows my name.
We often met at competitions.
The result was my victory.
I thought that I'd help him remember the past.
I kept seeing Min Kwon.
(Light and airy)
He didn't have the best technique in the past.
But he has good technique now.
I thought, "I'll need to work hard."
Seriously, the pirouette is the problem.
(Faltering)
Pirouette is my weak suit.
I was very worried.
Hold on.
The member who has confidence in the pirouette is here.
I have no confidence in the pirouette.
How many turns can you do?
If I do well, I do four turns.
- Otherwise, I do three turns. - Two turns.
You must be confident.
Pirouette is your specialty, right?
Can you do nine turns?
I can't do 9 turns. I do 6 to 7 turns.
(I'm jealous.)
(Fancy)
I think the pirouette is my strong suit.
It's my weapon and skill.
I have confidence.
My experience only goes back a few years.
But the other contestants are from Korea National University of Arts...
and a German ballet company.
It'll be tough.
- Still, - No, I can do it.
I don't get intimidated.
(Very confident)
I can spin very well.
I have confidence when it comes to jumping.
(Look at him.)
(He practices without a break.)
I'll go as far as I can.
Let's join the First Class.
I'll join the First Class.
I'll claim the title of the First Class.
Let's take our first position.
- I'm excited about Kang Yun Gu. - How cool.
- Music. - They must be nervous.
Start.
Three, two, one.
(Group C, Round 2, Center Technique starts.)
(Concentrating)
Allonge.
(Allonge: A lengthening movement of the arms)
Shin Min Kwon pointed his toes well.
He pointed his toes well.
Let's go.
(Pirouette: A spinning movement on one leg)
I'm really confident when it comes to pirouette.
Pirouette.
Oh, no.
(Oh, no!)
He wanted to do three turns,
but ended up doing two turns because the music rushed him.
And the spotting was very lacking. The head rotated with the body.
Jun On's spotting was very nice.
(Moon Jun On made good use of the spotting technique.)
What was that? They were unimpressive.
Sissonne.
Double cabriole.
Kang Yun Gu didn't do a double cabriole.
Perhaps, he can't do it.
(Kang Yun Gu and Moon Jun On beat their feet once in the air.)
(Shin Min Kwon beat his feet twice in the air.)
(Jete)
Ciseaux.
Nice.
You need to make a straight line with your legs in the air.
As for Min Kwon, he made a straight line.
It was very nice.
As for Yun Gu, his movement didn't look like a ciseaux.
(Disappointed)
The dominating thought was that I might get eliminated.
Six.
Min Kwon is clean...
- compared to the other two. - Yes.
I had the most confidence in the last one, passe tour en l'air.
I decided to wrap up in a cool way.
Stop.
(The ones who wrapped up stably were Shin Min Kwon...)
(and Moon Jun On.)
One. Stop.
- Be careful. - It's okay.
Stop.
(Kang Yun Gu ended the performance with an unstable landing.)
(He can't bear to watch it.)
How disappointing.
(Group C, Round 2, Center Technique ends.)
(Sighing)
(Kang Yun Gu can't hide his disappointment as he goes back.)
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
- Watching him made my heart ache. - I know.
(I see.)
That was unexpected.
- It was weaker than I expected. - It was too weak.
This is so sad. Seriously. I looked forward to seeing them.
- I know. - Yes.
They looked so beautiful in a standing position.
I'm in trouble.
I'm disappointed in myself.
As for Yun Gu...
I was just dumbfounded.
What was that? As for Yun Gu,
I still don't understand him.
We'll now reveal the dancer...
who got cut out...
and joined the Second Class.
I wasn't very worried.
I thought that I did pretty well.
I waited for the result calmly.
It'll be the one in the middle.
(Nodding)
The Second Class dancer is...
Unfortunately, you've ranked Second.
It's all right. Thank you.
Dancer Kang Yun Gu.
(Second Class of Group C, Kang Yun Gu)
(Wary)
(The result of Kang Yun Gu, the ace, brings tension to Group C.)
He has... He gives a lot of main character energy.
But unfortunately, the dancing did not support that.
- Yun Gu couldn't do any techniques. - You're right.
(Double cabriole)
(Failed)
(Ciseaux)
(Passe tour en l'air)
(Failed)
Kang Yun Gu is...
- below my expectations. - Me too.
- Good work. - Good work.
(Kang Yun Gu exits after a poor result.)
It hurt my pride, to be honest.
But there was a risk of an injury...
since I had taken a long break.
During my time in the Hamburg Ballet,
I sustained a big knee injury.
My dancing wouldn't be the same after the surgery,
so people advised me to get it after retirement.
So I haven't gotten the surgery yet.
When I watched the Center Technique video,
I realized that it wouldn't be easy.
There were many big jumps.
I thought, "What will I do if I get injured?"
"If I get injured,"
"it'll be a big loss."
I'm disappointed, but I can't undo the past hiatus.
Until the next mission, I'll get back into shape...
and show everyone.
Round Three will begin.
(Shin Min Kwon versus Moon Jun On, Who will be the First Class?)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
(Startled)
How cute.
You have confidence. I'll watch carefully.
Look at those youngsters.
Moon Jun On is on the younger side.
He has only done ballet for two and a half years.
But he came this far.
It means that he has talent.
So I became wary of him.
I thought, "This is insane."
I couldn't believe that my competitor was...
from Korea National University of Arts.
I had hopes of joining the First Class.
I couldn't wait to get started.
Music,
start.
(How will Ballerino Moon Jun On do on the verge of being First Class?)
- Let's go. - I hope he does well.
(Tour en l'air, 3 times)
Tour en l'air.
That's it.
(Impressed)
- Not bad. - He can jump well.
(Tour en l'air, 1st time)
His jumps are powerful. There's nice elasticity.
What? He's good.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
He has nice coordination.
- Yes. - He does it instinctively.
- He needs to be careful. - My goodness.
Be careful.
My knees continued to ache.
Let's see the manege.
(Manege)
(Sighing)
(Grinning)
(Manege)
The back leg was bent. He couldn't push through.
Because of that, his arms kept going up.
Watching his manege made me think, "I have a chance of winning."
My knees hurt so much.
(Groaning)
I decided to jump until the end.
- Keep going until the end. - Keep going until the end.
I think his knees hurt.
(Ciseaux)
(Passe tour en l'air)
(Ending pose)
Two, one. Stop.
(Moon Jun On endured the pain and finished Round 3.)
He didn't get injured, did he?
He got hurt. I'm 100 percent sure. His knees were hurt.
My knees hurt too much.
That was when my worry grew.
If I don't make a big mistake, I'll be able to win.
(Ballerino Shin Min Kwon takes over!)
Tour en l'air.
Okay.
His tour en l'air is perfect.
There are definitely comfort and stability.
(Impressed)
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
Good.
He's definitely good.
(Tour en l'air, 3rd time)
- It was clean. - He's very calm.
Manege.
I had confidence, so I decided to do it as I always have.
There you go.
Both legs form a straight line.
His arm movements are very stable too.
The upper body movements are very clean.
It's so clean.
He did very well. He had good basic skills.
I thought, "Nice. Let's keep it up until the end."
He has an intelligent vibe when he dances.
- He's like a gentleman. - He's calm.
Three...
"Let's get points with the technique I have confidence in,"
"passe tour en l'air."
(Passe tour en l'air)
(Ending pose)
Nice.
(My goodness)
He really looks like a prince.
(The last technique, grand pirouette)
I wrapped up well.
Let's join the First Class with the grand pirouette.
Will my knees hold out?
It was the last chance to make up for my mistake.
I decided to forget about my knees and do my absolute best.
I can do it.
I'll definitely win. My experience is on another level.
Four, three, two,
one. Go.
(Round 3, 1-on-1 Fixed Technique, Grand pirouette starts.)
Nice.
What? Why is he so good?
How is he turning so fast?
(Ballerino Moon Jun On shows incredible speed.)
His fouette is nice.
His pirouette is very nice.
He knows how to turn.
It's nice.
They say young blood is scary. He was so fast.
- Min Kwon... - He's stable.
- turns in a stable way. - He's stable.
He's very calm.
- Yes. - He's very cautious.
- His dance is very calm. - Very.
- That's why it looks very noble. - Yes.
In terms of the angle and speed, I'm a bit better.
It's very unexpected. I'm talking about Moon Jun On.
In terms of technique, Moon Jun On is better.
My goodness.
- What? - What?
(Moon Jun On loses his balance and falters.)
What?
They'll clash.
(Hold on.)
He kept coming closer to me. I was scared that we'd collide.
They'll clash.
(Faltering)
Use your strength.
(Moon Jun On finishes turning before the music ends.)
Oh, no.
- Three, - Interesting.
two, one. Stop.
(My goodness)
Had he landed well, it would've been fine.
(Disappointed)
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
(He hangs his head.)
- All right. Thank you. - Finish.
So important.
It's a big pet peeve of mine when people don't finish.
I mean, it's so hard.
It's so... I know it's hard.
But... Imagine if they had to do that onstage.
(Squeezing his eyes shut)
I couldn't believe it. I ended it like a fool.
Even if he couldn't finish doing 32 turns,
he had to fill the music with movements.
Had I clashed with him, it would've been a disaster.
I wanted to wrap up...
even if I had to end the performance a bit earlier.
The two of you did very well.
We'll now announce the result.
Shin Min Kwon,
you were very calm and noble.
You rarely faltered.
You even had a serene smile on your face.
Your performance was impressive.
Moon Jun On, you kept catching my eyes.
You pushed yourself to finish the performance.
Your resolution and passion to show what you can do...
moved me greatly.
If Shin Min Kwon and Moon Jun On had a difference...
It was a match between passion and basic skills.
Good work.
This is hard.
I have no idea who'll win.
(Rehearsal Director Matthew moves to announce the result.)
Ballerino Shin Min Kwon and Ballerino Moon Jun On.
The First Class is...
After advancing this far, I became ambitious.
I thought I had a chance.
You've achieved the highest rank first. Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
(First)
(First Class of Group C, Shin Min Kwon)
(Disappointed)
(The competitors of Group C applaud him.)
It made me happy.
I need to protect the title of First Class.
I'll work hard to do that.
I'll show everyone who Group C's First Class is.
(Shin Min Kwon in the 1st Class)
- You're the Second Class. - Thank you.
- Practice the basics a bit harder. - Okay.
Moon Jun On joined the Second Class.
I was very disappointed.
Had my knees been fine, I would've had a chance.
(Shin Min Kwon and Moon Jun On return...)
(as members of different classes.)
Your passion and spirit were nice.
You did well. You fought well.
- Youth is the best. - Moon Jun On.
I'll remember his eyes.
We're gaining energy from them. It's a therapeutic experience.
Dancers who throw their bodies into the performance...
give a therapeutic experience.
(Ballet, Physical and Technique Audition)
(Group D: Kim Kyung Won, Kim Sang Young, and Kim Yu Chan)
(Watching carefully)
They're neck-and-neck.
I think Group D is the group of death.
Yu Chan is a dancer who studied abroad.
He was in the Joffrey Ballet.
Kyung Won was in the Korean National Ballet.
Anyone will agree that he's a talented dancer.
(A tall man stands between the two talented dancers.)
(Kim Sang Young is a college student with a short and sweet resume.)
(Worked as a musical actor)
That was when I became incredibly nervous.
I was contending against professional dancers.
(His two hands become polite.)
I realized that I'd have to pull up my energy 100 times more.
Group D, Kim Yu Chan,
Kim Sang Young,
Kim Kyung Won.
(Kim Kyung Won blows a kiss in a relaxed way.)
(Satisfied)
(He's so relaxed.)
Nice.
He's relaxed.
I have so much confidence.
When they showed us the video of the techniques...
Okay.
I realized that there were many techniques I could do well.
There was the ciseaux.
And I have confidence in the cabriole.
I think I'll be the First Class.
(Glancing over)
I was a bit worried.
I have confidence in raising one leg and holding the position...
for the arabesque or doing the pirouette.
But jump techniques aren't my strong suit.
So...
I decided to use a different strategy.
That was why I decided to join Group D.
I don't start a losing fight.
I'll leave a strong impression from the start.
Many dancers in the previous groups made mistakes.
So I thought of ways to minimize the mistakes.
(Practice before the audition)
I can't do the ciseaux.
I'll do the assemble instead.
Just like that?
I need to do what I'm good at.
I can't perfect a technique in a short amount of time.
Instead of perfecting a weak technique...
in a short amount of time,
I'll show a strong technique and make an impression.
I have a plan.
Let's take our first position, please.
First Class is my goal.
Let's focus. Let's not get too excited.
Let's follow the plan.
(Staring intently)
Yu Chan's turn-out is very nice. So is Sang Young's.
Kyung Won's turn-out is nice too.
I love the way they're pointing with their back feet.
I'm looking forward to this group.
Music,
(Group D, Round 2, Center Technique)
start.
(Allonge: A lengthening movement of the arms)
Yu Chan.
(Yu Chan makes a strong impression by using the lines of his body.)
He's showing his strengths from the start.
He used a bit of a trick.
Pirouette.
I have confidence in the pirouette.
- Good. - Good. Sissonne.
One, two, three.
Four turns.
(Meanwhile, Kim Sang Young and Kim Kyung Won made three turns.)
I would've loved to see four turns. That was a bit disappointing.
Sissonne. Double cabriole.
(Double cabriole: A movement of beating the legs twice in the air)
Okay.
(Kim Kyung Won beat his feet twice in the air.)
Even his double cabriole was perfect.
Cabriole. One beat was disappointing.
Making two beats in the air is very difficult.
I have so much confidence in such techniques.
Grand jete.
(Impressed)
It was nice. He jumped high.
He's very springy.
He was in the air for a longer period of time.
Yu Chan also seemed to jump very high.
But it wasn't his jump that was nice.
It just seemed that way because he was flexible.
His jump is incredibly low.
But it looks high since his legs are split in the air.
As for Sang Young, he stayed on the same level.
His jump is a bit lacking.
(Here comes the ciseaux.)
I'm the most confident in the ciseaux.
Ciseaux.
(He has my approval.)
Nice.
His elasticity is very nice.
He's full of strength.
(How about Kim Yu Chan who had no confidence in the ciseaux?)
What was that?
He didn't do the ciseaux.
(Well...)
I think he did the assemble since he lacked confidence.
Kim Yu Chan's jump is a bit lacking.
Instead of doing a technique I have no confidence in,
I'll show a technique I can do well.
Chaines.
Tour en l'air. Yes.
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
(Just like Kim Yu Chan,)
(Kim Kyung Won wrapped up in a stable way.)
(Faltering)
(Kim Sang Young's landing was unstable.)
(I feel bad.)
The thing is, it's a big mistake.
I was disappointed.
I'm satisfied with my performance.
Even though I omitted the ciseaux because I had no confidence,
I didn't make any big mistakes.
I focused on that thought throughout the performance.
We'll now reveal the dancer who got cut out...
and joined the Second Class.
When I was waiting for the result,
what I did badly kept replaying in my head.
I thought that I might join the Second Class.
The Second Class dancer is...
(Turning)
Unfortunately, you've ranked Second.
Dancer Kim Sang Young.
Thank you for your hard work.
Sang Young's jump was a bit low.
His core strength was a bit lacking.
Thank you for your hard work.
(Second Class of Group D, Kim Sang Young)
I really enjoyed the performance.
Yu Chan,
your jump was a bit disappointing.
But I thought that your movements were very delicate and flexible.
I enjoyed the way you presented basic techniques.
When I watched Kim Kyung Won,
it was like a film noir.
Extreme charisma and jumps.
I think that was a very professional power.
Round 3 is the 1-on-1 Fixed Technique.
Only one ballerino...
can be in the First Class.
But they're both very good.
This will give us the answer.
- Let's go. - I can do it.
Because I feel confident in moving faster with more power,
I will be able to win.
If I beat all these outstanding ballerinos...
and enter the First Class, it'll be more satisfying.
First position.
Music,
start.
Five, four...
(Laid-back hand gesture)
(Charismatic)
(Mesmerized)
(Stretching)
(Tour en l'air, 3 times)
(Tour en l'air, 1st time)
(Exclaiming)
The landing was heavy.
Nice jump.
(Tour en l'air, 1st time)
When the spin looks clear in the air,
it looks even better.
That was neat.
I was full of confidence.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
That's right.
(Nodding)
I was worried.
I am the First Class.
(Tour en l'air, 3rd time)
That's amazing.
(A laid-back smile)
- Manege. - What have I done until now?
(Manege)
Okay. Good.
Keep stretching forward.
He tends to turn his arms upside down,
but still, it's very nice.
It wasn't impressive enough.
Three, two...
(Passe tour en l'air)
(Kim Kyung Won's ending pose)
Okay.
(They can't take their eyes off Kim Kyung Won's moves.)
Nice jump.
He showed masculine energy.
(Kim Yu Chan presents his techniques next.)
I should be confident.
(Tour en l'air, 3 times)
(Tour en l'air, 1st time)
His jumps are rather weak.
A bit more.
(Tour en l'air, 2nd time)
Oh, no.
Yu Chan looks like he turns once in the air...
and finishes the rest on the ground.
I have a chance.
His jumps and spins are a bummer.
(Manege)
I feel confident in manege.
(They are...)
(impressed.)
Gosh.
(Manege)
He's clearly flexible.
It's pretty. So pretty.
(Nervous)
The angle was different compared to Kim Kyung Won's manege,
He was good at jumping.
That is...
one nice and flexible manege.
His manege is nice to see since he's flexible.
(Passe tour en l'air and ending pose)
His manege was really pretty.
Good job.
The two are complete opposites.
I want to give Yu Chan points for manege.
And I want to give Kyung Won points for tour en l'air.
We'll have to see the pirouette...
- To know. - to decide it, right?
(Kim Kyung Won and Kim Yu Chan get ready for the grand pirouette.)
(Kim Kyung Won and Kim Yu Chan ran out of breath...)
(due to the series of technique combinations.)
Yu Chan.
(Kim Kyung Won passes Kim Yu Chan water.)
Thank you.
He looked pitiful.
I'm so drained. He must be drained too.
(Exhaling)
Good luck.
(Although they're rivals, they root for each other.)
Are you two ready? Let's begin the grand pirouette.
(At that moment, Coach Ryu Hoi Woong notices something.)
Hey.
(Look at this.)
Gosh. In here?
It says Yu Chan is good at grand pirouette.
(Kim Yu Chan picked grand pirouette as his confident technique.)
I'm good at grand pirouette, and I feel confident about it.
I can't help but become the First Class.
I'll have to focus as much as I can.
First position.
Music, start.
Five, four,
- three, two... - He's already confident.
(Round 3, 1-on-1 Fixed Technique, grand pirouette starts.)
- Nice. - Good.
(Watching)
(Yu Chan and Kyung Won continue with stable grand pirouettes.)
Good. They're both very good.
- They're very good. - Keep it up.
(At that moment)
He's bending his leg.
(Did I see that right?)
(Spotting)
My legs became jelly.
Kyung Won's leg is getting tired.
I expected him to falter.
I'll end it here.
(Kim Yu Chan even shows a variation.)
(Eyes focused)
Gosh.
He looked like a swan, didn't he?
He's putting on a very difficult technique.
I have to say Yu Chan is good.
I'll endure it until the end.
(One more time!)
(Impressive)
How...
(How is that possible?)
He nailed it.
(Yu Chan finished it before the music.)
(That's a shame.)
(No.)
I'll grit my teeth and endure it.
- Until the end. - Until the end.
Yes. Finish it no matter what.
(Kim Kyung Won finishes the grand pirouette according to the music.)
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
He should've turned until the end. That was a shame.
(Nodding)
(Sighing)
If I messed up the ending,
I might as well do chaines, despite losing points.
I did my best with no regrets.
(Respect)
Awesome.
That was crazy.
That was neck-and-neck.
How are they going to choose?
I think Kyung Won...
(The master and coaches begin discussing.)
was better.
Kyung Won was better,
but we can't ignore the grand pirouette.
He did a good job.
(Kim Yu Chan put on the perfect grand pirouette.)
His attitude and posture.
(The master and coaches have a disagreement for a while.)
I felt that his grand pirouettes...
Kyung Won was really nice.
(Kim Kyung Won's tour en l'air was better.)
(Kim Yu Chan's manege was better.)
(Although Kim Kyung Won's pose was a bummer, he still finished it.)
(Kim Yu Chan's pose was perfect, but he didn't finish it.)
(Who will be the one to become First Class?)
I'll announce the result.
One of you will become First Class.
And the other will become Second Class.
I vote for Kyung Won.
I vote for Yu Chan.
I'll announce the result.
Between the two, the First Class is...
(Who will win the First Class?)
We couldn't decide it.
(Unable to judge)
What?
(Then what's going to happen?)
So we're going to ask you for a favour.
(A favour?)
Can you put on...
your best ballet moves...
in 32 counts?
But it should be something that shows...
ballet techniques and basic ballet skills.
It's not easy.
That must be really tough.
How are they going to do that?
It's the end. I must pull it off.
My goal is to become First Class.
Let's start with Kim Kyung Won.
First position.
Music, start.
(The master and coaches' unprecedented suggestion)
(What will Kim Kyung Won present?)
It's already begun with his pose.
Should I show my best technique I already showed in Round Three?
I'll prove myself in an artistic way.
Go.
(Impressed)
(Amazing)
Gosh.
(He's good.)
I can do better than that.
Gosh.
Okay.
It's amazing.
It's wonderful.
Nice.
It's like watching a scene from "Carmen."
It reminds me of "Carmen."
Stay focused until the end.
Three, two, one.
Stop.
Gosh.
(Wrapping up with a controlled posture)
Well done.
(Approved)
That was cool.
- That was sexy. - I could feel...
his years of experience.
(Kim Kyung Won presented his charm with his artistic performance.)
I'm embarrassed.
(Kim Kyung Won is embarrassed after performing.)
I'm so tired.
Kim Yu Chan will start.
First position.
Music, start.
(Kim Yu Chan starts from the corner of the stage.)
What's he planning to do in the far back?
I've had many regrets.
This time, I decided to show my strength.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
Go.
(Eyes focused)
(A light and flexible jump to present his shape)
(Everyone is in awe.)
Gosh.
(Kim Yu Chan dances all over the stage.)
- He's flexible. - It's very nice.
(Kim Yu Chan's specialty, the grand pirouette)
He still has stamina left?
Yu Chan is full of energy.
(Kim Yu Chan overpowers the stage with his perfect technique.)
He's doing even better.
(A perfect turn)
(A relaxed expression as if he's enjoying the stage)
Three, two, one. Stop.
Two, one. Stop.
(A charismatic end pose)
That was unbelievable.
(You can watch the dancers' full performances on The CHOOM.)
(Kim Yu Chan showed off his various techniques and specialty.)
(As expected from the ballet strategist)
Dancers, please move to the center of the stage for your evaluations.
That was insane.
He's unbeatable.
Yu Chan had a great strategy.
- Who do you think it'll be? - Yu Chan.
- That was... - I'm the opposite.
- Really? - Yes.
Both of them were amazing.
It's tough.
Your dances were superb.
It was as we expected.
Kim Kyung Won showed us...
his confident energy.
Kim Yu Chan showed us his classic technique,
based on his basic skills.
Both of you are very different dancers...
and offer very different qualities.
So I think both of you should feel successful today in what you showed.
I will announce the result.
Ballerino Kim Kyung Won and Ballerino Kim Yu Chan.
The First Class is...
Who is it?
(Who is Ballet Group D's First Class?)
Ballerino Kim Yu Chan.
(Group D First Class Kim Yu Chan)
Congratulations.
Ballerino Kim Yu Chan.
(Bummed out)
(Comforting each other after their hard work)
(He agrees.)
You achieved the highest rank of first place.
- Congratulations. - Thank you so much.
- You were amazing. - Thank you.
Failing the ciseaux move...
in Round Two kept bothering me.
So I did the grand jete,
a different jump move,
to highlight my flexibility.
I didn't hold back on anything,
which makes me happy.
Ballerino Kim Kyung Won is in Second Class.
(Group D Second Class Kang Gyeong Ho)
Unfortunately, I got placed in Second Class.
But I'm satisfied with giving it my best in the audition...
and don't regret anything.
(The two finally smile.)
You're First Class.
I'm exhausted.
Great job.
(24 Korean dance classical scholars appear)
(Will there be a rival match between Ki Moo Gan and Choi Ho Jong?)
(24 contemporary dance beasts appear)
(The beasts are highly competitive.)
(The Physical and Technique Audition is finally starting.)
(The deadly battle to become First Class begins.)
(STF Dance Company where the dancers gather)
(What is the last genre to enter?)
(The orange locker room is prepared to welcome the dancers.)
(This bright and neat space is...)
(the Korean dance locker room.)
- Hi. - Hi.
(A Korean dancer with strong facial features appears)
I'm Jang Sung Bum in Korean dance.
Despite having exotic features,
I'm Jang Sung Bum who's majoring in Korean dance.
"Where are you from?"
People guess the Arab countries.
(An Arabian feature)
My hobby is playing Go.
I like makgeolli.
My favourite ice creams are the ones elders like with red beans...
and chestnuts.
I may have exotic features,
but I can express the Korean vibe well.
(He has the Korean moves.)
In a recent competition,
everyone said that I had a good physique and great technique.
The technique I'm most confident in is the walkover.
I can do it smoothly.
Give it to me.
The guy I came with today is Sung Hun Mo.
He's my only guy friend...
from Chung-Ang University's freshmen of 2018.
My focus is on Korean interpretative dance,
while he is focused on traditional dance.
Korean interpretative dance...
utilizes traditional breathing and moves as the base...
to add modern moves.
That's what Korean interpretative dance is.
The charms of Korean traditional dance are...
moving the legs heavily,
the chest lightly, and the fingers in detail using our breath.
Korean traditional dance...
encompasses Korean sentiments and the people's outlook...
on the world.
Hi. I'm a 24-year-old...
Korean dancer, Sung Hun Mo.
Majoring in Korean traditional dance,
I'm taking courses in National Intangible Cultural Heritage's...
Gang Seon Yeong Taepyeongmu...
and Seoul Intangible Cultural Heritage's Hanryangmu.
It's here. "Korean dance."
- Let's go in. - My heart is pounding.
(Entering)
(The two enter excitedly.)
- My gosh. - We're sharing the locker room.
It's so fascinating.
(We're here!)
(Opening)
(Let's have a look.)
There are a lot of bits and bobs.
(Customized gifts for the dancers)
(We love gifts.)
(While they're looking around the locker room...)
(Startled)
(What?)
(Name: Jang Sung Bum, Age: 25)
(Embarrassed)
(His beautiful profile photo made his friend laugh.)
Fifteen points rank you fourteenth.
You're sharing 17th place.
I'm in the far back.
(Shocked)
Neither of us even ranked in the middle.
I thought my physical score could become a weakness.
(A little anxious)
What?
(What's that?)
A shared second place.
Five points for squats, five points for push-ups,
five points for rotational stability,
and three points for balance.
- I could've done better. - Right?
- You're highly competitive. - I am.
I can do it.
(Burning with motivation)
As a dancer,
I get highly motivated...
if my physique falls behind.
The presence...
my gifted physique gives out is my strongest point.
Physique is the most important.
(Judging Groups Register)
I have to stick it on here?
(The dancers register for the Korean Dance...)
(Physical and Technique Audition.)
(They will be judged in their registered groups.)
Group D.
I don't really mind who I go up against.
As long as it's not Hyo Joon.
I'm Kim Hyo Joon who's majoring in Korean dance.
My body...
is made of compressed muscles from dancing.
A body fat percentage of 3 is a 1st.
Do you manage your body fat?
No. I only dance a lot.
As I dance, I make great use of...
my flexibility and muscular strength.
I'm confident in everything.
But my techniques stand out.
I modify jaban.
Utilizing novel textures and physical moves.
My goodness.
(The two are made speechless by their outstanding rivals.)
(Nervous)
What now?
- We saw them at the concert hall. - I know.
I went to watch Hyo Joon's performances a couple of times.
(This is bad.)
He's here.
Both of them have a lot of experience...
and are excellent dancers.
What now?
I hope they don't stick it next to mine.
(Spacing out)
Is it because the two are on top and bottom?
I can't take my eyes off those spots.
Right? I was going to go for Group B.
But Groups C and D don't look bad.
Shall we split into Groups C and D?
- I can feel it. - Which group is it?
I'm going to this group.
(Which group did Kim Si Won choose?)
(Korean Dance Locker Room)
What?
(Sung Hun Mo's neighbouring spots have been filled.)
(A bitter smile)
Hun Mo. You've been chosen.
(Laughing)
Why?
(Why me?)
(Why is it me?)
Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
Hyo Joon or Si Won? Who stuck their name next to mine?
(Opening)
(The two dancers who made them tense appear.)
- Hi. - Hi.
Hi.
(Nervous and wary)
(Peeking)
(The locker room is filled with tension after an awkward greeting.)
My heart is pounding.
(Looking around)
Who is next to me?
The locker next to Hun Mo's.
(A solemn face)
(Getting nervous as well)
Did you choose Group C?
(Unresponsive)
Did I look easy to deal with?
(Walking on eggshells)
(What?)
(Kim Hyo Joon chose Group C.)
I know his techniques and physique are great.
(Shocked)
I'm scared.
My eyes were drawn to it.
Whoever I compete against, I'm confident about winning.
(The locker room is silent after the group reveal.)
(Glancing)
(Pressured)
(Kim Si Won can't take his eye off someone.)
- We have similar hairstyles. - Right.
- Yes, our concepts overlap. - Right?
(The dancers' exotic features and long hair overlap.)
But I'm wearing a binyeo.
My hair is probably prettier.
(Kim Si Won: I have the best long hair!)
Do you two know each other?
- We're friends. - University friends.
(Surprised)
- Which university are you from? - Sungkyunkwan University.
Same here.
Are people from the same university coming together?
It seems like it.
(At that moment)
(Turning)
- Kyu Nyeon's here. - Kim Kyu Nyeon. It's Kyu Nyeon.
"The next-generation Korean dance talent."
Kyu Nyeon came first this year.
(Judging Groups Register)
Hi.
I'm a 23-year-old Korean dancer, Kim Kyu Nyeon.
I won quite a lot of competitions.
I must've won about ten awards in middle school.
(An awards collector since middle and high school)
I won the Grand Prize and Kim Paek Pong Award...
in the 54th Dong-A Dance Competition...
for general interpretative dance.
(The talent among talents)
The guys I came with today...
are Park Jun Woo and Kim Jong Cheol.
We're like a family...
from Korea National University of Arts.
That's why we came together.
Jun Woo has good techniques.
His jaban jumps are great.
The floor technique I created...
was very novel.
I'm good at it.
And I'm confident in making use of...
the smooth moves of Korean dance.
Those are my charming points.
Kyu Nyeon and Jong Cheol are my top competitors.
As for Jong Cheol, he has a sexy physique.
Jong Cheol.
"A wild charm?" He does look wild.
He has a great body.
Physique-wise, I heard I was masculine...
and had great muscles.
- I was shocked... - Yes?
when you walked inside.
Among the dancers I met here, you have a well-built upper body.
I like physiques like yours.
Thank you.
I'm a lot more muscular compared to other dancers.
Many have told me my dance...
is erotic and sexy.
Jong Cheol is very young.
He's 21 years old.
Isn't your age gap wide?
The dancers could be my disciples.
(Disciples?)
It doesn't feel easy anymore.
(His possible disciples have chosen their groups.)
(Kim Si Won and Jang Sung Bum have competitors now.)
(Gone mad?)
(Glaring)
(Can't help but let out a sigh)
A guy stuck his name in the group I was in.
Who is it?
I want to know who stuck his name next to mine.
Kyu Nyeon?
(His lips are trembling.)
- Jun Woo? - I think it's the other guy.
- Jong Cheol? - Yes.
(You mean Jong Cheol?)
(Opening)
- Hi. - Welcome.
(Kim Jong Cheol arrives just in time.)
- Hi. - Hi.
(Who stuck their names next to Jang Sung Bum and Kim Si Won?)
(Peeking)
(There's a tension in the locker room.)
I'm using the third one.
Okay.
So, who is it next to Si Won?
(Curious)
It's one of us.
Is it Kyu Nyeon?
(Looking away)
(Kim Kyu Nyeon answers with an awkward laugh.)
(Not giving up)
- Jun Woo. - Yes?
You're avoiding my eyes.
(Laughing)
Wait for me.
(The laughs can't cover up the suspense.)
(Which group did the three K-Arts students choose?)
(Kim Jong Cheol chose Group B.)
(Trying hard to smile)
(Come on.)
It's okay.
Is it because you like me?
Of course.
That wasn't what you said earlier.
(Flustered)
Am I worth a try?
(Why did Kim Jong Cheol choose Group B?)
- Do we stick it on now? - Yes.
This is crazy.
(What do I do?)
I choose this spot.
Si Won. I'll stick to you.
(Is it out of admiration for Si Won?)
I'll bring you down.
(Smiling)
The technique...
is not Kim Si Won's strong point.
I can earn First Class.
Did he think I was beatable?
Then I'll show him.
Give it your best, Jong Cheol, because I will too.
(Angry)
Where do I go?
These two are incredible.
But this audition has to do with physique and technique.
- Must we avoid the youngsters? - Yes.
Kim Si Won is my high school senior.
A junior challenging his senior. Group B.
I'll see you on stage, kids.
Come on. I'm full of confidence.
"Former acrobat?"
"Gymnastic acrobatics?"
We have our first five-star technique.
I was taken aback.
New words like cartwheel full twist, corkscrew, and such.
Are those techniques by Korean dancers?
- Hi. - Hi.
We're doomed.
(They chose the empty groups, A and F.)
(Everyone is relieved.)
(Thank goodness.)
Gosh.
It was a relief they weren't in my group.
More and more interesting people are arriving.
(The reveal of a new profile...)
(shocks everyone.)
(A dancer startling everyone is here?)
He's here.
Ho Jong is here.
He has all gold, silver, and bronze.
See that hashtag?
"National Dance Company of Korea lead dancer."
He's named.
The best in Korea.
Choi Ho Jong.
He is the dancer to dancers.
I can risk everything on him.
He's indomitable.
- My role model. - A legend.
He's been the lead dancer...
of the best national dance company.
A dancer would've watched his competition clip at least once.
I started dancing...
after watching Choi Ho Jong's video.
(Korean dancer Choi Ho Jong won...)
(the 2016 Dong-A Dance Competition Grand Prize.)
When I first started dancing, one of the clips I watched...
was Choi Ho Jong's competition performance.
It's what made me dance.
(The legend and the reason himself has come.)
His technique has been incredible since then.
From floor technique to jumping,
he's great at everything like an all-genre dancer.
The deity of the dancing world.
A monster.
His muscles aren't like a Korean's.
He has the best physique.
Putting aside his efforts,
Ho Jong has an outstanding physique talent.
Physical ability and mobility-wise,
I doubt there's a better dancer than him.
He's in first place.
(For real?)
(This is bad.)
As expected from the physical monster, he got a full score.
Darn it.
Ho Jong got first place for the physical test.
The fact that I was in second place was...
- But... - Each only has one star.
Why did he only give himself one star each?
(That's absurd.)
I'm shocked.
Thank you.
(Choi Ho Jong calmly walks inside.)
- Hi. - Hi.
(The legendary Korean dancer)
I will always give myself one star.
I started dancing at a late age.
So I lived with a sense of inferiority.
"What's wrong with me?"
"Why can't I do that?"
There was a time...
when I lost it and danced without a break.
I pushed myself to the point...
I had no sweat left in my body.
I realized back then...
that I should dance to be happy.
The awakening...
was my turning point.
(Choi Ho Jong stands before the judging groups.)
(He scans through the judging groups closely.)
I expected more distinguished dancers to participate.
It disappointed me a little.
(Quiet but deadly...)
I'm confident.
(is his confidence.)
(Which group did Choi Ho Jong choose?)
(Hands together)
I'm curious as to which group he chose.
This is putting me in fear.
I'm scared.
I should pray now.
It was nerve-racking since then.
First place.
(The top physique)
(Which group was chosen by Choi Ho Jong?)
(Opening)
(Korean dancer Choi Ho Jong has finally appeared.)
- He's here. - Hi, Ho Jong.
(Everyone is nervous.)
- Hey. - Hi.
(Choi Ho Jong looks relaxed.)
(Nervous yet curious)
He has this aura.
(Frozen)
I guess the atmosphere got chilly.
(Everyone is focused on Choi Ho Jong.)
Before I knew it, I kept my mouth shut since then.
All of us got overpowered by his presence.
(Please not my group.)
It won't be me.
Don't be next to me.
Oh, my gosh.
(Korean Dance Physical and Technique Audition Judging Groups)
(Choi Ho Jong chose Group E.)
(Laughing)
(I feel bad for him.)
(I'm the saddest person on earth.)
(All he can do is let out a sigh.)
I'm sorry.
(Smiling)
I wouldn't want to compete against me either.
It helped me feel at ease.
Since my group has an invincible dancer,
I can dance at peace.
(Resigned)
Everyone is good-looking.
I know, right?
I thought I would leave the strongest impression.
It made me wonder if the dancers were chosen based on their looks.
Everyone was waiting like classical scholars.
They looked very oriental.
I thought they were scholars, like no joke.
(They brighten up the locker room.)
(Who is the next attractive Korean dancer?)
(Who is this strange man approaching the STF Dance Company?)
Stage Fighter. I'm getting nervous.
(A guy wearing floral-printed clothes and not a scholar)
I've got to overcome it with my vibe. This is me.
Now then.
What can the people with long arms and legs do?
(An unusual move by an unusual intruder)
(Dancing)
(Flashy from head to toe)
Get over it.
(Who is this man?)
I'm a YouTuber with 58,000 subscribers.
I can make it through.
Hi. I'm a professional YouTuber, Suncapboi.
- What? - Hold on.
"Suncapboi."
(The dancers know Suncapboi.)
Is he Suncapboi?
"Suncapboi?"
I even asked him for an autograph.
- Really? - Yes.
Suncapboi got 17.92 million views for one short video.
I wanted dance to become an art loved by many.
It would be nice if people took an interest...
and came watch dance performances through Suncapboi.
It's my alter ego made for that purpose.
I'm a Korean dance graduate from Sungkyunkwan University,
Choi Jong In.
I started with popping, then moved on to Korean dance.
My hope is to make a charming dance with Korean dance as the base...
and pique people's interest.
(Name: Choi Jong In, Age: 29)
Isn't it like him to write silly dance as his other genre?
He's good at dancing.
But Jong In's...
technique is...
Okay.
Why did you stop midway?
He's my friend. I'll save my breath.
I believe dance and technique are different.
He put zero stars in his technique on his profile.
I wonder how he'll take and pass the Physical and Technique Audition.
(Opening)
(He enters the room with a sun visor.)
(He draws attention just by appearing!)
(Laughing)
(It's me!)
(I'm here.)
(They give him a standing ovation as if they're in a trance.)
I didn't think Jong In would come out,
but I understood why as soon as he entered the room.
He drew attention with his look already.
He changed the atmosphere of the space at that moment.
See what will happen when you're on camera with me.
(Laughing)
I'm going to erase you.
He was something else.
The moment Suncapboi came,
I hoped he wouldn't sit next to me.
He left a strong first impression.
I was like, "Can I win..."
"against someone like him?"
(Group F: Kang Seong Bae, Kim Sang Gil, Choi Jong In)
(Choi Jong In chose Group F with Kang Seong Bae and Kim Sang Gil.)
(As soon as the judging group is revealed, he starts observing.)
Group F.
He joined Group F.
It didn't go as I wanted.
But I think I can win with my techniques.
It feels like he's a hidden master.
I don't know what he's hiding.
He's like the Joker.
I'll prove why I'm here...
with my expression and texture.
You thought Group F was easy, right?
You were wrong.
I'll show you.
I hope the other people come quickly. I'm curious.
(Two Korean dancers enter the STF Dance Company.)
(Sighing)
I'm nervous.
- Wait. - Why are you nervous? Hey.
Let's just do it.
(Who are these young Korean dancers who look close?)
(Calm, nervous)
Here it comes again.
What? 19 years old?
He's young.
I guess he's the youngest.
It says "The cute youngest boy."
He's a freshman.
He's a baby.
The age gap between us is ten years.
Jong In, let's show them the power of veterans.
Yes.
(22-year-old Jun Woo who was listening to their conversation)
Twenty-year-olds are really fit.
(What?)
I think he disrespected you.
Hey, 30-year-olds are fit too.
(It's a joke.)
(I'm smiling, but not because I'm happy.)
They went to the same high school and university.
They went to Korea National University of Arts.
They went to Gugak National High School and K-Arts. Are they...
young dark horses?
They're elite dancers. You can't underestimate their skills.
I thought I shouldn't underestimate them even though they're young.
They must've learned percussion, traditional dance,
and interpretative dance at Gugak National High School.
Because they make you learn everything.
Min Suk is a great dancer.
Do you know him?
I saw him when I lectured in Korea National University of Arts.
He's passionate and a great dancer.
People around me often say I'm passionate.
I don't like it when I feel like I wasted my day.
When I'm given an opportunity, I try to seize it.
That's why I was happy to participate in the show.
I thought if there's something I can pour my passion into,
it'd be an opportunity for me to improve.
I'm young, so there's nothing to lose.
(Staring)
(The elite young dancers will choose their judging group.)
(There are only four spots left.)
Wait.
(Even the golden boys step back as they see the line-up.)
I think we came too late.
I know. There'll be only one spot left after us.
(Only Group A, Group E, and Group F have a remaining spot.)
(Kim Min Suk chooses Group F and Kim In Su chooses Group A.)
(You put your name tag next to mine.)
(Making passionate eye contact)
I'm Kim Min Suk.
(He hurriedly holds his hand.)
I put my name tag on Group F as I thought I could win.
The remaining spot is next to Ho Jong.
I knew it.
(In the end, Group E with Choi Ho Jong has a remaining spot.)
I just want to avoid Group E, the most competitive one.
(Surprised)
- Oh, my gosh. - Choi Ho Jong in Group E.
I should avoid it.
- It's a deadly group. - It really is deadly.
If my last choice is Group E,
I would hate it so much.
Who would be the last person?
Someone strong.
He'd be the last one.
(Who is the last Korean dancer who will compete against Choi Ho Jong?)
(Judging Groups Register)
(He's here.)
(The last remaining spot catches his eye as soon as he comes.)
(There's only one spot left in Group E.)
(Oh, my)
(He rushes to the empty spot.)
(He puts his name tag without hesitation.)
(After putting his name tag on,)
(he found the name!)
(How will the last Korean dancer react, spotting Ho Jong's name tag?)
(Tilting his head)
(Look at this.)
They made it like this?
Did they do this on purpose?
(Look at this.)
It's going to be interesting.
I want Ho Jong to come.
(During the interview in June)
He might come.
There should be someone who is that good...
to motivate me to put in blood, sweat, and tears.
(Who is the last Korean dancer who wanted to compete against Ho Jong?)
Hello. I'm Ki Moo Gan,
a dancer.
(Starting talking)
(Oh, my goodness)
I watched many of his videos.
Choi Ho Jong and Ki Moo Gan are really famous.
I thought it'd be interesting.
(I'm in trouble!)
He has 18 years of experience.
It's similar to our age.
(His dance career is 2 years shorter than their age.)
Come to think of it, Moo Gan has great techniques.
Moo Gan has amazing floor techniques.
Good dancers have come.
He has long arms too.
- He has a great body. - He really does.
I think Moo Gan has some of the best bodies...
among dancers.
I feel competitive against him.
A dancer with a great body. I couldn't give up on the title.
I think I'm lucky...
to have a small waist and long limbs.
My body is definitely better than my face.
What I hear the most is I have a presence.
They say I have an outstanding presence.
It feels different when I'm on stage and when I'm not.
Because I make a difference.
(Ki Moo Gan, the last Korean dancer enters the room.)
(Park Jun Woo in Group E is smiling, but not because he's happy.)
(Kim Min Su in Group E)
(Choi Ho Jong in Group E is wearing a suggestive smile.)
It's nice to meet you.
If he competes against Ho Jong, it's going to be interesting.
(Looking around)
It's a match between Ho Jong and Moo Gan.
(Suggestive)
I thought Moo Gan would be the biggest obstacle for me.
There's only one rival for me.
That's Ho Jong.
I'm so curious about Group E.
Group E is a group of death.
(Oh, my gosh)
I'm in trouble.
(Sighing)
Should I go home?
(The saddest smile in the world)
I'm in the group.
So it's going to be intense.
(Smiling)
We're now starting the Korean Dance Physical and Technique Audition.
Guys, something big is coming.
And next, we have Group E.
(Everyone is anticipating Group E, the group of death.)
It's crazy.
I think it's going to be crazy.
(Cracking his knuckles)
(All eyes are on them.)
Choi Ho Jong.
(The audition for Dancer Choi Ho Jong has started.)
He has a crazy aura.
I got goosebumps.
(Goosebumps)
And Ki Moo Gan.
(And Dancer Ki Moo Gan)
(Glaring)
(It's insane.)
It has finally come.
Are there any outstanding dancers among them?
(Dancer Choi Ho Jong)
This person.
- He must be so good. - Right.
Everyone is afraid of Ho Jong.
Everyone knows he's an all-rounder.
- Moo Gan too. - He's good.
He's amazing.
Moo Gan is a unique dancer...
with great techniques.
This group is...
It's a fight between Ho Jong...
And Moo Gan in the end.
I'm excited.
They have unique styles.
I wonder what they will show...
and how it will turn out.
If Ho Jong and Moo Gan compete against each other,
the one who is in a better condition will win.
(It's impossible to make predictions.)
Moo Gan must be a little nervous.
(Opening his eyes)
I'm not nervous.
I'm confident I'll execute it better than anyone.
I trust myself.
(Chuckling)
Actually, I think I must...
be in a high class.
I think that's how it should be.
If I don't...
(Questioning)
That's weird.
(A big match between 2 dancers who want to be in the 1st Class)
It's going to be fun.
(Choi Ho Jong versus Ki Moo Gan)
Music...
I must watch this.
How will Ho Jong do it?
It's going to be fun.
Let's watch their performance.
Start.
Three, two, one. Go.
(Korean Dance Physical and Technique Audition, Round 1 for Group E)
The head move.
I like the head move.
- He's good. - He's different.
(They're exclaiming at Choi Ho Jong.)
- It's crazy. - His breathing technique is great.
(Super focused)
The way he's moving his hands is different.
(Turning)
(The Korean dance coaches can't take their eyes off Ho Jong.)
(Covering his mouth)
(A perfect house turn)
The house turn.
- My gosh. - He's so good.
The one-leg spin was clean.
- I like the jump. - It was nice.
- His overall balance is excellent. - Yes.
It's crazy.
- Three, two, one. - His moves are relaxed indeed.
Stop. Change.
(They change positions.)
He killed it.
Ho Jong is amazing indeed.
(Ho Jong and Moo Gan switch spots after Round 1.)
Ho Jong wasn't that good.
I should watch Moo Gan this time.
- Four, three. - Let's see what he got.
Two, one.
- Go. - I'm good.
(To be continued)
(The Korean Dance Physical and Technique Audition continues.)
(That's an acrobatic movement!)
(I don't mind competing against anyone.)
(Contemporary Dance Physical and Technique Audition)
(The Contemporary Dance Physical and Technique Audition begins.)
(I'm confident to be in the First Class.)
(I should be on the top.)
(There was no one for me to keep an eye on.)
(A fierce competition among those with amazing bodies)
(I will kill them all.)
(He's showing all the best moves he got.)
(I'm not sure if this is Stage Fighter...)
(or "Street Man Fighter.")
(It became a dance battle.)
(It's the day of the Class Battle...)
(for the Dance Film Mission in different genres.)
(The judges will move them to different classes...)
(in the Class Battle.)
(Through the Class Battle,)
(only one dancer in each group...)
(will be in the First Class.)
(1st Class: Lead dancer, 2nd Class: Supporting dancer)
(Under Class: Ensemble)
(I want to be in the First Class instead of him.)
(I'll never go down.)
(I don't want them to take it away from me. It's mine.)
(I'll keep my position...)
(in the First Class.)
(When the judging groups for ballet were revealed)
(Glancing)
(My goodness)
(Kang Gyeong Ho and Kim Yu Chan got to compete in the same group.)
(They're all strong.)
(Isn't it a group of death?)
(There was an odd tension between them.)
(I'll fight well.)
(I'll raise my guard even more.)
(During a rehearsal on the day of the Class Battle)
(He missed a beat?)
(Gyeong Ho was the only one who moved to a different beat.)
(What is it? What's going on?)
(Because there was a fixed choreography,)
(I tried harder...)
(to stand out.)
(This is the original count.)
(Yu Chan points out Gyeong Ho counted differently.)
This is what Gyeong Ho did.
(Gyeong Ho is the only one who counted one more time.)
(I'll count to 8 then.)
(It was uncomfortable. He counted differently...)
(as he wanted to stand out.)
(I thought it wasn't right.)
(Kim Yu Chan,)
(Kang Gyeong Ho, I want to see your dance again.)
(I should go crazy to win.)
(I don't start a fight that I know I'll lose.)
(He deserves to be the main dancer.)
(Sexy)
(He has a star quality.)
(I think he should go to First.)
(Who will be in the 1st Class in Group 1?)
(It's followed by the Contemporary Dance Class Battle.)
(The main dancer? I want it, of course.)
(It's the last opportunity to move up to the First Class.)
(I want to switch their classes.)
(I was mad.)
(It felt like I was robbed of what I had.)
(The Class Battle where even the slightest mistake is not tolerated)
(You've been demoted to the Under Class.)
(It was so embarrassing.)
(I don't think he's good enough to be in the First Class.)
(I clenched my teeth and did my best.)
(The First Class has changed.)
(I wanted to die.)
(He's superior.)
(I think I'll be in the First Class.)
(Thrilled)
(His eyes are crazy.)
(As for this group,)
(there will be changes in the class.)
(I will announce the dancer to be demoted.)
(It's difficult to announce it.)
(Dancer Choi Ho Jong will be demoted.)
(Shocked)
No way.
(Does it make sense? I didn't think it'd turn out like this.)
(It's because I wasn't good enough. I couldn't do it.)