(Stage Fighter)
(A Casting Audition was held...)
(for the Mega Stage main lead role.)
(I should pick dancers I can surpass.)
(In the 1st Round, dancers chose...)
(sub lead roles to make them shine.)
(Look. He didn't dance like that earlier!)
(After intense strategic battles,)
(the 3 were cast as sub lead roles.)
(Kim Hyun Ho, Ryu Tae Young, Jung Sung Wook)
(The 2nd Round for the remaining 5 was interpretative choreography.)
(I had the confidence to become the main lead role.)
(His eyes are crazy!)
(Arming themselves with various techniques and expressions)
(Cheering)
(The performances shocked everyone.)
(Getting goosebumps)
(After the intense and tight matches,)
(the 3 were cast as the Mega Stage main lead roles.)
(How did their Mega Stage turn out?)
(STF Dance Company)
- Hi. - Hi.
This spot feels empty.
- You're right. - The main lead roles are missing.
Not being cast as the main supporting role...
made me furious.
(I'm more furious than you.)
In the last mission, I realized...
the sub roles have no special parts.
I can't be satisfied with a sub lead role.
(Agreeing)
Are there more missions?
I believe everyone has a role now.
(Mega Stage Mission Double Casting Audition)
It's up.
(What is that?)
"Double Casting Audition?"
(Announced to all dancers)
- What? - What?
What does "Double Casting Audition" mean?
If any of the three main lead roles get hurt,
that dancer takes his place.
Take me as an example.
It's to prepare for any situation.
Double casting.
When the first cast suddenly can't make the performance,
a second cast is there to replace the role.
Injuries are very common.
(Casting Change Announcement)
Double casting is nothing out of the ordinary in dance companies.
(Double Casting Audition Notice)
(Qualification: All dancers aside from the main roles)
It's a double for the main lead role.
Does that mean there will be three more dancers...
along with the three main lead roles?
Yes.
Does the ensemble have double casting too?
Please.
Sub lead roles, sub supporting roles,
and ensemble, aside from the main roles.
(The ensemble is surprised.)
What? Doesn't that mean we can get the main lead role?
We've been given the chance to become the main lead role.
The Under Class can be cast as the lead role?
It's possible.
Can our status rise?
Even the Under Class can jump up status.
When one door closes, another one opens.
It's a great opportunity.
I'm fired up.
- Take this off right now. - For real?
It's an opportunity for us.
It's my chance to prove myself.
What will the fixed choreography be?
Is the fixed choreography the one from yesterday?
(This one?)
(Revealing the double casting fixed choreography)
Here it is.
Okay.
My heart is pounding.
(The choreography starts with a ballet move.)
It looks like a swan.
The moves are very contemporary.
(Adding Korean dance)
This is Korean dance.
It doesn't look that hard.
There are many arm movements.
(The arm moves are the highlight.)
(An impressive ending)
(Everyone tries the ending pose.)
It's a mix of the three genres.
It's quite contemporary.
There was one hand move.
The choreography screams contemporary ballet.
The first part is ballet.
I can express myself as a ballerino well.
Honestly, I'm confident.
The majority of the moves focused on the upper body.
I simply need to show what I'm good at.
The choreography requires basic skills.
The moves will be tough if not prepared in advance.
Everyone must be determined.
The Second Class will most likely be the most determined.
- For sure. - They're only a class difference.
(Taking off his cast)
Tae Seok?
I'm applying to it.
I can't let the sub lead roles that take as well.
We should beat the First Class.
This is an opportunity for me.
I will get a good role.
I'm pumped up.
I will give it my 100 percent. Even 200 percent.
The Under Class will go all out.
They'll take it as their last chance...
and fight to the death for it.
- I'll give it my everything. - Yes.
It's now or never to climb up the class.
It'll be amazing if any of the ensemble dancers get it.
But the mighty dancers are in the First Class.
Getting up here won't be easy.
We'll stop them.
Let's show them how much better we are.
(Yes.)
I'm burning with passion again.
I want it to start this instant.
(Meanwhile, the 3 main lead roles...)
(don't know about the situation.)
What's going on?
What are we doing? Why were we gathered here?
Maybe we'll be shown something.
(Double Casting Audition Notice)
- What? - What does that mean?
"Double casting?"
We can lose our main lead roles.
It was hard to get this role. But to give it away so easily?
I hated even the slightest possibility...
that I might lose my role.
I shouldn't feel relieved to be the main lead role.
Someone will be after my role.
No. Come at me.
As a competition in good faith,
it's a great system.
Can we be replaced?
But it's hard to imagine that someone will take my role.
I'm actually quite confident.
I must apologize for saying this,
but it wasn't threatening.
Take a shot.
Whoever competes for my role, I'll protect it.
I'm determined.
It's a war.
(Each class starts practicing.)
(First and Second Classes practice...)
(for the audition in the same room.)
The First Class is more of a nervous wreck.
Second Class and Under Class...
seemed very prepared.
The other classes got the chance...
only the First Class could normally get.
There can be a dancer who suddenly exceeds the First Class dancers.
(The First Class...)
(watches the Second Class practice.)
I analyzed the dancers.
I get they're very energetic.
But if I calmly execute the choreography,
I can beat them all.
I can't back down now.
I didn't get the main lead role for the Dance Film.
Nor did I get it for the Mega Stage.
If I can't even get the double casting,
I'll stop thinking of myself as First Class.
I needed to be cast as the double.
I'm in First Class. Let's prove it to them.
I'm most confident in Hyo Joon's role.
I'm well aware that Jong Cheol is a great dancer.
He is my competition.
It was hard to get this role. But to give it away so easily?
- It's my role. - Right?
There could be a line of dancers behind you.
If Hyeok Jung goes for my role, I'll have to keep him in check.
Hyeok Jung got the sub lead role.
He'd want to make up for it.
It's an opportunity from the deity.
I can kill 2 birds with 1 stone.
I can go after the main lead role.
It is my chance to prove myself.
To compete against me,
the ballet dancers are...
They're after your role.
I feel betrayed, thinking they're determined to take my role.
Yu Chan got the main lead role.
Someone younger made a remarkable accomplishment.
As the older one, I can't lose to him.
(The Double Casting Audition is a matter of their goal and pride.)
Can you think of...
a contemporary Under Class dancer who will ace it?
Dong Hoon.
Go Dong Hoon?
He's motivated to climb up from Under Class.
It's a generous audition if even...
the Under Class gets an opportunity. Don't you agree?
They suddenly become the lead role from Under Class.
I also had such an experience.
I was in the ensemble but was cast as a double...
and got many chances as a soloist.
The ensemble dancers must be going all out.
They'll dance like crazy.
(Under Class Practice Room 1)
(The room is filled with heavy breathing.)
(The two ensemble leaders are practicing hard.)
With the need to focus on myself,
I locked myself in my very own room.
Despite his strong characteristics,
Go Dong Hoon needed to blend in with the ensemble.
So he had killed his color.
He'll do everything to seize the opportunity.
Dong Hoon must be filled with spirit.
I let go of my colors during the group dance.
But this is a solo audition.
It's my chance to prove...
who I am.
Treating me like an Under Class...
hurt my pride.
My plan is to make up for it.
It's my chance. Let's do this.
Dong Hoon would've made more jokes and stuff.
But he was really in his zone today.
(What's going on, Leader?)
(To the worried fellow dancer,)
(Dong Hoon smiles and goes back to practice.)
Let's focus. That's the most important.
(The other dancers are as motivated as him.)
I became dead serious.
Simply because I'm in Under Class, I've been forgotten.
It's time to show myself and remind the judges of the Under Class.
I was only after the main lead role.
I'll dance like I did in the Class Battle.
I had my own strategy.
To stand out among the crowd,
I had to use my energy.
We need to bend to stand out in contemporary dance.
Our stamina came first.
It's a battle of stamina. I shouldn't go all out.
It's no use if you get hurt.
I kept warming up during the breaks.
(Park Jin Ho took great care of his condition.)
Let's pour my everything onstage.
(Under Class Practice Room 1 is filled with quiet determination.)
An Under Class dancer could even jump status with the audition.
Anyone would be desperate.
I was really desperate. But...
(Studying)
There were moves I wasn't familiar with, which worried me.
(When the choreography was revealed)
It's a mix of ballet, contemporary dance, and Korean dance.
There were moves from different genres.
To execute the moves flawlessly,
I needed a strategy. It's called a Ditto strategy.
(Scanning)
I'll just copy them.
There are ballerinos...
and Korean dancers.
There's no reason I can't ask them.
- Hey. I have a question. - Okay.
After the passe jump,
where do my feet go?
- You have to straighten your leg. - I do?
Your weight is on the back leg.
- If you have any questions... - Okay, I'll ask later.
Okay. Thank you.
Come in and contract.
Gather and spread.
(Kim Do Hyun watches the two dancers.)
Like this.
Yes, but your fingers...
- I'm sorry, but... - Yes?
- This is how I dance. - Can I ask about ballet?
- Of course. - One.
This is so contemporary. Right?
Everyone copied the moves really well.
All the dancers had the same spirit.
Let's gather useful information,
grow, and advance.
(The ensemble quickly got the choreography down.)
Kyu Tae is amazing.
I was not going to miss this chance.
Give me a tip, and I'll give you one too.
(Choi Kyu Tae learned aggressively...)
(and kept practicing during practice hours.)
I want to dance well...
and get cast in 1 of the 3 roles.
It could be my last opportunity.
That thought didn't leave my head.
I poured my everything into it.
(Who are the winners among the 55 dancers to get the 3 roles?)
(They have gathered for the Main Lead Role Double Casting Audition.)
(Matthew, Choi Soo Jin, Han Seong Woo, Jung Bo Kyung)
Today is the Double Casting Audition...
for Stage Fighter's Mega Stage Mission's three main lead roles.
As all the dancers here may already know,
double casting is necessary in any ballet and dance company.
As for double casting...
When the lead dancer gets hurt...
Or if something urgent comes up,
we always need someone prepared...
to replace that very dancer.
It's to select a dancer who has the choreography memorized...
to use whenever possible.
It's a candidate. It's backup candidate number one.
To ensure the quality...
of Stage Fighter's performance,
we will proceed with a double casting audition.
The dancers selected as the three main lead roles' doubles...
will also get the chance to replace...
the main lead role dancers.
The choreographer can decide...
whether to replace the main lead role dancer...
with the double-cast dancer.
I don't think there are any dancers...
who can replace me.
There's more.
The three dancers selected as the double casts...
can perform the main lead roles like the main lead role dancers...
in the fixed section.
The three doubles...
will also get the same benefit of selecting the main roles...
in the next mission,
just like the main lead role dancers.
If I get cast,
I will get the benefit.
I had to become a double cast.
Let me explain...
how the Double Casting Audition will proceed.
The dancers will be split into three groups...
and have two auditions in total.
The first round is a fixed choreography audition.
The dancers in one group will dance together.
The coaches will evaluate as the dancers perform...
and touch the dancers in person.
The touched dancers...
are cut out from the casting audition.
They must stop dancing and leave at once.
Is it a touch-out?
This is incredibly cruel.
Once only the dancers with the possibility of being cast are left,
the first round of auditions ends.
After the 1st round is completed by the 3 groups,
the remaining dancers...
will move on to the second round,
the Formation and Choreography Audition.
The dancers will receive...
the fixed choreography with a formation on the spot.
They will have another round of auditions with that choreography.
(Sighing)
This is nuts.
It won't be an easy audition.
Go Dong Hoon from the ensemble.
Which of the three main lead roles...
do you think you’d be best at performing?
I want to be cast as the one opposing death,
Kim Hyo Joon's role.
I believe he's more than capable.
But...
(But...)
it's too bad that I have the main lead role.
(Receiving a heavy blow)
(Relaxed)
I will not let anyone take it.
Whoever comes at me, I won't let them take it from me.
They are all fighters.
Sub supporting role, Kim Si Won.
Is there a role out of...
the three main lead roles you think belongs to you?
I want to be double-cast...
for Kim Yu Chan's role.
(Thinking)
I'm guessing...
the dancers don't know who I am.
(His words stir up the room.)
I'm always up for the challenge.
He's scary.
Everyone is qualified to take this role.
But because you didn't prove yourselves well,
you're in your positions.
(That hurts.)
He's tough.
That really hurt.
I'm always prepared to battle.
No opponent scares me.
Is no one keeping Choi Ho Jong...
in check?
(Raising his hand)
(Who is it?)
(Second Class Korean Dancer Kim Sang Gil)
Please elaborate.
When it comes to the one consoling death,
no one other than me...
can replace Choi Ho Jong.
If you become my double cast,
I hope you learn and grow...
from how I play the role flawlessly.
- Goodness. - That's scary.
(The First Class dignity can be felt from his words.)
It's pumping me up.
Taking my role?
It's close to impossible.
It's a long shot.
All right. We will now begin...
the Double Casting Audition.
(Let's battle it out.)
Okay.
The dancers in Group 1 will start 1st.
(Double Casting Audition Grouping, Group 1 OAP)
Where you stand...
has been decided according to your class.
(Group 1 dancers are warming up before the audition.)
This is a tough group.
It's already intense.
I can tell who'll survive.
Ki Moo Gan.
He looks extremely determined.
In the Casting Audition, I made a huge mistake.
(Ki Moo Gan made a mistake in the additional audition and failed.)
I have to do my best this time. I'll excel in it.
I need to stay wide awake.
The Under Class might stand out if they do well.
Right.
They never had the chance to prove themselves.
Won't the judges focus on them more?
I thought it was my chance.
Even in the Technique Audition...
and the Class Mission...
(Kim In Su didn't do well enough and became Under Class.)
I could have done better in every mission.
I've always been a part of the ensemble,
so I wasn't able to express my unique style.
Naturally, I wanted to do well in the Double Casting Audition.
There were many parts that I could pull off...
in terms of Korean dance.
I was confident.
(Following)
(Kim In Su, 19 years old, confident and curious)
(The 19-year-old dancer has a lot to ask the older dancers.)
I'm the youngest, after all,
so I practiced right next to them.
(Breaktime for the Under Class)
But if they're casting three dancers...
(Worried)
You just need to work hard.
I won't leave any regrets.
I wanted to prove myself as the youngest...
and the Under Class of Korean dance.
(Ready to prove himself)
(Jae Jin is lost in his practice next to the confident youngest.)
I do regret things...
about the evaluation of the Dance Film.
(Jae Jin was demoted to Under Class for his attitude.)
Jae Jin was the only one wearing a cap.
That means that he's not willing to concentrate.
I wasn't humble enough to participate in a competition,
so I figured that was the reason I got bad results.
(He endlessly repeated the same move...)
(and even practiced during breaktime.)
Jae Jin was practicing so hard while sweating.
Enthusiastic Jae Jin.
Passionate Jae Jin.
When wasn't I passionate?
I've always worked hard.
Right.
It's a chance to play the main role.
I'll do my best in this mission.
Mega Stage Mission, Wihonmu.
The Double Casting Audition for the three main lead roles.
The moment you stop dancing,
you're eliminated from the Double Casting Audition.
(You're eliminated once you stop dancing.)
I was determined to show them.
I'll risk my life for the main lead role.
Stage Fighter,
the Mega Stage Mission Double Casting Audition begins now.
First position.
Music, start.
(Let's check out the audition of the determined dancers.)
Three, two, one. Go.
I had repeated it countless times, so I knew I could pull it off.
(Watching intently)
Tae Seok isn't dancing so hard, right?
His feet hurt.
I only see Hyeok Jung.
I'll have to show them what differentiates me.
Hyeok Jung...
- He's dancing in the original way. - Right.
Hyeok Jung is insanely good.
(Coach Choi Soo Jin gets closer for an accurate evaluation.)
I was aiming for the chance to be promoted.
(Looking closely)
He's got a gentle style, so...
It's not bad,
but I doubt it's the vibe that Soo Jin wants.
(The Double Casting Audition continues without a break.)
(Getting himself ready)
(Slipping)
(Spotting his mistake)
I Ban isn't so stable when he lands.
I want to do it energetically so that I won't regret it.
In Su!
How is In Su so good?
(Interested)
Come on, Tae Hu.
Tae Hu is still like a baby.
Yes, he's like a baby.
(Matthew and Soo Jin move...)
(to observe the details.)
I was going to stay wide awake and go all out.
I was thinking, "Please look at me."
Jae Jin has beautiful lines.
Nice, long limbs. He has nice proportions.
The one way in the back...
Jeong Bin?
I was so desperate.
- He's... - I'm surprised.
I told myself, "I can do this."
- They're so desperate. - It seems arduous.
Aren't their moves all so desperate?
I can feel their emotions.
Five,
- four, three, - This was my last chance,
- two, - and I was going to give it my all.
one. Go.
(The two coaches move to decide who to eliminate.)
Matthew looks so scary.
Too weak.
(Kim Min Suk in Under is out.)
(Jeon Tae Hu in Under is out.)
(Moon Jun On in Under is out.)
(Kim Hyun Ho in First is out.)
(Everyone is shocked.)
- What? - Hyun Ho!
I guess I saw it coming.
(After Hyun Ho in First is eliminated,)
(Moo Gan in Second is also eliminated.)
Oh, no.
(Ki Moo Gan in Second is out.)
What's happening?
I'm so ashamed to be dancing in front of 60 people.
(Kim Tae Seok in Second is out.)
- Ten, nine, - It hurt my pride.
- eight... - They're eliminated?
(The eliminated dancers swarm in due to cold-hearted evaluations.)
Five,
- four, three, two... - It was no joke.
I looked back, and there were only a few left.
I thought, "Let's keep going. You've got this."
- Four, three, - I was dying out there.
- two, one. Go. - But I still wanted to pull it off.
- Go. - Let's go, In Su!
(The last screening of Group 1)
Okay!
They shouted and cheered for me.
That motivated me.
In Su is good.
Let's go!
I need to win this part like my life depends on it.
- He's good, right? - It's so hard.
I didn't want to be eliminated.
Jae Jin!
- Why does this make me so sad? - I know, right?
(Everyone sighs.)
I don't like the one in the back.
(Han Jeong Bin in Under is out.)
Close enough.
(The Main Lead Role Double Casting Audition for Group 1 ends.)
In Su survived!
Jae Jin made it.
Jae Jin was amazing.
In Su's desperation...
I know, right?
(In Su is proud.)
- Hyeok Jung is certainly good. - Absolutely.
I got one more chance.
I'll win the main lead role.
I think I have a shot.
(The candidates are Jae Jin, Hyeok Jung, and In Su.)
Group Two, please begin.
(Jung Sung Wook, Ryu Tae Young, Kim Si Won, Kang Yun Gu,)
(Go Dong Hoon, Ha Won Jun, Park Jin Ho, Kim Tae Gang,)
(Choi Ji Won, Kang Seong Bae, Lee Young Woo, Han Sang Ik...)
This is so nerve-racking.
They all practiced so hard.
I think Jin Ho will advance.
Jin Ho is the standard of a neat style.
I wonder what will happen to Dong Hoon.
I hope he gets picked.
I personally want him to advance.
Don't you think Si Won has a chance?
He did so well during practice too.
Seven, eight.
(First and Second practiced together in the same room.)
When I lost the main supporting role last time,
I was very disappointed.
(Si Won lost to Hye Seong in the Main Supporting Role Audition.)
(You have not been cast.)
I realized that I was in trouble.
I was aiming to be in the First Class,
and if the competition kept getting fiercer like this,
it would be more difficult for me.
I didn't want to miss this opportunity.
(Si Won watches the First dancers practicing.)
(Looking closely)
He certainly uses his body well. Was it Hyeok Jung?
The muscular one in the middle.
Watching Sung Wook in First, who's a great ballerino,
and Hyeok Jung, who has great fundamentals,
I decided to copy their styles.
Hyeok Jung, do you swing your arm after this?
- I... - It's so pretty.
I think I kick like this.
(Learning Hyeok Jung's kick)
When you do a jump like that,
it's like a passe in the air.
You know, like this.
- Like this? - That's what I'm picturing.
And I wanted to express it to suit my character.
It's like I'm trying to intimidate people with my eyes.
(Lost in practice)
- Si Won... - It's like he has a competition.
(Si Won is practicing as if he has a competition soon.)
My tummy always hurts on the day of the competition.
- Does this feel like a competition? - It does.
(This guy is as nervous as on the day of a dance contest.)
It's like a jinx of mine.
I knew that it'd be my last opportunity.
I wanted to give my all...
and pull it off in my own style.
The beast in me came out.
I'm no longer a princess.
I'm going to make it energetic, no matter what.
We'll be doing the same dance moves, right?
I had to go hard...
to stand out among them.
(The wind sound is a given.)
Okay.
(Jin Ho's loud practice continues with the noises of victory.)
Five, six, seven, eight.
That's cool.
Why is Dong Hoon working so hard?
He must want to advance.
(Dong Hoon concentrates on practicing in the corner.)
I thought I needed to focus on myself today,
so I formed an invisible room for myself.
My primary goal is to be promoted from Under.
(In the Class Battle for contemporary dancers,)
(he got the Under Class.)
(In the 1st Class Movement Ceremony,)
(he got the Under Class once again.)
I got the Under Class twice after getting the First Class.
And kick!
And I was acknowledged for my leadership,
rather than my dancing skills.
This is an opportunity.
So, if I can be respected and acknowledged,
that's what matters to me the most.
I wanted to add...
some of my interpretation of the moves.
Death is urgent, and I'm desperate,
so I wanted to add that vibe.
What I'm good at and what I like.
I think it's fair that I show them that so that I won't regret it.
The audition will continue only until we have...
the dancers who are likely to be cast.
First position.
Music, start.
- This part is so nerve-racking. - Two, one.
- I hope Jin Ho gets it. - Music, start.
- Jin Ho. - Five,
- I'm going to watch Min Chan. - four,
- three, two, one. - Good luck, Young Woo.
Go.
(The Main Lead Role Double Casting Audition for Group 2 begins.)
(Observing him carefully)
I thought it'd be better to show them my style...
from the front row.
(Smiling)
Si Won stands out too.
Sung Wook does the port de bras in the ballet style...
without changing the moves too much.
- Sung Wook's moves are neat. - That's why he stands out.
(Catching everyone's attention)
Min Kwon...
Min Kwon made too many mistakes.
Oh, no.
(It seems like Min Kwon didn't practice the moves enough.)
(An intense ending)
- Five, four, - Si Won is pretty good.
- Yes. - three, two, one.
(Getting himself ready)
Go.
The one in the gray sleeveless shirt.
The one behind Si Won.
(Matthew spots him.)
I meant to give it my all so that I could dominate everyone.
(His eyes change.)
(Jin Ho's movements certainly stand out.)
Jin Ho is different, indeed.
I shot laser beams with my eyes, going, "Please pick me."
"I'm desperate."
(They made eye contact.)
The thing about dance is...
Well, in this situation,
you can feel their passion from their eyes.
Five, four,
three, two, one. Go.
(He goes twice as hard.)
(Coach Han moves to the right.)
(Noticing him)
There's no contraction in the upper body for Yun Gu.
It's too weak.
The coaches came and looked straight at me.
I wanted to dominate them and crush them.
Like, "This is my dance, so pay attention to me."
(Focusing)
I love his expressions.
Ten, nine,
- Dong Hoon might die. - eight...
- Dong Hoon. - Ten, nine,
- He certainly added his style. - eight, seven,
six,
- five, four, - I decided to trust myself...
- and not be intimidated. - three, two, one.
(Thinking)
- What do I do? It's so scary. - Two, one. Go.
(The coaches and the rehearsal director...)
(move to eliminate the dancers.)
(I'm so scared!)
I was terrified.
(Looking closely)
(Kang Seong Bae in Under is out.)
(An Si On and Kim Tae Yeon in Under are out.)
- Tae Gang? - Sang Ik, no!
(The dancers in Under are eliminated 1 by 1.)
Dong Hoon!
As they were tagged out,
I found the confidence and thought that I might make it.
(The remaining dancers give their all.)
(And Coach Jung Bo Kyung observes the dancers.)
(Glancing)
I was almost done with the moves, so I thought she'd walk away.
(The final tap)
(Go Dong Hoon in Under is out.)
- Even Dong Hoon? - Ten,
- Oh, Dong Hoon. - nine, eight, seven,
- six, five, - Good work.
- four, three, - It's tough.
two, one.
I guess I failed again.
(The final 3 dancers in Group 2 to advance to Round 2.)
Si Won did great.
I was one step closer.
How come Sung Wook is so pretty?
I was representing the ballet dancers,
so I was exhilarated.
We have a ballerino left!
Nice, Jin Ho.
He survived.
Although I was in my element, I wasn't going to let my guard down.
Kim Si Won.
Park Jin Ho.
(Watching the dancers advance to Round 2...)
Jung Sung Wook. These three members have survived.
Congratulations.
I thought, "Why? Why can't I be picked?"
Well done, Sung Wook!
- Jin Ho did great. - Good job.
Good work.
I failed again. This is making me mad.
Judging by the outcome, I've always been at the bottom.
That gets me worried,
and it also makes me worry...
that I might beat myself up too much because of this.
I just...
(Dong Hoon can't speak for a while.)
(He feels powerless...)
(as he's more desperate than anyone else.)
I'm sorry.
(During the Class Battle)
(Dong Hoon got the Under Class.)
(He performed with resilience...)
(and gave his best in his class more than anyone else.)
Let's go, guys!
(He strived for a better performance...)
(and looked after others before himself.)
I've been dancing until now because I loved it so much.
I couldn't give up as I couldn't forget about performing.
But it doesn't feel...
like my hard work and efforts are acknowledged.
I guess I was too eager today.
My passion and enthusiasm...
have not been satiated, so it was a shock.
It was a bummer, indeed.
I like to think...
that I'm being crumpled harder...
to be a paper ball that flies farther.
Group Three, please begin.
(Double Casting Audition)
Look at him using his facial expressions.
I love his image and all.
He's spiteful.
- What? - I like Kyu Tae's eyes.
He's very determined.
I think neat moves stand out better.
(Kwon Yo Han, the contemporary dancer, dances neatly.)
Kim Jong Cheol, Choi Kyu Tae, and Kwon Yo Han.
These three dancers have survived. Congratulations.
(Kim Jong Cheol, Yun Hyeok Jung, Jung Sung Wook, Kim Si Won,)
(Kwon Yo Han, Kim In Su, Kim Jae Jin, Park Jin Ho, Choi Kyu Tae)
In the second round, Formation and Choreography Audition,
we will reevaluate you with choreography...
that includes formations for the first audition's routine...
to assess not just basic choreography skills...
but also stage presence and expressiveness.
You will be given only 30 minutes...
to pull off this choreography and formation in your style.
(The choreographer demonstrates the formations.)
This should be easy.
And then...
Six, seven, eight.
But you need to beware...
It wasn't that difficult.
I was confident.
I was still First, though I didn't get the main lead role,
so I wanted to prove myself.
Shall we try again?
Do I look straight ahead in this part?
That's the original choreography.
Do I need to look up when I swing my arms?
I was eager to win.
Being in the Under Class doesn't exactly mean that you're Under.
I finally had this opportunity, so I wasn't going to lose it.
Okay.
- I need to bet my life on it. - What?
I'm betting my life.
I'm going to pour my everything into it...
and survive.
(Kyu Tae in Under is practicing, and...)
- And your hand... - I got a cramp.
My left leg.
(They apply emergency measures.)
I got a serious cramp during practice,
so I was worried.
I'll go back to practice when I'm good to go.
I need to memorize the choreography.
(He goes back to practice...)
(as he only has 30 minutes.)
Shoot.
(Kyu Tae falls due to severe pain.)
(He's back out for treatment.)
Gosh.
Then, come right up.
(He's upset that his body can't keep up with his enthusiasm...)
(and that he won't get this kind of opportunity again.)
I finally got the chance to show them my dance,
but I kept getting cramps during practice.
It was so hard to get this opportunity.
I was disappointed and angry.
Even if I have to roll out of the stage due to the cramp,
I'll give it a go.
I'd be too frustrated to walk away.
I'll go.
(Can he finish the audition safely?)
For the Main Lead Role Double Casting,
the second round, Formation and Choreography Audition,
will begin now.
I want to maintain the dignity of the First Class.
I'm going to prove them wrong as the Under Class.
I'm sure I'll win.
First position.
Music, start.
(Choi Kyu Tae, ensemble, Yun Hyeok Jung, sub lead role,)
(and Kim Si Won, sub supporting role)
Go.
(They put everything into their movements to get cast.)
Gosh.
It's too bad that he has a calf injury.
Hyeok Jung makes me go, "That's how a dancer should be."
(Very satisfied)
(Charging forward)
- All right. - The middle one is good.
(They end the choreography with their respective ending poses.)
Ten, nine...
- They're good. - Hyeok Jung is unrivaled.
He's a beast.
(The next group's choreography follows right away.)
(Kim Jae Jin, ensemble, Kim Jong Cheol, sub lead role,)
(Park Jin Ho, ensemble)
Go.
Jong Cheol is good.
Jin Ho isn't bad either.
(They show their characters with their gaits.)
- Okay. - The look in his eyes is insane.
He's doing a great job with the expression.
(Walking forward)
Nice.
(The 3 dancers' ending poses are unique.)
- All right. - Jong Cheol did well.
Jin Ho definitely stands out.
The revolt of the Under Class.
(The last group's audition follows.)
(Kwon Yo Han, ensemble, Jung Sung Wook, sub lead role,)
(Kim In Su, ensemble)
Go.
(Explosive energy)
All right.
Nice.
Yo Han's moves have weight.
Sung Wook is really good.
(2nd Round of the Formation and Choreography Audition ends.)
(You can breathe now.)
(Breathing)
(Dazed)
This is so much fun.
They're so cool. I need to be cool too.
You did well. I watched you from the back.
My balance wavered because I got too excited.
No, you did well. You did really well.
- Was my performance a bit weak? - I'm having the same thought.
Everyone's performance was intense.
I'm really disappointed.
I couldn't show what I prepared since I was worried about the cramp.
I was very disappointed.
(Sighing)
(The coaches begin a meeting.)
The ones who can't control their bodies...
- Jae Jin couldn't do the moves. - No.
Kyu Tae looked uncomfortable too.
(Kyu Tae couldn't show his skills due to a calf injury.)
In Su was too out of sync.
I don't know whom to choose among these four.
(They narrow it down to 4 candidates.)
They have similar energy.
Can we watch the four dancers once more?
Korean dance, Kim Jong Cheol.
(Korean dance, Kim Jong Cheol)
Contemporary dance, Kwon Yo Han.
Contemporary dance, Yun Hyeok Jung.
Korean dance, Kim Si Won.
We'll choose among these dancers.
- I think they'll drop one dancer. - Yes.
I think everyone else got eliminated.
I guess I didn't get the role.
I had no regrets about my performance.
Even if I don't get the role, it can't be helped.
(It can't be helped.)
First position.
Music, start.
- Five, four, - The end is near.
- three, two, - It's do or die.
one. Go.
That's insane.
Their energy is incredible.
My goodness.
All right.
Both of them are insane.
- My goodness. - Good.
(Powerful ending)
My goodness.
I could feel their energy from here.
(Rematch Group 2, Kwon Yo Han and Kim Jong Cheol)
I must move up.
I'll get cast no matter what.
Go.
All right.
It was neat.
(Relaxed)
(Full of unique charms)
(The ending was insane.)
(They have my approval.)
I made up my mind.
- This one. - The decision will be made.
Right?
We will now announce the result...
of Stage Fighter's...
Mega Stage Mission Double Casting Audition.
Firstly, we'll announce the dancer who became the double...
of Kim Hyo Joon, the dancer who was cast...
as the main lead role of the one opposing death.
(He pulled off various genres perfectly.)
(Kim Hyo Joon, main lead role, the one opposing death)
I'm the most confident about Hyo Joon's role.
The role I want is the one opposing death.
The dancer who became the double...
of Kim Hyo Joon, the dancer who was cast...
as the main lead role of the one opposing death, is...
Kim Jong Cheol.
Jong Cheol. I knew it.
- They have similar vibes. - Yes.
Kim Jong Cheol,
you showed the characteristics of Korean dance,
such as the beauty of the curves and the flow of the body...
through your dance.
You delivered impactful energy...
with your dance.
That was why you caught our eye.
With the dancer...
who got cast for the same role,
I'll work hard and give a good result.
(The one opposing death: Kim Hyo Joon, Kim Jong Cheol)
We'll announce the dancer who became the double...
of Kim Yu Chan, the dancer who was cast...
as the second main lead role of the one fearing death.
(Kim Yu Chan used elements of his specialty, ballet,)
(and pulled off the choreography perfectly.)
(He got cast as the main lead role, the one fearing death.)
I really wanted the role of the one fearing death.
I want to try that role.
The dancer who became the double of Kim Yu Chan,
the dancer who was cast as a main lead role, is...
(Who will it be?)
Yun Hyeok Jung.
Congratulations.
- Yun Hyeok Jung. - I knew it.
The fearful role suits you, Hyeok Jung.
Yun Hyeok Jung.
The explosive energy that comes out...
of your body...
stands out.
You can dance very powerfully.
You made good use of that...
when you did the dance moves.
I'm very thankful...
for this opportunity. I'll work hard.
(The one fearing death: Kim Yu Chan, Yun Hyeok Jung)
All the doubles are from the First Class.
(Both doubles are from the First Class.)
The chance of an ensemble getting cast is slim.
The remaining number of main lead roles...
that need a double...
is one.
It's the double of Choi Ho Jong,
the dancer who was cast as the main lead role...
of the one consoling death.
(He showed both hardness and softness.)
(Choi Ho Jong, main lead role, the one consoling death)
(I think you're a dancer...)
(a choreographer definitely needs.)
The dancer who became the double...
of Choi Ho Jong is...
- Who will it be? - Sung Wook?
I think it'll be Si Won.
The double of Choi Ho Jong is...
Park Jin Ho.
- Park Jin Ho. - There you go.
Congratulations.
(The double for the one consoling death, Park Jin Ho)
- Park Jin Ho. - There you go.
Congratulations.
(Dancers of the Under Class are happy for him.)
He moved up from the Under Class.
- My goodness. - He worked hard.
I thought he was nice.
I also thought that Jin Ho was very nice.
His techniques were nice.
His expressions were intense too.
He expressed himself beautifully.
(They voted for Park Jin Ho unanimously.)
Park Jin Ho,
you're crying.
I saw you wipe your tears.
(Happiness brings tears.)
Anyone would cry in that situation.
From Under Class...
Well...
Throughout the past missions,
I was ashamed of myself.
I felt like I had failed to show my true essence.
(From the start, people had high expectations for Park Jin Ho.)
(But Physical and Technique Audition put him in Second Class.)
Just now, Park Jin Ho...
(Despite his efforts,)
(he failed to get promoted in the Class Battle.)
(After the Dance Film,)
(he got demoted to the Under Class.)
I kept failing to meet my goal.
"Why can't I receive recognition?"
"What problems do I have to keep failing?"
Since I was desperate,
emotions boiled in my heart.
I was desperate for this mission.
I thought it was the last chance.
I performed as if my life depended on it.
I'll try hard to continue showing this side of me...
and work well with Choi Ho Jong.
Thank you.
(You're cool, Park Jin Ho.)
(The one consoling death: Choi Ho Jong, Park Jin Ho)
The three doubles...
must perfectly learn the main lead roles' choreographies.
For the quality of the performance, the cast could change...
even right before taking the stage.
For the Solo Choreography of the main lead role,
the main lead dancer and the double will be compared.
If the double performs the choreography better,
the cast for the section could change anytime.
Thank you for your hard work.
(The Double Casting Audition for the main lead role ends.)
You'll go one at a time after warming up.
Ho Jong is unbelievable.
It's something only he can do.
What should I do? It's already hard.
How am I supposed to do that?
(He needs to learn the choreography.)
I was quite pressured about getting cast as Ho Jong's double.
He'll do an incredible job of creating his Solo Choreography.
Still, I'll do my best.
(Walking over)
(He copies all the moves.)
I wasn't mindful of Jin Ho.
I was more focused on creating...
a good choreography.
(My goodness)
I can't help but resent Ho Jong.
Ho Jong made many changes.
In the past practice, the middle part changed.
Then the first and last parts changed.
It confused me a lot.
Still, I made a lot of effort to become his double.
I know that I'll regret it...
if I fail to shine.
That's why I'm desperate.
(Park Jin Ho didn't stop practicing until everyone left.)
To be honest, we practiced in a separate studio.
Let's begin.
(The 3 doubles practiced during their free time.)
I don't think I've ever done that during my time as a dancer.
I realized that all three of us were desperate.
(What will become of the 3 desperate doubles?)
(The day of the rehearsal)
Let's begin the rehearsal for the main lead role's solo part.
If the double does a better job...
of the main lead role's Solo Choreography,
the cast can change for the quality of the performance.
If the main lead dancer makes a mistake...
- The double will get the role. - The double will get the role.
Gosh, that's so cruel.
(It's time for Kim Yu Chan to rehearse his solo part.)
(Focused)
I won't let him take my role.
I will prove that this is my role.
(Kim Yu Chan's rehearsal begins.)
(Absorbed)
(Focused)
(Kim Yu Chan dances powerfully as if it's the actual performance.)
(Impressed)
(Wary)
(The flowing movements of ballet stand out in this choreography.)
(A difficult technique)
(His eyes go wide.)
(Kim Yu Chan's rehearsal ends.)
That was incredible.
How can a male dancer's leg touch the head?
He did the arabesque at once.
I was a bit anxious. But I still thought,
"I can do well with turns, the technique I'm confident about."
(Yun Hyeok Jung's rehearsal begins.)
(He pulls off the choreography in his own style.)
(Impressed)
(Wary)
(He pulls off the turn in a cool way.)
(A killer technique)
(Impressed)
(Yun Hyeok Jung's rehearsal ends.)
Good.
(A round of applause)
He changed it to his own style. He changed it well.
Although Yu Chan is on another level,
I can't remember his performance after Hyeok Jung's.
Kim Yu Chan,
you improved the quality greatly in terms of technique.
"How did he do it so easily?"
It takes skills to make people think that.
However, your expressions were...
a bit lacking.
Yun Hyeok Jung had the expression.
The biggest difference in the two performances was...
the part where you showed a kick from the attitude position.
Hyeok Jung changed it to a side kick...
to deliver the energy in a sharp way.
It gave a new vibe to the choreography.
(Yun Hyeok Jung and Kim Yu Chan received opposing reviews.)
Thank you for your hard work.
Choi Ho Jong's rehearsal will come next.
Please go back to where you came from, the Under Class.
(Choi Ho Jong's rehearsal begins.)
(Beautiful)
(That's it!)
It's smooth and pretty.
(Turning)
(What's that?)
(Choi Ho Jong showed his unique moves until the end.)
Choi Ho Jong did what he could do best.
It was so clean.
(It's time for Park Jin Ho's rehearsal.)
Will he show us?
I'll grit my teeth so that I can beat him.
I'm confident.
(Park Jin Ho's rehearsal begins.)
(Winking)
(Park Jin Ho copies the difficult moves with ease.)
(He wraps up with his own ending pose.)
(Park Jin Ho's rehearsal ends.)
Beautiful. Great job.
It was cool.
Jin Ho might've made the entire thing shine more.
Jin Ho, you showed the one consoling death...
that was different from Ho Jong's.
At the very end, you went down on the floor...
and created new moves. I was thankful for them.
Choi Ho Jong, I think...
you can execute the solo part nearly perfectly.
However,
the one who seemed to control the ensemble was Park Jin Ho.
When he motioned to the back, the spirits moved.
In that aspect,
Park Jin Ho is a dancer who deserves the main lead role.
Maybe I shouldn't have choreographed the dance that way.
Fear washed over me.
Kim Hyo Joon's rehearsal will come first.
I have no intention to give him my role.
I'll dance with gritted teeth.
(Let's see.)
(Kim Hyo Joon's rehearsal begins.)
(Charging forward)
(Impressed)
His facial expression is alive.
(Charismatic and intense eyes...)
(and memorable technique)
(Kim Hyo Joon's specialty, knee spin)
(Covering his mouth)
(Even the ending was intense.)
(It was so nice.)
- He did the best today. - Yes.
He did well.
His facial expression was no joke.
He's determined to win.
Okay. I'll show him what I can do.
(Kim Jong Cheol's rehearsal begins.)
(He fights charisma with softness.)
(Impressed)
(He's equally good.)
(A silent cry)
(Surprised)
(What's up with that pose?)
(Kim Jong Cheol's rehearsal ends.)
(The choreographer is satisfied.)
(He's good.)
Both of them did well.
Jong Cheol did better than he did during practice.
I'm a bit worried.
Hyo Joon showed...
powerful moves...
as well as a playful smile.
He showed various aspects...
of the one opposing death.
As for Kim Jong Cheol,
he showed a soft opposition. It was fun to watch.
How did the two dancers interpret the character...
in completely opposite ways? It was neck-and-neck.
I don't know which dancer to choose.
Which character will the choreographer want to use?
I'm a bit worried.
I'll move up and take the main lead role.
I think I did better than Yu Chan today.
I don't think my role will be taken away.
I'll beat everyone today.
The cast won't change.
(What will become of the 6 dancers after the fierce rehearsals?)
(The day of the Mega Stage Mission)
(The day of the Mega Stage Mission shoot)
(The dancers enter to prepare for the performance.)
(What?)
What?
Are you serious?
(The dancers look in one direction and become shocked.)
What?
(Staring intently)
(What shocked the dancers?)
- Let's go. - What?
(Grinning)
(The contemporary dancers become startled as well.)
(My goodness)
(Why is everyone congratulating Yun Hyeok Jung?)
I mean...
(The one fearing death: Kim Yu Chan to Yun Hyeok Jung)
When I think about the solo part,
I want the interpretation of fear...
to involve powerful energy. I want the dancer...
to deliver that energy and show the body...
that's full of fear.
But Yu Chan's energy is quite shy.
His moves were less expansive.
I thought Hyeok Jung's interpretation of the character...
and expressions were much closer to what I originally wanted.
It was difficult to decide,
but we should give him the solo part instead.
(Changed from Kim Yu Chan to Yun Hyeok Jung)
Congratulations.
- Thank you. - I wish you luck.
I thought that I should pay them back for their trust in me.
(There's another person who has to accept what's happened.)
- Goodness. - What?
Already in the morning?
(He tries to hide his feelings.)
I didn't expect to be noticed like this.
(Kim Yu Chan heads to the waiting room.)
(Startled)
(Everyone is walking on eggshells.)
(His hands become polite automatically.)
(Anxious)
Are you happy?
(He just laughs.)
(My goodness)
Good luck.
(Feeling embarrassed, they can only laugh.)
The decision has been made.
I decided to show what I've got...
for the remaining role.
(Where people are busy, getting ready for the shoot)
(Mega Stage film set)
(Welcome to the makeup zone.)
- It's sparkling. - This is nice.
- This is MAC. - It's MAC, indeed.
- Do I look good today? - You do.
You look amazing.
You look really handsome.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
Do you have any ideas?
As the performance is about death,
something more majestic...
There should be a different emphasis between...
the main roles and the sub roles and ensemble.
Emphasis is important.
With the pearl skin look, I'll make the skin elegant.
It's a concealer.
I'll highlight these parts.
- My look is changing. - Isn't it completely different?
A concealer that lasts for a long time is very important.
I'm applying glitters and gold underneath the eyes...
to make you look stronger.
You look like an idol singer.
You look more beautiful today.
The makeup turned him into someone else.
Seriously.
Do I look handsome?
- I look so beautiful today. - I agree.
Is this the power of MAC?
(Maximizing their beauty with makeup)
I will do my best.
I will work hard.
Music, start.
(The Mega Stage shoot is in full swing now.)
It looks amazing.
(Watching the monitor is a must.)
It will turn out well.
It looks like they set the angle beforehand.
Yes, that's how it is.
This scene turned out really well.
(The Mega Stage performance is getting completed.)
Six, seven, and eight.
Good work, everyone.
(The Mega Stage shoot ended successfully.)
(The Mega Stage is finally revealed.)
(The biggest scale that will hold you in awe)
(Exclaiming)
(The Mega Stage performance...)
(will decide the best dancer.)
(Is the benefit getting the main lead role?)
(I should become the best dancer at least once.)
(And the next mission)
(What's the K-Contents Mission that surprised everyone?)
Hello.
- Good morning. - Hello.
(The dancers come to work at STF Dance Company.)
(In harmony)
(Hello)
It looks like your hair got longer.
What do you think that we'll do today?
Won't it be an easy day today?
Right?
It's just the start.
I will work hard again today.
(Smiling)
Do I look good?
(The ballet prince always checks his looks.)
(Holding back his laughter)
(All the dancers arrive peacefully again today.)
(Mega Stage Mission)
Is the video ready?
We'll get to watch it.
My heart is fluttering so much.
Do you think that you'll get the benefit?
- Me? - Yes.
I'd love to. I should.
(His honest feeling)
I did my best during the Double Casting Audition,
so I'm hoping for a positive result.
I look forward to watching the fairies.
The Peter Pans?
Yes.
Unless there's a huge change,
I have a chance of becoming the best dancer.
I showed many of my weapons,
so I have high hopes.
Why do I feel so nervous?
"Who will be the best dancer from the Double Casting Audition?"
I kept thinking about that.
I got my solo part taken away.
I had hopes, but I felt nervous at the same time.
(It's starting.)
(Mega Stage starts with 3 main lead roles.)
(Everyone cheers.)
(What will the Mega Stage look like?)
(Feeling shy)
(Different versions of Mega Stage will be revealed on Mnet Plus.)
- His role looks amazing. - What's this?
Ho Jong's aura is too good to be true.
He's good with hand movements.
The look on Hyo Joon's face.
Their shadows look intense.
(Anticipating)
The shadows look unbelievable.
(Mega Stage opens.)
(The biggest scale ever)
This is crazy.
Let's go.
(Gulping)
(I'm Yun Hyeok Jung, the main lead role.)
Unbelievable.
That's how they changed it.
The camera is on Hyeok Jung too much.
(Nervous)
They filmed it so well.
It's giving me goosebumps.
Hyeok Jung looks amazing in this scene.
The best film of his life.
The quality is clearly different.
(He's being moved.)
- It's very majestic. - It looks amazing.
The ensemble appears often.
He's flexible.
They're so nicely in sync.
Here it comes.
Isn't this the highlight?
Hyo Joon's dancing is charming.
- The legendary facial expression. - Here it comes.
You can see it.
(This is crazy.)
Goodness.
(Ho Jong the Great)
Hey!
Ho Jong the Great.
The look on his face is very nice.
His movements are sharp.
The music makes it better.
He looks like a deity in a myth.
His moves are so smooth.
(His moves are so smooth.)
(Make some noise!)
Ho Jong did his thing.
(The main supporting role's part that everyone's been waiting for)
You can see all of them.
It's him.
- The fairies. - They look pretty.
- Side kick. - How are they so flexible?
(Pretty fairies)
(Side kick)
- It's impossible to find us. - Where are we?
The long hair stands out.
- Seong Yun looks amazing. - Right.
(Posing)
Did you see me teleporting?
(Coyness of long hair)
(Double-cast dancers and the main lead roles coincide.)
This scene looks amazing.
It looks incredible.
I love this part.
(Cheering vehemently)
(Their chemistry is amazing.)
The double cast looks like the main role.
Amazing!
There's the contemporary dance ensemble.
Kim Jong Cheol.
Jong Cheol is good.
(Smiling with satisfaction)
Goodness.
Here comes the princess.
(The princess is concentrating.)
(Karina appears with spectacular turns.)
- It's Karina! - All right.
What's that?
He looks sturdy.
(Fierce Hye Seong)
(Pure and innocent Hye Seong)
The Aoya.
Hye Hyun is doing his own dance.
- It looks amazing. - They're good.
Hye Seong's eyes might explode.
(Fancy)
- Cool. - Hye Seong's eyes might explode.
- Here it is. - It looks amazing from above.
I love it.
It looks magnificent.
From above, it looks different from what we saw.
It's nice.
The lighting on the floor is amazing too.
Ho Jong's face is incredible.
He looks too good to be true.
Goodness.
- This is amazing. - Seriously.
(People can't stop complimenting the best Mega Stage.)
It looks great.
- No! - Gosh.
Goodness.
- Gosh. - What's that?
(Different versions of Mega Stage will be revealed on Mnet Plus.)
- What? - Goodness.
(Covering his mouth and stomping)
Is that bromance?
Is this a dating show?
(The experienced one feels dizzy.)
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
(It's time to pause.)
(Goodness)
(Embarrassed)
The two of them.
- Ho Jong. - What?
- What? - We look quite close.
It can be...
a little dangerous.
It's close to love.
- Good job. - Oh, thank you.
- Did you apologize to him? - Apologize?
I should.
(He feels more embarrassed after watching the video.)
I had my solo part,
so I am satisfied with that.
I was walking on eggshells...
around Yu Chan in the locker room.
(He was intimidated.)
In this video,
we could see the ensemble...
and other roles more than before.
The energy of the ensemble in the background was good too.
The quality was...
- Didn't it come out well? - It was different.
You looked so sexy.
- You were great. - My face should've been zoomed in.
For Second Class,
I liked how...
- they showed various techniques. - Right.
Hye Hyun had...
one shot that was quite heavy.
(Kang Gyeong Ho...)
(and Kim Young Woong couldn't participate due to injuries.)
I remember the fairies the most.
I think that I showed everything that I could.
I was satisfied.
Who do you think will receive the benefit?
Among the main lead roles,
Ho Jong seems to have the highest chance.
Ho Jong is being unfair.
How is he so good? It's annoying.
Being a double was an advantage.
- Right. - Yes.
Since his face could be seen, he looked like the main dancer.
I think that Hyeok Jung will get the Double Casting benefit.
He took the role from Yu Chan too.
I think that you'll get it.
- Really? - Yes.
I feel nervous.
Hyeok Jung also did a good job.
Regarding Hyeok Jung,
he did a lot for someone who was double-cast.
I was half-hopeful and half-worried.
(Mega Stage Mission, Best Main Lead Role is revealed.)
(Everyone is paying attention.)
Jin Ho, be the best dancer.
Dancers cast for main lead roles...
and dancers who are double-cast...
will be given a chance to choose...
the main role in the next mission.
This benefit will be given to only one person...
among main lead roles, main supporting roles,
and double-cast dancers.
Here's how we'll determine the dancer to receive the benefit.
Five sub lead roles will evaluate the main lead roles,
and ten sub supporting roles will evaluate the main supporting roles.
The best double-cast dancer...
will be determined by the ensemble.
Who will it be?
(The Best Main Lead Role)
(Choi Ho Jong, 5 votes)
He got all the votes.
(Best Main Lead Role, Choi Ho Jong)
("It was clean and amazing. I give him credit for it.")
(Choi Ho Jong dominated the stage with his unrivaled style.)
He clearly showed his own dance.
- He's good again. - He did it like Ho Jong.
I wished that his dance wouldn't end.
Thank you.
I felt the need to grow more.
I was especially thankful to the ensemble...
who danced in my scene.
(Best Main Supporting Role)
(Kim Hye Hyun, 8 votes)
(Clapping in agreement)
Congratulations, Hye Hyun.
("Technically, he was flawless." "I trust in his solid movements.")
Thank you.
(Kim Hye Hyun increased the quality onstage...)
(with precise techniques and flawless movements.)
He gained our trust with his dance.
He's always reliable.
His Aoya was excellent.
Hye Hyun's technique was amazing.
He's very reliable like gukbap.
Gukbap? I like it.
People liked what I did, so I was picked.
Now, I feel pressured...
to show them more.
(Best Double Casting, Park Jin Ho, 21 votes)
It's up.
(It's great news for the Under Class.)
Everyone, Jin Ho won!
(Best Double Casting, Park Jin Ho)
(He feels extremely happy.)
(Park Jin Ho dominated the stage with his earnest expressions.)
He's good at giving emphasis to his movements.
His expression also catches people's attention.
He looked very desperate in that moment.
That's true.
He's the only one in the ensemble who got double-cast.
The effort that he made seems greater than others'.
It's my first accomplishment.
("I could feel him doing his best in every moment.")
- The hope of Under Class. - He's amazing.
I received poor evaluations,
but now, I'm qualified enough...
to redeem myself.
- I hope that it happens. - Hello.
- What? - It's Oh Na Ra.
Hello, dancers of Stage Fighter.
I'm Actress Oh Na Ra.
(Moved to meet her in person?)
(Going wild)
(They're even wilder.)
I'm Actress Lee Jung Eun.
I'm Actor Heo Seong Tae.
I'm Film Director Park Chan Wook.
(Things liven up as world-class celebrities appear.)
World-class.
- The scale is huge. - Right.
Dancers who are proving your skills...
in your positions,
you have worked very hard.
You tell stories and express yourselves...
by moving your body.
I find your talent very mysterious...
and impressive.
You must've been startled to see me all of a sudden.
Here's why I appeared in front of you so suddenly.
I can't wait to find out.
Why did actors appear?
They must be announcing our mission now.
I'm about to tell you your next mission.
I'm closely related to your next mission.
The next mission on Stage Fighter is...
- What is it? - What is it?
Stop.
Drum roll.
K-Contents...
It's the K-Contents Mission.
(K-Contents Mission)
- "K-Contents?" - What does "K-Contents" mean?
Does it include movies and dramas?
Aren't you curious to find out...
what kind of K-Contents pieces will be given to you?
It's one of the movies that I was in.
- "Parasite." - "Parasite."
It's "Parasite."
I knew it.
(This is it.)
I want to do this.
(I want to do this, no matter what.)
("Parasite," a luxurious party with dukes and aristocrats)
"A class war between butlers and aristocrats."
To be honest, I look like an aristocrat.
This music is perfect for ballet.
Korean dance would go well with it too.
I liked the melody...
of the music in "Parasite," so I wanted to do it.
The K-Contents piece I'd like to introduce to you is...
a drama called "SKY Castle."
("SKY Castle," children of the top 0.1 percent elitist family)
(Everyone gapes at the sound of the legendary soundtrack.)
This is it.
It makes you feel overwhelmed.
I like the effect.
Didn't I come too far to play a student?
(A drama about high school students)
The K-Contents piece I'd like to introduce to you is...
one of the works that I was in.
It is...
"Squid Game."
(A survival game to win the absolute power with dance)
- "Squid Game" is about survival. - Korean dance to this song...
What will you do?
- It sounds like fun. - I agree.
Wouldn't it be interesting to show something Korean...
with "Squid Game?"
It could be difficult with ballet.
The music didn't seem...
suitable with ballet at all.
That's why I was attracted to it even more.
Now...
- There must be more. - Is there more?
A movie by Director Park Chan Wook?
The K-Contents piece I'd like to introduce to you is...
one of the movies that I directed.
- "Oldboy." - It must be "Oldboy."
It's a movie called "Oldboy."
(What's classic is forever.)
Seriously? "Oldboy?"
(A man dreams of escaping after being imprisoned for no reason.)
(The introduction is crazy.)
The music is amazing.
Since it's a waltz,
it sounds the most familiar to ballet dancers.
I want to do this one.
Goodness.
It's number one based on the music.
As soon as I heard it, I thought that it'd be worth trying.
(Choosing the K-Contents Mission)
(Choi Ho Jong got the benefit. Which one will he choose?)
I don't have enough information.
("It was clean and amazing. I give him credit for it.")
Okay, I'll choose this.
I wanted to do it because I love the "Parasite" soundtrack.
(Kim Hye Hyun also has the benefit. Which work will he choose?)
("Technically, he was flawless." "I trust in his solid movements.")
I thought the concept behind "Oldboy" was...
the best match for me.
There was only one.
("I could feel him doing his best in every moment.")
(Park Jin Ho chooses "SKY Castle.")
(Dancers with the benefit get their main roles.)
I'll go my way.
(The dancers pick the work of their choice.)
I'll pick what suits me.
As contemporary dancers got the benefit, we get what we want.
- There aren't many spots left. - Only four spots remain.
- I'll do this. - It's complete.
(Choices Made for the K-Contents Mission)
For the K-Contents Mission...
Main lead roles will be given...
based on the Role Casting Audition.
(K-Contents Casting Board is revealed.)
(Main roles, supporting roles, and ensemble)
For "SKY Castle,"
Jin Ho got the benefit...
One of the main roles is already taken.
I'll take the remaining role.
I'm guaranteed to get the main role.
I must get the main lead role...
to find the strength to get ahead.
I'll risk my life to get it.
("Squid Game," lead roles, supporting roles, ensemble)
Still, compared to other teams,
"Squid Game" doesn't have clear main dancers.
You're right. Only "Squid Game" doesn't have them.
It'll be even more competitive.
The fact that there's another spot...
means the odds are better.
I think I could become one of the main lead dancers.
The classes have been taken apart.
Whoever is First Class or gets the main lead role,
it wouldn't be weird at all.
I just had one thought, which was to be the main lead dancer.
I want to be the final one.
Only our team has two spots available.
This could be doable.
("Parasite," main lead role Choi Ho Jong)
Although Ho Jong took the main lead role,
there's still another spot left.
I want to be the main lead the most.
It would be fun to be the main lead dancer.
I thought I should definitely get the main lead role.
I have no other choice. I'll just do it.
I can just cheer them on.
I'll be watching the fire from across the river.
("Oldboy," lead roles, supporting roles, ensemble)
(Main lead role Kim Hye Hyun)
I have to be the main lead dancer.
There was a strong competitive vibe...
for taking the remaining main lead spot.
Everything besides the main lead is meaningless right now.
I'll win the main lead role for sure.
I think they would've been jealous of me.
(The Audition Rules)
(Eligibility for Main Choreography Creative Audition: All dancers)
- Oh, there's a creative part? - Do you have to choreograph it?
All dancers who chose this performance can go for it.
(All dancers who chose this performance are eligible.)
(Yes, so they could even use an Under's choreography.)
Then, we could see choreography from all 63 of us.
The main lead will do the choreography chosen from that.
So, the Choreography Creative Audition isn't related to casting?
If you audition for a role with the choreography perfectly memorized,
you could have an advantage since it's your own creation.
This is my chance.
I'm confident.
The Unders haven't had a chance.
Let's show myself off.
For the other classes, this is an opportunity.
Everyone must be aiming for it.
I really wanted to dance to my own choreography.
I'm confident when it comes to choreography creation.
I wasn't really worried.
Hello, I'm the MC of Stage Fighter, Kang Daniel.
He's the scariest person.
Hey, brother. My brother.
I'm the MC of Stage Fighter, Kang Daniel.
For the second Class Movement Ceremony,
we will start the K-Contents Mission.
(The second Class Movement Ceremony?)
There will be changes in class?
How will the classes change?
In this Class Movement Ceremony,
there will be eliminations for the first time.
- Eliminations? - Eliminations?
(Oh, my...)
(Goodness)
It's really getting started now.
It's the beginning.
I think people will be more desperate with eliminations.
It really woke me up with a jolt.
I don't want to be eliminated.
Let's keep trying until the end.
This mission would be worth risking my life over.
There is no such thing as being eliminated in my life.
Soon, on the Mnet Plus app,
the Seat Class Evaluation will begin with the full performance videos...
of the K-Contents Mission.
Please vote by choosing the seat class befitting the performance.
(The dancers are faced with...)
(the K-Contents Poster Shoot Mission.)
(This is a battle of ideas.)
(Only the winning team's photos...)
(will be used as this performance's main poster.)
(Who will be the one to take the best benefit?)
(Time to create the main choreography for each performance)
I thought I wanted to do something very Korean.
I think I'll add something the public would like.
"What kind of character was Oh Dae Soo?"
I thought about such things...
to come up with some charming movements.
(The day of filming for each performance's main choreography)
(The filming for the main choreography of "Parasite" begins.)
I think I tried to pay attention to show the personality...
of the character in the beginning.
I think I tried to portray...
the attitude of a duke...
at a party.
(Scanning)
"I should do this. I should get this."
That was what I thought as I watched.
Well, going up to perform...
my own choreography...
is a great feeling.
Kim Young Woong's choreography...
was very powerful and eye-catching.
(The filming for the main choreography of "Oldboy" begins.)
(Creative choreography by Contemporary Dancer Kim Hye Hyun)
I hoped to deliver...
the concept of the story.
I tried to express that...
through imagery.
It didn't feel like "Oldboy."
It felt too much like a young boy.
(Creative choreography by Korean Dancer Ki Moo Gan)
I'm glad that I was able to...
add the movements I liked to such sentimental music...
and show people something.
I was finally able to show people my own dance.
I felt happy.
Moo Gan's style stood out way too much.
He came up with something that no one could do besides him.
(Filming for the main choreography of "Squid Game" begins.)
I heard tug-of-war being mentioned.
So, I used a lot of push and pull...
in my body.
The action and reaction of forces.
Being pushed and pulled.
I thought it would be nice to use these concepts.
(Creative choreography by Contemporary Dancer Kim Hyun Ho)
Hyun Ho's choreography looked really hard to memorize.
It was very detailed,
and although it included the imagery of "Squid Game" really well,
there were so many movements. That's what I felt.
(Filming for the main choreography of "SKY Castle" begins.)
I tried to think about the character...
of an elite student a lot.
I wanted to express that the character acts tough...
but is actually very lonely.
I thought it was about constant expression.
So, I expressed what I was feeling on the inside.
(The Main Choreography Creative Audition with all 64 dancers ends.)
(The Main Choreography Creative Audition results are revealed.)
They're announcing them right away?
(Sighing)
They're announcing the results.
This is so much pressure.
(The main creative choreography for "Parasite" is revealed.)
(Totally curious)
Who do you think are the likely candidates?
Ho Jong and Young Woong.
As long as it's not Young Woong or Ho Jong's choreography, it's good.
- I heard Ho Jong made it very hard. - Yes.
(Who will it be?)
The person whose choreography has been chosen...
for the Main Choreography Creative Audition is...
Choi Ho Jong.
(We knew it.)
(It's me!)
Congratulations.
As soon as I saw the results, I was worried about...
whether people would be able to do this dance.
How will we do that?
I was really worried.
It was charismatic...
and had good techniques, expression, musicality, and even character.
I think he showed everything that he had in mind.
(The strong choreography that went as the dancer intended)
- Who did "SKY Castle?" - Hyeok Jung and Yu Chan.
It's a rematch.
(This will be a big match.)
(During the Mega Stage Mission)
(Casting change for main lead solo, Kim Yu Chan to Yun Hyeok Jung)
(Hyeok Jung had taken Yu Chan's main lead solo before.)
(Mixed feelings)
(Yu Chan couldn't do anything but watch.)
I'm so curious.
I'm looking forward to this.
- You look nervous. - I'm not. I don't expect anything.
(The main creative choreography for "SKY Castle" is revealed.)
- Go. - I was really surprised.
It had really good basic skills and was nicely done overall.
And with the way it expressed the character,
it left a lasting impression.
What an interesting scene.
You took my solo part, so I'll take your choreography.
Hang on a minute.
(The room is in an uproar after Yu Chan's provocation.)
I think it's time for me to steal his thunder.
I can't let him take it. I'll hold on to what's mine.
(The main creative choreography for "Squid Game" is revealed.)
(The whole group is surprised.)
- This is bad. - I knew it.
We're in trouble.
The choreography that has been chosen...
is Kim Hyun Ho's choreography.
(For "Squid Game," Kim Hyun Ho's main choreography is chosen.)
He has a good understanding of the content,
and we could tell that...
he considered how to express that in his choreography.
That was why we chose Kim Hyun Ho's choreography.
His has so many movements.
I was so glad.
Hyun Ho's choreography, which I wanted to avoid the most,
had been chosen.
I'm in big trouble.
Since Hyun Ho's was chosen,
I'll make it mine and take it away from him. That's what I thought.
(The main creative choreography for "Oldboy" is revealed.)
- Hye Hyun's choreography... - I bet it's Hye Hyun.
seems most likely for some reason.
I'd be happy if they chose mine.
The choreography that has been chosen...
(What?)
That's so unexpected.
It's Kim Jong Cheol's choreography.
(For "Oldboy," Kim Jong Cheol's main choreography is chosen.)
What? That's me.
- What? - What?
I just hoped it wasn't this.
It looks a bit hard.
We thought that the character's mental state was...
most accurately expressed.
And the movements flowed with the music...
in a harmonious way.
(The 4 choreographies for the casting audition have been chosen.)
But does it even make sense that there are two main leads?
We only have 16 dancers per group.
Isn't it so weird that there are two who are confining someone else?
- It's weird. - Why are there two?
(K-Contents Mission Rules)
(From each performance, 1 main lead and 2 main supporting dancers...)
(will have a team battle. The ensemble dances with both teams.)
(Gasping)
I'm right, aren't I?
"The K-Contents Mission Process."
"From each performance, 1 main lead and 2 main supporting dancers..."
"will have a team battle."
You're right. Goodness.
"The ensemble dances with both teams."
We have to compete with other teams.
So I thought that my team should do well, first and foremost.
I'll have to choose good members.
And we'll have to have good teamwork.
(Main Role Casting Audition)
(Eligibility: All dancers besides the confirmed main lead)
For the Main Role Casting Audition,
you will perform the choreography...
that was chosen in the Main Choreography Creative Audition.
Only one dancer...
will be chosen as Team B's main lead dancer...
to compete against Team A's main lead dancer...
whose casting has already been confirmed.
Our main lead roles are undecided.
We have to choose both main leads.
That team will be in a bloody battle.
I'm jealous that they have two spots open.
The dancers who don't get called by the two main leads...
will be eliminated from the audition...
and confirmed as an ensemble member.
If we don't get chosen as supporting dancers, we end up in the ensemble.
(No way.)
We could end up in the ensemble in one step.
(An ominous mood sweeps the Firsts' locker room.)
Still, it's my choreography.
I think I have a high chance of being chosen as the main lead.
My biggest goal is to be chosen as the elite student main lead role.
Even the Unders could become main lead dancers.
This is the first ever mission where that could happen.
I can never miss out on this chance.
(The night of practicing for the casting audition)
We'll get started right away.
As you move your right leg, push.
Then, turn.
I have to teach them...
and practice myself too.
I'm competing against these people...
and having to prepare for the audition as well.
Since I was already confirmed, I felt proud of myself.
In a way, I was worried too.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask.
- Could we play the song again? - You don't get to ask questions.
(Half joking, half serious)
You can do whatever.
I didn't ask.
I can follow along even without asking questions.
Hyeok Jung is wary of me.
If Hye Seong adds his own style to my choreography,
my choreography could become poison for me.
There's no reason why I can't win.
The angle where they kick their legs are so different from us.
They're so flexible.
It looks so energetic.
Yu Chan's dance doesn't look like ballet.
- I know. - His lines look like ballet.
- But the way he moves is... - He doesn't move like a ballerino.
Actually, everyone followed along so well...
that I wasn't sure about myself as time went on.
I really don't know anymore.
I thought, Yun Hyeok Jung and Jung Hye Seong...
Also, Kim Yu Chan.
I think those three stood out to me the most.
We will now begin the Main Role Casting Audition...
for the "SKY Castle" team in the K-Contents Mission.
This is the most interesting part right here.
This team had a really intense competition.
I think the "SKY Castle" team has several good dancers.
This team has so many talented people too.
The Main Role Casting Audition...
for the "SKY Castle" team in the K-Contents Mission...
will be to choose the main lead and main supporting dancers.
The main lead will be cast through evaluations from...
the choreographer, myself, and the two coaches.
The main supporting roles will be cast by...
the two who were cast as the main leads.
For the Main Role Casting Audition,
you will be performing the creative choreography by Yun Hyeok Jung...
which was chosen during the Main Choreography Creative Audition.
All of the dancers who chose this team...
will be divided into three evaluation groups.
Only one dancer will be cast as the main lead of Team B...
to compete against the Team A main lead dancer, Park Jin Ho,
whose casting has been confirmed for the "SKY Castle" team.
Just one. Goodness.
Hello, everyone.
I'm choreographer Luda Lee in charge of "SKY Castle."
Nice to meet you.
(Welcoming her with enthusiasm)
First, I will focus on how well you manage the given dance...
and whether you can express the concept of "SKY Castle..."
and its character as I evaluate you.
Hyeok Jung, this is your own choreography, correct?
Which person are you wary of the most?
There's one dancer who has the closest style to myself.
I think Yu Chan has the most similar vibe as me.
This is it.
Big match.
Since the Mega Stage Mission,
I had hoped we could learn from each other and go up together.
But he went and stole my part.
So...
(Looking away)
Now, I think it's my turn to steal his thunder.
- Nice! - Go, Yu Chan!
(Burning up)
- Steal it! - Let's go!
- Steal it! - I love your speech.
I think it's time for me to beat Hyeok Jung...
and win the main lead role.
I've been eyeing this role the whole time but never got it.
I think it's really time for me to take this spot.
I'll put my life on the line to win this role.
If I take that spot when I was an Under,
I could be able to make history.
The main lead role is what I must win, no matter what.
We will now begin the Main Lead Role Audition for "SKY Castle."
Jin Ho was saying he felt so confused...
about who to choose.
Our team is so difficult to choose from.
- Which person to choose? - Yes.
The "SKY Castle" team is really talented.
I thought I was going crazy.
I think I was contemplating which dancer to choose...
so that I can stand out...
but have them fill the parts that I am lacking in.
The first group, we'll have Lee Jin Woo, Moon Jun On,
Jang June Hyuk, and Jung Hye Seong.
First position.
The pose is hard already.
Music, start.
Three, two, one.
Go.
(Impressed)
Hye Seong is pushing forward with his head.
(Grabbing everyone's attention)
Oh, Hye Seong.
Nice. He's so good.
Those two are definitely moving well.
They look like they're dancing in sync.
They're perfectly in sync.
(Hye Seong and June Hyuk grab their attention by being in sync.)
June Hyuk has good energy.
(Practicing in the meantime)
- Hye Seong is crazy. - Nice jump.
I think he got confused about the order.
He got lost.
Three, two, one.
Stop.
They're so good.
Hye Seong is hardcore. He's insane.
He's all the way at the end,
but I only saw him through everyone else.
The second group, we'll have Kim Tae Seok, Kim Tae Gang,
Kim Yu Chan, and Kim In Su.
The order is a shame.
Yu Chan and Hyeok Jung should've been in the same group.
- Right. - I'm looking forward to Yu Chan.
Three, two, one.
Go.
I think Tae Seok tried to interpret it in a ballet style.
(Stretching)
(This is it.)
He has an incredible kick.
He has great lines.
These guys are so good.
This competition is fierce too.
I love it.
I love Yu Chan's facial expression.
Tae Seok is doing amazing.
(Stretching again)
(He tore up the stage.)
There you go.
(Nervous)
Yu Chan's eyes have gone mad.
He's channeling some spirit.
(No way.)
(Impressed)
Three, two, one. Stop.
Yu Chan is insane.
I think Yu Chan is a madman.
You could tell that Yu Chan was so full of that dogged spirit.
And that'll make Hyeok Jung feel shaken up.
I thought there was a chance for me to become the main lead.
I could actually steal his choreography.
The third group, we'll have Jung Min Chan and Yun Hyeok Jung.
Five, four,
- I was wary of Yu Chan. - three, two,
- I should really do even better. - one. Go.
(Jaw dropping)
Min Chan is staying calm.
Min Chan isn't bad either.
(Yun Hyeok Jung's lethal kick)
(He's good.)
He's sexy.
They're dancing like this is a duet.
He's not backing down either.
(A crazy thrill)
Nice!
Gosh, I love this so much.
(The two competed fiercely until the very end.)
Three, two, one.
Stop.
All right.
(Feeling confused)
(Satisfied)
This group was amazing.
Hyeok Jung is so good.
Hyeok Jung's dance doesn't even have a tiny bit of error.
I personally want to see Yu Chan and Hyeok Jung...
dance together in the same group.
They stand out so much.
Jang June Hyuk.
This dance requires that you show the pressures of college exams...
and a rebellious manly power.
I thought you expressed that manly power really well.
I enjoyed how you released your energy outwardly.
Jung Hye Seong.
In your expressive abilities,
I could tell that you were actively portraying the character.
I liked that you expressed the concept of "SKY Castle" well.
And the two of you...
danced together so well as if you were a pair.
Kim Tae Seok.
You were actively expressing yourself,
and I thought you were very immersive and dynamic.
Jung Min Chan.
This was Yun Hyeok Jung's choreography...
and despite being right next to the original choreographer,
you weren't lacking in comparison at all.
You had good control, expression, flexibility,
and in all areas overall.
I could feel the strong desperation in your eyes.
I enjoyed your performance.
This is the rebellion of the Unders.
Kim Yu Chan.
I thought you were a ballerino who was only made for ballet.
As I watched, I thought you might have a hard time...
breaking out of that shell.
But you showed us a new language of dance...
that you could express as a ballerino. I enjoyed it so much.
I didn't think that I was bad,
but no one gave me an evaluation.
So I was like, "Why isn't anyone talking about me?"
This is very shocking.
No one made comments about Hyeok Jung. It's unbelievable.
Hyeok Jung doesn't look happy.
- He doesn't look happy. - Hey, sit down.
- Hyeok Jung doesn't look good. - Sit back down.
I didn't think that I did terribly.
Am I going to be sent to Under Class?
That's ridiculous.
(Extremely worried)
Is my choreography going to betray me? I'll be in trouble.
The choreographers are seen as the standard...
for the choreography.
He has to stand out even more. Just doing the choreography is...
- already difficult. - Right.
Hyeok Jung might be having a mental breakdown.
This work requires the technique...
of a ballet dancer.
In terms of movements,
we need contemporary dancers who are masculine.
In my opinion, these two are the best fit.
To be honest, I want to see more.
This isn't just ballet.
I want to see how much more they can dance.
The evaluation was taking longer than usual.
It was unpredictable. I felt nervous.
I'd like to see these two dancers.
It has to be me.
I was confident about doing better. I must do better.
I had a chance of getting eliminated.
I didn't want to believe it.
Dancer Yun Hyeok Jung and...
I felt relieved.
Dancer Kim Yu Chan.
Do I have to compete against Hyeok Jung again?
I thought that it wouldn't be easy.
With the same music,
please be free and show us your dance.
- This is it. - This will be big.
It will be a fight between water and fire.
A fight between a unicorn and a red horse.
(Anticipating)
I should attract more of their attention.
I should dance with all my might.
I pulled all the energy that I possibly could.
Okay, I'll give my all.
Hyeok Jung needs that kind of stimulus to really go after it.
He's gentle, but he can be quite competitive.
(How will Hyeok Jung and Yu Chan's improvisation battle turn out?)
Three, two, one. Go.
Gosh.
- He's covering him. - Yu Chan became spiteful.
(A competition of technique)
He's covering him.
(The two dancers dance without yielding at all.)
(A turn of satisfaction)
Goodness.
Gosh.
(There's power and elegance in their performance.)
They're so good.
(At that moment)
He's starting to turn.
(Holding her hands tightly)
What's this, a show?
Let's go, Yu Chan!
(His elegant manege against the powerful turn)
(Nervous and focused)
(Stumbling)
- Oh, no. Yu Chan. - Keep going.
(Two of them poured their everything into it.)
Three, two, one. Stop.
("SKY Castle" Casting Audition additional evaluation ends.)
Goodness.
It's harder to choose now.
Goodness, Yu Chan.
Yu Chan is insane.
It's Hyeok Jung who's insane.
How many illusion turns did he do?
It was crazy. It was the best I've seen.
Yu Chan crushed it in the beginning.
Hyeok Jung was amazing at the end.
They're making it difficult again. This is annoying.
Picking between them would be so difficult.
The dancer to compete...
against main lead role Park Jin Ho from Team A.
I'll announce the dancer who's cast...
for Team B's main lead role, an elite student.
The dancer who's cast...
for Team B's main lead role on "SKY Castle,"
which is an elite student...
I definitely showed it to them,
so wouldn't they pick me?
I was desperately praying...
for my name to be called.
It's Contemporary Dancer...
Yun Hyeok Jung. Congratulations.
("SKY Castle" Team B's main lead role, Yun Hyeok Jung)
(Congratulations, Hyeok Jung.)
As befits the original choreographer,
your expression was...
very clean and controlled.
You showed the beauty of restraint.
With much more explosive energy,
you have both the flexibility and strength.
Your technical movements were excellent.
The rebellious look in your eyes...
would be suitable...
to play the main lead role.
There were many ups and downs...
before I got the main lead role.
I'm very happy that I finally got it.
Now that I got the main lead role,
I must do very well this time.
The main lead role from each team, Park Jin Ho...
and Yun Hyeok Jung.
Among five dancers behind you,
you'll call two names and cast them.
We'll start with Park Jin Ho.
Please cast dancers of your choice for the main supporting role.
The dancer I'll cast for the main supporting role is...
I'm a dancer who can't be replaced.
Wouldn't he pick me?
I definitely showed my skills in front of them.
I had hopes.
(Who will be Park Jin Ho's first choice?)
It's Dancer Kim Yu Chan.
("SKY Castle" Team A's main supporting role, Kim Yu Chan)
He could show ballet moves...
that I don't have.
Yu Chan is much more flexible than me.
He has a strong foundation.
I picked Yu Chan who can cover...
what I lack.
Please call out your second dancer.
The dancer I'll cast for the main supporting role is...
I thought that I could overcome this crisis.
I felt confident.
He might pick Min Chan.
It's Dancer Jang June Hyuk.
His looks and physique are both impressive.
I wanted to pick someone who had matching energy as mine.
That's why I picked Jang June Hyuk.
Shall we start the main supporting role casting for Team B?
The dancer I'll cast for the main supporting role is...
I felt confident that someone would pick me.
Being in the ensemble will be bad news. I'll get eliminated.
I felt anxious.
It's Dancer Jung Hye Seong.
I got this one.
Hye Seong is a rebellious boy.
He's perfect for the role.
Hye Seong's strength is...
that his dancing energy is unique and strong.
He was the perfect match for someone rebellious.
Luckily, Hyeok Jung got...
got a very strong weapon.
It's impossible for him to lose.
That weapon is me.
Please pick your second dancer.
The dancer I'll cast for the main supporting role is...
(Who will get the last main supporting role?)
There was only one spot left.
If I'm sent to the ensemble, I'll turn black.
Will I be able to get somewhere safe from the edge of this cliff?
I hoped that he'd call my name.
The dancer I'll cast for the main supporting role is...
Dancer Kim Tae Seok.
(Bowing thankfully)
I picked Tae Seok because...
his jumps and turns will be good and precise.
I hope that both teams will do your best and prove yourselves.
For my first main lead role,
I'll pour my everything into it.
Jin Ho should stay wary.
On my team,
I have Yu Chan, the gem of ballet...
and Jang June Hyuk, the handsomest contemporary dancer.
That's all I have to explain.
("SKY Castle" Team A Cast)
("SKY Castle" Team B Cast)
- We'll start right away. - The special lesson will start.
Step forward.
Hyun Ho's choreography includes ballet moves...
and contemporary dance moves.
He even considered...
Korean dance in his choreography.
I thought that each dancer...
would bring out the strength in his part.
Since it's my choreography, I have the highest chance...
of getting the main lead role.
One, put it down in the back.
Two, hit it like this.
Then start the brise.
I'm not familiar with the terms. Was it brise vole?
Hop, brise, hop, hop, hop, hop.
(Hop)
That looks incredible.
I'm a ballerino. All right.
I'm a ballerino.
(Ballerino Si Won tries the brise vole again.)
(He fails.)
Goodness.
(His feet are moving idly in the air forever.)
I thought that...
all Korean dancers totally failed when it came to brise vole.
It was a mess.
He's definitely a ballerino.
His feet were moving elaborately.
I was in trouble.
He was teaching others,
but that's how ballet is.
Even if someone teaches you, you'll never get it.
I should give up completing the ballet steps.
Other than that, I was confident.
The right leg is underneath. Twist right here.
That's it.
(Is this correct?)
Oh, nice.
- Is that right? - Yes.
Should I lift both legs or sweep one leg?
- Pose first. - That's it.
Ballerinos, are you okay?
Do you want to see the legs again?
(Going over it one more time slowly)
(Despite that, Gyeong Ho can't keep up the floor movement.)
Of course, I was having a mental breakdown.
Only the brise vole was easy.
It was the only difficult thing for the rest of the dancers.
I can do the movements separately.
This is at the count of eight.
Hyun Ho taught me until I got it.
He helped me out until I could do it.
(Soon, Kang Gyeong Ho's floor movements become smooth.)
Gosh, he's really good.
He's really good.
Oh, ballet...
It's not easy for ballet dancers to do that.
I forgot that it was a competition for a second.
I belatedly noticed that I was in danger.
He acquired...
the details well.
Still, I'm the original choreographer.
I'll be different.
Dong Hoon...
Dong Hoon, let's practice together.
- I am. - Are you?
- Yes. - Okay.
- Now... - Practice here.
- Wait. - When you get here...
After the bridge...
I said I was managing my condition...
and watched them from the side.
It was more entertaining than I thought. It wasn't so bad.
It's worth taking it from him.
If I can't get it with my hands, I'll bite it.
If my teeth get pulled out, I'll bite it with my gum.
I was that desperate.
I'll shine bright in the part I'm good at.
It's the Korean dance.
I feel confident.
We will now begin the main role Casting Audition...
for K-Contents Mission "Squid Game."
Pulling off the given choreography is a given.
We'll focus...
on how you express the character...
in details...
without harming the original dance.
Since it's my choreography,
I'm likely...
to get the main role.
I'll get the main role no matter what.
Getting the main role...
is the only way.
If I become a group dancer, it's the end of my dance career.
First group. I Ban.
(I Ban from contemporary dance)
Park Jun Woo, Kim Hyun Ho.
First position.
Music, start.
Three, two, one. Go.
Park Jun Woo is confident.
(Exclaiming)
(Ballet technique section)
He's also good at ballet.
Can anyone beat the original choreographer?
Jun Woo is pretty good.
(Exclaiming)
Jun Woo is amazing.
What? He's dancing like it's his own.
Jun Woo knows how to use his energy.
This is risky.
(Hyun Ho is indeed good.)
(They're both good.)
Oh, Jun Woo.
(It's hard to tell who's better between the two.)
(Impressed)
Three, two, one. Stop.
("Squid Game" Casting Audition Line 1 ends.)
They were good.
Very good.
Jun Woo was amazing.
While dancing, I realized...
I found my path.
He was stable.
But I was better.
Because he came up with it,
he presented the intention and quality the best.
Line Two.
Lee Ha Nel, Kim Hyo Joon,
Han Jeong Bin, Kwon Yo Han.
A hope that I can move up.
I have to prove them.
I finally get to prove them.
I was confident.
Except for the ballet move,
I'll be more powerful...
on the floor.
Three, two, one. Go.
(Lee Ha Nel swings his arms the other way.)
(Due to the wrong arm move, he misses the beat.)
Awesome.
(What a shame.)
(Followed by the ballet technique)
(What? Why are they good at it?)
Good.
(Followed by tutting section)
Yo Han's good at tutting.
Because he was a hip-hop dancer.
Hyun Ho might lose it.
Hyo Joon never looks weird.
(His eyes move busily.)
(It's hard to tell who's in which class.)
Nice.
(Keep it up, buddy.)
Okay.
It doesn't look any strange.
Three, two, one. Stop.
Both Yo Han and Hyo Joon were good.
They were all very good.
Good job, Yo Han.
I thought I had a chance, obviously.
"I was pretty good."
"They probably liked it."
I thought they'd focus more on the dance techniques.
That'd get me...
more credits.
Hyo Joon was very good.
Since then, I was worried about him.
Line Three. Kim Min Seok.
Choi Jong In.
Baek Sang Ha.
Kim Si Won.
(Kim Si Won from Korean dance)
They're all Korean dancers.
Kim Si Won scares me.
He's splendid from the start, right?
No one is as strong as I am.
No one is as impressive as I am...
or dance as well as I do.
Three, two, one.
("Squid Game" Casting Audition for Line 3 begins.)
(Focusing)
(The difficult ballet technique section)
Oh, no.
(Awkward ballet technique section)
(Sad)
Korean dancers aren't good at the beginning.
(Ballet dancers sigh.)
(The tutting section is another crisis.)
Si Won pulled it off.
It's so neat.
(You got it!)
I've never seen Jong In dancing with so much passion before.
(Max enthusiasm)
Oh, Jong In.
(Bugged)
(Nodding, approving)
Si Won looks stable.
Sang Ha looks neat.
(Nervous)
Two, one. Stop.
("Squid Game" Casting Audition for Line 3 ends.)
Line Four.
Go Dong Hoon. Choo Seok Ho.
Kang Gyeong Ho.
I'll do my best for brise vole.
And for the floor technique and tutting,
I'll carry them out, so I wouldn't fall behind.
There are ballet and floor techniques.
It's favorable for me...
since I can pull them all off.
I must get the main role.
("Squid Game" Casting Audition for Line 4 begins.)
One. Go.
(Eyes focused)
Good job, Dong Hoon.
(Amazed)
(Standard example of ballet)
(That's it.)
(Is that what we're supposed to do?)
They're crazy.
Good job.
Nice.
What if they're only focusing on Gyeong Ho?
I must get their attention no matter what.
(Standard example of the floor dance)
(Cheering)
Gyeong Ho is good.
But it's the contemporary dance technique.
How can a ballet dancer...
do the floor dance like that?
This is risky.
(Exclaiming continuously)
Two, one. Stop.
They sat down at the end. Okay.
Dong Hoon was good.
I really liked Gyeong Ho.
How come they're all good at it?
Everyone is good.
Unless there's a big variable,
I expect to get the main role.
I made no mistake.
I expressed it just as I planned.
I could get my hopes up.
I might get it.
I didn't realize...
that other people were improving.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Hyun Ho, when I saw your choreography,
I felt that you considered...
all three genres.
(Ballet)
(Korean dance)
(Contemporary dance)
But because you were too considerate,
some dancers nailed your choreography.
(Nervous)
"Some nailed it."
Kang Gyeong Ho stood out big time.
I agree.
Ballet dancers aren't used to...
using the floor.
It might be awkward to do the dance with an accent.
You maintained balance,
yet you were flexible and soft.
You really pulled off Hyun Ho's choreography.
(Nodding)
Whereas Jun Woo's dance...
had the musicality.
You expressed each accent and intention.
You were the most suitable dancer for this work.
I was impressed.
Kim Hyo Joon in Line Two.
You just proved...
that depending on who sees the choreography,
the character changes.
You expressed...
that the role of the final one...
is completely exhausted.
It was very encouraging.
Thank you.
Dong Hoon, you finally proved yourself...
through this mission.
I waited for it. It was fun.
"Should I do this? Should I do that?"
"Do you want to fight?" That impression...
felt new.
No one expressed it like you did.
Thank you for that. I enjoyed it.
Fortunately, it was delivered.
During the Class Battle...
(Go Dong Hoon didn't catch the judges' attention.)
Under Class goes to...
(That's how he began as Under Class.)
(During the Class Movement Ceremony)
I became the promotion candidate,
and I thought I had a chance of getting promoted to Second.
(But what he received was...)
(the Under Class again.)
All my effort and enthusiasm...
(He did his best, but he wasn't acknowledged.)
I was shocked that I didn't meet the requirement.
I hated the judges for not approving me.
But I was doing better than I thought.
I was proud of myself and felt comforted at the same time.
Stage Fighter K-Contents Mission...
"Squid Game" Team A's main role.
I can do it. I'll get it.
I was certain.
I expected it to be me for sure.
I had confidence.
I hope it's me.
"Squid Game" Team A's main role goes to...
Kang Gyeong Ho.
("Squid Game" Team A's main role goes to Kang Gyeong Ho.)
- Nice. - Congratulations.
Of course, I was happy and proud.
I overcame the mountain in front of me.
That was relieving.
Now, the person who will be competing...
against "Squid Game" Team A's main role Kang Gyeong Ho.
We will announce Team B's main role.
Who do you think it'll be?
(Thinking)
Oh, I have no idea.
(That's a tough question.)
Hyun Ho or...
Since it's my choreography, of course, I want the main role.
Is it going to be Jun Woo?
Only one spot remained. I was desperate.
Dong Hoon?
I thought it'd be me.
"Squid Game" Team B's main role.
(Nervous)
It's Park Jun Woo.
("Squid Game" Team B's main role goes to Park Jun Woo.)
(Sad)
That's surprising.
I was relieved at once.
It was the role I'd always wanted to get,
and I finally got it.
Jun Woo has outstanding abilities for...
catching the point of the movement and the highlight.
Korean dance sometimes makes your body flexible...
and sometimes strong.
And you're well aware of how to use that rhythm.
(Grateful)
(It's a bummer, but he still approves.)
Each team's main roles, Kang Gyeong Ho and Park Jun Woo...
name two dancers you need...
for the main supporting roles and cast them.
Park Jun Woo,
cast the main supporting role you want.
The dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
My choreography became the fixed choreography.
I might have more chance.
If I become a group dancer again,
it'll hurt my pride big time.
The dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
Kim Hyun Ho.
("Squid Game" Team B's main supporting role, Kim Hyun Ho)
If Gyeong Ho takes Hyun Ho,
I might fall behind in the team battle.
He's good at making choreographies.
He has an outstanding technicality.
I knew I shouldn't lose him.
Jun Woo made the right choice.
I'll show you the impact the First brings...
when given the supporting role.
The second dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
I might not have a chance at all.
(Worried)
What should I do?
I was really anxious.
I could never guess the main supporting role.
Kim Hyo Joon.
("Squid Game" Team B's main supporting role, Kim Hyo Joon)
Because the choreographer is a Korean dancer major,
I chose Hyo Joon with technicality...
who's good at Korean dance. I must cast him.
I must do well.
Yes, Jun Woo. Let's take the main stage.
- He made a good decision. - Yes.
Let's begin the next main supporting role audition.
The dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
I probably suit the image the best.
I expected him to pick me.
I was worried about becoming a group dancer again.
I was in agony.
The dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
Kim Si Won.
("Squid Game" Team A's main supporting role, Kim Si Won)
I'd need at least one Korean dancer...
for the main supporting role.
Kim Si Won can express the rhythm and movements...
of Korean dance the best.
That's why I chose him for the main supporting role.
Gyeong Ho and my energy...
will form chemistry.
Name the second dancer.
The dancer I'd like to cast for main supporting role is...
He'll pick Dong Hoon.
Or will it be Sang Ha?
I think Yo Han was better.
(Who is the last supporting role in "Squid Game?")
Go Dong Hoon.
(Bowing)
("Squid Game" Team A's main supporting role, Go Dong Hoon)
Considering Go Dong Hoon's dance and personality,
despite the mission or movement given,
I believed he'd draw an even better movement.
I was happy that I didn't become a group dancer.
It's only the beginning.
All I could think about was that I had to prove myself again.
My team has a lot of weapons.
We have a lot of technicality, so I'm confident.
I think my team...
forms harmony.
That will be our strength to pull it off.
("Squid Game" Team A Cast)
(Kim Si Won, Kang Gyeong Ho, Go Dong Hoon)
("Squid Game" Team B Cast)
(Kim Hyun Ho, Park Jun Woo, Kim Hyo Joon)
(CJ ENM Ilsan Production Center)
(The return...)
Jump and down.
(of Ho Jong School from inferno)
I'm losing my mind.
I'm going to die.
(Everyone is groaning.)
(Now that they have tried it together)
He can only do that because he's Choi Ho Jong.
My brain couldn't function.
I don't know how to do that.
One bar has many movements.
He breaks that beat...
that's already broken.
It'll be tough for them.
I don't need to audition.
So I had no pressure.
There's no time to breathe.
(Will that do?)
Two hundred segments.
Who makes 200 segments?
How can people do that?
People were glaring like...
(What?)
(Full of enthusiasm)
Three, two, one.
(Screaming)
I have a chance of taking the main lead role.
Even if something fractures or breaks, I shouldn't give up.
Do it until I die. It won't kill me anyway.
Ho Jong has already taken one main lead role.
I want the other main lead role.
Let me get the main lead role. Let me get it first.
(Even during the break)
Can you play the music, please?
Oh, stop.
How are you going to distribute your energy?
Sang Gil is putting so much effort.
It's fun to watch Kim Sang Gil's dance.
It feels new.
Sang Gil has a unique style.
Tae Young looks like a duke just by standing.
He looks elegant.
(Ho Jong's hardcore class begins again.)
Again.
Won Jun looked like an herbivore.
Let's try it one more time.
I liked how he tried to keep up.
He has sturdy basic skills.
Catch your breath.
(Kim Young Woong continues to practice.)
(Sharp)
Kim Young Woong from contemporary dance...
not only picks up the choreography fast,
but he also moves smoothly like water.
His dance is detailed yet soft.
I like it.
(Watching)
Next, bring your left hand.
I noticed Ho Jong...
watched Young Woong...
with love.
I was jealous.
Kim Young Woong's tenacious power...
felt natural...
from the way he tried to acquire the choreography.
He was a strong candidate.
(Another person who pays attention to Kim Young Woong)
I was worried about Young Woong the most.
He's keeping up the best.
I was worried,
but I focused on getting the main lead role.
(Turning)
(Wandering around?)
I tried to watch...
how Kyu Nyeon was doing.
I heard Kyu Nyeon was Ho Jong's student.
It might be easier for Kyu Nyeon.
He dances like Choi Ho Jong.
It feels like our styles changed a lot.
Now that I grew up,
I want to dance in my way.
I want to show that I can be different from Ho Jong.
- Do you want to try? - Yes.
Kyu Nyeon is soft, flexible,
and gentle in his own way.
If there could be an unexpected strong rival,
that would be Kim Kyu Nyeon.
I could feel Kyu Nyeon's energy.
I'll give my all too.
I became determined.
I won't fall behind.
I don't plan to fall...
or do a bad job.
I'm going to clench my teeth for this mission.
(Who will get the last ticket to the main lead role?)
We will now begin the Main Role Choreography Casting Audition...
for K-Contents Mission "Parasite."
Hello.
I'm the "Parasite" choreographer, An Nam Keun.
The K-Contents Mission Main Role Casting Audition...
we're about to begin...
is held to cast...
the main lead role and main supporting role.
Only one main lead role will be selected in Team B...
to compete with Dancer Ho Jong,
now the main lead role...
in "Parasite."
That group seems more heated as there's only one seat.
I guess so.
(Tensed)
Now...
the Main Lead Role Casting Audition for "Parasite" begins.
(They are given a break before the audition begins.)
Look at Ho Jong. He's there...
as if he were a judge.
He's like a guest judge.
(He's looking at others' performance to select the Supporting Role.)
I've tried to see the expression of each dancer.
I mean, their unique characters.
Of course, I've already given some thought,
but I will take a look on the spot...
and decide the best dancer...
who fits me well.
- Very good! - Nice.
(In the 1st round, 14 competed each other with Ho Jong's choreography.)
- Nice! - Gosh!
(Feeling a shudder)
(7 dancers were qualified for the 2nd round.)
That was nice.
(2nd round, 1st group)
(2nd round, 2nd group)
(Only one will be selected as the main lead role in the 2nd round.)
Dancer Ha Won Jun, are you confident enough?
I will do my best as I believe this is the only opportunity...
given to Under.
For dancers in Under, this audition is literally a welcome rain...
in the drought.
Because they haven't got a single chance.
Everybody must've been feeling of danger.
"I'm glad I got this chance."
"Time to show them what I am."
If I were eliminated like this, I would quit my career as a dancer.
So, I'll make sure I stay here.
"I'll fight to death."
All I was thinking about was how to be the main lead role.
Music,
(2nd round, 1st group)
start.
Three, two, one. Go.
So nice.
- Gosh! - Oh, my.
Good!
(He completes checking their performance.)
- Seong Hyun's movement is so clean. - Oh, you think so?
Won Jun's doing well.
(Staring)
Nice!
(Focused)
- Three, two, one. - Yes!
- He's so flexible! - Stop.
(Stop!)
- Three, two, one. Stop. - Nice!
Amazing!
Young Woong's performance overwhelmed others'.
He was crazy.
Young Woong was so good on this stage.
(Thanks for your performance, guys.)
Won Jun was rather conspicuous.
The second group starts now.
"Calm down."
"Come on. I'm Choi Ho Jong."
- Kyu Nyeon was quite good. - Kyu Nyeon was rather...
inspired by Ho Jong.
From high school to concours in my senior year, he affected me...
in many ways and is my teacher.
The audition was based on his choreography.
So, I thought that was for me,
so I had to seize the opportunity.
(Nervous)
(2nd round, 2nd group)
One. Go.
I see.
(Stumbled)
(What a pity.)
Ryu Tae Young is like a duke.
Kyu Nyeon dances as if it were his choreography.
- Darn, Kyu Nyeon. You're so good. - Gosh!
Look at his facial expression!
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
He's truly sexy.
Look at him! Oh, my baby.
Tae Young's doing well too.
Three, two, one. Stop.
Kyu Nyeon. His performance was amazing.
(That was so nice!)
Now I see why he's Ho Jong's student.
If I imagine one strong rival,
I once thought...
it could be Dancer Kyu Nyeon.
For me, Dancer Bang Seong Hyun,
your dance was so amazing.
I see.
- Thanks. - The mood in this music...
allures us to only focus on emotions.
But you wisely restrained it and showed what you are.
Thanks for your performance.
(Seong Hyun's restrained movement with emotions caught the eyes.)
- Thanks. - Regarding Won Jun's dance,
you came all the way from Under to this audition.
It seems you adjusted yourself to this stage.
You have no issues related to technique, right?
Yes!
(Won Jun's amazing flexibility caught the eyes.)
- That's actually my weakness. - Oh, really?
(Embarrassed)
(He shows his unexpected charms.)
But all you showed us looked based on techniques.
- He's quite cute. - He's like a hamster.
Young Woong, as you feel confident,
your movement becomes very bold,
so your facial expressions and energy...
are good.
- It was nice. - Thanks.
Actually, I should mention...
that one dancer in this group surprised me the most.
It was the first time I realized...
that Kyu Nyeon is full of detailed expressions.
(Kyu Nyeon put so many different emotions into his dance.)
- Thanks. - It was very impressive.
I even imagined what if you and Ho Jong...
danced together.
Yours was this good at this stage.
He gave him a high phrase.
I have no idea who'd be selected.
Kim Young Woong and Kim Kyu Nyeon.
They would be the final candidates.
I think it'd be either Tae Young or Young Woong.
Now we announce the main lead role dancer for "Duke" in Team B,
who'll compete...
against the Main Lead Role Ho Jong in Team A.
The selected dancer for the main lead role...
in Team B is from...
(Tensed)
Who'll it be?
I have no idea.
- Second. - Gosh.
(First Ryu Tae Young is eliminated from this Main Lead Role Casting.)
Tae Young is First, right?
(Under Ha Won Jun is eliminated from this Main Lead Role Casting.)
In Second, there are...
three dancers in total. Kim Young Woong,
Kim Kyu Nyeon,
and Kim Sang Gil.
It may be Young Woong.
The main lead role for "Parasite" in Team B.
- Kyu Nyeon will be selected. - It could be Sang Gil.
I thought I was surely selected because that's where I belong.
"I do want to be the Main Role this time."
I thought it could be me.
The main lead role for "Parasite" is...
Dancer Kim Kyu Nyeon!
(The main lead role for "Parasite" in Team B: Kim Kyu Nyeon)
(Okay. I admit it.)
Congratulations!
Thanks.
First, your facial expression was so good.
I could almost hear the music...
through your expressions. It was quite impressive.
Yes, this is it!
(Casting for "Parasite" in Team B)
(Kim Kyu Nyeon the main lead role as Duke)
Dancer Kim Kyu Nyeon, are you sure you can beat him?
Actually, he's my teacher.
I'll do my best to defeat him.
Now I'm full of excitement...
before the new competition.
We're also excited to see you guys.
(It's time to select Supporting Roles.)
The two main lead roles,
Choi Ho Jong and Kim Kyu Nyeon,
each should choose two dancers...
from the six dancers standing behind.
- They want to choose Young Woong. - That's for sure.
(After playing drawing lots, Ho Jong chooses first.)
Starting from Dancer Ho Jong,
choose the main supporting roles.
- Tae Young would be their first. - It's Young Woong.
- It's Young Woong. - Will it be?
It may be Young Woong.
The first main supporting dancer for me is...
I was hoping Ho Jong would pick me.
As Ho Jong chooses first, it'd be Young Woong for sure.
(What would be his choice?)
Dancer Ha Won Jun.
(What?)
(Full of surprise)
Dancer Ha Won Jun.
Oh, this is unexpected.
(The Main Supporting Role for "Parasite" is Ha Won Jun.)
(It's me?)
- It is a story about human triumph! - Won Jun!
Won Jun!
It is a story about human triumph!
(Thank you so much!)
(Making a profound bow)
- He's so cute! - Hey, Won Jun!
You're feeling the greatest happiness now, aren't you?
Are you happy?
Now I enter his jewel box.
(That's unexpected gratitude.)
Then, I feel a bit strange.
(I feel so good!)
Then, would Ho Jong tell us...
why you put him...
into your jewel box?
During the practice for this audition,
I saw how well he followed my turn,
and I could feel he controlled his body very well.
- I think it'll work. - He was like a rough diamond.
I wanted to work with him and polish him.
Ho Jong picked me?
I was picked by him.
Thank you for putting me in your jewelry box.
He's cute.
The dancer I'm going to choose for the main supporting role is...
I wonder who he's going to pick.
It might not be Young Woong.
I think it'll be Young Woong. Or maybe not as he wasn't the priority.
That's what I'm saying.
Or is it Tae Young?
Gosh, I don't know.
It's Dancer Kim Young Woong.
(Kim Young Woong takes the main supporting role for "Parasite.")
Right.
Dancer Kim Young Woong was so good...
that I worried he might play the main lead role.
I wanted him to become the main supporting dancer...
and work with me.
I think it's going to be fun.
I'll do my best to show you a good performance.
(Ha Won Jun: Butler 1, Choi Ho Jong: Duke, Kim Young Woong: Butler 2)
Please choose the main supporting dancers on Team B.
The dancers I'm going to cast for the main supporting role...
is Dancer Ryu Tae Young.
(Ryu Tae Young takes the main supporting role for "Parasite.")
We had good teamwork when we practiced together.
I thought his looks and dance were charming.
That's why I chose him.
Please cast the next dancer.
The dancers I'm going to cast for the main supporting role...
(Choi Kyu Tae, Kim Sang Gil, and Bang Seong Hyun are left.)
Who would it be?
Sang Hyun?
Sang Gil.
It'll be Sang Gil.
Honestly, I really hoped he would call my name.
(Who is the last dancer to be picked as the main supporting dancer?)
It's Dancer Bang Seong Hyun.
(Bang Seong Hyun takes the main supporting role for "Parasite.")
(Trying not to smile)
(He made it.)
He can do various genres.
I thought he would blend in for any performance.
That's why I chose him.
Kyu Nyeon chose me as he trusted me.
So we must win no matter what.
I should work hard because he chose me.
(Ryu Tae Young: Butler 1, Kim Kyu Nyeon: Duke)
(Bang Seong Hyun: Butler 2)
I'd like to congratulate every dancer who was cast.
(You worked hard.)
I want to compete with them...
as dancers in a positive sense.
I hope Kyu Nyeon does the same.
(Ha Won Jun: Butler 1, Choi Ho Jong: Duke, Kim Young Woong: Butler 2)
(Ryu Tae Young: Butler 1, Kim Kyu Nyeon: Duke)
(Bang Seong Hyun: Butler 2)
Through this mission, there will be class movement...
and some of us will even be eliminated.
So it seems like we have to show everything we have desperately.
We're fighting regardless of the rank.
I think there are many good dancers in Under Class.
I want them to be promoted.
I was excited to see who would take the main role.
Hye Hyun already took the main lead role.
It's already taken.
If another main lead dancer is picked,
they're going to compete against each other.
Here,
you get hit. And bang.
(Like this?)
The dance is easy, but I can't do it like him.
The moves were made for Jong Cheol.
That's a big advantage for him.
It's so hard, Jong Cheol.
Those are the moves my body makes.
I was like, "If you turn like this, your body automatically follows."
But they found it difficult.
So I was like, "What? This is good for me."
As big as you can. Then here...
(But the dancers of "Oldboy" don't give up and try to follow.)
The contemporary dancers...
executed it well.
Among them, Do Hyun stood out to me.
It looked like he was dancing naturally...
based on his interpretation.
It feels like Seong Yun can do anything...
that is given to him.
But no one will be as good as me.
(I'm going to take the main lead role.)
There's none.
I thought I was the best during the practice.
If I'm not confident,
I should go home.
And kick here.
(Kim Jong Cheol continues to teach the choreography.)
I've never done disconnected moves.
So I worried I might not be able to follow.
Turn with your knee and your hands on the floor.
Ballet dancers don't really do floor techniques.
Flexible and fast moves like that...
are very difficult for ballet dancers.
I felt bad.
The mission was the most unfavorable to ballet dancers.
- I have no idea. - Seriously.
Can you teach ballet dancers separately, please?
Make the angle.
- The angle? - Yes.
(A good example)
(A bad example)
It's like...
- It's the elbow and the head. - The elbow?
Jong Cheol...
used a lot of contemporary moves.
I'm worried about how I can express that with my body.
I think we, ballet dancers, should pause here.
We can't catch up with others.
We should practice ourselves.
It must've been difficult for them...
as they're not used to those moves.
Let's do it again.
We can do it if we keep trying.
I was like, "How can they practice so much?"
They were working really hard.
They're the best when it comes to ballet.
I could see they were working hard not to look stupid.
It suddenly came to my mind.
I was just copying Jong Cheol.
"The feelings he didn't show."
"What I'm best at. I should show something like that."
(That's how Kyung Won started practicing in his own way.)
Kim Kyung Won. I like his eyes.
He was so charismatic...
that it looked like he became the character.
I thought he could take the main lead role.
My choreography was chosen.
So I think I'm likely to take the main lead role.
I can say I worked harder than the others with confidence.
If I become the main lead dancer, who should I pick?
I even thought about it.
(He's going his own way as well.)
We'll begin the casting audition for the main lead role...
in "Oldboy" for the K-Contents Mission.
(Contemporary Dance Coach Seong Chang Yong, Master Kim Joo Won)
(Kang Hyo Hyung, the choreographer of "Oldboy," Choi Soo Jin)
Only one dancer will be cast...
for the main lead role on Team "Oldboy" B who will compete...
against Hye Hyun, the main lead dancer on Team "Oldboy" A.
We'll primarily evaluate...
how engagingly you convey
the character's psychological state and the concept...
within the given time frame.
When my choreography was chosen,
I immediately thought I would take the main lead role with confidence.
No one would execute it like me.
The choreography has his distinctive moves.
So I thought it was very unfavorable to us.
"Can I do the moves?" I was worried a lot.
This isn't a matter of whether I can do it or not.
I don't care if I'm good or not. I'm going to try it.
I think I'm as good as him.
If I'm not confident,
I should go home.
I'm confident.
I'm going to call the dancers in the first group.
Dancer Shin Min Kwon, Dancer Kim Jae Jin.
Dancer Cho Tae Yoon, and Dancer Yang Seong Yun.
The casting audition for "Oldboy" will begin.
First position.
Music, start.
- I'm the best. - Four.
- Three, two. - I wanted to win, of course.
One. Go.
(Exclaiming)
I got goosebumps.
Nice.
Jae Jin is good.
Jae Jin and Seong Yun stand out.
Nice. There you go.
- Nice. - Nice.
Seong Yun is great.
I like his facial expression.
Nice.
Seong Yun is killing it.
(Agreeing)
(Exclaiming)
I like how Jae Jin is doing.
Jae Jin knows how to control his body.
Seong Yun stands out so much.
Three, two, one. Stop.
Well done.
- The others didn't stand out. - Right.
- Seong Yun was dominating. - Yes.
Seong Yun in the first group caught my eye.
The second group.
Dancer Kim Do Hyun, Dancer Jeon Tae Hu.
Dancer Ki Moo Gan, and Dancer Park Min Woo.
- Five, four. - Ki Moo Gan and Kim Do Hyun.
- Three, two, one. - I had high expectations of them.
(The second group for the casting audition for "Oldboy")
- Do Hyun. - He's good.
How is Do Hyun so good?
Do Hyun stands out.
I also like Moo Gan.
Nice.
(Impressed)
(Ki Moo Gan and Kim Do Hyun's jumps feel different.)
The jump was so good.
They're really good.
I wish Moo Gan's moves were a little bit more powerful.
It would accentuate the energy.
It's crazy.
- I like Do Hyun's moves. - He's crazy.
Everyone is crazy.
Three, two, one. Stop.
It was so good.
Do Hyun...
and Moo Gan are good.
The dancers in the third group.
(The third group for "Oldboy")
Here comes the choreographer.
Kim Jong Cheol, Kim Kyung Won, and Kim Tae Yeon.
- Five, four. - It's Jong Cheol's choreography.
- Three, two. - I'll show my dance.
- One. Go. - Then I'm going to make it.
Good.
I like Kyung Won.
He knows how to utilize his body.
Jong Cheol's dance is sensual.
He's good.
He's indeed the choreographer.
Kyung Won is also a veteran.
There you go.
I like their emotions.
It's over.
Oh, my gosh.
Jong Cheol's body lines are clear.
Kyung Won looks like he has a lot of experience on stage.
(Perfect spins)
- I like Kyung Won too. - One. Stop.
(The ending technique)
Bravo.
It was like Jong Cheol's solo performance.
Jong Cheol has become an amazing dancer.
I saw madness in Jong Cheol.
The dancers in the fourth group are Jung Sung Wook,
Choi Ji Won, and Sung Hun Mo.
- Five, four. - I should take the main lead role.
- Three, two. - I think I'll make it.
- So I'm going to do my best. - One. Go.
Sung Wook.
Sung Wook isn't bad.
I really like...
Ji Won's energy.
But he should show more.
His moves are unique.
(All eyes are on him.)
He's good.
It's light.
Sung Wook is crazy.
I like Sung Wook.
(The dance is reaching the climax.)
(The choreographer is checking.)
Nice.
- Their moves are all delicate. - Three.
- They're all delicate. - Two, one.
(The casting audition for the fourth group ends.)
Two, one. Stop.
Oh, no.
(The coaches are thinking after the audition ends.)
(You worked hard.)
- Hye Hyun. - Yes.
Who do you think is your biggest rival?
My rival?
Who will be your biggest rival if he becomes the main lead dancer?
There's none.
(Impressed)
(Smiling)
That's hip-hop.
(Who will take the main lead role on Team B and become his rival?)
Jong Cheol, your moves were unrivaled.
The character is in an extreme situation.
So I wanted to see the dancers express raw feelings.
In that sense, you expressed the feelings well.
You must've executed it well because it's your choreography,
but I was genuinely impressed.
Seong Yun, you're like a monster.
When you danced,
I couldn't think of the original choreography.
You expressed and interpreted it in your own way,
which gives it a unique energy and texture.
That's why you had a special presence.
You were one of the most impressive dancers.
I enjoyed it.
"I can execute this kind of dance very well."
There are dances that make them stand out.
I think Jae Jin and Do Hyun...
showed something like that, which was surprising.
Your expressions and movements of your bodies...
grabbed my attention.
From what I know, you were struggling on the bottom.
I think you're ready to escape the Under Class now.
(Let's escape.)
Yes. That's what I felt.
You've become an amazing dancer.
(Thank you.)
Moo Gan.
- Yes. - I always think...
you're very stable.
You're an exceptionally talented dancer,
in both your expressive abilities and execution of movements,
so I always have high expectations.
But I'm curious somehow.
Because I feel like you've been struggling.
Of course, you must be doing your best,
but I want to know how you feel.
I want to know what your mindset...
and approach toward this mission are.
(Thinking hard)
(He can't open his mouth easily.)
(Moo Gan...)
You were shining.
(What happened to Moo Gan?)
(To be continued)
I want to know what your mindset...
and approach toward this mission are.
(Thinking hard)
(Worried)
(Hesitant)
(He can't open his mouth easily.)
Actually, after doing the moves,
I'm a little disappointed in myself.
It looks like it. He could've been done better.
Participating in the audition for this mission,
I really wanted to do well for the first time.
But I haven't been able to manage my condition well.
(He participated in the audition sincerely,)
(but he's disappointed in himself as he's not feeling well.)
That's why I'm upset.
I want to do well.
I feel so bad.
(Trying to smile)
"I should do it well."
I rarely think like that.
Because I ruin it when I try to do well.
I appeared as if I was something.
But I've been struggling.
People had high expectations of me.
But I knew I wouldn't meet their expectations.
I knew I would be bad.
Their expectations weigh heavy on me.
I really wanted to do well this time.
But I knew I wasn't feeling well.
This is really annoying.
I was just so upset.
From my perspective,
you're an incredibly delicate and sensitive dancer.
So I felt that dancing with many other dancers...
was too stimulating and had a significant impact on you.
Yes.
I really want you to utilize...
your sensitivity and delicacy.
So next time,
I hope you forget about their expectations or the environment...
and dance more comfortably.
Thank you.
"I also hope I can do that." That's what I thought.
I was just so grateful.
I really liked his dance.
Goblin Ki Moo Gan, come back.
Honestly, today,
Jong Cheol expressed it so well.
- He was phenomenal. - Yes.
He executed his choreography the best.
- It can't he helped. - Right.
Based on the audition itself,
- It's him. - Seong Yun was unrivaled.
- Anyone would think that. - Actually, I also...
But it doesn't feel like he's the best for the role.
That's what makes me hesitant.
He was great in the audition, but it doesn't necessarily mean...
he suits the role or is essential for the performance.
It's a shame.
There's no way they won't cast me for the main lead role.
I thought I was the best. I think I'll win.
The casting audition for the main lead role in "Oldboy."
I'm going to announce the dancer who was cast...
for the main lead role on Team B, the one confining.
(He's also nervous.)
It's Dancer Kim Jong Cheol.
(Kim Jong Cheol takes the main lead role for "Oldboy.")
(Congratulating)
Dancer Kim Jong Cheol in First Class...
embodied the character in every aspect,
from this movements and perfect technique to the music.
Congratulations.
(Check the rest of the results on THE CHOOM.)
I've finally become the main lead dancer.
I've never played the main lead role in First Class before.
It felt great.
The Seat Class Evaluation based on the full performance...
in the K-Contents Mission...
will begin on the Mnet Plus app soon.
Please vote for their Seat Class by ticketing.
(The K-Contents Poster Shooting Mission...)
(for the dancers)
(Ideas are important.)
(Only the photo of the winning team...)
(will be on the main poster.)
(Who will earn the best benefit on the show so far?)
(After the fierce casting audition ends)
The air is so nice.
What do you think we're going to do today?
I can't make predictions.
Is it an interim review?
No.
- No way. - The crow is ominous.
What is it waiting for us today?
What is it?
- It's cool. - They're showing us something.
I guess we're going to do something.
Kang Daniel might appear out of nowhere.
What is it?
I'm Photographer Lee Se Hyeong.
It's nice to meet you.
(Known for his unconventional angles and sophisticated tones,)
(he's a renowned photographer who worked with domestic...)
(and international artists like JYP, TWICE, NCT, and ITZY.)
I'm going to give you a mission today.
There's another mission?
It's a mission again?
It's the K-Contents Poster Shooting Mission.
(K-Contents Poster Shooting Mission)
(A poster shooting?)
(Glancing)
I actually like cameras. So I was confident.
- Please help me. - We should discuss...
after washing up.
I don't have much photoshoot experience. So I wasn't confident.
It was the first mission that had fazed me.
We'll proceed with a mission...
to determine the main poster for the work...
through a competition between Team A and B,
based on how you interpret and express the character.
The winning team will receive a benefit.
The poster of the winning team will become the main poster.
And it will be posted on the online voting page...
as the main poster.
- When they press "Squid Game," - And the work...
our faces will be on the next page or not.
- That'll improve our image. - It'll give us an advantage.
Because they'll see the main poster a lot.
I can't let them take it.
The main lead dancers will have solo shots.
The main supporting dancers will have two shots.
And Team A and Team B will have group shots.
Each shot should be taken in ten minutes.
(Sighing automatically)
That's short.
It's time attack.
Let's start the mission right away.
Let's begin the Poster Shooting Mission for Team "Parasite."
(Main lead role: Choi Ho Jong)
(Main supporting role: Kim Young Woong, Ha Won Jun)
"How can we finish it in such a short time?"
I didn't know what to do. I was flustered.
(Main lead role: Kim Kyu Nyeon)
(Main supporting role: Ryu Tae Young, Bang Seong Hyun)
I thought we must win the mission...
because we need to grab people's attention.
- Please start the timer now. - Let's begin the shoot.
(The first group shot for the poster of "Parasite")
(Team "Parasite" A is checking the group shots.)
(Ho Jong is thinking while looking at the photos.)
The background stood out.
And it didn't go well with what we had prepared.
I thought it wasn't working.
(They stand diagonally.)
There are too many of you to stand in a diagonal line.
People in the second row are sitting too low.
We're in trouble. We have five minutes left.
I could tell Ho Jong's team was perplexed.
We have 2 minutes and 30 seconds. We need to take pictures now.
I saw them changing the composition at the last minute.
I thought we would win.
We have 40 seconds. Strike a pose, everyone.
(Team "Parasite" A continues with the shooting.)
Nice. It's the best one so far.
(They barely made it.)
I'm upset because it was unexpected.
- Hello. Yes. - We...
The composition...
We made it look like the ensemble was our skirt.
And Kyu Nyeon was looking at them like he was envious.
We created a triangular composition.
(Team B is shooting quickly thanks to their pre-planned composition.)
- Nice. - That's nice.
I got nervous after looking at their group shots.
Their message was delivered effectively. They did a good job.
(Park Jin Ho, the main lead dancer of "SKY Castle" starts shooting.)
There you go. It's much better with the hands.
(Veins are popping out as well.)
Good. I like it so much.
(The photographer keeps exclaiming.)
Nice. Just like that. This is cool. I really like this.
(Today, he's a prince, not a princess.)
It looks good.
I would've become a fan.
- Tell me if it's choking. - Okay.
(Yun Hyeok Jung, the main lead dancer of "SKY Castle" is shooting.)
- Good. - He...
just looks like an office worker who drank a lot yesterday.
(That was a good one, Yu Chan!)
Nice.
(Kill him!)
This is good.
That's what I'm talking about.
(Check their profiles and behind-the-scenes on Mnet Plus.)
Nice.
I like it.
It's the Poster Shooting Mission for "Squid Game."
(Main supporting role: Kim Hyun Ho, Kim Hyo Joon)
(Main supporting role: Go Dong Hoon, Kim Si Won)
(Main lead role on Team "Squid Game" A: Kang Gyeong Ho)
It's the Poster Shooting Mission for "Oldboy."
Great.
(Main lead role: Kim Hye Hyun)
Good.
This is nice. It looks like a myth.
(Please visit Mnet Plus to check the winning team.)
There you go. That's nice.
Stage Fighter on Mnet. K-Contents Mission.
Voting for the K-Contents Mission that will be reflected...
on the second Class Movement and elimination...
is now open on THE CHOOM and Mnet Plus.
You can vote for individual dancers on our official channel on YouTube,
THE CHOOM, through solo videos of the dancers.
Please vote for your favorite dancer by liking their video.
On the official platform of Stage Fighter on Mnet Plus,
you can vote for a team through full performance videos...
of the K-Contents Mission.
You can vote for a team through Seat Class Evaluation.
(How to vote for a team for the K-Contents Mission)
Watch the full performance video and vote for their Seat Class...
that suits their work by ticketing.
There are four Seat Classes.
VIP, R, S, and A.
Different scores will be added for each Seat Class.
Between Team A and Team B for each work,
which one will receive higher scores...
through the Seat Class Evaluation?
Please vote for their Seat Class by ticketing from now on.
(K-Contents Mission Evaluation: Individual voting, team voting)
(An episode with the K-Contents Poster Mission on November 5)
(Tuesday, November 12, at 10pm,)
(The K-Contents Performance Evaluation...)
(and the 2nd Class Movement Ceremony will be revealed.)
Let's begin the rehearsal.
(A rehearsal for Team "Parasite" A begins.)
Won Jun, you should go further in the back.
Won Jun, you should go that way.
(Won Jun keeps missing his position.)
(Serious)
Won Jun, you keep missing your position in the center.
When Young Woong is coming to the center,
you're the only one missing the position.
I'm nervous because of Won Jun.
I think we were nervous for one another.
(Shaking his head)
Won Jun, if you do it like this, we can't be in sync.
Honestly, I really wanted to go home.
They kept pointing it out,
but I couldn't get it together.
It was my first time to play the main supporting role,
so there was a lot of pressure.
- There you go. - That's right.
One point for Tae Young.
(The atmosphere is good, unlike Team A.)
(Team A is silent.)
The main lead and supporting dancers on our team...
will be in trouble because of me.
I'll get it together.
(What will happen to Team "Parasite" A?)
(Stage Choice by Public Mission)
- Oh, my. - What?
(What is it?)
(Stage Choice by Public Mission)
(Do you think we'll go to public places and do something?)
(Stage Choice by Public)
(The first mission where they are cast based on the public's choice)
(The first mission based on the public's choice on Stage Fighter)
(The public's choice?)
(The public will pick the main lead dancer?)
(Possessed by Matthew)
(We won't be divided into 1st, 2nd, or Under Class.)
(We'll be evaluated regardless of our class.)
(All of us are equal in front of the public.)
(The main lead dancer will make the choreography and direct it.)
(The main lead dancer will have the right to direct it!)
(- Isn't it the best benefit so far? - You suddenly get greedy, right?)
(The main lead dancers selected by the public will be revealed...)
(on Tuesday, November 12, at 10pm.)
(Impressed)
(That's sexy.)
(Dash)
(It's crazy.)
(This is what I'm talking about!)
(Salvation)
(Nightmare)
(It's right up his alley.)
(This is insane.)
(I think we're going to perform.)
(Is it a surprise performance?)
(You're invited to the recording on Sunday, November 10.)
(It's a chance to watch your favorite dancer's performance!)
(Check out the dancers' contents on Mnet Plus.)