In my opinion,
no more than fifty thousand taels.
Xiao Ning,
do you have any objections?
Let's do as Young Master Han suggests.
I'll go back and prepare the contract right away.
Is three days enough?
It's enough.
More than enough.
Master,
Xiao Ning is truly talented.
Acting so forcefully
might bring about unforeseen trouble.
Madam,
our Han family is the most prominent clan in the region.
Why should we fear someone as insignificant as Xiao Ning?
I know, Luo'er,
you're recruiting talent for the Han family.
But the Han family already has countless advisors.
For just one Xiao Ning,
it's not worth troubling yourself so much.
Master, I can't help but feel uneasy about it too.
Master.
My dear Ning'er
You finally know how to save money.
Father
You
Your luggage
It's all in the bundle, right?
I-I haven't had time to pack yet.
That's great, that's great.
Hurry, hurry.
This time, I really can't afford to provoke them.
Hurry up and go, hurry up and go.
You
Your life is more important.
Go!
I knew a leopard can't change its spots.
It's not what you think.
I'll explain to you when I have time.
Such forceful seizure
There's not a trace of a proper prime minister in them.
I'll go find them.
Han Wuguo is the prime minister.
Don't be so impulsive.
So what if he's the prime minister?
As long as they're still citizens of our country,
I absolutely won't allow them to act like this.
Do whatever they want.
You don't need to worry about the Han family either.
I promise you,
No one in the capital would dare bully you.
Of course, I keep my word.
Alright.
Truly a heroine among women.
I admire you, truly.
The tea is a golden yellow when brewed.
The cup swirls with a floral aroma.
As expected, the tea here at Your Majesty's place is delicious.
Ling Luo greets Your Highness, the Princess.
No need for formalities. Please, have a seat.
Miss Han.
Please.
This tea
comes from a tea shop among the common folk.
I've heard it has had quite an influence.
Recently, the literary style in Dajing has become more refined.
Prime Minister, are you familiar with this shop?
Isn't this Luo Qiuxian from the Tea Pavilion?
I didn't expect that Your Highness
also enjoys the tea brewed at the Tea Pavilion.
Miss Han, that's not quite correct.
It's not that I
am fond of the Tea Pavilion's tea.
Rather, this tea
belongs to me.
A simple tea shop
can actually inspire the scholars of Dajing.
To achieve this through business
is truly rare.
That's indeed the case.
So the methods you used before
must not be used on the Tea Pavilion.
Your Majesty sees everything clearly.
This Tea Pavilion
can contribute so much to our Dajing.
I believe the court should protect it.
Why would Your Highness say that?
Young Master Xiao and I simply share similar interests.
We just discussed some business together.
Why talk about using any methods?
Miss Han, there's no need to play dumb.
What Her Highness means is
your Han family
is not allowed to forcibly acquire the Tea Pavilion from now on.
Miss Qingfeng, don't be so fierce.
Since Her Highness has spoken,
as officials,
we naturally must obey.
It's just a small Tea Pavilion.
I actually don't care much about it.
What I want
is Young Master Xiao himself.
You are the young concubine of the Prime Minister's residence.
How can you say such embarrassing things?
Why is it embarrassing?
What Lingluo values is Young Master's way of doing business.
However,
someone as outstanding as Young Master Xiao—
who wouldn't want to keep him by their side?
Young Master Xiao is perceptive and wise.
He naturally knows who is truly trustworthy.
Then we
shall wait and see.
A small tea house
has actually attracted the attention of His Majesty and the princess.
It seems that Xiao Ning is highly valued.
I guess His Majesty wants to use Xiao Ning
as a pawn to break free from the influence of our noble families.
Now that he has become a royal pawn,
we can no longer forcibly take over the tea house.
All industries in Dajing
are controlled by the noble families of Dajing.
If His Majesty wants to fill the national treasury,
he has to start with these small businesses.
In my opinion, it's nothing to be afraid of.
Luo'er, you don't need to worry too much.
If a small tea house
can break through the blockade of the noble families,
and gives His Majesty confidence,
then in the future there will surely be
thousands upon thousands of tea houses appearing.
By then,
the status of our noble families
will probably be affected as well.
Luo'er, you think so far ahead.
In your opinion,
what should we do next?
To preserve the dignity of the royal family and the Han family,
we can't make a move for now.
However,
Father,
we're home.
Son,
are we really home this time?
Father, don't worry.
I've already thought of a solution.
I'll make sure you can live here in peace.
Alright.
Young master,
everything is ready.
Father, I'm going out for a bit.
Alright.
Let's go.
Finally home.
Why hasn't that boy Xiao Ning come back yet?
We told him to arrange a meeting with the owner of the Tea Pavilion.
He hasn't even sent any word.
Father, Mother.
Xiao Ning is just a servant.
He probably can't invite them at all.
The owner of the Tea Pavilion.
That's why he's too ashamed to come back.
Master.
The Tea Pavilion has posted a notice.
It says the owner of the Tea Pavilion
is inviting all the tea shop owners for tea.
Before this,
we tried several times to meet the owner of the Tea Pavilion,
but never succeeded.
This time, we've been invited to taste tea.
This is intentional.
Yes.
We don't know if today
we'll gain anything.
Right?
Let's hope so.
Master Su
Master Xu is here too.
You actually want to get tea from the Nong Tea Pavilion as well?
Let me offer you all some advice,
You are all people of status.
With the Su family here today,
I suppose
today is not your turn
to get the tea from the Nong Tea Pavilion.
Well...
You might as well leave early.
So you don't lose face.
What should we do now?
Yeah.
Look, even the top imperial merchant, the Huang family,
and the second, the Lin family, are here.
Master Huang, Master Lin.
You Su family actually dared to show up.
No matter what,
the Su family is still an imperial merchant.
Imperial merchant?
With the current state of your Su family,
you still have the nerve to call yourselves imperial merchants?
If it weren't for the Huang and Lin families
leaving you a bit to survive on,
your Su family
would have gone bankrupt long ago.
That's actually true.
Everyone knows the tea market is tough these days.
Whether any of us here can survive in this market
all depends on the Nongcha Pavilion.
Even top imperial merchants like Huang and Lin,
if we don't get the approval of Nongcha Pavilion,
our tea businesses will also go under.
So I hope everyone here
won't offend the owner of Nongcha Pavilion.
Otherwise, don't blame me, Huang,
for turning hostile.
Why should that be?
If we can't get tea from Nongcha Pavilion,
our Su family will be finished too!
Exactly.
So many people are waiting for Young Master Xiao.
Why don't you and I go greet him first?
It'll help us leave a good impression on Young Master Xiao.
That makes sense.
Please.
Let's go.
Nongcha Pavilion's business really is booming.
All three major imperial merchants are coming to them.
Sorry about that.
Sorry, everyone.
Thank you for waiting, thank you for waiting.
Well, well, Xiao Ning.
I told you to find someone,
but look at you,
hiding in Nongcha Pavilion and slacking off.
Xiao Ning, why didn't you come back to report?
This is the Su family's son-in-law.
Alright, alright, enough.
Hurry up and
bring out the owner of Nongcha Pavilion.
How dare he treat us so disrespectfully!
Our Su family is an imperial merchant!
Everyone,
the tea from Nongcha Pavilion has become extremely popular.
This has indeed caused some trouble for all of you.
So, the reason I called you all here today
is to decide to give a batch of tea
for you to sell at retail.
The profit won't be very high,
but I guarantee that for all of you,
it will be several times more than your salt tea business.
That's wonderful!
You are the owner of Nongcha Pavilion,
Young Master Xiao Ning?
You say he's the owner of Nongcha Pavilion?
Boss Sun,
are your eyes failing you in your old age?
If he were the owner of Nongcha Pavilion,
would the Su family still need to line up here?
Xiao Ning,
did you get a few people to cooperate with you
and put on a show for us?
I...
Stop making a scene.
Sorry to make everyone laugh.
Xiao Ning is the Su family's son-in-law.
He's just a servant at Nongcha Pavilion.
He's not the owner.
But we heard that the owner of Nongcha Pavilion
is indeed
a young man named Xiao Ning.
That's right.
Impossible.
Young Master Xiao.
There you are.
Mr. Huang and I have been waiting for you for so long.
That's right.
You two, please don't do this.
You're making me feel really awkward.
You—
Xiao Ning.
How dare you be so disrespectful to Mr. Huang and Mr. Lin?
Kneel and apologize to the two elders at once.
Su Mingzhuo.
How dare you show such disrespect to the owner of the Tea Pavilion?
Such insolence.
Are you trying to force the Huang and Lin families
to take action against the Su family?