This wine should only exist in heaven.
I
am momentarily at a loss for words.
Excellent wine.
Pour it.
Then I won't disturb Your Majesty's enjoyment of the wine.
I take my leave.
Summon Yun'er to see me.
I want to reward her properly.
Your Majesty,
the princess has not entered the palace today.
Speaking of which,
Yun'er hasn't returned to the palace for several days.
Could it be that she's with Xiao Ning...
No, that won't do.
This...
Young Master Yang, Young Master Yang!
I've been wanting to see you but couldn't find you.
I thought you liked Xiaoyao Spring the most.
We're offering it at a 70% discount now.
No, no.
Now that there are Yuxian and Minggong,
who still drinks Xiaoyao Spring?
Young Master Yang,
our Xiaoyao Spring tastes just as good.
And it's even cheaper.
Cheaper? Not really.
Now, Yuxian and Minggong,
a bottle only costs five taels of silver.
Compared to your discounted Xiaoyao Spring,
it's not much more expensive.
Don't you think so?
Young Master Yang,
No, no.
I knew Ning was lying to me.
So much for being friends and partners.
Could such a perfect peach blossom fortune be fake?
I didn't expect him and the owner of Yuxian Restaurant, Jiang,
to have such a wonderful connection.
Very good, very good.
In-law.
Are you calling me?
Our Ning and your family
have nothing to do with each other anymore.
I'm not your in-law.
You can't say that.
Even one day as a couple means a hundred days of kindness.
Xiao Ning was in our family
as our son-in-law for so long.
In-law, you must help us today.
Why are you looking for me?
We... we want to ask Xiao Ning
to authorize our Su family
to sell Yuxian Wine and Minggong Wine.
Your Su family is ungrateful.
And now you come to ask us for help.
How can you say that?
When Xiao Ning was with us before,
we treated him well with good food and drink.
He was the one who broke off the engagement.
He ran away from the Su residence.
How can you blame us for that?
If it weren't for your daughter
and that...
Han... Han Hongzhi, being so unclear with him,
our Ning wouldn't have ended up like this.
What do you mean by "unclear"?
Don't listen to those rumors outside.
But I heard
when Xiao Ning was running the tea house,
he and the lady owner of Yuxian Restaurant
were the ones who were really unclear.
Who's spreading rumors about Jiang Yun?
And who are you?
I'm talking about that little vixen Jiang Yun.
What does it have to do with you?
How dare you!
How dare you insult my Yun'er's reputation!
Guards!
What are you trying to do?
Master, today we're traveling in disguise.
If you need to punish the Su family,
I can go contact the Imperial Guards right away.
Forget it.
It's not the right time to make a big scene.
He's Jiang Yun's father.
Daoist Qianli is truly effective.
Mind your own business.
I am Xiao Hetai.
Xiao Ning is my son.
You are Xiao Ning's father.
Yes, Brother Jiang.
Brother.
Brother Jiang.
We don't need to argue with such a rude person.
Please, have a seat inside.
I have much to discuss with Brother Jiang.
Come, please, please.
No need to be so polite.
Let me buy you a drink.
Come, come.
Who wants to argue with you anyway?
Honestly.
Don't bother with such a rude person.
I'm so angry, so angry!
That's enough, Mother.
Yan'er.
Don't be upset.
Please.
I'm looking for your boss.
Is he in the shop?
Those wanting to meet our boss
are scheduled more than seven days out.
Who are you?
We came here especially to visit.
We're here to discuss the wine business with Young Master Xiao.
I knew you would come.
It was worth waiting so long.
So it's Boss Huang and Boss Lin.
Greetings, greetings.
If it were anyone else,
they definitely wouldn't get to see our boss.
Well...
But please, both of you, come inside.
Thank you, thank you for your trouble.
Please.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Please, you two.
Please.
Greetings, Young Master Xiao.
If you have something to say, please get to the point.
I still need to confirm the sales channels for Yuxian Wine and Minggong Wine.
Through which channels should they be sold?
Young Master Xiao,
The Lin family and I are the top two imperial merchants in Dajing.
We have many sales channels at our disposal.
If you entrust these two new wines to us,
and let us handle the sales,
you will definitely make a huge profit.
That's right.
Entrust them to you?
Last time at Wangjiang Tower,
weren't you unwilling?
Please forgive us, Young Master Xiao.
Last time, we truly didn't know that what you were selling
was Yuxian Wine and Minggong Wine.
Yes, that's right.
At that time, the Su family was also interfering.
We really didn't know the inside story.
We were deceived.
Yes, exactly.
That puts me in a difficult position.
I've already arranged most of the sales channels.
If you two join in now,
how am I supposed to explain it to the others?
It was indeed our fault last time.
Yes.
We're willing to give up twenty percent of the profits
to apologize to Young Master Xiao.
Twenty percent?
Why does this calculation not make sense to me?
Forty percent
We are absolutely sincere.
Whatever Young Master Xiao wants us to sell in the future,
we will sell it.
We will never doubt Young Master Xiao again.
That's right.
With such sincerity,
then I'll consider it again.
Then let me
explain in detail
the business layout of the Huang and Lin families.
Yes, yes, yes.
Alright.
Very good.
Come, Brother Jiang.
So, our Ning'er
not only does great business,
but is also considerate and filial.
As for our family house,
it was originally taken back by the clan leader.
He was worried that I, an old man, would have nowhere to live.
So he spent ten thousand taels of silver to buy it back for me.
What's ten thousand taels, anyway?
The money my Yun'er earns in various fields
could rival the Ministry of Revenue.
Jiang Yun's business
is all supported by our Ning'er behind the scenes.
So I say,
these two kids
are a perfect match made in heaven.
Don't you think so?
Yes, yes, that's right.
Uncle Xiao,
you've had quite a bit to drink today.
How about we...
Not much at all.
Jiang and I hit it off right away.
Just keep pouring the wine.
Qingfeng, pour the wine.
Fill it up.
Yes, sir.
Brother Jiang,
Jiang Yun and Ning'er are a perfect match.
Why don't we exchange their birth dates?
Let's pick a date and set the wedding.
Engagement?
No.
Why not?
Even Miss Qingfeng knows
that the two of them are interested in each other.
Qingfeng, do you know about this?
Qingfeng doesn't know.
Brother Jiang,
I know a place
that's perfect to visit after drinking.
I guarantee you've never seen it.
I can't believe there's still
a place in Dajing I haven't seen.
Let's go.
My lord,
let's go.
Watch your step.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Uncle Xiao,
let's go.
Slow down.
Then I'll hold on.
Hang in there.