Yun'er
You didn't come home all night yesterday.
Where did you go?
Yesterday...
I spent the night at Yuxian Pavilion yesterday.
You're acting a bit strange.
Did something happen?
No, no, nothing happened.
Yesterday, I...
All day today,
All day yesterday,
I was with Qingfeng the whole time.
Nothing happened at all.
Why is your face so red?
Could it be that you've caught a cold?
No, not at all.
I'm doing just fine.
Alright, alright.
I called you here just to ask you something.
What do you think of that Xiao Ning?
Yun'er.
I don't know.
Xiao Ning is quite nice.
What nonsense.
Your father just wants to remind you.
Xiao Ning is very scheming.
You must not let him fool you.
Xiao Ning would trick me?
Father, why do you say that?
That Xiao Ning secretly brewed a
new wine called Xiaoyao Spring.
It's supplied exclusively to the Han family's tavern.
In just a few days, it has already
earned the Han family ten thousand taels of silver.
I know about this.
You know?
Xiao Ning siding with the Han family is going against the royal family.
If you knew, why didn't you tell me?
Father, you've misunderstood.
Xiao Ning wants to use Xiaoyao Spring
to gain the Han family's trust.
Then I'll use even better wine
to completely defeat the Han family's tavern.
Xiaoyao Spring has already gained the Han family's trust.
Let them spend a few more million taels stockpiling goods.
Then I'll have Jade Nectar Dew
beat them so badly they won't know what hit them.
Everyone, stop right now.
Put it here.
Madam Su, the dining area is in the front hall.
What are you doing in the backyard?
My Su family is also the owner of Wangjiang Tower.
Is there a problem with me coming to my own backyard?
No problem, go ahead and look around.
Get to work.
What are you all doing?
He's just a hired hand.
You all have to listen to me.
Then what are your instructions, boss?
I want you to open all these jars of wine.
Add thirty percent well water to them.
This...
You're making fake wine.
The customers will find out.
And you call yourself a merchant.
Xiaoyao Spring is hard to come by these days.
If we don't find a way to sell more,
how will my Wangjiang Tower make money?
Faking things like this
will ruin the Han family's reputation.
I don't care.
Xiaoyao Spring is a strong liquor.
Add thirty percent well water to it,
and no one will be able to tell.
Add it for me.
Go ahead, add it.
Hurry up.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
You reap what you sow.
The wine in this warehouse
is supposed to be shipped to the capital.
All of Han Family's restaurants'
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Add it, add it.
Add more, more, more!
Add it.
This taste isn't right.
Xiaoyao Spring doesn't taste like this.
Where's your manager?
Hurry up and come out!
Is anyone in charge here?
Is anyone here?
Where's the shopkeeper?
Come out right now!
Dear guests, dear guests!
W-what's going on here?
We were drinking just fine.
Why are you getting angry all of a sudden?
This Xiaoyao Spring isn't right.
Did you water it down?
How is that possible?
Sir,
all our wine comes straight from the storeroom.
It's brought over directly.
There's no way it's fake.
It's not like we've never had Xiaoyao Spring before.
Do you take us for fools?
Exactly.
Yeah.
If you don't give us an explanation for this,
we'll smash up your Wangjiang Pavilion today.
That's right, we'll smash up your Wangjiang Pavilion.
No, it hasn't been watered down.
You must give us an explanation.
No.
It doesn't taste like this at all.
It must have been watered down.
How could this happen?
It's fake.
The whole storeroom of wine has been watered down.
The Han family is going to take a big loss this time.
Young Master Xiao, Young Master Xiao!
Young Master Xiao!
Something's wrong, there's trouble!
The guests downstairs are making a scene.
You'd better go take a look.
I'm only responsible for supplying the wine.
I don't handle anything else.
That's not your...
Go on, go on.
Hurry and tell Miss Han.
Master
Master, Second Madam
Something bad has happened.
Speak.
The matter of Wangjiang Restaurant diluting Xiaoyao Spring with water
has been discovered by the guests.
What?
Wangjiang Restaurant also has fake wine now.
Not a single Han family restaurant has been spared.
The Xiaoyao Spring served today
was all stock from Wangjiang Restaurant.
Could it be that Xiao Ning did this on purpose?
Xiao Ning is well-versed in the ways of business.
He personally blended this Xiaoyao Spring wine.
He couldn't possibly do something like
ruin his own reputation.
Master, it seems this wasn't done by Xiao Ning.
What else do you know?
Speak quickly.
Today I heard from the staff
that Madam Su seemed to have gone to the storeroom.
She said
she wanted to mix thirty percent well water into the wine.
Sun Hongyan.
It must be that Xiaoyao Spring is too popular,
so she came up with this dirty trick.
She wanted to gain even more profit.
How could she meddle with the wine of my Wangjiang Tower?
Yes.
Young Master gave the profits of Wangjiang Tower
to the Su family.
So she is also an owner of Wangjiang Tower.
What nonsense!
The Su family was meant to be used against Xiao Ning.
What exactly did that unfilial son say to the Su family?
Where is he?
Young Master.
Young Master went to the Su family.
Could it be that he really wants to
marry that Su Xueyan and bring her into the household?
Tell him to get back here immediately!
Master, please don't be angry.
The most urgent matter
is still to resolve the issue of the fake wine.
Luo'er, I'll have to trouble you with this matter.
Go.
Find Hongzhi.
Tell him to go to Wangjiang Tower at once.
He should learn the ways of business properly.
Yes.
Tell us how you're going to handle this.
Give us an explanation.
I understand.
This Xiaoyao Spring was highly recommended by Xiao Ning.
He must be behind this.
Where is Xiao Ning?
Xiao Ning!
Come out here right now!
Xiao Ning, get out here!
Xiao Ning! Xiao Ning!
Xiao—
What are you doing?
That's Xiao Ning.
You won't even let people sleep.
Xiao Ning.
Xiaoyao Spring costs ten taels of silver per jug,
and you dare to dilute it with water to sell?
Are you that obsessed with money?
Exactly!
Selling fake wine to fool people—
I, Xiao, truly look down on such things.
If you want a refund, talk to the owner here.
What does this have to do with me?
You—
If there's any problem, let me handle it.
Greetings, Miss Han.
This matter is indeed the fault of the Han family.
I will immediately refund everyone's money for the wine.
Here.
How much?
One jug.
That's great.
Here you go.
Two jugs.
Alright.
Thank you.
This is yours.
Thank you, Miss Han.
Thank you, thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Two jugs.
Alright.
Here.
Thank you, Miss Han.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Thank you, Miss Han.
It's still Miss Han.
Otherwise, we'd lose another ten taels of silver.
Miss Han...
Th-this...
About the fake wine incident,
That was done by Xiao Ning.
He should take full responsibility for this.
Young Master Xiao, do you have anything to say?
If I say I did it,
would you believe me?