(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
The ledger.
(Episode 14)
I have it.
All of it.
Come and...
clean this up for me.
The director.
He's dead.
As of today, I realized who the president was.
(Hyeseung Hospital)
Congratulations. You found the place.
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
I should be saying that.
This is...
Aren't you looking for the president?
The person...
who established Jeokmok and made you director.
Yes.
President Ji Seung Don.
He just lent his name.
He was a good guy.
His flaw was that he was too trusting.
Then you...
You're...
It was you?
Why come all the way here to back out?
What was the plan?
Weren't you going to kill the president and replace him?
I was frustrated.
I wanted a frank conversation.
Leader to leader.
I'm closing down the foundation.
There's no reason to keep it going.
You have 24 hours.
Run away.
Jay that punk is the president.
Now I must run.
Because I know his identity,
and he knows I was looking into him.
I could lust for more...
and end up losing my life.
(Da Jung)
(I'm outside. Na Sa will be there. See you in the afternoon.)
(Jay that punk is the president.)
Hey.
"Jay that punk is the president."
Is this...
It says Jay's the president. Is he?
We must find Ring Go first.
- We're back. - The car.
The car. Get the car!
What's going on?
Is this it?
There's not much.
Were you bluffing?
Or was it meant to be a surprise?
Why didn't you tell me?
For ten years.
Because it didn't matter...
between us.
It won't change anything.
That you're the president.
You didn't tell me either.
What would I get from showing I knew?
I covered it up,
for your sake.
For our sake.
Because...
I just need you.
Okay.
Believe that.
There's a suitcase in a locker at the airport.
You'll find a map and phone inside.
Go and wait.
Only spend cash.
Did you hear me?
Hurry.
Before a travel ban's issued.
Mr. Kang.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Moo Young.
What's this about?
I can't find your dad.
(Danger, Do Not Enter)
Please spare my life.
Spare me. Don't kill me.
What do you mean you can't find Dad?
I should've told you sooner.
What's going on?
I think something happened to him.
What?
Spare me, please.
Spare me.
Please spare my life.
No!
Hurry up and take a photo.
Go on.
Make sure you get everything.
Darn it.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Please spare me.
A month ago,
you appeared on TV...
as the lawyer of the Geumseong killer.
Your dad saw and came to me.
He'd given me some cash long ago,
and he wanted to tell me about it.
I should've...
told you about it then.
What money did Dad give you?
When you got into law school.
Your tuition.
My tuition?
You said it was a scholarship.
Back then,
he said you wouldn't accept it if I told you it was from him.
I should've asked him where he suddenly got...
such a huge amount of money.
There was no way he could've earned that money in a lawful manner.
Okay, so?
What about the money?
Where did he get the money?
I found out a month ago...
that he got the money in return for killing someone.
Please don't kill me.
Please spare me.
(Han Jae Seok)
- Say something! - What will you do?
- Do something! - Let go!
- Say something! - How will you fix this?
What did you say?
He got paid for killing someone?
I became a lawyer with the money...
that my father received in return for killing someone?
Moo Young.
What on earth are you talking about?
Who?
Who's the person he killed?
Who was killed?
What money? And how was it received?
The case that happened in Geumseong.
That murder in Geumseong.
He was one of the culprits in the murder of Lee Ro Um's parents.
Your father.
So we were just like gig workers. Shin Ki Ho and I.
Oh, there was someone else.
It was someone I had never met before.
- He's a ghost. - A "ghost?"
That's what Jeokmok calls their disposable workers.
They pick people who have hit rock bottom.
Their known weaknesses make them easy to manipulate.
Having nothing to lose makes them bold,
and more than anything, they're easily swayed by money.
He killed Ro Um's parents?
Here, wear this.
- Come on! - Yes, sir.
Wear this. Hurry.
What are you waiting for?
That's why your father came to see me.
He didn't get involved knowing what it was about.
He said he had no idea that he'd had to kill someone.
However, he did commit a crime,
so he decided to turn himself in.
He said he'd see you for one last time and go to the police with me.
But I couldn't reach him for the past few days, so I went to see him.
He left a note, saying he'd hate to cause trouble for you...
Hey, Moo Young.
(Slide to answer)
Did you like the gift?
Was it you?
Why? Did you think it wouldn't be me?
Did you trust me?
You...
Where are you now?
Open the gift first.
What are you doing?
The man in front of you...
killed your parents for 10,000 dollars.
Han Moo Young's father.
I know you wanted to find the last remaining ghost.
Stop talking nonsense.
I was...
There's a correct order for everything, including revenge.
You can't skip the middle step and go after the president.
I still have your gun,
so I'll help you.
Cut the gibberish.
Show yourself, and we'll talk.
Don't you worry. You'll see me very soon.
You know, Ring Go is here too.
He's lost a lot of blood.
He probably can't even speak Korean now, let alone other languages.
Where are you?
Where are you now?
Don't get worked up, Ro Um.
Enjoy.
You were always Ro Um's weakness, even when we were young.
How should I put this?
Shall I say she never hides her weaknesses?
Back then, I hated it.
But now, it's the reason I must spare you.
I'm hoping this imparts a message to her.
Every living thing will continue...
to be Ro Um's weakness.
Why isn't it moving? It's making me nervous.
The call cannot be connected. Please leave a message...
Ro Um isn't picking up.
Mr. Han isn't picking up either.
What are they doing? I'm so worried.
Gosh. This is driving me nuts.
Hey, does this even make sense to you?
Can you believe it? How could Jay be...
I had no idea.
Hey, Ro Um. Where are you?
Lee Ro Um!
Do you have Ring Go's location?
His watch was pinged in Geumseong, so we're headed there now.
Ro Um, that orphan. We found Jay in that photo.
And the photo of the note Ring Go sent says that Jay is the president.
Ring Go said he was going to meet Jay.
What should we do, Ro Um?
Ro Um.
First, go there and look for him.
And call the police.
Where are you?
Stay with the others. Don't go anywhere alone.
Take me to the president.
I don't think we can catch your flight.
The quality of the products was deemed impossible to be sold...
Just get to the airport.
Breaking news.
A special investigative squad of Navisgate will be formed...
at the Central Prosecutors' Office tomorrow morning.
The leader of this squad is...
likely to be Prosecutor Ryu Jae Hyuk...
who was once in the Criminal Trial Division.
Prosecutor Ryu had been...
investigating Navis Well-being by himself,
and discovered their plans of stock manipulation.
Though he's a junior prosecutor,
he's expected to help the prosecution...
that's being doubted of affiliating with Navis.
("Special Investigation Team Launched for Navisgate")
("Prosecutor Ryu Jae Hyuk Will Be Appointed to Lead the Team")
- Hello? - Hello, mister.
Are you really coming to join the Navis investigative team?
Yes, I arrived today.
The universe is helping.
A lot of things have happened to us.
I'm on a business trip, and...
You've been working on that this whole time?
Of course.
I didn't want to get into your head...
when you were just sent to the countryside,
so I kept you in the dark on purpose.
Did you get in touch with Mr. Han?
No.
Then, I'll help you catch up.
First off, I have left my company.
Were you fired too?
No, I wasn't fired.
Was anyone else fired?
It was an industrial disaster.
And I was willing to risk my job, anyway.
I have to go.
Let's have a drink later.
Wait, Mr. Ryu.
Navis is...
(To Do Errand Center)
It's his watch.
So, is this Hae Dong's blood?
How come he bled so much?
Does this mean that he's dead?
- Guys. - Hi, we're...
at 310, Taeseong-Gu, Geumseong.
I'd like to report a missing person.
Hae Dong!
Where are you?
- Su Ho. - What?
It's nearby.
Hyeseung Hospital.
The place that An Chae Hong said he saw Jay, the president.
Right.
- Tell us the address. - Right.
I saw that you let Han Jae Seok live.
We can talk after you send Ring Go back.
He won't die.
We have a lot to catch up on.
Send Ring Go back!
Why are you so mad?
No!
Should I kill him, so he won't get in the way?
Why did you let Han Jae Seok live?
Because of Han Moo Young?
Do you like him that much? Does he treat you well?
I didn't expect you to respond to such a thing.
Though we've been apart for ten years,
it feels weird every time I see your unexpected sides.
I'm...
going to kill you.
You can't.
You've become too soft-hearted.
What do you know?
Just because some parts of my information changed,
that doesn't mean our whole history disappears.
We go back years, don't we?
Why don't we start with the day that we first met?
October 22, 2002.
The day I decided to save you.
Ro Um, you seem nervous.
Yes, that's natural.
Now, please repeat the information, Ro Um.
To add value to our scholarship project,
I thought that a prodigy wouldn't hurt.
So I went there as I was curious, and you happened...
to make a mistake that day.
Let's take a break, guys!
Take five! Stop filming.
That didn't surprise me, though. You were only a kid.
But...
("Surprise 100")
You came back.
And you finished the shoot...
without a single mistake.
You were even smiling as if nothing had happened.
That's when I knew...
that you'd be my family if there even was one.
We were both born in a ditch...
and abandoned by the world.
But we're the type of people to dominate it in the end.
What makes you think I was born in a ditch?
You were performing at nightclubs at the age of nine.
You couldn't even go to school,
and you didn't have time to eat or sleep.
You had eight shows a day at the maximum,
including the ones in the countryside.
You put makeup on,
took photos with them, and played cute tricks.
Just like a clown.
You wanted someone to save you, anyway.
Also,
I didn't exactly kidnap you, Ro Um.
Your parents sold you for money.
Why?
Because your value was about to diminish.
They were foolish and short-sighted.
I said I'd do it.
They only respected your opinion?
It's only reasonable...
to take advantage of your skills when they have value.
Your psychological tests...
consistently showed one emotion.
Deep-rooted, cold anger toward your parents!
So what?
So what's your point?
Are you trying to say that you saved me?
You were trying to go back to that ditch.
(Messages)
(I'm sorry, but we need to talk.)
(I know where you are. I'm in the hallway.)
How did you know I was here?
Don't worry.
The director doesn't know about you two.
I just...
wanted to tell you that I knew.
I'll pretend that I don't know,
so I want you to pretend ignorance...
when I leave.
- You're leaving? - I'm going back.
What's the problem?
I believed that we both thought we were family.
Why would you return to your parents who's done nothing for you?
Maybe I have low expectations.
You were going the wrong way. I had to set you on the right path.
That's what a true family does.
It worked, didn't it?
Since then, for ten years, you focused only on me,
dreamed only of me, and lived for me.
The moment you came back to me.
It was such a thrilling thought.
I'm always on your side, Ro Um.
Only I am.
Now tell me.
Do you still think you have somewhere to go back to?
Then I'll destroy them one by one.
I don't expect you to think for yourself.
If need be, I will intervene.
What do you want?
Kyung Ja won't be able to leave the country.
Plan B is to stow away via Busan.
There's a temp agency.
You'll see her there in a few days.
While I handle Navis,
go beyond the point of no return.
You are...
a real scumbag.
You'll be the face of the next project.
You and Kyung Ja can't coexist.
Can you get along?
That woman was willing to risk her life...
to save you.
I have a fierce survival instinct.
No one protects me.
Stay alert.
I'll be watching.
The investigation is going nowhere due to the suspects' schedules,
and Prosecutor Ryu Jae Hyuk who's heading the investigation...
told the press of his plans.
Arrest warrants were issued for Navis Well-being's CEO Jang...
and three other executives.
The second search and seizure,
based on information found during the first search...
will include digital devices and financial institutions.
Jang Kyung Ja is currently on the run...
and a BOLO was issued.
She's banned from leaving the country,
so we're working hard with the goal of apprehending her...
in the near future.
Jang Kyung Ja was Navis Well-being's...
Ring Go! Ring Go is here.
Call for help.
Hae Dong.
Hello?
We're at 27, Taeseong-Gu, Geumseong.
- Someone's badly hurt. - Are you okay?
Yes, get here quickly.
Yes.
Hae Dong.
Hae Dong, let's go.
Let's get you to a hospital.
Another one can join us.
There's room for one more.
You should go. I'll take the van.
You're hurt too.
- It's not my blood. - Jung Da Jung.
See you at the hospital.
Bring her straight to the hospital.
- Okay. - Stay right behind us.
(Ambulance)
Get in.
Dear Almighty. Buddha. Whatever else.
Hae Dong.
Hang in there.
Hae Dong. Fight for us.
Hae Dong.
Hae Dong. Hang on.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there, okay?
Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
(Daesan University Hospital)
(Restricted Area)
Moo Young, are you all right?
Find my dad first.
Your dad.
He's here.
(Operating Room)
Why does he need a transfusion?
My brother's in there, so he'll be fine.
You shouldn't have let Ro Um go.
Sorry.
She said she had to make a stop.
She said she'd be right back. Sorry.
I'm not blaming you.
- Na Sa. - What?
I'll drop by the comic book store.
What for? Stay here.
Ro Um will look for us.
Can you reach the lawyer?
I texted him where we are.
Fill him in if he comes over.
Tell him what?
That Jay's the president.
Let's accept it. So we can get him.
(Restricted Area)
Okay, go ahead.
Yoo Neung, go with her. I'll stay.
Okay.
(Emergency Room)
Was it really you?
The Geumseong murder.
Tell me yourself.
Was it you?
I was going to turn myself in.
Then why did you disappear?
You didn't want to turn yourself in.
I tried to forgive you.
To meet you...
and see if I could find one thing worth understanding you for.
I don't care now.
What did you expect when you took that money?
Will you forgive me? Forgive me.
I'm not the person you should be begging.
I apologized to her too.
I did.
What do you mean?
You met Ro Um?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I didn't know...
what I'd have to do.
I just needed the money.
Did you ever...
regret it?
Regret it?
I did.
I hope...
you tell your son that.
She saved my life.
(Emergency Room)
Where did she go?
(Ko Yo Han, Jung Da Jung)
(Jung Da Jung: I can't reach you.)
(Where are you? Ring Go's badly hurt.)
(We're going to Sangjin Hospital. Call me.)
(Lee Ro Um)
Ro Um, where are you?
Why do you ask?
Why do you ask, Mr. Han?
Put her on the phone.
Ro Um is busy.
And she'll continue to be very busy.
Where is Ro Um?
Oh, did you know?
Han Jae Seok is the last remaining ghost.
Hello?
Han Jae Seok is your father, right?
How do you know this?
I only found out recently too.
And I swear, I didn't deliberately set it up like this.
How would I have known ten years ago that you'd get involved?
I never expected this.
Was it you?
Me? What?
Are you the president?
I guess it's your fault...
that Ro Um has turned into such a softie.
I worked hard to train her, and you ruined everything.
- Where are you now? - Why?
Now, you want to see me?
Where are you?
What could you even do if I told you where I was?
I asked you...
if you'd be able to kill someone for Ro Um.
It's so amusing, isn't it?
The fact that your father killed Ro Um's parents.
He sure chose a different path than his son.
Sacrificing his morals for greed.
"Amusing?"
You think this is "amusing?"
You took in innocent kids,
turned them into criminals, and committed fraud,
then even turned the victims into assailants.
You think you can get away with this...
because you don't have blood on your own hands?
Do you think it's over?
Now, in Ro Um's eyes, we're equally bad.
The only difference is...
that you're acting like a victim.
Don't run your mouth like that, or I'll rip your lips off.
I didn't know you could say stuff like that, Attorney Han Moo Young.
I do want to see the look on your face right now.
If Ro Um is hurt,
I will kill you.
I don't buy that.
Do you think I spared Ring Go by mistake?
The kids are mine,
and Jeokmok is my world.
My toy. My plaything.
As long as I'm alive,
this won't change.
It was fun knowing you, Han Moo Young.
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message...
I think someone went through these drawers.
I guess Ro Um was here.
Can you see what's missing?
Okay.
(Sanjeong)
Ro Um.
Hello?
Hi.
Where are you now?
How's Ring Go?
His surgery went well.
They've moved him to the recovery room.
Where are you now?
This is an announcement.
So his surgery was a success?
All passengers for Train 9787 bound for Sosan,
- please come to the platform now. - His surgery went well.
- This is an announcement. - Why weren't you at the hospital?
All passengers...
- for Train 9787 bound for Sosan... - I'm sorry for everything.
Why are you saying that?
Seriously, where are you?
Da Jung.
I'll...
put an end to this. I must.
Ro Um, I'll do whatever I can.
So first...
(Train to Sosan)
The call cannot be connected. Please leave a message...
- Yes, Mr. Han. - Hello, Da Jung.
Can you trace Ro Um's location?
Her phone turned off just now.
She took a different phone.
I talked to her just now and confirmed it.
She's at Sanjeong Station now.
I'll send you the number.
The call cannot be connected. Please leave a message...
(Sanjeong)
Ro Um.
Where are you?
Ro Um, I'm sorry.
I meddled in your life when I knew nothing.
It was reckless of me.
Whatever it is that you're trying to do now...
Don't go alone.
I'll take responsibility. Okay?
Ro Um.
Please, Ro Um. Please!
I listened to you, and I think it has only made me weaker.
Even weaker than when I was all alone and had nothing but a gun.
Ro Um.
I was wrong.
I must kill the president with my own hands.
Only then can we put an end to this.
Yes.
You're right, Ro Um.
Do that.
Or I'll die.
Ro Um.
This can't end in any other way.
Yes.
Mr. Ryu, I saw the news.
We found the last page of the notebook.
Jay, the head of Security at Navis Well-being,
is the president.
He shot Ring Go.
Did you report this to the police?
Yes, we did. And Ring Go underwent surgery earlier.
I'll send you all the info I gathered on Jay through Jeokmok,
as well as all the data I collected through Navis' network.
- He used the name, Ji Seung Don... - Da Jung.
I'm investigating Navis Well-being, not Jeokmok.
I can't share the details with you,
but we have no evidence to believe the head of Security was involved.
Besides, such evidence could be problematic.
Especially the kind of evidence that you collected.
I understand how you feel, Da Jung.
But to properly investigate this,
I must follow the rules and proper procedures.
If you'd like to share any information with us,
please contact the investigation team.
We'll go over your request according to the rules.
It took place in 2012?
Yes.
Sir.
Are you saying you're the real culprit of the case?
Yes, it was me.
I'm sorry.
The murder that took place in Geumseong in 2012.
Initially, the daughter was falsely convicted,
and the real culprit was caught last year.
There are three perpetrators.
Mr. Han Jae Seok is the only survivor for now.
Who are you, by the way?
I can be questioned by myself.
I'll tell you everything.
I'm Mr. Han's lawyer.
You can talk to me instead.
(Sangjin University Hospital)
(Intensive Care Unit)
Su Ho.
You're here.
We can't visit him yet.
I can't imagine how bad it is.
He said that he'd go and get the lighter from Jay.
He thought that Kyung Ja put the backup of the notebook...
in it.
I told him about it.
And I got him the copy of the lighter.
I sent him to the president on a silver platter.
Hae Dong.
What if he dies?
And what if Ro Um doesn't recover?
My toy. My plaything.
Mr. Ryu says he won't be able to see you for now.
Sure.
(Prosecutors' Office)
So, this is what Jeokmok is.
I checked the security footage of the trains that departed...
at that time and where they stopped.
But I can't find where they are.
I got the messenger's face near the abandoned building.
They probably drove an unregistered car,
and I put it on the wanted list.
What about Jay?
The phone he had used was a burner phone.
He's already dumped it.
He has a phone under his name,
but it stays off, so I can't track him with that.
What's the connection with Ji Seung Don?
Mr. Ji has regularly supported the orphanage since 1991.
Jay went to high school on a judo scholarship,
and he quit...
to be Mr. Ji's personal assistant.
It seems like he's been able...
to control Mr. Ji naturally since then.
I know Mr. Ryu is working hard,
but it's a bit frustrating to hear about it...
from the news.
I wonder if he's connecting the dots.
Post the messenger's photo online.
Tell them that he's a contract killer...
and charged with attempted murder.
Attorney Ryu Jae Hyuk, the leader of Navisgate Special Investigations,
has announced the first investigation result.
We've secured a testament...
proving that Ms. Jang ordered the stock price manipulation.
Some of the criminal proceeds were...
transferred to the bank account of Ms. Jang's cousin.
Recently, Lee,
who was imprisoned for murder,
confessed to his crimes while voluntarily returning...
the cash that Ms. Jang paid him for his help.
Judging from these, she's likely to have committed major crimes too.
Starting this moment,
Ms. Jang Kyung Ja, the accused of fraud,
is wanted for fraud,
violation of the Capital Market Act, and aiding and abetting a murder.
The special investigative team suspects...
that some executives of Navis have helped Ms. Jang escape...
I asked Professor Shin if she knew anything, and she said no.
I'm sorry.
Please put Ro Um on the wanted list.
You have the authority to put her on the wanted list...
when she's unreachable and can't be located.
Put her on the wanted list.
The call cannot be connected.
What are you doing here?
I wasn't sure you'd come.
But you did.
Who were you expecting? Jay?
The president?
You got what you wanted. Why did you come here?
I was wondering where that went. You had it all along?
That punk gave it to me to kill you with it.
You're lying.
Do you still believe...
that you have a future with him?
Don't you watch the news?
You're the president to the people of Korea.
What makes you think he's so powerless...
that he'll just watch that?
You know nothing!
If I don't, he'll kill you.
He can't.
When I'm dead, it'll put Jay in danger as well.
Did you think I'd let them kill me that easily?
I won't go down alone.
I'll be more than grateful if you manage to kill him.
Don't use Jay as an excuse.
It's what you wanted, isn't it?
You've been dying to kill me.
How thrilled are you to be in this moment?
No.
There are people...
I want to protect even if it means going this far.
Did you investigate Jay?
You know that I can't tell you anything about the investigation.
He's Jang Kyung Ja's lover. You must've investigated him.
- Mr. Han. - Ro Um has gone missing.
Mr. Han!
Ring Go, who you also saw,
was shot.
He's still in a coma.
You've heard about that too, right?
What Da Jung told you,
what materials she promised to send,
and how you rejected her. They told me all about it.
Even the reason I rejected it?
Why on earth did you reject it?
I can no longer work with you.
If people find out about the time I went beyond the law,
my investigation will not be justified.
That's your reason?
Is just catching them enough?
You said so yourself. That you'd go by the law.
It's not like you'll personally punish them.
While we follow the legal procedure,
people die.
So, we just ignore due process and judge them first?
You have no idea what kind of person he is.
He manipulates people to kill other people,
yet he bears no guilt or responsibility.
As we try to follow due process,
he slips out again and finds another victim.
As if he's playing a game!
Mr. Han.
That's enough.
Okay? Just stop.
How can I stop when nothing is solved?
I doubt that this is the way to solve it.
You're going to cross the line at this rate.
All right, then.
You can stop.
If crossing the line is what it takes to solve it,
I will gladly do so.
It's okay. As long as you're alive.
Mr. Han, Ro Um is back.
She says she's going to Ring Go's hospital.
The corporation provided the members...
with the annual membership of receiving...
its newly-released products at a discount of 30 percent.
As the service went on, the firm forced...
middle management...
Ro Um.
To buy its products every month.
Yesterday, their products...
Why don't we talk outside?
Have been analysed,
and the results are shocking.
The membership fee that they claimed...
turned out to be...
Are you all right?
Where have you been?
You said you'd defend me, right?
You said...
that you'd be there for me when I finished this job.
I did.
No matter what crimes I committed?
No matter what.
When I first got started,
I wanted to see my parents' killers...
suffer in anguish.
Enough that they wanted to die...
because they couldn't wake from their nightmares.
Do you get that?
I do.
Do you promise...
to defend me?
I promise.
Okay, then.
That'll do.
Lee Ro Um.
Surrender.
Breaking news.
Police identified a woman in her 40s who was found dead...
in a temp agency office in Busan.
It was Navis Well-being's CEO Jang Kyung Ja...
who was wanted for fraud and conspiracy of murder.
With Jang found dead,
the public are criticizing prosecution...
for possibly losing the chance...
to indict anyone for the billion-dollar fraud charge.
Police suspect Jang's death was a murder...
and identified a suspect based on evidence...
found at the scene, as well as witness statements.
Lee Ro Um, you are under arrest for Jang Kyung Ja's murder.
(Delightfully Deceitful)
Did you kill her, Ms. Lee Ro Um?
You want to put me away, don't you?
Is there proof against it?
Bring it to me, then.
I'll find you that proof.
Jay is really going to take Ro Um this time.
When Ro Um gets out,
I want her to not have a choice.
An article will go out tomorrow...
that says Han Jae Seok is your father.
I can't keep my promise to defend you.
I lose again, then.
I'm going to break you out of the Prosecutors' Office.