*[Love Scenery]
*[Episode 10]
*[Beautiful Soul]
Where is she?
She went offline.
Let it go, sir.
You have to forgive her, of course.
Get lost.
[Hello, Lu Jing.]
[Are you still online?]
[Hello?]
[Lu Jing.]
He's there.
But why isn't he talking?
Are you there, Lu Jing?
[Can you hear me?]
[Lu Jing.]
[I'm back.]
[Why aren't you saying anything?]
[Can you hear me?]
[I'm Little Box.]
Lu Jing.
Hi, I've entered.
I finally get to set off the fireworks!
Awesome! Cool!
Junior?
I graduated from Nanze University too.
[Are you from the 2013 batch?]
How did you know that?
[Because the university showed]
[a shockingly low passing score
that year.]
[Let's try the new DLC out.]
Okay.
Garden of Repose,
Zone A, Nanze University.
8A417.
To be received by Lu Jing.
Lu Jing.
Are you stupefied?
[Can you hear me, Lu Jing?]
[Are you there?]
I am.
What happened just now?
Nothing.
I got disconnected.
[Looks like he isn't mad.]
Then,
let's go online?
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Lu Jing.
Who said that he wouldn't
guide her anymore yesterday?
Are you alright, Lu Jing?
Put it on.
You don't want this helmet anymore?
It's not really useful on me.
You put it on.
Okay.
Do you still want the backpack?
Yes, of course. Give it to me.
I'll use it now.
Watch out. There are grenades...
[Are you alright?]
Why did you blow yourself up
like I did?
Let's go again.
Look.
Why aren't you opening the boxes?
Okay.
Don't you want the bullets?
I do.
The secret hole has been sealed.
Has the system recovered?
I...
Lu Jing, what's wrong?
Lu Jing.
Lu Jing!
Sorry, I got distracted.
What is it?
I have something else to do.
I'm getting offline.
Let's play again next time.
[Hold on.]
What is it?
Well...
Who did you
team up with last night?
A friend of mine.
I couldn't reject him.
I'm sorry I stood you up.
It's okay.
I'm leaving, then.
Okay.
Bye.
Stop smiling. Time to eat.
Ms Liang, get changed.
We need to go now.
Coming.
You got poisoned?
I think
that I'm blind.
Don't you think you're also deaf?
Little Deaf and Blind.
I told you.
Follow me and you'll find the exit.
Bad players like you
are usually lucky.
Get down here.
No, it's too high.
Get down or I'll shoot.
Check for me. I can't see it.
Okay.
What was that for?
Why did you do that?
-Tidy yourself up.
-What is it?
Didn't you say to check on it?
I recorded a video.
Do you want to watch it?
What video is that?
[Help!]
I'm saving your zig-zag runs.
[What have I done to Liang Chen?]
[I'm done for.]
I think you really are sick, Lu Jing.
Let me take you to the hospital.
When is the anniversary celebration again?
It's on Saturday.
Who will present the bouquet with Qi Qi?
Didn't you reject them?
Tell me. Who did they choose in the end?
Gu Fei Ming.
Shoot.
What now?
Gu Fei Ming?
What is it?
Now you regret it?
[Xiao Huan, Lu Jing]
[seems to be really good at the game.]
They're professionals, after all.
Xiao Huan,
do you want to do the task with me?
No.
The tasks in that game are too difficult.
Okay. I'll do it myself.
*[Beautiful Soul]
This won't do.
Get someone to teach you.
I wanted to ask Lu Jing to guide me.
But he's hiding from me.
What about Gu Fei Ming?
He...
Forget it. Not him.
Hurry. Steady.
You can't face him head on.
Go right.
Someone's on the left.
-Right.
-Left.
-Shut up.
-Right.
-Left.
-I said left.
-Right.
-You're dying. Go left.
Left.
-Left.
-Right.
What's wrong with you?
You got pregnant from completing a task?
I... I have 3D sickness.
3D sickness?
3D sickness.
What's wrong, Qi Qi?
Beautiful Soul is driving me crazy.
Its tasks are so difficult.
Yeah.
What's so interesting about those tasks?
Stupid program.
It wasted my youth and money.
You agree with me?
Do you know how to play the game?
I...
I do.
Can you guide me?
No?
No problem.
Thanks.
It feels like a celebration already.
Hold them for me.
I have something to attend to.
Where are you going?
Looking for Gu Fei Ming.
Excuse me.
Are you here for Gu Fei Ming?
-Yes. Is he in his room?
-Yes.
Wait here.
Stay here. Wait for me.
Gu Fei Ming!
Lu Jing is looking for you.
Gu Fei Ming.
Come out here, Gu Fei Ming!
Lu Jing is here for you.
Gu Fei Ming, come out.
Lu Jing is looking for you.
Who?
Lu Jing.
How do I look?
Like Daniel Wu of Nanze University.
Go, go, go.
Tell me. What is it?
Can we talk somewhere else?
No.
Just settle it here.
Fine. I won't beat around the bush.
I was asked to present flowers
to Liang Chen on the celebration concert.
But I rejected due to personal reasons.
Now I regret it.
So I wanted to discuss with you.
Not a chance.
Who do you think you are?
You rejected when you feel like it,
and now I have to quit
because you changed your mind?
I'm not that selfish.
That's why I came here to talk.
No way.
I need to ask my girlfriend's opinion.
But you don't have a girlfriend.
Yeah.
That's why there's no room for discussion.
There's a change in tomorrow's plan.
Meeting at office at 10 a.m.
Fixing the details
of live streaming at two.
Recording starts at 7.30 p.m.
Ms Qing, are you going to wear me off?
Don't worry. Your hair is still there.
The university's anniversary celebration
is not in the schedule?
It's on Saturday.
And the rehearsal?
There's no time for that.
We're not joining.
He Ye. Why did you keep this?
It stinks. Smell it.
Why won't you move?
Don't tell me you're broken.
Friendly reminder.
Lu Jing is on his way back.
All the best, guys.
Lu Xiu.
Lu Xiu, wake up.
Wake up, Lu Xiu.
Lu Jing is back.
Don't look.
Don't you know it needs charging?
Cha...charging?
Lu Jing, look at you.
Did you fail?
When did you buy this?
Why don't I know about it?
Which colour suits my mum best?
Blue. It looks elegant.
But my mum is a young girl at heart.
Orange looks shallow.
It's not for a mature, middle-aged lady.
I'll take this.
Please come with me.
Lu Jing.
Who told me that orange looks shallow?
You're taking advantage
of my adoration for you.
Jing, please tell me.
How are things going on
between you and Box Spirit?
What Box Spirit?
What's going on?
Something fishy?
Are you curious?
Let me tell you the story
of Lu Jing's cyber love.
It was really intense.
And it started
before we went to Guangzhou.
[Are you joining the rehearsal
tomorrow night?]
[Are you going?]
[Of course I am.]
[I'll be there too.]
Look at that lewd smile.
Did Gu Fei Ming agree to step down?
No.
Why were you smiling then?
Do you think I can't handle Gu Fei Ming?
Ms Liang, time to go.
Come on.
Ms Liang,
you've been studying the schedule for long.
Is something wrong?
Adjust the time of recording
to 7 a.m. tomorrow.
Then we'll have to leave before dawn.
I reckon today's filming
won't end before midnight.
Don't you need to sleep?
Just do as I say.
Thanks.
[Will I see Lu Jing tomorrow?]
Xiao Ming.
Was this the book?
I'll borrow it for you.
No. I can do that myself.
Tally these up.
Hi. It's RMB55.
What else do you want? I'll buy for you.
Never mind.
I can afford it.
Here you go. You didn't have lunch.
I'm too tired to eat.
No thanks.
That won't do.
At least drink the soup.
Or you can't last till tonight.
You're right.
I don't need the spoon.
Let's do the task later.
Oh, no.
I have a basketball match.
You...
Didn't you say you were free?
Sorry. I forgot.
Or you don't want to guide me?
Nothing like that.
Next time. When I'm free,
I'll guide you.
Let's go.
Hurry.
It must start with high spirits.
Get everyone in the mood.
*[70th anniversary of Nanze University]
-Okay.
-Practise more, okay?
Come on. Turn on the stage lights.
Quick.
Hurry up and lay the carpet.
The two flowers,
place them at the centre of the table.
Where are the three female dancers?
Come up and try. Quick.
Hurry. Find your positions.
It's your turn next.
Get ready.
You're next after them.
Okay.
Yes. Okay.
What are you doing here, non-staff?
I'm looking for Qi Qi.
Senior.
Have a seat, senior.
Do you have the clothes
for the celebration ready?
Of course.
This is a chance
to get close to Liang Chen.
I'll cherish it.
Shouldn't I?
Yeah. I don't have the chance for that.
I can only complete tasks
and set off fireworks.
Let's form a team next time, senior.
I heard you're a very good player.
Actually, I'm not as good as Gu Fei Ming.
Really?
I invited him today.
But he said he had no free time.
I have free time.
I was just busy.
Since we're free after the rehearsal,
let's do it.
Can you make it?
Can you?
S...Sure.
Get your hand off me.
Qi Qi.
Hold this for me.
Let's go to the toilet.
When did they become so close?
How unscrupulous.
What should I do tonight?
Let's talk it through.
No way.
I won't agree no matter what.
Liu, to Nanze University. Go faster.
Okay.
You were rushing
just so you can join the rehearsal?
Do I look good?
Yes.
It's just a rehearsal.
Aren't you taking it too seriously?
I have to be serious
even during rehearsal.
I can't let the boys...
And the girls think badly of me.
Lu Jing.
Don't forget your promise.
No worries.
It means more to me than you.
Look, Liang Chen is here!
Liang Chen?
Liang Chen is here for the rehearsal?
Where is she?
Liang Chen!
It's her in person.
Make way, please.
Come on in.
Given the university's poor condition,
we only prepared a room for you to rest.
Liang, please make do with it.
This is great. Thank you.
Okay. Get some rest.
Come to me if you need something.
Okay. Thanks.
No problem.
Let me through.
What are you doing?
Liang Chen is really pretty.
I want to get her autograph.
[I wonder if Lu Jing is here.]
I'm closing the door, guys.
Bye.
Can we take a photo together?
Where's my lipstick?
Hurry.
Didn't you just apply lipstick
before entering the campus?
That was less than ten minutes ago. Why...
Bright red seems too aggressive.
This colour makes me look old.
Is this colour suitable for this season?
No.
You look fine
with that tangerine you've applied.
Like an energetic young girl.
Is that true?
It seems like it.
Okay.
But does it match my clothes?
I'm wearing punk style today.
Look.
Do my shoes match my make-up?
You look extremely beautiful.
You couldn't be prettier.
Really?
Why am I so pretty?
[Where are you?]
Liang Chen.
Come on. Calm down.
Sit down.
Liang Chen.
-She's so pretty.
-She's so skinny.
Enough. Quiet.
Get back to work.
Go now. Get back to work.
-Mr Luo.
Let me introduce.
Liang Chen, the pride
of Nanze University.
I'm sure you guys know her.
They are the masters of ceremony
for the concert.
You may discuss the rundown
of the concert.
Hi.
[Where are you?]
A dancing performance first.
The flow is pretty simple.
Our staff will guide you.
Don't worry.
Thanks.
Ms Liang, you have a message.
I'm at the small hall.
She's on her phone.
So, celebrities play on their phones too?
She also publishes posts
and watches live stream videos.
As if you've seen that.
Gu Fei Ming, lend me a hand.
Sure.
[Which part of the hall?]
[Are you here?]
[Do you need me to pick you up?]
[No. I'm not yet there.]
[Liar.]
[Okay. I'm at the registration counter
at the entrance.]
Ke Ke.
Thanks. We'll leave now. Bye.
Bye.
Ms Liang, what are you doing?
Liang Chen, you're my idol.
I like you very much.
Thanks. Let's work hard together.
Can I have your autograph?
-Sure.
-Really?
Thanks.
Ms Liang,
Mr Luo wants us on the stage.
Bye.
She's really pretty.
Even prettier than on television.
What a wonderful voice.
She's pretty and she can sing.
She is perfect.
But she's still a bad gamer.
I have stomachache.
Your stomach aches all of a sudden?
Are you alright?
It hurts.
I need to go to the hospital.
I'll leave it to you.
Gu Fei Ming!
You... What is he doing?
Seriously.
Can I take his place, Mr Luo?
Sure.
You go.
You two, get ready.
It's your turn soon.
Go and get ready.
Let's go.
Lu Jing,
is it okay if you give her the flower
and I give her the gift?