♫When I've chosen a path
There's no going back♫
♫Just ignore the rumours
♫Even though there may be more rain
Than sunshine on this path♫
♫I don't care if I'd be reduced to ashes♫
♫All I want is to be on the stage♫
♫The light shining from my back
Is full of hope♫
♫Swim through the sea of mediocre
To reach a brand new future♫
♫And once I held my breath♫
♫Let our youth blossom
On the sea of conviction for our dreams♫
♫I still stubbornly believe in it
At every moment♫
♫Refusing to back down♫
♫Never stop
We don't need to♫
Enjoy the solitude♫
♫Never stop
Till the sun sets♫
♫I'll walk my own path♫
♫Till the end of time♫
♫On this path of dream♫
=Love Scenery=
=Adapted from Qiao Yao's Novel=
="It's Easy To Dodge a Gun,
But Hard To Prevent a Crush"=
=Episode 26=
Orange.
Were you thinking...?
What?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I'm here to report to you
about my schedule moving forward.
Tell me.
Next week, I'll be preparing
for the big data competition.
I may not be able
to come and see you often.
As such, for the time being,
you'll have to put up with it.
Try not to miss me too much.
I have a competition in the coming week.
Focus on your studies.
I don't have time to miss you.
Are you sure you won't miss me?
-What is so difficult about that?
-You're right.
After all, you've come to see me
at school numerous times before.
Let's make a bet.
How?
Well...
In the coming week,
the person who can't help
but see the other person...
will lose the bet.
-Are we allowed to call each other?
-No.
-What about WeChat messages?
Video calls are okay, right?
Of course not.
If I win the bet, what will I get?
Why are you so sure that you'll win?
Who knows? I might be the winner.
If you win, I'll go on a trip with you.
What if I lose?
Then you'll go on a trip with me.
Something is not right.
Either way, you're the winner.
Don't you want that to happen?
I... I'll win for sure.
I'll have the final say.
Okay.
Let's have a toast
with some Doubendou soy milk.
See you next week.
I'm leaving.
Don't push yourself too hard
when you miss me.
It's okay to admit defeat.
I'm leaving for real.
You can go now.
You need to let go of me first.
The bet hasn't started yet.
Let me hug you a little longer.
Director Ma said
that you changed the original song.
What happened?
Unti and I chose the same song.
Her schedule is packed.
She doesn't have time for rehearsal.
That's why I let her have the song.
You gave up the song so easily.
You have only three days left,
and you're changing your song
at the last minute?
Do you really have to be so kind?
She doesn't have time for rehearsal,
but you do?
I was hesitant when I picked the song.
I've always wanted
to adapt "First Dance of Winter."
But the competition is in three days.
You don't have the time
to adapt the song.
You're running out of time.
Ms Qing.
I want to give it a shot.
♫The disappointment♫
♫The pain of turning and jumping around♫
♫Leave behind the sensation♫
♫Dance♫
The emotion of the song unfolds
according to the rhythm.
If we change it, it will not be better
than the original version.
The composition of the song is layered.
It's difficult to compose.
Now, we have to adapt the song
on top of the composition.
It's too difficult.
It's because it's difficult
that I want to give it a try.
Try it. Turn a bicycle into a motorcycle.
No. The rhythm is too flat.
It can't get the crowd going.
Let's remove the last part.
We can redo the composition.
No way. It'll ruin the layering.
My request is simple.
I just want to take the vocals
to a whole new level...
without changing the nature of the song.
We should make good use
of rock and roll elements...
to bring the song to its full potential
on stage.
Everyone knows that.
But the problem is,
we don't know if we can do it.
Don't be nervous.
To us, this is something new.
Let's give it another try.
I believe we can do it.
It's not working at all!
What should we do?
You need to use
the random forest algorithm.
The algorithm is extremely complicated.
I suggest you spend some time
to understand it in detail.
We're running out of time.
Don't I need to eat and sleep?
You're learning big data on your own.
You don't even understand the most
basic things like linear regression...
and support vector machines.
How can you take part in the competition?
Work on the basic calculations.
Change the pseudocode.
You'll understand it
if you spend more time on it.
It's easy for you to say.
I'm trying to solve the problem.
You expect me to master the basics
and change the pseudocode?
We're preparing for a competition,
not conducting research.
Can't you just tell me the solution?
Forget it.
Just leave it.
I'll finish the rest.
Fine, I'll learn it all over again.
I'll start from the beginning.
I'll learn it.
-Zhou Zhou.
-Leave me alone!
Ms Ma.
I bought a new car.
Isn't it nice?
Hop in. I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. Thanks.
Ms Ma.
Ms Ma, if you don't get in the car,
I'll send food to your place every day.
Come on.
I heard Orange ran into some difficulties
at her rehearsal yesterday.
You know everything.
What difficulties?
It's about her choice of song.
What song did she choose?
That song...
has something to do with winter and dance.
-You mean "First Dance of Winter?"
-Yes.
You're indeed a professional.
Why did she choose that song?
What's wrong with the song?
Ms Ma?
Say something.
What's wrong with the song?
I'm intrigued.
Be it the performance or the adaptation,
this song is extremely challenging.
What should she do?
Ms Zhou.
I know. You have a lot of projects
on your plate right now.
However, we're really running out of time.
I don't have time to get a new composer
to mesh with Chen Chen.
I'm at my wit's end. I need your help.
If you help me, first,
you'll be helping Chen Chen...
Sure, got it.
Sorry to bother you, Ms Zhou.
I've been making calls all day.
On such a short notice, I can't find
any composers who can adapt the song.
I'm at my wit's end.
Tell me, what should I do?
Ms Qing, you should go back first.
Take a rest.
I'll figure it out.
You'll figure it out? How?
Are you going to perform
the incomplete version?
Ms Chen, since it's impossible
to complete the song,
why don't we switch to another song?
I think we can choose a song
that is safer.
That's right, Ms Chen.
Let's make sure you get through
to the next round first.
When we have sufficient time,
we'll let you choose the song.
Okay?
If we choose a safe song,
I'd have failed myself,
let alone the audience.
The reason I'm participating in this show
is to push my limits.
Otherwise, why would I be here?
Chen Chen.
You'll get what you want in the future.
Let's deal with the problem
at hand first, okay?
Please understand that
if you fail in the coming performance,
it may very well be the end
of your entire singing career.
Can we consider the consequences
before making a decision?
When I decided to join the show,
I thought it through.
Whatever the consequences are,
I'll bear it on my own.
You think you're the only one
who has to bear it?
Have you thought about your company
and your team?
Are you aware that your success
is the blood and sweat of many people?
If you're ruined,
everyone's effort will go down the drain.
Have you thought of my feelings?
Have you?
You haven't, have you?
All these years,
I've been living according to your plans.
But this time,
I just want to follow my heart.
I want to do it my way.
Am I wrong?
Ms Qing.
You're my manager.
I hope you can respect me.
Fine.
It seems I can't interfere
in your business, so I won't.
Ms Qing. Ms Qing, don't be mad.
Where are we going?
Ms Ma.
Do you know what this is?
It's a building.
Ms Ma, you're so humorous.
This is Liang Chen's
newly-renovated studio.
When I become rich, I'll buy a Martin D28.
When I become rich,
I'll buy a set of Yamaha PHX.
I will also build a studio
for the both of us.
We should live in the studio.
Sure!
Since we're already here,
why don't we check out the studio?
Let's take it from the top.
Ms Shan Shan.
How did you recognise me?
Chen Chen doesn't have many friends.
You're the one she mentions
the most often.
She always tells me
how you two used to make music together.
Are you coming or leaving?
I'm leaving.
She's been quite busy lately.
I don't want to bother her.
Be safe.
Ms Ma, let's go inside.
Come on. This way.
It's time for soup.
Thank you, Ms Chen.
This is for you.
Who's the caring angel?
The soup is a godsend.
Drink up and stop talking.
Sure.
Save some for me.
No persistence will go wasted.
All the best! I love you.
I didn't violate the rules.
Shan Shan, what brings you here?
I'm here too.
Can't you see me?
We were passing by
and decided to check out the studio.
Come and have a seat.
Take a seat.
Do you want some soup?
You bet we do.
It's chicken soup.
Ms Ma, have some soup.
I've eaten.
It's okay, there are two bowls of soup.
I'll put it here.
How's the song adaptation going?
I can't seem to find any better ideas.
Why don't you take a look?
Just a small part of it.
I think it's lacking something.
Shan Shan, what do you think?
I...
I have no idea.
Shan Shan, what's wrong?
I have to go.
Ms Ma, wait for me.
Lu Jing, you're back.
I have many questions to ask you.
Can you please teach me?
What questions?
I'm drafting the calculations
for a support vector machine.
The programme is working
but the error rate is very high.
What should I do?
Something is wrong
with line 54 of the code.
The dot product should be placed here.
Now I get it.
You're indeed a genius.
You can solve any problem at one glance.
Let me run the code.
Don't look at me.
I feel nervous when you look at me.
If you're so free,
why don't you get me some drinks?
Sure.
I want them cold.
I know.
Ms Ma.
What should we have for dinner?
How does hotpot sound?
What did you say?
I said, what should we have for dinner?
Aren't you full from the chicken soup?
It's so little.
I can eat more if I loosen my belt.
Orange is doing her best.
I heard they're working around the clock
and not getting any rest.
If Orange flops during the competition,
does that mean she can retire early
and get some rest?
Ms Ma, you're so quiet.
Are you down with a flu and sore throat?
Should I send you to the hospital?
I haven't had enough fun with my new car.
Ms Ma! Ms...
Ms Ma! Where are you going?
Aren't you going to say goodbye?
Ma...
She's quick.
No matter how I change it,
I still feel that something is missing.
Ms Chen,
let's just switch to another song.
We can't go on like this.
Tomorrow is the last day. Can we do it?
No, I must perform this song.
Let's do it again.
Why are you giving up on your dream?
I can't do music anymore.
I can't do it.
Is it because of Lin Qi?
Is that why you give up?
You have no idea.
You have no idea! You know nothing!
You don't understand me at all!
Do you know how much pain I'm in?
I can't even listen to music.
Even a note or a bar,
I just can't listen to anything!
It reminds me of him.
This place...
Every day, every minute and every second,
this place is full of notes and music.
It's full of memories of him!
I can't take it anymore.
Are you just going to give up
on our dream?
Because of that jerk?
I don't know how to calculate it.
You're still practising?
Why don't you try this?
We're pressed for time.
That's the best I could do.
Take a look.
My goodness. Ms Ma, you're something else.
Just cut to the chase.
It's okay.
The second part of the song
is in a high key.
And it's quite long.
It requires
not only excellent vocal control,
but continuous, explosive power.
If the singer is out of breath,
the whole song will be a disaster.
But I believe...
Orange can do it.
Is that it?
We did it!
You can sleep now.
Ms Chen, just give up if you can't do it.
Don't hurt your throat.
Can't we lower the key?
That way, it'll be less challenging.
If we lower the key,
Shan Shan's composition
won't be as fantastic.
Orange.
Why don't you adjust the key?
The composition is fine.
I made a mistake when I sang.
I'll try again.
Let's try again.
Ms Chen has been singing all day.
If she keeps singing,
I wonder if her throat can take it.
(SOMERSET)
Ke Ke.
You should go home first.
Rest early.
Perhaps everything will get better
when you wake up.
Don't worry.
Sorry, the subscriber you've dialled
is powered off.
Hello.
Ms Ke Ke.
Didn't you say that Chen Chen is home?
She went home a while ago.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I sent her home myself. What's the matter?
Sorry, the subscriber you've dialled
is powered off.
Sorry...
Chen Chen!
Sorry, the subscriber you've dialled
is powered off.
Where did she go?
Watch the time, everyone.
Check the equipment again.
Go through the equipment thoroughly.
Don't forget the lights.
Pay attention to the details.
Don't make any mistakes.
Stay on top of everything!
-Is Liang Chen here?
-Not yet.
Tell her to hurry up!
The show's about to start.
Yes.
Let's welcome Liang Chen to the stage.
-Liang Chen!
-Liang Chen is the best!
Liang Chen!
I love you, Liang Chen!
♪I stand on the stage and sing softly♪
♪The song illuminates an ocean♪
♪I look at the strange yet familiar face
♪nd tears fill my vision♪
♪Who's acting up again♪
♪And demands to be appreciated?♪
♪If only I didn't pour my heart
Into this love song♪
♪I sneak a peek at you♪
♪Just as a gentle breeze pass over you♪
♪I kept thinking about you♪
♪Your cheerful spirit
Melts away my stubbornness.♪
♪It warms my palm♪
♪And brings me peace and strength♪
♪From now on♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪My love, you are my only one♪
♪A beautiful coincidence♪
♪I'm so glad you're the one
Who's beside me♪
♪And will be for the rest of my life♪
♪Your cheerful spirit
Melts away my stubbornness♪
♪It warms my palm♪
♪And brings me peace and strength♪
♪From now on♪
♪You are my everything♪
♪My love, you are the only one♪
♪My love♪