=Auspicious Nobles=
=Episode 25=
(Steal My Woman? I'll Blow You Up)
Why did it fail again?
I've already tried 101 fuses.
What am I doing wrong?
You talk
like you're fiercer than a tiger,
but you're all bark and no bite.
Some people
are nothing but walking bad luck.
Misfortune follows them everywhere.
If someone hadn't
stuck to me like glue,
my newspaper and bank
would've already made my little goal,
and I'd be living the good life by now.
If you hadn't been so secretive
and so suspicious,
I would've never gotten involved.
Yet here you are,
making a deal with the devil
and bringing trouble upon yourself.
Foolish.
Utterly foolish.
I'm foolish?
No matter how foolish I am,
at least I wasn't stripped
of my title as Crown Prince.
And I wasn't put on
the nation's wanted list
by my own brother.
♪Snowflakes settle gently
upon your brows♪
♪Your dark hair
brushes across my fingertips♪
♪Your smile♪
♪Melts away the winter snow♪
(Why do I still care about her?)
♪One fleeting glance says more
than a thousand words♪
♪Yet I stand before you♪
It worked!
Just tweak the formula a little,
and it'll become gunpowder.
♪Though fate tries♪
♪To make us pass each other by♪
♪I choose to make our story whole♪
What are you hiding from?
♪As day turns into night♪
Don't tell me you still like me.
♪One glance at you lasts a lifetime♪
♪Blessed by fate♪
Then I'll stab you again.
I haven't forgotten
how you treated me
when I had lost my memory.
No, thanks.
Then again...
I guess you're
not a glutton for punishment.
♪And wander the world together♪
I wasn't the one
who burned down the bank.
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
What did you say?
♪Is the brightest moon♪
It was Zheng Yuanzhao.
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
Has he lost his mind?
His own money was in there too.
Do you think he's as foolish as you?
He took his money out long ago.
He robbed the robber.
Zheng Yuanzhao,
Just you wait.
I'm going to blow you up
and get every last coin back.
(Pan Residence)
Have you two lost your minds?
Untie me!
Well...
Your wedding to the Crown Prince
is just around the corner.
If the bride goes missing now,
I won't be able to answer for it.
You coward!
When Zheng Yuanzhao
laid hands on your parents,
you didn't dare say a word.
What?
Now that I'm down,
you're here to rub it in?
Never.
Qingqing...
Ah, no.
Your Highness, the Crown Princess.
You've risen to the top now.
Please don't forget
the Pan family's kindness.
That's right, Qingqing.
Once you're with the Crown Prince,
put in a good word for us.
After all, without our devoted care,
you never would've lived
to receive such a great blessing.
If you want this blessing so much,
you can have it.
I do!
You two clowns.
Once I get out of this,
you're the first ones I'll deal with.
As long as it makes you happy,
you can kick me all you want.
Go ahead.
Shameless.
Get lost!
You missed.
Just hang in there a little longer,
the Crown Prince
will be here any moment.
The Crown Prince has arrived.
What are you two doing?
Let me go.
(Wedding Procession)
Don't move.
Qingqing,
where's your dowry?
Stop disgusting me.
Let go!
Qingqing,
my residence has everything you need.
Once the wedding ceremony is over,
you can move in at once.
Coo...
What are you doing, laying an egg?
You may not be good for much,
but you sure changed your tune fast.
Come, Qingqing.
I'll go.
But what about Caiyuan and Jiuzhu?
Move.
Kneel.
Yuanzhao, is this the best you've got?
How predictable.
As long as it works.
Once you marry into my residence,
whether it's Wangshi Tower
or the Pan family,
I'll let bygones be bygones.
If you still resent Pan Yang,
I can kill him right now.
I know I was wrong.
This...
This is my repeating crossbow.
That's right.
Let Pan Yang die
by the repeating crossbow you designed.
It'll be the perfect way
to settle your grudge.
You stole my blueprints
and didn't even pay me
a single coin in royalties.
Qingqing,
you've misunderstood me.
I merely had them
recreate the repeating crossbow.
It took quite a bit of effort.
The auspicious hour has arrived.
Please escort the Crown Princess.
Don't move.
Father,
today,
I shall take Lady Li
as my Crown Princess.
It so happens that Your Majesty
has been unwell.
May this joyous occasion
help drive away your illness.
You jerk! Let go of me!
Qingqing,
be good.
Once the wedding is over,
I'll release your maid and Jiuzhu.
Father,
please proceed to the main hall
to preside over Qingqing's wedding and mine.
What took you...
Not this again.
He.
Father!
Yuanhe.
You've finally come.
I knew you couldn't let Qingqing go.
Let her go.
You...
You arranged this marriage
to force him into the open?
Why not kill two birds with one stone?
Yuanhe,
you came here all alone.
No matter how brave you are,
what can you possibly accomplish?
Jiang Shuo.
Jiang Shuo!
Take them away.
Your Highness,
all the rebels have been subdued.
Caiyuan! Jiuzhu!
Tower Master!
At least you still have a conscience.
You remembered to save them.
You've already
lost your military command.
How is this possible?
Too bad you didn't know.
The Inspectorate
answers to only one master.
Even with the Inspectorate,
there's no way
you could've gotten here this quickly.
He has gunpowder.
One throw,
and it blows everything apart.
What good are your troops
if they're all wiped out?
Yuanhe,
the person you hate most
is also the one you love most.
How does that feel?
Didn't you hate her?
Then today, I'll kill her for you.
Zheng Yuanzhao, don't take this too far!
I've lost my mind?
I just can't stand the sight of him.
You made such a grand spectacle.
If you want her to live,
then the two of you...
one lives,
one dies.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You've been walking around
with that gloomy face.
I've been sick of looking
at you for a long time.
You've been following
Qingqing around every day.
I've been sick of you
for a long time too.
What are you two doing now?
Fine then.
Let's
- settle this.
- Settle this.
♪Snowflakes settle gently
upon your brows♪
♪Your dark hair
brushes across my fingertips♪
♪Your smile♪
♪Melts away the winter snow♪
♪One fleeting glance says more
than a thousand words♪
♪Yet I stand before you♪
♪Unable to recognize your eyes♪
♪Though fate tries♪
♪To make us pass each other by♪
♪I choose to make our story whole♪
♪Though time slips by♪
♪As day turns into night♪
♪I still remember
our days at Wangshi Tower♪
♪One glance at you lasts a lifetime♪
♪Blessed by fate♪
♪I believe this moment
will last forever♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪