=Auspicious Nobles=
=Episode 3=
(The Crown Prince Takes What He Wants)
I'm nothing more
than a carefree wanderer.
I have no interest in court affairs.
Tower Master, I hope you'll reconsider.
There's no hurry.
Take care.
Tower Master.
Your voice-changing skill is incredible.
Naturally.
I'm practically
an expert in voice acting.
Caiyuan.
Have Jiuzhu follow that creep.
Keep him under constant watch.
I turned him down just now.
He's definitely figuring out
how to get back at me.
Get Second Prince here at once.
I need to teach him
some modern business principles.
Yes, Tower Master.
(Wangshi Tower)
Yang.
Will we get to see
the Tower Master today?
What if we don't?
The Tower Master of Wangshi Tower
holds power beyond measure.
Even the Crown Prince
and the Second Prince
rely on her support.
Even if she has us beaten,
we'll have no one to complain to.
I don't even know
how I offended the Tower Master.
If I can't earn her forgiveness today,
I'm afraid my life will be at risk.
How could we have
offended the Tower Master?
Who's trying to set us up?
I don't know.
Tower Master.
The Helilao Restaurant
you told me to open
is making nearly 7,000 taels a month.
(Zheng Yuanzhao, Great Yong's Second Prince)
It's already the most popular restaurant in the capital.
Tables are fully booked every day.
(Account Book)
(It costs 30,000 taels a day
just to keep the restaurant running.)
(A few thousand taels
barely scratches the surface.)
Tell me.
Why haven't you met
the performance target I set?
The restaurant is doing well,
but making 100,000 taels
a month is nearly impossible.
For the sake of everything I've done
for the Li family over the years,
You don't have to anymore.
But with Helilao,
you take most of the profits.
I only get twenty percent.
And you're still pushing me this hard.
That's just not fair.
If you can't do it, just say so.
I can always train someone else.
Tower Master, don't forget.
I, Zheng Yuanzhao,
control the empire's merchant network.
I'd say I'm the only one
in all of Great Yong who can meet
that... what do you call it?
That performance target.
Besides,
even if you replaced me,
you'd never find anyone as obedient
or as easy on the eyes.
Fine.
Then let's revise your target.
You're lowering it?
10,000 taels a day.
This...
How much?
10,000 taels.
Tower Master,
why don't you see how much I'm worth
and just sell me?
There's no way I can do it.
I know you can't.
But what if I told you
I could make
every merchant in the empire
earn money for us?
Every merchant in the empire
working for us?
In a few days,
I'll give you the perfect plan.
All you need to do
is build the platform
and expand the business.
Now you've really made me curious.
Who are you, Tower Master?
Could you truly be
an immortal sent from heaven?
If only I could
catch a glimpse
of the Tower Master's true face today.
Mind your manners!
Break his legs.
Yes.
Guards.
Hold on.
Since the Tower Master is too shy
to reveal her true face today,
I'll come back another time.
Another time.
(Wangshi Tower)
My dear, she's out.
She's out.
Please let the Tower Master know
that my husband is the General
of the Northern Expedition Cavalry.
He wishes to request
an audience with the Tower Master.
Never heard of him.
Do you have an appointment letter?
An appointment letter?
No.
If that's required,
I'll write one right away.
Do you think
just anyone can enter Wangshi Tower?
Even those who qualify
must submit an appointment letter
seven days in advance.
Only after the Tower Master reviews it
will she decide whether to see you.
Hey, may I ask
which family you belong to?
How did you manage
to meet the Tower Master?
Mind your own business.
Move along.
I... I'm a General
of the Northern Expedition Cavalry.
If you can arrange
a meeting with the Tower Master,
I'll reward you handsomely.
A General
of the Northern Expedition Cavalry?
You really think you're somebody.
Who does he think he is?
Your Highness.
No wonder that fool Yuanzhao
managed to double
the imperial merchant business
in just a year.
So Wangshi Tower has been backing him.
His Majesty has always used
the Second Prince to keep you in check.
If the Second Prince
and Wangshi Tower...
I know.
Since Wangshi Tower
insists on helping Yuanzhao,
then make her disappear.
Yes.
(Jiuzhu, Great Yong's top assassin.
The Tower Master's personal shadow guard)
What a headache.
The imperial merchant business
brings in 70,000 taels a month.
I'm ashamed.
I've been tied up with too many affairs
and neglected the business.
That's why the profits are a little low.
Please punish me, Father.
You little rascal.
You say you're ashamed,
but you're really
waiting for me to praise you.
You think you can fool me
(The Emperor of Great Yong)
with that little act of playing humble?
You're wise as always, Father.
No one knows me better than you.
You
are capable and intelligent,
yet never arrogant
because of your achievements.
Unlike Yuanhe, who's
so stubborn and headstrong.
It's just a pity
you were born a few years too late.
Otherwise...
Starting tomorrow,
join me at morning court.
It's time you learned
how to handle affairs of state.
No, Father.
I'm perfectly happy
making a little money every day
and living as a carefree rich man.
Very well.
Since your ambitions lie elsewhere,
I won't force you.
Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince has arrived.
Father,
I've already
finished reporting the accounts.
I'll take my leave now.
Zhao.
You've handled
the imperial merchant business well.
I'm very pleased.
Greetings, Father.
Yuanhe.
The Inspectorate again.
Take a look.
These are all memorials impeaching you.
As long as I can rid Great Yong
of its corrupt officials,
why should I fear impeachment?
Still as stubborn as ever.
A single move in the imperial court
can affect the whole kingdom.
(That cold, arrogant face again.)
(No wonder nobody
likes him wherever he goes.)
(My warm smile is much more charming.)
The court is losing people's support.
Your Highness.
I'll get the list
of every official who impeached you
and have
the Inspectorate investigate them.
Let's see if any of them
are truly above reproach.
There's no need.
They're nothing more
than the Second Prince's pawns.
They pose no threat to me.
But that Tower Master of Wangshi Tower
sure has been going all out
to help Yuanzhao.
Why did you ask me to come?
What took you so long?
I've been trying to reach you all day.
Didn't I already tell you?
A professional errand runner
is all about speed.
The moment your client calls,
you've got to get here fast.
So much for Great Yong's top assassin.
I've lost that little gadget.
I can't hear you.
You...
This...
This won't do.
How am I supposed to reach you
the next time I'm in trouble?
It cost me a fortune
to make it with ultrasonic bianstone.
Besides, it goes pretty well
with your outfit.
How's the surveillance
on the Crown Prince going?
I've learned my lesson.
Business comes after payment.
Ten taels.
The Crown Prince watched the Second Prince
after he left Wangshi Tower.
I'm guessing that after the attack
on the Li Residence,
he suspects you've already joined forces
with the Second Prince.
I was having too much fun back then.
That never even crossed my mind.
This is bad.
That scheming prince must think
we're plotting a rebellion
with the Second Prince.
Caiyuan.
Pass the order.
Abandon this hideout.
Seal off the entrance
at Yinma Town as well.
Suspend production
at the workshop for one month.
Tower Master,
that's a lot of money to lose.
We're already short on funds.
Even if the Crown Prince knows
the Second Prince is connected to us,
do we really
have to shut everything down?
I know we can't afford to.
This will cost us millions of taels.
But the Crown Prince is a madman.
He's bound to think
we're helping the Second Prince
take his throne.
If we stay, we'll all be dead.
You dared meddle
in the affairs of the imperial family.
And now you think you can run?
Too late.
Hurry!
Tower Master,
why is the street completely empty?
Don't worry about it.
We're racing against death now.
One step too slow, and that lunatic
might catch up and kill us.
I really do jinx myself.
What do we do, Tower Master?
Just stay calm. Act natural.
Okay.
Keep moving.
My Lady, don't worry.
With the Tower Master's guidance,
the young master's business
has come back to life.
Stop right there!
♪Snowflakes settle gently
upon your brows♪
♪Your dark hair
brushes across my fingertips♪
♪Your smile♪
♪Melts away the winter snow♪
♪One fleeting glance says more
than a thousand words♪
♪Yet I stand before you♪
♪Unable to recognize your eyes♪
♪Though fate tries♪
♪To make us pass each other by♪
♪I choose to make our story whole♪
♪Though time slips by♪
♪As day turns into night♪
♪I still remember
our days at Wangshi Tower♪
♪One glance at you lasts a lifetime♪
♪Blessed by fate♪
♪I believe this moment
will last forever♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪