=Auspicious Nobles=
=Episode 18=
(I'd Rather Be Your Kept Lover)
Your Highness,
the assassins are in position.
If Li Qingqing is in danger
and Jiuzhu appears,
then she must be the Tower Master.
Miss.
Do it.
Yes.
Wait.
Find out what that pendant is about.
Immediately.
Yes.
Tower Master,
just as you predicted,
they've entered Noble Bank.
Your Highness,
we've found out.
It was personally designed
by the Second Prince
as a gift from Noble Bank
for major depositors.
The imperial merchants who do business
with him all have one as well.
(So I misunderstood her.)
(Thank goodness I didn't make
an irreparable mistake.)
Let's go.
Young Master,
someone asked me to deliver this to you.
(Wangshi secret workshop)
(located three li west of Yinma Town
on the outskirts of the Capital.)
(Hidden deep within a cliffside valley.)
(Respectfully.)
Investigate it.
Yes.
Tower Master,
the little goal matter,
I did a pretty good job, didn't I?
Aren't you going to praise me?
Praise you? Not a chance.
This isn't over yet.
Come here.
In a moment,
act like
you're into me.
Like you're always
finding excuses to get close to me.
That way, he won't suspect
we're close because we're accomplices.
Got it?
Do I really have to act?
I really
have feelings for you.
Don't make me slap you.
Did you understand what I just said?
You mean playing a charming rogue
whose love isn't returned?
Got it.
What are you doing? I'll hit you.
Don't move.
My brother's here.
Let her go.
Your Highness,
you said you wanted
to discuss business with me.
But instead,
you...
Yuanzhao,
as a prince, is it appropriate
to use your status
to pressure a young lady?
The same goes for you, Yuanhe.
I heard about the Spring Banquet.
Let's not mock each other.
At least I wouldn't force her.
If you love someone,
you have to fight for them.
If you're as hesitant
as you are, Yuanhe,
I doubt you'll ever win her heart.
(He insisted on walking me home.)
(And he hasn't said a word.)
(What is he trying to do?)
(Pan Residence)
Your Highness, we've arrived
at the Pan Residence.
Thank you, Your Highness,
for escorting me home.
I'll be going in now.
Wait.
I have something to say to Qingqing.
- Yes.
(Pan Residence)
Your Highness, what else would you like?
I've seen Pan Yang recently.
While you're out running the household
and managing the family business,
you were nearly taken advantage of.
Meanwhile, he's out
having fun with his concubine,
without a care in the world.
Why do you insist
on keeping this title?
It was my own choice.
You needn't trouble yourself,
Your Highness.
Do you think
I'm supposed to just stand by and watch?
Watch you in this mire,
tormenting yourself
and tormenting me?
(You've read too many romance novels.)
Your Highness and I
have nothing to do with each other.
How could I possibly torment you?
Since you refuse to divorce him
and insist on remaining Mrs. Pan,
I can stay by your side as someone
who must remain in the shadows.
I
am willing to be your kept lover.
No...
This...
You're far too lovestruck.
You're the Crown Prince,
the future Emperor.
Can't you come to your senses?
Come on...
♪Snowflakes settle gently
upon your brows♪
♪Your dark hair
brushes across my fingertips♪
♪Your smile♪
♪Melts away the winter snow♪
♪One fleeting glance says more
than a thousand words♪
♪Yet I stand before you♪
♪Unable to recognize your eyes♪
♪Though fate tries♪
♪To make us pass each other by♪
♪I choose to make our story whole♪
Yang,
look.
The carriage is rocking.
Which shameless couple
is fooling around
outside my Pan Residence?
Let's see who's so bold.
Which shameless pair is it?
Come out!
If he sees this,
will he still want you?
Getting into it, aren't you?
Let's see how I deal with you today.
Who are you going to deal with?
Your Highness!
I deserve death.
I offended Your Highness.
Keep your eyes shut.
Until I give the order,
if you dare open them, you die.
- I won't.
- Yes.
(Yuanzhao was right.)
(If you love someone,
you should fight for them.)
Let's go.
Yang,
Who do you think
was in His Highness's carriage?
Shut up.
Let's head back.
(Pan Residence)
What is going on today?
Zheng Yuanhe
has completely lost his mind.
Ptooey!
Pour me some more water.
Right away.
Getting mixed up with that mad dog
has brought me nothing but bad luck.
Li Qingqing,
when did you get back?
What?
Do I have to report to General Pan
whenever I come home?
Do I not even have the freedom
to leave the house anymore?
Have fighting bandits
made you lose your mind?
You really think you're somebody.
Enough with the smart remarks.
I'm asking you.
One stick of incense ago,
the Crown Prince's carriage
stopped outside.
Where were you then?
Were you inside the carriage?
You're out of your mind.
First, you accused me
of meeting some pretty boy.
Now you're slandering
the Crown Prince and me.
Why are you so obsessed
with accusing me of cheating?
Then let me see
what shoes you're wearing.
Let me take a look.
Get away from me!
You worthless scoundrel!
Where are your shoes?
You're the one
who's always fooling around outside,
without a shred of shame.
So you assume
everyone else is just like you?
The shoes I saw on that woman earlier
looked a lot like yours.
Which eye of yours saw me
getting into
the Crown Prince's carriage?
Stop throwing false accusations at me.
If you've got the nerve,
go ask the Crown Prince
who was in that carriage.
Instead, you come here
to throw your weight around.
You bully the weak and fear the strong.
I only asked.
Why are you so worked up?
Get out!
The sight of you makes me sick.
I'm warning you.
From now on,
don't come into my courtyard
without my permission.
Otherwise, tomorrow I'll go to the Inspectorate
and beat the Drum of Grievance,
accusing you of slandering
the Crown Prince and me.
Let's see whether the Crown Prince
skins you alive first
or tears my mouth apart.
Fine.
I'll leave, all right?
Get out!
Crazy woman.
Watch what you say.
Get out!
Why does this feel like
I'm about to get caught?
That Zheng Yuanhe is my natural nemesis.
Your Highness,
I don't understand.
Why are you helping the Crown Prince
find Wangshi Tower's workshop?
Those clever little schemes of hers
aren't enough
to bring down my dear brother.
She needs to be ruthless.
Give her a reason
she has no choice but to kill him.
Then why did Your Highness
help Li Qingqing just now?
Next...
We'll set a fire
and burn down the bank.
Your Highness,
there's a lot of our money in there.
Which one of us
do you think is the fool?
Quietly have someone withdraw the money.
Then burn it down
and pin it on Zheng Yuanhe.
That way,
she'll hate him
even more.
(Qingqing.)
(You are clever.)
(You're just not ruthless enough.)
(Let me help you with that.)
♪Snowflakes settle gently
upon your brows♪
♪Your dark hair
brushes across my fingertips♪
♪Your smile♪
♪Melts away the winter snow♪
♪One fleeting glance says more
than a thousand words♪
♪Yet I stand before you♪
♪Unable to recognize your eyes♪
♪Though fate tries♪
♪To make us pass each other by♪
♪I choose to make our story whole♪
♪Though time slips by♪
♪As day turns into night♪
♪I still remember
our days at Wangshi Tower♪
♪One glance at you lasts a lifetime♪
♪Blessed by fate♪
♪I believe this moment
will last forever♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪
♪Your smiling face♪
♪Is the most beautiful poem♪
♪I'd rather spend my days with you♪
♪And wander the world together♪
♪Holding you close♪
♪Envying neither lovers nor immortals♪
♪Your tenderness♪
♪Is the brightest moon♪
♪I'd rather
pledge three lifetimes to you♪
♪Our love will never fade away♪
♪Though heaven and earth grow old♪
♪My heart will remain forever pure♪