AN UNEXPECTED SURPRISE.MP4
Sera.
It's my fault.
Don't touch me!
You want to see it, don't you?
I'll strip for you!
Don't!
THERE'S JUST A THIN LINE
BETWEEN RIGHT AND WRONG.
CROSS IT, AND THERE'S NO TURNING BACK.
LIN GUOGUANG
Sera.
THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL
ANY RESEMBLANCES ARE PURELY COINCIDENTAL
Listen to me, Sera.
I know you saw some things on my computer.
There are grown-up things
that you won't understand.
You're not a real philanthropist.
You're disgusting!
Don't touch me!
Ma'am.
How long has your shop been open for?
I'm not the boss. He isn't here yet.
Has your shop been around
for at least four years?
We've been around
for seven to eight years.
Can I ask you something?
Do you still have the CCTV footage
from 29 February 2020?
You're joking.
Why would anyone keep a copy
of CCTV footage from four years ago?
Thank you.
Tingting, I'm home.
I'm making pasta tonight.
Tingting.
MASSIVE JERK!
ZHANG JAMES, YOU MASSIVE JERK!
‪It's true.
My father isn't that kind of person.
Stop talking.
Your father isn't a good guy
- no matter what you say, so stop.
- He's really good to me…
Hey! What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Dad!
- Dad, stop!
- Why did you touch my daughter?
Come for me if you dare!
Don't touch my daughter!
What are you talking about?
Are you nuts?
She was the one who looked for me!
Get your facts straight!
You're a lunatic.
Why did you look for him out of the blue?
I knew that Paul misunderstood you,
so I wanted to help you clear the air,
but why must you be so rash?
Tingting.
Are you really going to ignore me?
We agreed to never go to bed angry.
I was very worried
when I saw the photo Paul sent,
and then
I hit him because I got anxious
when I saw the situation unfold.
However, I know this isn't a good excuse
because I still did something wrong.
You should go.
I'm going to sleep.
If you're going to ignore me,
I won't tell you a secret.
I thought we agreed
not to have any secrets between us?
I'll tell you a secret then.
Your grandfather was an abusive man.
He used to hit your grandmother.
Whenever he hit her,
I'd shield her from his attacks.
When I was 18 years old,
he was drunk one day.
He took a knife
and tried to slash your grandmother.
I used my body to shield her from it.
That slash severed our ties
as father and son.
I eventually became
a violent person myself.
I felt that I could protect
myself with violence,
and that it could solve all issues.
That all changed when I met your mother
and came to know God.
They taught me to look toward the future
and not at the past.
So,
I forgave your grandfather
and mended our relationship.
However,
earlier today,
the person who I hate returned.
For that,
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Don't worry.
I won't look back at the past.
You're still
the adorable dad that I love.
How adorable?
You're this adorable!
I'm sorry for scaring you.
Go to sleep soon.
Good night.
Good night, Dad.
NEXT WEEK IS YOUR BIRTHDAY.
CAN MOMMY CELEBRATE IT WITH YOU?
ARE YOU FREE?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO EAT?
I'LL COOK IT FOR YOU.
Sun Shanwen, reply to your mother.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're as nosy as them!
I'll reply to her for you.
‪Hey.
- Give it back!
- Hey…
Here, take it back.
Where exactly are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Sun Shanwen,
why are you being so mysterious?
Are you the famous sculptor?
‪Hey, hey!
How's business today?
It's a rare day.
Starplayer brought his friend
to try the escape room today.
Sun Shanwen?
No wonder I saw his mother nearby.
His mother?
I'll take over from here.
Go for your lunch break.
Boss, it's already 2:30 p.m.
I've already eaten.
Would it kill you to eat again?
My third aunt died from overeating.
Are you talking back to me?
Seven.
Four.
Three-seven-four.
Sun Shanwen.
You're really good at this!
Look! We figured it out in 20 minutes!
My parents were often not at home.
My sister would come up
with riddles and treasure hunts.
She would get me to play them.
We still have some time left.
Let's not waste our money.
Let's just sit here and chat.
Actually,
this is my first time in an escape room.
It's because of my dad.
He doesn't let me
do any dangerous activities.
Are escape rooms dangerous?
Yes! You'll get scared.
I was born with a hole in my heart.
It eventually closed up,
but…
my mother died from a heart attack,
so my father has always
been worried about me.
So, you've never been on a roller coaster?
Not even a cable car.
However,
I must thank you
for giving me a new experience today.
My life feels like an escape room.
I can't solve any of the riddles.
We always stay in our rooms.
It feels like…
we're letting my sister down…
if we live happily.
Sun Shanwen,
the riddle you wish to solve…
is right here.
Also, you're no longer all alone.
You have me now.
I believe that
Auntie Ruoyun and your father
are trapped in their own escape rooms too.
They can't find their way out either
and are as miserable as you.
You look frail.
I guess you haven't been
sleeping or eating well.
Why does it feel like I'm at the doctor's?
I'm not so capable as to treat you,
but I know someone who can:
Sun Shanwen.
He's my poison.
He's your antidote.
Look at this glass of water.
You see it as half-empty,
but I see it as half-full.
I'm trying very hard
to crawl out of this dark space
I'm trapped in.
However, no matter how much I try,
I'm stuck in the same space.
We'll have to…
feel and see the invisible thread.
This thread is known as the Rope of Grace.
There's an invisible thread
that ties each family closely together.
Regardless of how tense
the relationship is,
blood is still thicker than water.
My dad was abusive when I was a child.
At the time,
I thought my mother hated him to her core.
However, at his deathbed,
she cried her heart out.
I later realized that…
hurt people hurt people.
Those who've been hurt
will arm themselves.
They'll unknowingly hurt others.
Let's talk about something else.
Shanwen's birthday is next week, right?
I remember that his and Tingting's
birthdays are four days apart.
Shall we celebrate
their birthdays together?
You can really read my mind.
I looked for you
in the hopes you could act
as a middleman for me.
He hasn't replied to me,
even though I've tried contacting him.
Rest assured.
Leave it to Tingting and I.
Thank you.
You should eat something.
Here.
What about this?
I'll have this.
What do you want written on it?
"Happy Birthday, Tingting and Shanwen".
"Shan" like in kind (shanliang)
and "Wen" like in quiet (wenjing).
"Ting" is the word for pavilion
with the "woman" radical.
Sure.
How many candles do you need?
They're both turning 18 years old,
so I'll just get a single candle.
Are they fraternal twins?
No, they're not.
They're classmates.
I'm the girl's father,
and she's the boy's mother.
All right. Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
Hi.
What a coincidence.
You're Mr. Sun, right?
It's nice to meet you. I'm James.
- I often see you on television
- Hi.
James is Shanwen's classmate's father.
Is that so?
All right. I won't hold you back.
You arranged it beautifully.
You're an artist indeed.
It's all right.
It's more than all right.
For my part,
the ratio of the egg mixture
and stock is 1:2.
If I can get the ratio right,
it's half the job done.
It's the same
as when I make sculpting clay.
Dad.
Will you be done soon?
Shanwen said that he'll be arriving early.
- He'll be arriving early?
- Yes.
I still have many things left to do.
Auntie Ruoyun,
you're so nervous,
as if you're meeting your boyfriend.
Aren't you feeling nervous?
What do I have to be nervous about?
Are they…
I don't think so.
However, if that were the case,
would you approve of their relationship?
Although they're still young,
Tingting is such a good girl,
so I would be more than happy.
She's too good for Shanwen though.
Nonsense.
However,
maybe only when they are older.
We'll have to be on the same page then.
But I'm afraid that Tingting will be
snatched up by someone else by then.
Do you have so little confidence
in your son?
He's here.
Sun Shanwen!
Here.
Why did you bring alcohol?
Your father asked me to bring some.
We haven't reached
the legal drinking age yet.
A few days doesn't make much difference.
Shanwen.
Don't be rude. It's my birthday today!
Your mother is my guest. All right?
They went out early in the morning
to buy the ingredients.
Don't look so upset. All right?
Greet my dad.
- Hi, Uncle.
- Hello.
Have a seat. We'll have dinner in a bit.
Come on.
Tingting. Come give me a hand.
Dinner will be ready soon.
Happy birthday, Shanwen.
Go ahead and open it.
Shanwen.
Open it.
That year,
when you won the arts award,
I promised to make you
a sculpture for your birthday.
I'm sorry…
that I'm a few years late.
You remembered.
I've never forgotten my promise.
Shanwen,
the place I'm staying at
isn't too far from your school.
Come stay the night next week.
I won't be free that day.
It's all right
if you don't stay the night.
You can invite Tingting over for a meal.
Shanwen.
Good night.
Hello.
You want to see it, don't you?
- Go away!
- Don't!
Don't touch me!
Hello.
Who is this?
What do you want?
Were you the one who sent the envelope?
Hello?
Hello!
That's quite good.
Thank you, Teacher.
All right. Class is over.
You can continue next week
if you haven't finished painting.
Someone has been in a good mood recently.
Indeed.
I've straightened out my thoughts.
What do you mean?
You said that…
getting a divorce
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
You're right.
Divorce is a good thing for all parties.
Our dear Shanwen has grown up.
He has become mature too.
So, does that mean
you're no longer mad at Auntie Ruoyun?
Are you free later?
Why? Are you asking me out?
I want to frame this painting.
I have more here.
Take your time to look through them.
- We'll get this one!
That's right.
You lovebirds have really good chemistry.
Sir, you've misunderstood us.
We're just friends.
You'll become
more than friends in no time.
- I'll call you when it's done.
- Thank you, sir!
You're still denying it
despite having such good chemistry?
We…
Let's go in and have a look.
Which one do you like?
I'll gift it to you.
Why do you need to gift it to me?
It's to commemorate…
you becoming my girlfriend today.
This is nice and beautiful.
Miss, this one.
Give me your hand.
Do you like it?
Auntie Ruoyun likes such bracelets too.
Shall I buy one as a gift for her?
It's all right. She has sensitive skin.
She makes sculptures,
so she can't wear any accessories anyway.
She doesn't even wear her wedding ring.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Auntie Ruoyun, something dropped inside.
So, that's where it went.
Cindy had the same bracelet.
Who knew that Cindy and I
share the same taste.
Such bracelets are common.
They're sold everywhere.
I'll go pay for this.
Miss, I'd like to pay.
This way, please.
Hey.
It's been so many years.
This place hasn't changed much.
Thank you.
I ordered a cup of yuan yang for you.
It's blander than I remember.
Certain tastes may become bland,
but not for family relationships.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
I… don't know what you're talking about.
Cut the pretense.
I ran into Dehui earlier.
He told me everything.
Hey, Sister-in-Law. What a small world.
You're looking good.
I'm no longer your sister-in-law.
I take my hat off to you.
You cut all ties with my brother
once you found out
he has no money or authority.
What are you talking about?
Haven't you heard?
He sold all his shares to Mr. Deng.
I have an ulterior motive.
I'm not a match for Dehui,
so I sold all my shares to the big fox,
so he can tackle the little fox.
I'm sorry…
that I made you pay such a high price.
Don't apologize to me.
I was in the wrong as well.
I…
deserved it.
That day,
you asked me if I have killed…
You don't have to tell me.
You deserve to have your secrets.
Let's…
respect each other's privacy.
Everything we do is for our daughter.
That's right.
It's all for Sera.
Calm down.
Let's talk about this at home, okay?
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Don't touch me!
You want to see it?
You want to see it, don't you?
- I'll strip for you!
- Don't!
Don't touch me!
Boss, did you change the passcode
for the storeroom?
Yeah.
What's the new passcode?
I'm not planning to tell you.
You don't need to enter
the storeroom anymore.
Why?
That's because I'm the boss!
Hey, Shanwen!
Ruby.
Go home first.
I'll stay to close the shop.
You're asking me to go home first?
You're staying to close the shop?
Why?
That's because…
That's because you're the boss.
Get lost already!
I'm getting lost now.
XINGYOU CLUB
Allan.
What are you doing here so early?
Did Shanwen come to look for you?
He didn't. Did something happen?
He didn't come home yesterday.
I tried calling him,
but he turned his phone off.
I thought he might be here.
Why would he come here?
Did something happen?
Did the two of you get into a fight?
No.
We didn't.
It just seems like he hasn't been
in the best mood recently.
- He's been in a bad mood?
- Yes.
Let me check with Tingting.
- Hi.
- James.
Sorry to disturb you.
Don't worry about it. Come on in.
Hi, Mr. Sun.
I haven't been able
to get a hold of Tingting.
It's a Saturday after all.
The church members
are visiting an old folks' home.
She's probably in the midst of it,
so she hasn't answered my calls.
I'm not too sure
why you're looking for her urgently.
Our son hasn't come home all night.
He turned off his phone, and we wanted
to know if he's with your daughter.
From what I understand, he's not with her.
Young people won't usually turn off
their phones unless they're in a bad mood.
Allan said that he hasn't been
in the best mood recently.
Did he get into a fight with Tingting?
I don't think so.
Tingting was in a good mood
when she left this morning.
Don't worry.
Shanwen should be fine.
Shanwen often goes to an internet cafe.
It should be somewhere near Daoming Road.
Do you know of it?
I've heard Tingting mention it.
It's called Lost.
Are you saying that Shanwen
might be there?
In that case,
I'll join you to search for him.
All right. Thank you.
I'll head in first, Ruby.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Do you know this person
by the name of Sun Shanwen?
Sun Shanwen.
Do you mean Starplayer Samuel?
Yes! That's him!
- Did he come by last night?
- He did.
What time was that?
I left work at 11:00 p.m.
He got here at around 10:00 p.m.
What time did he leave?
Do you know where he went?
Boss told me to clock off
not long after he arrived.
He was the only person left in the shop.
I'll call and ask him for you.
Thank you.
That's weird.
His phone is turned off.
Can we see the CCTV footage?
No! You're not the police.
We just want to know what time he left.
I can't just show it to you.
Boss will scold me if he finds out.
- Is there any way to contact him?
- I can't give you that too!
Boss will scold me if he finds out.
Why can't you just help us?
Will you be responsible
if something happens to my son?
They're Shanwen's parents,
so they're feeling agitated and nervous.
I apologize.
I'm sorry. I can't help you
I have customers coming soon.
There are many things to prepare.
How about this? This is my business card.
Inform me immediately
if Shanwen comes by again.
Is that all right?
Thank you.
FIRST COMBINED ESPORTS ARENA
AND ESCAPE ROOM OPENS