Where Stars Land
Episode 20
Hello?
If you have my radio with you, can you hear my voice?
If you have my radio... You're listening to me, right?
Can I give it a try?
Sunbaenim Oh Dae Gi. Sunbaenim Oh Dae Gi, where are you?
Oh Dae Gi's~not here! I said he's not here, why do you keep looking for him?
He only answers if I call him by your name.
Look here, sir! That radio is not something you should be playing with.
I don't know who you are but I demand that you return it to me this instant.
The act of not returning things you've found is also considered as theft.
Elder!
Sunbaenim Oh Dae Gi.
Sunbaenim Oh Dae Gi!
Who are you?
I'm Oh Dae Gi from the Security Team.
- This crazy guy...
- What?
Who's he calling Oh Dae Gi when he's Oh Dae Gi?
It's not like that. This is because you are not answering me.
So... You want to find your radio?
Yes, I hope you return it back by all means because it's an important thing for security.
Then sit down.
- What?
- I said to sit down.
Yes, I sat down.
Stand up.
I stood up.
Sit down again.
I sat down.
Look at you lying. You must not want your radio back.
- Elder. Perhaps, you are looking at us now?
- Sit down.
Elder, stop playing.
Playing?!
I'm testing you to see how badly you want your radio back.
So... You want to find your radio? Then, sit down.
Elder!
I told you that I'd treat you.
We aren't allowed to accept anything from others.
And especially you, since you're associated with the airport.
Are you dating that man from before? Are you two a couple in the same office?
Oh, my god.
Right, you were popular with boys since high school. Right?
What do you want to talk about?
You seem to be busy so I'll make it short. Get me four fast-track tickets.
I'm actually flying some VIPs out next week.
Do they have physical disabilities?
Their personalities are a bit difficult. I told you, they're V-I-P.
Fast-track was made for passengers that have difficulties moving around.
Regular customers, even if they're VIP, can't use Fast-track.
So that's why I'm asking you.
Isn't it a piece of cake for you since you're on the Passenger Service team?
What are friends for?
Have you ever been a friend of mine?
Will you do it?
No, I can't.
And I have no desire to. If you really want it that badly, go about it the proper way.
Please ask the airline directly by yourself.
Will you keep doing this?
If you keep acting like this, I'm going to want to open my mouth again.
This time, who do you want me to go to? To that man who was next to you earlier?
Or should I go to your office and blab it out? Would you be okay with that?
Look down.
Get it for me by this weekend. It's just four passes.
Thank you for yesterday. I apologize for the late greetings.
What happened in the parking lot yesterday?
How did you break the car like that?
How exactly are you sick and how serious is it? Is it an illness that causes seizures?
Do I need to talk about it to you?
Of course not.
But, I wonder if it's something I should tell Yeo Reum.
Including what I saw at your house yesterday.
You saw? What did you see?
It was in the room.
I ended up seeing it.
I've told you this before but Han Yeo Reum and I, we talk about everything, even our deepest thoughts.
Wouldn't it be better if you told her about it yourself than her hearing it accidentally from me?
It's not a matter for you to talk about that easily.
You said you like Yeo Reum?
Yes, I like her.
If you like her, don't you think there shouldn't be any secrets?
Because I like her, there is something I want to hide from her.
Is that so?
Then, I can't help telling Yeo Reum what I've seen either.
Even if I ask you not to, you're going to tell her?
I'm not your friend. I'm Yeo Reum's friend.
I don't want her to get along with someone who's trying to hide something from her.
So, please, Lee Soo Yeon, tell her directly.
I'll give you until the end of the week.
Focaccia set please. Put the coffee in mugs instead of plastic cups. No need for straws.
And I just need exactly two paper napkins.
Just help yourself.
No. I have no appetite.
Are you not eating because I bought it?
Just wait until that jokester gets caught...
Are... Are your injuries okay?
I'm fine. I used to get these kind of injuries in the past when I was a professional athlete.
I'm talking about your shoulder.
So... Did you see it?
Long-time friends who are athletes tend to attack directly.
But the punks we deal with don't care if others get hurt or not.
So... don't just run into situations like that. You'll end up really getting hurt.
Do you understand?
And endure it until the end of this month.
Next month, when we get three new members, I'll change your team.
Yesterday, I was a bit harsh.
But you were making demands in front of my juniors, so ...
After you left, I regretted it a lot.
I'll switch your team for you. If it's really that difficult, then I have no choice.
Why are you coming back alone? You didn't meet Lee Soo Yeon?
I met him but we were in different sections.
I plan on going around one more time later.
Good work. The thing about work is, it's only fun when you're doing your own work.
If it's someone else's work, you really don't want to do it.
Excuse me, Section Chief Gong...
Ah, what is it?
About the Fast-track card, which department can I get that from?
It's the Operations Planning Team.
The Operations Planning Team?
After being approved by the Team Leader of the Operations Planning Department, it's handed over to the Airport Love Team. But why?
What? It's nothing.
How is the highway construction proposal going?
It's still under review.
Check that quickly.
This time, since the counters requested by J2 Airlines and PV Airlines are overlapping, then...
Ah... I was just passing by. Then...
First, go to the Public Relations Team. I'll catch up with you soon.
Yes.
This is really driving me crazy!
What do I do? I can't ask the favor, but I can't not ask either.
What kind of favor I can do?
Team Leader.
Do you have something you want to ask me?
Ah, that thing is...
Han Yeo Reum
Just tell me. Let me hear what kind of request you have.
I mean that thing is...
Han Yeo Reum?
I can't. I really can't tell you about it.
So, let's do this.
Why don't we both do favors to each other?
You do what I asked of you yesterday. And I'll grant your request.
I'm sorry, but I can not do that.
There's so much I don't know about Lee Soo Yeon either,
and I don't know how my getting involved between you two can help.
I don't think your request is something I can do anything about.
What did he request from you?
Agent Lee Soo Yeon.
What did this person ask you to do?
No need for you to know. I was just rejected anyway.
I asked Han Yeo Reum.
Aren't you going to answer me?
Team Leader Seo wanted to be on better terms with you.
He said you were brothers once.
Did you even talk about that?
With Han Yeo Reum?
I assumed that Han Yeo Reum knew it.
But when I brought it up, she didn't seem to know much about you.
About the fact that you and I were family for a while,
about the accident twelve years ago,
and also about your current condition.
But... Han Yeo Reum, have you not felt curious about it, not even once?
What do you mean?
You saw Lee Soo Yeon's personnel record on my desk.
You must have seen it clearly written that he has a level 1 of disability.
Usually a level 1 disability is a serious disability in the arms or legs.
It means it's difficult to move on one's own.
But somehow, Lee Soo Yeon ambulates freely and without any abnormality
and, even more, he has this strange super strength.
Han Yeo Reum, have you really never felt curious about it?
I just thought there would be a reason for that, or it could have been an error in the record.
I know it has nothing to do with an error in the record.
Soo Yeon, would you like to answer?
How in the world is that possible?
What exactly are you hiding underneath your clothes?
Agent Lee Soo Yeon.
I'm sorry.
Everyone has something within them that they wish to keep hidden.
♫ Someday in your life, running in different ways ♫
♫ Can someone come and take me to my way? ♫
I don't want anyone to see it.
♫ So lay down just for one night ♫
A secret I do not want to tell anyone...
♫ Will I know. Or see the way of life ♫
Welcome. Thank you for coming.
♫ Will I ever know what's going on? ♫
Look down.
♫ Will I ever see you, ♫
Stomp on her.
Just thinking about it still is a sharply cutting feeling,
a terribly painful memory
Those memories seem to appear in the most unexpected places,
they come out and strike me at present so that they are merciless.
♫ Every time I look at myself in the eyes  ♫
♫ Sometimes when I see it
I’m lost in my own eyes ♫
♫ Every time it feels like an ending for all  ♫
Agent Lee Soo Yeon. Where are you now?
♫ Maybe it's our day to stop  ♫
If you can hear me, please give me an answer.
Agent Lee Soo Yeon.
Lee Soo Yeon.
♫ Life is too short to cry ♫
♫  Every time I look at myself in the eyes  ♫
♫ Sometimes when I see it, I'm lost in my own eyes  ♫
So what about your radio? You haven't found it yet?
Yes. I haven't found it yet.
Ah... Okay.
For the time being, you'll be on stand-by until you find it.
Na Yeong Joo.
You too be on stand-by with Oh Dae Gi. Every time other teams request help, provide them with support.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I understand.
Team Leader, I'll be on stand-by alone. Please exclude Na Yeong Joo.
Why? Does it bother you that she'll suffer for her senior's sloppy work?
That's not a bad attitude to have. But, teamwork isn't only when things are good.
It's enduring together when things are bad and difficult.
Then, good teamwork is going to be created from it at the same time.
Do you have any objections to what I said?
No, sir, I don't.
If it pains you to see Na Yeong Joo suffering, then find the radio quickly.
Understand?
My husband
Yes, it's me. I was too busy to pick up the phone.
Did you finish the work needed on your business trip?
Okay, I got it. Be careful on your way back.
While it's important to work quickly, it's more important to do good work.
Because it's a rest area lounge for our employees.
Ah, yes. I understand.
Oh, look at the time!
It's a shame to part ways already. Should we stop somewhere for a drink?
What?
Ah, well...
Okay.
Let's go then! Let's have a drink and order some eel.
Han Yeo Reum, are you not leaving?
Ah, Lee Soo Yeon has not come back yet.
He'll be back when he's ready to come back. You can call it a day.
Yes, I understand.
Fast Track Pass
Now it's four, but next time it's going to be five...
If you keep going along with it, you'll end up in a position that you won't be able to handle.
Either get to that point and regret it, or stop it now.
You're the only one who can make that decision.
Team Leader.
Lee Soo Yeon will be fine. You don't have to worry about him.
Fast Track Pass
What brings you here at the end of the work day?
You needed 4 fast track passes, right?
I asked for them by the weekend, but you already got them?
See? I knew you could get them if you tried. Girl, thanks!
Do you happen to know this?
Because of you, I lived with no self-esteem or confidence.
My mom and dad both adored me to no end,
but I wasn't able to see their love.
Because the abuse and hate that you and your friends projected towards me,
it hurt so much.
Without hesitation, I would feel intimidated and cower.
Because I seemed ugly to myself.
Hey, why are you bringing up the past?
Those were pranks that everyone does when they're young.
They were just pranks to you?
To me, it was horror and felt like death.
"Should I have never been born?"
"Maybe it would be better if I wasn't living."
Those are some thoughts I had.
This isn't any fun.
Stop talking about the past and just give them to me.
Now I won't live like that anymore.
Han Yeo Reum! What are you doing now?
I won't concern myself with you coming and going in the airport, since it's your job.
However, let's not act like we know each other.
That's how I'm going to be with you.
You! Are you saying you're going to ignore me?
Yes.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Yeah. So you also should live a proper life.
How old are you to still be acting this way?
Aren't you even embarrassed living that way?
Lee Soo Yeon, do you know why my name is Han Yeo Reum?
It's because I was born in the middle of summer.
Mom, it's me. What are you doing?
Did you have dinner?
Yes.
But the season I like the best is actually autumn.
Because I first met my parents in autumn.
How about you, Agent Lee Soo Yeon?
What is your favorite season?
It's summer. Because I first met you
in that season.
I'm sorry.
Truthfully,
I was excited.
Thank you.
In any case, I'm thankful.
Truthfully, I was shaking,
and my heart felt like it was going to explode.
You saw Lee Soo Yeon's personnel record on my desk.
You must've seen that it said Level 1 disability, too.
Like crazy,
and I was angry,
What? You think you found out the cause of it?
Yes. I think I know what it is.
What is it? What is causing the malfunctions?
Han Yeo Reum.
♫ If you see me today, my heart beats. ♫
♫ You comfort all my days. ♫
♬ Because I know you, the yearning for you makes my heart beat  ♬
Where Stars Land