=The Hidden Heir Ye Chen=
(Adapted from "The Peerless Son-in-Law")
=Episode 5=
Today,
we're definitely going to win.
I really didn't expect it.
Xiao Group was almost going bankrupt,
but they've managed to latch onto Dihao.
I heard
the eldest heiress, Xiao Churan,
landed the deal.
I wonder what she did.
You don't know?
It was Mr. Zhang Wenhao
who set up the meeting.
Why would he help her?
What else could it be?
I get it now.
But doesn't she have a husband?
That useless guy?
If it were me,
I'd pick Mr. Zhang too.
Later, Ms. Wang is going
to slap Zhang Wenhao in the face.
This place is nice.
Quit acting here.
Churan,
you should talk some sense into him.
It's still not too late to admit defeat.
What did you say?
I can't hear you with the mask on.
I heard ice packs
help with swelling faster.
Reverse.
Grandma,
look at the time.
Ye Chen,
is Ms. Wang really coming?
Not only has Ms. Wang not come,
but none of Dihao's representatives
have shown up either.
Did they get played?
Ye Chen,
just admit defeat.
Ms. Wang won't be coming today.
Ye Chen, how dare you?
Are you trying to ruin our family?
Don't worry. If I say Dongxue will come,
she'll definitely come.
Get out, now!
- Get out!
- You hear us?
- Hurry up!
You hear us?
Ye Chen,
aren't you going to leave?
Stop embarrassing our family.
Seriously.
Wait.
Get on your knees first.
Exactly.
Ye Chen,
a bet's a bet.
Do you need me to help you out?
She's here!
She's here.
Ms. Wang's here.
(Perfect timing.)
- Don't move!
- Stop!
Stay still.
Mr. Hong.
I've got more numbers.
Zhang Wenhao did this.
He sent me here.
Get him.
Move!
Ms. Wang.
Thank you, Mr. Hong.
Why are you here?
I'm Ye Chen's friend.
He sent me to keep an eye on things.
Thank you.
Ms. Wang,
welcome.
Ms. Xiao, Mr. Ye,
sorry I came late.
Ms. Wang, you're too kind.
Ms. Wang,
it's an honor to have you here.
shall we head upstairs?
Ms. Wang, you're not only capable
but also young and pretty.
Exactly.
Ouch.
I can't feel my arm.
This show is just getting started.
You're leaving?
Since you care so much about Churan,
how can you not witness
her big moment together?
Come on.
Ms. Wang,
here's to a great partnership.
Shall we begin now?
Wait a minute.
I think
Ms. Xiao Churan
should represent Xiao Group
to sign this contract.
It's thanks to her excellent proposal
that we chose to work with Xiao Group.
Grandma,
did you forget something?
(Jinxi Resort Strategic Partnership
Signing Ceremony)
Oh, right.
I can't believe I forgot.
Everyone,
I'd like to take
this moment to announce
that I will propose to the board
to appoint Xiao Churan
as the Chief Operating Officer
of Xiao Group.
Sit still.
(Dihao Group Jinxi Resort
Project Agreement)
(Dihao Group, Wang Dongxue,
Xiao Group, Xiao Churan)
Thank you, Ms. Wang.
Stop right there.
- Grandma.
Get up.
Look at yourself.
I'm getting old.
Watching you youngsters do so well,
I think it's time I step down.
I will propose to the board
to appoint Xiao Hailong
as the chairperson of Xiao Group
and Xiao Weiwei as the CEO.
They'll lead Xiao Churan and the others
and be fully responsible
for the partnership with Dihao Group.
Grandma, you used us
and just threw us away?
You...
You heartless witch.
I disagree.
As long as Grandma is here,
it's not your turn
to manage the Xiao family.
Exactly.
What are you even?
Ms. Wang,
do you agree?
Of course, I don't agree.
Ms. Wang,
I'm doing this
for the reputation
of both our companies.
At Dihao Group,
we only care about Ms. Xiao Churan.
In the future,
we'll only be dealing with her.
If you want to push forward
with your personnel changes,
then I'm sorry,
but I'll have
to terminate the partnership.
But we've already signed the contract.
I can afford the penalty fee.
However, from now on, Dihao Group
will join forces with all our friends
to completely blacklist Xiao Group.
I announce that the previous
appointments are void.
Xiao Group will be led
by Xiao Churan as the chairperson.
She'll be fully responsible
for the partnership with Dihao.
Nice!
- Grandma.
Save your breath.
You'd better think
about how to kneel later.
You two were the ones
who insisted on betting with me.
A bet's a bet.
What do you think, Grandma?
Get on your knees.
Grandma.
Wait.
Don't kneel just yet.
Sit here.
The coronation ceremony has to be grand.
Now you can kneel.
Wait.
This is such an important occasion.
We have to get a photo.
Alright.
Congratulations, Ms. Xiao.
Thank you.
Ms. Xiao,
let's work together in the future.
I got to say,
thank you for today.
You were really cool.
Well, I won't see you off.
Alright, bye.
Did you see
Mr. Zhang's face just now? What a sight.
It's all thanks to Ye Chen.
Churan, can you take
Mom and Dad home first?
I've got something to take care of.
Alright.
Be careful.
Just kicking him while he's down.
Mom, Dad, take care.
Who did he mean?
No one. Let's go.
Alright, let's go.
Guys, thanks for your hard work.
Chen.
Chen, you're too polite.
We're going back to report to Mr. Hong.
Give him my regards.
Sure thing.
- We're leaving now.
- Thanks.
How was that?
Wasn't that a great show?
Did you enjoy it?
Ye Chen,
don't get too cocky.
Our issue isn't over yet.
Zhang Wenhao,
you and your family are done for.
Ye Chen,
my family might not
compare to Dihao Group,
but we're still
one of the top in Jinzhou.
We've got a big business.
You can't just say we're done for.
Who do you think you are?
(Dad)
Answer it.
There might be a surprise.
Yes, Dad?
You troublemaker!
What did you do on earth?
Dihao Group just told me
they're terminating
all partnerships with our family!
Now all the shareholders
are dumping our stocks.
You've ruined
our decades of hard work!
Dad, wait.
You're not my son!
I...
Mr. Ye.
Mr. Ye, I'm sorry.
I surrender.
Mr. Ye,
please have mercy on me.
Please spare my family.
I have two important women in my life.
One is Madam Li,
and the other is Churan.
You kept Madam Li from getting surgery.
You harassed Churan
and spread rumors about her.
I might forgive anyone in my life,
but not you.
Mr. Zhang,
see you next time.
Wait, no.
I hope I never see you again.
♪I belong to no one♪
♪I am the ember
that refuses to bow to destiny♪
♪Even if the world burns me into ash♪
♪I will rise upon those ashes♪
♪They said I was only meant
to gaze at the light♪
♪Never knowing I am the flame itself♪
♪I am fireworks, not a fire cast aside♪
♪I open my eyes amid the ruins♪
♪No one shields me
from the wind or the sky♪
♪Let them mock, let them sneer♪
♪I sharpen my silence into blades♪
♪Every cold word, I remember♪
♪Etching my path of defiance
into my heart♪
♪Fate did not sign my future for me♪
♪I carved my own light
with clenched fists♪
♪I belong to no one♪
♪I am the ember
that refuses to bow to destiny♪
♪Even if the world burns me into ash♪
♪I will rise upon those ashes♪