=The Hidden Heir Ye Chen=
(Adapted from "The Peerless Son-in-Law")
=Episode 27=
It was her!
She's the one who said it!
She said your mother-in-law is very rich
and loves to show it off.
She hates your mother-in-law.
So she asked me
to set up this scheme with her.
It was her.
Qian Hongyan!
You lowlife!
You actually set me up to scam me?
She's lying!
She was the one who came to me first!
She told me
to lure you into the trap.
She'd already had her eye on you.
You lied to me, didn't you?
You lied to me!
Come out now!
Come out!
You lied to me!
Mom! Mom!
Qian Hongyan, you liar!
Stop it!
Take her back to our house first.
I'll deal with her later.
Get up!
Move!
Now that no one else is here,
let's talk about the USB drive.
Who sent you?
I... I don't know.
I don't know!
-Talk!
- The money came
from an overseas account.
They paid me to set up this scheme.
(Another overseas account...)
Ms. Lan, I was wrong!
Please forgive me!
Please forgive me, Ms. Lan!
Changkun, I was blinded by greed.
Please don't hold it against me!
I'm begging you. Please let me go!
Churan, you're the most sensible one,
the kindest one.
Please say a few words for me.
You liar!
And you still have the nerve to cry?
Why...
Why are you all looking at me?
Alright, I was wrong, okay?
I...
They tricked me into it!
If you weren't so greedy,
could they have tricked you?
I...
I don't know what came over me.
Mom,
Ye Chen already has it hard enough.
Please stop making things harder for him.
You can't blame Mom entirely either.
Their real target was me.
Chen, you're the best.
Can you tell me what's
on that USB drive?
Is it very valuable?
Both yes and no.
It's just some commercial secrets.
Mr. Qin asked me
to keep it safe for him.
Ye Chen,
I was wrong!
Please let me go! Please forgive me!
Let me ask you one thing.
Did the rest
of the Xiao family know about this?
Did the scam work?
Did you take the photos?
Did you get the villa?
Did Ye Chen cry?
They called the police!
They're going to send me to jail!
I don't want to go to jail!
Xiao Changqian!
Save me please!
That's enough already.
Why call the police?
I'll beat some sense into you!
You hit me?
So what if I did?
I'm your uncle.
If you pull this kind of stunt again,
I'll slap you again.
But you didn't really lose anyth...
Do you even hear yourself?
Xiao Changkun!
Have you lost your mind?
How dare you hit my children?
I'm telling you!
If you won't discipline them, then I will!
I...
Come on!
Hit me.
Go on.
Hit me again.
Come on.
I...
Let me tell you.
if you don't teach your kids,
someone else will have to.
Look at the state our family is in now.
It's a disgrace.
Are you even still my elder brother?
When we were kids,
you treated me so well.
You saved my life.
I nearly drowned
when I went fishing in the river,
and you were the one
who saved me, remember?
Right?
But look at you now.
Your hand is raised,
like you're going to hit me.
Are you really my brother?
Enough!
Hongyan may be at fault,
but you were unfilial first.
What's all this fighting for?
We're all family here.
I've never felt like we were family!
Who here ever treated me like family?
Mom,
you've looked down on me
since I was a child.
You never respected me.
You thought I was stupid, useless,
and that I wasn't cunning enough!
After Father died,
you got even worse.
You drove my family out
of the ancestral house.
And later, when Changqian
bullied me again and again,
did you ever stop him?
Are you really my mother?
Let me tell you,
you're the one most responsible
for the state our family is in now.
Family scandals
shouldn't be aired in public.
Xiao Group
is still under my control.
If you keep making trouble,
then Xiao Churan
can forget about staying chairwoman.
Fine.
Then I won't
be chairwoman anymore.
Ye Chen,
you jinx!
Look at what you've done!
Look what you've
turned the Xiao family into!
Weren't you the ones
who always called me trash?
Called me useless?
So why do you think so highly of me now?
To be honest,
I've always disliked you all.
But at the same time,
I'm grateful to you all.
If it weren't for you all,
I wouldn't have married
into the Xiao family.
I wouldn't have met kind-hearted Churan,
upright Dad,
and Mom, who can be vain
and greedy at times,
but with a good heart.
We are the real family.
And I won't allow any outsider
to bully my family.
What do we do?
The police are here.
Who sent that scammer?
I've already asked Song Wanting
to track that overseas account.
At the same time, I've asked Kun
to investigate the phone number
that directed him.
Whoever is behind this,
the truth will come out soon.
Trying to mess with me won't be so easy.
What I'm worried about is you all.
Just look, Mom got dragged into this too.
I've already talked with her properly.
After this,
she'll definitely change.
Qian Hongyan is involved
in a major fraud case.
She'll be in prison
for at least several years.
Old Mrs. Xiao and the others
weren't directly involved,
but they've been detained
for a few days.
They'll be released soon.
But no matter who it is,
anyone who dares to touch my family
will pay the price.
(Lawyer's Letter)
On behalf of Dihao Group,
I hereby formally notify you.
Dihao Group has decided
to terminate all cooperation
with Xiao Group.
(Lawyer's Letter)
Huaying Pharma
has also decided
to terminate all cooperation
with Xiao Group.
Song Group
will never have any business dealings
with Xiao Group too.
(New Xiao Group)
Congratulations, Ms. Xiao!
(Grand Opening)
Congratulations!
- Thank you, Mr. Hao!
- Thank you.
Please, come inside!
Congratulations, Ms. Xiao and Mr. Ye.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Churan.
Dihao will give you our full support.
Thank you, Ms. Wang.
Thank you.
Madam, congratulations.
Happy grand opening.
(Super Red Envelope)
Here's a gift.
Thank you.
My dad also said,
if any of our projects interest you,
feel free to pick whichever you like.
Congratulations, Mr. Ye.
Thank you, Ms. Song.
Ms. Song,
my madam's company just opened,
and you're only congratulating
my master?
My apologies.
I've been rude.
Congratulations to you as well,
Ms. Xiao.
Miss Xiao?
Shouldn't you call her Mrs. Ye?
It's alright,  Ms. Song.
Thank you.
Churan, go greet the guests.
- I need to talk to  Ms. Song.
- Okay.
- Please, this way.
- Alright.
Smooth sailing and prosperity.
The three accounts you gave me
were routed through multiple layers
of a Myanmar scam network.
They were transferred many times,
taking countless detours.
After comparing all the transactions,
we finally traced the original source
of the funds
to an offshore company registered
in the Cayman Islands.
And the actual controlling shareholder
behind that company is...
Tang Sihai.
Looks like you already
have your suspicions.
Haven't you always had a partnership
with Dihao?
Why would Tang Sihai...
It's a long story.
Hard to explain in a few words.
Do you need my help?
Actually, there is something
I could use your help with.
Sure.
But once it's done,
you must join Song Group
as our Chief Appraiser.
Have you found out
who's using the phone number
that instructed He Lian
to set up the trap?
Not yet.
Give me a little more time.
We've been friends for years.
I know you too well.
Does it have something
to do with Wang Dongxue?
That phone number
is indeed registered
under Dongxue's name.
But I'm sure
there must be some misunderstanding.
Dongxue is such a good person.
There's no way
she'd do something like this.
Even if she did,
I'm sure Tang Sihai
was the one behind it.
You can't blame Dongxue entirely.
Daokun,
we're best friends.
I won't force you.
Cut the nonsense.
We're best friends for life.
(Hired killer to stage a car crash.
Obsessed with the formula)
(The mastermind)
(Hired killer to stage a car crash.
Killed Madam Li)
(Old Mr. Xiao kept one copy
of the formula)
(Cooperate with the Xiao family
under Tang Sihai's orders.)
I knew I'd find you here.
(The mastermind)
Are you sure?
We're still waiting
for Song Wanting's confirmation.
What are you going to do next?
Revenge.
Mr. Tang, have a drink.
Excuse me.
Ms. Song, if you have something to say,
just say it.
I'd like to make a deal with you, sir.
Go on.
Hand Ye Chen over to me.
You can't handle him anyway.
And you think you can handle him?
I could try.
Nothing.
There's nothing.
See? I told you
there must be some misunderstanding.
Think about it again.
Ye Chen is mine.
No one is taking him away.
Let me offer you a piece of advice,
Ms. Song.
Some games are not something
you should casually step into.
This is bigger than you can handle.
Thank you for the concern, Mr. Tang.
But I'm already
in the game.
♪They said I was only meant
to gaze at the light♪
♪Never knowing I am the flame itself♪
♪I am fireworks, not a fire cast aside♪
♪I open my eyes amid the ruins♪
♪No one shields me
from the wind or the sky♪
♪Let them mock, let them sneer♪
♪I sharpen my silence into blades♪
♪Every cold word, I remember♪
♪Etching my path of defiance
into my heart♪
♪Fate did not sign my future for me♪
♪I carved my own light
with clenched fists♪
♪I belong to no one♪
♪I am the ember
that refuses to bow to destiny♪
♪Even if the world burns me into ash♪
♪I will rise upon those ashes♪