[Guilty Maid]
[Episode 18]
Aren't you scared?
I am.
But the living terrify me
more than the dead.
There are things I have to uncover.
I can't just become a scapegoat.
Wait for me.
Master,
I have to protect Xingyan.
Qiuyue.
Call for me
when you're done.
Madam,
you're upright and honorable.
So there's no need to be afraid.
Come here.
You know how to conduct an autopsy?
Common knowledge.
No abdominal swelling.
No wrinkled soles.
No silt under the nails.
No foam or mud in the nose or mouth.
Hands clenched in a defensive posture.
Madam,
the Master didn't die from drowning.
He was thrown into water after death.
Clenched fists.
Defensive posture.
He was defending himself.
That proves he was murdered.
But I only know how to
check for drowning.
Still, we've confirmed
it was a staged drowning.
So, Second Madam,
you can rest assured
and invite a coroner now.
The First Madam left the mansion late
at night with the Master's body.
She's implicated
in his death.
Now,
there's no point in staying here.
But with this face,
even if I return to the Su family
and confront Shaohua,
will my parents believe me?
This curse upon me
was likely brought about by Shaohua.
The world is vast.
Yet where do I belong?
What are you doing now?
Zhou Furong is in a coma.
Did you know?
How would I know?
Qiuyue is all thumbs.
She can't administer an abortifacient.
How could she conduct an autopsy
or use my mother
to absolve herself?
I...
I was pretending all along.
Now it's a matter of life and death.
I just don't want to hide anymore.
I'll give you a chance.
Tell me you're not Qiuyue,
and I'll spare you.
Shen Xingyan,
I won't trust you again.
Mr. Shen, what do you mean?
I am Qiuyue.
No sigil?
Mr. Shen, if you want me,
I'd be more than delighted.
Why resort to force?
You're indeed not her.
Mr. Shen,
I'm already carrying your child.
Why play hard to get?
Stop spouting nonsense.
Xingyan,
[Account Book]
these are our family's accounts.
I've reviewed them. There's no problem.
Take a look at this.
Someone left it at my doorstep.
It scared me to death when I opened it.
It records all the secret accounts
of the Shen family
over the years.
Secret accounts?
Take a look.
The jewelry we sold
to those officials and nobles
in the capital
turns out to be
gold-plated silver fakes!
If this ever reaches the capital,
the entire Shen clan
couldn't appease their fury.
Check this out.
This was ordered by the Princess.
She's wearing it at the Marquis's
birthday banquet next month.
It's all fake.
Strange.
Why are there so many transactions
with the Su family?
Xingyan,
the Princess and the Marquis
are ruthless killers.
What will we do
if they ever find out?
Oh no, we're doomed.
The Shen family this time...
We're truly finished.
What do we do?
What should we do?
Mother,
you're the mistress of the house now.
No more panic like this, OK?
I...
I'll investigate
these secret accounts.
The Su family has always dealt
in medicinal herbs.
I've never heard
of any business dealings
with the Shen family.
Is it
connected to my sister?
Mr. Shen,
we still haven't found Miss Su.
Keep searching.
Mr. Shen,
with the Shen family in such turmoil...
I told you to search.
Need I repeat myself?
No, sir.
[Account Book]
Su Yunqing,
why do you always make me
search for you?
Greetings, Fourth Madam.
Qiuyue, come and sit.
No need for formalities.
Though we've never interacted before,
I've seen what you did
regarding the Master's death.
I just like
clever girls like you.
Here.
Thank you, Madam.
But
I don't think you called me here
just to say that.
Qiuyue,
what are your plans for the future?
Plans?
What plans could I possibly have
with this face now?
With your insight, you didn't come here
just to be a concubine, did you?
Rather than living under others' roof,
at their mercy,
why not
stand tall as your true self?