[Guilty Maid]
[Episode 5]
Do you still remember
our three-month pact?
Do you still remember?
Mr. Shen,
did you hear that?
So Wei Xian
is truly your lover?
Yes.
The Fourth Madam
threatened me with my account books.
I finally found an opportunity
to bring her down.
Why must you
ruin your own reputation to shield her?
She is innocent.
I'm not shielding her.
You're still denying it?
The Fourth Madam
has already exposed my secret ledgers
to the First Madam.
If she pursues this,
years of my efforts will be wasted.
And it's all thanks to you!
Quietly throw her
into the well
in the Fourth Madam's courtyard.
Don't let her sully the feng shui here.
Understood.
I can't die yet.
I haven't found my sister.
If you want to survive,
you'll have to learn patience.
I'd rather not return
to find you in the mass graves.
No.
No, please!
Third Madam!
Third Madam, have mercy!
The matter of the falsified accounts
can be a big deal or a minor one.
If I can help you
get through this crisis,
will you spare my life?
Falsifying ledgers
is no trivial offense.
We might as well hear her out.
Spare you?
Why should I trust you again?
I have a plan.
Please hear me out.
Speak.
It could work.
But I don't trust you.
Cuiqiao,
keep an eye on her.
Yes.
Mount Wudang's Fuzhen Temple
is a sacred place for scholars.
Each Chinese New Year,
only the first ten devotees
who offer incense may receive
the Taoist master's blessed amulet.
Some have offered
a thousand liang of gold,
yet failed to obtain
such divine blessings.
This amulet
cannot be acquired on a whim.
Third Madam could have someone
purchase a common talisman.
I can craft a convincing replica.
Liuli.
This concerns Mr. Shen's future.
No one would dare tear open the amulet
to verify its authenticity.
Thus, the plan is foolproof.
Third Madam,
[Shen Mansion]
what do you have to say?
First Madam,
I did falsify the accounts.
But some transactions
simply cannot be recorded openly.
Well, well.
[First Madam of the Shen family]
Abusing your position
to embezzle family funds
and you still dare to justify yourself?
Ms. Liu.
[Ms. Liu, First Madam's Head Servant]
Mete out the family's punishment.
First Madam, do not be hasty.
Look.
Divine blessings are beyond price.
The more one sacrifices,
the more one gains.
This is an amulet
I secured for Mr. Shen
to ensure his smooth career advancement.
You spent so much on an amulet?
If it truly came from Mount Wudang,
no amount of money would be excessive.
Divine blessings are beyond price.
What worries me
is that someone might deceive us
with a fake.
A fake?
This was consecrated
by Mount Wudang's Taoist master himself.
Second Madam,
if you doubt its authenticity,
you may open it and check.
But let me warn you,
once opened,
Mr. Shen's career
will suffer dire consequences.
First Madam,
if you wish to examine it,
I will tear it open
to prove my innocence.
Mr. Shen's future
outweighs all else.
This is no trivial matter.
You're only so bold
because you know no one would dare
gamble with Mr. Shen's prospects.
What a clever move.
Admit
this is your forgery!
Second Madam,
how could I possibly
have fabricated this amulet?
[Cuiqiao, Head maid]
On your knees!
Even Cuiqiao left her
after all those years.
You're new here.
How dare you hide things?
Say this amulet is fake!
The the funds she embezzled
were never spent on this.
Second Madam,
Cuiqiao sacrificed Mr. Shen's future
for her own gain.
She's the one who should be punished.
Still defiant, are you?
You think I won't risk
my son's future, don't you?
Fine.
Cuiqiao,
fetch the scissors.
Now,
I'll cut open this amulet
and see what's truly inside!
I've seen consecrated ones before.
They cannot be replicated.
Look.
Look!
This is clearly...
This is...
It's...
This is clearly...
Last time, I ruined
Cuiqiao's chance at merit.
And she holds grudges.
If she exposes this,
I'll be in grave trouble.
Fortunately, my sister's sachet
contains the very talisman
I once procured for her.
I've kept it with me all this time.
It was consecrated.
They shouldn't be able to
tell the difference.
Madam,
it's indeed from Mount Wudang.
They say Mount Wudang's Fuzhen Temple
is a sacred place for scholars.
Miraculously potent.
Truly hard to obtain.
How can this be real?
How...
How could this happen?
As Mr. Shen's mother,
how dare you sever his divine blessings!
You seek to ruin his career,
to destroy the Master's plans
in the capital!
Impossible!
This can't be real!
You!
Didn't you claim
it was fake?
You're the one who set me up!
I...
This is what you get for crossing me!
Taking my money and lying to me!
You'd better pray my son
becomes the top scholar,
or you'll pay dearly!
I must inform Shen Xingyan
of my situation
and ask him to tell me
where my sister is.
But where can I find him?
If I speak rashly,
will he even believe me?
What's happening?
This feeling
is like last time.
This is
the woodshed?
I've become Cuiqiao this time?
I have loads of money.
I doubt whether you possess
anything of genuine worth.
I've devoted my entire life
to refining this elixir.
Upon ingestion,
it concentrates one's vital energy
to form a lycoris radiata sigil
at the Yunmen acupoint.
Will this
truly condemn her
to a lifetime of misery?
Whenever those she despises face peril,
she shall assume their forms
to bear their misfortunes
and to live eternally
wearing the faces of her loathed ones.
Are you satisfied?
Su Yunqing.
I feel like I've become someone else.
Su Yunqing!
So this is the sigil.
She was truly cursed
with something so vile.
You're finally awake, Mr. Shen.
Here.
The physician said it was krait venom.
A moment later,
and you might have been dead.
This is all my negligence.
Don't blame yourself.
Who could have thought
the First Prince's men
would resort to venom?
How long was I unconscious?
Five days.
What about the investigation
into the Fourth Madam?
I've been secretly observing.
But she bears no resemblance
to Su Yunqing.
However,
when we rescued
the Fourth Madam that day,
a maid mentioned something
about a three-month pact.
Where is that maid now?
Mr. Shen,
easy there.
It was the one
who exposed Wei Xian's identity.
But the Third Madam
took her away afterward.
Get her back now.
Understood.
Su Yunqing,
no matter what you become,
I'll always find you.
Wait for me.
You'll remain here
until the imperial results
are announced.
If my son fails to place first,
you'll suffer dearly.
But he never sat
for the imperial examination.
How could he possibly place first?
What should I do?