[Guilty Maid]
[Episode 16]
I heard about the blueprints.
Familiar, aren't they?
I helped design those
for my former best friend.
But she's dead.
Now,
I have no friends left.
Yunqing,
it is my bad.
please,
please help me!
Yunqing,
Mr. Shen threw me out.
Even the First Madam hates me.
I don't want to go back to the workshop.
Yunqing,
give me a hand,
just this once.
Please help me one last time!
Yunqing,
I only have you now.
please,
I beg you.
Please help me!
I'm no longer the Su Yunqing you knew.
The Su Yunqing you knew
is already gone.
Yunqing.
Su Yunqing!
Qiuyue,
why're you here?
Well,
it's you.
You made that blueprint, didn't you?
Besides Su Yunqing,
only you knew
I designed those pieces.
You're all trying to ruin me.
You're all trying to ruin me!
Why?
I finally made it to the main house,
yet you still won't let me go!
You bullied me.
I have no choice.
So it's you.
Why do you always oppose me?
Why?
Say something!
Tell me,
why!
Bury the corpse.
Keep it quiet.
Just a maid.
Wait,
this's a human life.
Madams,
don't you obey the laws?
How do you know she didn't kill herself?
A proper investigation would tell.
We should report this.
First Madam,
in my opinion,
there's something evil
in this house.
Three maids have fainted.
Now one is dead.
Shouldn't we find a master...?
Nonsense!
We're all fine
without any trouble.
If word gets out,
we'll be laughed at!
I said to bury her.
And no one can object.
She must've died earlier.
So there's a foul smell lately.
It's strongest near First Madam's court.
Not here.
Did she die there first?
Who knows?
First Madam acted strangely today.
Just hold up!
It's so unlucky.
Escort me back.
My head aches.
Strange events mean trouble's near.
Could it be...?
Someone else died in her court?
She's hiding it
and won't report this.
Why did First Madam order a carriage
in midnight?
I saw Zhou Furong leave with her too.
Were they heading out together?
Things aren't peaceful in the mansion.
I guess something would happen.
Be careful these days.
Madam.
First Madam!
Don't believe Zhou Furong's lies!
She's a liar!
What are you yelling at midnight?
Zhou Furong,
don't hide in First Madam's carriage.
Come out!
What are you hiding from?
Come out right now!
Face me!
Shut up!
You want to wake everyone up?
Zhou Furong isn't here.
Ms. Liu,
come here.
First Madam.
Madam.
Madam!
Things have come to this.
There's no other way.
Pity the child in her womb.
First Madam!
Look what you've done.
You just woke everyone up.
Zhou Furong isn't here.
Go back now.
I don't believe it!
First Madam fell into the lake!
Someone!
Help!
Hurry up!
This way!
Is she okay?
Master Shen.
Where's Master?
Useless fools!
Save Master!
Go save him!
Save him!
Why was Master in the carriage?
When did he come back?
So late at night,
why were they going out together?
Why would they share one carriage?
That's strange.
Qiuyue!
She killed Master!
Go! Catch her!
Don't let her escape!
Go, go, go!
I heard Qiuyue's been caught.
I can't believe she killed Master.
She's crazy.
She'll be beaten to death this time.
Oh no,
am I turning into Qiuyue?
So it's true,
I've become the murderer
who killed Master.