Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Reunion: The Sound of the Providence Season 2
Episode 7
Don't cry.
I'm still alive and kicking.
Mr. Third Junior
You got such a serious illness.
Why are you hiding it from me?
I didn't hide it from you on purpose.
I didn't plan to tell everyone
from the very beginning
But have you ever thought about
everyone around you wants to know how you're doing,
especially the one who loves you.
You are still too young.
You can't tell the difference between love and worship.
I hope you can grow up and
don't act on impulse.
Right now Xue and his gang
are watching every move of our Wu family.
They've put surveillance on me.
If you don't believe it,
go outside to take a look now.
Xue's people are everywhere out there.
So right now anyone who gets close to me
will be in trouble.
I don't want you to get involved.
I'm not afraid of troubles.
Is there anything that I can be of help?
Just tell me.
Bai, thank you.
If I need help,
I will definitely go to you.
I'll come to see you later today.
Rest in bed.
Okay.
Fatty, Fatty!
Hurry up! I need to go to the bathroom.
You feel the call of nature suddenly?
Okay.
Sit on this and I'll push you there.
I need to pee so bad.
You should have let Bai take you to the bathroom.
Of course I couldn't tell her that!
Bai did ask me just now
that what she could do to help me.
I was too embarrassed to say that I needed to go to the bathroom.
Will we be like this when we are old?
When we're pushing eighties…
Can you hurry up? I can't hold back anymore!
I know, I know.
Hold it back!
You must hold it back.
Go, go!
Can you stop joggling it?
Speed or stability? Pick one.
Steady and fast. Hurry up!
Go, go, go!
Mute.
When will the tide ebb?
Should be today.
What time today?
Soon.
You said so every time.
Mute.
Mute. This is bad.
Don't speak.
Take a deep breath.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
What is this place? There are holes everywhere.
Glasses.
Look around. Be alert.
Mute.
This hole is so strange.
There is nothing inside.
It scared me.
Have you found anything?
No.
How about you?
Me either.
Let's go.
Tony Qiang and I were caught by Mr. Jiao.
Bring the map to Thunder City here to save us.
The video has expired for several days.
Do you want to do it or not?
It's been a whole day.
Black Glasses didn't do anything.
He definitely doesn't like you.
There is nothing wrong with your video.
Why hasn't Black Glasses showed up?
You saw it yourself.
I'm not important to him at all.
Mr. Jiao.
I have done everything you asked me to do.
It's just that to Black Glasses,
the thing you want is more important than me.
Yes indeed.
Since he doesn't care about you at all,
why should I still keep you alive?
Right?
Mr. Jiao, I beg you.
Please let me go.
Let you go or not,
it's up to the thunder to decide.
Sorry.
Thunder wants you to die.
I love you.
I only have 30 hours left to solve Xue's problem.
I don't know if Uncle Erbai's still alive.
And I don't know what's going on with Kylin either.
I have no money now.
Xue.
It all comes down to whether you'll take the bait or not.
Mr. Third Junior.
I've finished sorting out the goods.
But there are not many left actually.
Bai.
Make a signage for me
saying that
Hao's Antique Shop is going to have an auction.
Auction?
Yes.
But the few things left
are not very valuable.
I don't think the buyers will want them.
Of course we can't just rely on those antiques.
I'm going to take out my big gun.
It's something that Xue always wanted.
What is it?
Grave Robbery Notes?
You want to auction Grave Robbery Notes?
If you want to catch big fish,
you need to use good bait.
This time
I'm going to settle the accounts once and for all with Xue.
I'll let him know
how I earned my reputation in this cycle back then.
Hao's Antique Shop
Wu Xie
Mr. Third Junior, look.
What do you think?
You women's makeup stuff is like magic.
But can you make me look healthier?
Look healthier?
Sure.
Hao's Antique Shop
Grave Robbery Notes' Auction Plan
Mr. Third Junior.
Why do you want to
show Xue that you look healthier?
Those who are dying of illness
will have a short moment of looking better right before they die.
Don't jinx it.
I was just saying.
I just want to make
myself look better
so that Xue won't be sure what's going on with my body.
This is called confusing your opponent. Do you understand?
This is the first step in my plan to deal with Xue.
I have spent a lot of thought on it.
Looking healthier?
So that roughly equals to a flushing complexion.
No problem.
Leave it to me.
Alright, we're finished.
Mr. Third Junior.
What are you doing?
These people are
all seniors in the antique circle.
They will never let the Grave Robbery Notes
fall
into the hands of that old bastard Xue.
So
we are going to tell everyone that
we're going to auction the Grave Robbery Notes.
The bigger the fuss is, the better.
Be friends with the enemy of our enemy.
This is the second step.
Roger that.
What's so funny?
Bai Haotian!
It's from one of the five famous kilns.
Mr. Fifth.
You really have a keen eye for good stuff.
Let me tell you.
This is a plum vase with carved patterns produced in Ding Kiln.
Close it.
I won't say anything harsh.
But Ding Kiln porcelains
have a sleek outline and beautifully drawn patterns.
Look at that lousy patterns
drawn with trembling hands of an amateur.
Are you kidding me?
Mr. Fifth.
You can't just decide it's a fake
with nothing but your judgement.
If it weren't for my granddaughter's sick and I need money,
I wouldn't have wanted to sell it.
I need the money to save her life.
If you have a family emergency and
you need money to save your granddaughter,
no problem. Just leave it here.
I'll give you 20,000 yuan.
If you need more, just come to me again, okay?
But Mr. Fifth.
This is taking advantage of you.
I can't take your money.
If you don't accept it,
what are you going to do with your granddaughter's illness?
I was just kidding.
Just accept it.
Actually I also need to ask you for a favor.
I heard that
you granddaughter
has a photographic memory.
I want her to
do something for me with this ability.
No problem, Mr. Fifth.
As long as I can be of help,
I'll call her over right now.
Mr. Third Junior.
Do you think Xue will really come?
The news that we are going to auction Grave Robbery Notes
has already spread out.
I believe, from what I know of him,
he will grow suspicious
and so
he will
sound me out again before the auction.
This is the third step in my plan to deal with him.
We'll just wait for him to take the bait.
Mr. Third Junior.
Why do I feel that
you've become a different person after you woke up this time?
That's because you didn't know the real me before.
Hey, don't be so rude.
The grand auction.
You are not welcome here.
I'm here for this.
You even made tea for me?
You think this is your cup? You just drank from it.
Why can't you live your life more daintily?
Mr. Third Junior. You are still so dainty
when you have hit the rock bottom.
Fine.
The conflicts between us
are long-existing.
I don't have any resources to fight against you anymore.
Now you brought your people to have a good laugh of me?
What?
Kicking someone when he's already down?
I'm not here just to have a good laugh.
I heard that you are going to have an auction.
But you sold fake antiques earlier
and we still haven't settled the score yet.
If I allow a shop like this to hold an auction,
the rules of the industry will be broken.
As the industry leader,
I can't just sit back and watch it happen.
How about I smash this shop again
so you can forget about having an auction?
You can try.
If you dare touch anything in here,
you'll have to answer to me.
You even have a sidekick.
Okay.
Or you can do a package deal
of selling this shop together with
all your baubles to me.
Then it will quench my anger.
While you're still breathing,
hurry up to save the people you want to save.
Maybe you can see them one last time.
I mean you guys can see each other one last time.
Mr. Xue.
I thought you didn't think
my baubles have any value.
Don't play dumb with me.
What I want is Grave Robbery Notes.
Oh, you want Grave Robbery Notes?
If you want it,
you'll have to
wait for the auction.
Take the offer while I'm still talking to you nicely.
I'll still get it in a few days no matter what.
The problem is, it's not that I don't want to give it to you.
Everyone has known that
I'm going to auction off the Grave Robbery Notes.
If you suddenly break the rules by
taking it from me with force in advance,
can you still do business in this industry
when everyone finds out what you did?
I refuse to give it to you for your own good.
Or I can ask around for you to
see what everyone has to say.
Hello, Mr. Sun.
Nothing important.
I just want to tell you that
Mr. Xue is here in my shop
saying that he wants to take Grave Robbery Notes.
Could you do me a favor asking
Mr. Zou and Curator Liu to
see if they are okay with it?
Will they agree to let Mr. Xue
take Grave Robbery Notes ahead of the auction?
If you guys agree,
I will give it to him now.
No can do?
Just with your cheap antiques,
I'll take your last name
if they show up at your auction!
Let's go!
Hello, Fatty?
How are things going at your side?
Yes, I'm here keeping an eye on her.
Don't worry.
What's the current progress of the stuff now?
It's no use rushing her.
She's a master, right?
Masters all have attitude.
Just focus on your job.
How are things going on your side?
Xue has already been here.
The only thing we need is your stuff.
You have to make sure it's finished on time.
Got it. Rest assured.
Consider it done.
Day 1
Master.
Can you take some time out to
work on my rush order first?
It's still early yet.
It's not early.
It'll be too late if you don't get started now, master.
You have taken a deposit.
You can't do this to me.
I will refund you the money.
I won't take this job.
Don't, don't.
Come on!
That's not what I meant.
You have to take this job.
Who else can I go to if you don't take this job?
But we're really in a hurry.
I'm begging you, okay?
When will you need it?
The day after…I mean tomorrow.
I can't. I won't take this job.
But we desperately need it.
Someone's life depends on it.
No.
Say it.
What exactly do you want?
Unless
you give me your skin.
Nonsense!
You're such a nutjob.
what kind of sick joke is this?
It seems that you don't want it desperately enough.
I do!
I'll give you ten seconds.
Ten.
You…
-Stop it.
-Nine.
-Young lady!
-Eight.
What kind of trick is this?
Five.
-Four.
-I've seen
-Three.
-this world so much more than you have.
-Two.
-You think you can scare me away?
One.
Okay! I'll do it.
But which part of me do you want?
Are you making my skin into a bag
or a leather jacket?
Even if it's a bag, wallet or duffel bag?
Mr. Fifth.
Wu Xie!
It's me.
Them are here.
All of them want to go to Hao's Antique Shop's auction to get some stuff.
Hao's Antique Shop has valuable stuff.
Xue wants to go solo this time.
We can't let him have it.
What's going on?
Mr. Xue.
Since everyone is present today,
I'll cut to the chase.
You know very well
whom Wu Xie made an appointment secretly to see his goods.
You can't keep all the good stuff to yourself.
What are you talking about?
Watch your mouth!
Curator Liu is a senior.
It's not easy for him to come visit you.
Can you two calm down?
That's exactly why we called both of you here to confront
since we don't trust each other.
I know what you mean and
we did always do as Mr. Xue said.
But didn't we all agree that
none of us would go to
Wu Xie's auction?
We'll wait until he can't insist anymore, then
we'll buy his shop and split the profits we earn.
How can you go without us
asking him for that Grave Robbery Notes?
Mr. Xue.
We always follow you
no matter you wanted to us to gang up to squeeze down the goods' price or get a bargain.
But this time
if you want to ditch us to get the good stuff to yourself,
we won't let you do it.
Mr. Zou, relax.
You know it better than anyone
if Wu Xie has valuable goods or not.
He's just bluffing.
So you mean
there is nothing precious at all in this auction?
What treasure can he possibly have now?
This is nothing but his plan to turn us against each other
like what we're doing now.
He'll profit from it
if we can't team up to squeeze down the price.
Then why did you go visit him?
I went to sound him out, obviously.
He told me he had a precious antique.
I went there and
I didn't even see anything.
If you believe me,
just listen to me this time.
None of us makes a bid in the auction.
He won't be able to sell at a high price so
all of his things will still be ours.
Why can't you just calm down and wait in patience?
That's well said.
But I'm just afraid that some people might point us to the wrong direction.
I'd say
let's listen to Mr. Xue
and not go to the auction this time.
That's right.
Since you guys are here now, don't be in a hurry to leave.
Spend the night in my place and
let me entertain everyone.
Sixth, get the guest rooms ready.
Mr. Third Junior.
I asked around.
They are at Xue's place.
I guess they're questioning him.
I will get some more tea.
Hello?
She's working on it. I'm keeping an eye on her.
But I dare not rush her.
Okay.
I'll take another look.
Don't hang up.
Master.
Are you tired?
Master?
Let me get you some water.
How is it going?
Can you be quiet?
Or
I can sew up your fat lips.
Just wait.
I don't know when she can finish it.
Anyway, do as fast as possible.
Xue has taken the bait.
We must hurry and
get the thing ready before the auction.
Sure, no problem.
Okay. Gotta go.
This is bad, Mr. Third Junior.
Those who originally said they would come to the auction
are not coming.
Who are they?
Mr. Zou, Vice President Sun,
and Curator Liu all said they're not coming.
That's great.
That means Xue
have detained these people.
He is determined to get
our fake Grave Robbery Notes.
He will definitely buy it.
Really?
Bai.
Go away.
Don't try to bully us!
No one can bully us.
Hao's Antique Shop
Hao's Antique Shop's Auction
Grave Robbery Notes
This is the first time
I've seen an auction with so few bidders.
You see, only I've come.
So Mr. Xue, you want to
get all my goods at a rock-bottom price?
Do you think I'm interested in
the goods you put on the list?
It doesn't matter if you are interested or not,
I won't sell
the Grave Robbery Notes to you.
I don't want it either.
Wu Xie.
I'm here
to do business with you this time with sincerity.
Let me take a look at your box.
There is information of so many ancient graves there. I'll just pick one
and the money is all yours.
I wouldn't have hit rock bottom of my life
if you were a man of his word.
Wu Xie.
Listen carefully.
I admit I was a bit intimidated by you earlier.
But now you are nothing in my eyes.
This offer I gave you
was well thought out.
I know you can't refuse it.
What if I do refuse it?
That's why your Uncle Erbai looked down on you.
Don't be childish.
What you need now is money,
not your meaningless self-esteem.
My money in name
is spent to buy your auction goods,
while actually what you give me is just the grave's location.
It depends on me whether I can get the antiques out.
This is an opportunity for both of us.
Do you know how much my information is worth?
It's enough
to buy your whole shop.
That little suitcase of cash is nothing.
Mr. Xue, you're trying to have a free ride.
Okay, then I want to see
who dare come to your auction.
OK, suit yourself.
Bai.
Get ready to greet our bidders.
He didn't take the bait.
Don't worry, he will definitely take the bait.
Is Mr. Xue here?
No.
Why do you want to see him?
Where is he now?
Who are you?
When he comes back,
tell him to come to this place to find me.
I have all the money ready.
Huo Daofu?
Who the hell is he?
Why did he act like he's king of the world?
I wanted to smash him when I saw him like this.
If you are able to smash him,
you wouldn't need to kiss Xue's ass.
Do you know the Huo family?
Yes.
Huo Daofu is the most outstanding one
among the younger generation of the Huo family.
I never heard there's any business dealings
between Xue and him.
What was the money he prepared for?
Unless…
Unless
Xue got something precious
from Wu Xie with rock-bottom price behind our back.
I knew we can't trust that old fox.
I have to go and see what he's up to.
Don't go!
Curator Liu.
Will Mr. Xue be able to handle it?
Let's go help him.
He can't handle it?
Hao's Antique Shop's grand auction
starts now.
Let's bid the first lot.
Blue and white porcelain jar with ice-crack pattern.
What's wrong with you?
Only the two of us are here.
What's the point of the auction?
Starting at 15 thousand yuan.
Any bid?
Go outside to
see if our people are here.
Starting at 15 thousand yuan.
Any bid?
I'm going to ask one last time.
Blue and white porcelain jar with ice-crack pattern.
Starting at 15 thousand yuan.
Any bid?
Pass.
Next item.
Late Qing dynasty round vase.
What took you so long?
I know.
Where's it?
There you go.
What do you think?
How about it?
Nice. Very convincing.
You can think about how to thank me.
The content inside is also well done.
I know.
This can easily pass as a real one.
OK, take your time to read it.
I have to go for some errand now.
Come back here!
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
Come on!
Why did you only ask her to do half of it?
The second half is nothing but blank pages.
What should I do with it?
Hear me out.
Let me tell you, there was really no time to finish the whole copy.
Let me tell you, that chick
is a weirdo!
But the problem is, she is the only one who can do such a good job.
But it's only half done!
Hey!
If it were someone else, he couldn't even bring anything back.
I'm the only one who can pull it off!
Just put it down.
The ink is not fully dried yet,
you know.
She said that
it would take another three or four hours to dry.
You have to use your wisdom to improvise.
If you show it to them now, your secret will be revealed.
Right?
Fine.
Bro, wish you all the best of luck.
I have to do some of my own business.
You have your own business?
Everyone has his own business!
It's Piaopiao.
Piaopiao didn't contact me recently.
She's probably blaming me for putting my friend over my girlfriend.
Of course I need to go see her.
Off you go. Surely you must go.
Just think about how you're going to repay my favor.
Thank you.
I'll pass on your offer of water.
Okay?
Alright.
-You're on your own now.
-Bye!
I wish you success.
Wish me success…
I want to kick your ass!
Mr. Xue will let you guys in in a while where he'll
show her something.
She needs to read and memorize it by heart.
Write everything down after that.
After the job's done,
Mr. Xue will reward you generously.
Okay.
Young lady, memorize everything you see with your whole heart.
Fifteen thousand yuan.
Any bid?
Late Qing dynasty round vase.
Starting at 15 thousand.
People are in position.
As soon as Wu Xie takes out Grave Robbery's Notes,
I'll let them in.
Wu Xie is buying time.
Call Wu Xie out.
Did you hear me?
Late Qing dynasty round vase.
Starting at 15 thousand yuan.
If you keep stalling for time, I'll have to take action.
Give it back! How can you snatch our goods?
You!
What are you guys doing here?
We can't come?
Just the right timing.
I thought you guys wouldn't come.
In my hand is the
Grave Robbery Notes.
What you guys need to do now
is asking your people to send cash here.
No cash,
no bidding.
Look at Mr. Xue.
He brought with cash early in the morning.
You see?
I knew there are valuable goods here.
You are very greedy, Wu Xie.
I learned from Mr. Xue.
Okay. I announce now
the auction officially begins.
Wait.
Everybody.
We have agreed beforehand that
I'll take care of this matter.
Now you have broken the rules.
If Mr. Erbai knows this,
you won't be able to do business in this circle.
But no one knows whether Mr. Erbai will ever come back.
Mr. Zou, what do you mean?
You don't want him to come back?
That is not what I mean.
No matter if he can come back or not,
I want this thing but
everyone will have a share of the profit.
I'll take 50% and
the rest of you can split the rest 50%.
I have always wanted this thing.
You know what I'm capable of doing.
Xue.
We are all in business.
What can you possibly do to us?
Does it make sense
to bluff to us?
Xue.
Everyone knows
how much the notes is worth.
Wu Xie is now auctioning it which means
he wants to sell it for real.
Let's just take its course to bid for it.
Whoever has the most money wins.
With the notes,
that person can easily make the money back?
I don't understand
what business you are trying to do here.
Alright. Wu Xie.
Mr. Third Junior.
Don't listen to Xue.
Just start the auction of it.
Okay.
So you've completely changed you attitude.
So be it.
Let's all change our attitude then.
That's not what you said earlier.
So when we talked over tea,
you just pretended like you agreed with me?
Okay.
You haven't forgotten what happened to that girl in that hair salon, right?
Do you want to end up like her?
Xue, what do you want to do to us?
What are you doing?
Come on!
Go ahead.
I'd like to see who dares step up.
Take a seat.
What should we do?
This trick doesn't seem to work.
Wu Xie.
No one is going to bid.
You can inspect the goods now.
Mr. Xue.
This
is definitely the authentic Grave Robbery Notes.
But you can only read half of it.
Are you going to choose the ancient graves written in the first half
or the second half?
You need to make a choice.
A piece of advice.
I advise you to read the first half.
Because all the important graves
are in the first half.
Stop joking.
Your grandfather wrote the notes since he was a young man.
What important ancient graves could he find when he was young?
The big fish is obviously in the second half, right?
I'll choose the second half.
Have you read the notes before?
No.
Bai.
Wrap the first half for him.
Okay.