Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Reunion: The Sound of the Providence Season 2
Episode 3
Hello, everyone.
I'm Ding Gen, the newly appointed director of Warehouse 11.
It's an honor for me to be promoted to L14
and to work with you.
I hope we can work well together
in the following days.
Thank you all.
Thank you
Good.
Tian Youjin didn't allow Wu Sanxing to show that person out.
Being afraid that he couldn't make it out of there,
Wu Sanxing found a camera
with which he recorded what Tian Youjin did
as the clue for newcomers
to find out the truth.
Trapped there,
Wu Sanxing has been a keen observer
of the person they were looking for.
That person was a nobody in the warehouse,
who was listening to thunder whispers in the section of unredeemable goods.
Wu Sanxing recorded with his camera
the weird acts of that person.
After a long time,
he found that person was always listening to thunder.
It was said that the source of providence was in an ancient kingdom in the South Sea.
Sanxing thought
it was a significant archeological discovery.
Therefore, he took that person out of there
through the passage created by Tian Youjin.
Later, he organized an archaeological team
to visit the South Sea King's Tomb.
We finally made it.
That's the origin of Project 044.
I heard that they suffered a lot
in the tomb
and got to know the existence of Thunder City.
When they got out of the tomb,
it was those pseudo weather observers that welcomed them.
Holding Yang Daguang and Mu Xuehai as hostages,
they forced Sanxing to do research on and find Thunder City.
Yang Daguang died and Mu Xuehai went mad.
Sanxing was compelled
to bring the team to Thunder City.
So it was true that Uncle Sanxing was forced to go there.
A few days ago, I received a message
from Sanxing out of the blue,
saying that he went to Thunder City under threat.
That message seems to be a cry for help.
He talked a lot about you back then.
Now, you came here
by following my clues,
which proved you're competent.
Now go to Thunder City to find him.
You should have asked me to go to Thunder City directly.
Going directly to Thunder City without coming here first
would mean certain death.
Alright,
now you can have
your final award.
You've been looking for information
about Thunder City, haven't you?
Follow me.
I'll show you the place
Sanxing once lived in.
No one knew
what was on his mind.
You're his nephew and you were close to him.
You are supposed to know him better than I do.
I hope you can find him in Thunder City
and save him.
My job is done here.
Mr. Third Junior,
what are these paintings about?
Timelines and coordinate systems.
And some topographic maps.
Whoever enters Thunder City
will have no more regrets.
The ritual implement does exist.
Wu Xie,
you repeatedly broke the rules of Warehouse 11
by visiting the section of unredeemable goods without approval.
However, such fault is offset
with your contribution to Warehouse 11.
Now, you're fired.
Bai Haotian is provisionally suspended.
To Bai: Hope you find a boyfriend soon. By Wu Xie
To Bai: Hope you find a boyfriend soon.
It seems you haven't washed that clothes ever since.
But you're leaving
even before I find a boyfriend.
How are you supposed to find a boyfriend
if you never leave Warehouse 11?
You might want to travel around.
But I belong to Warehouse 11.
I'm not going anywhere else.
Then,
take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Thank you for what you did for me.
Mr. Third Junior,
your departure from Warehouse 11
requires my approval.
Will you come back to file the application?
When will you come back?
Are you a drama queen?
Why are you crying?
I'm inviting you to dinner tomorrow.
I've got some questions for you.
Close the warehouse.
Welcome to the free world!
That's all you've found after all this time?
Just these photos?
The best thing is
that we learned about what really happened.
And the cause of the repeating thunder whispers
in the photos.
That's good enough.
I thought Uncle Sanxing went to the underground river.
How could he send messages
to you and Wang Junyi?
Is he dead or not?
Wang Junyi thought Uncle Sanxing was crying for help.
Isn't he trapped in Thunder City?
There is even cell phone service in Thunder City?
That's impressive.
The message sounds just like him.
But I'm not sure if it is him.
I don't have time to check it out.
It seems you have to believe it.
Fine,
let's play it by ear.
These photos were stuck by Uncle Sanxing
to the wall
in the section of unredeemable goods.
It seems he was looking for something.
The more you look at it, the more confused you become.
These are all kinds of mountains.
It seems he was looking for a valley.
Is Thunder City located in a valley?
It was in the South Sea King's Tomb
that Uncle Sanxing saw the map of Thunder City.
If the pictures he posted in Warehouse 11
directly point to Thunder City,
he wouldn't need to go to the South Sea King's Tomb.
So, these clues
do not directly lead to Thunder City,
or the South Sea King's Tomb.
Is there any place
that we may have ignored?
This place enjoys good Feng Shui.
It seems to be a burial ground.
We don't get cell phone reception here.
I think this is the weather station.
Weather…weather station?
Uncle Sanxing asked me to go there
not only to see Yang Daguang.
He must have left some key clues,
which we missed because we were frightened
by Yang Daguang and the tape.
Let's go to the weather station now.
Are you free tonight?
Come and have dinner at my place.
What makes you so happy?
Today is a good day.
But tomorrow is even better.
So, perhaps we should
make some preparation today.
It's a big deal, after all.
We'll leave tomorrow morning.
The early morning.
It's like that old saying, "the earlier, the better".
Don't you think so?
We'll go to the weather station tomorrow.
You're gonna have to do one more thing for me
if you really want to save your daughter.
That is, persuading Fatty
into betraying Wu Xie
and working for me.
I don't think I can do that.
You're a woman.
A pretty woman.
Surely you can do it.
These days, I've been…
I'm thrilled.
Why do I feel so hot here?
Do you have a crush on me?
Well…
let's forget it. I'll drink it.
I wasn't hesitating.
I… I…
I'd better be standing when I say the following words.
Piaopiao.
I have a crush on you!
Come on!
That's hilarious!
Where is my chair?
Well.
Don't cry, baby
Stars are shining
Light from afar warms up the path
When you see the warm, bright, soft light from the stars
You should go look for it bravely
It's a mixture of bitterness and sweetness
You're waiting for someone's steps
Sometimes you want to cry when you smile
Let's cry
Let's forget
Look at the shining stars in the sky
They seem to understand your words
Don't be surprised
Don't be frightened
Let me get a candle.
Are you alright?
Did you hurt yourself?
I'm not sure.
Let me have a look.
Are you alright?
I'm alright.
Let me have a look. Let me have a look.
Does it hurt?
Is it here? Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
I really want to
take good care of you.
It's just
that my friend is in trouble.
It's not right for me to enjoy my life
and watch him suffer.
That wouldn't be honorable.
When things come to an end,
I'll come back
and…
Well…
I'll start a new life with you.
Would that be okay
for you?
You're all alone,
with some much trouble.
That's too hard for you.
It would be better
if you got a man to help you.
Anyway,
feel free to contact me
if you need any help.
See you.
I should tell you something.
For Mei's operation, we still need to work on it.
We've found a donor.
But we still need to wait in line for the operation.
Let's split up the workload.
You go to the hospital
to do the talking
and to take care of Mei.
I go to the donator
to persuade him
into having the operation soon.
What do you say?
It was you who went to the hospital
for the matching?
I guess I could do that
without telling you first.
Why didn't you tell me that?
Alright, alright.
Alright.
It was my fault.
I should have told you that.
Listen,
Xue is really an asshole.
Don't go to his place since tomorrow.
You may spend some time with Mei
at another place.
I'll take you back
after solving the problems.
You smashed his place
and destroyed all his antiques.
Do you think he'll let you off the hook?
He'd think of all the ways to ruin you.
No big deal.
I got it.
You'll be fine.
Kylin,
Fatty,
you know what,
I'm closest to my uncle this time.
He truly was compelled to do that.
I think I'm about to…
Why haven't they finished drinking yet?
I still need to continue down his path.
Let's call his friend,
asking him to take them away.
He had so much to tell me.
I totally understand you.
That's why I have a huge crush on you.
Are they drunk?
Almost.
How much do I owe you?
Two hundred and twenty yuan.
You only need to pay two hundred yuan.
Here is three hundred yuan. Keep the change.
Thank you.
What's going on here?
Wake up, wake up. Are you alright?
Fatty.
Why did you drink so much?
I miss you so much.
Where is Kylin?
Kylin?
He is not Kylin.
Let me introduce her to you.
You must be Fatty!
Am I right?
You're so famous.
Who is this guy?
What are you talking about?
Do I look like a boy to you?
It's not that obvious, but…
Bai.
This is Bai. Bai Haotian.
Bai Haotian from Warehouse 11.
My, my, my, the spider and the fly.
Look how drunk my friend is.
She is awesome.
She really is awesome.
Who won?
Me! Me!
Bai! Bai! Bai!
Listen…
That's enough. That's enough.
He is my best buddy.
Fatty is my best buddy.
I got it.
He accompanied me to the most dangerous places.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He'd always be by my side.
Yeah.
Along the journey,
I met
a lot of friends,
none of them accompanied me to the end.
But you did it.
Come on, you're gonna make me cry.
Let's go. Let's go.
I mean it. Fatty is the only one who did it.
He is the only one who did it.
He'd support me
for everything I do, every choice I make.
I'd support you, too.
Alright, alright.
That's enough.
Dude, dude.
Alright, alright.
You're drunk. You're drunk.
Come on.
It's okay.
Let's go back home. No, no, no.
Okay? Come back!
Listen, I want to
take this chance to…
What are you doing?
I want to take this chance to
have a drink with you.
We haven't had drinks together
for a long time,
have we?
Come on, here is a toast to you.
Yeah.
A toast to you.
Come on, bottoms up.
Let's be there for each other
in this mundane world.
Who are you?
-Who are you?
-Bai!
Who are you? Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
It's okay. Calm down. Calm down.
Who are you?
Sis,
what are you doing?
Who is your sis?
Why are you in our bed?
Don't you remember it?
Last night…
That's not true. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
I asked you not to come but you insisted.
You said you must do something or you'd be worried.
What do you mean by that?
Now I see, you're not here to do something.
You're here to do someone.
I carried you to the sofa last night.
How did you make it to our bed?
Are you still gonna deny it?
Are you gonna deny it because you got drunk?
I just knew it.
Are you still gonna deny it?
I have evidence.
I recorded it.
Here is the video.
Check it out for yourself.
Today, Wu, Bai, Fatty,
the three of us become sworn brothers and sisters.
Hear, hear.
We'd eat kebabs together.
Yeah!
We'd drink wine together.
Along with Uncle Sanxing.
Today, Wu, Bai, Fatty,
the three of us become sworn brothers and sisters.
Hear, hear.
We'd eat kebabs together.
Yeah!
We'd drink wine together.
We'd go look for Uncle Sanxing together.
Let's raise our head.
We'd be best buddies.
Where should we put these kebabs?
Here, here.
Here.
We'd be doomed if we betray each other.
Come on, let me have a look.
-I'm so happy!
-Let me have a look.
Is it okay for you?
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go look for Uncle Sanxing. Let's go look for Uncle Sanxing.
This is my fourth sister.
This is my third brother.
You're drunk.
Why do you keep moving?
Why do you keep moving
even when you are in your seat.
You really are drunk.
Be nice to me.
Love me.
When I get married…
I'll give you one day off when you get married.
I'll give you a big bonus check when you get married.
I need to use the bathroom.
I don't want to be your sister.
It seems you do have a big crush on him,
something unstoppable in the world.
You're impressed by yourself.
Sis,
I'm afraid it's too late.
It's no use regretting now.
We already became sworn brothers and sisters
after taking vows and burning the incense.
That's not true.
We burned kebabs, not incense.
The man you hold in your arms
is your third brother, understand?
You're not supposed to have feelings for him.
I, the hot guy talking to you,
am your second brother.
Please feel free to have feelings for me.
Your big brother is not here today.
He is awesome.
Big brother? He is even elder than you?
Yep.
It's called maturity, okay?
In your big brother, you see sincerity.
Come on, our big brother is definitely mature.
Absolutely elder than him.
Absolutely.
I, I need to use the bathroom.
I'm really…
Please don't go.
Anyway,
though our big brother is not here today,
the four of us have finally become family.
We should do our business now.
Do our business?
Yeah.
Do our business.
What business?
Our business is…
I want to go to the bathroom first.
Sis.
Director Zhao,
the operation went well.
Sorry for the delay.
Okay.
See you in two days. Okay.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Doctor Xie,
do you have news of Glasses?
I want to talk to him.
He is a man
without plans.
What matters now is that your throat gets better.
Don't worry about him.
Don't wait for him.
Did he tell you something?
I heard that he turned you down.
He told me that we belong to two different worlds.
We're in a modern world today.
How could he turn me down using such excuses?
It seems you don't know him well.
You're right.
Ever since I met him,
I had the feeling that I never got to know him.
Would you mind telling me
about yourselves?
Our ancestors
worked in the underground world.
Now, our job is about
archaeology and historic preservation.
It's a dangerous job.
It's not surprising that he turned you down.
You mean archaeology and historic preservation?
He is right.
You two are from different worlds.
I don't care.
Besides,
there is no such rule
that people from different worlds
shouldn't fall in love with each other, right?
For those who are not afraid to die,
nothing in the world
would be a threat to them.
That's why
they wouldn't waste their time
on a relationship.
That's not true.
Doctor Xie,
thank you for telling me so much.
Even if what you said is true,
I don't want to give up.
I want to say something to him
face to face.
Thank you for curing my throat.
These days,
you took good care of me.
Now, I need to go back to the company to report on my work.
He asked me
to protect you.
So, you're gonna stay here without going anywhere.
Mr. Jiao wouldn't let you off easily.
I'll find a way
to handle his threat and keep you out of this.
Thank you for your kindness.
Don't worry.
I'm an adult.
I can take care of myself.
You can tell
why we belong to different worlds
by watching how much I would do
for things
he asked me to do.
Doctor Xie, take care.
Darlings, I'm back.
Guys, I'm back.
Bro, hurry up.
Welcome, welcome.
Thank you for all you've done.
Thank you. Thank you.
Let's send a warm welcome to Chu!
Welcome! You have a beautiful voice.
You're cured. You're cured.
You have a good voice.
You're cured.
Here is the wine.
Come on.
Guys, I want to say something.
First,
welcome Chu
to bring our team back.
Great!
Second…
My sister,
your workmate,
can speak now.
We have two things to celebrate.
Cheers!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
We should emphasize
the difference.
And amplify the effect.
The third thing is color tone.
The color tone
is still not good enough to me.
Make the background music louder.
I want to create a certain ambiance for this part.
Cheers!
Drink it up. Drink it up.
Great!
Awesome!
Cool!
Here is the cake.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Look.
Come on, stop it.
Get off my back.
Do I know you?
I'm sorry.
Fatty,
do you remember
how many times
along our journey
we've heard information from thunder whispers?
The first time was on the ship in South Sea King's Tomb.
You went crazy on hearing thunder.
Hey,
where is hotpot?
Where is hotpot?
What are you talking about?
Sis, I have something to tell you.
She is sleeping. Just leave her alone.
I'll tell her about it later.
Another time was at Yang Daguang's cave of treasure.
The thunderclaps were so horrible
that we almost got ourselves killed there.
So,
we were equipped
both times.
Then, what about this time?
What am I going to use this time?
Hey,
it's kind of like visiting an old place.
Thanks.
Uncle Sanxing should have expected
that we ignored something last time.
Let's look carefully.
Sis,
let me show you around.
Follow me.
Let's go.
These old appliances were repaired and renovated.
There should have been more.
Some of them were abandoned and removed.
There are mosquitoes here.
You might need insect repellent.
Hey, I get jealous of him.
I'm bigger in size than him.
You should get me insect repellent instead, sis.
Don't call me sis.
But you're…
What are you doing?
Stay out of this.
Get down here.
You wait there.
Why are wiring stealers so furious these days?
Perhaps I should teach them a lesson.
I might need to use this later.
You're weak. You're a girl.
Just get some rest over there.
Are you sure you can take care of this?
I don't want to waste our time.
You have two minutes for this.
-That's too long.
-Bai, let's go.
We are in charge of this area.
Who are you to scold us?
Is there any wrong with that?
Look, you got a mosquito there.
I'm surprised that you're so weak.
I haven't enjoyed myself enough yet.
How about we fight again?
Is that all you've got?
Alright, Fatty, let's do our business.
In a second.
Today is you lucky day.
I'm a nice person.
I give you a chance to make things right.
I want you to find something for me in the garden.
Okay.
Spare no effort in finding that thing.
Do you understand?
Understood, understood.
Hurry up. Go, go, go.
Stop!
Where are you going? Do you know what you're looking for?
Why are you so stupid? Take this!
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Let's go! Hurry up!
Bro! Bro!
It seems we found something here.
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
Let's go. That's a horrible scream.
Good job. You're free to go now.
Thanks. Thanks.
Go, go, go. Let's go.
Fatty.
Southern Weather Bureau.
Look.
Yeah.
I found something there.
An urn.
A wine urn?
This is an urn for bone ash.
Why is it here?
Uncle Sanxing saw that horde of tomb raiders
doing rituals outside the ancient tomb
and learned their method.
Do you mean
that those tomb raiders had also been here?
Maybe.
Fatty,
check if there is something else.
Nope.
Come on.
Let's keep looking.
Where are you going?
Well, it seems Uncle Sanxing…
-Was it for…
-I'm coming.
What did you see?