Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Reunion: The Sound of the Providence Season 2
Episode 11
Jiang Zisuan.
You're still too young to beat me.
Are you okay, Fatty?
I even got my clothes dirty because of you.
Are you guys all okay?
Look at this disgusting face
Are you sure you want to personally disguise as him?
Do you want to do it?
But you can't even fit in his clothes.
The only thing that might give me away is my body.
No. Your face doesn't look like him, either.
But I can beat you with my acting skills! Do you believe it?
I do. I shall not dare doubt you.
You
need to figure out how to play him.
This guy is very sullen.
You need to figure out how to make convincing look in your eyes.
You two, take off his clothes.
What do you think?
Do I look like him?
I want to kick your ass now.
I can pass as him, right?
I have to go to Jiang Zisuan's room
to see if the entrance is really there.
I've come in.
How is the situation?
It won't be so easy to find.
Okay, be patient.
Take your time.
Kun and Gen shall be put in the center with the element of Earth.
Qian and Dui shall be paired with the element of Metal while Zhen and Xun with Wood.
I didn't expect this room
was built according to Feng Shui theories.
How's it going?
I found it.
There's a panel inside the wall which is sealed by welded rusty iron.
There is a vertical scratch on it.
It was cut open by a chainsaw once.
Can you open it?
It was welded from the inside.
But I can try to force it open.
I think we should try this risk.
Fatty.
I need Hong to
send me some sulfuric acid now.
You want Hong to send you sulfuric acid?
Where can we find that right now?
There's an old-model scooter at the door.
It uses a lead battery which is full of sulfuric acid.
Wait.
Fatty.
My poison is going to kick in soon.
Hang in there.
Come on.
So soon?
Jiang Zisuan.
Open the door, Jiang Zisuan!
Jiang Zisuan!
What?
I am not welcome?
You're so passionate.
Shall we have some drink
to liven things up?
Why didn't you turn me down today?
That's a good start.
What is this?
What's wrong?
You can't wait to have me, right?
Why? You're dumbfounded by me?
This floor is still under examination.
Mr. Jiao said that no one is allowed to go in there.
Fine.
Pick up, pick up!
We can't do this again.
What happened?
Are you scared?
Mr. Jiao is not a kind person.
If he knows about our affairs,
neither you nor I will live.
Besides,
I want to kill Wu Xie.
I don't want to cause any other troubles before that.
It's always Wu Xie.
Let's go back to the
previous employer-employee relationship.
It's good for both of us.
Jiang Zisuan
You…
You're just fooling around with me.
You should leave.
You finally answered your phone!
You got the sulfuric acid, right?
Okay.
I'll wait for you at the stairs.
Come on.
Let me tell you,
this is even more dramatic than those salacious suspenseful stories.
That woman is crazy and out of control.
You have to watch out.
Everyone has their sad story.
Love brings all kinds of evil.
Fatty.
I'm going down to the secret tunnel.
Keep an eye on the situation outside.
Don't try to do anything!
If you move,
I'll electrocute you.
And don't say we're abusing you.
You have food and water here.
Wu Xie asked you to do this?
What does he want?
Actually I don't need you to tell me.
He's not here and
he asked you to watch me so that
I can't leave this room.
He wanted me to leave the place
where I would stay for a long time.
If I am right, he is
in my room now, right?
You are very simple.
Don't know how to maintain a poker face.
Then you will get yourself in danger by Wu Xie's side.
You have to watch out for yourself.
Wu Xie doesn't like girls who don't pay attention to their looks.
You really like him.
There's always someone who likes him.
Wu Xie never lacks admirers.
Is it wrong to like someone?
Don't you have someone you like too?
But liking someone can be fatal sometimes.
My sister
died from her love for Wu Xie.
Manager Bai.
How about I guard him for you?
It's okay.
How long have you been in love with him?
Let me tell you a story.
It's about my sister and Wu Xie.
They met during an expedition.
At that time they belonged to different sides.
But as you know,
there is no absolute right or wrong in the world of adults.
Soon the two enemies became friends.
They teamed up for tasks
and explored the unknown secrets together.
She finally fell in love with Wu Xie.
Give me your hand.
My sister was a passionate woman, to both her love and her enemy.
That was the first time she had fallen in love with a man.
She sacrificed everything for him.
She chose to look the other way for him.
But the man left her there and
left her to die alone.
The last time I saw my sister,
she said that she was going to
a place called Snake Marsh.
She said she wanted to help Wu Xie find someone.
I know Wu Xie had been looking for that person.
And every time
many people died because of his mission.
I tried to persuade her.
I asked her not to go.
But she didn't listen and
she still went with him.
And she never came back again.
Ning.
I don't want you to go.
You will die if you go, you know?
You always do as Wu Xie asks you to.
But you never listen to what I say.
Say no more.
I will go no matter what you're going to say today.
Ning!
When you are out there alone,
take good care of yourself.
She died.
Between my sister
and that person he was looking for,
Wu Xie didn't choose my sister.
My sister finally
died tragically in Snake Marsh.
He is not that kind of person.
Your sister fell in love with him because he is gentle to others
and he is never such a selfish person.
Do you know men?
You don't even understand human nature.
Let me tell you,
there are two kinds of good people in this world.
The first kind is those really good people.
They are really innocent and nice.
And for the second kind,
kindness is just a weapon for him.
This kind of person won't treat you badly
when you are still useful to him.
He will manipulate you
so that you'll die for him willingly.
Your Wu Xie
is the second type.
That's bullshit!
He doesn't need to manipulate me.
I have been most willing to do what I did!
Congratulations, then.
You have been manipulated by him.
Don't be surprised.
You will end up just
like my sister in the end.
Wu Xie
who you admire and worship
is a person who will achieve his own purpose
even if he has to betray the whole world.
He is not such a person!
He has been helping me all along.
He came here to save people.
This is why he's a master of manipulation.
He made everyone thank him
as if he was the savior.
But what you guys don't know is that
he was the one who caused you
to get into all the troubles in the first place.
Kylin left a mark of danger at the entrance.
There are traps ahead
after I cross this circle.
We can't get in there rashly.
No one is on guard.
Remain silent, ye who enter here
All shall be killed with the presence of sound
What's going on?
Don't try to play any tricks.
I have a serious craving for smoking.
Young lady, can you do me a favor to
hand me a cigarette?
Just uncuff one of my hands.
No.
It's more than enough for you to kill me
with one uncuffed hand.
Forget it then.
Just smoke like this.
It seems that you have found the entrance.
Don't move. Don't move!
Don't be afraid.
Liking someone doesn't mean I am weak!
Alright. Okay.
Calm down.
I see great potential in you.
That's what happened.
I wanted to be with him
but he is not interested in me.
So I don't want to make him happy.
I'd rather to be killed with him.
Is that true?
Jiao, do it now.
Kill him and me.
You just go to Thunder City.
You
want him to die, right?
Yes.
You want to die with him.
A couple died for love.
Do you really like him?
Do you know why I wanted to make you my mistress?
Was it just because of your body?
The most interesting thing about you is that
although you are willing to sell your body and soul,
you still have some true feelings inside you.
That's what I paid you for.
So I won't kill him.
And I will grant all your wishes.
Is there anything that you want to say?
I'll give you one last chance to defend yourself.
Not talking?
Acknowledge it with silence?
Okay, then.
Chop his fingers off.
Okay.
I'm happy to do that.
Don't worry.
I will do it nice and quick.
Sir!
Look!
He is not Jiang Zisuan.
It is you.
What are you doing?
I have to go.
Where are you going?
You're getting more and more fierce.
We can't just wait here doing nothing.
Go ahead then.
Just storm in there.
You'll only get yourself and him killed.
Mr. Fatty.
Let's trade him to get Wu Xie back.
Use your brain!
This nobody can't be compared with Wu Xie in value.
Call the police then.
Why did I forget our honorable police officers?
Why is there no signal?
The signal has been unstable since just now.
You won't get through.
Mr. Jiao ordered yesterday
to disconnect phone signals
when ordinary guests were almost gone.
And there is only one cell phone base station nearby.
Someone should have cut off the power just now.
It wasn't you, right?
How could it be me? I've been here all the time!
Be quiet.
If you guys want to call someone,
you can only use a satellite phone.
Why are you here?
I…
I came to travel.
Do you think I am silly?
Don't.
Mr. Jiao, don't get me wrong.
I really came here to travel.
Besides,
this is not your territory.
I'd suggest you abide by the law.
When did you come here?
I just arrived yesterday.
And I immediately bumped into you today.
The two of us are destined to meet.
Let's have a drink together in a while.
What do you think?
You played the game really wild.
Where's Jiang Zisuan?
When was
the last time any of you saw Jiang Zisuan?
Last night, I think.
Find him, now!
Yes, sir.
What were you doing
sneaking into his room
pretending to be Jiang Zisuan?
The entrance is in Jiang Zisuan's room!
Come on!
Hurry up!
Mr. Jiao.
The people you got in Dumb Village before
were all mercenaries.
Why are the people working for you this time
are nothing but rubbish?
Is Wu Erbai
under the ground now?
I have no idea.
Did you find Jiang Zisuan?
Not yet.
Do a nose count.
Everyone in this building now is our people.
They must be hiding in one of our guys' rooms.
Yes, sir.
Let's talk.
Sure.
Wu Erbai,
I know you are under the ground.
I know you won't be trapped in there.
Your nephew
is in my hands.
Let's talk about terms.
I'm going to count to three.
If you don't answer by then,
I'll killed him.
Mr. Jiao.
Stop shouting, will you?
Uncle Erbai is not stupid.
He knows I'm dying.
Will he still make a deal with you with me as the hostage?
You are still too young and too insensitive.
Wu Erbai is getting older.
You can't tell if he
can be as cruel as you young people.
Uncle Erbai.
Sorry that
I caused troubles to you.
I can't live long anyway.
Just concentrate on your own business.
I have observed
his people.
All are useless.
You punk!
They are not capable of passing the mechanism traps in the tunnel.
So don't worry.
Then I'm going to kill you.
What happened?
Sir.
Sir!
Go.
Go!
Go get them!
It's a surprise attack!
Keep up!
Keep up.
Dude, sorry.
This time we made a lot of noises.
I guess we'll have to disturb your sleep.
Whose side will you take?
I…
I am in a dilemma now.
Give me some time to think.
Take your time to think.
We met again.
Your Wu family is still so insidious and cunning.
You got trapped, you got out,
but you didn't leave.
That means this place
has something to do with Thunder City.
You really won't give up.
Let's negotiate.
Sure.
The tide has not ebbed.
Your people can't make it through.
Why should I negotiate with you?
Your Wu family people are all evil.
I'm trying to persuade you for your own good.
Besides,
I have been observing
your gang for a long time.
You can't win this battle.
Erjing.
What if I still have a trick up my sleeve?