Sub by iQiyi & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Reunion: The Sound of the Providence Season 2
Previously on Season 1
My name is Wu Xie.
My grandpa was a famous grave robber
before the founding of New China.
He had a mysterious notebook
titled
Grave Robbery Notes.
Uncle Sanxing has never come back
since when he went out at a time
I think he might have died.
Message Uncle Sanxing: Beixin Bridge, smoke in bamboo grove and rain on locust tree,
Uncle Sanxing!
someone returning in the cold lamplight at night, deep ruts in the path of a field.
East of Nanjing Drum Tower.
Beijige Metrological Museum.
Locker No.221.
The monarch of Luoyun Kingdom of the South Sea is South Sea King.
Its people had seven ears.
Legend has it that they could understand the Thunder God's words,
so they got to know a lot of secrets from the Heaven.
He's listening to thunder.
Your uncle
was the only one of the whole archaeological team who was missing.
Your uncle went to Thunder City on his own
and ended up dying on the way.
No way!
My uncle was not that kind of person!
Uncle Sanxing,
if
there is anything I haven't finished yet,
it is to find you.
I want to die without regret.
I may never get out.
The Section of Unredeemable Goods is so big.
I can't find a way out.
I've been here for three years.
It seems that it should be
the source of the thunder whispers.
So whatever happens,
I must go to the Section of Unredeemable Goods.
Episode 1
Actually there is a legend about the Section of Unredeemable Goods.
During the War of Resistance Against Japanese Aggression,
Warehouse 11 was under the jurisdiction of one of the last few administrators
Zhang Qishan, aka Zhang Fo Ye.
When the war started,
we were outnumbered ten to one,
and everybody thought we'd lose.
It was a very intense war.
When the Japanese soldiers were about to capture our stronghold…
Attack!
Everybody, speed up!
In the nick of time, Zhang Fo Ye
lured a group of well-equipped Japanese soldiers
into the Section of Unredeemable Goods in Warehouse 11.
Hurry up! Get a move on!
Go!
What?
What's going on?
Watch out, guys!
Thanks to the numerous traps Zhang Fo Ye had set up there,
the Japanese army was annihilated as a whole.
What's more,
as I heard from a warehouse clerk who stored goods there,
even to this day, that place
is still being haunted by screams of Japanese soldiers
and voices of evil spirits,
so nobody dares to go there
and people rush away as soon as they leave the goods there.
What you said
makes it even more imperative for me to go there.
Why?
Back then my uncle
was coerced into entering the Section of Unredeemable Goods,
and he left
very important clues there,
so I can only know the truth by going down there
and know who coerced him.
Normally there would be a legend like this
for places with hidden secrets
to prevent others from getting close to the truth,
but this is a poorly made-up legend.
The warehouse is about to be closed. I'm off.
I'm going too.
I've also received a text message.
I'm gonna go and get my reward.
What reward? Don't add yourself to the trouble.
You can't get in without me.
Why?
The passageway from Ganyang Warehouse to the next warehouse
is under the water.
But
this entrance is blocked by the goods in stock.
If you want to enter the outfall,
you have to move those goods first.
But each underwater container
has a sensor on top.
The defense system is activated
as long as it is not the time for storing or retrieving goods.
Once the goods are subject to external forces
and can't keep balance,
the traps will be activated,
bringing electricity
into this reservoir.
There is an indicator light on each container.
Green indicates safety,
yellow indicates safety zone has been reached,
and red indicates trigger of traps.
That's to say,
we must move the goods
while keep their balance?
I'll see what I can do about it.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
Keep up with me.
I'm keeping up.
Now your stature shows…
shows its advantage.
Let's get started.
We'll first thrust a rope through the iron chain.
Then you'll dive underwater
to get some lead blocks for anchoring the goods.
After that, we'll just need to
cut off the iron chain with an electric welder.
When the lead blocks sink,
they can lift up the iron chains
anchoring the goods.
In the last step, the two of us will pull the goods at the same time.
When they are kept horizontal,
we'll be able to lift the containers
blocking the outfall.
Bai!
Hurry up! Go and have a look over there!
OK.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Hurry up! Someone has broken into the Ganyang Warehouse!
Here.
Someone has broken into the Ganyang Warehouse! Stop!
Someone has broken into the Ganyang Warehouse! Everybody on alert!
Everybody on alert!
Go over there. Over there.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Over there.
Search in separate directions, guys.
Be careful.
Bai.
Here.
How are you doing?
How are you doing? Are you OK?
Yes.
Thankfully, the electricity was on and off once you triggered the traps.
What shall I do if you really die?
Do you want me to be in your debt for the rest of my life?
I won't let you
take risks with me again next time.
That's just a precautionary warning.
How can they kill people with electricity for real?
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
We'll lose
if we expose ourselves.
I don't want you to lose.
Even if the voltage was low,
what if you had an accident underwater?
I made a bet in my heart
before we went underwater.
What was your bet?
I wouldn't die
as long as you are alive.
Are you insane?
What logic is your bet based on?
You're still alive because you are young,
because we were lucky.
What does that have to do with whether I'm alive or not?
I won anyway.
You've lost your mind.
All right, let's stop talking about this.
Warehouse 11 is in a state of siege now.
We have no way back.
We can only move on.
What's more, this is our only chance.
We have absolutely no way to get in here again next time.
Get a move on.
OK.
This way.
I'll leave that window to you.
Go.
Stay still.
There's another monitor here.
Cover your face.
What?
What for?
Warehouse 11 is a rule-based place.
As long as our faces are not captured,
we can just refuse to admit it's us.
Is there even such a rule for Warehouse 11?
Let's go.
Go.
It's Wu Xie and Bai Haotian.
They are in the passageway area.
Location K13-8.
Run!
Why are you still covering your face?
Get out of here quickly.
Be quick.
They are in Location K13-8.
Notify clerks of other warehouses
to outflank them through Passageway M7.
This way.
Be quick.
Close all warehouse gates immediately.
Close all warehouse gates, close all warehouse gates!
Mr. Third Junior,
we'll be locked in the passageway
once the warehouse gate is locked.
We must hurry up.
Run!
Hurry up.
Dong,
take a couple of people to go there with you.
The rest of you, come with me. Hurry up.
Go, go.
Stop!
Stop there!
Where are you running?
T08-9, T08-9.
You must intercept them at T08-9.
Hurry up, keep up!
Go. They are in the front.
Request to open the gate.
Stop going after them. Stop.
That warehouse is off limits.
We can catch them if we go in.
Ahead of us is the Section of Unredeemable Goods.
Nobody can set foot in it.
Section of Unredeemable Goods
This pit should be the entrance to the Section of Unredeemable Goods.
All the goods are shipped down
through this boom truck.
It looks so deep.
If you go back now,
you'll just be demoted in the worst case.
If you keep following me,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Till now I still believe
that I wouldn't die as long as you are alive.
And I also have things I want to do.
I'll go down first.
Take care.
Go.
What are we gonna do now?
There is still a great depth down here.
Uncle Sanxing was put in here a long time ago.
He should still be down there.
Let's find out more about the surroundings
and straighten things out.
OK.
Mr. Third Junior.
There is light down there.
Turn off your flashlight.
That's a distress signal.
Who are you?
Anybody there?
Is anybody there?
Who is over there?
Uncle Sanxing.
Wait for me here. I'll go and have a look.
No!
You can't go.
I think there is something weird about that distress signal.
It is weird indeed.
But as you know,
I must go down to have a look.
I'll go with you then.
Here.
Take it.
We can't both go down.
If anything happens to me down there,
can you pull me up?
I trust you.
Be careful.
Got it.
Anybody here?
Who's there?
Say something!
Is it you who sent the distress signal just now?
Xie,
help me.
I'm stuck here.
Xie,
someone wanted to kill me.
He threw me down here.
He wanted to harm our Wu family.
No,
you shouldn't be here.
Erbai fell for a set-up.
Go quickly!
What's down here
can cost your life.
Go!
Go quickly!
Uncle Sanxing.
Let me get you out of here.
Let me get you out of here!
Go!
Give me your hand!
Xie.
I can't.
Xie,
go.
Go.
No.
Uncle Sanxing,
I've been looking for you for over ten years.
I've finally found you today.
I won't let you stay here.
I'll definitely get you out of here.
Go with me.
Go with me!
Come on.
Uncle Sanxing,
why haven't you aged at all?
Uncle Sanxing!
Mr. Third Junior.
Bai.
Bai!
I didn't lie to you.
Mr. Third Junior…
Bai.
Bai!
Come on.
Bai.
Bai!
What's going on?
Get up.
Let's go.
Are you OK?
Here.
My goodness.
Are we safe now?
I think we are for the moment.
Here you are.
What was that just now?
It may be a kind of venomous bug.
It can kill people
once it enters their brains.
Go.
Let's move on to have a look.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Did I say anything to you
when I was in a coma just now?
Yes.
You said…
You said you suddenly felt hungry and wanted to have BBQ skewers.
And then you ordered four skewers of grilled garlic
and two skewers of grilled leek.
Didn't I say anything else?
Anything else?
Yes.
"Two more skewers of grilled lamb kidneys please."
Why do you prefer such a strong taste?
Let's go.
Wait for me!
Off-limits Area of the Section of Unredeemable Goods
The goods are the same as the ones above,
and they are not placed in order.
The surroundings here
feel somewhat different
from the surroundings where I saw
my uncle was in the video.
He should be further inside.
Go.
Mr. Third Junior,
this place is haunted indeed. Listen.
This way.
These bells are laid or hung in the middle of the road
as a man-made warning.
It's like a hunter lurking in the shadow is alerted
when a prey touches the trap.
Mr. Third Junior,
what's that sound outside?
Maybe it's thunder.
Mr. Third Junior, are you OK?
Are you OK?
Yes.
The Section of Unredeemable Goods is much bigger than we thought.
Zhang Fo Ye must have expanded this place
when he was preparing for the war back in those years.
Could it be that the Section of Unredeemable Goods
has really ambushed
the Japanese soldiers who entered here?
Did you hear that?
What sound is that?
There's something off about the sound.
Let's take this way. Come on.
Bai.
Bai!
Mr. Third Junior,
the sound seems to be coming from there.
Mr. Third Junior!
Bai!
Mr. Third Junior.
I've read lots of accounts about Zhang Qishan
in my grandpa's Grave Robbery Notes.
For example, there is one account
which says
a black Japanese military train numbered 076
pulled into the station late at night in 1933.
Mr. Third Junior.
Mr. Third Junior!
Could that be true?
All the carriages of the military train
were welded shut with iron sheets.
Blood kept seeping out of the train through the cracks.
Could it really be the Haunted Train No.076
Mr. Third Junior talked about?