[English subtitles are available]
[Sword and Fairy 4]
[Episode 31]
[Buzhou Mountain]
According to Elder Chongguang’s description,
the entrance to the Netherworld should be here.
Watch out!
This is no ordinary thunder and lightning.
You mortals.
This is the Netherworld.
Leave right away.
This should be the Illuminating Dragon of Buzhou Mountain.
We want to go to the Netherworld.
Divine Dragon, please let us pass through.
In the six realms,
you're just insignificant mere mortals,
yet you want to enter the Netherworld?
Do you know what kind of place the Netherworld is?
I'm a disciple of Qionghua Sect of Kunxu.
I specialize in cultivating immortality and following the Way.
I know the Netherworld
is where the primordial spirits gather
before they dissipate.
If it wasn't urgent,
we wouldn't have come here to bother you.
Mortals who dream of cultivating immortality are even more ridiculous.
Through the ages,
how many people can fulfill their wishes?
Why don't you just accept your fate?
After you die,
let your primordial spirits enter the Netherworld.
We can't wait any longer.
We must go to the Netherworld today.
Answer me.
What's your name?
My name is Yun Tianhe.
Divine Dragon.
I know you guard Buzhou Mountain.
But I also have family I want to protect.
We must go to the Netherworld today
and get the Barrier-Crossing Branch to save her.
If it's possible,
we can save even more people.
Well, Divine Dragon.
Don't be angry.
Tianhe is not good with words.
Did you forget?
Elder Chongguang warned us
not to enrage him.
It's been thousands of years.
All I've heard
were words of humble mortals praying for blessings.
This is the first time I've heard such nonsense.
Fine.
I'll give you a chance.
But you have to go through my test.
Okay.
What test?
Tianhe.
We are just mortals.
How can we accept a trial from a divine lord?
I don't think it has a murderous aura.
Besides, for us to enter the Netherworld,
we'd have to go through its trial no matter what.
So just let me try.
Be careful.
Divine Dragon!
I accept your test.
Yun Tianhe.
I admire
your courage.
If you can resist one attack of mine,
I will open the path to the Netherworld.
Otherwise, I'll send your primordial spirits
into the Netherworld.
As a mortal,
you could actually become the master of the Primordial-Spirit-Initiating Moon-Chasing Bow?
Tianhe.
That's unexpected.
It's a wound caused by the divine dragon.
How can a mortal's magic heal it?
If you want something,
you have to pay the price.
Is this so-called trial
to help Tianhe
or do you have other intentions?
Heaven's secrets cannot be divulged.
Yun Tianhe.
The Hou Yi's Sun-Shooting Bow in the Divine Mausoleum
makes a pair with the Primordial-Spirit-Initiating Moon-Chasing Bow.
You can only compete with me if you can get it.
Divine Dragon.
So I've passed your test, right?
Can you let us go to the Netherworld now?
I won't break my promise.
No one has ever returned after entering the Netherworld.
You need to figure out a way
to return to the mortal world yourselves.
As long as you don't cause any trouble,
this spell, which lasts for six hours,
will prevent your living spiritual auras
from being noticed by the Netherworld envoy.
Divine Dragon, thank you for protecting us.
I, Yun Tianhe,
will definitely repay your kindness today.
I have been guarding this place for 9,900 years.
I'm about to complete my accumulation of merits.
It's just another good deed.
Yun Tianhe.
I will fulfill your wish today.
But one day, when you've experienced all the hardships in the world,
you may come to resent such a fate.
I will wait until the end of your life
and see if you would still be
as free-spirited as today.
Divine Dragon said
wounds from the divine dragon can't be healed by mortals.
What should we do about your wound?
It's fine, Lingsha.
I'm not a mortal.
I have boundless spiritual energy.
Don't worry about me.
Time is running out.
Let's hurry to the Netherworld.
Let's go.
[Netherworld]
Don't look at me. Don't look at me.
Lingsha.
You've been looking at that bead.
Did you sense something?
I sense my feelings.
I didn't realize it when I was in the mortal world.
Only now do I know that so many people die every day.
I feel bad inside.
We shouldn't stay here for long.
Let's go find the Barrier-Crossing Branch.
Okay.
Stop there!
Why do I feel like I smell living beings?
Maybe it's because I just arrived in the Netherworld
and haven't been the Netherworld envoy for long,
so my primordial spirit hasn't been integrated yet.
You're right.
I've been guarding the Barrier-Crossing Branch every day.
It's as if I've forgotten the smell of living beings.
The Barrier-Crossing Branch is rare in the Netherworld,
but as the tool that enables travel through the six realms,
if it's stolen by an obsessive primordial spirit,
I'm afraid it'd cause chaos in the mortal world.
Then you two should go to guard the Barrier-Crossing Branch now.
I still have to go receive other primordial spirits.
Do you still remember me?
I was the faceless woman Wumian in the Tomb of Prince Yunan.
Follow me.
Thank you, Sister Wumian.
We'd be in trouble if they find out we're alive.
Since you are alive,
why did you come to the Netherworld?
Do you remember Mengli?
Simply put,
Mengli is in danger.
We must come to the Netherworld
to get the Barrier-Crossing Branch to save her.
The Barrier-Crossing Branch grows in the Impermanence Hall.
But we, the Netherworld envoys,
will use it to guide the primordial spirits.
I just heard that you are a Netherworld envoy.
May you give me the Barrier-Crossing Branch?
I'll be very grateful.
It was all thanks to Benefactor Yun that my primordial spirit was saved.
After that, thanks to Mr. Yun,
Miss Han and Miss Liu's prayers,
it was freed.
I'm the one who should be grateful.
Thank you, Miss.
Looks like
my fight with that divine dragon wasn't in vain.
Thank you, Sister Wumian.
Sister Wumian.
Why did your primordial spirit remain in the Netherworld
instead of dissipating?
I was going to leave.
I didn't want to see Benefactor Yun's primordial spirit here.
He has a deep obsession
and refuses to leave the Luminous Mirror Platform.
So I stayed here as a Netherworld envoy
to wait for you with him.
Why does my father have a deep obsession?
He said he only felt guilt towards you throughout his lifetime.
He wants to apologize to you personally.
Can you take me to see him?
Although your living spiritual auras are concealed,
keep your voices down
to avoid being noticed.
Thank you for the reminder.
Follow me.
Benefactor Yun is at the Luminous Mirror Platform.
Go now.
I'll guard outside.
Father.
I'm here to see you.
Brat.
Long time no see.
Father.
You haven't changed a bit
from when you left me.
What you see now is my primordial spirit.
Of course I'm the same.
But you...
you've grown up quite a bit.
You no longer have
that fearless expression from when you were young.
You seem to have a lot on your mind now.
Father.
I didn't expect...
you to be waiting for me here.
Father.
I...
miss you so much.
Have you forgotten?
I hate it when men cry.
But...
But I...
I repeatedly told Big Pig Demon to keep an eye on you.
As expected,
you still escaped out of Qingluan Peak.
Father.
In order to save me,
Big Pig Demon was killed by Xu Zhao.
In order to protect the Wangshu Sword,
I had to go down the mountain with my sword.
You know the name of this sword?
It means you have been to Qionghua.
Don't tell me
you've become a disciple of Qionghua?
Yes.
I have been to Qionghua.
But everyone in Qionghua
said that you and Mother stole the Wangshu Sword
and betrayed your fellow disciples.
But I didn't believe it.
I became a disciple
to clear Mother's and your names.
Tianhe.
I stopped you from leaving the mountain
because I didn't want you to get involved in the predicament from 19 years ago.
It really is karma
and fate playing tricks on people.
Don't tell me
everything I'm doing is wrong?
No.
It's fate that's wrong.
Xuan Xiao and I joined Tai Qing's sect together.
I was mocked by my peers because of my unruly personality
and he was ostracized for being stained with his parents' blood,
until I beat up his peers for him
and he took the Ice and Fire Whipping punishment for me.
I was looking for you everywhere.
So you are here.
For you,
my face was beaten up to this state.
You should at least show some gratitude.
Thanks.
I'll find a chance
to teach that Xuan Ji a lesson.
What's wrong?
You're hurt?
I'm fine.
Let me see.
Ice and Fire Whipping?
I was the one who beat up my peers.
Why did Master punish you?
I'll go find him.
At worst, he'll give me a beating.
Don't go.
Master gave me the punishment of Ice and Fire Whipping
to see if I have perseverance.
Only those with strong perseverance
can hold the Xihe.
Really?
You have become the host of Xihe?
That's great!
No one in Qionghua Sect will dare to bully us anymore.
You
will definitely become
the most powerful Sword Immortal in history.
Tianqing.
Do you know what?
I want all the people in Qionghua who look down on us
to see us in a new light.
Based on what you just said,
I will treat you as my best friend forever.
Although my spiritual cultivation is average,
if someone dares to bully you,
I'll make him suffer all the same.
It is said that Master
is going to host the Divine Sword Recognition Ceremony.
We will soon get
Xihe and Wangshu soon.
Senior.
I was looking for you in Zuihuayin
but didn't see you.
So you two are practicing here in secret.
Xuan Xiao.
Master said
we need to cultivate the two swords together to connect our minds
in order to prevent the backfiring of the sword auras.
Don’t be held back by others.
Yun Tianqing.
You just idle around all day.
Don’t disturb our sword training.
Tianqing.
You are talented and smart.
You should study and train hard.
Don't be looked down upon by others.
Senior Su Yao.
Senior Xuan Xiao.
Junior Tianqing.
This is Junior Su Yu, an apprentice who just came up the mountain.
She is now a disciple under Grandmaster.
Senior Xuan Zhen asked me to bring her here
to meet everyone.
Greetings, Senior.
Greetings, seniors.
What are you looking at?
Aren't you going to greet her back as a senior?
Greetings, Junior.
This Senior Xuan Xiao
is the golden child of Qionghua Sect.
And I,
Yun Tianqing...
am an ignorant troublemaker.
Junior.
Why are you here for immortal cultivation?
You are already
as beautiful as a fairy.
Tianqing.
Stop talking nonsense.
Beauty
is only skin deep.
A true immortal cultivates their character.
From that day on,
the three of us became inseparable friends.
But it was at that time
that Xihe Sword and Wangshu Sword were forged
and ruined everything.
Hundreds of years ago, the Dream Tapir Demon Clan
stole a lot of spiritual purple crystals
and built the Huanming Demon Realm.
They hid in the horizon
and often caused disaster to the people.
But all the immortal sects did not know how to track them down.
The 20th grandmaster of our sect, Immortal Dao Yin,
observed the stars at night
and found that Huanming Realm moves like a heavenly trail.
Every 19 years, they approach the skylight region of Kunxu.
So he planned a strategy to exterminate this demon clan.
Zong Lian.
Tell the disciples about it.
The demon-exterminating strategy is to forge the Yin Yang double swords
and use their immense spiritual power
to form the sword pillars that charge straight up into the sky.
When Huanming passes by,
we'll capture them.
After three generations,
I've finally
forged the divine swords of Xihe and Wangshu.
But the two swords
must be awakened by the spiritual aura of the living.
Xuantian Goddess once issued a divine decree stating that
if the divine swords were forged,
everyone in the sect
can abandon their mortal bodies and become immortal beings.
I've chosen the hosts of the double swords.
Xihe's host is Xuan Xiao.
Wangshu's host is...
Su Yu.
Master.
Didn't you say
I am the real host of Wangshu?
You have a half Yin body.
Su Yu has the ultimate Yin body.
Your qualifications are worlds apart.
But Master,
you promised me.
Please give me another chance.
Is this how a senior should act?
If you dare to mess around again,
I'll expel you.
Master.
Take the swords!
Follow Master's orders.
This is the Spiritual Light Zao Jade.
It can open up the forbidden area.
From now on, you two will cultivate at the forbidden area.
Zong Lian forging these two swords
also marked the beginning of a huge mistake.
Everyone in Qionghua
became a pawn in Tai Qing's palm.
Father.
If you and Mother hadn't taken away the Wangshu Sword,
would Brother Xuan Xiao
not have been driven crazy
and not have been sealed in the ice?
But
you were able to go back to save Xuan Zhen's daughter.
You couldn't have abandoned your friends and peers.
Father.
What exactly happened back then?
I promised Su Yu
not to tell you this.
Father.
But now,
Huanming is about to reach above Qionghua.
It's very likely that a war
like that of 19 years ago would break out again.
I have to know the truth
before I know what I should do.
So after demons die,
their primordial spirits would also come to the Netherworld.
There's no difference between humans and demons here.
One may be a human in this life
and a demon in the next life.
One may be a demon in this life
and a human in the previous life.
Then why would humans and demons fight each other?
Then those demons who died by my sword...
all died in vain.
As for me,
I may be a human in this life
but I may become a demon in my next life.
If you've really thought this through,
there will be no estrangement
between you and Tianhe and Mengli.
Lingsha.
I thought
I should just try my best in everything
and to live and die together.
How is that possible?
Sister!
Lingsha!
-Lingsha!
-Sister!
Lingsha.
Sister!
-Sister!
-Lingsha!
Miss Han.
Among the dead,
there's one who can't let go of their obsession.
I asked around and found out she was your sister.
So I brought her here to see you.
But you must control your emotions.
Otherwise, the immortal master and Mr. Yun will be implicated.
Okay.
Seven?
Sister!
Why are you and the immortal master here?
We are not dead.
We just came to the Netherworld to get the Barrier-Crossing Branch.
Sister.
Didn't you take the Fuyao Immortal Fruit Pill
and had recovered?
How could you have died?
It's not due to a disease that the Han family members die early.
How can it be cured?
I saw my father's primordial spirit.
He told me
the reason the Han family members have short lifespans.
Reason?
Father.
I know you and Mother are doing this for my own good.
But I can't stay out of this anymore.
I have someone I want to protect.
You have someone you want to protect?
Okay.
I'll tell you.
That day,
your mother learned that
I offended Grandmaster in order to get the Fuyao Immortal Fruit Pill,
so she went to Xuan Zhen to plead for leniency.
But unexpectedly,
she found out the real reason of the war.
Senior.
You’ve always been considerate of us.
Did Tianqing really offend Grandmaster
because of me?
Senior.
Please help Tianqing plead for leniency with the grandmaster.
Junior Su Yu.
You don't know
I'm no longer that formidable disciple
in Grandmaster's heart.
Why?
Grandmaster is here!
Grandmaster is here.
I don't want to implicate you.
Hide now.
Hurry!
Greetings, Grandmaster.
Xuan Zhen.
Make a cup of tea for me.
Yes, Master.
Master, please.
When I brought you up the mountain,
you were only 8 or 9 years old.
Do you remember
why I named you
Zhen?
It's from the Hexagram Zhen.
Smile
in face of an adversity.
It's a warning to be prepared for danger in times of peace
and to remain calm in times of danger.
I regarded you as a role model of Qionghua's disciples.
But you lied to everyone
and got into a relationship with the female disciple Jingci
and gave birth to a daughter, Xuanye.
You should know
that people who engage in an illicit relationship will be expelled from the mountain.
The child born out of an illicit relationship
will be executed according to the rules.
Master.
Please spare Xuanye's life.
I'll die for her!
You are my first disciple
and the person I trust the most.
Apart from Zong Lian and I,
only you know
what I want to accomplish.
I know you
want to absorb the power of the purple crystal of Huanming Realm
for your ascension.
That's why I lied to the whole sect,
saying that we're exterminating demons to protect the people.
But you caused such a big trouble at the crucial moment.
Master.
This is not the right way to become an immortal.
You're disregarding countless disciples' lives
for your own selfish desire.
Besides, the Dream Tapir Demon Clan has never harmed the mortal world.
Must an entire clan be sacrificed
for your ascension?
With my ascension,
all my disciples will become immortals.
What do you mean by selfish desire?
Demons can't change their nature. They are harmless now,
but it's inevitable that they will bring disaster to all living beings in the future.
The extermination of a mere demon clan
is no big deal.
But you,
what's your decision?
I know your intention.
As long as you let Jingci and my daughter live,
I'm willing to be the vanguard in the invasion of Huanming Realm
to give my life
to you.
In order to protect others,
Su Yu only told Xuan Xiao and me about this.
Xuan Xiao was the host of Xihe.
His heart was filled with ambition.
He chose not to believe it.
But I did.
My father told me
the ancestors of the Han family were proficient in feng shui.
They aspired to explore all dangerous places
to search for various rare treasures.
Unexpectedly,
they accidentally entered the divine clan's forbidden area
and were infected by the poison of extreme coldness.
As a result, the descendants of the Han family
have short genetic lifespans
and do hard labor to relieve the divine punishment...
to atone for our sins.
Then...
what happened to my parents
and uncles?
I didn't see your parents.
I think they have no worries anymore.
My father
is in the Netherworld.
He willingly became a ferryman who transports primordial spirits
and never stops working.
Since it's a divine punishment,
is there a way to resolve it?
It's a consequence of a sin
which repeats cyclically.
How can it be resolved?
The only way is for my descendants to stay away from the forbidden area.
Seven.
You must promise me
not to go to the forbidden area again.
Okay?
Sister.
You waited for me here
just to tell me the truth?
Master Ziying.
You promised me
to be with Seven to the end of time
and let her
spend the rest of her life happily.
Miss Lingxiang.
I'm not one to express myself.
But right now,
I can promise you
I can give up everything
just to accompany Lingsha
to fulfill her wish.
Miss.
It's almost time.
You must leave.
Sister!
Seven.
I'm leaving.
You must cherish every day
and cherish the people around you.
Sister!
Lingsha.
I know you're sad.
You still have us.
Since you trusted my mother,
why didn't you take her away then?
At that time,
I was about the same age as you are now.
I was full of doubts,
but I didn't know how to resist.
Just like you now.
Don't you
also have a lot of doubts
about Xuan Xiao?
But you still helped him break out of the ice
out of your friendship.
Tai Qing knew I would risk my life to protect Su Yu,
so he used the Fuyao Immortal Fruit Pill as a condition.
Xuan Zhen and I were ordered to invade the Huanming Realm.
So,
you invaded Huanming Realm because of my mother.
But I've always believed a saying,
that humans and demons are the same.
They both have good and evil.
You are better than me in this aspect.
I couldn't determine if the Dream Tapir Demon Clan was good or evil,
until the day of the great war.
Qionghua has set up the trap with the Wangshu and Xihe double swords
and the barrier is about to open!
We must protect the Purple Crystal Mountain to death!
Yes!
The human race has broken its defense.
Kill!
Master is really doing this to seize the power of the purple crystal.
The Dream Tapir Demon Clan has stayed away from the mortal world
and has no intention to harm the human race.
But you took away my Purple Crystal Mountain
and exterminated my clan!
Aren't you afraid of retribution?
I was wrong.
I did everything wrongly.
Qionghua Sect
can't make any more mistakes.
The Immortal Sect actually suddenly came here?
How is Lady Chan You?
The demon chief Chan You couldn't protect herself.
I'm here to get rid of them conclusively!
Senior, no!
Senior!
It's our fault.
You should be well aware
we’re the ones slaughtering the Dream Tapir Demon Clan.
Tianqing.
She’s the young chief of Huanming. We can’t keep her.
Senior.
You know all this is wrong.
Why are you still doing this?
I just want to go back alive
and see Jingci and my Ye.
This little demon
is as big as my Ye.
You must take her back.
This will be me accumulating merits for Ye.
Go back alive.
Go...
Young Chief.
I'll die with you.
19 years ago,
the humans and demons who participated in that great war
were all sacrificed for Tai Qing's own selfish desires.
That
includes your mother.
Father.
I know you don't want to talk about it.
But I really want to know this.
You'd already taken Mother away from Qionghua.
So why did she die?
She died...
because of you.