Sis,
it's not that I don't want to give up the quarry.
It's just that these quarry workers
are all surplus labor from various villages.
You know,
they don't have much education.
If I shut this down,
where will they make a living?
I've already discussed all of this with Shengqiang Group.
The quarry workers can be hired in the eco-city in the future.
Security guards, cleaners,
sanitation workers, maintenance staff, these positions
can be offered to them first.
After it's closed,
what can I do?
All the road paving in the eco-city
and exterior wall decoration can be given to you.
I...
Did I hear that right?
You heard correctly.
I know you're quite familiar with stone materials.
They happen to need that expertise,
so you can help oversee it for them.
Believe in the light.
We must believe in the light.
With your word,
I'll shut it down tomorrow.
Oh, right.
There's one more thing
I need you to do for me.
Your business is my business,
sis.
Go ahead.
That's it.
Sis,
don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Take it easy.
Goodbye.
Sis,
take it easy.
Don't see us off.
We can go by ourselves.
Wait a moment, sis.
Xiaolong, Xiaohu.
Did you get the stuff?
Hurry up.
Brother Wei,
coming.
Quick.
What's all this?
This is Brother Wei's private collection.
This is so cool.
The duck necks are free now.
Hurry up and load it into the car for me.
Alright!
hurry up!
Oh, right.
Remember what I told you earlier.
Don't worry.
I'm good at this.
Take care, sis.
Take care, ladies.
Take care.
You two,
come with me.
Where are we going?
Where to?
To play mahjong.
Where are you from?
I reserved this room.
You're Sister Lin, right?
Yes.
Sister Zhang and Sister Xu can't make it due to some matters.
I'm their cousin.
I'm here to fill in.
Those two unreliable ones.
Please, have a seat first.
Alright.
Yan, where are you now?
On my way.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Have they arrived?
Those two unreliable ones.
they have something urgent today.
They can't make it.
What should we do then?
Someone has already filled in.
Alright.
I'll be there soon, wait for me.
It's disconnected.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm late.
You're finally here.
We've been worried sick.
Don't even mention it.
The kid has midterm exams today.
His father insisted that I take him.
It's so annoying.
He's old enough now.
Yet they still insist on you taking him?
Tell me about it.
But a stepmom is still a mom.
If I don't take care of it,
my husband
would give me hell.
He'd have to eat you every day to keep that up.
You're such a pain.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, right.
These two are Xiao Xue's cousins.
They're here to join us.
This is Sister Yan.
Hello, Sister Yan.
Please, sit down, sit down.
In a bit.
Give me a few more rounds, sis.
No problem.
I'm good at this.
You see,
young people
have potential.
Two bamboo.
Take.
One ten thousand.
Six bamboo.
Take.
Winning on a kong.
Nine dots.
Pong.
Self-draw.
One of characters.
Kong.
I'm sorry.
I self-drew again.
No way.
What did you eat for lunch?
Are your hands that skilled?
We're all beginners.
Maybe it's just beginner's luck.
Don't give me that.
You're playing dumb to take advantage of us.
Yan'er,
we might lose everything here today.
Let's play two more rounds.
Let's continue.
I don't believe this.
Come on, let's go.
Six ten thousand.
I've won.
Won again.
This is never-ending.
Let's keep playing.
Sure, we can keep playing.
However,
Sister Yan,
Sister Lin,
you two
need to settle the bill first.
Sister Yan,
you owe
88,000.
Sister Lin,
you owe 66,000.
Do you two
want to pay in cash
or by transfer?
Is it really that much?
There are so many people watching.
We won't default on our debts.
Right.
I'll give my husband a call.
Sister Lin.
I'll call my husband too.
Honey,
What are you doing?
I'm having dinner with the leaders from the provincial government.
I see.
My best friend
Yes?
is sick
and urgently needs 100,000 yuan.
She lost at mahjong again, didn't she?
I'm not a bank.
What are you doing?
Come on, hurry up.
Let's have a drink.
Alright, alright, I'm coming.
Yan Jie.
Someone's looking for you at the back door.
Coming.
What are you doing?
Let go!
Help!
Get down!
Let me go!
I'm not going!
Are you crazy?
This is kidnapping, you know that?
Don't you know who my husband is?
Yan Jie.
Debts must be paid.
it's only right and proper.
Even if your husband is the king of heaven,
you still have to pay up, don't you?
I never said I wouldn't pay you back.
My husband is at a business dinner.
When he's done,
he'll definitely give me the money.
Well then, I'll just have to entertain myself a bit too.
What are you doing?
Don't come any closer!
Bring her in.
Let's go.
Lin.
How did you get caught too?
Is this really necessary?
I never said I wouldn't pay you.
Speak up.
Yan,
it's all Sister Lin's fault for wronging you.
What do you mean?
Yan Jie,
this good friend of yours
has been setting you up all along.
That Sister Lin and Sister Xu
are all her accomplices.
Only you,
stupid as you are, got sold out
and you're still counting your money.
Lin,
is it true?
How could you do this?
I was wondering why I kept losing.
I even helped you with your tea business.
How can you face me?
You've gone too far!
I'll beat you to death!
Stop it.
Sister Fei.
In fact, nine out of ten gamblers lose.
There's rarely such thing as real luck.
This...
Isn't this just like in Hong Kong movies?
In reality,
it's even more ridiculous than that.
Yan Jie,
actually,
when I was playing cards with Xiaolong earlier,
I was cheating and switching cards the whole time.
You just didn't notice.
After playing mahjong for so many years,
you've been playing for nothing.
Yan Jie,
look who's here.
Honey!
Darling!
What took you so long?
Don't be afraid, don't be afraid.
You scared me to death.
It's okay, it's okay now.
I couldn't see you anymore.
Lanlan,
thank you so much this time.
Director Jia,
if you want to thank someone,
thank this Miss Bai.
She's the one who helped you.
Miss Bai,
I won't bother with words of thanks.
Come over for tea when you're free.
Talented individuals like yourself,
we are very willing
to cooperate with and support you.
Then I thank you, Director Jia.
I should be thanking you.
Do come by.
Honey, let's go home.
I've prepared some bird's nest soup for you.
Honey,
you're still the best to me.
You're my wife, after all.
If I'm not good to you, who else would I be good to?
Let's go, let's go.
Miss Bai.
My brother said you're very efficient.
I've learned a lot this time.
It's just a coincidence.
Just in time.
I already knew Hong Wei before.
Hong Wei.
This is General Manager Gao.
About the stone materials you mentioned before,
it was specially approved by General Manager Gao.
So you're General Manager Gao.
I've heard so much about you.
I'll take care of the stone materials.
I'll make sure General Manager Gao is satisfied.
Then, Brother Wei, please keep a close eye on things in the future.
You must be joking.
Little Wei.
Call me Little Wei.
Sister Xiaofe,
well, um...
the third item.
Cast
Hu Yue as Bai Xiaofe
Dong Xuanyu as Zeng Qingqing
Yu You as Xu Youyou
Yuan Mingze as Xu Yue
Yang Jingwen as Xiao Zhi
Li Yimu as Hong Wei
Su Yuanbo as Chen Feng
Wei Xin as Cao Xin
Liang Tingyu as Brother Kun
Sun Qixuan as Na Zha
Chuo Fujun as Second Uncle
Yang Huimin as Second Aunt
Li Zixuan as Assistant Xiao Qi
Zhao Xiaowei as Old Zhou
Chang Ruikun as Guest
Wang Hongzhi as Xiao Hu
Wang Xingyu as Xiao Long
Wang Yipeng as Liu Shuai
Yan Xihan as Secretary Dong
Bi Hongwei as Secretary Li
Zhang Xiaolian as Aunt Liu
Dang Fenglai as Grandpa Qian
Zhao Jian as Security Guard A
Special Appearances
Liu Dan as Dean Wei
He Yunwei as Old Xu the Fish Vendor
Cao Han as Gao
Hou Naisen as General Manager Zhang
Also Starring
Jia Tianhao, Huang Xinlong, Chen Bingjie, Li Zhaoyu, Su Nan, Ge Xinzhe
Directing Team
Director: Guan Xiaojie
Script Supervisor: Liu Zhizhuo
Casting Director: Chen Ming
Actors Coordinator: Liao Yang
Cinematography Team
Director of Photography: Peng Qiang
A Camera Operator: Wang Wenxing
Focus Puller: Quan Qinling
Camera Assistant: Yin Zilong
Camera Assistant: Quan Qinling
Camera Trainee: Yin Zilong
Lighting Team
Art Department
Art Director: Sun Hongxi
Set Designer: Liu Xu
Props Team
Props Master: Tong Kai
Set Props: Yang Shuangshuang
On-set Props: Wang Yan
Costume and Make-up Department
Styling Director: Du Juan
Hair Stylist: Wang Junya
Executive Producers: Zhang Xinjie, Shi Jun
Chief Planner: Liu Shuai
Producer: Fang Cen, Hai Qing
Life Producers: Wang Qiannan, Zhou Yunhua
Finance: Yu Dan
On-site Producer: Fan Peng
Vehicle Management: Zhai Jingxin
Post-production
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Post-production Supervisor: Tao Ye
DIT: Gao Yang
Video Technicians: Gao Yang, Wang Ning
Colorist: Jiang Jiang
Colorist Assistant: Wei Liguo
Special Effects: Li Shuangyang, Kang Jian
Licensed Music Provided by: Shengxing STUDIO
Dubbing Director: Yi Ruoxun
Dubbing Coordinator: Miao Taijiu
Voice Actors:
Xu Youyou - Miao Taijiu
Wu Yuxuan - Dong Yan
Xu Yue - Fan Xiang
Chen Feng, Yi Duge
Other Voice Actors:
Dong Yue, A Fu, Da Miao, Douhua, Feng Shentan
Wang Xiaoxiao, Liu Haoyu, Qiao Lingxi
Beijing Dubai Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Jinyue Film Co., Ltd.
Shijin Film (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Beijing Ziyang Haohan Media Technology Co., Ltd.
Beijing Fangcun Boyu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Baoding Jiuxin Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Dubai Film and Television Co., Ltd.