From childhood to adulthood,
we've been desperately running towards that unbridled,
carefree moment of happiness.
However,
the further we go,
the lonelier we become.
I gaze into the abyss,
while withdrawing from the conformity of my shell,
trying to find
the train that would stop for me.
Yet,
life is like a catalyst.
Before the flower can bloom,
the branches are already withering.
Until one day,
when I discovered that true strength
is not about confrontation,
but about allowing things to happen,
allowing regrets,
allowing foolishness,
allowing ugliness,
allowing efforts without rewards,
I knew
at that moment,
we are each other's confidence and support.
Sister.
Sister, sister.
Don't throw it, don't.
Please give me a few more days.
I'm begging you, I'll definitely pay you.
What do you mean, 'give you more time'?
If everyone was like you and didn't pay rent,
how am I supposed to survive?
Take your luggage and get out now.
Sister.
Sister, open the door!
Hello?
Zeng Qingqing.
You really know how to stir things up, don't you?
It hasn't even been a month since you started.
That stunt you pulled last night cost me a big client.
We lost five million.
Don't bother coming to work today.
Go straight to HR and resign.
Manager Chen.
I...
Hello?
Gazing at the misty lake waters,
green reeds standing tall.
How's that?
Come on, let's drink to that.
Qingqing is such a beautiful name.
Let me tell you something.
The third line is the most famous.
Green grass by the river bank,
we two swim in the water.
Come on, let's drink up!
Qingqing.
I really like you.
Where are you running off to?
Just my luck, I'm soaked.
Born after 2000, huh?
Who are you?
Don't come any closer.
Before,
I stood where you're standing now.
Bai Xiaofei, what are you doing?
Don't come any closer.
It's just a man, isn't it?
Is it worth it for someone so disloyal?
Let's go back.
Can we start over?
We're still young, there's still time for everything.
Will you come back with me?
You...
Where are you taking me?
Remember,
the best way to deal with pain
is to face it head-on.
Lao Chen,
you're so unreliable.
what kind of people did you invite?
this is so dishonorable.
look, they vomited all over me.
I don't even want to talk to you about it.
you figure out how to make up for this yourself.
Hey, you,
get Dr. Feng
to come here and see me right away.
Director Wei,
I think Dr. Feng is on duty today.
On duty?
I'm in this state, and you're talking about being on duty?
Go and arrange it quickly.
Director Wei,
her husband got injured in a fall.
I think he's admitted to our hospital today.
Which is more important, her husband or her work?
Ask her.
Does she still want to be the deputy director or not?
Work is more important.
Then what are you waiting for?
I'm so angry, I can't even...
Where is this?
What's the room number?
Do you believe me?
You have to stand up for yourself.
You're just in time.
Give me a massage.
It has to be you, Xiao Feng.
This is firm yet gentle.
That feels good.
Why is it you?
Oh, Old Chen, Old Chen.
You're quick to make amends, huh?
What's up?
I've figured it out.
Come down.
Come on.
Come on, get down.
This smooth skin.
Qingqing.
Put this on.
Come on.
I'll go take a quick shower first, then we'll go together.
Wait for me.
Baby.
Hurry up.
It's ready.
Serve the food.
Dean Wei.
Didn't you say 'Three cups of wine for the mundane world'?
Come, let's have the first cup.
Yes, yes, yes. Let's do it.
Cheers!
You're making great progress!
You seem to be having a lot of fun.
Honey, what are you doing here?
A long time ago,
someone told me
that happiness is closing one eye.
I tried,
but I couldn't do it.
If you can't accept something,
there's no need to force yourself.
In fact, no winter is insurmountable,
and no spring will fail to arrive.
Today.
Thank you.
Don't thank me,
thank yourself.
You're the one who forgave yourself.
This is a book I bought today.
I don't know how to express my gratitude to you.
I'd like to give you this book.
I hope you'll like it.
You know, many times,
things aren't as good as you imagine,
but they're not as bad as you think either.
Get a good night's sleep,
and believe that when you wake up tomorrow morning,
it will surely be a better day.
Oh, by the way,
if you need anything in the future,
feel free to come to me anytime.
Okay.
Miss,
Where are you going?
I...
No, if you're a visitor,
you need to register at the front desk.
I'm not a visitor.
I need to see someone.
Just let me in.
It's complicated to explain.
If you can't explain clearly,
then you definitely can't go in.
I really have business here. Just let me in.
If I let you in,
what am I standing here for?
Come on, you're handsome and nice, right?
What do you mean I'm nice?
You can't go in.
Sister Xiaofe!
It's me, Qingqing.
See? I'm here to see Sister Xiaofe.
Please let me in.
President Bai of Pudu PR.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sister Xiaofe.
Cast
Dong Xuanyu as Zeng Qingqing
Yu You as Xu Youyou
Yuan Mingze as Xu Yue
Tang Duoer as Yang Xingyu
Zhao Kangwei as Wu Yuxuan
Li Yimu as Hongwei
Su Yuanbo as Chen
Wei Xin as Cao Xin
Liang Tingyu as Brother Kun
Wang Tianyu as Yu Zhen
Yang Huimin as Second Aunt
Li Zixuan as Assistant Xiaoqi
Zhao Xiaowei as Old Zhou
Wang Ziyi as President Sun
Chang Ruikun as Client
Wang Xingyu as Xiaolong
Wang Yipeng as Liu Shuai
Yan Xihan as Secretary Dong
Sun Jihong as Cleaning Lady
Bi Hongwei as Secretary Li
Zhang Xiaolian as Aunt Liu
Dang Fenglai as Grandpa Qian
Zhao Jian as Security Guard A
Li Qiuyang as Security Guard B
Wang Kangxu as Company Security Guard
Special Appearances
Liu Dan as Dean Wei
He Yunwei as Old Xu the Fish Vendor
Ren Shen as Liu Yan
Gu Minghan as Gao Qiang
Hou Naisen as President Zhang
Also Starring
Shan Chunyan, Wang Xingyu, Liu Hailing, Yang Huimin, Sun Hai, Yuan Hao, Li Jian
Jia Tianhao, Huang Xinlong, Chen Bingjie, Li Zhaoyu, Su Nan, Ge Xinzhe
Directing Team
Director: Guan Xiaojie
Executive Director: He Jinfeng
Casting Director: Chen Ming
Actors Coordinator: Liao Yang
Photography Team
A Camera Operator: Wang Wenxing
Focus Puller: Quan Qinling
Photography Assistant: Yin Zilong
B Camera Operator: Zhang Guohui
Focus Puller: Zhang Fucheng
Camera Assistant: Yin Zilong
Lighting Team
Lighting Director: Sun Tongjun
Lighting Assistants: Sun Gaoming, Wang Hao
Art Department
Art Director: Sun Hongxi
Executive Art Director: Liu Xu
Art Assistant: Li Xuehui
Props Master: Tong Kai
Set Props: Yang Shuangshuang
On-set Props: Wang Yan
Hair Stylist: Wang Junya
Production Team
Executive Producers: Zhang Xinjie, Shi Jun
Chief Planner: Liu Shuai
Producers: Fang Cen, Hai Qing
Production Manager: Dong Haijun
Coordinator: Yu Yuanyuan
Finance: Yu Dan
On-set Producer: Fan Peng
Post-production
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Post-production Supervisor: Tao Ye
Editor: Liu Hualong
DIT: Gao Yang
Colorist: Jiang Jiang
Color Assistant: Wei Liguo
VFX: Li Shuangyang, Kang Jian
Audio Production: Liu Qiang
Music Production: Si Ye, Wang Zicen
Dubbing Director: Yi Ruoxun
Dubbing Coordinator: Miao Taijiu
Voice Actors:
Bai Xiaofei - Jiang He
Zeng Qingqing - Yi Xin
Wu Yuxuan - Dong Yan
Xu Yue, Fan Xiang
Chen Feng - Du Ge
Other Voice Actors:
Yang Jiani, Zhang Rulin, Su Yanglin, Zhang Jiahui
Production Companies:
Shijin Film (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Beijing Ziyang Haohan Media Technology Co., Ltd.
Beijing Fangcun Boyu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Fujian Qile Rongchuang Cultural Industry Group Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies:
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Baoding Jiuxin Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Dubai Film and Television Co., Ltd.