Is your Manager Bai in?
Yes, Manager Xu.
This way, please.
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
I've been waiting for you.
You don't mind if I bring him along, do you?
Why would I mind?
It's best to keep things in the family, right?
That's great.
That's why we say Teacher Bai has a broad vision.
You're destined for great things.
I'll cut you first, you know.
Let's not do that.
There's no need to trouble yourself with that.
Let me do it.
You two are really arch-enemies.
My biggest regret is not disabling him before he went abroad.
I should have crippled him first.
Otherwise, how could he have had the chance to mess with both of us?
Let's not say anything more.
Let's first toast with a fragrant pear.
Fragrant pear, parting ways.
Love leads to separation.
It's quite fitting, actually.
I forgive you.
Teacher Bai is generous.
Peel an apple for me, please.
As you wish.
Xiaofei,
let's get back to the main topic.
Tomorrow, Yuxuan and I are going to Myanmar for filming.
It'll be about a month.
About the favor you asked me last time to help find your cousin,
I've already inquired with the contact person there.
When we get there,
we'll search thoroughly.
However, I still advise you not to get your hopes up too high.
She's a constant worry for my second uncle.
Perhaps if we find her,
my second uncle's illness will improve.
Your second uncle treated you like that.
I really don't understand.
Even food can't stop you from talking.
No matter what,
let's try our best to search.
Maybe there will be a miracle.
Okay.
Leave it to me.
Oh, by the way,
how's Qingqing?
She's doing fine.
She stayed at a colleague's place last night.
I gave her two days off
to let her get some rest.
Is it a man or a woman?
At our receptionist Xiao Yang's place.
However,
my brother has indeed been a bit different lately.
But I can't put my finger on what's changed.
Men's thoughts,
don't try to guess.
Once they get an idea in their head,
they can be even more complicated than women.
If anyone dares to have any ill intentions this time,
I'll keep that in mind.
After withdrawing the money, quickly deliver it to them.
Okay, got it.
Driver,
why do you keep looking at me?
You're so young, yet your memory is so poor.
Have you forgotten who I am?
Green reeds grow in rows,
we two swim in the water.
I really like you.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
Let me out of the car!
Don't be nervous.
What do you think I want to do?
I'm driving for Didi now.
You're driving for Didi?
It's all ruined because of you.
My ex-wife kicked me out again.
I lost my job.
So I had no choice but to drive for Didi.
I'm sorry.
We didn't want things to turn out this way either.
It's not your fault.
I blame myself for having evil thoughts.
It's what I deserve.
At the last drinking party,
didn't they say you graduated from Fudan University?
Can't you do something else?
I'm getting old.
I don't want to bother anymore.
This job is quite flexible.
I'm just living day by day.
Don't be nervous.
Feel free to sit back.
There are cameras all over this car.
I promise to get you safely to your destination.
We're here.
Thank you then.
No problem.
Remember to give me a good rating.
Call me again next time you need a ride.
They'll be doomed sooner or later.
Bad people never come to a good end.
they'll be doomed sooner or later.
Bad people never come to a good end. They'll be doomed sooner or later.
Bad people never come to a good end.
Grandpa Qian,
I've come to see you.
Here,
your favorite White Rabbit milk candy.
White Rabbit is good.
White Rabbit doesn't bite.
Please, have some.
White Rabbit is good.
White Rabbit is good. White Rabbit doesn't bite.
Director.
Qingqing is here.
This is this month's
living expenses from Sister Xiaofei for the elderly.
I happen to be off work today,
so I withdrew it and brought it over right away.
President Bai is spending money on us again.
It's our duty.
Oh, Director,
how is Sister Xiaofei's second uncle doing recently?
It's strange,
since you last visited,
he hasn't run out even once.
He just sunbathes and plays cards every day,
and he's been quite well-behaved.
That's good.
Just don't let him run out and cause trouble for Sister Xiaofei again.
Don't worry.
What are you doing here?
If my boss finds out, I'll lose my job.
I'm bored.
I wanted someone to have lunch with.
Why can't it be any other time?
Does it have to be now?
And right outside my office building too.
Having lunch with my own daughter.
Do I need to schedule a time for that?
Keep your voice down.
When you abandoned my mother and me in Shandong,
why didn't you come for us?
Now that your new family has fallen apart,
you suddenly remember you have a daughter, right?
Did you get what I asked you to?
I can't take it.
I won't let you do anything to harm Xiaofei.
Did I say I was going to hurt her?
I don't care, I just can't take it.
Alright, I'll leave first then.
But there's one thing you need to remember,
your surname is Wei.
Xiao Yang.
There's a bunch of men's skincare products behind your mirror.
Whose are they?
That guy surnamed Zhang.
He's already gone, and you're still keeping them?
I wanted to throw them away.
I've been too busy these past couple of days.
I'll throw them out later.
Don't waste them.
Save them for the next one.
You're making fun of me again.
Keep them for your boyfriend.
Forget I said that.
But Qingqing,
I think you're quite strange.
How am I strange?
Your ability to heal yourself is really strong.
It's only been a day, and you're acting like nothing happened.
Well, I...
It's called 'come fast, go fast.'
Love passionately,
break up quickly.
Do you understand?
I'm impressed.
Can we meet?
I have something for you.
Didi Wei.
What is it?
You'll know when you see me.
What do you want to give me?
You.
Cast
Hu Yue as Bai Xiaofei
Dong Xuanyu as Zeng Qingqing
Yu You as Xu Youyou
Tang Duoer as Yang Xingyu
Zhao Kangwei as Wu Yuxuan
Yang Jingwen as Xiao Zhi
Li Yimu as Hong Wei
Su Yuanbo as Chen Feng
Liang Tingyu as Kun Ge
Wang Tianyu as Yu Zhen
Sun Qixuan as Nazha
Chuo Fujun as Er Shu
Yang Huimin as Er Shen
Wang Ziyi as Sun Zong
Chang Ruikun as Client
Wang Hongzhi as Xiao Hu
Wang Xingyu as Xiao Long
Wang Yipeng as Liu Shuai
Sun Jihong as Cleaning Lady
Bi Hongwei as Secretary Li
Yuan Hong as Nursing Home Director
Zhang Xiaolian as Aunt Liu
Dang Fenglai as Grandpa Qian
Li Qiuyang as Security Guard B
Wang Kangxu as Company Security Guard
Special Appearances
Liu Dan as Director Wei
Ren Shen as Liu Yan
Gu Minghan as Gao Qiang
Cao Han as Gao Lan
Hou Naisen as Manager Zhang
Shan Chunyan, Wang Xingyu, Liu Hailing, Yang Huimin, Sun Hai, Yuan Hao, Li Jian
Jia Tianhao, Huang Xinlong, Chen Bingjie, Li Zhaoyu, Su Nan, Ge Xinzhe
Executive Director: He Jinfeng
Script Supervisor: Liu Zhizhuo
Casting Director: Chen Ming
Photography Team
Director of Photography: Peng Qiang
A Camera Operator: Wang Wenxing
Focus Puller: Quan Qinling
B Camera Operator: Zhang Guohui
Focus Puller: Zhang Fucheng
Photography Assistant: Quan Qinling
Camera Assistant: Yin Zilong
Lighting Director: Sun Tongjun
Lighting Assistants: Sun Gaoming, Wang Hao
Art Department
Art Assistant: Li Xuehui
Props Department
Props Master: Tong Kai
Set Props: Yang Shuangshuang
Costume and Makeup Department
Styling Director: Du Juan
Hair Stylist: Wang Junya
Production Team
Executive Producers: Zhang Xinjie, Shi Jun
Chief Planner: Liu Shuai
Production Manager: Dong Haijun
Coordinator: Yu Yuanyuan
Life Producers: Wang Qiannan, Zhou Yunhua
Finance: Yu Dan
On-site Producer: Fan Peng
Transportation Manager: Zhai Jingxin
Post-production
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Editor: Liu Hualong
DIT: Gao Yang
Video Technicians: Gao Yang, Wang Ning
Colorist: Jiang Jiang
Color Assistant: Wei Liguo
Audio Production: Liu Qiang
Music Production: Si Ye, Wang Zicen
Licensed Music Provided by: Shengxing STUDIO
Dubbing Director: Yi Ruoxun
Dubbing Coordinator: Miao Taijiu
Bai Xiaofe - Jiang He
Zeng Qingqing - Yi Xin
Xu Youyou - Miao Taijiu
Wu Yuxuan - Dong Yan
Xu Yue - Fan Xiang
Other voice actors:
Yang Jiani, Zhang Rulin, Su Yanglin, Zhang Jiahui
Dong Yue, A Fu, Da Miao, Douhua, Feng Shentan
Wang Xiaoxiao, Liu Haoyu, Qiao Lingxi
Production Companies
Beijing Dubai Film and Television Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Jinyue Film Co., Ltd.
Shijin Film (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Fujian Qile Rongchuang Cultural Industry Group Co., Ltd.
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies
Beijing Shengxing Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Ningbo Ziyang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Dubai Film and Television Co., Ltd.