Taobao Shankou invites you to watch the nine-unit true gold
Cut, kill the gold
It's rare to kill the gold so fast
But it's faster
Come on, afternoon tea is here
I am Meng Ziyi
I use Taobao Shankou to order takeout
More advantageous
Come here
You're shameless
I killed you
Vijaya!
You bastard!
Mother!
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
Father, mother,
I will avenge you.
I am in your heart.
Chunfeng,
you should have been more lead.
I will cut you if you go.
You little party.
Junior?
Senior,
what is your martial arts development?
Could you teach me?
Do you know?
I have learnt sword dance.
I practiced martial arts with you.
Yes.
I want to learn
the martial arts of killing.
The martial arts of killing?
Senior.
Is there anyone on the island who is good at music?
Music?
Are you talking about the sound of the flute?
Master's sound is the most important.
Master?
Our master doesn't care about the skill of martial arts.
He knows the heavenly culture and the geography.
He knows the martial arts of eight-storied pagoda, the Qimen, the Dunjia, the Qingqi, the Shugu.
He knows the calligraphy and calligraphy.
What kind of person is Master?
Actually, Master
is a very strict person.
No, no, no.
Senior, you are wrong.
Master
is a very kind person.
When did Master become kind?
Master is a weird person.
I didn't say anything.
Junior sister.
Anyway, it's been a long time.
You will understand it naturally.
Junior sister.
I saw you didn't have breakfast.
I brought it for you.
What did you call me?
Junior sister.
This cake
was made by my teacher.
It can't be bought outside.
The Little Face
Look, your face is red.
Stinky girl.
You are fighting with me, aren't you?
You don't eat a good meal.
I will have a good wedding for you today.
Don't move.
Go.
Master.
Where is Xuan Feng?
Second Brother.
You practiced late last night.
I think you got up late.
You said Chen Xuan Feng
practiced late.
You are lying.
I am lying.
Master.
I have been very serious recently.
I will be very careful.
You have been
working hard recently.
You have been drinking and playing.
And you have come up with such a little trick.
You are very happy, aren't you?
Master.
There are thousands of beautiful things in the world.
Spring has flowers, autumn has moon.
Summer has cool wind, winter has snow.
If you only care about practicing martial arts
and ignore the beautiful scenery,
isn't it a pity?
Yes.
There are thousands of beautiful things in the world.
It's a pity
that you don't go to see them.
Master.
I was wrong.
You were not wrong.
Peach Blossom Island
is a free place.
Whenever
you don't want to stay,
you can leave at any time.
Why did Master leave?
Didn't he teach us martial arts?
It's the end of the class today.
Master is so casual.
Okay, okay.
Master is wrong.
Don't hurt him, Second Brother.
Second Brother.
You are not a good person.
Master didn't ask you to get up.
Kneel down for a while.
Get up.
You kneeled down, didn't you?
You are the one who is lazy.
It has nothing to do with me.
Brother, I'll leave it to you.
No need.
You are not so obedient.
You can go to Master's house in Louria.
You think I dare not?
Because of you,
I can't learn martial arts from Master today.
You are really a bad luck.
Come on.
The horse of the sea.
What's the matter?
Master.
I want to learn the most powerful martial arts of Peach Blossom Island.
Please teach me.
You have to start from the entrance.
The best way to learn
the entrance martial arts is the Xuan Feng.
Go find him.
But I want to learn from Master.
Go.
Second Brother.
Are you here to see my fun?
I'm here to learn martial arts from you.
I'm a horse of the sea.
How can I teach you?
I offended you before.
I apologize to you.
Master said
the best way to learn the entrance martial arts
of Second Brother is the hand-shake.
He asked me to learn from you.
I had toistic my power in объ
Older brother, please teach me.
Not to hide from the unknown?
Avoid thearkanant festival科
Martial arts of the Goddess.
The Shis are sitting under the Bodhi tree
for 49 days.
They are sitting under the Bodhi tree for 3 seconds.
Do you understand?
Clean it carefully.
Tip.
Why are there more?
The essence of a strong handshake
usually...
Hit me.
Slip in and slip out.
A man of martial skills
The most important thing is patience.
Chen Xuan Feng, you're playing tricks on me.
You're so impatient. How can you play tricks on me?
I know you hate me.
You can stop teaching me if you don't want to.
Why do you make fun of me?
Who is it?
Coming.
Do you have a beggar's attitude?
I don't have time to play tricks on you.
You come to beg people in the daytime,
but you don't smile at night.
Are you from Kuizhou?
You've changed so fast.
Say it.
Are you not going to force me to grow up?
I don't want to waste time with you.
I'll go and ask Senior Brother to teach me.
I don't want to.
I was going to give it to you.
Just put it there.
What a good-for-nothing.
I...
Mei Ruo Hua.
You want to kill me
just because you've practiced some tricks?
You're looking for death.
Senior Sister.
Are you all right?
Why can't you learn it?
I was too anxious, panic and confused.
Master said
I have to practice for an hour.
I can only practice
when I'm not in the mood.
I can't be too anxious.
Fourth Brother,
you're really good at
memorizing Master's words.
Sister Shi Min,
your movements are too rigid
and your expression is very serious.
You have to be as weak as you can.
I have to be as weak as I can.
I have to learn the moves
and then I can run as I want.
Sister Shi Min, don't worry.
I'll teach you.
You have to relax first.
Don't be too hard.
I'm as weak as a mountain
and I'm as soft as a stone.
Do you have any tricks?
No.
The Bibo Palm is simple,
but the first move and the first move
are all Master's new tricks.
They are the foundation of Taowa Martial Arts.
You can't learn it
in one move.
Practicing martial arts is about the progress of the world.
The disciples of Taohua Island
all practice from the Bibo Palm.
Even if you're a private,
you have to practice it a year later
to have the chance to get to know other masters.
I think you
have to practice for three years.
Less than a year.
I will definitely become the Bibo Palm.
You three go to practice first.
Sister Shi Min, come with me.
Senior, what are you doing?
Sister Shi Min, come.
Sister Shi Min,
every move of the martial arts
is like a lighthouse.
Every move of the martial arts
is like you walking into
a new dark room.
This room belongs to you.
But you don't understand.
Master means
you are the master of the dark room.
you have to
touch it by yourself.
Little by little,
inch by inch,
until you know
the sides and corners of this room.
You have to find out everything.
Then it really belongs to you.
Otherwise,
we are just
guests in this room for the time being.
But Senior,
if I don't know the order,
can't I see
the whole appearance of this room?
It's not easy to enter the room.
So you have to
spend time to repair it by yourself.
Master often said
that you can't do anything
without practice.
I can't remember.
Stop practicing.
There is a dragonfly in the mountains and seas.
You can do it with your hands.
What dragonfly?
Dragonfly in the mountains and seas.
I can't understand.
Say something.
Seafood buns.
Master's favorite is
your favorite dish.
I'll send it to Master.
Senior,
we haven't eaten yet.
I just brought it from Master.
He left it for us.
Seafood buns.
Pig ears.
Cow's kidney.
And...
Legs and legs.
All kinds?
There are only five kinds of meat.
But the same foot
is 25 times.
25 times.
It's the same as the five-five plum blossom.
We should
write
the name of this dish.
The name...
I'll wait for you to write it.
Go to bed now.
Go to bed.
Where's the water?
Green lilies?
Bis K physique of notify.
Master,
my brother says
this is your favorite dish.
What's the matter?
Master,
I want to ask you
how to practice the Palm of Bibo.
Peach blossoms fall, not the sword of God.
The sword of Bihai is in full bloom.
The essence of it is the Palm of Bibo.
The Palm of Bihai is the song of God.
It's your master's creation.
The Palm of Bibo
is the foundation of our Taoist martial arts.
Zhuangzi, Tao Dejing, Shijing.
The martial arts of Peach Blossom Island are not important.
Before you learn the martial arts,
finish reading these books first.
Maybe it will help you understand the Palm of Bibo.
Thank you, Shijing.
I will finish reading them as soon as possible.
It doesn't matter if you finish reading them.
What's important is to understand the art of palm.
It's easy to understand and doesn't need any etiquette.
This is the essence of our Taoist martial arts.
Thank you, Shijing.
Zhuangzi, Tao Dejing.
Why did you give her these books?
Weren't you the one who told me
that when she read herself or is too close to the direct world,
she will end up in a pontos.
Studying is more than teaching her to manage the world,
it's also for adjusting her personality.
My wife
sounds like a traditional people.
is truly careful like a Stephanie아아
He called me by name Mrs you
I have to thought to try
Senior brother
drawers
Hurry
Leng Zeyue
People call her gentle, but she would leave in fear when she hopped into her home Wait for a moment
Do you know
why the arm такed trained?
yes
Actually
there truly is a barrier
After mastering this Martial Arts
one has to go to a very dangerous Bukkak
Spirituality cannot be known
except during moments of danger
Give me a little bit.
Tao Hua.
ixon,
alert!
Your operate has been carried out.
Senior sister0
as soon as possible
Attorney
Wuケ
You're awake.
Lie down.
Xuan Feng.
Is this how you protect your sister?
I...
Senior.
It's not Senior's fault.
I was the one
who broke in.
Xuan Feng, you should go.
Let Chao Feng have a good rest.
Yes, Senior.
Yes.
I will go then.
Your master
seiner than ever
I'm sorry.
Senior.
Actually,
I know there's a formation
in the Peach Blossom Forest.
Senior Xuan Feng told me about it.
Don't worry.
I'll be more careful in the future.
Senior.
I must learn martial arts.
Learn martial arts
for what?
I asked your master about it.
How did he answer?
He didn't answer me either.
But revenge is not the only meaning of learning martial arts.
You have to figure out why you live.
Go to sleep.
Sleep well.
You'll get better tomorrow.
Today,
I'm Daxi's wife.
Ugh!
What?
I'm asking your master
how to practice V recurrence palm.
Why am I joints hè?
Have a look.
What are you looking at?
A wave?
What's that?
Metal is danmyâ?
A wave.
Lengthen and move multiple times,
but
why am I still danmyâ?
I don't know.
Close your eyes.
Feel it.
Feel the wind of the four seasons.
The Daoist flower is in full bloom.
It's beyond your own reach.
Feel it well.
This is the essence of Taohua Dao Martial Arts.
The essence.
The Daoist flower is in full bloom.
It's beyond your own reach.
Feel it.
Feel the wind of the four seasons.
The essence.
The manages every day
to exchange their skills.
Yuqing 경찰
has a biofather.
Here, master.
Open your eyes.
This is my father?
Yes, master.
Ah!
H puppet.
What aieth level that you can move?
Ooooh.
These two aditす you open your eyes.
Oh, Liu is
That's what I do on your chest.
Look at Liu.
to reach such a skill.
Who wants to compete with him?
It's several levels
more powerful than my skill.
The poison in your body is getting stronger.
It's getting more frequent.
Whenever you use the new method of Lianyang
to heal your wound,
you'll become a demon.
I'm afraid that
you'll be dead for a long time.
Don't say anymore.
I'll be back.
Go ahead.
The key.
Madam.
Where's your master?
Master told me to stay here to guard him.
He went to make medicine for you.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
How about him?
Is he doing well?
He's doing well.
How could he be not well?
That's good.
Master.
Now you know.
The world's most invincible pharmacist
is actually
just a
a tired
and lonely
person.
A person who's always
a person
who doesn't want to be like the moon
and change.
Master.
Everyone
has his own persistence.
Others won't understand.
But for this person,
it's very important.
Thank you.
Chao Feng.
I'm sorry.
I've seen the most gentle person.
Sometimes like a mother.
Sometimes like a friend.
You're the best person in the world.
But such a good person,
why should he suffer so much?
The world is unbearable.
You're the only one.
Master, we're saved.
What?
The West Jade White-Square Manor sent a letter.
How do you know it's saved?
You stole the letter?
The West Jade Wind.
Who?
The West Jade White-Square Manor sent me a letter.
The Jianghu Yuanchen sent me a letter.
What's it?
Brother Yao.
We've never met since we parted.
That day you said that you couldn't cure your illness.
I'm sorry.
Today I'm looking for the West Jade White-Square Manor.
I've found a way to cure it.
The Yin Wheel Pill
is the most powerful poison in the world.
I can use it to save you.
Fire Flower.
Fire Flower is a flower that can cure the disease.
It can cure the poison.
But this flower is rare in the world.
It grows in the mouth of the volcano.
It's located in the south of the East Sea.
Liu Bo Island.
Liu Bo Island?
Is she not going with us?
I didn't tell her to leave today.
Why did you leave her?
Liu Bo Island is very dangerous.
I'm afraid she'll be in danger.
She's injured.
It's not a good idea.
Sister.
Why are you here?
I'm going too.
Sister.
Isn't it just going to Liu Bo Island?
We're brothers.
I'm afraid that if I don't go,
you won't be able to get the Fire Flower.
You're so weak.
What are you talking about?
You're so stubborn.
It's better to go together.
Come back.
I will be your friend forever
My eyes
Even if we are wronged
Please don't be afraid
You say you don't want to compromise
But you chase