[theme music]
♪ The game of youth starts with passion ♪
♪ Make the first move and never give up ♪
♪ Let the blood inside you flow ♪
♪ Let the world see that I am invincible ♪
♪ Young face, heaving chest ♪
♪ As always
I'll chase my dreams like I used to ♪
♪ Swallow my tears
And make myself stronger ♪
♪ Sweat illuminating in the hot sun ♪
♪ Dear youth ♪
♪ Keep running, your dreams lie ahead ♪
♪ Don't be afraid, work hard and grow up ♪
♪ We are in the best years of youth ♪
♪ We should seize the day ♪
♪ Live the way ♪
♪ You want to live the most ♪
The Prince of Tennis
~ Match! Tennis Juniors! ~
[tense music]
[tense music continues]
[Yan Zhiming] Tian Zilong.
Hai Guang's vice captain.
One of their top three.
His style is quick, stable, and accurate.
I guess he is closely matched
with Ji Jingwu.
[Tang Jiale gasps]
[Yan Zhiming] Yuan Chi.
He's a baseline player.
Sometimes, he plays
violently and subconsciously,
and attacks his opponents physically.
[blows air]
Hm? But he looks gentle in the video.
That's because Tian Zilong is there.
Oh.
[tense music]
Why are you late?
I...
overslept.
Double your training volume
after the match!
Yes.
[Zilong] We must win
the national tournament.
Get ready to train. Dismissed.
[all] Yes.
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[groans]
-[thwacks]
-[grunting]
[gasps, grunts]
[both gasp]
What?
How could he win?
-And so easily?
-Whoa.
That's what Hai Guang is.
I'll send the video to all of you later.
[Dayong] We have to take this seriously.
[inhales]
[panting]
[ominous music]
[thwacking]
[calm music]
[calm music continues]
[sighs, scoffs]
[Tang Jiale] We didn't
play together against Xing Yao today.
Yes, I was disappointed.
And the fact that you were not there
made me realize
how much you mean to me.
GOLDEN PARTNERS NEVER LOSE
[Tang Jiale] Only when I stood
at your position
did I realize
how hard you were struggling
as the other half of the Golden Partners,
and how much understanding you needed.
Even though we have been called
the Golden Partners for a long time,
I have never truly understood you.
STOMACH MEDICINE
[Tang Jiale] Dachi...
[mouthing]
as your partner...
...no matter whose fault it is,
-you always apologize first.
-[Tang Jiale] I really feel like...
-But the percentage
-I should apologize.
of you missing the balls have increased
by 7.35 percent compared to before.
In fact, the main reason
for missing the balls
is that Jiale is much faster than before.
[Baiyang] Are you okay?
Let's rest for a bit.
[Tang Jiale] No problem. I can continue.
The ability to give each other
confidence and trust during a match...
[mouths]
Dachi.
...we will be partners again, right?
Mm-hm.
[sighs]
-[sighs]
-[cell phone ringing]
[inhales sharply]
What's up?
I think...
No.
I'm ready to bring back
the Golden Partners.
[sighs]
Do you...
Do you still want to be my partner?
When Coach separated us,
you didn't say no.
When I played against Xing Yao,
you were not there with me.
So, do you think it's over?
Mm-hm.
Chi Dayong,
do you remember
how we got together and became partners?
Yes.
Fine.
Let's do it the usual way.
Let the game speak.
Sure.
[light music]
[light music continues]
Chi Dayong.
Do you remember the first time
we played tennis together?
How could I forget?
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
[grunts]
[Dayong pants]
Chi Dayong.
[Tang Jiale] It's 3-0.
We can't bring back the Golden Partners
if you don't exert more effort.
You made great progress.
[sighs sharply]
Do you want to give up?
I really don't
want to lose this game.
But you won, Jiale.
If I beat you someday,
our partnership will end.
Okay. That's the deal.
[chuckles]
Okay.
[Tang Jiale] According to our deal
at that time,
the day I beat you
will be the day our partnership ends.
I admit defeat...
and totally accept the result.
But I want to make one more deal.
Let's bring back the Golden Partners
when I beat you.
[sighs]
What if I say no?
[gasps]
Is that so?
Then...
-[Tang Jiale grunts]
-[Dayong gasps]
Then what?
Then you'll just forget about it?
[Tang Jiale] Let me tell you.
Sometimes, I'm nice,
but sometimes,
I will argue over petty things.
[somber music]
You think I'm not as good as Xinglong
because I can't do his Earthquake Smash?
I can't do Zhuo Zhi's three turns
or Lu Xia's drives.
But does that mean I'm not qualified
to play with them or play tennis?
The same goes for you.
You also have irreplaceable abilities.
No person is exactly the same as another.
Just make the most use of your strength.
You can't be perfect in every way, right?
You're right.
I have been so wrong.
I'm not the same Tang Jiale
as the one who made that deal before.
You just said
you wanted to win this game
no matter what.
So did I.
I also wanted to win
so we could end that deal.
[gasps]
We are not who we used to be.
So at this moment,
I want to make a new deal with you.
Let's bring back the Golden Partners.
[tranquil music]
There is no deadline.
Our partnership will never end.
-We are the Golden Partners 2.0.
-Mm-hm.
Golden Partners 2.0.
[laughs]
We will work hard together.
[chuckles]
That's the deal.
[Zhuo Zhi] Finish all of this.
That should do.
It's not as easy as you say.
It's just a math test. It's easy.
It's easy for you.
[Yu] I have known it since we were young.
We're not the same.
You can do difficult things easily.
But I might not be able to do them
as well as you can
no matter how hard I try.
Just like tennis.
We tried so hard, but we still lost.
Do you think we're stupid?
I admire you.
Everyone says you're a genius,
but don't think
you can do everything well.
When we were little,
bigger kids bullied you for protecting me.
[Yu] And you didn't care.
[young Zhuo Zhi] Does it hurt?
[young Yu] Not at all.
Don't try to be brave.
Why did you run to me?
Then why do you say sorry for me
every time?
[young Zhuo Zhi]
Because I'm your big brother.
I must protect you.
Will you do the same thing now?
If someone bullies you,
I will still protect you.
You always have excuses. I don't like it.
[Shiting] Zilong.
It's cold.
You should go back.
[breathes heavily]
I spend so much time in the ward
every day.
Stay with me for a while.
Our team is in good shape.
They have exceeded
their training volume...
and are getting ready
for their next matches.
Thank you, Zilong.
You work so hard every day
while I can only stay here.
[scoffs]
I guess I am an irresponsible captain.
No.
How do you feel?
[somber music]
I'm fine.
What did the doctor say?
He said I'm fine.
THREE YEARS AGO
-[rackets thwacking]
-[men grunting]
[men grunting]
[Hai Guang coach] Shiting.
Coach.
You are both newcomers.
Please help each other.
And get along with your team.
Hello. I'm Bai Shiting.
Hi, I'm Tian Zilong.
[chuckles]
-[man 1] One.
-[grunts]
[man 1] Two.
One.
[grunting]
Two.
-[man 1] One.
-[men grunting]
-Two.
-[grunting continues]
[man 1] One.
Two.
One.
-Two.
-Have you decided?
[sighs]
Yes, I have.
I have decided to win
the national tournament with you.
Good.
Let's win three
consecutive championships...
starting this year.
Mm-hm.
[upbeat music]
[men grunting]
[ominous music]
[gasps]
[Zilong and man 2] Captain!
[men gasping]
-[man 2] Captain!
-[Zilong] Captain!
-[rackets clanks]
-[man 3] Captain!
[players] Captain!
-[Zilong] Ambulance!
-Captain, what's wrong?
-Captain!
[Zilong] Ambulance! Call an ambulance!
[doctor] You should know
your illness well.
You've been sick for so long.
[doctor sighs]
Anyway,
you can't play tennis anymore.
[somber music]
-Thank you.
-[doctor] Mm-hm.
[retreating footsteps]
-I...
-[Zilong] We promised each other.
Just leave the team to me.
We will remain unbeaten
and await your return.
Okay.
What is it?
Do I not look well?
[breathes heavily]
Everyone is ready.
They're waiting for the captain's return
to win our third championship.
[sighs]
[thwacking]
[Xiangqian] Receive this.
[groans, suck teeth]
Dad, what are you doing?
I think you might be bored
with playing alone.
-Let's have a game, okay?
-No, thanks.
I want to practice alone before the match.
It's boring to play alone.
If you have any doubts,
your mental advisor is here.
I can figure things out alone.
Son, remember,
Daddy is always with you.
[playful music]
-Dad.
-Mm-hm?
-Just go to sleep.
-Why?
You're disturbing me.
Here you go.
I'll make midnight snacks for you.
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE PROVINCIAL
QUALIFYING FINALS
I checked our latest data.
Based on my predicted lineups
and the data comparison
between us and Hai Guang,
I came up with a new training method.
You can give it a try.
Who will try it first?
[Tang Jiale clears throat]
[Qiao Chen clears throat]
Don't be afraid.
I can guarantee that it will help you
make great progress.
[soft chuckle]
Good.
I can see you're all brave and active.
So...
Lu Xia.
You will have the two-player,
high-speed attack training
with Chi Dayong and Xinglong.
Lu Xia will play
against Xinglong and Chi Dayong.
Xinglong will attack
with Earthquake Smashes
while Dayong will defend Xinglong.
[sighs]
That sounds horrible.
I especially made this training plan
for dealing with Tian Zilong
from Hai Guang.
[Yan Zhiming] He is a formidable opponent
who possesses both strength and speed.
You can imitate his attacks
with this training.
That sounds good.
Mm-hm.
Next, Jiale.
[gasps]
You will play against Baiyang,
Zhuo Zhi, and Qiao Chen.
Huh? Why do I have to deal
with three players?
Because you have to improve your speed.
Ah.
[Tang Jiale and Dayong sighs]
[playful music]
[sighs]
What a suffocating lineup.
[action music]
Hm.
Come. I'm ready.
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
That's fast.
There's no time to think
about how to return it.
You have to hit it once you see it.
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[gasps]
[ball whooshing]
[panting]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
Aren't we being a little too cruel?
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is a special training,
so I will score it.
The team with the lower score
must try the Energy Special Yan-juice
I especially made for this training.
[gasps]
[grandiose music]
Come!
I will show no mercy.
[action music]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[Lu Xia gasps]
[Lu Xia] Just return the ball.
[yells]
[Lu Xia] That's it.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[gasps]
I can be faster.
[Lu Xia] Bring it on.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Well done, Jiale.
You are much faster than before.
It looked like
there were two Jiales on the court.
[chuckles]
Now that you have praised me,
let me grandly introduce
the Tang Jiale Two Pace.
Whoa.
The name is very unoriginal.
[scoffs]
Zhiming, pass me a towel.
Oh.
-Here.
-Huh?
[clears throat]
[sniffs, groans]
All right, the next group
is Baiyang and Qiao Chen's
cooperation training.
[Yan Zhiming] You have already
played doubles together before,
so I don't need to say much.
What's wrong with you?
Let me read the training plan.
Let's do it the usual way.
I make the plan
and you supervise the training.
What do you think?
Well, you better be careful
if you're going to slack off.
I will not let you go
if you don't finish the plan.
Just wait and see.
-Go.
-I'm going. Right.
-You are good at going.
-Sure, I'm better than you.
-Can't you go faster?
[Qiao Chen] Do you have
horns on your head? My head hurts.
[Baiyang] You have horns
on your head, right?
Zhuo Zhi.
I also made a training plan for you.
Huh?
This is what you made for me?
Right.
I adjusted this pitching machine
to Yuan Chi's speed.
You can give it a try now.
[chuckles]
I think my speed is fine.
It's up to you.
I believe you can have
the same speed as Yuan Chi after this.
That sounds interesting.
I will try that next time.
Next time? When?
Just next time.
[chuckles]
[comical music]
[school bell chimes]
[gasps]
Sorry, Lu Xia.
Oh. He has practice
with the tennis club today.
[sighs]
Do you remember
what I just said?
[all] Yes!
Dismissed.
[scoffs]
[Yaren] Look, this is what
I said last night.
Vice-Captain Tian only brings me bad luck.
-[Zilong] The new style is good.
-He makes us stay late every time.
And his face is horrible.
-Darn it.
-[Yaren] Let's try it later.
-Okay?
-[Zilong] Okay.
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[pants]
[Yan Zhiming] Don't be limited
by your own achievements.
Those achievements are in the past.
You have to think
about how to make a breakthrough
with your experiences.
You will finally have
your own tennis theory.
[panting]
That's the third racket you broke
during practice. Well done.
You are really focused.
The strings need to be replaced.
Three rackets need to be fixed.
This will take a long time.
There is a sports store
ten kilometers away.
Get them all fixed.
You can return to school in two hours
if you run.
-I sent you the address.
-[cell phone chimes]
Do I have to run there?
Hmm...
It is a little difficult.
Wait a second.
Let me bring you
some of my new Yan-juice...
[gasping]
[quirky music]
I'm going.
Mm-hm.
[panting]
Wait, Lu Xia.
You're making him run?
It's okay. I'm fine.
[breathing heavily]
Wear these.
Don't push yourself.
Uh-huh.
[playful music]
Dachi.
Look.
[ominous music]
The last several balls
look different.
Mm-hm.
[sighs]
Chi Dayong is even more awful
than Yan sometimes.
Have you prepared for the match
with Yu Qing next week?
Is that even necessary?
They are just a bunch of clowns,
except for Mu Siyang.
It seems that Mu Siyang
will not play in this match.
[snickers]
Then it will be an instructional match.
[Yuan Chi] We will show them
what tennis is.
Hey.
Hey. You're the little one, right?
You just can't avoid your enemy.
I can show you what tennis is right now.
The final round is coming soon.
We will fulfill our promise.
We will keep being unstoppable
and enter the nationals.
[Zilong] Then we will achieve
our third consecutive championship
when you return.
So just take care of yourself.
What is it?
The doctor scheduled my surgery.
It's on the day of the match.
Don't worry.
We will end the match before your surgery.
And we will bring you
the provincial championship trophy.
You must not lose
in the next match.
[tense music]
[Yuan Chi chuckles]
[snickers]
[Sheng] Yuan Chi, the captain messaged us
to go meet them.
I can beat him in 15 minutes.
[Yaren] Captain.
Why are you hiding here?
Captain, we brought you a cake.
The view here is nice.
And we won't disturb the other patients.
The match is coming soon.
How are your preparations?
Very good.
[Jie] Don't worry.
We have done practical training
for the national tournament.
Mm-hm.
Where are Yuan Chi and Lu Sheng?
They were not with us.
They are on the way.
[Lian] Did he sneak away again
-to play with someone?
-I'll go check on them.
As for the surgery,
you can tell them.
[gasps]
Captain, look.
GET WELL SOON
[Wentai] Do you like it?
[laughing]
[light music]
Just serve.
[tense music]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[Yuan Chi] No way.
[gasp]
[Yuan Chi] He has an even stronger serve
than he did in the match with Xing Yao.
You still have a long way to go.
[Yuan Chi] The game is just starting.
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
[gasps]
How was it?
Can you receive it?
Unbelievable.
He is evenly matched with Yuan Chi.
[tense music]
Hey, Lu Xia.
Take the weights off your legs, okay?
You take yours off first.
[racket clatters]
The vice-captain
will nag me if I take these off.
Come.
[suspenseful music]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
Yuan Chi is being forced
to be on the defensive.
[ominous music]
[Sheng] This is not good.
Yuan Chi is going...
[thumps]
Yuan Chi!
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[Lu Xia groans]
If you always stick to the rules
when playing tennis,
you will overlook some details.
I'm sorry.
[foreboding music]
Even I don't know
where this one will land.
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[Lu Xia groans]
[breathing heavily]
Don't worry. I have more
where that came from.
You can aim for my face if you're so good.
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[groaning]
I never expected this kid
to last this long.
You are not qualified.
-[thwacking]
-[grunting]
[pants]
[groaning]
Yuan Chi, that was not necessary.
[panting]
[snickers]
[Sheng] Yuan Chi becomes even faster
every time he's like this.
[Lu Xia] Hold on.
I must focus my attention
and not think about my knee.
[ball whooshing]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[gasps]
Can Lu Xia do the same thing
as Yuan Chi
after his eyes turn red?
[in English]
You still have a lot to work on.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I can't understand you.
You're just making a fool out of yourself.
[Yuan Chi] What's going on?
He suddenly got unbelievably focused.
[bones crack]
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
[groans]
[Yuan Chi] He's so fast.
[pants]
[in English]
Nobody beats me in tennis.
[upbeat music]
A left-hander?
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
-[ball thumps]
-[gasps]
-[thwack]
-[grunts]
[gasps]
[Yuan Chi] How could that be?
What happened?
-[thwack]
-[grunts]
[Yuan Chi gasps]
[tense music]
[Yuan Chi] Unbelievable.
He has such potential.
[pants]
[Zilong] Yuan Chi.
Hey!
[chiming]
[telephone ringing]
HOMESTAY
Hello.
[man 4] Hello, Mr. Lu.
You never know what will come first,
tomorrow or an accident.
But my phone call comes first.
Are you interested in wealth management?
Based on different
wealth management styles,
we have different ways
to keep your money safe.
Where do you put your money,
in a bank or a financial institution?
In the shoebox.
[telephone ringing]
[man 4] Sir, do you want more time
to think about it?
I'm thinking about calling the police.
[telephone ringing]
You aren't quitting, are you?
Are you interested in Italian Harvest?
[Coach Qi] Lu Xiangqian,
your son has been in an accident.
[foreboding music]
[sighs]
[gasps]
-How do you feel?
-[gasps]
I...
How did I get here?
The students from Hai Guang took you here.
-Where are they?
-They left.
I know you want to win against them badly.
But if you don't alternate
training and resting,
you will be in a bad state.
I will find a way. I will win.
Every success requires patience.
I have told you before.
You can ask a veteran for help
if you have any problems in the court.
It will be better than practicing alone.
I want to play my own tennis.
Other people's experiences can't help me.
[closing theme music]
♪ The childlike face
Is changing little by little ♪
♪ Destiny gives me callused hands ♪
♪ On the playground,
We hang on and practice once more ♪
♪ We vow with a high five on the court ♪
♪ A bunch of youth
Is dashing forward with hope ♪
♪ The air is filled with cheers ♪
♪ I want to have
An impressive performance ♪
♪ An impressive performance ♪
♪ I will never be tired
Of standing by your side ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Hey, hey, yeah ♪
Subtitle translation by Vanessa Ding