[theme music]
♪ The game of youth starts with passion ♪
♪ Make the first move and never give up ♪
♪ Let the blood inside you flow ♪
♪ Let the world see that I am invincible ♪
♪ Young face, heaving chest ♪
♪ As always
I'll chase my dreams like I used to ♪
♪ Swallow my tears
And make myself stronger ♪
♪ Sweat illuminating in the hot sun ♪
♪ Dear youth ♪
♪ Keep running, your dreams lie ahead ♪
♪ Don't be afraid, work hard and grow up ♪
♪ We are in the best years of youth ♪
♪ We should seize the day ♪
♪ Live the way ♪
♪ You want to live the most ♪
The Prince of Tennis
~ Match! Tennis Juniors! ~
LAGOOON
HEAVY RECOMMENDATION
Wash your hands.
They are dirty.
[soft chuckle]
Okay.
Yu Qing will play
against Xing Yao tomorrow.
Will you play?
[soft chuckle]
So you're going to cheer for me, right?
Will you do your best if I cheer for you?
Maybe.
As long as I don't lose.
-Do you know who your opponent is?
-Not exactly.
But it's probably going to be Song Ci.
Song Ci?
He looks sleepy all the time.
But when he's on court
he's completely different.
I know. You lost to him.
Not again.
In this case,
do your best.
But maybe you can't win.
I think I won't have many
more opportunities
to play tennis with you all
in the future.
So, I will strive for it
with the strength that I have.
This should be fun, right?
Right.
I really should
try my best for once.
I'll go wash my hands.
GOLD MEDAL ROAST GOOSE
FRESH, TENDER, TASTY
♪ Somewhere, ♪
♪ somewhere far away, ♪
♪ we can find the light that never ♪
♪ dies out in our hearts ♪
[rock music]
♪ Forget those hurts ♪
♪ Forget how long the journey is ♪
♪ Forget fear, confusion and arrogance ♪
♪ Forget the past that you can't forget ♪
♪ Dream is to brave the wind
And the waves ♪
♪ Dream is a harbor leads to tomorrow ♪
♪ Sweat is the soft light
Reflected by victory ♪
♪ Growth is the weight of love
And youth ♪
♪ This is life
Perfect is only a daydream ♪
♪ The young face smells at the wounds ♪
♪ Youth is crazy.
Do your best to pursue ♪
♪ Our perseverance ♪
♪ Light up the place we want to go ♪
♪ We'll finally get there ♪
♪ Wait for the dreams to come true ♪
♪ The parabola draws the setting sun ♪
♪ Somewhere far away in the future ♪
♪ Is our only faith ♪
♪ Light up the light that
Never dies out in your heart ♪
[rock music]
NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL MEN'S TENNIS LEAGUE
THE PROVINCE QUALIFYING ROUND SEMIFINAL
[upbeat music]
YU QING, BOUND TO WIN
I waited for an hour.
[sighs]
We went to sign up.
Put it on.
No. It's ugly.
Why would you say that?
This is the color of victory.
[sighs]
You can't lose to Xing Yao on momentum.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[tense music]
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[crowd cheering continues]
Dachi hasn't come yet.
Did he come across a pregnant woman
and helped her to the hospital?
You often use this excuse, right?
Yes. Only you can come up
with such a lame excuse.
[comical music]
Hello, Dachi.
What? Help a pregnant woman
to the hospital?
[Lu Xia] Look.
Many people use
this lame excuse.
-[sighs]
-No.
Dachi is not like you.
How?
Dachi only tells the truth.
[Qiao Chen] We still have time.
Coach, I'll go get him.
-Qiao Chen.
-Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
[Coach Qi sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[PA on speaker] The match
between Yu Qing and Xing Yao
-will begin.
-[crowd cheering] Xing Yao will win.
-Let's start the match of second doubles.
-Xing Yao will win.
[cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing!
-Lu Xia, go!
-Come on, Yu Qing!
[crowd cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing!
[crowd cheering continues]
[Zhiyuan] I never heard of you.
Relax, we will show no mercy.
[crowd cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing!
Xing Yao will win!
Baiyang, remember what I said?
It's the opponent's serve.
Feng Zhiyuan can do a gale serve.
-So--
-Zhiming.
It's noisy. I can't hear you.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[crowd cheering continues]
It's okay.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[crowd cheering continues]
[tense music]
[whooshes]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[Baiyang] That was fast
GALE SERVE
[Yan Zhiming] Gale serve.
The ball speed is over 200km per hour.
Reaction time for the opponent
-is less than half a second.
-Point for Xing Yao, 15-0.
[cheering]
Come on, Xing Yao.
Feng Zhiyuan's prided trick gale serve.
I assume...
that only you can receive it.
[rock music]
He is taunting us with his serve.
They went too far.
Yan has been using his
super-high-speed service to train Baiyang.
Unexpectedly, he still
has no clue in the match.
Average speed
is over 240km per hour.
[Yan Zhiming] That's not the same level
as super-speed serve.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Point for Xing Yao.
Xing Yao will win!
[ominous music]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[umpire 1] Point for Xing Yao.
[cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[crowd cheering]
You can do nothing about their service.
Nothing?
First thing we can do is calm them down.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[crowd cheering continues]
Double baseline.
Baiyang is going to use...
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[Yan Zhiming] Chance of hitting midline
is 96%.
Easy ball.
[Yan Zhiming] Therefore the chance
for Baiyang to return a snake-ball is 78%
-[whooshes]
-[thwacks]
[gasps]
-[umpire 1] Point for Yu Qing, 15-0.
-[cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing! Yu Qing will win!
[Zhiyuan] What a terrible shot.
Who'd believe?
It's okay, I'll take it.
Okay.
[crowd cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing! Yu Qing will win!
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
-[whooshes]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
How's that possible?
[tense music]
[thwacking]
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL
[Jingwu] Hu Liangliang has
become a lot more focused
since that incident.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
Hey.
Your strategy is useless.
From now on, I'll play as I want.
Suit yourself if you don't believe me.
[scoffs]
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[tense music]
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
[Yan Zhiming] Compared to Feng Zhiyuan,
Hu Liangliang with a stronger strike back
is harder to deal with.
[grunts]
[all] What's it?
Baiyang is nuts.
He can't win doubles himself.
HU LIANGLIANG, FENG ZHIYUAN VS
ZHANG BAIYANG, YANZHIMING. ROUND 4-0.
WRIST POWER: 57 KG
[Yan Zhiming] The chance of Hu Liangliang
returning a Super Half Volley
has risen to 94 percent.
[pants]
Match ends, 0-5.
[crowd applauds]
[Zhuo Zhi] Can Baiyang keep going?
[Liangliang] Hey.
Are you Baiyang?
What do you want?
Not bad.
You actually came this far.
But no matter how much will power
and stamina you have,
it will wear out.
[Liangliang] Pity.
You are doomed.
[chuckles]
He can rest over there.
I can take you two.
[scoffs]
How's it going?
Done with data gathering?
Almost.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao!
You've done a good job, Baiyang.
Thank you for trusting me.
[Lu Xia] Yan hasn't shown his best yet.
[cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing! Yu Qing will win!
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Chance of a straight ball is 100%.
[action music]
-What?
-[Yan Zhiming] Pity.
Possibility of hitting back is...
...zero.
WRIST POWER: 57KG
[gasps]
We got fooled!
[Zhiyuan] Zhang Baiyang is
gathering data for Yan Zhiming.
Let's fight back, Yan.
[action music]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
HU LIANGLIANG, FENG ZHIYUAN VS
ZHANG BAIYANG, YAN ZHIMING. ROUND 5 TO 4.
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
AGILITY: 3.5
STAMINA, SPEED, TACTIC,
MENTAL, ATTACK, DEFENCE
They are giving it their all.
Yes.
But it is still early to assume victory.
Let's take this one.
Score 40-30.
Of course our win rate...
To wave out the water in your towel...
[grunts]
[Yan Zhiming] You shouldn't only use
your wrist,
you need to connect your shoulder and arm,
focus and wave altogether.
WRIST POWER: 45.5%
[Yan Zhiming] Chance of reaching sideline
is 100%.
To the single area.
Not good.
That means it's easier to catch.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Feng Zhiyuan will cover for Hu Liangliang.
Then...
If the ball goes there...
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[pants, gasps]
[thuds]
[umpire 1] Point for Yu Qing.
[exhales sharply]
[Yan Zhiming] We have objections.
My data shows that
my ball
should surpass the baseline by 0.31 cm.
It's a pity,
but it is out.
Please confirm.
[sighs]
We decided to have a rematch.
[applauding]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
Yan is honest as always.
Yan is committed to data.
But he still showed us a spectacular game.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[gasps]
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[exhales sharply]
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao will win!
[action music]
-[thuds]
-[Baiyang grunts]
[groans]
Xing Yao High School won.
[crowd applauding]
Good game.
[shouts]
-[Liangliang] Great.
-[crowd] Good game.
[panting]
[light music]
[puffing, grunting]
[uplifting music]
They have already
won the match.
Captain.
What?
Dachi might not come.
He's helping a pregnant lady.
[Qiao Chen] He can't find
any contact info of her family.
So the hospital insisted that he stays.
[tense music]
[distant groaning]
[panting]
Are you okay?
Come.
[both grunting]
Slowly.
No.
-[panting]
-[whimpering]
[woman 1 whimpering]
[Qiao Chen] He sprained his wrist
when helping her.
So he can't play today.
Then you and Jiale should go.
Jiale,
-Yes?
-Dachi is not coming.
You and Qiao Chen will
play this game.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I will do my best to cooperate.
Mm.
Okay, you guys get ready.
[He Xinglong] Go for it.
Trust me.
It'll be okay.
[sighs]
-[Zhuo Zhi] Go for it.
-Qiao Chen.
Your arm guard...
Ah.
Chi told me to
wear this arm guard while
playing doubles with you.
[somber music]
[all] Come on, Yu Qing!
[all] Come on!
Come on, Xing Yao!
Temporary group?
Where is your golden partners?
[scoffs]
None of your business.
Yue Yang is here.
It will be easier to beat you.
Loser, Yu Qing.
[scoffs]
Qiao Chen.
We are going to win
whatever it takes.
Yes.
-Go for it.
[action music]
[umpire 1] Xing Yao High School
versus Yu Qing High School.
Doubles game starts. Yu Qing serves.
[Jingwu] The golden partners is nothing.
What can a temporary group do?
-[whooshes]
-[thwacks]
Let me.
[thwacks]
What's happening?
He can jump higher than Jiale?
[both grunting]
Damn.
Leave it to me.
The direction of wrist
determines all. Here.
[Shixing] So naive.
No way he can predict my ball.
Not good.
The ball is behind Jiale.
[grunts]
[crowd applauds]
[umpire 1] Point for Xing Yao.
-15-0.
-It can't be.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao!
What happened?
It's different from what they said.
That frightens me.
I never thought
that you could play doubles, Qiao Chen.
You just figured it out?
[soft chuckle]
[sighs]
It's a pity that we didn't get
that ball.
It's okay, we will try harder.
Mm.
They thought this
hasty decision can compete
with Xing Yao's doubles?
[scoffs]
So naive.
It shouldn't be.
[Tang Jiale] What is Qiao Chen doing?
You better take it seriously.
[scoffs]
Why are you wearing an arm guard
and flapping around like him?
It shouldn't be.
[Tang Jiale] Focus.
[tense music]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[thwacks]
[grunts]
Yue Yang
plays acrobatics tennis
better than Jiale does.
I told you not to say things like that.
Sorry.
That's not how Jiale usually plays.
Yan told me
a good doubles player
can play two to three times
stronger than usual.
[thwacks]
[Qiao Chen] Another blind zone.
I should run towards the net.
[soft chuckle]
[pants]
[whooshes]
[gasps]
[Qiao Chen] High ball.
[umpire 2] 1-0, Xing Yao is leads.
[crowd applauds]
[Coach Qi] Jiale and Qiao Chen's status
is not good.
Qiao Chen is playing weird today.
He's not like his usual self.
Indeed.
The opponent can see through
their fake move right away.
Xing Yao
has their golden partners for this match.
And their teamwork is all over the place.
They don't trust each other completely.
Instead of doubles,
they are playing two singles.
[crowd cheering]
Xing Yao!
[Qiao Chen] This will turn out to be bad
for us.
We need to find a way
to lock their move.
[tense music]
Here.
-[thwacks]
-[zooms]
Unbelievable.
They can catch
the core vertical jump shot.
Careful, Jiale.
-[gasps]
-[zooms]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Great! Good for you, Qiao Chen.
That vertical jump is a decoy.
As I expected. I‘d play it like that too.
Qiao Chen must have foreseen this.
-[whooshes]
-[thwacks]
[tense music]
You Shixing is a genius in Xing Yao.
Hitting back a ball like this
would be easy for him.
[Qiao Chen] He returned
my vertical smash.
The situation
seems bad for us.
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
[umpire 1] Yue Yang and You Shixing won.
3-0.
Just wait for your loss.
[whooshes]
[thumps]
[Tang Jiale] Why are you not here, Dachi?
CALLING TANG JIALE
[somber music]
CALL ENDED
Jiale should be okay
even if
I'm not there.
[sighs]
[crowd cheering] Xing Yao!
-[zooms]
-[thwacks]
[both grunting]
[umpire 1] Xing Yao won. 4-0.
[both panting]
[tense music]
[Tang Jiale] Will it end like this?
[Qiao Chen] Dachi handed such
an important position to me.
It shouldn't be like this.
Let's try this.
[gasps]
Why is Qiao Chen
always looking at his hands?
I saw it too.
Is there any winning secret?
There is no winning secret.
Even if there is,
It's too late to learn it now.
[Qiao Chen] This game
is depending on the secret.
[tense music]
[thwacks, whooshes]
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
[whooshing]
[thwacks]
[umpire 1] Tang Jiale, Qiao Chen
from Yu Qing, 15-0.
[crowd applauds]
[action music]
Perfect, Jiale.
We won one point back.
Let's give it our best.
Okay.
[distant thwacking]
-[zooms]
-[thwacks]
[grunts]
[umpire 1] Yu Qing won, 1-4.
Great, Jiale.
Perfect.
Huh?
[Tang Jiale] It's darker.
Were you poisoned, Qiao Chen?
No.
JIALE HITS A HIGH BALL AT RIGHT BASELINE,
THEN DEFENSE AS PARALLEL FORMATION.
Dachi, are you done yet?
You are running out of space.
There is one most important thing.
Is this Kongfu scripts?
Write to win?
Don't move.
This is for you.
For me?
For you to play doubles.
TO DEAL WITH A FAST SERVICE,
TWO PEOPLE SHOULD STAND VERTICALLY
TO GIVE OPPONENT PRESSURE...
AUSTRALIA
[sighs]
Jiale can only depend on you now.
Relax, don't underestimate Jiale.
I have never underestimated Jiale.
Time is running out. I'll get going then.
Wait.
[light music]
I put on this every time
I go to match with Jiale.
Put it on.
Take care of Jiale.
[uplifting music]
Remember,
this is not only for doubles.
This is for everyone.
Take care of Yu Qing.
Don't worry, vice captain.
Leave it to me.
[comical music]
[whispering]
What are you doing, Qiao Chen?
Many people are watching.
This is embarrassing.
Dachi said,
you will understand after you see this.
AUSTRALIA
What is this?
Seems like an English word.
Let me see.
Jiale, may I put down my arm?
[exhales sharply]
Qiao Chen.
It's time to try it.
It?
That's it.
What?
Come.
[whispering]
Understood.
[uplifting music]
Now we do the Australian formation.
Qiao Chen will be alright, right?
[Yan Zhiming] Time is running out.
They need time
to accommodate this formation.
[exhales sharply]
Australian formation.
[Jingwu] Qiao Chen will take
Chi Dayong's position.
Forget about the formation, just do it.
Do not rush, Yue Yang.
-[thwacking]
-[both grunting]
Left.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[umpire 1] Tang Jiale, Qiao Chen
from Yu Qing, 30-30.
It's Australian formation.
Qiao Chen is good.
Qiao Chen and Jiale
are both so handsome.
Not bad, Qiao Chen.
[sighs]
Sorry, Shixing.
I'm too focused on Tang Jiale's movement.
That has to be a coincidence.
This formation takes a lot of practice.
The formation is to open up the sides
to cover for both sides at the same time.
It needs a lot of cooperation.
This is a temporary team, no pressure.
Therefore,
hit the ball behind Qiao Chen,
he is near the baseline.
[tense music]
[thwacks, whooshes]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[Qiao Chen] Jiale.
Dachi told me before coming here
that if you don't give up,
chances are everywhere.
Believe in ourselves.
Jiale, don't give up.
[Dayong] Chances are everywhere.
I will have your back.
[soft chuckle]
[action music]
-[thwacks]
-[both grunting]
Qiao Chen, leave the back area to me.
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
[thwacks]
[crowd applauding]
[all] Great.
Their teamwork is good.
[Huang Jing] We did it.
[both] Great.
-Great.
-How's that, Jiale?
Great.
That is you, go for it.
They are much better than expected.
Their cooperation is getting better.
[panting]
[dramatic music]
Thank you for today.
It's okay.
Sorry for keeping you so long.
I'm so sorry.
Oh. It's alright.
I stay until your husband comes.
I heard you and your friend.
[woman 1]
Does someone need you very badly?
[sighs]
Sometimes you just need to show up
even if you do nothing.
To someone,
it could mean a lot.
Really?
Of course.
Sometimes it's not that
you cannot hold any longer.
You are just hoping
for someone to show up.
Then you will feel safe.
[dramatic music]
[soft chuckle]
[sighs]
[groaning]
[crowd cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing!
-Go! Go!
[dramatic music]
[crowd cheering]
Come on, Yu Qing!
That's impossible.
Tang Jiale.
He's really good.
Now he is leading the attack.
[both scoff]
Jiale is taking the role of Chi Dayong.
He is leading Qiao Chen
and starting to control the game pace.
He dared to give up
his pride acrobatics tennis,
and let Qiao Chen
jump to his usual height.
Jiale has grown much.
But in their doubles,
there are more than two people.
-[thwacking]
-[grunting]
[dramatic music]
[Tang Jiale] It's harder than I expected
to be in the backcourt.
Dachi used to support me
quietly in the back.
Maybe we should switch back.
Don't worry, Qiao Chen.
As a senior,
I will stay at the baseline
and give you my full support.
[action music]
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
[rasping]
[whooshing]
[gasps]
[all] Great.
Awesome! It's like
I'm watching the golden partners.
Here comes the strike back.
[crowd cheering]
Yu Qing will win!
[both panting]
[umpire 1] Point for Yu Qing, 15-40.
[Dayong] Well done, Jiale.
[Coach Qi] Even Jiale who sticks
with his own way at the front
has grown
in this match.
They have won three games in a row.
[scoffs]
Something must be wrong.
[low grunt]
[both sigh]
When Jiale hits a powerful cross-shot,
and goes back to hit the ball
across the net gently...
[scoffs]
How can you
be distracted in a game?
It looks so.
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
[umpire 1] 4-4. Tie.
[Qiao Chen] It's the same
as Dachi told me.
[crowd cheering]
Yu Qing will win!`
This is our chance!
[all] Yu Qing will win!
[uplifting music]
-[Qiao Chen] Great.
-[umpire 1] Yu Qing scored.
[both] Great.
Dachi.
[uplifting music]
There are more than two people.
It's a doubles of three people.
[panting]
[Yang] What's going on?
-[thwacking]
-[all grunting]
Yue Yang is worn out.
He is an aggressive player.
That's true.
But he has to consider the time
when it's hard to win easily.
[Yang] No. We may lose.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
Yu Qing leads, 5-4.
I thought you were good.
You are no better than me
when I'm out of power.
[Yang] They are just a temporary team.
How is their teamwork so good?
Great. We score again.
Yue Yang is getting tired.
They can't even jump.
Yue Yang's strength goes down.
Jiale's energy finally comes in use.
[whooshes]
[Shixing] I have to turn the tie
with this one.
Is Qiao Chen thinking he can
suppress You Shixing's all actions
on his own?
[Shixing] Suppress me?
[grunts]
The boy wearing glasses is fighting back.
Jiale, careful!
[tense music]
[closing theme music]
♪ The childlike face
Is changing little by little ♪
♪ Destiny gives me callused hands ♪
♪ On the playground,
We hang on and practice once more ♪
♪ We vow with a high five on the court ♪
♪ A bunch of youth
Is dashing forward with hope ♪
♪ The air is filled with cheers ♪
♪ I want to have
An impressive performance ♪
♪ An impressive performance ♪
♪ I will never be tired
Of standing by your side ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Hey, hey, yeah ♪
Subtitle translation by Vanessa Ding