[theme music]
♪ The game of youth starts with passion ♪
♪ Make the first move and never give up ♪
♪ Let the blood inside you flow ♪
♪ Let the world see that I am invincible ♪
♪ Young face, heaving chest ♪
♪ As always
I'll chase my dreams like I used to ♪
♪ Swallow my tears
And make myself stronger ♪
♪ Sweat illuminating in the hot sun ♪
♪ Dear youth ♪
♪ Keep running, your dreams lie ahead ♪
♪ Don't be afraid, work hard and grow up ♪
♪ We are in the best years of youth ♪
♪ We should seize the day ♪
♪ Live the way ♪
♪ You want to live the most ♪
The Prince of Tennis
~ Match! Tennis Juniors! ~
See you. We'll go to watch your game.
-Mm-hm.
-[chuckling]
-Bye.
[Coach Muyun mutters]
Let's go.
-Did you have fun?
-Yes.
Eh? Let me see your racket.
Hey, sit.
Hmm.
Oh.
The strings hold up well.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
This grip tape won't do.
-[gasps]
-Oh.
What are you worrying about?
You don't trust me?
[chuckling]
Hey.
Let me tell you a little secret.
[Coach Muyun] I fell in love with a girl
when I was your age.
In order to court her,
I wrote romantic poems every day.
Did you get her then?
[groans]
I was a terrible poet.
The girl ran away.
But I've loved writing poetry
ever since then.
Then what?
Hard work always pays off.
Finally, I had a poem
published in the newspaper.
[chuckles]
I don't think that's a great success.
Hey.
If you only think about how to succeed
whenever you do anything,
it won't do you any good.
You'd better think about
the significance of what you're doing
right now.
[light music]
I want to improve myself.
Why?
Because I want
to beat everyone in front of me.
Aren't you tired?
No.
[soft chuckle]
Boy, you are still young.
And you do love playing tennis.
I don't only love playing tennis.
I love winning even more.
Even though we all play to win,
we should try to savor the joy
that every tennis game gives us.
[Coach Muyun]
Playing tennis is like traveling.
The journey is more important
than the destination.
Uh, look at my boys.
They are happy
as long as they can play tennis.
Don't you ever have such feelings?
[snickers]
Don't worry. You have plenty of time.
Take it easy.
But remember.
Don't ignore the happiness
on your journey.
[Coach Muyun] Hm?
[chuckles]
It's done.
[Coach Muyun groans]
Here.
I hope you play well in your game.
Bye.
[sighs]
What is your last poem about?
"Poem"? Oh...
[Coach Muyun] Let me read it for you.
"Glory is as superficial as a dream.
Awards are merely some notes
written in your biography.
One's career can be a place
as dangerous as the deep sea.
What's the point in getting up early
in a freezing winter
to practice just to beat others?"
[Coach Muyun laughs]
XING YAO
18 DAYS BEFORE YU QING VS XING YAO
[upbeat music]
So this is Xing Yao.
[camera shutter clicks]
Hello, I am the coach
of the Xing Yao tennis club.
My last name is Fu.
I am a reporter from Tennis Monthly.
-You can call me Sha.
-Okay.
Your team seems to be pretty relaxed.
That's true.
We've almost finished
the school qualifying.
You can interview the qualified players
and take photos of them.
I've arranged everything for you.
Hmm.
Thanks.
FENG ZHIYUAN
Feng Zhiyuan.
[tense music]
[Sha] Feng Zhiyuan
is famous for his ultra-fast,
mighty serve.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[Sha] Yue Yang.
[gasps]
[Sha] Yue Yang has good flexibility
and a quick response.
He's good at freestyle shots.
YUE YANG
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL PLAYER
HUA CHONGHONG
Hua Chonghong.
[Sha] Hua Chonghong
has superhuman strength and a pure heart.
He is an all-rounder
with both skill and strength.
HUA CHONGHONG
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL PLAYER
[Sha] You Shixing.
You Shixing is a mysterious talent
and a perfect net player.
He is a talented player
with thousands of tricks.
Yue Yang and You Shixing's doubles team
didn't lost a single game last year.
JI JINGWU
Ji Jingwu.
[thwacks]
[Sha] Ji Jingwu
is a talented all-round player.
He is the soul of the tennis club.
[camera shutter clicks]
[snaps]
[camera shutter clicking]
Use these retouched photos
for your report.
[gasps]
[comical music]
[sighs sharply]
[Sha] Hu Liangliang.
Hu Liangliang.
A right-handed
defense and counter-attack player.
His unique skill
is the ultrafast super volley
and the Blockade Australian formation.
[umpire 1] 6-0. Hu Liangliang won.
HU LIANGLIANG
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL PLAYER
Yes!
[Sha] Is he the one who lost to Xu Ziping?
[camera shutter clicks]
The last member of our main force...
goes to our bench player,
Ji Nuo.
[gasps]
Let's take a rest and get ready
for the next training session.
Coach.
[Liangliang gasps]
Don't make a fool of yourself.
[panting]
Captain.
JI NUO
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL PLAYER
[Liangliang] I won.
[ominous music]
But it also was you who lost badly.
The coach won't let a loser
play again.
But he has been training really hard
since his last loss.
So what?
It's no use talking to me.
[Liangliang panting]
What a brutal war.
[Sha gasps]
[groaning]
Huh?
Song Ci?
SONG CI
XING YAO HIGH SCHOOL PLAYER
[sighs]
The genius player?
More like a genius sleepyhead.
[Liangliang] Coach.
[panting]
Coach.
Coach, wait.
What's up?
Coach.
Please let me play.
He's worked hard
ever since he lost the last game.
His training was almost inhuman.
[grunts]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
[somber music]
[both grunting]
[both breathing heavily]
Senior, call it a day, okay?
Mm-mm.
No, go on.
You push yourself too hard.
[panting]
I said, go on.
This kind of training
is far from enough.
If he cannot enter the starting lineup,
-it's unfair.
-[scoffs]
"Unfair"?
Fine.
You can also quit the starting lineup.
-Coach.
[tense music]
[Liangliang] I will never ever
lose a game.
[Zhiyuan] Coach, please.
[sighs]
I also saw how hard he was working.
I hope...
you can give him another chance.
[sighs]
Whatever.
[gasps]
How can you carry scissors
when practicing?
Mind your own business.
[camera shutter clicking]
Captain, we will do better than our best.
[sighs]
Are you frightened by our cruel attitude
to our own teammates?
We take tennis seriously.
If you go to Yu Qing to interview,
please help me tell Siyang
that I will not...
spare him this time.
SPECIAL REPORT
ON XING YAO TENNIS CLUB
JI JINGWU
HUA CHONGHONG
HU LIANGLIANG
[sighs sharply]
[thwacking]
[gasping]
[doctor] If you insist on playing,
you should be mentally prepared for it.
This could be your last match.
[somber music]
[exhales sharply]
This is my new formula.
I haven't tested it thoroughly.
It's good.
Much better than before.
Don't worry.
I'm improving the formula all the time.
[soft chuckle]
How is my new Yan-juice?
I succeeded.
Even the captain said it's good.
I will make adjustments on the basis
of this formula.
Then we can start batch production.
Mm-hm.
Why don't you save some for me?
I forgot.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
[comical music]
[soft chuckle]
It seems successful.
Oh, Dachi.
Jiale.
Uh, why haven't you gone home?
Oh. The teacher assigned us new homework.
I came to buy some notebooks.
How about you?
-Why haven't you gone home then?
-Uh...
Oh, I ran out of pens.
I'm here to buy some.
-Fine.
-Hmm.
Why do you two
look like some middle-aged couple
who met years after their divorce?
It's like you're acting in a movie.
Uh...
[chuckles]
No.
[sighs]
That's insane.
Oh.
I'm going to have some omelet rice.
You said you wanted to have some, right?
Let's go together, okay?
No, thanks.
I have a lot of homework to do today.
I have to buy the notebooks
and go back to do it.
Oh, it's okay.
-Go on then.
-Mm-hm.
Ma'am, could I have an A4 ruled notebook
with horizontal lines?
They're sold out today.
Hey, I have one.
Dachi, you can have it.
Use mine first.
How can I do that? You must need it.
It's fine. I don't need it now.
No, thanks.
I can buy it somewhere else.
Oh. Fine.
-I'm leaving then.
-Okay.
[sighs]
-[chuckles]
-Are you two quarreling?
No.
Then why are things so awkward?
He didn't even want your exercise book.
It's just a book.
I've no idea what he thought.
[chuckles]
YU QING
15 DAYS BEFORE YU QING VS XING YAO
YU QING HIGH
TENNIS QUALIFYING MATCH, GROUP C
TENNIS QUALIFYING MATCH, GROUP D
This is the schedule
of the qualifying match.
Please remember your group.
Lu Xia is in group D.
[Xiuwen] He didn't come
to practice these days.
Can he make it in time to the qualifying?
Mind your own business.
Will he come or not?
[Xiuwen] He can't enter
the elimination match
without playing in the qualifying match.
How can he play against Xing Yao
if he doesn't enter the elimination?
[shushes]
Maybe he is exploring a new theory.
I wonder how it's going.
Isn't it better if he practices with us?
He will easily go
into a dead-end if practices alone.
He is even more stubborn
than me sometimes.
It's the coach's idea
to let Lu Xia practice alone.
She has her own reason for that.
[somber music]
The match against Xing Yao
is crucial for us.
[Siyang] The result determines
whether we can enter the Nationals.
So I hope everyone
can do a good job in school qualifying.
We will show Xing Yao...
our strongest squad.
-Yes.
Lu Xia?
Why are you here?
I was always here.
[light music]
I have to go.
[thwacks]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[doctor] The strain of muscles and joints
will accumulate.
So it is usually late
when you can feel the problem yourself.
[ominous music]
-[thwacks]
-[grunts]
12 DAYS BEFORE YU QING VS XING YAO
-Yan.
-Yes?
Could I have a look
at my training plan today?
Mm-hm.
Oh.
ZHUO ZHI, MU SIYANG
Is this Siyang's training plan?
Mm-hm.
MU SIYANG
Isn't it too much?
[stutters]
Ours are all one-page training plans.
How many pages is his?
Siyang himself made his training plan.
I only documented it
and made minor modifications.
-[Baiyang snickers]
-Oh.
[comical music]
How long are you going to warm up for?
We are in the same group today.
Don't slow me down.
It's all my fault.
It's because of me
that Lu Xia was troubled
and didn't show up.
[Huang Jing] It seems like...
I must take responsibility.
What responsibility?
[sighs]
I will be Lu Xia's replacement
after he leaves.
I will be qualified
as the winner of group C.
You too.
Fight when you should fight.
[scoffs]
[blows air]
You haven't even
seen the group list, right?
We are in the group of death.
[Qiao Chen] In the same group
as the captain.
How do you win?
I just wish
we won't be eliminated.
[quirky music]
[blowing air]
It's okay. Just be like me.
Focus on other games.
Strive for those you can win.
And just give up
when you don't see a chance.
[sighs]
What's on your mind?
I'm thinking about
how to beat the captain.
[scoffs]
[exhales sharply]
[comical music]
[thwacks]
-[thwacks]
-[Lu Xia grunts]
[breathes heavily]
[Lu Xia] I must find my own tennis theory.
-[thwacks]
-[Lu Xia grunts]
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
[grunts]
The meal is ready, son.
You've been practicing one move
for an hour.
Let me play with you.
I'll use only one hand, okay?
Have your meal first.
It's lonely to eat on my own.
Let's play a set.
I can also see if the grip fits properly.
You said your hands are disabled, right?
Bad boy.
How can you blame your old man
when his hands got hurt?
[Xiangqian] My goodness.
[comical music]
-Where are you going?
-To replace my strings.
Let's play first.
You can pick up the balls
if you want to do some exercise.
Hey.
Why is he getting angry so easily?
[sighs]
He cares about me.
Son, I made you a Spanish stew.
BAILING ISLAND
CLOSED FOR THIS WEEKEND
[phone beeps]
[Qiao Chen] Where are you?
Hello, little Lu Xia. It's been so long.
[light music]
It's okay that you didn't
practice with us.
But why don't you have lunch with us?
He's scared that you might take his food.
You...
We came to see you.
We aren't in the same grade,
and you didn't come to practice.
We can hardly meet you.
XINGLONG
I brought some food.
And I brought drinks.
[clears throat]
Let's find a place to sit down
to have some food and drinks.
Come on.
[Tang Jiale chuckles]
Yes, let's go.
-Come.
-Go.
[Dayong] Lu Xia, when will you return?
When I get myself ready for the game.
How's it going?
Um, what were you practicing on your own?
[Tang Jiale] You are always in good form.
You never lose.
I keep losing.
It's normal to lose
to a legendary player like your father.
Do you think everyone
has no ambition like you? Loser.
Even the most impressive people
lose sometimes.
Even Federer loses sometimes.
Right.
I think it's more important
to play a match first.
I need to be more prepared for the game.
I can't be like this.
Not all games can wait
until you have reached your best form.
[light music]
Little Lu Xia, anyway,
we all hope you can return
and play against Xing Yao with us.
Hmm.
[Zhou Zhi] Cheers.
[Xiangqian] Come on.
Sit.
[groans]
What?
See these fishing rods here,
what else can we do?
Are there any fish?
Yes, I just put some in.
[Xiangqian]
But I don't know where they are swimming.
-I was going to cook some.
-Let's order a takeout.
Sit, sit, sit.
You know, many discoveries are made
-when the giants are fishing.
-[sighing]
You have to think like a fish
if you want to catch it.
And you have to think
like a master if you want to be one.
[light music]
If your obsession with tennis
is only because you want
to beat different opponents,
but you don't truly understand
who your opponents are
and never treat them as real human beings,
I think you should give up.
I think I know my opponent well.
I don't think so.
I'm not saying you don't know me well.
I mean, there are two on the court.
Your real opponent is not me,
but is the other one.
You've been back for a long time.
I believe you've already realized
why you choose to play tennis.
Your opponents on the court
come and go all the time.
But who will always stand in your court?
That one is your most important opponent.
It's not me.
I will get old.
[Siyang] Lu Xia.
Why do you play tennis?
A man.
What will you do after beating him?
What will you gain after that?
[Coach Muyun]
Playing tennis is like traveling.
The journey is more important
than the destination.
Whoever you set as your target,
and no matter
whose skills you want to learn,
you've only just begun to learn tennis.
As long as you go on playing,
you'll meet different types of players.
[Siyang] Maybe...
you'll meet someone stronger
than your target
even before beating that person.
The significance of what you're doing
right now.
But who
will always stand in your court?
That one is your most important opponent.
Is it myself?
[chuckles]
I'm ordering a takeout.
What about the fish?
Let the fish take the bait.
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
[school bell tolling]
7 DAYS BEFORE YU QING VS XING YAO
I was talking
about the Enlightenment.
[teacher] Now, let me tell you
about some thinkers
during this period,
as well as the significance
and differences in their ideas.
-Now...
-[Xiangqian] But who
will always stand in your court?
That one is your most important opponent.
[teacher] ...anti-despotism.
The one is who spinning the pen.
[tense music]
Right. You.
Please tell us
the different characteristics
of each phase in the Enlightenment.
I found you staring out that window
very often.
I think we'd better seal that window
as soon as possible
to help you study better.
[teacher] Qi Ying.
[gasps]
Here.
I'll leave it to you, you are the monitor.
Okay.
[teacher] Let's continue.
The pursuit of democracy,
equality, and freedom...
[woman 1] Hey, Ms. Ma.
He's here to inspect again.
Let's go. Quick!
-Madam.
-[Ms. Ma] Hello, young man.
Hello.
You are punctual to the second.
You're no mortal, right?
You always stick to your post.
Few stockholders can be like you.
I want to escape, too.
But my legs are weak.
And besides, what should I do
with my vegetables if I escape?
Young man.
What would you like today?
Wait.
For what?
For the perfect time
to pick the fruit and vegetables.
What?
Every fresh fruit and vegetable
has a perfect time to be picked.
Picking them at that moment
can maximize their nutritive value
and water content.
For instance, this onion
has to wait two hours to be picked.
That's its perfect time.
Its nutritional value
will be highest then.
[gasps]
Huh?
[playful music]
ORGANIC FRUITS AND VEGETABLES
[chuckles]
Ooh.
-[Ying chuckling]
-Qi Ying.
[gasps]
Lu Xia. What are you doing here?
To buy some study materials.
You like fish?
Mm-hm.
[calm music]
I've loved little animals
since I was a kid.
[Ying] Once, I went to the aquarium
and saw the fish there.
They were adorable.
I couldn't help but touch the glass.
Then a clownfish swam towards me.
I've loved them since then.
Just like that?
Yes. Just like that.
Love occurs in a flash.
What about you?
Have you experienced anything like that?
[Ying] Like the moment
you fell in love with tennis.
[machine whirring]
[playful music]
[phone beeps]
[man 1] Saturday at 12 p.m.
See you at the cafe.
[Yan Zhiming]
You changed your profile picture.
The previous one has 7,728 pixels.
The current one has 8,963 pixels.
[indistinct chatter]
9 DAYS BEFORE YU QING VS XING YAO
[upbeat music]
A girl who is nice to everyone.
[chuckles]
Me?
A girl who can make omelet rice.
[chuckles]
[soft chuckle]
I don't have any specific requirement.
[upbeat music]
An intelligent girl
who can pass her math exam with ease.
I'm the right person to ask.
I like a girl who is like my mother.
She'd better play a little tennis.
Long or short hair. I don't care.
And our family conditions
should be similar.
Not too good...
[Qiao Chen groaning]
[Qiao Chen] I'm not finished yet.
It's better to be Xing Zi.
Me?
-I like small animals.
-[Peng] Huh?
What kind of animals? Adders?
Lizards?
Tortoises?
Crocodiles?
-Or spiders?
-Hey.
Why are you doing the interview
in our changing room?
[Peng moans]
[clears throat]
I like someone who adores me.
[Peng sighs]
Go away.
[Huang Jing] Hey.
-[panting]
-[Peng gasps]
A girl who greets me when we meet.
[Peng groaning]
-[Huang Jing] Hey.
-[Peng gasps]
[sighs]
I only ask for a girl who knows my name.
Is that okay?
Do you realize
that I'm asking
what kind of cheerleaders you like?
I'm not asking
about your ideal girlfriends.
Is the interview going well?
Yes.
I interviewed everyone
except Lu Xia.
Where is he?
He is practicing at home.
The school qualifying is approaching.
Will he be back?
What are you all doing here?
Peng Xiang?
[Siyang] This is our changing room.
How can you be here?
-Hmm...
-[Xiuwen humming]
No more doughnuts and sweet milk tea
[suspenseful music]
[Xiuwen screaming]
YU QING LABORATORY BUILDING
LU XIA, TANG JIALE, CHI DAYONG
ZHUO ZHI
[sighs]
-Zhuo Zhi.
-[soft chuckle]
You're still here?
The training has finished.
Seeing you stay here,
I wonder what you are doing.
It's going to rain.
I guess you don't have an umbrella.
I'm thinking about the lineup
of the school qualifying.
[Siyang] The coach will determine
who can play against Xing Yao
according to the qualifying result.
I'll wait for you.
Okay.
[sighs]
[upbeat music]
[grunts]
[panting]
Baiyang, let's be a doubles pair.
No.
I won't let other people affect me.
I will win on the singles.
It's okay if you want
to go on practicing your Boomerang Snake.
But it's no use
if you can't use it in your match.
You can't create enough curve in a match
to make your Boomerang Snake ball
fall in the single's sideline.
It gives you no advantages.
What's your point?
Your practice
needs to be tested in a real game
to give you the confidence to use it.
What do you think?
Let's be a doubles pair
to strengthen your Boomerang Snake.
What about you?
I can also make progress in this way.
[thwacks]
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
You're supposed to be practicing
at the club at this time.
The coach let me practice alone.
Have you been eliminated?
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[Xiangqian] It seems
he's trying hard to find his style.
[Xiangqian] It's going to rain.
You should go inside.
[Zhou Zhi] I remember walking this road
every time after training
when I was a freshman.
[Siyang] Hmm.
I've been thinking about something.
What is it?
What if we are...
in different teams?
How did you come up with that?
Haven't you thought about it?
We would have
met on different occasions
and had a good game if so.
-[grunts]
-[thwacks]
[calm music]
[chuckles]
Maybe.
Which do you prefer?
Being teammates on the same team...
or being opponents?
Don't think about things
that only take place in your imagination.
I knew you'd say so.
Now that we are on the same team,
let's work hard together
and make it to the end.
You want more than the Nationals, right?
Of course, I want to keep winning
if I can stay on the court.
So...
as long as we do our best,
then we won't have regrets.
It's unnecessary to give yourself
so much pressure,
whatever the result is.
[breathes heavily]
Zhuo Zhi.
What do the Nationals mean to you?
Do you want to win?
What about you?
What do the Nationals mean to you?
Just like you said.
Everyone is working so hard,
and they want to win.
I don't want to let them down.
So I'll do my best
to meet their expectations.
I believe we will win.
[thunder rumbling]
[soft chuckle]
-Siyang.
-Hm?
It's going to rain.
[sighs deeply]
I remember the weather was just like this
when we went mountaineering last time.
Yes.
[Zhou Zhi] Let's climb the mountain again.
When the weather is clear.
Climb to the top with our team.
[upbeat music]
Sure.
As long as there is a chance.
[Zhou Zhi] It's raining.
[closing theme music]
♪ The childlike face
Is changing little by little ♪
♪ Destiny gives me callused hands ♪
♪ On the playground,
We hang on and practice once more ♪
♪ We vow with a high five on the court ♪
♪ A bunch of youth
Is dashing forward with hope ♪
♪ The air is filled with cheers ♪
♪ I want to have
An impressive performance ♪
♪ An impressive performance ♪
♪ I will never be tired
Of standing by your side ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Sweating for our dreams ♪
♪ The splendor of growing up ♪
♪ Fight with the rackets,
A grand slam in youth ♪
♪ We fall together and stay together ♪
♪ We keep our promise ♪
♪ And support each other ♪
♪ In the undying flames,
The victory glows ♪
♪ Shouting in tears,
We're each other's safe harbor ♪
♪ Hey, hey, yeah ♪
Subtitle translation by Vanessa Ding