♪Roaming freely
through the cycles of time♪
♪In an ardent and liberated soul♪
♪Over thorny roads,
across treacherous heights♪
♪With whom do I travel along?♪
♪I'm willing to brave
life's twists and turns♪
♪For the well-being of people♪
♪Still embracing the original innocence♪
♪Promises made, heard and fulfilled♪
♪And it reaches far and wide♪
♪I will shine like stars
in the dark night♪
♪And stride through fate's ups and downs,
leaning toward the sun♪
♪Moments turn into eternity,
fleeting years become forever♪
♪Despite the long journey ahead,
the light within never dims♪
♪Because someone is waiting for me♪
♪And they will shape the dream
to completion♪
=The Legend of Zhuohua=
(Adapted from "She Was Once
a Playful Soul" by Sui Yu Er An)
=Episode 16=
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Xiaoqin Pleasure House)
Gentlemen,
it wasn't us
who couldn't afford to lose,
but Southern Chen.
Northern Liang will definitely win.
Northern Liang will triumph!
Lord Ding,
you came uninvited
and disrupted our merriment.
Is this how Southern Chen
treats its guests?
Why?
Prince Yemu,
you were usually keen to see
if I would still be good
at drinking and combat.
I have specially come
to invite you for a drink today.
Yet, you seem disinterested.
Ladies,
let's go.
Prince Yemu,
don't you want to ask
why I've come to you today?
I would never imagine
there would be a day
when you and I share a drink like this.
You were poisoned with Yuanluo Flower.
Yet, you managed to survive.
Southern Chen is vast
and filled
with countless skilled physicians.
The mere Yuanluo Flower poison
is nothing.
Seeing that I'm still alive,
it must be truly
disappointing to you.
Haha!
Why would I be disappointed?
I'm only a little surprised.
I've always thought the generals
of Southern Chen
were valiant
and would rather die than be dishonored.
However, you shamelessly live
until today
when all your trusted elite soldiers
perished long ago.
When we faced each other back then,
I saw you bravely slaying enemies
without regard for your life.
But now,
you value your life so much, Lord Ding.
Prince Yemu,
have you ever tasted human blood?
You've asked the right person.
Of course, I have.
Me too.
It was scalding hot,
carrying the scent of iron and rust.
He was my subordinate
and my mentor.
I remember from the first day
I joined the army,
it was him
who led me
and guided me.
At that time,
he cut his own wrist.
He squeezed my cheek,
and his blood flowed
into my mouth.
When his blood had cooled down,
another comrade came.
On the battlefield,
he could entrust his back to me.
(In the face of life and death,)
(he chose to entrust his life to me.)
(After that,)
(I lost consciousness.)
(I can't recall)
how many of them
had offered their blood and lives
to me.
Prince Yemu,
if you carried the weight
of so many lives on your shoulders,
you wouldn't be willing to die either.
You've seen through my strategy
and laid an ambush for me.
Someone within the army
must have tipped you off.
And this person holds a high position.
Later,
I was unconscious with severe injuries.
The morale of our army was low.
But you didn't seize the opportunity
to launch a counterattack
and achieve a major victory
by attacking us from both sides.
This could have been used
as a bargaining chip
to negotiate for more favorable terms.
So I believe the person
who tipped you off
wasn't under your control.
It's even possible
that you don't know who the guy was.
Prince Yemu,
let's make a deal.
If you tell me everything you know,
I promise
not to invade Northern Liang
for ten years.
What kind of deal is this?
Do you think I'll be afraid
if you invade us?
Well, I believe
you will be afraid.
Lord Ding
didn't age
as you hoped.
And our First Prince
is young
and hostile toward Northern Liang.
Moreover,
Your Highness
seems eager to return to Northern Liang.
What do you mean?
Has something significant happened
in the royal camp of Northern Liang?
Or else, why would you
be in such a hurry
to pack your belongings?
You're currently here.
Inside the royal camp,
only the First Prince
and the Second Prince are present.
This is a very unfavorable situation
for you.
Lord Ding, since you are so magnanimous,
I might as well make a deal with you.
The person who tipped me off
was Xue Xiaotang.
He has been hiding in Northern Liang.
Up until this peace negotiation,
he disguised himself as a mute slave
and stayed by my side.
Lord Ding,
are you satisfied
with this great gift?
Haha!
My Lord,
it's clear that Yemu Jing
doesn't really want to make a deal.
But he wants to disrupt Southern Chen's
internal affairs on purpose.
You've also noticed that?
This person is ambitious
and is not someone who advocates peace.
I don't trust him.
He wants to return and fight for power
with two of his elder brothers.
But he couldn't
let Southern Chen become stronger.
That's why he mentioned Xue Xiaotang,
hoping to sow discord
within Southern Chen.
But how could I
grant his wish?
My Lord, I'm glad
you're sensible about this.
At least this matter
has some initial results.
Now, it seems
that Xue Xiaotang
is one of the main culprits
behind the war at Juma River.
He's the Grand General of the Nation.
In Southern Chen, his prestige
was extremely high.
Back then, he went to war with me
to fight against Northern Liang.
The reason the Northern Liang Army
was able to ambush us unexpectedly
must have been
because he threatened Yuan Chengming
to obtain the marching map,
leading to our defeat.
My Lord,
the political scene is clear,
and the world is at peace.
All hidden matters
will eventually come to light
as long as you don't give up.
My Lord,
you've already done a great job.
What he betrayed
was his dignity as a human.
It's not related to you.
The peace negotiation
will definitely succeed after today.
I'm genuinely happy for you.
Since I'm done with my task,
I shall take my leave now.
Why are you trying to run off again?
You've been avoiding me lately.
Am I a terrifying beast?
You're not a terrifying beast.
You just make me feel restless.
What?
Nothing. Nothing, My Lord.
It's just that I need some quiet time
to calm down.
My Lord, farewell.
Restless?
(Why is she avoiding me?)
(Laiyuan Relay Station)
Jing,
are you really going back?
If I don't return,
I'm afraid I won't even
have a chance to compete.
But we've gained nothing
from this peace negotiation.
I've already lit the fire.
Remember
to add fuel to the fire
at the right moment.
We must let the fire burn
hotter and hotter
until it's uncontrollable.
Jing, are you talking
about the mute slave?
I understand it now.
You've been living comfortably
in Southern Chen.
But never forget our people
who suffer back home.
I won't forget.
But...
As long as we can ignite this fire,
the type of fuel
doesn't matter, right?
Of course.
That scoundrel Yemu Jing
has finally dragged himself back
to Northern Liang with his lackeys.
You're Southern Chen's Crown Prince.
Mind your language
when speaking in public.
If not for Southern Chen's dignity,
I would have surely
knocked his teeth out.
Now that Southern Chen
and Northern Liang have formed an alliance
and ceased hostilities,
the people at the border
can finally enjoy peaceful days.
You're right.
Lord Ding is indeed ingenious
to disrupt Yemu Jing's negotiations
by using the King
of Northern Liang's illness.
By creating this distraction,
Yemu Jing became restless
and eager to leave.
Surely, he would have to agree
to all the conditions proposed
by Southern Chen.
Lord Ding is truly skilled
at making people restless.
Jinghong? Ms. Mu?
(Oh, no. What should I do?)
- Greetings, Lord Ding, Your Highness.
(To block a formidable opponent,)
(I can only seek help
from another formidable figure.)
Your Highness, how is your leg injury?
It's a lot better now.
Thank you for asking.
Ms. Mu, your medical skills
are truly remarkable.
Why have you been avoiding me?
I...
I haven't been avoiding you.
Uncle, when has she ever avoided you?
By the way,
I have something
to discuss with you, Ms. Mu.
Grandmother had Father
remove your teaching position.
His Majesty knows
I've been busy entertaining
the diplomatic corps
and was being considerate of me.
That's why His Majesty relieved me
from such duties.
Mr. Shen.
I have to discuss
an important matter with you.
Come with me.
Your Highness,
I'll take my leave for now.
You don't always have to
be considerate of others
or speak up for others.
Your Highness, I'm flattered.
I'm not a revengeful
or ungrateful person.
About the previous incident,
I've misunderstood you.
I also know
the teaching position
holds great importance for officials.
I've discussed it with Father.
You can return
to continue teaching anytime.
Your Highness, you...
What about me?
Your Highness,
you treat others sincerely.
It is an honor for me
and a blessing for the world.
(So this is the reason
why you're distancing yourself from me.)
My Lord, what is it that you wanted
to discuss with me?
Never mind.
We'll discuss it another day.
Uncle, she complimented me.
Mu Zhuohua said
I always treat people sincerely.
When have you not
treated people sincerely?
Uncle, you were right.
Mu Zhuohua does have great potential.
She truly understands me.
I'm not like that two-faced Liu Yu.
During the peace negotiation
with Northern Liang,
she contributed a lot.
So I asked Father
to resume Mu Zhuohua's
teaching position.
Did she agree?
I think so.
It's not a bad thing, after all.
Uncle,
Mu Zhuohua found a clue
about Yemu Jing's intentions to leave.
Aren't you planning
to reward her in some way?
No.
"Official Shen Jinghong
of the Ministry of Revenue
shall be promoted
to Primary Fifth-Rank Director.
This decree takes effect
on the 27th day of the 4th month,
the 24th year of the Zhaoming Reign.
Granted by His Majesty."
My thanks for His Majesty's benevolence.
"Official Mu Zhuohua
of the Ministry of Rites
shall be promoted
to Primary Sixth-Rank Administrator.
This decree takes effect
on the 27th day of the 4th month,
the 24th year of the Zhaoming Reign.
Granted by His Majesty."
My thanks for His Majesty's benevolence.
Ms. Mu, your promotion
wouldn't have happened
without Lord Ding's support.
I understand.
Thank you for reminding me, sir.
You sure pick up fast.
By the way,
tomorrow is Lord Ding's rest day.
It's a perfect chance for you to visit
and thank him in person.
I will.
My Lord,
since it's your rest day,
why not take a herbal bath later?
All right.
My Lord,
Mu wishes to see you.
No.
Yes.
Wait.
Let her in.
Let's see what excuse
she'll come up with this time.
Greetings,
My Lord.
Nowadays,
you don't visit me
unless there's something important.
I'm here to thank Your Lordship
for helping me develop my potential.
But I don't know how to repay you.
I remember
you appreciate calligraphy,
and I've heard that Wenxin Pavilion
has stocked up a batch
of extremely precious ink stones.
So I bought one as a gift for you.
Please accept it, My Lord.
I'm sure you spent a fortune on this.
But it's rare for you to do this.
I feel grateful to you, My Lord.
This ink stone is just
a small token of appreciation.
A few days ago,
First Prince mentioned to me
about requesting you
to resume your teaching duties.
What are your thoughts?
Whether I leave or stay,
I shall let Your Lordship
and His Highness decide.
I've already told you
not to get involved
in the princes' conflicts.
Why won't you remember?
I do remember.
You're aware
that First Prince is most likely
to succeed to the throne.
So you approach him,
trying to please him.
Haven't you learned your lesson
after the fight
between the princes back then?
If you get close to First Prince,
the other two princes will target you.
At that time,
your life will always be in danger.
(I know it's dangerous.)
(But I'm more afraid of losing myself
because of you.)
My Lord, you're right.
So...
You still insist on resuming
your teaching position?
(How can I tell you)
(the reason I want to keep
this teaching position)
(is to stay away from you?)
Why?
You don't even dare to answer now?
(I just don't know how to answer.)
(I'm afraid of being troubled by this
and affecting my future.)
It looks like
you've already made up your mind.
My Lord,
- I...
- Never mind.
You may go now.
I don't want to say anything more.
Young Lady, you're back.
By the way,
have you thanked Lord Ding?
I did.
But...
But what?
I get so restless whenever I see him.
My thoughts are all over the place.
I can't understand anything,
nor can I do anything well.
Tell me, how would I dare go near him?
Men
are so terrifying.
What a distraction to my future.
That won't do, Young Lady.
How could you make Lord Ding angry?
Aren't you afraid your current behavior
might affect your future?
He already said
he wouldn't blame me.
But
you don't seem very happy today.
It's because Lord Ding seemed upset.
What should I do?
Young Lady,
Lord Ding is a forgiving person.
He wouldn't hold a grudge.
Maybe I should prepare
some sincere gifts
and visit him tomorrow.
And I'll explain it to him.
It's all my fault.
It's all my fault for being so inept.
Juli, let's go
and deliver this to Lord Ding.
Young Lady, why isn't there anyone
at Lord Ding's Residence?
It seems
Lord Ding is truly angry with me.
That's not good.
By the way,
you used to say that Lord Ding
is a person of...
A person of noble character.
In any case, he's definitely
the forgiving type.
I think as long as
we show a good attitude,
he will forgive us.
Let's go to Lord Ding's Residence.
Miss Mu.
Miss Mu,
I'm not getting in your way on purpose.
His Lordship
is already resting.
Maybe you can come another day?
All right.
Could you please give this
to His Lordship?
♪You made me put down my guard♪
Take care, miss.
Thank you.
♪I melted into your gaze
like snowflakes♪
♪Enduring the flying sand
whisked by time♪
♪Allowing each other's wounds to heal♪
♪Love is the concern
burning in the heart♪
♪Like winter waiting for the midsummer♪
♪It sears within me,
nurtured throughout my lifetime♪
♪Love is silent, it's measured
by fate even when apart♪
Young Lady, it's very cold out there.
Have some warm water.
The weather can be unpredictable.
Lord Ding didn't look
too good last night.
Today, Butler Zhang said he's unwell.
Do you think...
Could Lord Ding have caught a cold?
I was wrong before.
How could the miss vanish
just because we are far apart?
He doesn't seem to be angry now.
But he refuses to see me now.
It seems like he knows
what's on my mind.
But for some reason,
I'm feeling even sadder.
♪Conquering the unpredictable
twists of fate♪
Juli,
do you think Lord Ding...
♪A beautiful smile only for you♪
has given up on me?
♪Love is the concern
burning in the heart♪
♪Like stars chasing the skyline♪
♪It sears within me,
nurtured throughout my lifetime♪
♪Once two entwined hearts embraced♪
♪Love remains forever untainted♪
First, there was a drought in Jiangnan.
After the eager expectation,
the heavy rain
finally brought sprouts of crops,
and it attracted swarms of locusts
that covered the sky.
The scout reported
that the locusts covered the sky.
They devoured the crops,
leaving the land barren by evening.
The people are struggling
to find enough to eat.
Oh, Heaven.
You're really causing me distress.
Father.
The King of Northern Liang
is seriously ill.
I feel like my strength
is dwindling too.
In recent days,
even your uncle has been feeling ill.
The peace talks
can at least ensure stability
along the borders for several years.
But these internal issues...
When I think
of the Jiangnan people suffering,
it feels like
a fire scorching within me,
and my heart feels like
it's being cut by a knife.
Father,
please take care of your health.
Uncle should focus on nursing himself.
I'm not a child anymore.
I would like to share
the burden with the elders.
Father,
I request permission
to go to Jiangnan
to assist in disaster relief
and help the people settle down.
Good.
Your trip to Jiangnan
will encounter challenges
and difficulties.
It will be a great experience for you.
But I won't
let you go alone.
How about this?
I'll send you two assistants.
They will surely be able to aid you.
Do you mean...
Mu Zhuohua and Shen Jinghong, of course.
Both of them
will be a sheath and a sword.
If they can complement each other,
they'll surely achieve great things.
Father, I...
Chen,
Mu Zhuohua may be a woman.
But she's intelligent, perceptive,
and possesses great foresight.
She's a true talent.
You mustn't underestimate her.
I've witnessed
Official Mu's abilities firsthand.
I no longer hold
any prejudice against her.
Speaking of which,
it was Uncle's keen eye
that first recognized this hidden gem.
I'm fortunate enough
that I didn't miss out either.
(The locust plague in Jiangnan
leads to famine.)
(Jishan Hall's efforts fall short,
seeking Your Highness' instruction.)
Your Highness,
are you reading the letter
from Jishan Hall in Jiangnan?
Yes.
The famine is widespread
around Huaizhou.
And Jiangnan Jishan Hall's food reserves
won't last much longer.
Speaking of the disaster,
I heard His Majesty
has entrusted Jiangnan's disaster relief
to First Prince.
He's going to the south soon.
I've heard of it too.
Well, Official Shen
will likely travel with him.
After all, His Highness
has always valued him.
Go and pack up some belongings.
I'm going to Jiangnan.
Now?
We must act fast to solve this.
I can't rest assured
unless I take a look myself.
Yes.
Traveling with His Highness
can save a lot of trouble.
Moreover, with Mr. Shen around, he can...
Bring along General Xue's portrait too.
Yes, I'll go and make the preparations.
(Zhixing College)
Your Highnesses,
do you still have any questions
that I need to answer?
After I return, I'll revise the lessons,
and I'll ask Ms. Mu for guidance
in the next class.
I'm afraid you might be disappointed.
There might not be a next time for now.
What do you mean?
Are you planning
to cause trouble for Ms. Mu again?
Do you think
I have nothing better to do like you?
That makes sense.
You will depart for Jiangnan
for disaster relief.
I wonder
if Ms. Mu is joining too.
Yes.
You're exceptionally talented,
and you're from Jiangnan.
Are you willing to join me
on this trip?
I shall comply.
You didn't let me down.
Your Highness,
has Lord Ding replied
to the official document yet?
Why?
Are you worried Uncle won't approve it?
(I'm just worried
he'll approve it too quickly.)
(Mu Zhuohua is to join the journey.)
My Lord, here are today's documents.
The one on top is from First Prince.
He said it was somewhat urgent.
I shall take my leave.
(Department of State Affairs)
Lord Ding went to visit His Majesty.
He hasn't returned yet.
He's not available again?
Looks like I won't be able
to bid farewell to him.
If it's something urgent,
perhaps you can...
It's all right. I'll just wait
for Lord Ding here.
Thank you.
Ms. Mu,
do you still plan on waiting?
I have to set out now.
Please convey this to Lord Ding
that Mu Zhuohua is about to set off
for Jiangnan for disaster relief
and came to bid farewell.
Yes, Ms. Mu.
Thank you.
My Lord,
Official Mu came by earlier.
She wished to have a word with you.
Why did she come to me again?
No idea.
Everyone knows
you haven't been valuing her lately.
My Lord,
I heard that Official Mu
has already gone to Jiangnan
for disaster relief with First Prince.
It seems she won't be bothering you
for the next few days.
Jiangnan? Disaster relief?
Yes.
Weren't you the one who approved it?
♪You made me put down my guard♪
My Lord!
♪I melted into your gaze
like snowflakes♪
(Mingde Gate)
♪Enduring the flying sand
whisked by time♪
♪Allowing each other's wounds to heal♪
♪Love is the concern
burning in the heart♪
♪Like stars chasing the skyline♪
♪It sears within me,
nurtured throughout my lifetime♪
♪Love is silent,
I'll measure it with my life for you♪
♪This untainted heart
imprints your image♪
♪Accompanying me like a shadow
all around the world♪
♪This untainted love forms a couple
with intense emotion♪
♪Longing is a home of love♪
(Capital)
♪Unceasing love stalks my mind♪
♪Couldn't get over it♪
♪Memories touch the edges of our souls♪
♪Nowhere to anchor, lost in the expanse♪
♪We gaze at each other
in the drizzling rain♪
♪But you have gone without a trace♪
♪Leaving me all alone in the world♪
♪Like waves without a shore♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Clearly, our eyes brim
with muffled affections♪
♪For a hug, we burn our life♪
♪Searching for you
throughout the long journey♪
♪Clearly you know, clearly I understand♪
♪We swear to stay together
in every lifetime♪
♪For this heartbeat,
I can suffer for aye♪
♪Never part ways,
we made this promise long ago♪
♪Love and hate entwined, unforgettable♪
♪Even if we are far apart♪
♪Two souls embrace in chaos♪
♪Impossible to erase, destiny's light♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Clearly, our eyes brim
with muffled affections♪
♪For a hug, we burn our life♪
♪Searching for you
throughout the long journey♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Our minds occupied with each other♪
♪For this heartbeat♪
♪I can suffer for aye♪
♪Want to have one more glimpse of you,
even just for a second more♪