♪Roaming freely
through the cycles of time♪
♪In an ardent and liberated soul♪
♪Over thorny roads,
across treacherous heights♪
♪With whom do I travel along?♪
♪I'm willing to brave
life's twists and turns♪
♪For the well-being of people♪
♪Still embracing the original innocence♪
♪Promises made, heard and fulfilled♪
♪And it reaches far and wide♪
♪I will shine like stars
in the dark night♪
♪And stride through fate's ups and downs,
leaning toward the sun♪
♪Moments turn into eternity,
fleeting years become forever♪
♪Despite the long journey ahead,
the light within never dims♪
♪Because someone is waiting for me♪
♪And they will shape the dream
to completion♪
=The Legend of Zhuohua=
(Adapted from "She Was Once
a Playful Soul" by Sui Yu Er An)
=Episode 24=
(This is a work of fiction.)
If His Majesty were to know
that she's a problematic person,
I'm afraid she'll be removed.
Lord Ding,
what are your thoughts on this?
Miss Sun.
What you did was unethical.
Yet you dare to ask for my opinion.
Your Majesty, I shall take my leave.
Greetings, Your Majesty. I'm Mu Zhuohua,
the Director of the Ministry of Revenue.
Mu Zhuohua.
Do you plead guilty?
Your Majesty.
What is it that I am guilty of?
Observer Sun, tell her.
What exactly is Mu Zhuohua guilty of?
You changed your birthplace
from Huaizhou to Yanzhou.
Deceiving the Emperor
is a grave offense.
Mu Zhuohua.
Drop your act.
(My change of origins
was like a hanging knife.)
(I didn't expect it
to fall on me today.)
Mu Zhuohua.
Last time, I gave you
30 floggings as punishment.
How should I punish you this time?
Do you have anything else to say?
I...
I have nothing to say.
Guards!
Take her away!
Wait!
Down.
Greetings, Your Majesty, Lord Ding.
Your Majesty.
Mu Zhuohua is unworthy
of her title as Tanhua.
She is originally
from Huaizhou, Jiangnan.
She is the seventh daughter of Mu Rong,
whose family is the richest in Jiangnan.
Her real name is Mu Qi.
She took the metropolitan examination
by changing her birthplace.
I can explain,
Your Majesties.
I changed my birthplace
because I didn't have a choice.
I am indeed from Huaizhou.
At the time, I was forced
to marry Zhuang Wenfeng.
I refused to do so.
I was determined
to pass the imperial examination
and become a scholar.
I only changed my birthplace to Yanzhou
out...
out of desperation.
Even so, it is a crime
of deceiving the Emperor.
Mu Zhuohua gained the title of Tanhua
with her talents.
But due to the change in her birthplace,
she has been
walking on thin ice and living in fear.
She was afraid that if it got exposed,
everything she did
for the people of Southern Chen
would go down the drain.
What about you, Miss Sun?
You were born with advantages.
You made it to a political observer
with the merits of your ancestors.
However, you never thought of ways
to benefit the people.
Instead, you are acting shamelessly
and meanly for your own gain.
Miss Sun.
Do you feel worthy
of being a political observer
in the Ministry of Revenue?
Your Majesties.
I gained this position
according to the system of the court.
I have never deceived the Emperor.
That's enough!
I was already aware that Mu Zhuohua
changed her birthplace.
How can that be?
I am now clear
about Mu Zhuohua and the change
of her birthplace.
Your Majesty,
how do you plan to punish her?
How do you want me to punish her?
I dare not overstep my authority.
It's just that
passing the examination isn't easy
for a lady.
Moreover, Mu Zhuohua has exceptional
character and abilities.
I hope you can forgive her.
It is rare to see you
think so highly of someone.
Mu Zhuohua's reason
for changing her birthplace
is justified.
Furthermore,
she is the right-hand woman
whom I am planning to keep
for the new emperor.
Don't worry.
I value talent more than you do.
I thank Your Majesty
on Mu Zhuohua's behalf.
Lord Ding had informed me
of this matter long ago.
It was to show me
if Tanhua Mu
was really competent.
The reason I sent her to Jiangnan
was to see
if she was able
to turn the tide in her hometown.
She has proven
that she is capable of it.
But you?
If you really thought she deceived me,
you should have come to me about it,
but not the Dowager Empress.
Don't forget
that you are now not the Young Lady Sun
but a political observer
in the Ministry of Revenue.
Please have mercy, Your Majesty!
Have mercy?
You have held this position for so long,
yet you addressed yourself
as a common person.
Miss Sun.
If you don't intend to be an official,
why take up the position
of a political observer?
Yunyun was just...
Mother.
Please stop interfering in politics.
Sun Yunyun.
Since you have no intention
to be an official,
you can go home
and be the young lady of the Sun family.
As for Ms. Mu,
deceiving was not your intention,
but it was still wrong
to change your birthplace.
I'll deduct your salary for three months
as your punishment.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave.
Still feeling scared?
My Lord.
Changing my birthplace
was enough to get me executed.
I just came back from the gates of Hell.
I'm obviously scared.
I'm still feeling scared.
My Lord.
Why didn't you tell me
that His Majesty was already
aware of it?
Only His Majesty needs to know.
This matter cannot be disclosed.
If it weren't for Miss Sun
picking a fight today,
His Majesty and I would have planned
to take it to our graves.
You are right.
After all, I wasn't honest about this.
I am really lucky
that I am still alive.
I can finally have a good sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
I won't sleep in your carriage.
My Lord.
Xue Xiaotang is having another relapse.
He seems unlikely
to make it through this time.
Imperial Physician Lu
is doing his best to save him.
Quickly return.
Yes, My Lord.
Hold him down.
Imperial Physician Lu.
I'll help you.
Get the needle.
He can't carry on like this.
Imperial Physician Lu.
I heard the Imperial Academy of Medicine
has rare books.
Please try to find another cure.
Alright, I will look through them
right away.
Miss Sun.
Official Fang.
Are you going home?
I'm waiting for someone.
You may go ahead.
All right.
Thank Official Mu for me.
Thank her for looking after me lately.
It's just that
dealing with so many men every day
is not good for a lady's reputation.
I didn't know any better at first
and took the wrong path.
Now that I've come to a realization,
that means farewell.
Stop, miss.
No need to relay it.
How many people
have had a hard time walking
this short journey?
(Department of State Affairs)
Some people go straight to the top
and still criticize others
with a petty heart.
It is truly ridiculous
and pathetic.
You are wrong, Official Mu.
Even if a sparrow
has the ambition of a swan,
it won't be strong enough
to fly up high in the sky.
One's destiny is fixed.
How can the silt rise above the clouds?
Rise above?
I'm afraid what you said was wrong.
Everything I have today
was earned on my own.
Besides,
to me,
my career as an official
always comes first.
- Lord Ding.
- My Lord.
I know
that I have no place in your heart,
but you don't have to emphasize it
all the time.
Official Mu.
What a coincidence.
My Lord.
We must set some rules from now on.
All right.
Act appropriately in front of others.
We can't let them
find out about our relationship.
My Lord is so clever.
I'm returning to my duty.
(Department of State Affairs)
Was this also sent to other places
or am I the only one getting it?
Officials of Six Ministries
don't have it, to say the least.
Thank you.
My Lord.
Ministry of Personnel
extended their thanks.
Ministry of Justice, Ministry of Rites,
Ministry of War, and Ministry of Works
as well.
And the Ministry of Revenue?
Did they send someone to say thanks?
The cost of the ice
was appropriated from them.
Minister Xu feels upset over it.
He probably won't come.
Anything can be solved,
as danger is nothing to be afraid of.
Is this
what the Ministry of Revenue
thinks of the disaster in Jiangnan?
Tell me what you think.
The locust plague was cruel,
but you are wise, My Lord.
You are not making any sense.
Next.
I think there is nothing wrong
with that remark.
Thanks to your decisive judgment,
we were able to overcome the crisis.
It's also a blessing in disguise
for the people of Jiangnan.
Full of flattery.
Not a word is sincere.
Next.
We will do
as you say, My Lord.
No one
from the Ministry of Revenue
can make things clear.
I will go
and figure something out.
What am I supposed to do?
Official Li, how did it go?
Is His Lordship happy?
Happy?
Far from it!
Official Li.
Ms. Mu.
The hopes of the Ministry of Revenue
all lie with you now.
I don't know
what is going on with Lord Ding today.
He's so cranky.
He's unhappy with everything.
He keeps torturing us.
We have appropriated funds
for the ice today.
Why is he always
giving us such a hard time?
That's why we have no choice
but to send you to deal with him.
Me?
(Department of State Affairs)
Is he in a bad mood?
My Lord.
It took them long enough
to send you here.
What are your thoughts
on the disaster relief for Jiangnan?
Disasters don't come out of nowhere.
Blessings don't fall from the sky.
This is what I think.
The disaster in Jiangnan
was both natural and man-made.
But isn't it a good thing for the people
if corrupted and greedy officials
were weeded out
because of this?
Yes.
No one says it better than you.
You have had a hard time
writing documents lately.
Come.
Come on.
I've been waiting for you to eat.
I'm still on duty.
I have to go back and tidy up.
Eating is also an important matter.
My Lord.
You have caused
the Ministry of Revenue
to be in a panic today.
That's good.
This way, they will learn
that brown-nosing
won't solve the problem.
Then they will always send you here.
After all, I am just your secret lover.
I cannot be with you
in public.
All right. My Lord has suffered.
Are you happy now?
I'm not upset anymore.
Have some more.
My Lord, I'm done eating.
I have to go now.
So soon?
Once I am off duty,
I'll wait for you outside.
I'll bring back the document,
tidy up for a bit, and come out.
This step forward that His Lordship took
is such a big step.
We should learn from him.
Official Wen.
It's been a while.
What brings you
to the Ministry of Revenue?
Not long ago, good scholars
were being appointed.
I was chosen to be
a political observer here.
Well, not only are we
from the same batch,
but we're also colleagues.
Please look out for me in the future.
You're being too humble, Official Mu.
Now, you are
the Director of the Ministry of Revenue,
while I'm just a low-ranking
political observer.
I'm in no place to act superior.
If that's the case,
not long ago,
I was a low-ranking
political observer, too.
I am ashamed of myself.
Why are you ashamed?
Because you are a man,
but your ranking isn't as high as mine?
I...
I was sort of pedantic in the past
over the difference
between men and women.
I am truly...
Truly sorry.
Just admit your wrongs and change.
Bowing to me is unnecessary.
I should get going.
Official Mu.
Official Mu, are you married?
She is really popular with men.
According to the law of Southern Chen,
women can marry once they are 16.
Have your elders in the family
made any arrangements for you?
I'm dedicated to serving my nation
with no intention to marry.
In that case, I will be frank.
What do you think of me?
Well...
You are a gentleman.
I have always respected you
like an elder brother.
Indeed, I am slightly older than you.
But I wouldn't claim myself
as your brother.
A few days ago, I thought
you and Official Shen were...
I found out
it was a misunderstanding later on.
That's why I made
a bold confession to you today.
I...
Greetings, Lord Ding.
Be at ease.
It's already late.
Is the Ministry of Revenue
still working?
Your Lordship,
we were just about to leave.
You may leave first.
I have something important
to discuss with Official Mu.
My Lord.
I didn't want this to happen.
I know that.
I have an idea.
It will stop him from bothering you.
What is it?
Cater to his taste.
Make him distant himself.
Well, I'm counting on you, My Lord.
(Department of State Affairs)
Official Mu.
Have you considered
what I said to you the other day?
I...
Official Wen.
I have made it clear that day.
I really have no intention to marry.
Look.
Marriage is a natural thing.
How can a woman not marry?
To tell you the truth,
the elders in the family often say
that a woman without talent is virtuous.
I initially thought so, too.
But ever since I heard of
what you did in Jiangnan,
I changed my mind.
I think women
should be like you.
Well-educated and well-mannered.
Be exceptional
in both appearance and intellect.
You are fine-looking and talented.
But I don't share your feelings.
I really have no intention to marry.
Official Mu.
If you think
I'm not good enough for you,
just be frank with me.
If I could improve it,
I would change it for you.
Not at all.
You are not lacking in any way.
It's just that I...
I am not good enough for you.
Not at all.
I think...
I think you are incredible.
If we get married,
we can surely help each other.
Greetings, Lord Ding.
Official Mu.
I have work to assign you.
Come with me.
Yes, My Lord.
My Lord.
My Lord, I thought you said
you had an idea
to stop Wen Shizong from bothering me.
What exactly is it?
What if you have offended me?
Will he dare marry you?
You have shut the door so tightly.
Others can barely see a thing.
It'd better be.
I think so, too.
♪The water hides the reflection
of the full moon♪
♪Its light cascades upon your face♪
♪In this vast galaxy,
your eyes sparkle like the white snow♪
♪The night rain wakes up the sparrow♪
♪As the young student
became an official♪
♪Afraid of adding more twists and turns♪
♪Your endless beauty♪
♪Accompanies me through my years♪
♪Countless words and expressions♪
♪Cannot compare to our shared journey♪
♪Your endless beauty♪
♪Surpasses even the palaces of heaven♪
My Lord.
What is this?
♪With you by my side♪
♪I quietly wait
for challenges to fade away♪
I gave you a mole
that brings bad luck to your husband.
Let's see who dares
to covet you from now on.
My Lord.
Official Xu, Minister of Revenue,
wants to see you.
Please have mercy, My Lord!
I was wrong.
Were you?
Do you know what you did wrong?
I...
I was wrong for...
For...
You are greedy and cowardly.
You have a glib tongue.
Bold as brass. Lack foresight.
There's more.
You acted in bad faith
and went around attracting bad admirers.
What? Bad admirers?
Anyway,
go back now
and reflect on yourself.
Yes, My Lord.
I shall take my leave.
My Lord.
Was it that bad?
Yes.
He's so petty.
A mole that brings bad luck
to my husband?
Aren't you jinxing yourself?
He was furious?
Yes.
Think of something.
Ms. Mu.
Official Mu.
We heard
about what happened this morning.
Though we haven't
worked together for long,
all of us
truly admire your abilities.
How could you be so careless
and end up offending Lord Ding?
I...
I find it strange.
Is it because of the documents
you worked on all day
to make him approve
all the Ministry of Revenue documents?
And that upset him?
Exactly.
I talked back to him that day
so that I could get all the documents
for the Ministry of Revenue.
I guess I am getting
my retribution today.
And I am panicking now.
I just hope Lord Ding will forgive me
and show mercy.
That's our fault.
It's our fault!
I'm sorry.
Official Li.
I need to be alone for a while.
Please excuse me.
I feel bad for Ms. Mu.
Yes.
It's not easy for her.
Let's go, Official Li.
Uncle.
I thought you've always
admired Mu Zhuohua.
Why did you criticize her
so badly this time?
What did she do wrong?
You caught wind of it so quickly.
That's for sure.
After all, she and I have gone
through thick and thin before.
It's normal
that I am concerned about her.
It was just a business trip to Jiangnan.
That's barely thick and thin.
How is it not?
You see.
The days we spent on disaster relief
were tough days.
Returning to the capital
and being rewarded were good days.
Uncle.
You haven't answered me.
You always admired
Mu Zhuohua's talents.
Why are you giving her a hard time now?
When young people
have made a bit of achievements,
they become impetuous and careless.
I must humble her.
Uncle.
I'm sure it was just a careless mistake.
Don't be so hard on her.
I heard that she cried
after getting scolded by you.
Why are you looking at me like this?
Chen.
You are 21 now, no?
At the palace banquet back then,
was there any young lady
that caught your eye?
His Majesty can arrange
the marriage for you.
Uncle, stop making fun of me.
Are these noble young ladies
out of their minds?
I have avoided them so hard,
but they still keep coming to me.
It is not that they are foolish.
It is that their families are crafty.
This won't do.
It's terrifying.
I can't even have a meal at ease.
I must find a way
to end it once and for all.
To be honest, if it is Mu Zhuohua,
I think I can accept that.
Uncle.
Why are you
staring at me like that again?
She's not for you.
I know that.
Mother and Grandmother
have been nagging at me
since the coming-of-age ceremony.
They said I must marry
a noble daughter
as the Princess Consort.
But I don't like it.
Just like you, Uncle.
You have remained unmarried.
It's because you refuse
to be controlled
by these noble families.
If I don't marry, I won't have an heir.
To some people,
it is a good thing.
Do you have it ready?
Look.
Just fresh out of the bank.
She just got scolded by Uncle.
She must be upset.
If she sees this,
she will cheer up for sure.
Come on.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Yes, Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Have you seen Ms. Mu?
Ms. Mu left very early today.
She said she was going to dine
with Mr. Shen at Xiaoqin Pleasure House.
Xiaoqin Pleasure House again?
She invited Jinghong
but not me.
Your Highness.
I've finally found you.
His Majesty has summoned you
to Wende Hall
to discuss your visit
to the temporary imperial residence.
Let's go.
(Xiaoqin Pleasure House)
Sun, what are you doing?
Recently,
Yunyun has acted out of line
and caused you a lot of trouble.
I feel really sorry.
I apologize to you
on my sister's behalf.
Sun, you don't have to do this.
I'm not someone
who'd take it out on others.
I'm too ashamed to face you.
You and her aren't the same.
Besides,
she has left the Ministry of Revenue.
It's water under the bridge now.
Come on, Sun.
All right.
Stop standing there.
We are at a place of entertainment.
Let's just talk
about entertaining things.
Come on. Sit down.
He's right.
Shen, let's drink to Sun.
Sure.
Good.
Then I shall drink to you two as well.
Come on, we are not done drinking.
- Drink up, Sun.
- Carry on.
I knew you two would quickly
rise through the ranks.
One is the Director
of the Ministry of Revenue.
Another one is the Director
of the Ministry of Personnel.
Among those from our batch,
you two are the quickest to rise!
All right, Sun.
Don't be self-deprecating.
You have true talent and knowledge, too.
You would've been successful like us
if you hadn't been burdened
by your family.
Shen.
Are you talking about Jiangzuo?
The Sun family already has Consort Shu
and Minister of Works.
So they can't have
a director of the Ministry of Works.
You know what?
I am really willing
to work as the administrator
of the Ministry of Works
until I retire.
I get it now.
So do I.
Sun, what do you get?
The edge of this table isn't straight.
Bring me my ruler.
I'll straighten it out.
Sun is delighted after having drinks.
It's not cut straight.
Here, Shen.
Let's drink up.
Cheers.
My Lord.
Why don't you join them?
They are hanging out as peers.
I shouldn't be a bother.
While Official Mu is drinking
and chatting happily
with other men,
not only is His Lordship waiting alone,
but he also has to secretly protect her.
Drink another.
Here. I'm feeding you.
Here.
His Lordship is truly magnanimous.
♪Unceasing love stalks my mind♪
♪Couldn't get over it♪
♪Memories touch the edges of our souls♪
♪Nowhere to anchor, lost in the expanse♪
♪We gaze at each other
in the drizzling rain♪
♪But you have gone without a trace♪
♪Leaving me all alone in the world♪
♪Like waves without a shore♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Clearly, our eyes brim
with muffled affections♪
♪For a hug, we burn our life♪
♪Searching for you
throughout the long journey♪
♪Clearly you know, clearly I understand♪
♪We swear to stay together
in every lifetime♪
♪For this heartbeat,
I can suffer for aye♪
♪Never part ways,
we made this promise long ago♪
♪Love and hate entwined, unforgettable♪
♪Even if we are far apart♪
♪Two souls embrace in chaos♪
♪Impossible to erase, destiny's light♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Clearly, our eyes brim
with muffled affections♪
♪For a hug, we burn our life♪
♪Searching for you
throughout the long journey♪
♪Clearly you know♪
♪Clearly I understand♪
♪Our minds occupied with each other♪
♪For this heartbeat♪
♪I can suffer for aye♪
♪Want to have one more glimpse of you,
even just for a second more♪