[Shadow Love]
[Episode 13]
If that's the case,
let's settle all accounts.
You've spoken inappropriately
to me multiple times.
What punishment do you think you deserve?
I was trying to save you,
and save myself as well.
But if you want to talk about
genuine feelings,
there were some as well.
What about just now?
Your wounds have clearly healed,
yet you still asked me
to feed you medicine.
Since I arrived at your residence,
I've rarely seen you so gentle.
So
I just got a bit carried away.
I originally wanted to
enjoy it for a few more days,
but
I couldn't bear
to see you
working so hard for me day and night.
You looked quite pretty that day
in that dancer's outfit.
When will you
wear it for me again?
How dare you talk nonsense like that!
Shuang!
How is she?
How long have you been experiencing
these dizzy spells?
It's been a while.
I just didn't pay much attention to it.
You're suffering from melancholy,
combined with deficiency
in both qi and blood.
If this continues,
there will be serious consequences.
You really need to recuperate properly.
It can't be that serious.
I just need some rest.
You're always like this.
When your soldiers have
even the slightest ailment,
you're more concerned than anyone;
but when it comes to yourself,
you keep making all the excuses.
This time, you were unconscious for a day,
and you were lucky it wasn't worse.
But what about next time?
Report, General.
We've received a message from the capital.
[To Li Shuang]
Look at the state you're in.
How can you read letters?
Don't read it. Rest.
A letter from the capital
must carry important business.
Don't be petulant.
Don't read it.
Give it to me, Lu Xin.
Don't be petulant.
Come on.
Father writes that
His Majesty
has pardoned our Li family's crimes,
and Father has been reinstated
to his post.
That's great!
Cuiyun.
Make a run to the Changfeng Army
and deliver this news
to Qin Lan and Luo Teng.
Yes.
Now that peace has been restored
and everyone is happy,
you can finally breathe a sigh of relief.
Why not take this opportunity
to properly recover?
When you're feeling better,
we'll go to Cang Mountain together.
I know
a unique medicinal herb which grows there,
the dragon blood herb.
It's excellent for
replenishing blood and qi—
just right to help you recover.
Cang Mountain?
Cang Mountain is
a hundred li from Lucheng.
I'm the General.
How can I abandon my post
without permission?
It's exactly because you are the General
that you must take care of yourself.
The Yao State has already
withdrawn their troops.
In the short term,
they won't wage war again.
So put your mind at ease.
But
there are still many important matters
in the camp that need my attention.
Those matters
can be handled by Qin Lan and Luo Teng.
Your top priority now
is to recover your health.
If your health fails,
who will lead the army in battle?
Besides,
didn't you just promise me
that you would
take better care of yourself?
What,
are you already going back on your word?
General.
This coachman looks a bit unfamiliar.
I just recently recruited him.
What,
Miss, you think I'm not reliable?
To be honest with you, Miss,
I know every inch of Lucheng
and all its roads, big or small,
like the back of my hand.
With me, Ouyang Jun, as your guide,
you can rest completely assured.
Ouyang Jun?
That name sounds
suspiciously boastful.
What was that?
I heard something like "full."
I mean full of yourself.
Well, thank you then.
By the way, General,
that wheel is broken.
I forgot to tell you.
We won't make it halfway
before it falls apart.
I think we should get it fixed
before leaving.
How long will that take?
Fixing it isn't the problem;
it's just we need to unload
the heavy stuff first,
otherwise it'll be hard to work on.
Go ahead and fix it.
Your surname?
None of your business.
Qiao will accompany me on this trip.
You all stay at the mansion.
If there's any urgent matter,
send a message by carrier pigeon.
Do not delay.
Don't worry, General.
Ouyang Jun, let's go.
Yes.
Please go upstairs.
Private room guests have arrived!
Please take care.
Honored guests, are you
looking for lodging?
Our inn has all kinds of rooms:
some with mountain views,
some with lake views,
others overlooking the street.
-Which kind would you prefer?
-Where are we?
Cangshan Town.
I want...
No matter where you are,
you should enjoy life.
You are the only person
in this world who truly matters to me.
I hope you can live a better life.
Give us the best rooms.
Certainly!
Please come in, everyone.
Lu Xin?
That really hurts.
Seems my efforts weren't wasted.
Someone has finally learned to enjoy life.
Well, someone told me that
occasional indulgence
can't really be considered wasteful.
Shuang,
since when have you been so willing
to spend money?
Is my room like this too?
This is our room.
Our?
I booked two rooms.
We have three men and three women,
so three people per room—
cozy but just right.
Money
should be
spent when necessary
and saved when possible.
What are you listening to?
You walk so quietly.
I don't think it's my light footsteps,
but rather your heavy thoughts.
Aren't you here to see Shuang?
Why don't you go in?
What are you doing?
Jin'an has something to tell you.
The carriage is ready.
We can leave
for Cang Mountain
early tomorrow morning.
Got it.
I'll be going then.
Wait.
Qiao
bought a lot of candy.
We can't eat it all,
so take some back with you.
Let me try a piece.
It'll be a waste if you try.
Thank you.
I thought
you bought this candy...
Just let me try some.
He's been standing at the door
for quite a while.
Are you asleep?
Yes, I am.
Then chat with me for a while.
What stage are
you and Jin'an at now?
What?
What do you mean by "what stage?"
You two are always flirting.
Do you really think I can't tell?
Actually, Jin'an
is quite nice.
He's handsome,
considerate,
and knows how to make you happy.
Back then, he risked his life
to take Li Zhangyi hostage.
It was to help you and the Changfeng Army
enter the city, right?
When you were unconscious,
he refused to eat or drink,
and stayed by your side for a whole day.
I've never seen a man
so completely devoted.
It's a shame though,
he's a bit weak.
Two punches and he'd be down.
If there's ever a real emergency,
he'd be useless for sure.
That man in black who appeared earlier,
what's your relationship with him?
Why do you want to know?
I heard that man in black
defeated the Yao Army and was unstoppable.
The people all say he's a great hero.
No wonder you can't decide.
Are you considering him as well?
You're getting more and more ridiculous.
Even if you don't think about him,
he might think about you.
If he only cared about fame and fortune,
why did he disappear
as soon as the battle was over?
When it comes down to it,
it was just an act of a hero
coming to the aid of a damsel.
That's a headache.
One is handsome and considerate,
while the other is strong and brave.
How should you choose?
Just take them both.
Nonsense.
Men can have multiple wives,
so why can't women do the same?
One could
accompany you on the battlefield,
while the other stays at home
for romance and pleasure.
Just imagine how wonderful that would be.
You'll truly be a pioneer among women
and a model for us all.
I know you have doubts about me.
But you're a good person.
And I really have no reason
to dislike you.
Have you forgotten
that I caused you to fall off that cliff?
I'll never forget that.
But there were reasons for it.
Besides, I'm
still alive, aren't I?
Stop pretending to be nice.
I know
when I was imprisoned,
you went to see the General
to plead for me,
and that's why I was pardoned.
You did that just to win me over.
I won't be indebted to you.
Do you think
everyone will fall for
your cold and aloof act?
Let me tell you,
I helped you for no other reason
than Lu Xin.
Miss Lu?
If Lu Xin hadn't pleaded for you,
you'd probably
still be rotting in prison.
A girl
lowers her pride
and devotes herself entirely to you,
and what do you do?
You just sulk all day,
showing no gratitude,
and treating her with contempt.
The falling flower may have feelings,
but the flowing water is indifferent.
If she continues to pursue me like this,
she'll only get hurt.
That may be true,
but you don't have to be so cold.
You can be nicer
and still make your point.
Though the world is vast,
this dragon blood herb
is a miraculous medicine
that only grows on Cang Mountain.
Even in
the prosperous and magnificent Yunjing,
it's nearly impossible to find.
What's so special about it?
Is it the Supreme Lord's
Golden Elixir?
If that's the case,
our quest for this medicine
seems quite challenging.
We came here
fully prepared for a difficult journey.
At worst,
we'll just have to put in more effort.
We'll find it eventually.
Ladies and gentlemen,
your noodles are ready.
Let me.
Careful, it's hot.
Sir,
do you know
how long it takes from here
to Cang Mountain?
Are you folks heading to Cang Mountain?
Could it be for
the dragon blood herb?
You know about the dragon blood herb too?
Around here,
every household grows it.
We have as much as you want.
There's even some under your table.
So...
So beautiful.
Your arms must be tired.
Put it down now.
Why give me that face?
I did say this herb
grows exclusively on Cang Mountain,
but I never said it's rare.
There's plenty indeed.
Never mind.
At least we've found what we came for.
Let's buy some
and take it back to Lucheng.
That won't do.
Although this herb is very potent,
its effectiveness
depends entirely on freshness.
Once picked for more than half a day,
it becomes no better than dried grass.
So it must be consumed fresh on the spot,
and it needs to be taken
for at least three days
to be effective.
This young lady really knows her stuff.
The ones under your table
are quite fresh.
You've said enough.
You may get back to work.
Health comes first.
Since we're already here,
let's follow Lu Xin's advice
and stay for a few more days.
I suppose that's the only choice.
Hey, Missy.
Wait for me.
Missy, let's take a break.
We've been walking for two hours.
Missy!
Wait up.
You're walking too fast. I can't keep up.
You're weak.
Don't hold me back.
This poor girl,
selling herself to save her mother.
She really is.
How pitiful.
This girl is truly unfortunate.
What do you want to do?
Help her.
Why?
I've seen this kind of act
too many times.
It's all fake,
just some old tricks we've used ourselves.
Don't believe it.
Let go.
I'm telling the truth.
Don't be rash.
Take this money.
Go home and get treatment for your mother.
May I ask your name, Miss?
I'm willing to serve you in any way
to repay your grand gesture.
No need to repay me.
Once the illness is cured,
just eat well
and live a good life.
What a kind person!
Thank you, benefactor! Thank you!
This girl.
Even more stubborn than a mule.
So many people.
How lively.
Everyone!
Our tavern has been open
for five years now,
and thanks to your patronage,
business is booming.
Today,
we're holding a wine-drinking competition.
Anyone
who participates
will get 30% off their meal.
Great! Great!
And the winner
can eat for free!
Great! Great!
Would any
of our guests like to
join the competition?
I'll do it!
Me!
Any other guests willing to compete?
Let's go join the competition too.
You can drink?
I can't,
but you can.
Didn't the owner say
just participating can get us 30% off?
Alcohol is bad for your health.
Don't go.
That's because you don't know
how much Shuang can drink.
She knows her limits.
I know my limits.
A young lady is participating too!
Please. Please.
She really knows her limits.
Right?
What?
Nothing.
Let's have a drink.
Everyone!
Let the competition
begin!
Great! Great!
Drink! Drink!
Stop drinking
if you can't take it anymore.
Don't fuss.
Drink up!
That's about enough. They're all...
Well done!
Nice!
Everyone!
I declare
tonight's winner
is this young lady!
Nice! Well done!
Everyone!
Thanks to the owner's generosity
for waiving my bill.
Everyone's drinks tonight
are on me.
Great! Great!
She's had too much to drink.
Let's go.
Let's go dancing too.
Come on, let's dance!
♪ Memories dye the red thread completely ♪
♪ A tiny spark burns in the heart ♪
♪Asking the moon, does the old friend
seem as at first sight ♪
♪ Silently the threads of affection pull ♪
♪ Yet they turn into
this endless longing ♪
Jin'an, come dance with us!
Come on.
♪ The bonds of this life
are hard to untangle ♪
Come and dance.
♪ Heaven and Earth cycle endlessly ♪
♪ In a fleeting glance,
affection lingers ♪
♪ I wish to stay with you,
watching fate fade like smoke ♪
♪ Counting the days and nights ♪
♪ Gently caressing every inch of time ♪
♪ Traversing mountains and rivers,
no separation remains ♪
Come on.
♪ No regrets in this life ♪
♪ Seeking a lifetime side by side ♪
♪ Eternity in a moment ♪
♪ Braving life and death to fulfill
the vow of growing old together ♪
♪ Staying close even through partings,
never straying far ♪
♪ United as a song of promise ♪
♪ Encircling you and me ♪
♪ Endless longing
that cannot be expressed ♪
You look quite beautiful
when you're drunk.
I'm giving you a chance
to redeem yourself.
The Changfeng Army
is in need of talent right now.
Your martial skills are impressive.
Why not stay
and do something meaningful
for your country and people?
Your men
could also stay in the camp
and have proper jobs.
Lady Li.
Here.
You've impressed me once again today.
Cheers.
Lady Li.
I don't mean to gossip,
but has Miss Qiao
always been this stubborn?
Today at the market,
we met someone selling herself
for her mother's burial fee.
I told her it was a scam,
but she...
But she wouldn't believe it.
Exactly.
She emptied her money pouch for that girl.
I checked afterward,
and that woman
specifically targets passersby.
Even those egging her on nearby
was part of the scam.
Qiao is the type
who appears tough
but has a soft heart.
Do you know
how she entered my General's Residence?
Stop hitting her!
She'll die if you keep going at her!
Stop!
Get up.
Come on.
Or she'll really be beaten to death.
Indeed.
Beating a defenseless woman
in broad daylight.
What kind of crime is this!
My Lord,
but we paid for this.
One is willing to beat,
the other willing to take it—
what crime is there in it?
That's right.
She voluntarily signed
this life-and-death agreement.
My Lord,
don't blame them.
They paid to hit me.
This is a business transaction.
These ropes
were also tied by myself.
If you pay,
you can beat me too.
What kind of business is this?
This...
-Thank you, My Lord.
Make way. Move.
Break it up.
Let's go.
Do you want me to take you to a doctor?
Are you hurt anywhere else?
I'm alright,
My Lord.
Why are you in this kind of business?
Their lives are hard,
and they're full of anger,
so they need someone to take it out on.
I've trained in martial arts
since childhood.
I can take a beating.
I see there are
many shops hiring assistants in town.
Why don't you try that instead?
I did.
They
complained about how much I eat,
and after just a few days,
they kicked me out.
What about your family?
Why don't they care about you?
They died
in the war.
What's your name?
You can call me Qiao, My Lord.
Qiao,
would you like to
come work for me?
Will I get enough to eat?
So this girl Qiao
has had a hard life too.
Qiao is just
this kind of person.
She'd rather be deceived herself
than have one more person
in this world suffer like she has.
I was wrong.
It won't happen again.
Cheers.
Bottoms up.
Miss. Miss.
Come dance with us!
Let's dance!
Why are you here?
Is this a good time?
Of course it is.
No, it's not.
Our General needs to rest.
You seem well-fed.
I noticed you were just drinking earlier
and barely ate anything.
Try some.
It smells wonderful.
Careful, it's hot.
Smell it. Doesn't it smell great?
-I can't take it anymore.
-Doesn't it smell great?
General, I'm too full.
The smell makes me feel like vomiting.
I'll go outside to digest a bit.
Is it really that bad?
Why did she leave?
Perhaps
she went to find more food.
Come on, have a try.
It tastes so good.
Really good.
Why aren't you eating?
Have some yourself, too.
Eat.
It's good.
Have another one.
You eat it.
I have something for you.
"The Tale of Mr. Bat."
Let me.
I've wanted to give this to you
for a while,
but
I never had the time.
Since we'll be staying here
for a few more days,
reading some books
might help pass the time.
Why does this
look different from what I usually read?
The paintings on this
are much more detailed.
Look,
what's this?
The original ending for Mr. Bat
was too tragic.
So I wrote my own version.
Although the story
isn't as dramatic as the original,
at least
everyone gets a happy ending.
When you read it,
you won't feel so sad.
You know what?
In this world,
how can everything go as one wishes?
Things that are already destined
should
not be forced.
But I believe
we make our own fate.
As long as you're determined,
you can definitely change the outcome.
Thank you.
No need to be so formal with me.
No,
it's not about Mr. Bat.
There are many things
I need to thank you for.
If it weren't for you,
how could the countless soldiers
and civilians of Lucheng
enjoy today's peace?
But there's one thing.
I'm afraid the matter of the man in black
can't be kept secret any longer.
But don't worry.
Although I've reported everything
truthfully,
I
didn't reveal your true identity.
I understand.
The higher you rise,
the more attention you attract.
You're trying to protect me.
But this way,
all your military merits and salary
will be gone.
This is
really unfair to you.
In that case,
I really am at a big disadvantage, right?
But don't worry,
I'll take care of it.
Just think about what you want.
Other than promotions and titles,
I'll give you
anything else you want.
My greatest wish
is to stay by your side forever.
Listen.
Things that have already come true
don't count as wishes anymore.
Think of another one.
If I must make a wish,
I hope that you,
who are invincible on the battlefield,
after leaving the battlefield,
could be like an ordinary woman—
someone who can feel fear,
hunger,
and cold;
someone who needs warmth
and protection from others.
General?
Gen...
Shuang.
Did you call me?
Shall we drink?
Let's drink!
Come on,
let's go get a drink.
Let's go
get a drink.
Let's go for a drink.
Come on.
Let's go.