=Love For Two Lives=
=Episode 13=
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Hong Guo'er.
Manners.
The Princess must've had a rough journey
coming all the way back here.
She needs more food.
I do.
I was in the desert alone
when I woke up.
I was starving on the way.
I was worried about you.
I sent out people looking for you.
Now I can finally rest assured
seeing you are safe.
Oh.
Where's your king?
When is he marrying me?
Princess.
I have to tell you the truth.
His Majesty
has a new Queen now.
What?
Don't be mad, Princess.
How about I send people
to escort you back home?
No.
I have to be the Queen.
I left Dongshan Kingdom to get married.
How can I go back like this?
Hong Guo'er.
Prepare water
for the Princess to clean up.
Your Majesty.
Don't play stupid with me.
If I can't get married,
the thousands of soldiers
in Dongshan Kingdom
won't let you off the hook so easily.
Princess.
The new Queen
is a witch.
She enchanted His Majesty.
The court failed to convince him.
She's even disrespectful
to Her Majesty.
Ay.
I'm getting old.
His Majesty
won't listen to me anymore.
Unbelievable!
She enchants my future husband?
Where is the witch?
I'll go see her.
You should finish
your meal first, Princess.
The witch is very strong.
What?
Lv Guo'er, show her the way.
Fei'er.
You are getting better and better.
One day you'll be
the head of this palace
and everyone will kneel before you.
It's because I have
you as my teacher, Aunt.
Where is the witch?
Come out.
Witch.
Show yourself.
We tried our best to stop her,
but she fought her way in.
Who are you?
Strong.
Handsome.
I like you.
You may leave now.
Yes.
Who are you?
How dare you break into
my resting palace?
What?
You are the King?
You are not quite good enough
to be my husband.
Are you Princess Xiangxiang?
So it's you, witch!
I'll kill you here and now.
Who said you can touch my Queen?
Your Majesty.
You are the ones who are unreasonable.
Did you forget about our engagement?
What do you want?
I'll give you three days
to get rid of her.
Otherwise,
the soldiers in Dongshan Kingdom
will tread over your Kingdom.
She's not kidding.
What a shame.
If I weren't engaged,
you can be my husband.
I'm talking about you.
It's so boring here.
Give me a tour around your palace.
What are you going to do
three days later?
Are you going to marry her?
Are you worrying about that she'll
take your place?
Don't flatter yourself.
I don't want to be your Queen.
She's so strong.
I'm afraid you can never win her.
Is that so?
Yeah.
In your language,
are you jealous?
Jealous?
I'm not.
No way.
Weird guy. Let's go, Zhenzhen.
You have a good taste,
Princess Xiangxiang.
These are all best of the best.
General Sa, let me take some of them.
I can take it.
Then why are you sweating so much?
You broke them?
I'm sorry, Princess.
I really like that bracelet.
Princess, I have a lot of bracelets.
You can have them all.
You are a handsome man,
so I'll let it pass.
♪Traces of time and space,
and forgotten galaxies♪
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪The rain touches the breath♪
♪Get close to you♪