A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 4
Today, we have a new student in our class.
Chen Qingqing.
Only the seat in the last row
is not taken.
You can sit over there.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello, I am your new deskmate.
I'm Chen Qingqing.
Situ Feng.
I don't care who you are
outside of school,
you must be friendly
to your classmates here.
Situ Feng.
The new semester has started.
Let's begin the class.
Please open your textbooks.
-What is she doing?
-What?
Is she crazy?
Ma'am, I'm ready. We can start now.
Chen Qingqing.
What are you doing?
Go back immediately!
Don't laugh!
I'll write a few questions for you to do.
After being home tutored
for so many years,
I finally know how it feels like
to study at college.
Do you think
if you pretend not to know me,
I would let it go?
I've given you the money.
What else do you want?
What about you? You even followed me here.
And you said you weren't my fan?
Hey, Situ Feng.
You are shameless.
I followed you?
Do you know
how unfortunate it was for me to meet you?
Do you know how much
I've suffered because of you?
I didn't know they would take
a photo of us and post it online.
This thing is over.
And...
do not mention it again,
or it will only get more complicated.
Do you think this is something
I could let go so easily?
Chen Qingqing, Situ Feng.
Stand up, the two of you.
On the first day of school,
you disrupted the classroom.
As a punishment,
you two will clean the classroom today.
The class is dismissed.
Stand up.
Goodbye.
-Goodbye, ma'am.
When will Your Highness
release another album?
-We like you so much.
Were the things I learned
as a child useful?
-Chen Qingqing.
-Yes!
Mr. Jin Taiyong, please teach me!
An ultimate move to win.
Front leg kick followed by
a 360-degree single leg whirlwind kick.
If you asked me a minute ago,
I would say they were useless.
But now,
I'll tell you,
they are very useful.
Excuse me, everyone, please move aside.
Chen Qingqing.
We can talk if you want.
Situ Feng.
Nice to meet you.
I would appreciate your advice.
Thank you.
That's her, the strange transfer student.
Let's go. Where did she come from?
That's her.
I don't know what trick she used
that she got to be Situ Feng's deskmate.
She's Situ Feng's stalker.
I heard she'd do anything
to get his attention.
She even kissed Situ Feng.
I'll say it one more time.
I'm not Situ Feng's stalker.
Aren't you his stalker?
I heard you told everyone
that you were his fiancée.
Hey, can you get your facts straight?
It was Situ Feng who begged me
to be his fiancée.
See, she said she is his fiancée herself.
Shameless.
-Who did you call shameless?
-You're shameless.
They don't really mean it.
-Let's go. We need to clean the classroom.
-Psycho.
So defensive.
That Situ Feng!
The teacher said clearly that
we should clean the classroom together.
But he got away.
What kind of person is he?
He really thinks he's as a superstar.
Then what does it make me?
Qingqing, you'd better keep a low profile
and stay out of trouble.
And remember what I told you,
-do not--
-Do not mess with Situ Feng.
Do you think I want to do that?
I don't want to have anything to do
with that jerk.
That's good.
And don't go against Miss Chen Xiao.
I didn't.
I'm serious.
Chen Xiao, known as the Old Witch,
has a reputation of being cold-blooded
and heartless.
Rumor has it that many years ago,
a student talked back to her in class.
And on the very same day,
he disappeared.
No one has ever seen him again.
That's horrible.
Anyway, we should focus on our studies.
Don't mess with the wrong people.
Okay.
You should clean the blackboard first.
Jerk!
That big jerk!
-Leaving me here alone--
-Chen Qingqing.
What?
Situ Feng didn't feel well,
so he went to the infirmary.
Give me that eraser.
You should mop the floor.
You still have a little conscience left.
-Well, Chen Qingqing...
-What?
The day at the wedding,
I didn't mean to lie to you.
I didn't know that Situ Feng...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I won't hold a grudge against you.
Hello? Hello, who's this?
A delivery for me?
What kind of delivery service is this?
Why do I have to come to the rooftop?
What a coincidence.
You two have even become deskmates.
But based on the way you look,
I don't think I have to worry.
-There won't be any rumors about you two.
-Hey, who the hell are you?
I'm Situ Feng's manager.
What are you doing?
For heaven's sake.
-Did you call your manager here
-You...
-to make me pay for the medical expenses?
-No...
Let me be clear. There's no way I'd pay!
Hey.
Do not assume everyone
is as bad as you are.
Are you trying to blame me?
Who brought me to your dad's wedding?
Who told everyone that I was your fiancée?
Who kissed me twice against my will?
Twice!
There are so many people out there.
Fine, I've given you the money.
And I've also helped you find your bag.
What else do you want from me?
Don't talk
as if you were the victim, okay?
Look at me.
I am the victim here.
No one has dared to hit me before.
You are the first one.
Fine.
Let me tell you this.
From now on,
I will hit you more often.
That's enough, stop fighting.
Take a look, did you post this?
What is it?
SITU FENG'S FIANCÉE
APPEARED IN MING DE COLLEGE
Who took such an ugly photo of me?
Who?
Who took it?
That's not the point.
Anyway, it's great
that you didn't post it.
I called you here today
to put an end to the rumors about you two.
If the media or fans ask about it,
I want you to say
that you are Situ Feng's assistant.
-Assistant?
Yes.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, you don't want to? That's great.
I don't want you to be my assistant too.
I don't want to have anything to do
with a jerk like you.
If you weren't a woman,
-I would have--
-What would you do?
I know what happened at the wedding.
He's young and ignorant. Don't mind him.
Please accept this.
What's this? Is it a check?
This is a VIP ticket
to Situ Feng's concert.
-Concert?
-Yes.
Why would I want to go to his concert?
This...
Could you afford a VIP ticket?
It is worth 10,000 yuan.
Well, don't make rash decisions.
This is my business card.
Call me after you think about it
thoroughly.
Call me.
Situ Feng.
Aren't you afraid that your image
will be ruined?
Well, let me tell you this.
From now on,
I will be your archenemy.
I will spare no effort
to talk bad about you everywhere.
Hey.
This girl is a pain in the neck.
How many times have I told you?
Don't put on a cold face every day.
People will be offended, okay?
Although, nobody will believe
the story about this fiancée of yours.
I have told you many times,
you must keep a good relationship
with your classmates. You are...
Can you let me finish before you leave?
Can't you respect me a little?
Do you have to be like this every time?
Let's go have dinner.
I have something to do.
What do you want to eat?
I'll get it for you.
There's no need.
I'll eat before I come back.
I'm leaving, bye.
Bye.
Hello, ma'am.
I want Boston lobster pasta.
I want my lobster shelled.
For my fruits,
I want Hokkaido Yubari melon.
And A bottle of the 1990 Romanee-Conti.
Thank you.
Chen Qingqing.
I don't think they serve those
in the canteen.
Aren't these the most basic things?
Then what do we have here?
We have mantis shrimps, noodles with
soybean paste, cantaloupe and grape juice.
The school is so big.
Where can I find information
about my dad?
Chen Qingqing, can I sit here?
It's you.
Yes, I am Xiaobi.
This is Xiaosi, Xiaoyi
and that's the class president.
You just transferred
to a new school today,
don't you feel lonely?
It's all right.
You dare go against the old witch
on your first day.
Are you really a fan of Situ Feng?
I heard you claimed to be
Situ Feng's fiancée.
There are too many rumors going around.
Which one of it is true?
Do you really want to know?
-Yes.
These are all confidential information.
You must trade it
with the information you have.
Not to brag,
but there are only a few things
in this school that we don't know.
Go ahead and ask.
If I want to know the information
of a Ming De graduate, who should I ask?
I remember the graduation information
of all previous students
are in the Student Council's office.
Then can you take me there? Now.
The Student Council's office
is not open to anyone.
Yes and you're not a sophomore,
they won't let you join them.
I see.
Is there another way?
Another way?
There is one.
Gu Nanxi is the current president
of the Student Council.
You can try and ask him.
Although he seems to be
very nice to everyone,
he does everything by the book.
Is that so?
I see.
Okay, we've told you everything we know.
Now, can you tell us
what is your relationship with Situ Feng?
Situ Feng is...
Come closer.
Let me tell you,
Situ Feng is a very careless man.
You know what?
How could he be--
Also...
Chen Qingqing.
You broke into
the Student Council's office
and sabotaged school property
in the first week of school.
-It's just a lame painting? So--
-Lame?
This was painted by the art master,
Burton Goldman.
He personally painted this
for our first chancellor.
It's the most memorable piece of art
in Ming De College.
Sir.
How much do you think I should pay for it?
How about 100,000 yuan?
What? 100,000 yuan?
-I--
-It's famous, you know.
If I don't pay...
what will happen?
If you don't pay?
Let me see.
Breaking into a forbidden area,
sabotaging school property
and refusing to pay...
-You'll be expelled.
-Sir!
I'll pay.
Can you give me some time?
Fine.
I'll give you a week.
Go.
Our chancellor...
This is bad.
It's 100,000 yuan?
Where can I get that much money?
Do I
really have to be
a fake assistant to Situ Feng?
Chen Qingqing, are you losing your mind?
How can you do that?
But what should I do?
Hey, Fangfang.
Hello? Qingqing.
Hello? Fangfang.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the library.
I'll come back later.
It's not appropriate
to make phone calls here.
I'm going to hang up now.
Okay.
What is she hiding?
Fangfang?
Qingqing?
Why are you here?
No, why are you here?
And why are you dressed like this?
I see you've been sneaking around
these days.
I don't know why you go out.
I was worried about you
so I followed you today.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Really?
So all this time,
you've been working here?
Actually, I came to Ming De College
on a scholarship.
It only covers my tuition and other fees.
So I have to earn money
to pay for everything else.
I see.
Fangfang, you should have told me--
Are you enjoying your chat?
You didn't even hear
the customer calling you.
I paid you to work,
not to have some kind of free party.
I'll deduct your pay.
Ma'am, you've deducted
almost all of my pay this month.
There won't be anything left for me.
Then go bring out the coffee right now,
or I won't pay you a penny.
Okay, I'll go.
Qingqing, I have to go back to work.
You can take a rest here.
Fangfang, don't work here anymore.
Let's make money together.
Making money is not that easy.
Trust me, with my brain,
making money is as easy as that.
Fangfang, don't hesitate.
You go in right now and say goodbye
to that vicious woman.
Tell her, "I quit!"
Fangfang, hurry up and go.
Go.
You can do it.
Gu Nanxi.
Don't act like you are so perfect.
You are only an illegitimate child.
You have no inheritance right.
Don't get me wrong. I didn't mean that.
As a member of the Gu family,
I just want to do my duty.
You and your mom should lay low.
I can kick you and your mom out
anytime I want.
Goodness.
Darling, here you are.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Chen Qingqing.
Why are you here?
Me?
I came to look for you, obviously.
Hey, who is this?
He is my cousin, Gu Donglin.
Your cousin? I see.
Donglin.
I really want to thank you
for taking care of my Nanxi.
There's not much coffee left in your cup.
Let me fill it up for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Donglin.
You see, I normally don't do
things like this.
But it doesn't matter.
I don't think you wanted
to drink it anyway.
You don't get to decide what I want.
Listen, Gu Nanxi.
I'm leaving now.
I'll talk to you next time.
Bye, Donglin.
Sorry, Gu Nanxi.
I happened to hear you two talk
from over there.
I couldn't stand him, so I came here.
I hope you could keep it a secret
from others.
If you need help in the future,
you can come to me.
I will do whatever I can.
You can help me now.
I want to join the Student Council.
-You want to join the Student Council?
-Yes.
But recruitment is already over.
I think there must be
something you can do.
Mr. Gu.
All right.
Let me ask you a question first.
Why do you want to join
the Student Council?
Because...
Because I'm looking for another way
to learn new things,
to train myself,
to make myself more serious
and more dedicated to my studies
so that I could be a useful member
of the society.
In that case,
I'll talk to the head of the departments.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you, Mr. Gu.
See you at school.
See you, Mr. Gu.
Bye, Mr. Gu.
Qingqing.
-Fangfang.
-Wasn't that Gu Nanxi?
Yes.
What did he say to you?
Nothing much.
I told him that I wanted to join
the Student Council.
-You want to join the Student Council?
-Yes.
Don't worry about that, Fangfang.
We should start our money-making
plan right now.
What are we going to do?
Well...
You will find out tomorrow.
Today is the first day of business
for Qingqing's Errands Service.
This is for you.
Chen Qingqing.
Just give it up already.
SEAT FOR RENT - HIS HIGHNESS
Don't you have enough money already?
Your errands service
should stop right now!
Why are you doing this?
Once you signed up to be my assistant,
if you breach the contract,
you'll need to compensate me more
than that painting is going to cost you.
Hey, you spilled the water!
Do you want me to push you into the pool?
You can joke about anything else,
but this.
Situ Feng, you...
Help!
Subtitle translation by Jing Chang