A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 22
Later in the afternoon today,
we shall be hearing from Situ Feng
in his press conference.
He will be performing a new song
as a rebuttal of his recent rumors
on plagiarism.
Will he be able to live up
to the expectation
and create an excellent song
within a short period of only three days?
Let us anticipate the outcome and see
how it is going to affect his career.
Please stay tuned.
Follow us for more updates.
Where is Situ Feng?
He's on his way.
I'll call him again.
Hello?
The line got disconnected.
What is this all about?
I've told you.
If anything goes wrong
with the press conference,
all of you can stop coming to work!
Of course nothing will go wrong.
Damn it.
-Daniel.
-You're here.
Where is Situ Feng?
I can't reach him at all.
Why is this happening?
The press conference will commence
in a short while.
Situ Feng and his team, please get ready.
You wait here. Let's go.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Daniel and I'm Situ Feng's manager.
I would like to thank every one of you
who made it here.
As you know,
Situ Feng is such a devoted artist.
He has worked so hard for this new album.
Just for your information--
Daniel, can you stop
beating around the bush?
Where is Situ Feng?
That's right. Is it because he wasn't able
to produce a new song so he chickened out?
Doesn't this mean he is admitting
to the plagiarism rumors?
Please give us your honest response.
-Yes.
Calm down, everyone.
We will definitely...
Just, please calm down...
We will give you an honest response.
I knew Situ Feng wouldn't be able
to create a new song within three days.
Sir, we have to celebrate.
-Come.
-Let's make a toast.
-What is this?
-Exactly!
What kind of press conference is this?
Situ Feng, I have faith in you.
I believe you will come here
and prove everyone wrong.
-Can you explain what is happening?
-Who does he think he is?
I knew it. I knew Feng would appear.
I'm sorry, sir!
Hello, everyone.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Today's press conference
is mainly being held for me
to clarify about the plagiarism rumors.
What I want to say is that
I did not plagiarize anyone's song.
As a musician and a songwriter,
it's an absolute shame
to plagiarize other people's songs.
Thus, I, Situ Feng
will swear on my name that
what is being accused of me is not true.
We're now still investigating the matter.
Thus, the main song of the album
shall be officially changed
to this new song that I've written
which I will be performing it live today.
I hope you will all like it.
-Go ahead.
-Hi.
I'm sure all of us are aware that
the main song of this album
will need to grab the listeners' attention
as soon as they hear it
and it shall determine
the quality of this album.
May I know, given the time limit
how did you manage to complete the song?
Or was this new song casually written?
Were you just trying to get done it with?
I hope you can listen to it
and judge for yourself.
Actually, before I came today,
I thought about giving up.
To give up clarifying for myself.
But I realized later that
this is something very precious to me
and no matter what the outcome is,
I have to try my best.
Hence, I came.
I'm here to prove my love for music.
This song, "To Be Your Love"
was written
for someone who has been
supporting me unconditionally.
Someone who's very important
and special to me.
I hope you will like this song.
Lights touched your naughty curls
Lights kissed on your rosy cheeks
Lights quietly lit up
The freckles on your face
When you feel down
When you couldn't speak
How do I make you smile again
Get your cuteness back
Turning through the alleys
Where we first met
Those absurd moments
What is to be anticipated?
Let me stay in your heart
You affected me so deeply
I would give you my everything
No matter how it will end
The journey is sweet
Let me occupy your love
Never say no and hide it
I won't hesitate to kiss you
You'll be my exclusive sweetheart
Thank you.
-Sir, please wait.
-Sir...
Hang on, everyone.
-Daniel, I'll leave this to you.
-No problem, see you then.
You may ask your questions to me.
What did you say?
The culprit has been found?
Lin Yiyang was the culprit?
What is the official date
of release for the new album?
It'll be soon.
All my dear media representatives,
there's an update that the real culprit
of this case has been caught.
We can now confirm it was all a setup
from the start.
Are you Lin Yiyang?
Who the hell are you?
We're supporters of His Highness.
You were the one
who started the rumors, right?
Aren't you leaving?
Go.
Take care!
Hurry.
-Now!
-Let's get him!
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
Thanks for your gift yesterday.
I thought you were going to ignore me.
Did you like it?
Of course.
Well...
How are you going to repay me?
That new song was written for you.
It was great. I loved it.
Thank you.
I should be the one thanking you.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have made it through
that quickly.
Ye Bei, what's wrong?
Situ Feng, your fans are crazy!
Where's Lin Yiyang?
He is stuck back there!
Qingqing, wait for me here.
Be careful, Situ Feng.
-Punch him!
-Kill him!
-Carry on!
-Carry on, guys!
-Kill him.
Punch harder!
We will punch you if we see you again.
You'd better watch out!
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm still alive.
Have you forgotten?
I'm good with being attacked by people.
Why did you help me?
Because I can't just watch
you get beaten up.
Don't you know?
I was behind everything.
Yes, but I should thank you instead.
Having gone through the whole incident
made me grow as a person.
I did horrible things to you.
Why are you still being nice to me?
Because...
we're friends.
One, two, three, four, five, six!
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers.
A peck of pickled peppers
Peter Piper picked.
Good morning!
Today is the day my errands service
resume its business.
Morning call!
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Hello, sir.
Hello, good morning, sir.
Listen to Qingqing
Wake up, wake up
What's wrong with everyone today?
What's up with these early morning calls?
It's the weekend.
Why should I wake up so early?
Whatever.
I'm going back to sleep
for ten more minutes.
Qingqing, are you going back to sleep?
Fangfang, where are you going?
The library.
We have to go right now.
Fangfang, slow down.
Get over here.
What's wrong with everyone?
What did I miss?
Why are they walking like zombies?
Qingqing, it's two more weeks
to the finals.
The major finals
before our semester break starts.
Our major finals?
But isn't this a little too much?
Everyone has to queue up
to enter the library.
Let's go, shall we?
Okay.
Fangfang.
So many books?
Our college's examinations are tough.
They're difficult and strict.
It's worse than hell.
Although some students here
are from really affluent families,
but everyone will be treated equally
during finals.
If they failed to score well
for the exams,
the college will put up a notice.
Put up a notice?
Once they are listed in the notice,
it'll be difficult
for them to apply for scholarships
or good universities in the future.
Ming De is well known
for its academic achievements.
There's going to be strong competitions.
-I'm going to look for a book.
-Okay.
Qingqing, why are you here?
It's the finals week.
Fangfang brought me here to study.
What about you?
I'm here to study
the topics for our finals.
-Topics?
-Yes.
It's our college's regulations.
If we pick a national level topic,
there are going to be bonus points.
You're worthy of your title, Mr. Gu.
Qingqing,
do you want to have dinner together?
Sure.
I have something to discuss with you too.
I'll see you tonight.
-See you later.
-See you.
Right.
Let me tell you this.
Even if you get those bonus points,
I'm going to do better than you
in the finals.
Situ Feng.
Your fan club's representative came.
These are all gifts for you.
-It's so hard to remember.
-Look, your favorite chocolate.
I'm going to the library.
-Where?
-The library.
I'm going to study. Don't stop me.
Where did he say he was going?
The library?
Talk about when pigs fly!
I want to straighten up.
Sir, are you leaving us?
Sir, I admit I was careless
in handling Situ Feng's case,
but please don't leave us.
What I meant was
I want to live a normal life now
and stop causing troubles for myself.
As for the two of you,
you're always going to be my good friends.
I knew it.
Three heads are better than one.
He would never leave us.
Yes!
I'm leaving now.
Sir, where are you going?
The library.
Where the hell is Qingqing?
C is the answer.
Thanks.
How much did you score
for the monthly test?
It wasn't bad, I guess.
An average of 60 marks.
I scored 142 marks for my English test.
How about Math?
I failed.
What was your score?
It was 15.
How about this?
I will teach you Math like Einstein.
You can teach me English.
Wasn't Einstein an inventor?
Was he?
I thought Thomas Edison was an inventor?
-It's DaVinci!
-He was the one.
-Yes.
What do you feel like eating?
If I tell you what I want to eat,
would you buy them for me?
Of course, as long as
it can be found in Yuncheng.
But if it can't be found in Yuncheng,
I would take the plane.
I was joking.
Let me think.
I feel like having street food.
-Street food?
-Yes.
Don't you know?
There are stalls selling beer,
skewers and baked eggplants.
Well, now that's a problem.
I've never eaten those before.
What's the fun to be always eating
at fancy restaurants?
The real hidden gems are on the streets.
We should go and experience it ourselves.
Shall we go?
Of course.
Let's go.
Why don't we take the car?
Why drive? Let's walk.
This is how you can fully experience
-living as an ordinary citizen.
-Okay.
This place looks really nice.
I think so too.
Thank you.
Come. Cheers!
-Nanxi, I...
-Right, I...
-You first.
No, you first.
Ladies first.
It's about Situ Feng.
What is it about him?
Like what you said to me,
Situ Feng has sacrificed a lot for me.
Hence,
I want to be serious
about our relationship.
I want to tell him
that I like him.
But...
-But what?
-Goodness.
But...
he still doesn't know
that I am Qingchen.
Are you serious? You haven't told him yet?
I am serious, Gu Nanxi.
I couldn't find a suitable time
to tell him.
You should have told him by now.
What should I do?
Should I just keep it a secret forever?
Chen Qingqing, Situ Feng
is a very direct and sincere person.
If he finds out that his friends
hasn't been truthful to him,
he's going to be mad.
But I think,
he will eventually understand.
So, if you really want
to take your relationship seriously,
you should be honest with him.
I already knew about it,
but I haven't told him yet.
If things go wrong later,
we'll have to carry the burden together.
Thank you so much.
Why are you thanking me?
Cheer up.
This is not the Chen Qingqing I know.
That's right, I'm a fearless witch!
Sir, I'd like half a dozen
bottles of beer!
It's examination period.
So what?
I've never failed my exams before!
I'm so glad to have you as my friend.
Let's drink to our heart's content.
Can you still drink?
Of course.
-I'm all right.
-Didn't you say you were good at drinking?
Was this what you called good at drinking?
Be careful.
I'll call a cab for you.
Hey.
Be careful.
I'm going to show Feng
that Chen Qingqing
doesn't deserve his love.
Gu Nanxi.
I thought you were my best friend!
My best friend
and the girl I love
treated me like a fool.
It hurts!
Is that what you think of me?
Am I such a horrible person?
Situ Feng, can we talk?
You know what?
You're right, I am materialistic.
That's why I approached Situ Feng.
Subtitle translation by June Tian