A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 20
Qingqing.
Why are you walking so fast?
Situ Feng, tell me.
You and Lan
were rolling on the ground just now.
What exactly were you two doing?
There was a wind,
-then--
-Wind? Nonsense.
What happened to your hand?
-I'm all right.
-Show me.
It's only a small scratch.
Hey, Qingqing.
Is Lan really your best friend?
Yes, why?
It's nothing.
I think that you haven't met
a lot of people yet.
You still need to learn
how to read people.
Don't just pour your heart out to anyone.
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
Hey, there's a scarecrow.
Hold this.
Qingqing.
You really like flying kites, don't you?
When I was young,
I flew a kite once with my parents.
That's my only memory of them.
I understand
how you feel.
My mom left me
when I was young. And my dad,
you've met him.
He's never cared about me
since I was young.
Every time we meet,
we'll get into a fight.
I've wanted to talk to you about this.
Perhaps your dad
is not as mean as you think.
My dad?
He thinks that I've brought disgrace
upon him by becoming a singer.
He would love to disown me.
That's not true.
Let me show you something.
Remember that last time you got sick?
I went to your house to visit you.
I walked into the wrong room at that time.
I accidentally went into his study.
Situ Feng?
In fact,
your dad loves you more
than you can imagine.
He just doesn’t know
how to express himself.
I actually envy you.
I've been trying hard
to get used to a life
without my parents.
I've become so tough.
Even if no one likes me,
I don't care.
Sometimes I would fly a kite alone
and that's when
I would feel
that no matter how hard I try,
I couldn't make the kite fly.
Then, I would think,
if someone
could stay by my side,
how nice
it would be.
Qingqing.
I have something to tell you.
You were the one
who helped me overcome my darkest moment.
If possible,
I hope that I could always
keep you company.
Ever since I met you,
I've noticed
that I've started to care more and more
about what you think.
Qingqing.
I...
I like you.
Situ Feng.
Actually...
There you are.
Mr. Chen asked me to come
and look for you.
There are jackals around.
Hurry up and come home with me.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Let's walk together.
-Sure.
It's getting late.
It's time for me to go home.
Didn't you say that my grandpa asked you--
Actually, I wasn't only doing
Mr. Chen a favor.
As your best friend,
I also wanted to check him out for you.
I wanted to make sure
that he is compatible with you.
When we were hanging the bed sheets...
Let's go downtown tomorrow.
It's far more interesting
than this small village.
Sure.
We can ask Qingqing to come with us.
You're a city boy.
Don't you find the life here
really boring and intolerable?
Not at all.
I wanted to see the place
where Qingqing grew up.
I think that
this is a really good place.
You can't stop talking about Qingqing.
I don't think that you two
are just classmates.
You obviously care about her.
That's right.
We have been through a lot together.
To me, she's not just
an ordinary classmate.
Actually, an outstanding guy like you
shouldn't be hanging out
with an ugly and poor girl.
Why don't you consider me?
Hey!
Although Chen Qingqing
doesn't have great looks,
in my opinion, she's a great girl.
I won't let you badmouth her.
We outsiders probably worried too much.
You have good taste in men.
Let's go.
Grandpa.
It's inappropriate
for a young man and a young lady
to wander around in the mountains.
He's going to spend the night here.
Hurry up and tidy his room.
There's no electricity here.
You won't be able to see anything later.
Mr. Chen.
There's no electricity?
Grandpa.
This is unbelievable.
Are you not providing electricity?
We're living in a village.
That's how impoverished this place is.
Mr. Chen, that's not what I meant.
I will help Qingqing out.
Why don't we
-sit here?
-Sure.
Here.
Situ Feng has done so much for me,
yet I've been lying
to him this whole time.
Qingqing.
-Yes?
-How do you feel
about what happened
this morning?
Situ Feng.
Can you give me some time
to think about it?
I will give you an answer later.
Look.
The stars tonight are so pretty.
Yes, they are.
Situ Feng.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to fix the wires.
You know how to do that?
Yes.
-The electricity is back on.
-Yes.
-Qingqing.
-Yes?
-I need to tell you something.
-What is it?
I...
I have to leave.
Right now?
I'm going to release my new album soon.
My agency has arranged for me
to get some training in Korea.
Daniel has already left.
I will meet them there.
Let me take you to the airport.
You don't have to.
Stay with your grandpa.
I'm going to go now.
Be careful on the road.
Qingqing.
I really had a good time
these past two days.
I'm going to go now.
Qingqing.
See you later.
Travel safely.
Remember to give me a call.
Go inside. It's cold out here.
Grandpa, you're awake.
The light?
Situ Feng fixed it.
Where is he?
He just left.
Why didn't he tell me?
He didn't want to disturb your sleep.
He's quite thoughtful.
Grandpa.
I want to tell Situ Feng the truth.
If you think it's worth it,
you can make your own decision.
You'll be the one who will bear
the consequences anyway.
KOREA
Chen Qingqing.
When are you going to call me?
Hello, Qingqing?
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I'm going back to campus tomorrow,
so I was packing my luggage.
My grandpa forced me
to bring a lot of things.
Are you going to bed now?
It's still early.
I can talk to you for a while.
Qingqing, let's do a video call.
No!
I mean,
there was a power cut.
You know, the power went out.
It's really dark.
You won't be able to see anything.
Fine.
You were training all day.
Was it tiring? Were you exhausted?
It was all right.
It wasn't really tiring.
I had nothing to do just now.
So...
So I kind of missed you.
Hey.
Situ Feng.
Stand by the window.
The window?
Hey, Qingqing.
Don't tell me that you came to Korea?
Situ Feng.
You haven't removed
your makeup yet, have you?
That's right. I haven't.
Qingqing, where are you?
Are you really in Korea? I don't see you.
Did the liquid foundation
get into your brain?
Haven't you cleansed your brain?
I don't have the money to go there.
Are you really not here?
I'm really not.
Situ Feng.
Look outside the window.
The moon is so round today.
It's indeed very round.
What should I do?
I'm really
not sleepy at all right now.
How about this?
I will sing you a song.
Which song?
The title track of my new album.
-Am I the first listener?
-That's right.
You've just got a Super VIP pass.
Hey, Situ Feng.
Hold on.
This is such an important song.
I need to prepare something.
Prepare what?
Change the frequency to 72.5MHz.
You're currently listening
to Ming De College Campus Radio.
Idol singer, Situ Feng, is bringing you
the title track of his newest album.
The name of the song...
It's a secret.
I'm going to sing now.
Wounds are smoothened by memories
Thank you for being here
There are too many memories
Our worlds begin to cross path
You exist in my past
Like a novel
The stories are hidden under a tree
Quietly waiting for you to pass by
Waiting for you to pass by
This song is great.
I'm certain that this song
will be really popular.
What should I do?
It's even harder for me to sleep now
after hearing this song.
How about I sing you another song?
Sure.
Do you have another song?
What should I sing?
Hey, Qingqing?
Qingqing?
Good night.
Chen Qingqing.
I'm not around. Who are you going
to see a movie with?
How did you know?
I've planted an informer around you.
It's Gu Nanxi, right?
Don't change the topic.
Tell me. Who's going with you?
Fangfang doesn't have to work today,
so we decided to go watch a movie.
All right.
Go to the movies with me when I come back.
I pity myself.
I've only watched a few movies this year.
Chen Qingqing.
Welcome back.
Come on.
I've arranged a celebration for you.
Let's go eat together.
Thank you, Lin Yiyang.
I'm going to the movies with Fangfang.
I'm busy.
Aren't you going to eat?
Let's eat together.
I'm not hungry. I don't want to eat.
-Qingqing.
-Fangfang.
I'm so hungry. Let's go eat.
Perfect.
I've reserved a table
at the restaurant across the street.
Let's go eat together.
It's a free meal.
Let's go eat.
Feel free to order anything.
You don't have to be modest.
Chen Qingqing.
I think you look prettier
after you came back from your hometown.
What's gotten into Lin Yiyang?
He just complimented me.
Did you hear that? Pretty?
Well,
I think I will go to the bathroom first.
I know this place well.
Let me take you there.
I can go there on my own.
I need to go to the bathroom too.
Chen Qingqing.
I want to talk to you alone.
There's nothing
that we need to discuss alone.
Fangfang is waiting for me.
Qingchen.
Or
should I call you
the granddaughter of Chen Xiaotian,
the wealthiest man in Jincheng?
Chen Qingqing.
Did you investigate me?
You blew your cover by going home.
No.
Actually, your background
simply catches people's attention.
But don't worry.
I'm not interested in you.
One more thing.
Stay away from Situ Feng.
What does this have to do with Situ Feng?
I know.
You two are close.
But have you ever thought about it?
If Situ Feng finds out
that you've been lying to him,
what will happen?
If the press and Situ Feng's fans find out
that he has been lying to them,
what's going to happen?
"A liar who has fooled his fans."
This kind of negative coverage
will ruin his reputation.
Lin Yiyang, you're distorting the truth.
No one will believe you.
I can make up any scandals.
By the way,
Situ Feng is about
to release his new album.
Imagine how his reputation
could be destroyed by you.
Why are you doing this to Situ Feng?
Because he doesn't deserve love.
Is this because of Lan Xinyu?
It happened a long time ago.
-Lin Yiyang, why can't you let it go?
-Chen Qingqing.
You don't understand.
Anyway, Situ Feng's career
is in your hands.
It's up to you.
Let's go.
Qingqing, what took you two so long?
They've served all the dishes.
Go ahead and eat.
What happened just now,
you know I didn't do it on purpose.
I hope
that we could get along peacefully
from now on.
Welcome back, Chen Qingqing.
Is the movie over?
Can you talk on the phone now?
Qingqing, why don't you answer it?
It's just a crank call.
Hello, Gu Nanxi?
Qingqing is right next to me.
I'm not here.
She has fallen asleep.
Should I wake her up?
All right, bye.
Situ Feng must've made Gu Nanxi call you
in order to talk to me.
What happened between you two?
We had a small fight.
It's not a big deal.
You've worked hard.
Go home and get some rest.
We'll soon start promoting your new album.
Daniel, take me back to school.
There's something I need to do.
What do you want to do there?
Go home and rest first.
Go back to school first.
All right. I'll listen to you.
Back to school.
Come on. Let's go.
Talk to him.
I'll go back to the dorm first.
When did you come back?
I came here straight from the airport.
You must be exhausted
from all the training.
Why didn't you go home and rest?
Because...
I miss you.
Qingqing.
I've been standing here for too long.
My legs are numb.
Can you give me a hand?
Sure.
Give it to me.
No.
You're so stupid.
Qingqing.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
My battery ran out.
I see.
Qingqing.
Have you eaten yet?
Is there something
that you want to ask me?
Go ahead and ask.
I have a feeling that you're avoiding me.
Why is that?
Do you remember
when you were at my place,
I promised to give you an answer?
I remember.
When I came back,
I thought hard about it.
So...
I have the answer now.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes.
I think...
I think
it's better for us to stay as classmates.
As normal friends.
Are you sure about this?
Don't you like me at all?
Yes.
I'm sure about it.
I don't like you at all.
Oh, right. I still have work to do.
I have to go back.
Qingqing, Situ Feng is in trouble.
What happened?
IDOL SINGER, SITU FENG,
IS ACCUSED OF PLAGIARIZING.
How did this happen?
Situ Feng released his new album today.
Many people soon discovered
that this song is very similar
to another original song on the internet.
Although I don't know much about music,
a lot of musicians have pointed out
that there's a possibility of plagiarism.
After all, that song
was released two weeks ago.
Therefore,
the press is talking about this matter.
Wounds are smoothened by memories
Thank you for being here
There are too many memories
Our worlds begin to cross path
Where is Situ Feng right now?
Does he know about this?
I've just asked him.
He's at the agency.
He probably has heard of it.
Gu Nanxi, there's something I need to do.
I have to go back to my dorm.
There's no way to prevent a thief
who lives under your roof.
Did I give you my permission?
Lin Yiyang.
I knew you were the one who did it.
There's no evidence to prove
that we stole the music sheet.
I'm going to do everything
to make him miserable.
Stop me if you can.
Quit now.
Quit? What's in your head?
I didn't know Situ Feng
was this kind of person.
I've recorded what you said.
Situ Feng's reputation will be ruined.
Subtitle translation by Judy Lu