ADAPTED FROM THE WEBCOMIC YI REN ZHI XIA
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
ALL ACTIONS AND ABILITIES PERFORMED SHOULD NOT BE IMITATED
Members of Sinister Pleasure
are inside the room.
Yuan Tao and Fool should have recovered by now
from the Ganbei Grassland battle.
Why didn't they join us for dinner?
Mr. Xia,
are you free for a chat?
We booked a private room
because we wanted to eat in peace.
Lyu Liang,
when did you become this detestable?
Leave.
I told you to leave. Didn't you hear me?
What is Lyu Liang doing here?
It seems
I have no choice but to speak with you.
Am I right?
Mr. Xia,
please clear the table.
We can have a nice chat after this.
Yes, sir.
Erzhuang, did you see that?
That's not the Lyu family's Soul Whisperer.
What was that?
I'm not sure either.
We must observe them before making a move.
This is more like it.
Only when we're united
can we work toward our goal.
I've implanted the memory related to that woman
into your brains.
I only have one request.
Find that person
at all costs.
-Yes, sir! -Yes, sir!
You must be careful when you go inside.
Don't worry.
Lyu Liang, wait for me!
Come after me!
I'm number one!
You cheated!
These are the remaining coins from this afternoon.
Hold onto them.
It has only been a few days.
What's with the grand display?
Who are you?
Have you erased your own memories too?
Who gave that to you?
You.
Unlock your memories
and tell me the truth.
I gave you two pieces.
Where's the other one?
Lyu Liang,
you weren't using the Lyu family's Soul Whisperer just now.
What was that?
You're still as shameless as always,
Zhang Chulan.
Why don't you check this out first?
No, you must not go back.
We must not let Master know about this.
What epiphany did you receive
for you to say something like that?
Dummy.
Let's go. We're running out of time.
I'm coming.
One of them is my grandfather.
Who's the other person?
Duanmu Ying.
Just like your grandfather,
she is one of the 36 Thieves
and one of the creators of the Eight Supremes.
Her supreme is called Double Quan Palm.
You asked me what I used just now, right?
I was using Double Quan Palm.
Soul Whisperer
is just a small part of Double Quan Palm.
Now I wield one of the Eight Supremes too.
So why are you looking for her?
I want to clarify something with her,
and I'll kill her after that.
Is she still alive?
Soul Whisperer.
Double Quan Palm.
Soul Whisperer?
Ms. Bao!
What's wrong?
Why are you so agitated?
Ms. Bao, don't you understand?
Soul Whisperer is Double Quan Palm!
What's Soul Whisperer's specialty?
It can manipulate memories!
You suddenly appeared after the Jiashen Calamity
and don't remember any of it.
Have you ever suspected that your memories were tampered with?
The only Eight Supremes that affects memories
is Double Quan Palm.
The wielder is called Duanmu Ying!
Memories?
I'm sure Duanmu Ying knows your identity and background.
We have to locate her before Lyu Liang.
How can we find her?
Erzhuang!
Erzhuang isn't replying to me.
Xu San.
NDT EXPRESS
Erzhuang is an entity
under the highest level of confidentiality.
Not only did you two steal my glasses,
but you're also posing me a problem.
Xu San, this concerns Ms. Bao's memories.
Two generations of Xus have protected her.
Now, we can finally find out her background.
What's stopping you here?
Chulan, you don't need to provoke me.
I know.
You want to locate Duanmu Ying
through Erzhuang.
-Right? -That's right.
Lyu Liang is also looking for Duanmu Ying.
That's why we need to find her before he does.
Chulan, you should think twice.
The person you're looking for
is one of the wielders of the Eight Supremes.
Even Sinister Pleasure and the Ten Elders couldn't harm her.
Xu San,
we're not here to negotiate a deal.
If you don't help us out,
we'll come up with a way ourselves.
You!
Doggy would've definitely helped me
if he were still around.
Fine, I'll bring you to Erzhuang.
But I don't know if she will help you.
Erzhuang is in the research lab.
You guys can reach out to her directly.
Ms. Bao, Zhang Chulan, hello.
We finally meet.
This is me, Erzhuang.
Don't feel sorry for me.
I'm already used to it.
What do you wish to ask me?
How did you end up like this?
Something happened to me some time ago.
I ended up like this.
My father utilized all of his resources
to create this machine.
Therefore, I managed to survive.
As repayment,
I have to help NDT
manage their system and data.
Anyway,
I was able to stay alive.
However, I'm living in a different way from you guys.
What about you?
Do you wish to live like this?
I thought it was fun when I was young.
I gradually realized
that although there was nothing and no one I couldn't find
in the world,
I could only stay trapped in this dark room.
I couldn't go anywhere.
Delicious food, fun games,
and all the interesting people
have nothing to do with me.
Afraid that I would be bored,
my father taught me Out-of-Body Technique.
I can leave my body in the form of electromagnetic waves.
That's the reason you see me everywhere.
Did you guys know?
I watched a lot of your videos
during the Outsider Martial Arts Contest.
I wanted to join the contest
with you at Mount Longhu so badly.
But I knew
it could only be a dream.
In the end, I'm just a cripple.
I can't even get dressed or eat by myself.
It's fine.
I'll bring you to the next Outsider Martial Arts Contest.
You don't even need to fight.
I'll bury all of your opponents for you.
You'll definitely be the champion.
Right, Zhang Chulan?
That's right.
Thank you.
-Erzhuang. -I know.
You still want to know about Duanmu Ying.
I can tell you right now.
Duanmu Ying's Double Quan Palm
has two effects.
First, it can alter one's memories and cognition.
Second, it can alter one's body.
It can even regrow limbs.
My father has been looking for clues related to Double Quan Palm
ever since I got into an accident.
He hoped that he could restore my body
with Double Quan Palm.
That's when he discovered the Lyu family's Soul Whisperer.
But it's an incomplete version of Double Quan Palm.
It can only extract and replicate memories.
It cannot restore our bodies.
The real Double Quan Palm
is more comprehensive.
One palm can restore bodies
while the other can manipulate memories.
Not only can it extract and replicate memories,
but it can also erase them.
After that, my father received a report from someone.
He learned that Duanmu Ying was imprisoned by the Lyu family.
He came up with a way to save her
and brought her back to the company.
Since you guys have already found Duanmu Ying,
why are you still in this state?
It's complicated.
I don't know the exact reason either.
I hope you guys
can uncover the truth behind everything.
I would've joined you in the investigation
if it weren't for my disability.
Go now.
We'll definitely meet again in the future if there's a chance.
Yes.
NURSING HOME
Erzhuang sent us the address.
It's a company property.
I'm sure NDT's security guards are there.
What should we do?
We have to get help.
Xu San and Xu Si?
This case has drastic implications.
We mustn't implicate them.
Why aren't they here yet?
I'm done waiting.
Ms. Bao, wait a bit longer. This is NDT's turf. It's dangerous.
Our help will be here soon.
What's going on? Where is he?
Chulan!
Ms. Bao!
He's over there.
Chulan, Ms. Bao, long time no see!
Chulan, what are you doing? Don't be shy.
Turn off the sound system and go there!
-All right. -No problem.
You should've told us earlier.
I told you three to keep a low profile.
What's with the getup?
It depends on the occasion.
We mustn't embarrass Ms. Bao.
Is this your so-called "help"?
Get your equipment and follow my orders!
There are a lot of people inside.
I'm sure there's an ambush.
They all sound like experts.
I hear blunt weapons hitting the ground.
It seems like everyone is armed.
Someone is approaching-- Ms. Bao!
We'll cover your back.
You two should find a chance to escape.
Stop playing!
Time to watch our show!
Here I am!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the three of us came here today
to deliver warmth and wellness
to all of you.
What is this?
What are you guys doing?
Excuse me.
What are you doing? No salesmen allowed.
-We aren't salesmen. -We're delivering wellness and warmth.
We're here to deliver warmth.
Ms. Bao, I've searched all other areas.
I couldn't find Duanmu Ying.
This is the last place left.
Let's search it thoroughly.
Zhang Chulan.
That's her.
Madam,
we aren't crooks.
My name is Zhang Chulan.
My grandfather is Zhang Huaiyi.
So does she have my memories?
I don't even know
if she has her own memories right now.
Didn't you notice that she's acting the same way
that the villagers did in Lyu Village?
I now understand
why Erzhuang's father sent her to a nursing home
instead of imprisoning her.
She has no qi at all.
No matter what, we should bring her back first.
We'll think of what to do later.
Guys, it only costs 50 yuan.
Here's the QR code to pay.
Please take them!
Let us dance!
Let us do it.
-Up! -Up!
Let's go.
A self-driving vehicle?
A runaway van?
Did we call for help?
Does it look like it?
Is the van that advanced?
Thanks, Zhang Chulan!
I'll treat you to a meal later!
Who's that?
Mr. Zhang, did you bring your chauffeur?
It's amazing.
Go after him!
Ms. Bao, we don't need to chase him.
My phone is in the van.
Erzhuang can help us track down his real-time location.
LYU FAMILY MANSION
I'm addressing you as my elder.
You should stop pretending to be senile.
Take a good look around.
You were imprisoned here for several decades.
Doesn't it feel familiar?
Where exactly is my sister?
Both you and I are wielders of Double Quan Palm.
I don't need to waste my breath.
This is my sister's memory.
Why do you have it?
Where did you keep Lyu Huan?
Tell me.
Is Lyu Huan dead or alive?
Tell me and I'll set you free right now!
Lyu Liang,
you're acting just like your great-grandfather.
Zhang Chulan,
you had better stay out of this.
This is our private matter.
You spent so much effort and went out of your way
just to find your sister.
I'm so disappointed in you.
Do you still remember the day she fell off the cliff?
She never fell off the cliff.
Duanmu Ying altered their memories
and framed me for her death.
However, I will never forget that day.
The beginning of winter eight years ago.
Do you know how Duanmu Ying left Lyu Village?
I saw it in my great-grandfather's memories.
Someone from the company took her away.
The company received an anonymous call
two days after your sister's death
saying that Duanmu Ying was detained in Lyu Village
Who reported it?
I don't know either.
But I retrieved the voice recording before I came here.
Listen.
Hello, this is NDT Command Center.
Hello?
Can you please put Mr. Gao
on the line?
May I know who you are?
Please contact him, okay?
Lyu Huan?
I have something important to tell him.
Please wait a moment.
It's Lyu Huan.
Duanmu Ying.
Tell me!
Where exactly is Lyu Huan?
Tell me! Where exactly is Lyu Huan?
I won't tell you.
You mustn't tell anyone either.
What did you say?
Are you Lyu Huan?
Could it be…
Is this Cola or Sprite?
Is it you, Lyu Huan,
or me, Lyu Liang?
The Cola-Sprite Theory.
Lyu Huan.
Come closer.
Let me take a look at you.
Earlier, you told me
about the Cola-Sprite Theory.
My mind was a mess earlier.
I didn't catch what you said.
Can you tell me about it again?
According to my brother Lyu Liang,
if you get rid of the Cola
in a glass
and fill it with Sprite,
it will cease to be…
Lyu Liang!
What happened?
Duanmu Ying stole Lyu Huan's body
and tampered with everyone's memories.
I'm sorry.
You were the one
who crushed her consciousness
in order to steal her body.
Your useless husk
retains only a sliver of her memories.
I won't tell you.
You mustn't tell anyone either.
GRAVE OF ZHANG XILIN
Dummy.
DUANMU YING, 25 YEARS OLD
Are you saying that her body
holds your sister's remaining consciousness,
which knows only a pair of sentences?
So, to you,
is she alive or dead?
Even if it's only one sentence,
at least she's still alive.
The real Duanmu Ying is inside Lyu Huan's body.
Where is she?
We're looking for her too.
Zhang Chulan,
give me your grandfather's memory qi orb.
I'm sure there are leads in his memories.
I only managed to unlock a portion of it before.
Now that I possess
the upgraded abilities of Double Quan Palm,
I may be able to unlock the rest of it.
If you wish to find her,
let's work together.
Do it here.
It might take a long time.
It's fine.
We can wait.
PROGRESS TO REVEALING THE TRUTH
AT 98%
What's wrong?
There is a seal in here.
I don't know
what will happen if I unlock it.
I cannot continue.
What if I want to force it open?
It might distort time and space
and open a portal to other dimensions.
It might be very dangerous.
Ms. Bao, are you afraid?
No.
What about you?
Don't you wish to see your sister again?
The seal in Grandpa's memories
really opened up a door to another dimension.
Lyu Liang!
Where are we?
This person
possesses your grandfather's qi.
Is he Grandpa?
Is this a memory we're reliving after breaking through the seal?
If it's a memory,
why are we inside of it?
Are we in phantasmagoria?
I don't think it's either.
Is all of this
actually qi?
These images are formed
by the lingering qi here.
That means
this event did take place in the past.
Your grandfather looks so young.
It should've been several decades ago.
The Jiashen Calamity.
Who are these people, then?
Why does he look so familiar?
He's Feng Zhenghao's grandfather,
Feng Tianyang, the creator of Dispatch of Detained Spirits.
FENG TIANYANG, DISPATCH OF DETAINED SPIRITS
The one in the suit
is Gu Jiting, the creator of Daluo Dongguan.
GU JITING, DALUO DONGGUAN
That bald guy
is Ruan Feng, the creator of Six Vault Immortal Thievery.
RUAN FENG, SIX VAULT IMMORTAL THIEVERY
This guy who resembles a teacher is Zheng Zibu,
Infinite Heavenly Talisman's creator.
ZHENG ZIBU, INFINITE HEAVENLY TALISMAN
And this chap
is Ma Benzai, the creator of the Divine Forge.
MA BENZAI, DIVINE FORGE
Six of the eight creators
of the Eight Supremes are here.
Where are the other two?
Where are Zhou Sheng and Duanmu Ying?
Where are they going?
ZHOU SHENG, QIMEN MANIPULATION
This should be Zhou Sheng.
Where's Duanmu Ying, then?
Where is she at this moment?
Is she in that cabin?
Who is this?
He's number four among the 36 Thieves,
the world's strongest martial artist,
and Sinister Pleasure's leader.
Wu Gensheng?
WU GENSHENG, SECT LEADER OF SINISTER PLEASURE
If he is Wu Gensheng,
who is the one inside the coffin?
Is it Duanmu Ying?
Why is he crying?
Am I dead?
Ms. Bao,
I think she just resembles you.
You're alive and kicking in front of me.
Plenty of people look similar.
This is me.
What's her relationship with me?
Feng Baobao.
Feng Baobao!
Lyu Huan?
Lyu Huan!
Lyu Huan,
is it really you?
It has been so many years,
yet you're still searching for her.
Duanmu Ying.
You were the one who killed Lyu Huan!
The entire Lyu family,
each and every one of you,
is spineless.
Aren't you going to kill me?
Get out of my way, then.
Lyu Huan died because of me.
I shouldn't have brought up the Cola-Sprite Theory.
In the end, they still did it.
Feng Baobao,
it has been so many years,
yet you haven't changed at all.
Ma'am,
do you know me?
Not only do I know you,
but I also know your father.
Your father is Wu Gensheng.
Gensheng is our fourth brother.
Am I the person inside the coffin?
Am I dead?
You're dead.
Let me put it this way.
You were once dead.
Ms. Bao.
Everything is related to karma and destiny.
If you wish to know the truth,
then follow me.
PROGRESS TO REVEALING THE TRUTH
AT 99%