Not bad, Yifan.
Fang Group paid a fortune
for Lot 6 across from our Wanhe Mansion.
Let me have a sip.
Now the flour costs more than the bread.
Our sales office gets clients asking daily
when Phase Two launches.
They're all scrambling for our units.
That's exactly what I was hoping for.
Nice going, brother.
Every step's gone exactly as you planned.
For next week's agents' gathering,
besides Su Yuanyuan,
I invited every agent we've worked with
to join us.
Together?
That's right.
Our Phase Two right now
is the hottest property on the market.
We've got to bring in more bidders
to drive up the price.
You're absolutely right.
I'm at Garden of Fortune Hotel next week.
Let's see what tricks you pull.
Why are you here? It hasn't started yet.
I came to give you a heads-up.
At the gathering later,
there will be other companies
after Wanhe Mansion Phase Two's agency.
Chairman Zheng gave the sales agency
to Xiao Yifan.
You need to get that contract signed fast.
What's the rush?
Exclusive underwriting—
can the other companies even handle it?
Exclusive underwriting is more profitable,
but the other firms aren't pushovers.
Tonight,
you absolutely must
close the deal with Xiao Yifan.
I've already booked the room, haven't I?
Good.
Then here's to you, Director Su—
may tonight go just as you wish.
Tonight I'll look absolutely stunning
and be the center of attention.
Xiao Yifan,
I won't just win Wanhe Mansion's exclusive
underwriting. I'll devour you whole.
That project of his is pretty impressive.
Yifan.
Mr. Zhang.
You all got here pretty early.
We just arrived too.
I was just introducing our new director.
Hello, Ms. Su.
Mr. Zhang, your team is full of beauties.
Beautiful director?
She's just a pretty face.
A vixen stealing money from men.
So she's Fang Bing's wife.
Hmph, nothing special.
She looks like a hostess with that makeup.
Go ahead and pour.
Ms. Su can drink anyone under the table.
I can't drink that much.
Mr. Xiao is the real heavyweight.
Anyway, I'm not drinking today.
If Ms. Su doesn't get drunk,
then none of us stand a chance.
Hahaha.
Thank you all for coming.
You're all our company's partners.
Thanks for your support.
Here, I'll down this glass first.
Mr. Xiao, Mr. Han.
You two are the hosts tonight.
But I still want to say something.
The marketing of Wanhe Mansion Phase Two,
my company is very eager to cooperate.
I hope you two bosses
will give us plenty of opportunities.
Everyone should already know,
the Wanhe Mansion sales office
is swarming with customers.
Phase Two will definitely sell out.
As for our company,
we want to recoup funds quickly.
So,
this time, Phase Two
will use exclusive underwriting,
requiring a one-time payment.
Today,
it depends on all of you,
who shows the most
sincerity.
Mr. Xiao,
exclusive underwriting
puts very high demands
on our cash flow.
However,
for Wanhe's projects,
we'll definitely keep cooperating.
I'd like to toast you.
Mr. Xiao,
our company is also very confident
in serving Wanhe.
I'll drink three glasses to you.
This...
That's a very sincere offer.
Wow.
Alright, two glasses.
Three glasses.
What a drinker!
Mr. Xiao, we'll drink to that.
But,
for the Phase Two sales rights,
our company is very sincere.
We can offer up to
25,000 per square meter.
Come, come, come.
I'll drink first as a sign of respect.
Mr. Xiao,
Since Mr. Zhu is being so sincere,
let me make my stance clear to you too.
Our company
will take on the second phase
at 25,500 per square meter.
Allow me
to toast you three times.
My company offers 25,800.
I'll drink straight from the decanter.
Alright.
Thank you all so much for your support.
I'm clear on the prices now.
And I understand
everyone's intentions.
Let me toast you all once more.
Ms. Su,
with a beauty like you here,
I'll have to drink a few extra today.
Now, don't tease me.
You already have a beauty by your side.
And you still want to drink with me?
I'd rather have a drink with Mr. Xiao.
Yifan,
we were colleagues over a decade ago,
and now we're business partners.
So tell me,
how should we drink this?
Mr. Xiao,
I had no idea you two went back like that.
Shouldn't you two do a Wedding toast then?
Everyone here has known me
for over ten years.
As for this drink,
let's all drink together.
Ms. Su,
what do you think?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yifan's in the Peony Hall.
He is bound to get drunk with this crowd.
Let me give Yang Hui a call.
We're off.
Bottoms up, bottoms up.
Let's go.
Take care.
Have one more! Today's a happy day!
Mr. Xiao, look.
Ms. Su's toasting you. One more!
This isn't even your limit.
Let's drink straight from the decanter.
Right? How about it?
Mom, your phone.
Dad must've had a lot to drink.
You need to rein him in.
It's Uncle He.
Hello.
Hello, Sister-in-law.
I'm at the Garden of Fortune Hotel.
If it's convenient,
come pick up Yifan.
Okay.
I'll head over as soon as I finish up.
Mom, are you going to pick up Dad?
No rush.
I'll finish this problem with you first.
Mom, come with me.
What is it?
Mom, I picked this pretty dress for you
to go pick up Dad.
Why is that?
You didn't notice?
The way Auntie Su looks at Dad,
her eyes light up.
She likes my dad.
She's been Dad's colleague for a decade.
And now they're business partners.
Sweetie, what are you thinking about?
Mom, I picked this pretty dress for you
to dazzle Auntie Su.
Okay.
Does it look good?
It looks great.
Such a good girl.
You've had enough to drink.
Mr. Xiao, let me take you to the hotel.
When Yifan comes home late from a dinner,
he always messages me.
Why no message at all tonight?
Yifan.
There are cameras here.
Come back to my room with me.
Be good.
Go home.
Let me go home with you, okay?
You two...