What?
Six hundred million?
Oh, come on
Don't get worked up
Look at it this way
At the current market price
The Wanhe Mansion Phase Two units
will earn at least
4,000 yuan per square meter
After deducting expenses
the profit is substantial
Isn't Fang Bing rich?
Don't you two
make plenty of money?
He hasn't settled the material fees yet
That's why I'm in a rush
But my loan
hasn't come through yet
I know you can definitely sort it out
Once we make money
I'll save you a share of the profits
Wanhe Mansion Phase Two
does have substantial profits
Alright then
I'll push the loan through
Aunt, I knew you loved me most!
I'll arrange the launch right away
Aunt, I'm off
I'll cover it for her first
That way,
the profits...
I can get a piece of them.
Sorry, Director Qin
I was signing a contract with a partner
Sorry to keep you waiting
Not at all
President He is a busy man
I understand
Please, sit
Director Qin,
how have you been?
Anything you need from me,
just let me know.
We're all old friends here
no need to be so formal
I came here
just to find out
when the supervisor bidding for Plot 7
will take place
The supervisor bidding?
We're already preparing it
Director Qin,
are you interested in joining?
A project this big,
of course I'm interested.
When the time comes,
I'll have to ask President He
for plenty of support.
Sure, no problem
Any news
I'll let you know promptly
Thank you
This way, please
Was that person just now
Jianrun Corporation's Director Qin?
Yeah.
You two know each other?
More than just know each other.
Him and I,
we go way back.
Manager Shi from M&E didn't come?
Oh, Director Qin.
Manager Shi had urgent business back at the company.
He sent Deputy Manager Xiao Yifan to attend.
For such an important meeting,
he sends some greenhorn?
What decisions can he even make?
Well...
Director Qin,
I may be young,
but I have experience on three projects.
Rest assured,
any issues that come up,
I'll record them all,
and handle them properly for you.
Young people
don't know their place.
From now on, meetings like this
must be attended by the top boss.
Any leave must be requested through me.
Director Qin,
our Deputy Manager Xiao,
though he's quite young,
is extremely diligent and responsible.
Our company is grooming him as a key talent.
We hope you, the Old master,
will give him chances and guidance going forward.
Hahaha.
Since President Zhu put it that way,
let's continue with the meeting.
Last time we covered
the foundation and foundation beam structural drawings.
Let's take a look.
Whoa.
So you've had your own miserable moments too.
So for this supervision bid,
are you still planning to let him take part?
Of course.
I absolutely will.
And also,
this time,
the project director defense meeting,
I'll attend in person.
Hello, honey?
Hey, babe.
Don't forget to make some time this afternoon.
We need to handle the property transfer.
Babe,
you're behind the times.
Property transfers nowadays take just minutes.
I'll leave work half an hour early
to pick you up.
What are you talking about? There's still a queue.
Was buying School district housing easy?
I'm taking our son there now, hurry over too.
Babe,
just relax.
If it's not done in ten minutes,
I'll do all the housework for a year.
Then it's a deal.
Alright, that's settled.
Daddy
Honey
You're here
How did it go?
Wow
That was really fast
Thank you
Let's go
We'll go look around
Okay
Come on
Sweetie
What do you want for dinner tonight?
Ice cream! I want ice cream!
Can you make it?
I can't
Bing
Checking out other women again?
I wasn't
Lying to me again
How about...
you have a child for me too?
Having a son isn't that simple
Who'd raise him?
What are you afraid of?
You give me a son
and I'll treat him like royalty
I've got plenty of money
But what if that shrew of yours
finds out?
What are you worried about?
She hasn't gotten pregnant in all these years
Just go ahead and have one
I'll buy you a house
Really?
I hear Wanhe Mansion Phase Two is amazing
It's a high-end community
You want a place at Wanhe Mansion?
Mm-hmm
She'd find out too easily
How about I buy one somewhere else instead?
Okay, sure
Don't worry
Wow
How much stuff did you buy?
You brought the whole mall home!
Aunt
All this jewelry is for you.
Our Wanhe Mansion Phase Two
is launching very soon.
Consider these
a little gift for you.
Good girl.
Aunt didn't dote on you for nothing.
When is Fang Bing coming back?
Let's all have a meal together.
I already called him.
The Plot 7 Phase One general contract
is up for bidding right now.
He's busy entertaining clients.
Aunt's telling you,
you're not getting any younger.
You can't just think about making money.
Find an opportunity,
you need to have a baby.
I know.
Once Wanhe Mansion Phase Two sells out,
I'll think about it.
Okay.
This just in:
To ensure stability in the housing market
and firmly implement the policy of
"Houses are for living, not for speculation,"
our city today issued
the Notice on Further Strengthening
Real Estate Regulation Work.
Local and non-local homebuyers
will face purchase and sales restrictions.
The details are as follows.
What?
How could this happen?
Aunt!
It's all over, it's all over!
My money!
My money's gone!
My Plot Six,
it can't be launched now.
Yuanyuan!
Hurry up!
You, you, figure something out fast!
Cash out 600 million for me!
All my money is tied up in projects.
What am I supposed to pay you back with?
Let me tell you,
this whole thing,
I'm sure it was
a trap set by Xiao Yifan and his people.
He...
They knew all along
the government would crack down!
It's all over!
My Plot Six,
the plot hasn't even launched.
How am I going to face
my shareholders?
How do I answer to my shareholders?
Aunt,
if Xiao Yifan knew about this,
how could you not have known?
Why didn't you warn me in advance?
I had heard about it before,
but the word I got was
it would take a few more years.
I didn't know it would come this fast!
All my money's tied up in Wanhe Mansion Phase Two.
Why isn't Fang Bing picking up?
What's the point of calling him?
Can he fix this?
Aunt.
You must have a way, right?
Please help me, I'm begging you!
Quiet, quiet, let me think.
Here's what you do.
Listen to me, do it this way.
Go find a way to ask Xiao Yifan.
Find out what their cost price is.
Then we set ours just slightly above it.
We rush into pre-sales right away.
Even at base price plus 10% profit,
I'd still be at a loss!
All my various costs,
celebrity endorsements,
the bank loan interest...
No matter how I calculate it, I lose.
That's exactly why
you need to start pre-sales fast!
Here's the plan.
First, release some discount and bargain units.
That way we recover some cash first.
Then you figure out the rest bit by bit.
Did you hear me?
I figure it out?
Figure out what?
What am I supposed to figure out?
That's your problem now.
Aunt!