♪In a fleeting moment, beneath the skies♪
♪The next heartbeat
may span a thousand years♪
♪I look back♪
♪And everything has changed with time♪
♪Before my eyes,
the graceful youth appears♪
♪As silver moonlight brushes willow tips♪
♪When will the Divine Oracle descend?♪
♪A charming glint between my brows♪
♪The Mirror has shown me a sign♪
♪It lets me change my form,
cross the heavens♪
♪To seek the path of destiny♪
♪Only then can I meet with you♪
♪A gentle smile, a tender sway♪
♪My heart longs for you to understand♪
♪In youthful days, unbound and free♪
♪This other world grows ever fairer♪
♪See me draped in clouds
and drifting mist♪
♪I wish our hearts may meet♪
♪From afar, I gaze to see
whose brows hold that smile♪
=A Farmer's Fortune=
=Episode 6=
Hey everyone.
Don't just pass by, you have to see this.
- News!
- There's a thief at the Fu Family.
Yes. Attention!
Come take a look.
The Fu Family's been robbed.
Everyone, come over and see.
He Datian, what tricks are you pulling?
Well well, He Qingqing.
I knew my family's old secret...
Potato cold bean jelly.
The secret Recipe for it has vanished.
Turns out you're the one who took it.
You two really flipped the truth
upside down here.
It was my own creation.
When did it become ancestral?
She claims she invented it herself.
With that lazy attitude of yours,
if you could actually create bean jelly,
then sows could climb trees.
Qingqing,
hand over the recipe
and we'll let it go.
- We'll drop it.
- Yeah, let it go.
You all came here in such a big show.
Just to let it go?
What a waste of such drama.
You...
Let me tell everyone,
this recipe is only passed to men.
But she stole it.
My mother
is so angry
she can't even get out of bed.
My poor mother.
He Datian, that's enough.
Girl,
what do you have to say?
Alright.
Since
you're saying it is a family recipe,
then tell us,
in the cold bean jelly,
what are the three most important seasonings
and what are the first few steps?
The recipe is passed down.
- Of course we wouldn't know.
- Exactly.
We're not like my eldest sister-in-law
who disrespects family tradition.
If you've never seen it, how can you know
it's passed down?
Qingqing,
you know what kind of person you are.
Everyone's seen it for themselves.
A few days ago,
you ran out of money
and came to our place to take stuff,
scaring me so bad
I nearly had pregnancy complications.
Tell me,
if you just wanted some rice
or flour, fine.
We're family after all.
Can't just watch you go hungry.
But I never thought…
you'd cause such a scene
all to steal our family recipe.
Thief.
You said it with such drama and conviction.
Sounded pretty convincing.
I almost believed you.
What's that supposed to mean?
- It's true.
- That's how it is.
- It is ours.
- Yes.
You took our secret recipe.
- It's ours.
- Alright, enough, enough.
You're still family.
No need to make this uglier.
Girl,
I believe you wouldn't steal.
It's just that…
you grabbed the wrong one by mistake.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Picked up the wrong thing.
Just return the recipe.
We won't hold it against you.
No hard feelings.
- You're awful!
- Tangbao.
- Why?
- Seriously?
Believe I'll slap you?
Get up, come on.
I can give you the recipe.
But if you touch the kid,
you'll regret it big time.
Right, right.
I said that it belongs to us.
That's called returning
to the rightful owner.
I passed through the West Market.
I saw a thief caught
stealing from others.
He was beaten to death in public.
For misbehaving,
you'll face the consequences.
What do you mean?
Even if you put on a perfect act
these days,
your true colors showed through.
I'm telling you, it's time to stop.
Don't be a bad influence.
My true color is... I'm your dad.
You're out of your mind.
(Divorce Letter)
He Qingqing
has shown improper behavior.
(Fengyang House)
She stole the family secret recipe
and violated the Seven Grounds for Divorce.
(Divorce Letter)
Father.
Tangbao.
Come here.
What's up?
Why did you want to see me today?
Father.
Go and cheer Mother up.
Me? Cheer her up?
Why?
Some people lied and said
Mother stole the recipe.
They even snatched it away.
She must feel terrible inside.
You mean
Mother didn't take the recipe?
Of course not.
It was Mother and Tangbao.
We worked it out together.
It took them so many days.
I see.
So I wrongly blamed her.
Father.
Mother's a good person.
In that case,
Tangbao.
Take Father with you.
Go get the recipe back.
How about it?
Sure, let's get the recipe back.
That'll make Mother happy.
Let's go.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
What are you doing?
Hand over the recipe.
That was taken away by your wife.
Why should I hand it over?
- Still trying to keep it?
- Ouch.
Don't think she has no one
backing her up.
Fu Qinghuai.
What are you all doing here?
Mother.
Father and I came to help you
get the Recipe.
My neck's about to snap.
I'm reporting
you for intentional assault.
Fu Qinghuai.
Let him go first.
He Datian.
Is this recipe really yours?
You know the truth better than anyone.
Don't act innocent
after taking advantage.
The village chief awarded us the recipe.
That means it belongs to me.
I'm done wasting words with you.
I'm going home to make bean jelly.
Just let him leave.
If you owe me again...
You don't want it back?
Now you believe I didn't steal it?
Tangbao already told me everything.
Sorry.
Mother.
Tangbao is really upset.
My little treasure, please don't be mad.
I'll show you something exciting.
Let's go.
Honey.
I'm back.
Hurry, hurry.
Listen,
I've reached out to the buyers in the city.
They said they'll take as much
the potato bean jelly as we can make.
Honey,
we might be hitting it big soon.
It's because I worked so well with you.
Otherwise your sister
wouldn't give in that easily.
You're really smart, you know that?
Come on, hurry.
The recipe.
- We're gonna be rich.
- Read it.
I've got it.
Two liangs of cinnamon.
Two liangs of star anise.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
That hurts like crazy.
Water, water, water!
How did this happen?
How did you pull that off?
Seriously,
no way I'd give them the real recipe.
I gave them
a quicklime reaction formula.
Let's see if he dares to steal my recipe.
Mother, you're so smart.
Tangbao's smart too.
Whoa.
He Qingqing.
I knew it was you.
He Qingqing!
Go, go, go! Run!
He Qingqing, you troublemaker!
He Qingqing, stop right there!
After her!
Mother, fireflies!
They're so pretty.
Absolutely gorgeous.
Aren't these just ordinary things?
Where I live, they're rare.
What I mean is
because they're so common,
that's why
we often overlook them in daily life.
People do tend to be blinded
by what they already believe.
Tangbao, come here.
Let's watch together.
See that one?
Doesn't it look like you?
It kinda looks like...
Father.
It makes sense.
And... what about that one?
Looks just like Mother.
You got it!
Tangbao, you're amazing.
Why aren't they back yet?
Tangbao.
I like
being with Mother and Dad.
Fu Qinghuai.
Let's call a truce.
Just think of it
as being for Tangbao.
You have to tell me
the real reason you stayed here.
I already told you.
To buy back the Fengyang House
and raise the two kids.
Alright.
Let me help you.
I'm the only one who doesn't belong.
You can't leave.
(Next Episode)
Xiaosheng, Xiaosheng, are you in there?
Come home with me.
From now on,
it will never be my home again.
- Go away or not?
- Watch out.
Can you...
give us a chance?
How did you get so many wounds?
I can take care of it.
I... I...
♪Like fish in a pond longing for the ocean♪
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪
♪My home spans ten acres wide,
eight or nine thatched rooms in gentle shade♪
♪Elms and willows shade the eaves,
peach and plum trees bloom before the hall♪
♪A distant village veiled in haze.
Smoke curls lightly through the fields♪
♪Dogs bark in the deep alley,
and roosters crow atop the mulberry tree♪
♪No dust disturbs the quiet court.
An empty room holds endless peace♪
♪Long was I caged within the world,
now I return to nature's grace♪
♪In youth, I had no taste for fame.
My heart was drawn to hills and streams♪
♪By chance I strayed into the world snare,
thirty years gone in a flash♪
♪A captive bird yearns for its forest,
like fish in a pond longing for the ocean♪
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪