♪In a fleeting moment, beneath the skies♪
♪The next heartbeat
may span a thousand years♪
♪I look back♪
♪And everything has changed with time♪
♪Before my eyes,
the graceful youth appears♪
♪As silver moonlight brushes willow tips♪
♪When will the Divine Oracle descend?♪
♪A charming glint between my brows♪
♪The Mirror has shown me a sign♪
♪It lets me change my form,
cross the heavens♪
♪To seek the path of destiny♪
♪Only then can I meet with you♪
♪A gentle smile, a tender sway♪
♪My heart longs for you to understand♪
♪In youthful days, unbound and free♪
♪This other world grows ever fairer♪
♪See me draped in clouds
and drifting mist♪
♪I wish our hearts may meet♪
♪From afar, I gaze to see
whose brows hold that smile♪
=A Farmer's Fortune=
=Episode 2=
(Fengyang House)
Xiaosheng.
Tangbao.
(Fengyang House)
Where is everyone?
Open the door!
Brother, why did you lock Mother inside?
She took advantage while Father's away.
She sold off all our family property.
- Xiaosheng.
- She even planned to sell us to Wang Cheng.
Treat it as if we have no mother.
But Mother…
She did save us and bring us back.
That was just another of her tricks.
Open the door.
We can't stay in the village any longer.
I'll take you to find Father.
Let's go, Goaty.
I can still bring Fengyang House back.
If our ancestors turn away,
who will carry it forward?
Who will alter the precepts?
I refuse.
Hurry up.
It's gone wrong.
Stop right there!
It's you.
If there's an issue, face me.
Snatching a child in broad daylight.
What kind of skill is that?
You and your brother
played tricks on me.
I haven't settled that score.
And now you act up again.
That child was sold to me by you.
Taking him away is rightful.
What are you doing?
I'm warning you, don't use force.
I deal in lawful trade of people.
I have their deeds of Sale.
I have reason on my side.
Wang Cheng, isn't it?
No matter what I signed before,
you cannot
take away the people.
I've already paid for them.
Two children.
Two taels for the deeds.
Fengyang House as collateral,
worth thirty taels.
This Fengyang House was sold to you?
That's right.
I handed your brother money.
Are you trying
to back out now?
Business is about profit for you.
You wouldn't wish ruin on the family, right?
How much debt do they owe?
I'll repay you.
If I can't repay,
at your mercy.
Not right now.
One month later.
Do you take me for a fool?
I'll add fifty percent interest.
A month is too long.
Ten days only.
Repay four taels.
Four taels of silver?
Can you even do the math?
And what about the time you struck me?
Treating my wounds cost a coin.
Deal.
Withdraw.
Hurry up.
Do you hear
what they just said?
Spare me your false kindness.
We're going to find Father.
Let him set you free.
Alright.
Lead this goat along.
Just walk straight out.
Your deeds of sale
are still in his hands.
I'd like to see for myself
if you can even reach
the edge of the village.
Brother, I'm scared.
I don't want to go anymore.
Don't be afraid.
For now, Fengyang House can wait.
The pressing matter now…
is the deeds of sale
for these two ancestors
and fixing the door.
Will this business with Wang Cheng
end up angering your sister?
I doubt it.
She's not exactly a virtuous woman.
I'll charm her into agreeing again.
She'll follow our lead.
(Well, speak of the devil.)
(Enemies do cross paths.)
Sister, come on, sit down.
Why didn't you send word before coming?
I even told Dacheng,
we should go and offer you an apology.
Sit down, quick.
Sit, sit, sit.
The food looks decent.
Is it bought with
Wang Cheng's thirty-two taels of silver?
That's right.
Thanks to you, sister.
We finally drained the Fu Family's coffers
down to the last coin.
Just as we agreed before,
these thirty-two taels
will all mine.
The owner of this body
never even split the spoils evenly
when scheming.
She was so eager to spoil her brother.
I need it urgently now.
Hand me the money first.
Qingqing,
you suddenly come over
just to ask for money.
Isn't that like taking our lives away?
Unless...
I give you the child in my belly
as compensation.
Stop right there.
Where's the money?
Just...
Just these few coins left.
Anyway, all the signed papers
carry your name on them.
If...
the Village Head learns of this,
none of us will come out well.
You...
I'm new here.
Still figuring things out.
Better not cause too much trouble.
Alright.
No money?
Then trade something instead.
Brother, I'm so hungry.
Hold on a bit more.
Tonight, I'll make you roasted potatoes.
Time to eat.
Smells amazing.
Tastes so good.
Brother.
She has meat.
Feeling sleepy.
I'll take a nap.
Then eat afterwards.
Were you sneaking bites?
Mother.
If someone must be punished,
let it be me.
Don't hit my brother.
Tangbao just wants a taste.
Looks like he's been beaten often.
No wonder he's so guarded.
Stand properly.
I won't lay a hand on you.
Nor will I yell at you.
This food here,
you're all welcome to eat it.
You're being so generous?
Of course, there's a condition.
You need to go into business with me.
Go into business?
Let me lay it out for you.
It costs money
to redeem a deed of sale.
Redeeming Fengyang House
costs money too.
So, we
must start making trades now.
Are you tricking us?
And right now?
I hold the knife and the power.
You're just prey.
So you have no choice but to trust me.
Smells incredible.
Alright.
Okay.
Sit down, let's eat.
There's still work to do.
Luckily, there are still potatoes
in the field.
We've got the ingredients.
Now for the most important seasoning,
where can we find it?
Let's go.
Chili pepper...
So in this era,
chili peppers are just for show.
Perfect.
I'll make good use of it.
Tangbao, hold this.
Miss,
my home is right across from yours.
I'd like to trade a flower pot.
Want the chili pepper?
Exactly. What's your offer?
Go ahead, name it.
Wait right here.
Thanks.
A close neighbor is better than
a distant relative.
The people here
are truly pure and...
He Qingqing.
Don't think a change in your tone
will stop me from recognizing you.
Go on, bite her.
Hey kids, why'd you wander off so far?
(Next Episode)
Come take a look.
Delicious potato bean jelly.
Only three wens a bowl.
You won't regret buying
nor be fooled.
Calm down, all of you.
The owner of this body is so despised.
Mother.
Tangbao wants to sleep with you tonight.
You're not afraid of me?
Xiaosheng, run!
Sir, let's talk this out.
Father.
(Divorce Letter)
I want a mutual divorce.
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪
♪My home spans ten acres wide,
eight or nine thatched rooms in gentle shade♪
♪Elms and willows shade the eaves,
peach and plum trees bloom before the hall♪
♪A distant village veiled in haze.
Smoke curls lightly through the fields♪
♪Dogs bark in the deep alley,
and roosters crow atop the mulberry tree♪
♪No dust disturbs the quiet court.
An empty room holds endless peace♪
♪Long was I caged within the world,
now I return to nature's grace♪
♪In youth, I had no taste for fame.
My heart was drawn to hills and streams♪
♪By chance I strayed into the world snare,
thirty years gone in a flash♪
♪A captive bird yearns for its forest,
like fish in a pond longing for the ocean♪
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪
♪My home spans ten acres wide♪