♪In a fleeting moment, beneath the skies♪
♪The next heartbeat
may span a thousand years♪
♪I look back♪
♪And everything has changed with time♪
♪Before my eyes,
the graceful youth appears♪
♪As silver moonlight brushes willow tips♪
♪When will the Divine Oracle descend?♪
♪A charming glint between my brows♪
♪The Mirror has shown me a sign♪
♪It lets me change my form,
cross the heavens♪
♪To seek the path of destiny♪
♪Only then can I meet with you♪
♪A gentle smile, a tender sway♪
♪My heart longs for you to understand♪
♪In youthful days, unbound and free♪
♪This other world grows ever fairer♪
♪See me draped in clouds
and drifting mist♪
♪I wish our hearts may meet♪
♪From afar, I gaze to see
whose brows hold that smile♪
=A Farmer's Fortune=
=Episode 1=
Cheers.
Drink up!
Hold on, everyone.
My family,
once the signing ceremony
in the Ancestral Hall is done,
Fengyang House will be officially sold.
Everyone will get a share of the profit,
no one left out.
Alright.
Come on, cheers.
Fu Datian.
Sister.
Who said you could sell Fengyang House?
If I decide to sell, I sell.
What's that got to do with you?
I took Fengyang House from near ruin
to opening over a dozen branches.
Every brick and tile was earned by me.
Doesn't it have anything to do with me?
Even so, it still won't matter.
Listen,
the house passes from father to son.
I, your brother, am the sole heir.
That's right.
Qingqing.
It runs because of your hard work.
But you're not your brother.
Qingqing, I'm not trying to put you down.
You're not even fit
to enter the Ancestral Hall,
let alone inherit the Fengyang House.
Exactly.
Just have Datian give you more profits.
Yes.
That's more reasonable.
My dear sister,
as long as our family
has a man standing,
you won't enter the Ancestral Hall.
Is that so?
I'd like to see
who dares lay a hand on me.
(Ultrasound Medical Imaging Report)
You're with child?
You're not even married yet.
This is improper.
She did this just to seize the house.
Even if that's so,
you still can't enter.
That depends on who the father is.
Our family has many
in the collateral line.
You're not the only man here.
By seniority,
you'd have to
call him great-grandfather.
Nonsense.
You can use the family rules against me,
but I can't?
Hurry, bow to your great-grandfather.
- Bow now.
- What are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
You're crazy, Fu Qingqing?
I was just teasing you.
Told you. She fooled us.
This girl's temper is really something.
Well played, Fu Qingqing.
Mom.
Lawyer Zhang is here too.
Just sign this and it's done.
Tian Xifeng.
Well, well.
You two took advantage of Mom's dementia.
One blocked me.
And one held Mom down.
Quite the teamwork you have.
Qingqing,
it was all her decision.
We only acted according to her wishes.
Like I'd believe that.
Step aside.
Mom.
Qingqing.
You... you must
look after your younger brother.
You mustn't take what's his.
Mom.
Fengyang House is
my life's work.
It's also the legacy of our ancestors
passed down for generations.
We can't let
my useless brother sell it.
Our forebears decreed,
it shall pass to sons, not daughters.
You must obey.
Mom.
I've been managing the house all along.
I'm the one in charge.
Why should it be otherwise?
You're the elder sister.
You must care for your younger brother.
You need to behave.
Be good, alright?
Stay obedient.
(Fengyang House)
Passed only to sons, never daughters.
Such outdated thinking
only brings harm to others.
(In memory of Fu Xiaosheng)
What?
Why, are you upset now?
(In memory of Fu Xiaosheng)
Fu Xiaosheng, right?
If you dare, show yourself to me.
I'll scold you if I must.
This...
(In memory of Great-grandmother Madam Chen)
(Fengyang House)
What's going on here?
See? My sister's been waiting for you.
Your sister...
She… she truly wants to be with me?
Of course.
Her husband's been missing.
She lives like a lonely widow.
She's just waiting for you, Boss Wang.
Then I'll…
Go on, enjoy yourself.
I'll go put the child in the cart.
Have a good time.
Qingqing, I've missed you so much.
So you finally came around.
You rogue, what are you doing?
You foul woman.
Your brother said
you wanted to be with me.
Changing your mind, are you?
My brother?
That scamp, he dares
pull such tricks.
You two siblings
tried to set me up.
If I get angry,
you'll be in serious trouble.
What's going on here?
Go.
Hurry up.
Go, move faster.
- Da Tian.
- Come on.
Stop right there.
Sister.
Why so fast?
You rascal.
I used to think you were just wasteful,
never expected you'd scheme against me.
It's just sleeping with Boss Wang.
I'm helping you find another patron.
I...
Enough, I need to sell the children now.
Sell the children?
Yeah, those two kids of yours.
Mother.
- Please don't sell us.
- Let us go.
We'll behave, we promise.
When my father returns,
he'll make sure you pay for this.
Let us go!
Enough with the noise.
Mother, please don't sell me.
We'll be obedient.
Tangbao, don't call her mother.
She's not our real mother.
Wicked woman, when my father returns,
he'll make sure you're punished.
You little brat.
Always running your mouth.
- Brother.
- Quiet.
I raised you.
No one knows
where your father died off to.
If it weren't for the fact you two
are still worth a few coins,
I'd tear your mouths apart.
Datian, come here.
These are the deeds of sale for them.
Take them to Boss Wang.
See if you can get a good price.
Sister.
You're worth much more
than them.
(I... What?)
(Mother of a child?)
(I've crossed over
into being a stepmother.)
Move.
Little rascal,
I'll thrash you.
Sister.
How dare you!
Why are you hitting me?
You deserve this.
It's just sleeping with Boss Wang.
Say that again?
It's just some money.
What did you say?
Have you lost your mind?
- You.
- You deserve it.
He Qingqing, are you crazy?
Yes, I've gone mad.
Mother.
No way...
I really transmigrated...
into the cruel stepmother of them.
This family truly is dirt poor.
Father, Mother.
Please bless my brother to wake soon.
Praying to them won't help.
Your brother
was knocked out.
A good rest will work.
(In Memory of Father Fu Qinghuai; Mother)
Tangbao.
Your family surname is Fu?
That's right.
Then what's your brother's full name?
Fu Xiaosheng.
(In Memory of Fu Xiaosheng)
These two children...
are my ancestors.
I can't believe I've ended up
as my ancestors' stepmother.
Where are the Fu Family Letters?
There's no such book at home.
They've all been thrown away.
We don't have any ancestral letters.
Which means,
if I start from today and change
the thinking of these two ancestors,
then there won't be
pass-only-to-sons ancestral precept.
And no one will
use this as a reason to
stop me from running Fengyang House.
Tangbao.
Where is our Fengyang House?
Head left out the door and keep walking,
then cross the wheat fields.
Reach the ferry
and take a black awning boat
to Jinshui Town on the opposite shore.
♪I already know the ending♪
♪Springtime lingers softly♪
♪Facing the reflection, I understand♪
♪Cloud-like robes dance,
feathered sleeves flutter♪
♪In a fleeting moment, beneath the skies♪
Follow the main road and keep running.
It's the third shop on your right.
You'll see it.
♪Before my eyes,
the graceful youth appears♪
(Fengyang House)
But...
Fengyang House...
(Fengyang House)
You've already sold it.
♪A charming glint between my brows♪
♪The Mirror has shown me a sign♪
(Next Episode)
I don't want it.
Hurry up.
Stop right there.
If you've got a problem, bring it to me.
Snatching a child in broad daylight?
What kind of skill is that?
I gave your brother the money.
Are you trying
to back out now?
You're taking our lives into your hands.
No money?
Then give something in exchange.
Were you sneaking a bite?
I won't hit you.
Nor will I scold you.
You're really being this kind?
Of course, it comes with conditions.
You have to do business with me.
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪
♪My home spans ten acres wide,
eight or nine thatched rooms in gentle shade♪
♪Elms and willows shade the eaves,
peach and plum trees bloom before the hall♪
♪A distant village veiled in haze.
Smoke curls lightly through the fields♪
♪Dogs bark in the deep alley,
and roosters crow atop the mulberry tree♪
♪No dust disturbs the quiet court.
An empty room holds endless peace♪
♪Long was I caged within the world,
now I return to nature's grace♪
♪In youth, I had no taste for fame.
My heart was drawn to hills and streams♪
♪By chance I strayed into the world snare,
thirty years gone in a flash♪
♪A captive bird yearns for its forest,
like fish in a pond longing for the ocean♪
♪I till the southern fields once more,
content in my humble, rustic ways♪