[Fated to Love You]
[Episode 7]
Thank you for saving me, Your Majesty.
No need for thanks between us. Just sit down.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You've suffered in the Imperial Clan Affairs Office.
I listened to you and order an old coroner to check the marquis' corpse.
It was indeed odd.
This is the mark of a jade pendant left by the marquis.
I want to find an expert to decipher the mark.
This mark looks like Grand Master Meng's.
Grand Master?
How could it be him?
You'd have to ask Zhang Yuan Qing.
The grudge of killing my father is irreconcilable.
I must make them pay for the blood debt.
Grand Master Meng holds immense power.
Without any witness or evidence,
this jade pendant's mark isn't sufficient to prove that he is the killer.
The most urgent matter now is still finding the ledger
in order to knock down Grand Master Meng in one strike.
Zhang Yuan Qing has the ledger.
I must hurry back to the manor to search.
You can't rush this matter.
You can hide here for a couple of days.
Once I return to the palace, I will find a way to exonerate you.
Yes.
Strange. Why would Xiao Ren Yan write a letter to me?
[I'm fine at the same old place. Don't worry.]
My Lord, someone wants to meet you.
Thanks, Pretty Lady.
Why are you here?
I'm here to congratulate you on becoming a dad.
Are you pregnant?
Nonsense. I never did anything with you.
Yes, it's all my fault for being incompetent.
I didn't try hard enough, so you refuse to do anything with me.
That isn't the case with Zhang Xue Fei.
The imperial physician already said that she was pregnant. I bet she'll deliver a chubby son for you.
Wife, I'm innocent.
I never laid a hand on Zhang Xue Fei.
Please investigate thoroughly.
I'll only have a child with you in this life.
I'm not having a child with you.
All right, let's get to business.
Zhang Xue Fei's child has to be a ploy by Zhang Yuan Qing.
I can't return to the Marquis' Manor for now.
Zhang Yuan Qing thinks I'm locked up in the Imperial Clan Affairs Prison.
She'll scrutinize you. You have to be careful.
Since she's plotting my downfall,
I'll scheme against her and catch her red-handed.
Besides, Zhang Xue Fei is the key to this matter.
I asked Wei Hong He to keep a close eye on her.
We're bound to have leads.
Jia'er, you're too trusting of other men.
I already trust that Zhang Xue Fei isn't pregnant with your child.
Don't I trust you enough?
You're very dutiful and wise.
I can only return the favor by offering myself to you.
Oh, no!
Madam, there's trouble!
Calm down and take your time to talk.
- Zhang... Zhang Xue Fei is dead!
- What?
The manor's imperial physician said that someone poisoned her bird's nest soup.
Two lives were lost!
[Marquis of Xuanping's Manor]
Madam, the windows and doors have been locked. What do we do?
I'm not even anxious. Why are you so flustered?
Take a seat and enjoy a cup of tea.
This isn't the time to be enjoying tea!
Men!
Liu Jing Shu, how dare you poison and kill Yan'er's only heir.
The Marquis of Xuanping's Manor can't keep a vicious woman like you.
You're accusing me of killing Zhang Xue Fei,
but where is her corpse?
I have to see that before I can admit to a crime.
If I don't see the corpse with my eyes,
how would I know if she's really dead?
You'll see it once we're in the Judicial Court.
Men, arrest her!
Yes.
Move it!
- Madam.
- Move it!
Madam!
Stop!
How dare you touch her!
Get lost!
Why aren't you resisting?
I was waiting for you to save me.
Haven't you been arrested by the Imperial Clan Affairs Office?
Why are you here?
Make a guess.
Xiao Ren Yan, you're lawless and impudent.
How dare you break out of the prison?
Men, arrest both of them!
Let's see who dares to do that!
I think the lawless and impudent one is you.
Young Master Wei.
The show hasn't started.
How can the star leave the stage?
Zhang Xue Fei.
Aren't you dead?
Madam.
I served you for years.
I've been so loyal.
I never thought you'd brutally kill me!
I have a wretched life,
but the child in me
is your grandson, the son of Second Young Master!
Xue Fei, you've served me for years.
You haven't had your period for two months.
Did you really think I wouldn't notice?
Madam, please spare me.
How could you bear to kill me?
I didn't do it!
Liu Jing Shu poisoned you!
I'm seeking justice for you!
You were the one who told me
if I faked my own death to frame the wife of the Marquis' heir,
you'd let me hide in the manor for the time being.
Once the child is born,
you'll let Second Young Master take me in as a mistress.
I never thought you'd
order someone to forcefully poison me!
Utter lies!
How could I ever do that?
Are you still going to deny the truth at this stage?
Zhang Xue Fei, you...
What are you doing? I'm pregnant with the second young master's child!
How dare you!
Second Young Master wouldn't care about that bastard in you.
Old Madam already told us to eliminate this problem at its root.
Drink it!
Drink!
Women only know how to cry when they're in trouble.
Hey, Zhang Xue Fei.
Consider wisely.
Even if I save you now, Zhang Yuan Qing will surely try to silence you again.
Do you really want to die for no good reason?
Zhang Yuan Qing.
Since you're heartless,
I won't show any loyalty, either.
Are you still going to deny the truth at this stage?
This isn't a surprise.
An old hag like you didn't just use Zhang Xue Fei.
You even want to kill her to bury the truth.
What else do you have to say for yourself now?
Zhang Xue Fei, I've always been generous to you!
Why are you colluding with others to ruin me?
Second Madam, you're really stubborn to the bitter end.
I'm a First Rank Lady under the imperial mandate.
How dare you pin a crime on me just because of a brat's words.
Since you're bent on accusing me,
I'll head back and wait for the Imperial Clan Affairs Office to arrest you.
We're leaving.
Are we just going to let her leave?
She's just someone else's pawn.
She'll be useful to have around.
That's the only way for us to lure out the mastermind.
It's time to settle scores.
[Ancestral Hall]
Ming'er.
What are you doing?
Zhang Xue Fei knows too many secrets.
We have to leave the Marquis of Xuanping's Manor at once.
Don't worry, all preparations have been made.
Change into these clothes and come with me.
I'm the Marquis of Xuanping's heir.
Why should I leave?
Don't be silly.
Have you forgotten how the Marquis died?
How could I forget?
You killed Father.
Ming'er, I'm your mother.
You're my mother,
that's why you should pave my future for me.
I'm clueless about everything you did.
Men!
Zhang Yuan Qing viciously killed my father!
She's even trying to run away from her crimes!
Xiao Ming.
Do you think that making me the scapegoat for everything
will earn Xiao Ren Yan's forgiveness?
Xiao Ren Yan?
He can't even defend himself!
He doesn't have time to meddle with me.
Arrest her.
This is water boiled with pomelo leaves.
It can cleanse all the bad luck from the Imperial Clan Affairs Prison.
Thank you.
Jia'er.
You can wipe yourself. I'm leaving.
Hold on!
My wife, even though we experienced so many hardships,
I'm still glad I could marry you.
If you hadn't taken your sister's place in the marriage,
I would've lost the love of my life.
Jia'er.
It seems like the Heavens want us to be in love and grow old together.
But I'm still the evil child.
If someone finds out, you'll definitely be implicated.
You never did anything wrong.
The problem lies with those ridiculous ancient teachings that doom the second child as evil.
I'm not afraid of getting into trouble.
My only fear is losing you.
Jia'er, you suffered immensely after marrying me.
Once I help His Majesty eradicate the toxic Grand Master Meng,
I will take you away from the capital.
We will travel without care for worldly affairs.
We will enjoy a carefree life.
His Majesty? Have you been acting on His Majesty's orders this entire time?
My mother is His Majesty's aunt.
I grew up with His Majesty.
When my mother passed away,
my father's heart wavered.
He was bewitched by Zhang Yuan Qing
and even colluded with Grand Master Meng.
It was a moment of foolishness for His Grace.
Grand Master Meng holds great power. Disloyalty has festered within him for a long time.
I have to eliminate him for the nation and my own reasons.
But the former emperor trusted Grand Master Meng greatly.
Moreover, Grand Master Meng holds great authority.
Without sufficient evidence, you can't bring him down.
The evidence of Grand Master Meng's crimes lies with Zhang Yuan Qing.
"Zhang Yuan Qing"?
Are you willing to come to the Imperial Clan Affairs Office with me?
Chang Ming.
You've suffered.
I knew you'd come. Save me from this place.
You've committed the grave sin of matricide.
I can't help you.
Chang Ming, I've done so much for you over the years.
I even gave birth to Ming'er for you.
You have to save me.
I helped you become the Marchioness of Xuanping.
You enjoyed riches and luxuries as a First Rank Lady under the imperial mandate.
What else do you want?
You know that you're the only one I love.
For you and Ming'er,
I don't even care about being the Marchioness of Xuanping.
You made your own choices.
I didn't force you into anything.
Are you really going to abandon me?
Don't forget that you killed the Marquis of Xuanping.
- That private—
- I have a firm grip on my title as Grand Master.
I can still prevent your death.
If you implicate me,
you'll be doomed to death.
Before you speak, consider wisely.
If I can leave this place,
I'll keep my mouth shut.
If I can't...
I sure know a lot.
Fine, I'll get someone to save you from this place.
However, once you're out of here...
My lips will be sealed tight.
Marchioness of Xuanping.
Did Grand Master Meng send you to save me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Stop!
Don't chase after him.
Are you two here to kill me, too?
We can kill you easily.
Why would we play along with your farce?
Take a good look at who is trying to kill you.
Meng Chang Ming.
How could he try to kill me?
You're hopelessly devoted to Grand Master Meng.
You committed arson and murder for him,
but this is how he treats you.
I really feel aggrieved for you.
Xiao Ren Yan.
You must be over the moon.
Don't you want me dead?
I don't care if you trust me or not.
Xiao Ming has severed ties with you, and Grand Master Meng wants to kill you.
If you want to live, I'm the only one who can help you.
What do you want me to do?
I only have two questions for you.
Answer me, and I'll free you from the Imperial Clan Affairs Office.
What do you think?
What are your questions?
First, did Grand Master Meng murder my father?
Second, where did you hide the ledger for the private mine?
Xiao Ren Yan,
I really underestimated you.
You pretended to be a frivolous playboy for years,
but you've even dug up information about my private mine.
Do you think
I'll join hands with you just to save my life?
Back then, Chang Ming and I were in love.
Just because I was a concubine's child,
I was forced to marry your darned father as a mistress.
Your mother was a prideful woman who ignored my existence.
So what?
She died and I became the Marchioness.
Your father
indulged in wine and women.
He was useless and foolish.
He can't even be compared to my dear Chang Ming.
Right now, I'm doomed to be ruined by your hands.
I accept my fate.
But joining hands with you?
Dream on.
Meng... Chang... Ming.
Xiao Ren Yan, how will you find what you're looking for if she's dead?
Zhang Yuan Qing was captured all of a sudden.
She didn't have the chance to pass the ledger to someone else.
The ledger should be in the manor.
We'll definitely find it if we search the entire manor.
Xiao Ren Yan.
Let's find a place to bury her.
According to my father's will,
I should be appointed as the heir.
If I inherit the Marquis of Xuanping's Manor,
I'll be your ally, just like when my mother was alive.
The entire capital is filled with rumors about my involvement in the Marquis' death.
It isn't a good time for me to help you.
You may be unaware,
but Xiao Ren Yan has been searching through my mother's items in the manor.
What is he looking for?
Did he find anything?
The Marquis of Xuanping's manor isn't very big.
As long as he's determined, he'll find it eventually.
I mean well.
I'm worried that he will find something detrimental to you.
I heard my mother mention this before.
You have incriminating information
about General Liu's Manor and Xiao Ren Yan.
Grand Master, there isn't any time for delays.
Don't miss this chance.
I understand your intentions.
Don't worry.
I've already made arrangements regarding this matter.
I've found the midwife who delivered General Liu's child.
She will make a report to the emperor tomorrow.
General Liu's Manor will be exposed for concealing an evil child.
This time, Liu Jia is doomed to die.
I'll be waiting for your good news with a peace of mind.
This rascal has unfettered ambition.
[General Liu's Manor]
Madam Liu, you sure are bold.
How dare you conceal an evil child!
Where is she? Get her out here.
Grand Master Meng, my husband has served as a general in many wars.
Spare my poor daughter! I'm begging you!
His Majesty has sent an imperial decree.
Your entire family will be penalized.
The evil child won't be the only one.
Every last one of you won't be able to escape.
Where is she?
Preposterous!
It's outrageous to force a parent to kill their child!
Are you trying to defy the imperial decree?
If the evil child doesn't appear, you'll be the one suffering the punishment!
Men, arrest her!
How can you disregard the law so brazenly?
Jing Shu, Jing Shu!
Jing Shu, are you all right?
I'm the evil child you're looking for!
Jing Shu!
Stop!
I'm Liu Jia, the evil child you're looking for.
His Majesty's token is with me.
Let's see who dares to act recklessly.
Xiao Ren Yan, how dare you defend the evil child!
You should be locked up as well!
I have His Majesty's orders to personally imprison Liu Jia in the imperial prison.
The rest of General Liu's Manor is to wait in the manor for orders.
Will you stop me from completing my task?
I was the one who seized the Liu family for the evil child.
I should be in charge of this case.
Do your wishes override the imperial decree?
Men, lock Liu Jia up in the prison.
Move it.
My wife, leave this to me. Don't worry.
Liu Jia, this isn't the end.
Fine!
Great!
Since His Majesty has issued a decree,
I will let this evil child live for a few more days.
Sister Jing Shu, wake up.
Sister Jing Shu.
Mother-in-law, please don't worry.
I will protect Jia'er.
You can't leave Liu Manor for now.
Please bear with this for a little longer.
Sure, I'll leave Jia'er to you.
Wait for me. I'll be back to save you.
You have to be careful out there.
Don't worry. I won't let anyone hurt you.
Boss! Boss!
How can you still smile when Jia'er is locked up?
I have good news!
Sister Jing Shu regained her memories!
What?
[General Liu's Manor]
If it was so easy to regain my memories, I should've hit my own head sooner.
What happened after you arrived at the Marquis of Xuanping's Manor that day?
I wonder where Xiao Ren Yan lives.
There isn't a single servant in such a huge manor.
There's someone there. I'll ask them.
The Ancestral Hall?
[Ancestral Hall]
Yuan Qing, I've been too busy lately to visit you.
Chang Ming, it's fine.
Keep this ledger safe.
Who's there?
Liu Jing Shu?
Sister Jing Shu, take a break if it's too agonizing.
I'm fine.
Did you see Grand Master Meng in the Ancestral Hall?
I only found out later that he was Grand Preceptor Meng.
That day, I was in a hurry to flee.
But I ended up bumping into Meng Han Jiao.
Move out of the way! A good dog doesn't obstruct the path!
Liu Jing Shu, are you here at the Marquis' Manor as a thief or a guest?
We're all sitting in the main hall, but you're the only one in the backyard.
What are you plotting?
That's none of your business.
You haven't even been wedded, but you're already putting on airs!
What's so impressive about you? You're just marrying the heir.
He's just lazy and a frivolous womanizer!
What a pity! Some people just love frivolous wastrels!
They even wailed to Grand Preceptor Meng so many times.
Do you think I'm clueless?
What can I do?
What can I do? The capital's Second Madam will always be second.
You can only marry the second son!
Once I kill you, I'll be number one!
I'll be the top!
What are you doing?
I didn't do this on purpose! You deserved this!
Meng Han Jiao has always been at odds with me.
That day, she strangely picked a fight with me.
In a moment of anger, I insulted her a little.
I never thought she'd shove me into the lake!
Thank goodness I can swim.
If I couldn't, I would've drowned.
When I climbed out of the lake,
I ended up seeing Zhang Yuan Qing and Grand Master Meng standing by the lake.
They knocked me out and dragged me into a secret room.
How did you escape?
A secret room can't trap me.
I overheard their discussion.
They were deciding whether to kill me or to let me live a little longer.
When they were leaving,
I feigned unconsciousness and escaped.
I really thought I was going to die at that moment.
Luckily, luckily!
There's a secret river passage that leads from the lake in the Marquis of Xuanping's Manor to outside the city.
So I floated out with the current.
A blessing! I've struck it rich! She's clearly from a wealthy family!
I'm rich!
You're awake.
Where am I?
This is Li Village.
Who am I?
Don't... don't you remember?
You're my granddaughter!
Granddaughter?
You all know what happened after that.
I only wanted to reject the marriage on that visit.
Who knew that I'd almost end up as the murder victim of an adulterous couple?
The old widow almost sold me to the brothel as well.
There are too many dangers for single women in this world.
So full of difficulties and hardships.
It's all my fault that I didn't recognize Sister Jing Shu at that time.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have suffered so terribly.
It's fine.
These happenings are all part of my experiences.
Besides, only by experiencing something myself
I can understand the hardships of civilian women.
That's why we should try harder to understand them and protect them.
Grand Master Meng and Zhang Yuan Qing are distant relatives and in-laws.
Even though it's inappropriate for them to meet in private,
they can easily find a believable excuse.
So why did they have to kill you to shut you up?
What did you see?