♪ Oh, tailor… ♪
["Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix this ♪
- ♪ Oh, tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's done ♪
♪ In the chaos of the world ♪
- [Chipper] Where's Draco?
- [guard] The magician, boss.
[guard] He's probably the one
who took the chicken.
[Chipper] Useless!
[Chipper] I'll kill that scumbag magician.
[man] Hey!
- [Atoy] We're heading out.
- [Karla] Oh, okay, okay.
- [gasping]
- [Tonet shrieks]
- [Atoy] Move, move, move!
- [grunting]
[Atoy] Let's go, let's go.
[guard] Boss, they escaped!
What's your read?
Does Dad know about
the projects I've been hiding?
[in English] The real problem
is your sister.
[Martina] We need to find a way
for her to go back to the US.
[Mercado] I told you
I won't be embarrassed.
[Atoy] What do you want?
I'll return this car to you.
Should I do it now?
Actually, I'm outside with the client.
[Mercado] Ah, maybe just drop it here?
[Dmitri, in English] I'm Dmitri.
And you are?
[in English] I'll just call you
the Master Cutter.
[Audrey, in English] I want to meet him.
I think he can help me.
[in English] My daughter is here.
And it looks like she also wants
to ask you to find someone.
[Atoy] She's asking you
to find her ex-boyfriend, right?
Or maybe the guy who cheated on her.
[in English] Dad!
[music concludes]
- [attendant] Uh, ma'am.
- Ah, yes?
Ma'am, sorry. You parked
in a reserved slot.
- Oh, sorry. I-- I didn't know.
- [mutters]
- Okay, okay. I'll move it.
- [attendant] Okay.
[tense music playing]
[Dmitri, in English] It seems
we have a chance to escape.
[in English] What do you mean?
[in English] My daughter is leaving.
[in English] And thank you
for the swift return of my Draco.
[in English] But I think
you'd better leave now.
My daughter might come back.
- [in English] Of course.
- [in English] Thank you, sir.
Ah, just call me if you need me again.
[in English] I will.
[in English] Thank you, Colonel.
Thank you very much.
[in English] Sir.
[sinister music playing]
I think his daughter's ex is broke,
that's why he doesn't
want them to get back together.
[chuckles softly]
That's why I avoid rich women, sir.
Their families might
look down on us, right?
We'd be doomed.
Really, huh?
[chuckles]
[music concludes]
I don't want to be punished, Sis Ame.
Just apologize. Atoy has a point.
But it seems he doesn't accept apologies.
He's an old bachelor.
That's why he's grumpy!
[Tonet clears throat]
Just relax, baby girl.
I've got a solution,
so we won't get punished big time.
- [Tonet chortles]
- Hmm? What will you do?
- Act cute? Seduce him?
- Hmm?
- Excuse me. I'm not like that.
- [whimsical music]
I'm conservative. Maybe that's your style.
[Ame] Huh? Why would I do that?
I was born cute.
Anyway, I know what to do.
I'll buy delicious barbecue
to lighten Atoy's mood when he comes back.
I've got you, baby girl.
I'll handle it. [smooches]
- Thank you, Sis Tonet!
- [Tonet] I'll be right back.
[whimsical music playing]
Ibyang, it seems…
you're siding with Tonet now.
Like you prefer her for Atoy.
Huh? You know,
I don't get you and Sis Tonet.
It's obvious you both
have a crush on Master Grumpy!
Why deny it to each other?
[mutters] Whatever!
Tonet mustn't notice, because she might…
step up her moves on Atoy.
I won't be able to catch up.
My legs are short.
What do you even like about Master Grumpy?
Maybe he's never had a girlfriend,
because he's… strict,
snobbish, negative!
[music concludes]
Well, that's even better, that he's NGSB.
So, I'll be his first girlfriend.
- [chuckles softly]
- [quirky music playing]
Oh my gosh!
She's delusional now.
[quirky music playing]
[music concludes]
[sinister music playing]
[car blips]
[music intensifies]
[music concludes]
Son of a thread!
[epic music playing]
- [horn honks]
- Hey!
[horn honks]
[music concludes]
[suave music playing]
[in English] Gotcha.
Son of a thread!
[sinister music playing]
[horn honks]
[in English] Rude!
[music concludes]
Dad, I saw you with two guys earlier.
- [in English] Who are they?
- [in English] Some friends I met here.
Too bad, I wish I came earlier.
Then I could have met
your contact, the tracker.
Oh, yes! About that,
I mentioned you were interested,
but unfortunately,
their client list is full.
They said they'll update us when possible.
[in English] But…
[scoffs] What exactly
are you… looking for?
Or who?
[pensive music playing]
[in English] A man, actually.
[in English] To be honest, Dad,
I don't even know his real name.
I met him when I was living on the island.
We were supposed to meet
before I disappeared, and…
ever since I recovered…
I've been wondering where he is…
what happened to him.
[in English] Do you think
he wonders about you too?
Why didn't he look for you?
[in English] I mean, maybe because…
Sweetheart, Audrey…
[in English] Look, it's been…
It's been eight years.
[in English] Don't you think
it's about time you let go of that guy,
and move on?
[in English] For Christ's sake.
[in English] You are a Regalia.
I don't want people thinking
you're the one chasing after a man.
[in English] You deserve more than that.
[somber music playing]
[in English] Okay?
[Karla] That's it.
- [Ame] Rice?
- [Cita] Let's eat.
[utensil clatter]
[woman] I've spoken to the families
of the other missing girls,
and we believe they didn't elope.
So, I hope that through this account,
through this video I'm making,
the police will finally
take their case seriously.
- [Tonet] Ah, Atoy, there's barbecue!
- [Ame] Brother Atoy!
Look, there's an issue now on FlipTok.
There are missing girls.
The police said they eloped.
But the families said
they met someone on a dating app,
then disappeared?
They're asking for help.
[sinister music playing]
Oh, but the police already knew that.
They know what to do.
Just trust them.
I'm hungry. What's this? What's this?
The barbecue is from me and Sis Tonet!
There's no poison in this, right?
Those dating apps are dangerous.
Don't get involved in that!
Yuck, Mom. I haven't
even thought about that.
[Cita] Hmm.
You too, Tonet.
Oh, Miss Cita, you're too much.
Why would I swipe there
if my TTH is just around?
[Cita] Hmm?
TTH, yuck.
What do you mean by "yuck"?
I ate a strand of hair.
[quirky music playing]
- Atoy, one more?
- [Atoy] Mmm.
I haven't even finished this yet.
[man] Atoy?
[Tonet] I-I'll do it. Water?
- [Ame] Rice?
- Ah… Oh, oh…
Hungry, huh?
- [mumbles]
- [Tonet] Okay.
[quirky music continues]
[Tonet] I gave him barbecue.
It had a lot of pepper.
‪[music concludes]
Father, this task you gave is simple.
I'll make sure that
before your Sunday Mass begins,
this is done.
Huh? I'll handle it, and…
This one's on the house.
As usual, I'll take care of it.
Hey, Atoy, that's business.
But thanks, huh.
[chuckles]
Uh, can Queenie pick it up instead?
Sure.
Oh, Queenie, say hi to Karla.
Weren't you best friends before?
- Um, we're still friends.
- [Atoy, in English] Shoulders, eight.
That's right, Father.
We just have different interests.
I hope Karla becomes like Queenie.
Look at her, such a lady and so modest.
You must have many suitors, right?
Oh, uh, I'm not allowed
to have a boyfriend.
Uncle Father said only after I graduate.
[chuckles]
- [Atoy, in English] Twenty-three.
- Correct.
Honestly, I thank God
because my niece is so obedient.
She doesn't give me problems. [chuckles]
- Oh, Karla, did you hear that?
- [Karla] Oh, no!
- Why me again?
- [Atoy, in English] Eighteen, armhole.
Loosen this a bit.
- [Cita chuckles]
- [mutters]
I'm gaining weight.
[music concludes]
[crickets chirping]
Dad, shouldn't we be celebrating?
We found Draco.
[in English] I'm not in the mood.
Why? What's the problem?
[in English] It's Audrey.
[sinister music playing]
[in English] Audrey wants
to look for some guy.
A guy she met on an island.
[in English] Though she
doesn't know his name.
How do you find someone
without knowing his name?
[in English] But she hasn't forgotten
about this guy.
What if…
that man is important to Audrey?
we made a mistake with what we did before?
[in English] Dad, what's done is done.
There's no point in thinking
about what we did.
[in English] What's important…
is that we protect our secret.
[Audrey, in English] What secret?
[music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
Um…
Dad and I were talking
about his Kelso chicken.
[sinister music playing]
He wanted to file a case
against the one who took it…
but it's better to keep
how it was taken a secret.
[in English] Oh, did you want
something, Audrey?
[in English] Ah, yes.
[in English] Um, I was thinking
about going away for a few days.
[in English] Quick vacation,
just to clear my head.
[in English] I just wanted
to let you know, Dad.
Where are you going?
[in English] Do I need
to tell you everything?
[in English] Fine.
But bring someone from the staff,
so you'll have company.
[in English] No, please. Dad, I just…
wanna be alone for a while.
[in English] Okay.
[in English] Thanks.
[tense music playing]
[music concludes]
Finish it.
- [Tonet] Hmm.
- [Ame and Ibyang chuckle]
- [Tonet] Hey, Atoy.
- Oh.
Here's your share.
- For helping me get the chicken.
- Ah.
[Tonet] No need, Atoy.
- I'm just happy I helped you.
- Me too.
Remember, if you need
my help again, just tell me.
Me too, Atoy.
I'll always be here for you. [titters]
[Atoy] Refusing is not allowed.
You worked for that,
so you need to take your share.
If not, people might say
I'm taking advantage of your kindness.
No, take it. It's yours.
I'm fine with it.
[quirky music playing]
- Huh?
No. What I said was,
you're really so kind, Atoy, yes.
[in English] You're such
a good guy! [chuckles]
That's why I'm Team Atoy. Go, team!
[in English] Ah, Team Atoy?
All this Team-Team Atoy talk…
Can you stop with those team things?
Honestly, I'm even thinking if I should
include you in the next operations.
You're putting my plans at risk,
because you're too stubborn.
Huh?
I'm really sorry!
[mocking] "I'm really sorry."
It's my fault too, Atoy.
I just felt sorry for our baby girl.
Oh, it wouldn't have
come to that if she hadn't left.
Don't you realize what you did?
It would've been fine if I
were the one who got into trouble.
No problem, I can handle it.
But what if it was Ame?
What if something happened to her?
[pensive music playing]
What if it was Tonet?
What if something happened to Tonet?
What about you?
What if something happened to you, huh?
- Me?
- Yes.
That means you care about me.
- [Ibyang] Hee…
- Concerned?
Ah, "concerned"? No, listen to me.
If I say stay here, stay here!
- Hmm?
- [Ibyang] Got it.
Got it.
But you have to admit
that you're concerned about me.
"Concerned"? What are you talking about?
This kid really…
always talking nonsense.
[stammers] You-You, eat…
Here. Just read instead.
[Tonet] Mmm, there.
Oh, just read instead.
That's for you too.
[gentle music playing]
[boat engine whirring]
[Vilma] Elaine!
Vilma!
Oh my God! It's really you!
[shrieks]
- Vilma! [giggles]
- [Vilma] How are you?
[Vilma] Wait. Oh my god.
You look so different now!
You've become even more beautiful!
- You are too.
- Oh, wait!
What happened to you?
We were worried about you.
You suddenly left without saying goodbye.
It's… It's a long story.
Uh… There was a family emergency and…
[in English] I had to leave
the country with my dad and…
work on some things.
But you didn't even contact us.
You disappeared for years.
I even searched for you on social media.
But you didn't have
a profile page. [sighs]
You know, I even thought you were gone.
I'm so sorry, Vilma.
- [Vilma] Hmm.
- So many things happened back then.
But I'm here now,
and I'm still alive!
[in English] Thank God!
Why did you just visit now?
I just got back from the States
since I left here.
[Vilma sighs]
[Audrey] I missed you all
here on the island.
We missed you too.
I'm looking for someone.
[Vilma] Ah. [sighs]
Okay. Wait, wait, wait! Wait.
Belen!
Elaine is here!
[nostalgic music playing]
[sighs]
The last time I saw him was at your hut…
and he was looking for you.
He was also surprised when you left
without saying goodbye.
[sighs]
He came back for me?
[gentle music playing]
Vilma, where could I find him?
Elaine, why do you want to see him?
Were you in a relationship before?
[scoffs]
[Vilma scoffs]
When you left,
didn't you hear about what happened here?
The man you're looking for was involved.
What-what happened?
There was chaos here before.
He killed the bodyguards
of the Italian visitor.
There was even an explosion at sea.
The news we heard
was that they were military spies.
[Vilma sighs]
It was intense.
Part of his plan
was to get to know
and win the trust of the people here
for their operation.
[Audrey shrieks]
[gentle music playing]
‪[sighs]
So, your suspicion was right
that he didn't have amnesia,
because he was just pretending.
Wow, he was a liar.
He used the kindness of the people here.
[music concludes]
- But he didn't…
- [Vilma scoffs]
do anything bad to the locals, right?
No, because he had another agenda.
That's why he kept approaching you, right?
You were the only one who doubted him,
so he won your trust right away
so he wouldn't be exposed.
[gentle music playing]
Looks like that's what happened.
[Vilma] Did you fall for him?
Were you in a relationship?
[scoffs, in English] No. No way!
How could I fall for him?
[in English] I don't even know
his real name.
That's true!
Who would be foolish enough to fall
for a man you don't even know, right?
[in English] Right? [scoffs]
But if you were there
when he came back to your house,
you probably would've
been together then, right?
[scoffs]
There was something between you before.
- [sentimental music playing]
- [both scoff]
[nostalgic music playing]
It's nice living on the island.
The air is clean.
Life is simple…
The people are happy.
Have you seen the sunset here?
Mmm. It's beautiful.
But it's even more beautiful if…
you have someone holding
your hand while watching it, right?
[chuckles]
[in English] What a sweet talker.
[gentle music playing]
We're even.
Maybe that's really where it ends.
[in English] Nothing more.
Hey.
You've been there for a while.
Where's the book I asked you to read?
Huh?
Instead of playing games all the time.
Read it! Go!
That book is boring. It made me sleepy.
[in English] Boring?
That's a really good book.
It was my favorite when I was a kid.
Come on, read it now.
Don't be lazy. You're so lazy.
You're playing games all the time.
Go on!
[gentle music playing]
Oh.
[Atoy] Hmm? Oh, what happened?
Nothing. I'm just fixing it.
"Once upon a time…"
"Once upon a time"? What's that?
Is that a history story?
No, just read it.
[music concludes]
"There was a beautiful princess
on a faraway island,
and she was with the swimming fishes."
[quirky music playing]
Then?
- [Atoy] Fish?
- "Then someone jo--"
[chuckles]
That's not what's written here.
There are no fish.
You're making things up.
Well, this book is boring,
so I made the story better.
- [Atoy] Ah!
- [Uh…
- See, isn't that better?
- [scoffs]
So, Ibyang is a writer
after all, Brother Atoy!
[Atoy] Oh, wow!
You're actually good at making up stories.
So, what happened to the fish?
Then, after that, what happened?
Atoy!
Father, perfect timing!
I was about to deliver your cassock.
Queenie didn't pick it up.
Well, that's the problem.
Why, Father? What's the problem?
[tense music playing]
Atoy, Queenie is missing.
They need your help.
[Karla] Huh?
[electronic blipping]
[music intensifies]
Help us find my niece.
Well, where could she have gone?
Where can we find this Jeff?
[Karla] He might be behind
Queenie's disappearance.
[grunting and groaning]
- [bone snaps]
- [man shrieks]
You know, Atoy's new assistant
is really a chick, right?
Just snobbish.
[Ame] Are you hiding from Emerson?
Why would I hide from him?
Who is he anyway?
- Well, your crush!
- What?!
If I hadn't listened to you,
we wouldn't be hiding
anything from Audrey!
And I'm dreading the day the wound opens,
and everything is revealed!
But that won't happen, right?
Because only the three of us know,
and no one will tell her.
Ah, Father, let's just meet at…
Queenie's house.
Get some matches!
UP NEXT
[tense music playing]
[swishes softly]