♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
["Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
- ♪ In the world's mess ♪-
- [Cita] Why are you crying?
[Cita] There's nothing wrong
if you like someone.
Huh?
[doctor] Mr. Regalia,
you're going to be a grandfather.
[in English] What?
[doctor, in English] Your daughter
is around five months pregnant.
What kind of girl gets pregnant with a man
whose name she doesn't even know?
[Martina] It doesn't make sense.
What if they see each other again?
[Atoy] Elaine!
Elaine, why didn't you show up at…
[Tonet] I've noticed something
about Gavin.
- [Karla] What?
- [Tonet] He likes you.
- Likes?
- [Tonet] Crush, that's it!
[Tonet] He wants to court you!
- Shut up already!
- [Tonet] Sorry.
[Roki] Can I hear your favorite song?
[Tonet] Sorry, I'll go ahead.
PREVIOUSLY
Read the names one by one.
[Atoy] Names of missing women.
I don't want to read them anymore.
- I'm creeped out.
- Creeped out?
Ah, all right.
Good luck with that then.
Creeped out?
Hey, you're just making excuses
because you don't want to read, right?
[upbeat music playing]
[Tonet] Oh! Gavin?
He went to the CR!
- But maybe you're right, Tonet!
- Ah.
Huh?
About Gavin!
It looks like he really has a crush on me!
You saw earlier,
he was so jealous of Raki.
Yiee! [laughs]
[giggles]
You're really crazy, huh?
Teasing yourself like that.
[sighs]
But if you show him that you
are sincerely asking forgiveness,
and you've become a good person,
your brother won't be able to reject you.
Ah, I'll go ahead.
I need to leave now.
Huh?!
Why are you leaving me?
I just have something to do.
[in English] Sorry, Karla.
[rock music playing]
- [Karla] Tonet, wait!
- [man] Miss!
[sauve music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[snipping]
[engine rumbles]
[sewing machine whirring]
[machine whirring]
[gunshots]
[gunshots blasting]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[objects clattering]
[door hinge squeaks]
At last! You came home.
Where do you see a shop assistant
leaving during work hours?
Sorry, Miss Cita.
I sent Karla instead.
I won't do it again.
Oh? Why does your face look like that?
[pensive music playing]
I'll follow your advice now, Miss Cita.
I'll confess to…
To Emerson? Really?!
Oh, I'll pray for your plan. When?
Ah, I was hoping now.
Oh. Go ahead. Go.
You have my permission. Go, go.
- Thank you, Miss Cita.
- Yes. Be careful.
All right.
- I knew it!
- [shocked gasp]
Hey! Little mushroom!
Where did you come from?!
I heard you and Tonet!
She's going to confess to Emerson.
Mmm, I'll push her to do it!
So, I won't have a rival for Atoy.
Hey, hey! Where are you going?
Where are you going?!
To Tonet. Maybe she needs moral support.
Go back… Don't meddle!
Oh my! These kids are such a headache!
Oh!
[sighs]
I told you so, I told you so.
[lively chatter]
[laughing]
[Emerson] I told you so!
[in English] My Baby Tonet!
[in English] My Baby Tonet.
Ah! [scoffs] Ah, ah,
do you need something?
Hey! Thanks.
Is this for me?
Is that a puff pastry?
Captain, do you eat this?
Me, it's my favorite.
Puff pastry, yes.
I wanted to talk to…
Emerson.
[quirky music playing]
[teasing]
[Emerson scoffs]
[Emerson, in Engilsh] Sorry, Captain.
[smirks]
- [in English] Sorry.
- Emerson?
[scoffs]
[clears throat]
- Yes.
- Let's go then!
Captain Paldo!
[indistinct chatter]
You're not "gonna win big"!
- [music fades]
- [clears throat]
Uh…
Captain, what's going on?
I can't accept it!
What did Tonet see in Emerson?
I'm more handsome than him!
Hmm?
If you're jealous, just close your eyes!
As for me, I support Sis Tonet.
Hey! You call her "sis" now?
Quiet, all of you.
Don't meddle with them.
Stop it.
[music concludes]
Oh! Uh, thanks.
You know, I knew it.
You were the one who left the puff pastry
and my wallet here at the shop before?
[gentle music playing]
I was going to confess something to you.
Ah… [smirks]
Actually, I've known for a long time.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
I noticed whenever I saw you.
So, you knew?
You were so obvious.
So, you're not angry?
Well, um…
As a "fatter of mact",
this isn't the first time…
someone fell for my good looks.
- Huh?
- [in English] Several of you.
Ah, yes.
But let me be honest with you.
I'm sorry, young lady.
You really are beautiful,
but you're too young for me.
Mmm-hmm.
[in Visayan]
Stop talking, Big Brother Emerson.
[unsettling music playing]
What? What…
What's that…
What's that "Big Brother"?
No one calls me "Big Brother"
here in Manila.
Do we know each other?
Big Brother, I'm Netchai! Your sister!
[music intensifies]
Netchai?
It's Netchai. [titters]
It's Netchai, your sister.
[unsettling music playing]
Ah, ah, wait, wait.
Did I hear that right?
You're siblings?
Huh?
All of you!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Give me that!
Ah, Big Brother! Big Brother, Big Brother!
It's me, Netchai!
Stop being so nosy, okay!
Let them talk inside!
- Go home! Go!
- We don't know what happened.
Go home, go home, go home!
Big Brother, sorry-- inhales]
Big Brother, sorry if I didn't fulfill
our promise, Big Brother.
[pensive music playing]
[sobs]
[young Emerson] ♪ Hele, hele ♪
♪ Sleep now… ♪
♪ Your mother is not here ♪
[humming]
[in Visayan]
Don't worry, even if Mom is not here,
I will always be here for you.
Hmm?
[in Visayan] Just be patient.
After I've saved up a huge amount,
we will go to Manila.
I will work there, and you will study. Ha?
[in Visayan]
Big Brother, please don't leave me, huh?
[in Visayan] Of course not.
No, no, no.
Didn't we make a promise?
Promise not to leave each other.
Promise?
Promise, promise.
[gentle music playing]
[humming]
[Emerson] Netchai?
Netchai!
[door clicks open]
Netcha--
[in Visayan]
What are you doing here?
[in Visayan] Since you are leaving,
I will just get the kid.
[chuckles sarcastically] Huh?
[in Visayan] Then what?
You will leave her alone?
Huh? Huh?
[in Visayan] No, no.
I will bring here with me in Manila.
Netchai, come here.
Wait, let us ask the child here
who she wants to go with.
Netchai? Who do you want to go with?
With your Big Brother or with me?
Netchai.
[gentle music playing]
Sorry, Big Brother.
[in Visayan] But I also
want to be with Mom.
[sighs]
[in Visayan] Netchai,
I took care of you, didn't I?
Huh? Right?
[in Visayan] I have been
like a mom and dad to you.
[in Visayan] She is useless.
She didn't do anything.
[in Visayan] Stop it, Emerson! Let's go.
- No, Netchai.
- Let's leave. Let's go
Netchai.
[music continues]
Netchai!
[sobs]
[in Visayan] I regret it, Big Brother.
I am really sorry.
[sobbing]
I did everything to survive here
in Manila, Big Brother.
[sobs]
[in Visayan] But Mom left me.
[music continues]
[in Visayan] She has
her own family already.
[music continues]
[sobbing]
[in Visayan] But I did everything
to find you, Big Brother.
[music continues]
[in Visayan] I asked
everyone, Big Brother,
so we can find you,
so I can find you,
to say sorry to you.
[music continues]
Manang, oh.
I drank a lot of water.
I was shaken by those two.
What about Tonet, huh?
Oh, what's OA's issue now?
Because Emerson found out Tonet
is actually his long-lost sister.
What?!
[suspicious music playing]
They're siblings?!
Oh, so who's OA now?
Atoy, maybe you can check on Tonet.
They said Emerson is furious.
Mom, I don't want to meddle in that.
It's a family matter.
Come on! You're just going to check.
She's your employee and my boarder.
Maybe it's okay to show concern for her.
Oh.
[gentle music playing]
What do you want to happen?
What do you want?
You want me to pity you, is that it?
[chuckles sarcastically]
[pensive music playing]
You don't know the agony
I went through here.
[sobs]
It's so hard being alone here.
But I had to come here because--
To keep you alive.
Because I love you.
[sobbing]
You're the reason I…
I live!
You're my only family!
[sobs]
You're the sibling I love the most.
[sobbing]
And then you left me. [sobs]
And now what, huh?
[sniffles]
What do you want to happen now?
For me to pity you?
You want me to pity you?
[sobbing]
- Mano… Big Brother, if only I could--
- I can't do that.
I can't.
If only I could go back
in time, Big Brother.
If only I could go back, I'd choose you.
[sobbing]
No.
It's too late. Too late, too late.
It's gone. It's over.
Leave.
- Big Brother…
- You can leave now.
- I'll make it up to you, Big Brother.
- No.
You can leave now.
Big Brother…
- Sorry, Ma…
- Netchai…
Leave now, Netchai.
I'm your sister, Ma…
Netchai, leave now.
Netchai, leave now!
Leave now!
[intense music playing]
No! No!
No, no!
Leave! Go! Go!
[Emerson] Leave now! Get out!
Leave! Out!
[Cita] Emerson!
[music fades]
I don't want to see your face here!
Emerson, what's wrong? Calm down!
You shouldn't do that to your sister!
- What?!
- Sister?!
You have a sister, Emerson?!
I knew it. You're both Bisaya!
So, what, all Bisayas are his siblings?!
Everyone's a know-it-all!
You, I don't want to see your face here!
[woman] Oh, harsh! Harshness!
That's too much! Too much! Let's drink!
- Psst, hey!
- Are you a drunkard?
- [indistinct chatter]
- Take it easy!
Show her some mercy.
[Emerson] Oh, you're here again.
You, always acting like
the main character!
[man] Oh!
What do I have to do with this?
You always act like
the main character among us!
[man] Right!
You're the most handsome, the best!
You're the blessed one!
You're the son of God!
Oh, so why me?
You, we're just stopping you.
We're concerned about you!
That's the thing.
This is none of your business.
But you meddle even with sibling fights.
Well, you're already hurting people!
You could talk it out properly.
Talk it out?
You're always acting superior.
You deserve to have your face smashed!
- [Cita] Emerson, stop!
- [Emerson] What?!
[jeering]
Are you sure? He's stronger than you.
He'll beat you up. I can handle him!
[Emerson] What?!
- You want me to smash your face?!
- Just let him be.
Go ahead. Go on. Bring it on!
[Emerson] I will really bring it on!
- [Atoy] Go ahead. Bring it on!
- You're always starting something.
- [Atoy] I won't fight you.
- What, do you want this?!
- [Atoy] No, just bring it on.
- [Cita] Stop it!
- [grunts]
- [people squeal]
[grunts]
'Son.
[intense music playing]
[grunts]
[people squeal]
Emerson, stop.
You know, your anger won't solve anything.
Huh? Relax!
- I'll join in!
- Don't!
- No!
- Hey, hey!
- [chanting] Emerson!
- Emerson!
Emerson!
I won't fight you.
I understand you. Chill out.
- [people cheering]
- [Emerson] Stop it, 'Son. Stop it!
- Atoy! Atoy! Atoy!
- Emerson! Emerson!
[groans]
[Emerson] Hey, your safety pin!
Relax, 'Son! Relax!
No one wants to fight you here!
You think you're the best?
I can do that too! Try me! Fight me!
I won't fight you!
[man] Give it to him!
[man] Go on!
[people gasping and jeering]
[Emerson] Hey!
[in English] One, two, three!
[in English] And you're out!
[indistinct chatter]
[in English] And the winner is…
Atoy!
Let me go! Let me go!
[people jeering]
Big Brother.
Stop it.
I don't want to see your face!
Go with them!
[pensive music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Paldo] Emerson!
[man] Hey. Go, Captain, follow him.
[man] Video, video, video.
[man] Video, video! Hurry!
[somber music playing]
Let's leave Emerson alone for now.
He'll calm down eventually.
It doesn't look like it, Miss Cita.
He's just shocked, Tonet.
All of us are.
And you didn't tell us you had a sibling.
I thought we were close.
Sorry I didn't tell anyone.
Especially when I found out
he and Atoy were enemies.
[pensive music playing]
Enemies?
Hey, let me clarify.
I don't have enemies. He's not my enemy.
If he has an issue with me,
I don't have an issue with him.
Oh, Atoy!
It's hard to get involved
in family drama like that!
It doesn't make you look good.
Ah, maybe that's why you have
so much family drama, huh?
Hey, what-- There you go again.
You're throwing shade at each other again!
You know, Ame has a point.
Think about it. You already apologized.
But he's still full of pride.
Because if Emerson completely
cuts you off from his life,
maybe that's a blessing in disguise.
Right? It's better not
to have that burden.
Look at me.
No siblings, no enemies, no problems!
See? Life is simple.
[laughs]
So, being aloof and loveless is fine?
All right, Atoy, thanks again.
Sorry again.
Miss Cita, I'll go ahead.
[gentle music playing]
Can you believe it, bro?!
I could've been your brother-in-law
if things turned out that way!
If Tonet likes you too!
- But she doesn't!
- Come on.
Hey! But Emerson, in fairness,
your sister is beautiful.
It's like you really took care of her.
[woman] Actually!
She doesn't look like she
grew up drinking rice water.
Of course!
Because I raised her,
and I didn't abandon her.
And wait…
Why is it when you talk,
you act like I'm not here?
I can hear everything you're saying.
It's just them.
I'm handsome too, you know!
Yes! I just got stressed
because of what she did!
Come on, bro!
That was a long time ago.
Forgive your sister.
Then set me up, okay?
Bro, brother-in-law!
If I become Tonet's boyfriend,
I'll make you the official tailor
of Barangay Tabang Lupa!
[Paldo] What?
[man] Come on, let's go.
Let's go, come on.
Yes! We still have things to talk about.
- [overlapping chatter]
- [woman] Nestor, let's go!
- [man] Come on, Nestor.
- [woman] Yes.
[woman] Hey, buy us a drink, Nestor!
[man] I'll take care
of your bottle, Sir Nestor!
[woman] There.
Psst. So, bro?
C'mon!
Stop it, Captain.
I don't fall in love often.
[somber music playing]
Emerson's in here.
[in English] Tonet, are you okay?
No.
[in English] Um, sorry.
I just want to be alone.
[somber music playing]
[music fades]
Around 18 to 21 years old.
And those without family here in the city.
If they do have family,
they don't get along,
or maybe they only have a guardian.
That's the similarity
among the missing women.
I always check on that girl.
But she never mentioned any problem to me,
not even about her sibling.
Father, that's how teenagers are.
Right?
They struggle to open up to older people,
so they're always more comfortable
talking to peers.
[mysterious music playing]
Aside from her classmates,
doesn't she talk to anyone else?
I can't say.
But lately, she's always on her laptop.
Maybe a school project.
[music intensifies]
The women who dated on MatchTayo,
then suddenly disappeared.
Mandy also had a MatchTayo.
[intense music playing]
Do you know if…
she used the dating app MatchTayo?
Do you know that app?
- I don't know…
- [Atoy] Where's her laptop?
Where's her laptop?
- Here.
- [Atoy] Ah.
[soft grunt]
- [laptop blips]
- There. Here it is.
This is the last app she used.
MatchTayo.
This… This is the app used by another girl
who's been missing for a month now.
She met her date here.
My God!
[Rachel inhales]
Do you know her username and password?
Ah, no.
Okay. Wait.
[laptop key clicks]
[laptop blips]
[music continues]
[Peping] You were able to open it?
How did you do that?
No, the site was still
in the default browser setting.
And here, her username and password
were still registered and logged in.
I don't understand.
But go ahead, son. Six seven.
[mysterious music playing]
[laptop key clicks]
[laptop blips]
There! Bingo!
Who's Bingo?
No, Father. It means
I opened it. I got in.
Here, I see it now.
Here, here. This is the last person
she talked to.
They said they'd meet last Friday.
Friday. That was the last day
before she disappeared.
Where?
It doesn't say, but here, look.
He asked for Queenie's number.
There. So most likely,
they were talking on the cellphone.
[laptop blips]
Raki. Raki Roman.
[bustling chattering]
[in English] Hey! I know you!
[ominous music playing]
- Are you alone?
- Isn't it obvious?
What's your name again?
Sorry, I'll just order.
Ah, I have a table there. Come on.
Ah, no. I'm fine here.
[in English] Hey, I'm trying
to be nice here.
Why are you so arrogant?
I just want to drink alone!
[in Visayan] One more,
and I will really hit you.
Hey. What's that?
If you don't translate that,
I won't let you go!
Maybe you're already selling me out!
[barman] Raki!
Leave Tonet alone.
[bustling chattering]
Is this Queenie's type?
Can you find that man, Atoy?
[tense music playing]
Father.
Even if he hides in the eye of a needle,
I'll find him.
[music intensifies]
[electronic blipping]
After Queenie,
I'll focus on Ibyang,
so she can be helped too.
You'll look for Ibyang's parents?
[in English] Dear, I'm worried about you.
You might get too obsessed with that man,
when he's not even looking for you.
[Mercado on phone]
I spoke with Mr. Regalia's child.
She's looking for something.
She wants to meet you first.
Karla, why are you befriending
people like that?
Mom, it's not like that!
He has a punk rock band!
Munting Sigaw!
That's what Sis Tonet
was listening to earlier.
[Atoy] I'm just looking for someone!
His name is Raki Roman.
[grunting]
[grunting and groaning]
[swishes]
‪UP NEXT
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
‪Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias