[brazen music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[Ibyang] Did you find her?
Why aren’t you with her?
[Atoy] I’ll handle it. Don’t meddle, okay?
I need a disguise to get
inside Endless Nights.
[Cita] Tonet might be able to help you.
[Lorna] Okay, bring that inside.
Where are our additional janitors?
[guard] They’re not here yet, Ma’am Lorna.
But the agency already called.
They said they’re on the way.
- [Lorna] Jeffrey Matulak?
- Present, ma'am.
[Lorna] There’s a lot that needs cleaning
in the back area.
I want it cleaned thoroughly, okay?
[warped beep]
What’s this?
Why does it need numbers?
[Ibyang] I don’t even like math.
‪PREVIOUSLY
Master Grumpy?
Yes, keep quiet.
- Is that you?
- Yes.
Why is your hair different?
- Ah, just keep your mouth shut.
- [Lorna] What’s happening?
Why is there a child here?
[Ibyang] Do you have food there, madam?
[Atoy] Unbelievable!
[Atoy] I told you to watch her.
I rarely give you orders,
and she still managed to escape from you.
[Karla] We got carried away
playing basketball.
I didn’t notice she bolted.
[Ibyang] Big Sister Ame saved me
when the orphanage burned down!
[brazen music continues]
[hooters honking]
[melancholic music playing]
Ah, uhm, good day.
Are you looking for a kitchen helper?
I’m good in the kitchen.
Here, I brought my resume.
Maybe you’d like to check it.
Can you even reach the kitchen counter?
You’re funny, girl.
[melancholic music continues]
Ibyang?
Ibyang, what are you doing here?
Later, okay?
Ibyang.
What’s going on? Someone’s sleeping here!
Big Sister Ame!
What are you doing here?
I’m the one asking you.
Weren’t you transferred
to another orphanage?
Yes, sis.
But…
The people there are mean!
And there are so many kids.
It’s chaotic.
So, I escaped to find you.
You’re crazy.
You’ll get into trouble doing that.
Good thing no one kidnapped you here.
They’re afraid of me.
Good thing you found me.
- It's a good thing.
- [gentle music playing]
Come on. I’ll take you back there.
Just be patient.
You don’t have a choice.
It’s dangerous for you
to sleep on the streets.
Big Sis, I don’t want to go back there.
I want to be with you.
You’re the only one who’s nice to me.
Ibyang, my life isn’t good
right now either.
I lost my job because of the fire.
I have no savings.
Only debts.
I can’t give you a good life.
That’s okay.
What’s important is you’re kind to me.
And I want to be with you.
Please, don’t give me away.
[in English] Please.
[somber music playing]
Even though Big Sister Ame had no money,
she still took me in.
Sometimes we only ate once a day.
But that was okay
because we were hungry together.
[sniffles]
She loves me very much.
Even if I’m stubborn,
she never yells at me.
Unlike Master Grumpy, who helps,
but has a bad attitude.
That’s why I’ll do everything
to save Big Sister Ame.
[somber music continues]
Ibyang.
Ibyang, your Big Brother Atoy is kind too.
That’s why he’s doing everything
to save your Big Sister Ame.
Okay?
I don’t want him anymore.
I don’t want him anymore, miss.
I don’t want to be with Master Grumpy.
So, I hope he brings back Big Sister Ame,
so I can leave this place.
[Cita clicks tongue, sighs]
[sobbing]
[somber music continues]
[sniffles]
[deep breath]
[suave music playing]
[machine whirring]
[swooshing]
[cutting]
[machine whirring]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots blasting]
[machine whirring]
[cutting]
[metallic clink]
[Lorna] Listen, all of you.
I don’t want to repeat myself.
We have back-to- back peak nights,
so prepare yourselves.
It’s payday today,
so for sure they’ll be
burning money later.
Tomorrow is Havana Friday Night,
so expect our D.O.M. patrons to flock in.
Okay?
Now, I don’t want anyone wandering
or acting stupid here on the main floor.
When I call you, only then
should you come.
And when I call you, you come immediately.
I don’t want to be kept waiting.
Got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
[Lorna] Okay.
For now, I need someone
to guard the gold card area.
Two. I need two janitors.
- [Lorna, indistinct]
- Ma’am, I’ll do it.
You?
You can’t.
You’re new. You might mess up.
You might cause problems.
I want experienced ones. You, you.
You two, okay? Do a good job.
[sinister music playing]
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
[Lorna] Go on. Work.
[man mutters]
[tense music playing]
[Atoy] Bro, wow.
Ma’am Lorna is really strict
about the gold card area.
What’s in there?
The big-time people.
Just do a good job here,
next time you’ll be assigned there.
It’s a win there.
The customers tip big.
Especially those betting on the fight.
Fight?
What kind of fight?
Like boxing?
[janitor] Yes, kind of.
But the fighters are dwarfs. It’s brutal.
[dramatic music playing]
I heard some even die there.
But it never makes the news.
[dramatic music continues]
[Datryl] No one else can help you
get out of here but yourself.
[fire crackling]
[pensive music playing]
[inquisitive music playing]
Darryl. Teach me how to fight.
That’s it!
That’s what we need here. Someone cocky.
Like this. Let’s start with the basics.
Stand like this, so you won’t fall easily.
I don’t really know much,
but I still win my fights.
Ah, is it like this? Am I doing it right?
That’s fine.
I just copy what I see in boxing matches.
Your hands should always
be raised to your head.
Like this.
[mid-tempo music]
Like that?
Yes, that’s right.
So, when you get punched,
your face won’t get hit directly.
[laughs derisively]
[Datryl] What’s
your problem again, Tessie?
We’re just minding our business here.
It’s just funny watching you both.
One fool, one idiot.
[laughing]
We’ll see, Tessie.
Next time we face each other,
I’ll knock you down.
Really?
So scary.
[laughing]
Ignore her.
Throw a punch, Ame.
[tense music playing]
When you stand like this,
this is where you should
draw your punch from.
Are you right-handed or left-handed?
- Right… Right-handed.
- [Darryl] Yes!
So, your left foot should be in front.
[Darryl] Like that.
[intense music continues]
Do you know who owns this bar?
I know there are many owners.
But the biggest boss is the one
they call Boss Alpha.
Does he watch the fights?
I don’t know. They say he’s often abroad.
You know what?
Don’t even think about them.
What’s important is you
give them a good fight.
There’s one customer here,
I’ve never seen him,
but I know he always bets big on me.
[in English] Big time.
I only know him by the name ROJO.
He’s my favorite,
because whenever I win, he sends food.
He’s kind too.
He’s only kind because, of course,
they profit from us.
But I suspect they’re doing
other illegal things.
[Red] Vladimir.
- [in English] Red! How are you?
- [in English] Welcome to my humble home.
- [in English] Ah, it’s beautiful.
- [in English] How was your flight?
[in English] Very good.
At the same time, very sexy.
[in English] But, uh,
I have a gift for you.
[in English] You can choose one
if you want.
[clicks tongue, in English]
I have to check them out first.
[Vladimir, in English] Sure.
[in English] Go ahead.
- [Red sniffs]
- [inquisitive music playing]
[Red sniffs]
- [Vladimir, English] How do you like them?
- [in English] Ah… I like…
[music intensifies]
Oh? Um…
[in English] Martina, Vladimir.
Vladimir, my wife.
[in English] Martina,
it’s a pleasure to meet you.
[in English] Very beautiful.
[in English] So… ladies.
[in English] What else, aside from
spreading your legs, do you do for money?
Psst. Are you serious?
[in English] What?
[in English] You--
[in English] You do know that you could
also use your mouths for speaking, right?
[clears throat]
[in English] Vladimir is part
of the Black Meridian.
He’s the biggest supplier
of women in Asia.
I need him because I have many clients
who need Filipina women.
[in English] Understand?
[in English] I don’t care.
[in English] This is my house.
Do your business somewhere else.
- [in English] Um, it’s okay.
- [sniffs]
[in English] We can find
another place to do business.
[in English] How about we find a place
where we can meet Manny Pacquiao?
[in English] You know any?
[in English] I actually know a place.
- [Vladimir, in English] Oh, let’s go.
- [in English] Yeah. Let’s go.
[tense dramatic music playing]
[Red, in English] The girls?
[in English] Ah! Girls, shall we?
[tense music playing]
[Vladimir, in English] I’ll grab you guys.
[MC] Okay. Listen, all of you.
These are the fights tonight.
After I announce the matches, get ready.
When I call you,
I want you to move immediately.
[in English] Okay. First fight.
[in English] Arturo versus Nemuel.
After that, Ame versus Pam.
[unsettling music playing]
Can I volunteer?
I’ll fight Ame instead of Pam.
And why would I do that?
I’ve been annoyed with this woman
for a long time.
I’ll make sure the audience
enjoys what I’ll do to her.
[people jeering]
Okay, fine. You better mean it.
Yes, Boss. Not just a knockout,
prepare a body bag.
[tense music playing]
Don’t mind her.
She’s just trying to scare you.
Just remember everything
we practiced earlier.
I’m not afraid of her.
If that Tessie is an obstacle
for me to see Ibyang again,
she’s mistaken about
who she’s messing with.
[intense music playing]
[Tonet] Come in.
Good thing you’re back, Ibyang.
We were so worried about you.
This child wandered a long way
from here, my goodness.
Did you talk to Atoy, Ibyang?
I don’t want to talk about
that Master Grumpy.
He’s grumpy and heartless.
I hope he finds Big Sister Ame soon,
so I can leave this place.
[somber music playing]
Ibyang, don’t say that.
You know, I do understand you.
I know it’s hard to get along
with your Big Brother Atoy.
[chuckles]
But I know he regrets what he said to you.
And, whatever happens, I promise you this…
Your Big Brother Atoy will never stop
until he finds your Big Sis Ame.
That’s the kind of person he is.
Huh?
[hopeful music playing]
[indistinct chatter in the background]
[upbeat music playing]
[phone chimes]
IBYANG HAS COME HOME
[upbeat music continues]
[suspicious music playing]
[beeping]
[mysterious music playing]
[suspicious music continues]
[upbeat club music playing]
- [man] Oops.
- [suave music playing]
You stay here. I’ll stay there.
[in English] Come on.
[in English] Thank you.
[brazen music playing]
- [indistinct chattering]
- [inquisitive music playing]
[brazen music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
- [bell rings]
- [crowd cheering]
‪[energetic club music playing]
[crowd buzzing]
- [bell rings]
- [man] Sir Red is here.
[man, in English] Welcome, Sir Red.
[attendant] Wait, I’ll get your table.
[in English] Yup.
[man shouts]
- [crowd buzzing, clapping]
- [Red sniffs]
[crowd cheering, clapping]
[crowd cheering]
[in English] What is this place, Red?
[in English] You’re gonna love this place.
[in English] It’s a, uh,
battle of mini gladiators.
- [in English] I like.
- [chuckles]
[man, in English] Welcome, Sir Red.
- [man] Here, please.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
- [indistinct speech]
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
[energetic music playing]
[loud puff]
- [glasses shatter]
- That’s been going on for a while!
- [waiter] Sorry, sir.
- [patron] This place is getting crazy.
- [dramatic music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
Miss, I really can’t find Ibyang.
- Huh?
- Not even in the kitchen or the restroom.
Why? Karla, did Ibyang escape
from you again?
- [Atoy] Where is she?
- [Ibyang] This suits me well, huh?
[metallic clicking]
[brazen music playing]
‪UP NEXT
They say he has a client
in Japan. Make him happy.
Then your life will change, right?
- Can you do my makeup again?
- Of course.
[Tonet] What look are you going for?
Bring my keep bottle here, okay?
[brazen music continues]
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias