[brazen music playing]
‪[electronic blipping]
[Ibyang] Why would Miss Bebang bring
my sister in a place full of sexy girls?
- My sister Ame isn’t sexy.
- [brazen music playing]
- [crowd cheering]
- [Ame shrieks]
- Fight! Fight!
- [crowd cheering]
Looks like there’s some shady business
going on inside.
[Mongki] Maybe you want to place a bet.
There are new fighters.
[Red] I want to see.
[Red] Don’t you know me?
Bro, sorry. I don’t talk to drivers.
[Red groans]
[Atoy] What’s behind that door?
It seems very interesting.
There’s a special show happening in there.
[Atoy] Oh, have you been inside?
What’s going on there?
[Georgia] My client said
it’s very entertaining, yet bloody.
[Karla] Why would they kidnap your sister?
You’re not rich.
I don’t know either.
[Karla] Maybe a syndicate took her.
[Ame] Brother!
[rattling]
[Atoy] Ame was here earlier.
[Mongi] Why are you here?
Show me how tough you are.
[Mongki shouts, grunts]
You animal, you’re making
it harder for us.
[energetic club music playing]
[intense music playing]
Stop that!
You know Boss Alpha doesn’t
approve of that inside the bar, right?
You’ll pay a big fine.
Okay.
Take him outside.
[Mongki] We’ll handle this, Boss.
[thug] Come on.
[sinister music playing]
[man] Because someone
tried to escape from you,
all of you get no dinner!
Let’s go!
Great.
The newcomer, really.
What did you get from your stupidity?!
Now, we’re all not going to eat
because of this idiot!
[sinister music continues]
[unsettling music playing]
He can’t come back here anymore!
[in English] I want him banned here!
[host] Yes, Sir Red.
He won’t be able
to come back here ever again.
- [Red] Go on!
- [thug scoffs]
Someone tried to escape but was caught.
What?
Nothing, sir. Um…
Someone tried to escape earlier,
but it’s okay now. We got her.
[somber music playing]
Stand up there.
[Ame] Huh?
Are you deaf?!
I don’t want to repeat myself!
That’s enough, Tessie!
Why, Darryl?
If it's okay with you not to have dinner
after our arduous work, I don't care!
I’m sorry.
I just really needed to go home
because a child is waiting for me,
so I tried to escape.
I don’t know what happened to her anymore.
I’m really sorry.
I don’t care
who’s waiting for you outside!
Don’t you get it?!
You can’t get out of here, witch!
Put that in your head,
so we don’t get dragged down!
- [Ame whimpering]
- I said enough!
Leave Ame alone, Tessie!
We’re all in the same boat here!
[somber music playing]
[tense brooding music playing]
[Atoy] We walked so far.
You’re just wasting your effort.
[Atoy grunts, coughs]
[Mongki] Don’t worry.
Your night will soon be shorter.
[Mongki grunting]
[thugs shout]
- [thugs shout]
- [Atoy grunts]
‪[thugs grunting, shouting]
[exhilarating music playing]
[Mongki grunting]
[shouting, grunting, groaning]
[grunts]
[gun clatters]
[suave music playing]
[indistinct speech on TV]
- [sound on TV switches off]
- Brother, I’m still watching.
You’re wasting too much electricity.
- Where’s Ibyang?
- Maybe in the kitchen, Brother.
She was hungry earlier.
All right, Brother.
I’ll go ahead.
- Okay.
- You take care of that child.
Take care.
[chiming]
[pensive music playing]
[water burbling in distance]
Damn!
[water burbling]
What happened…
Damn!
Ibyang?
[Atoy] What happened here?
Ibyang!
[Atoy] Hey!
‪Psst!
[Atoy] Son of a thread! What’s happening?
Hey! What are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait, I’ll do it, I’ll do it.
Ah! What happened here?
[sobbing] I was just washing the dishes,
- [faucet squeaks]
- then suddenly the faucet burst.
It’s your fault.
You keep meddling with things.
This isn’t even your house.
That’s why I was washing dishes.
Because I wanted to thank you
for letting me stay here.
And for looking for Sister Ame.
If this is how you want
to thank me, then don’t!
You’re not helping,
you’re just causing trouble.
The dishes in the sink
aren’t even rinsed properly.
All right, all right,
I’ll do it, I’ll do it.
[somber music playing]
[clatters]
Oh, Sister, why are you still awake?
Well, I’m still awake too.
I’m not sleepy yet.
Are you still adjusting to the place?
Not really.
You, where did you come from?
From Atoy’s.
They have me watch the shop
whenever he’s not there.
How did you become close with Atoy?
When I was little,
Mom used to bring me to the shop.
She was an assistant there.
Since no one could watch me,
I ended up hanging out
at the tailoring shop.
What about your father?
Do you have a father?
He was a helper, so he
only came home on weekends.
And Atoy? How is Atoy? Is he kind?
You like him, don’t you?
Huh! Oh?
[upbeat music playing]
It’s obvious.
- [squeals]
- See? I told you!
You really like him!
[inhales] Okay, I’ll ask you straight.
It’s a yes, it’s a no?
It’s a yes. It’s a yes.
I like him. Why, is there
something wrong with that?
There’s nothing wrong with that!
You’re an adult.
You can do whatever you want!
You want to be close to him?
You should apply
as an assistant in his shop.
So, I won’t have to watch
over the shop anymore!
Right?
[indistinct shriek]
Very good!
You’re very smooth, very smart.
Hmm.
I don’t have a job yet,
so I need to work, so…
[in English] This is it.
[playful music playing]
Will Atoy like me?
I think, as an assistant,
- of course, yes!
- Ah…
As a girlfriend?
Try it. He’s grumpy.
- Just try.
- [chuckles]
[playful music continues]
[loud exhale]
‪[music concludes]
Where are you going again?
You might slip there!
What’s that… What are you doing?
Stop that, Ibyang! What’s that?
To make it faster, Master!
I feel embarrassed.
Where did you get that fabric?
Where else would there be fabric?
Let me see, let me see.
[funky music playing]
This isn’t a rag!
It’s the sleeve of the uniform I’m sewing!
You’re unbelievable!
Oh, I’m sorry.
- It looked like a rag.
- Oh my!
Can you just stay in the corner?
Every time you move, trouble follows.
That’s Sister Ame’s bracelet!
[pensive music playing]
What’s the news, Master?
Did you see her?
Why isn’t she with you?
‪[bucket scraping]
Did you pick that up there?
So, it’s true!
Is my sister Ame in Endless Nights?
Enough!
I’ll handle it. Don’t meddle.
I was just asking. Is that meddling?
Of course, I just want to know
the update about Sister Ame.
I’m worried.
So, did you see her?
[pensive music continues]
Hello?
Am I a person,
a plant, air? Ignored on earth!
[somber music playing]
Do you know how to use a machine?
Ah, machine?
[in English] Sewing machine.
Oh, I only sew by hand, Miss Cita.
But I can learn it, promise.
[feel-good music playing]
Ah… Do you know
the different kinds of fabric?
Not really. Oh!
Miss Cita, I know I don’t know much yet.
But promise, I can learn everything
for my Mr. Right!
For TDH!
- You’re accepted.
- [chuckles]
Thank you, Miss Cita!
Promise you won’t regret it.
All right, all right. I’ll count on that.
[softly] Thank you!
Oh.
[melancholic music playing]
Oh? Why does this baby look sad?
[Tonet] Ibyang?
You look like you haven’t paid your debt.
She was scolded by Atoy last night.
[Tonet] Oh. Poor baby.
You know, it’s okay. He’s really grumpy,
but that will go away
once he falls in love with me.
[Cita chuckles]
Why are you still sad?
What do you want to do?
Nothing. I’ll probably get scolded again
by that Grumpy Master.
Just focus on how you’ll be happy.
You know, you look like Catriona Gray.
Do you want to be
Little Miss Catriona Gray?
Miss Universe?
Yes, I’ll take care of you!
I also want to be Miss Universe!
- [Cita gasps]
- [Tonet chuckles]
See?
No problem. I got you!
[feel-good music playing]
If Brother Atoy gets mad,
you’ll cover for me, huh?
[exclaims] Yes! I got this.
He won’t get mad.
Promise. [indistinct speech]
Oh!
Are you excited? [shrieks]
Here. When I say
three, two, one, walk, okay?
[in English] In three, two, one, go!
Oh, three, two… Oh, oh…
All right. Oh…
One more! Oh!
[Tonet exclaims]
Hey! She even spun around!
[chuckles] Oh!
This baby is really amazing!
You’re better, Sister Tonet!
You’re great at applying makeup!
[Tonet chuckles] Oh!
One more. Say, "Philippines!"
- Here.
- Okay.
Three, two, one!
- Philippines!
- Very good!
OPEN
PLEASE COME IN!
Son of a thread!
[upbeat music playing]
What are you doing here again, huh?
This is a tailoring shop.
Not a parlor. What are you doing?
Gosh, Ibyang!
Every time I come home,
it’s either chaos or noise. Noise, chaos.
[mischievous music playing]
- [music concludes]
- Ibyang, ever since you got here,
I haven’t had any peace.
- It’s always chaos.
- [brazen music playing]
Well, if you want silence,
then just hang out in the cemetery.
[Tonet mumbles]
Ah, so you’re even being sarcastic, huh?
[mischievous music playing]
[chuckles] Atoy, sorry.
It was me. I told her
we should do a fashion show.
Because doesn’t she
look like Catriona Gray? [chuckles]
- She looks like her.
- [titters]
- [Atoy] Catriona Gray?
- Doesn’t she?
[Ibyang] I’m sure
he doesn’t even know her!
[clicks tongue, inhales]
Exactly. Since she looks
like Catriona Gray,
I thought of putting makeup on her.
We wouldn’t have done this
if we knew you had clients coming.
Because Miss Cita said
after she leaves,
we should close the shop.
Ah, so you’re the one behind this. Wait.
What are you doing here again?
Why are you here again?
[chuckles] Oh, right!
I’m your newest
and most beautiful shop assistant.
[Atoy scoffs] Oh, you?
- [Tonet] Yes!
- [in English] Wow, shop assistant.
- [in English] Yes.
- And this is the first thing you did
on your first day as shop assistant?
Wow! So, who accepted you?
Who interviewed you?
Miss Cita!
[Atoy] Ah, Miss Cita?
- Did you pass her interview?
- I passed with flying colors.
- Well, with me, you didn’t.
- Huh?
- [music ends]
- You failed.
[somber music playing]
Uh…
[in English] Sorry.
I’m sorry again, Atoy.
[inhales]
I’ll go ahead, Bebe.
Sister will leave first. [chuckles]
Sorry, Sister Tonet.
[in English] Sorry.
Sister Tonet only did this
to make me happy.
It’s just that I always
mess up in your eyes.
And when I ask about Sister Ame,
you don’t answer me.
Because you’re so stubborn!
I already told you that I’ll handle it.
Still, you keep asking.
It’s like you don’t trust me.
If you want, you can find someone else
to look for her and help you!
[Cita] Atoy?
- Yes?
- What’s this again?
That’s enough!
[somber music continues]
‪[music concludes]
Darryl,
why don’t we all help each other here?
Didn’t you say we’re all in the same boat?
Why don’t we all work together so we can
escape and report them to the police?
Ame, that’s enough.
Tessie bullying you is wrong.
Haven’t you learned your lesson?
What do you mean?
That all of you have lost hope?
[Darryl] They’ve tried that before.
Nothing happened.
The syndicate that holds us here
has deep connections, Ame.
How did you end up here?
They kidnapped me.
Me, I really looked for this.
I heard there was money
to be made for people like us.
Why?
Because I need money.
[somber music playing]
Otherwise, I can’t pay
for my father’s hospital bills.
I signed a contract for ten wins.
I flaunted my skills here.
Not once did I try to escape.
That’s why they trust me.
After my tenth win, they’ll release me.
Last night’s win was your…?
Ninth.
Do you really believe
that after your tenth win,
they’ll release you?
Why not?
You’d probably report them to the police.
Of course, they’ll make sure you don’t,
especially since they know
this is illegal!
I won’t do that.
Honestly, I might even come back here
after paying for my father’s
hospital bills.
Are you serious?
You know, I understand you.
But this job…
It could kill us!
It’s better than having no job, right?
There’s no job waiting outside, Ame.
Especially for people like us.
So, if I were you,
instead of fighting this situation,
embrace it.
Accept it, even if you don’t want to.
We’re different.
I didn’t choose this.
[somber music playing]
[Ame] Brother!
I hope…
I hope Brother comes back.
[sobs]
Maybe he can help me get out of here.
[phone ringing]
Aren’t you going to answer that?
How could I, when I don’t have
anything to say to him.
[somber music playing]
That’s my problem.
I can’t even do my real job
because of what Ibyang keeps making me do.
And she’s so persistent.
So, what happened
with your search for Ibyang’s sister?
I’m still thinking
how I can re-enter Endless Nights,
since I’m wanted there.
So, for now, I’ll probably just do
what I was really tasked to do.
I’ll look for Mercardo’s rooster.
‪Hmm…
- [Cita] Hmm.
- How are you, Big Bro?
Mom, I’ll get my allowance.
[in English] Allowance?
Karla, take Ibyang out.
Bring her outside, wherever you want.
She’s too restless here, too noisy.
- [Karla] Big Brother, I have plans.
- [Cita] Come on.
Please help your brother Atoy. Oh.
Make it last, okay?
- Thanks, Mom.
- [Cita] Mmm…
Ibyang!
Oh.
[bright music playing]
[Karla] Come on. I was told to get you.
We’re going out. Thanks, Mom!
- [Cita] All right, take care.
- Psst! Banana cue.
[phone ringing]
- [upbeat music playing]
- [boy 1 exclaiming] Oh…
[boy 2] Come on!
- [boy 2] Let’s play basketball.
- [exclaims] Oh, oh!
[boy 3] Hey!
Ibyang, stay here, okay?
Yo Karla, mah men!
- [shrieks]
- [Karla]
[exclaims] Shoo!
Oh, who’s that little kid?
Just don’t make trouble.
My name isn’t "basta".
It’s Ibyang!
Ibyang.
All right, stay here, okay?
We’ll play first.
Can I join, Sister?
You? Play? Are you sure?
Just kidding!
What do I know about basketball anyway?
- [Karla] Hmm…
- [Ibyang] Wait, wait!
Can I have some coins?
I’ll buy snacks.
I’m hungry!
We don’t have money,
and you’re asking for more.
Please! Give me, please!
This kid, really.
Come back, okay?
Oh. All right, I’ll play now.
[funky music playing]
[Karla] Hey, kid!
- [Karla chuckles, mumbles]
- [boy 2 mutters]
[boy 1] Wow!
[funky music continues]
Yes, sir.
I’m just finishing one job.
It’s a bit of a personal mission.
Then I’ll take care
of your missing rooster.
Okay, sir.
- Godmother.
- But…
I need a disguise
to get inside Endless Nights.
Then contact Lee.
Isn’t he the one you go to
when you need to change your look?
[clicks tongue] That’s the problem.
He’s no longer in the Philippines.
[clicks tongue] Who else could help me?
Tonet has talent in makeup.
Maybe she can help you.
- [Cita mutters]
- That’s true.
That kind of skill could work.
[upbeat music playing]
Do you think that's okay?
How? You fired her, remember?
[Atoy clicks tongue, chuckles]
[intense music playing]
[Ibyang] As they say,
no big thing can get into the eye.
[Ibyang] Don’t worry, Sister Ame.
I’m coming!
- [in English] How about a rematch?
- Yes. [in English] Winner takes all.
I’ll shoot for three points.
[boy 1] Three pointers are too easy.
[in English] Halfcourt shot.
You have to win always
because that’s the only way
to get out of here.
[Darryl] Even that man you said you saw?
With all the guards here?
He’s useless!
NEXT
- [muffled screaming]
- Shh!
- Why is there a child here?
- I know her.
You know this kid?
[intense music continues]