♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
["Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix this ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ In the world's mess ♪
[Cita] Atoy, Queenie is missing.
They need your help!
[Atoy] She didn't sleep here last night.
Where could she have gone?
[Rachel] I know she only goes
to school and home. And Bayah Kayakap
Bahay Kayakap?
[Dmitri] We're all here
at Martina's event.
[in English] It's a shelter for women.
- [Audrey] Where is he?
- Who?
[Audrey] I just thought I saw someone.
[Atoy] The guy I fought with
at Endless Nights is here.
[Karla] What's he doing here?
Brother, could there be
an underground fight bar inside?
[Atoy] I don't know.
But every time I see him,
something illegal seems to be happening.
[Peping] But they told us maybe…
Queenie eloped.
She wouldn't do that, Atoy.
[Atoy] Jeff said she had a boyfriend.
She met him on a dating app.
Maybe I'll make a profile on MatchTayo.
Just to check if Queenie's there.
Don't!
[Atoy] Just give me
all the names of the victims.
I'll handle it.
I'll find a way.
PREVIOUSLY
[song concludes]
♪ Fix this ♪
I used to think, Emerson,
that you would get angry
at me if you saw me.
[sniffles]
But it hurts more knowing
that you've already forgotten me.
You've already forgotten me, Emerson.
‪[melancholic music playing]
[door clicks open]
[Cita] Tonet?
[melancholic music playing]
[Tonet] Ah, oh, Miss Cita.
Oh?
[Tonet chuckles softly]
[Cita] Why are you crying?
Oh, nothing.
Is it because Ame
teases you about Emerson?
[quirky sting]
Oh, well, there's nothing wrong
if you like him.
- Huh?
- [quirky sting]
Gross, Miss Cita.
[chuckles]
What's really the problem?
He is my brother.
‪-[dramatic sting]
‪-What? Good heavens!
Emerson is my older brother.
But we haven't seen
each other for a long time.
[nostalgic music playing]
That's why he doesn't
recognize me anymore.
Oh, why don't you introduce yourself?
Go to him.
I'm sure he misses you.
I don't think so.
He's been here a long time.
Has he ever mentioned having a sibling?
Well, it's like…
No, because he's angry with me.
He's very angry with me
because I wronged him.
Maybe he still hasn't forgiven me.
[soft grunt]
You know, Tonet?
It's truly painful
when family members hurt each other.
But if you show him that you are
sincerely asking forgiveness,
and you've become a good person,
your brother won't be able to reject you.
[music fades]
[sauve theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[whirring]
[snipping]
[sewing machine whirring]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots blasting]
[clicking]
[music intensifies]
[knocks on door]
[door clicks open]
[in English] Hi, Dad.
[Dmitri] Hi.
I just wanted to tell you that, um…
I already talked to Martina,
and I put her in her place.
[in English] Dad,
I can take care of myself.
Don't worry. I won't fight with her.
- [in English] Okay?
- [in English] Yeah.
But if your relationship becomes toxic,
while we're all here,
you know, we can probably
go back to the States.
Anyway, my business here is done.
Draco is back with us.
[unsettling music playing]
[in English] I don't think I'm…
ready to go back just yet.
[in English] Is this because…
of the man from your past?
[in English] I'll think about
what you said.
[in English] Okay?
[in English] I just want to rest, for now.
[in English] Good night, Dad.
[in English] Yeah.
[in English] Good night.
‪[music fades]
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Mr. Regalia, I have here
the results of Ms. Audrey's tests.
[in English] Anything
we should be worried about?
Congratulations, sir,
you're going to be a grandfather,
and you'll be an uncle.
[sinister music playing]
[in English] What?
Your daughter is around
five months pregnant.
This explains the physical changes
in her body.
Audrey is pregnant?
But, Doc…
Is it safe for her, and her baby,
with her condition?
[in English] Well, we need to monitor
her pregnancy closely,
and there are some things
I'd like to discuss with you.
- Let's do that later, Doc. Thank you.
- [in English] Excuse me.
[music intensifies]
It looks like Audrey
had a boyfriend on the island.
[in English] Who could be the father
of Audrey's child?
The question is, do you want
to continue the pregnancy?
[in English] Or should we
just terminate it?
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Martina already spoke to the orphanage
that will take the child.
[pensive music playing]
[Red, in English] Don't worry.
[in English] They cannot
trace it back to us.
[in English] Are we really
doing this to Audrey?
It's still her child.
My grandchild! Your niece!
Dad, we don't even know
who got her pregnant.
For all we know,
she hooked up with someone else,
then got pregnant. That's it!
[in English] Don't talk
about your sister that way!
[in English] Dad, Dad. Dad.
Red and I are just thinking
what would happen if Audrey woke up
and she has a child.
What if she looks for the father?
We might lose her forever.
[in English] You lose her forever.
[unsettling music playing]
We should continue with our plan,
the one we had before
we knew she was pregnant.
You should bring her to the US,
get her treated while she's in a coma,
then, when she wakes up,
therapy continues.
You'll rebuild your relationship.
[in English] All will be well.
But that can only happen
if she's free
from distractions and responsibilities.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Red] Martina and I will handle it.
So you won't have to worry.
- [baby cooing]
- [music intensifies]
[baby crying]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
You know…
I really can't stand that woman anymore.
[in English] I need her out of here.
- [sighs]
- Didn't you hear what she said?
She even plans to meddle
in the company, right?
I don't know if she's just provoking us.
[in English] But I won't let her.
Why don't they just go back to the US?
Our setup was perfect then, Red.
We can move the way we want
because they weren't here.
[in English] We even sacrificed
that damn baby to get to this point.
[in English] And now Audrey
is here to ruin everything?
And she claims she'll watch over things,
like she's so good and perfect!
I mean, what kind of girl
gets pregnant by a man
whose name she doesn't even know?
[in English] It doesn't make sense.
I feel like that mystery guy
is the reason she won't leave.
Exactly. What if they see each
other again?
And then they figure out
they have a child.
[in English] What then?
- [in English] Impossible.
- [in English] No.
There's social media now.
[in English] You can find anyone
and everyone there.
How would she know?
She doesn't even know his name, right?
[pensive music playing]
You know what? Don't worry about Audrey.
The time will come that she'll get tired,
and she will realize that… [inhales]
…what she's doing is pointless.
By then…
we'll be the ones to push her
and Dad to go back to the US.
[in English] Relax.
[in English] Okay.
[music fades]
[birds and crickets chirping]
‪[footsteps approaching]
Ma'am, Sir Gavin said
he'll join you for breakfast.
Good. So I'll have someone to eat with.
‪[footsteps approaching]
[utensils clattering]
[mysterious music playing]
What are those… on your necklace?
Um, this, ma'am? It's a scapular.
And the other one?
Is that Saint Anthony?
[maid 1] Yes, ma'am.
[Audrey] Can I see it, please?
It's beautiful.
Where did you get this?
Oh, from the church
of the miraculous saint, ma'am.
The image of Saint Anthony
was missing before, then returned.
And since then, everything and everyone
missing in their barangay
had been found.
[dramatic sting,
sentimental music playing]
[in English] Well, he is
the patron saint of lost things.
Yes, ma'am.
Um, which church is this?
In Barangay Tabang Lupa, Baclaran.
Are you going?
Did you lose something?
[Gavin, in English] I'll take you.
- Really?
- [in English] Yeah.
We play ball with my friends in that area.
[in English] So, I know the place.
[in English] Okay.
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Why do you play in this place?
[in English] Better basketball courts?
[in English] Let me guess.
Prettier girls, right?
Just one girl!
- Hmm.
- [in English] I only have eyes for one.
[in English] And, yes, she's…
She's always around here.
That explains it.
[gentle music playing]
You, Auntie, what are you praying for?
[in English] Closure, I guess.
It feels like I'm getting
mixed signals from the universe.
[in English] I just want closure
once and for all.
- [phone rings]
- Oh!
Uh, Auntie, excuse me.
- I'll just answer my friend's call.
- Yes, go ahead.
[phone clicks]
[Gavin] Hello?
[pensive music playing]
[soft chuckle]
I believe…
you are the one who can give me
the answer I'm looking for.
If it's really meant to be…
you'll find a way for us to meet again.
[music fades]
I spoke with a friend
of another missing girl.
We'll see if there are similarities
with Queenie's case, Father.
If there are, it will surely help us.
The police still have no news.
Oh, Atoy, I pray to Saint Anthony
almost every day
that Queenie will be
returned to us safely!
It will happen, Father.
- It will happen.
- I can hardly eat.
I can't sleep!
I keep thinking of her.
Oh. What happened to that child?
Father, don't worry. It will happen.
I won't stop until she's back with you.
[Peping] I'll get sick from this,
with what's happening…
I don't know what's with that child.
[epic music playing]
[pensive music playing]
Really.
[sobs]
Atoy, uh…
- Help me.
- Father, Father, just a moment.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, wh-where are you going…
Atoy! [gasps]
[invigorating music playing]
[Peping gasps]
Elaine!
[Atoy] Elaine!
[dramatic sting]
[music fades]
[Atoy] Elaine?
[pensive music playing]
[Atoy] Elaine.
Elaine, why didn't you show up at--
Oh. Sorry, miss.
Forgive me. I thought…
I thought…
[somber music playing]
[music intensifies]
Auntie, are you sure you're okay now?
Jason invited me out last minute.
[in English] Go. Be with your friends.
I can go home alone.
[in English] Well, I hope you get
what you prayed for, Auntie.
I hope so.
And good luck with the girls
you'll be courting.
Girls?! None, ah! What girls?
You can't fool me, Gavin.
There's really no one!
[in English] But are you sure you're okay?
- [in English] Promise?
- Go on. Go now.
[in English] Okay. I'll go ahead.
Drive safe!
- [in English] Bye. Have fun!
- [Gavin, in English] Yes!
[gentle music playing]
[girl] Since freshman year,
Mandy and I were roommates.
So we became friends.
Her parents are in the UK,
busy with their careers.
They rarely talk.
But I know the plan was for Mandy
to follow them to the UK
after she graduated.
But then…
She's been missing for a month?
Her parents came back to the Philippines,
but had to return quickly
to the UK for work.
Actually, Mandy's style
of dress suddenly changed.
I was surprised too, because…
Mandy was a soft girl.
Wasn't anyone influencing her?
[suspicious music playing]
Did she meet someone new or…
become friends with someone?
You're also thinking
Mandy eloped, aren't you?
No, no, no.
No, I don't think that about your friend.
Promise, I don't think that about her.
I'm just asking.
I'm checking the similarities
with Queenie.
Queenie met someone.
Became her friend.
She even dated him
through a dating app, MatchTayo.
Do you know that?
Actually, Mandy also had MatchTayo.
She kept her identity secret there.
She told me she was going
to meet a guy at a bar.
But she didn't tell me which one.
And after that…
nothing.
She never came home.
[music intensifies]
[energetic music playing]
I don't want to go to that bar!
It's too early!
It's a restobar. That's why it's open!
Come on!
There's not much work at the shop!
And I want to see the inside,
because many bands play there.
Famous bands!
Perfect timing. Gavin invited us.
[quirky music playing]
You know, I've noticed
something about Gavin.
What?
He's always hanging around here.
And now he's inviting you to a bar.
He likes you.
- Likes? What do you mean likes?
- Likes!
Crush, that's it! He wants to court you!
No way!
Impossible.
[pensive music playing]
Oh?
Hmm, why are you blushing?
- What blushing?!
- Hmm.
So, you like Gavin too?
Then why don't you two just go out?
Go on a date together?
- Hey, don't say that!
- Why should I come along?
Don't say that! We're not leaving
each other, Tonet!
[music fades]
[bustling indistinct chattering]
[Karla] Too bad.
No band yet. It's still early.
[in English] Next time.
[teases]
Wow! So, there's a next date for you two.
Shut up!
[in English] Sorry.
[bustling indistinct chattering]
- OMG, sis!
- What?
- It's Raki!
- Who's that?
[Karla] You don't know?
- Huh?
The vocalist of Munting Sigaw!
That band!
That's him, look!
Sis, he's so handsome!
- [Karla] Hey, sis! Sis!
- [Tonet] Oh, he's coming over.
Hi. I'm Raki.
Hello!
[energetic rock music playing]
Hey!
He's so handsome, sis!
- Huh?
- [scoffs]
Sis, I feel like I'm drowning!
- That's it?
- I met him, finally!
He's my idol!
You're too giddy over that Raki.
Well, of course!
I listen to their music,
then suddenly I meet the vocalist!
You do know band guys
are womanizers, right?
You have so much to say.
Can't I just be excited
because I met someone famous?!
You're overreacting!
Okay.
[upbeat music playing]
I'll step aside. Maybe…
- [Karla] Huh?!
- I might just disturb you.
- [Karla] Stay here.
- Shh. Go on.
This is your moment! Behave.
Sit.
[nervous chuckling]
[in English] Drinks? Coffee, tea, me?
[giggling] Just kidding.
You got this.
[music fades]
Sir, three of your best-selling
non-alcoholic drinks, please.
Okay.
[indistinct chattering]
Mmm, how often do you come here?
Ah, not really, sir.
Don't call me "sir".
[in English] What kind
of music do you like?
[Tonet] Uh, me?
Uh, I'm not really into music.
Are you sure? Not even one?
Actually, I have one favorite…
"Ili-Ili Tulog Anay".
Because my brother used to sing it
when we were kids.
Ma'am, here are your two drinks first.
Can I hear your favorite song?
[Tonet] Sorry, I'll go ahead.
[suspicious music playing]
[laptop keys clicking]
Why do you have a laptop?
- Hmm?
- Are you going to play games?
[in English] Games?
All you think about are games.
That's all that's in your head.
I don't really have anything to do here.
[Atoy] Is that so?
Hmm. [clears throat]
Do you want something to do?
Here.
- What's that?
- Read these names one by one.
[Atoy] Hmm?
[Atoy] What's the first?
‪[mysterious music playing]
Hmm?
Um, whose names are these?
[Atoy] Names of victims.
Names of missing women.
What I'll do is,
after you read me the names,
I'll look up their social media accounts.
I'll check what similarities they have.
Why they became victims.
So, what do you say?
Ah, I don't want to read them anymore.
Why not?
It gives me chills.
"Chills".
Ah, all right. Good luck with that then.
You're creeped out?
Hey, you're just making excuses
because you don't want to read, right?
[sinister music playing]
[music intensifies]
[intense music playing]
[tense music playing]
[Paldo] I can't accept it.
What did Tonet see in Emerson?
I'm more handsome than him.
If you're jealous, close your eyes!
I was going to confess something to you.
[Cita] Maybe you can check on Tonet there?
They said Emerson is furious.
[Emerson] Get out of here!
- [Emerson] Leave!
- [Cita] Emerson!
[Atoy] You could talk this out properly.
You're always acting superior!
You deserve to have your face smashed!
- [clamoring]
- [Cita] Hey! Stop!
UP NEXT
I always check on that child.
But she never mentioned any problem to me.
Doesn't she talk to anyone else?
Lately, she's always on her laptop.
Friday, that was the last day
before she disappeared.
Here, here. This is the last person
she talked to.
[in English] Hey! I know you!
Are you alone?
I have a table there. Come on.
Raki. Raki Roman.
["Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias