[brazen music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[Mercado] Our person already has a lead
on the rooster you asked to be found.
That is good news, Colonel.
[Dmitri, in English] Draco
is my best fighter.
[Mercado] He will get your Draco,
whatever the cost.
[Martina] Why did you come back here?
Dad forced me.
Are you planning to take
the company from Red?
- Bah!
- [Karla shrieks]
[Karla] My God.
[Dmitri] Master Cutter
is close to finding Draco.
[Audrey, in English] Master Cutter?
[in English] He can find anything
or anyone on this earth.
[Audrey, in English] Anything?
[Dmitri, in English] Why?
- [Dmitri] Do you want someone found?
- [in English] Maybe.
[Ibyang] Is a birthday party fun?
[Ibyang] I have not joined
parties like that before.
[Tonet] Poor you.
Oh no, do not continue those thoughts.
It will only be for a moment.
Let go of that.
That is worth more than your life.
Just a moment.
[rooster clucks and flutters]
- [thumps]
- [grunts]
[Dmitri, in English]
Do you have someone in mind?
[Audrey, in English] Yeah.
Someone from my past.
[music concludes]
- Wait, hold on!
- [Tonet] Oh.
Hi, ma'am! Do you have an invitation?
An invitation?
Yes. This birthday party
requires an invitation.
Walk-ins are not allowed.
Ah--
[tense music playing]
- [in English] More! More! More!
- [kids exclaiming]
- [kids cheering]
- [playful music playing]
[applauding]
- [kids] Hi!
- [Ame] What?
Did you find the rooster?
[music continues]
[rooster clucking]
[both chuckle]
[Ame] Oh, come on.
- What? What am I?
- Juggling, juggling.
Ah, juggling, juggling.
- [feint applause]
- [sharp inhale]
[music continues]
[kids cheering]
[music fades]
[sauve music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine whirring]
[gun cocks]
[thumps and gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[music fades]
It is your fault! Why did you do that?!
What did I do?
You ran outside!
So now, what are we going to do?
We left our things inside,
including the invitation!
I am really dead
when your mother finds out!
If she finds out that you went outside,
she will really be angry!
She will call the police, soldiers,
all of them!
- Ma'am.
- I'm here for you.
So, sister, please. Let us go back inside.
My boss will really be angry
if he finds out my charge went out.
Please, come on.
You really are being disobedient.
Hurry. Go back inside.
[soft rock music playing]
She is right. Thank you, sis.
There, she is right.
[music fades]
[elegant classical music playing]
That is Ibyang and Tonet.
What are they doing here?
Oh no. How did Ibyang get here?
[inaudible]
Do not disturb them.
We are just peeking here, right?
- [Ame chuckles]
- [both tittering]
[music fades]
Psst. Hey, Ibyang!
We did not agree you would eat here.
Well, we are already here, sister.
It would be a waste.
[bustling chatter nearby]
Try it. It is super delicious!
All right then.
[bustling chatter nearby]
- Delicious, right?
- [exclaims] It really is delicious!
Get some more.
[bustling chatter nearby]
Oh no! Why is Brother here?
[sneaky music playing]
Why, Sis Tonet?
Which brother?
[music swells]
[in English] And for our final act… This.
- [kids, in English] Yes!
- This ball…
I will turn this into a bird.
[kids gasping and cheering]
[Atoy] Oh!
- [applauding]
- [playful music playing]
[Atoy] Oh, oh.
- [in English] Blow.
- [magical twinkling]
I am not fooling you.
[music swells]
- [kids] Wow!
- [cheering]
I am turning it into a bird for you.
- Wow!
[applause]
[in English] Miss, excuse me.
Where is the opening?
There it is.
- [somber music playing]
- [mumbling]
Wait, wait, wait.
[kids applauding]
[host] Okay, kids, did you enjoy?
- [kids] Yes!
- [applauding]
[host] All right, parents, you may now
get food and drinks at the back.
[in English] Thank you!
Has it been too long,
or did he really forget me,
that is why he did not recognize me?
[Ibyang] Mmm…
What is Emerson doing here?
Everyone from Tabang Lupa
is here, invited?
[buyer] Is there no more bargaining
for Draco?
We both know that you only took
Dmitri's rooster from him.
[in English] Planning,
effort, and execution…
cost a lot of money!
Of course, I need to profit!
Maybe your hens already wore him out.
[in English] You will be the judge.
[in English] He is in prime condition.
Even if you fight him tomorrow,
your win is guaranteed!
[chuckles]
[suspicious music playing]
[Chipper, in English]
What the hell happened?
[tense music playing]
Where is Draco?
[music continues]
Hey! Get up!
Why are you sleeping there?
Where is Draco?
The magician, boss. He was here earlier.
He suddenly attacked me.
Most likely, he is the one
who took the rooster.
Useless!
[music continues]
- [gun cocks]
- [in English] Guys, let's go!
- [kids] Yay!
- [exclaiming]
[in English] Give me that! Who are you?
[in English] You are not my classmate,
and you are not my friend!
Why are you here at my birthday party?!
Atoy, they caught Ibyang.
What are we going to do?
[music intensifies]
Ah, Maya…
[music continues]
Um, they are my siblings.
Yes.
They do not have anyone with them
at home, so I brought them along.
Ah, I was the one who let them in here.
[clicks tongue, in English] Okay, fine.
[in English] Here is your doughnut. Sorry.
[music continues]
[in English] Guys, let us hit the piñata!
- [kids] yay!
- [exclaiming]
[Chipper] Stop that magician!
[tense music playing]
Come on, come on.
[music continues]
Find him!
What?! Find him!
You, you are an idiot!
Hurry!
[music intensifies]
[Tonet pants]
- [Tonet shrieks]
- Oh, wait, wait!
- [Tonet] Ibyang.
- Where are you going?
- [thumps]
- [man] Hey! Oh, hey!
Do not let go of me!
[screams]
[grunts and groans]
[Tonet] Whoa!
[grunting and groaning]
- [Atoy] Go, go, go, go!
- [Ame] Come on!
[Atoy] The phone! The phone!
[tense music playing]
[Ame panting] Wait.
[Tonet] Ame.
[phone rings]
Brother?
- [Atoy] Come on, come on, hurry, hurry.
- [Atoy on phone] Karla!
- We are coming out now.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- [man] Hey, stop!
- [Ame] Oh, Ibyang!
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[car engine revving]
- [Ame shrieks]
- [Atoy] Move aside, move aside!
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[Atoy] Go, go, go.
[Ame] Ibyang!
- [Atoy] Get in, get in, get in.
- Get in now, hurry!
[Atoy] Get in.
[tense music continues]
[Atoy grunts]
[Atoy] Hold on, hold on.
[music continues]
[car engine revving]
Boss, they got away!
Go!
[music fades]
So until now, no one has seen
the old man who caused trouble at the bar?
What is that, a ghost?
Find him!
[phone blips]
[Red] Idiot.
[pensive music playing]
‪[Martina sighs]
[liquor pouring]
Do you want your head to get even hotter?
[sniffles, sighs]
What is that?
I spoke with the prodigal daughter.
[in English] It seems like Dad is going
to give her the company.
[music intensifies]
What is your read?
Does Dad already know
about the projects I am hiding?
He might be hearing things,
but nothing concrete.
[in English] Do not worry.
The main building is almost done.
And once Dad sees that,
he will see nothing wrong with you.
[in English] He might even
be proud of you.
[music fades]
[in English] The real problem
is your sister.
[tense music playing]
We need to find a way
for her to return to the U.S.
[in English] No Audrey… no problem.
[music continues]
[music fades]
[gentle music playing]
This is important to me.
[Atoy] I will come back to this.
I will come back for you.
Tonight, I will explain everything to you.
[dramatic sting]
Did he look for me
when I suddenly disappeared?
[Dmitri] Master Cutter
is close to finding Draco.
[in English] He is a tracker.
[in English] He can find anything
or anyone on this earth.
[suspicious music playing]
Ma'am, here is the food
you asked to be cooked.
Ah, later, miss.
I will just go see Dad first.
[in English] Thank you!
We have been here for a while.
Well, because we cannot
go straight to the gate.
They are already
watching us there with security.
- Because you even brought Ibyang inside.
- [somber music playing]
We could have already left earlier.
I was the one who invited Sister Tonet.
I just wanted to eat at the birthday.
Ibyang, why did you come along here?
Did Atoy not say he does not like
annoying and stubborn people?
He will be angry again with you.
Sorry.
Apologize to Sister.
[somber music playing]
Oh?
Why do your faces look so sad?
[Karla, in English] Don't worry.
Brother Atoy already foresaw
situations like this.
We will get out of here alive.
[brazen music playing]
[Atoy] Hurry, hurry, hurry, Karla!
[brazen music continues]
I am almost done here.
[Karla] I am almost there too, Brother.
[Atoy] Oh, go, go, go, go!
[music continues]
BAYANET
SURELY CONNECTED
[Atoy] Is it done?
- [Karla] This is the last one.
- [Atoy] Is it done?
[music fades]
You are all idiots!
All of you were slipped past!
The magician's companions,
one woman and two kids!
What? Have you seen them?
Boss, all our roving guards are moving.
But they are all posted
at the village gate.
- Just make sure they do not get out.
- [tense music playing]
[in English] I want Draco back,
and I want that man's head!
[tense music playing]
[guard] There, the van.
It is white!
With a red sticker
is what we are watching for.
Did you not read it? Bayanet!
And it is marked for us,
The Amazing Tomtom!
[music fades]
[woman on phone] Sorry, sir.
We do not know the magician
you are talking about.
You work there, but you do not know them?
[scoffs]
Maybe you are an accomplice
of the thief, huh?
[in English] Let me speak to your boss!
[woman on phone]
Sorry, sir. What I mean is,
we do not know the magician,
because we did not send anyone there.
Did you not cancel the booking?
Are you making me a liar?
I was not calling to cancel the booking!
[woman on phone] Wait, sir,
I have a recording of our conversation.
We do that in case situations
like this happen.
- [phone bleeps]
- We have a policy that if you cancel,
the down payment will not be refunded.
[Atoy on phone, in English]
That is all right.
Ah, the child changed her mind.
Ah, she does not want to see a magician.
[phone blips]
[brazen music playing]
- [gunshots blasting]
- [screaming]
You are unbelievable.
Oh, boss, thank you.
[guard, in English] Sir, sir, sir!
[music fades]
Boss…
What happened to your mouth?
[ominous music playing]
His mouth? Oh! We ate spaghetti.
- Brother! It is your fault!
- [mutters]
That spaghetti was intense!
Brother, you are like a child
when you eat.
The spaghetti they gave
is really delicious…
- Yes.
- Ah.
Ah, because there was spaghetti
being given there.
Yes, this was from
the party earlier, brother.
- [guard] Is that so?
- Delicious, yes.
- [guard] Okay, boss.
- All right, thank you!
- [guard] Okay.
- [Karla] Thank you!
["Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, tailor! Holding the scissors ♪
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
You take over there.
[Tonet] Go ahead.
[Karla] Ibyang still has so much to say.
- Sir Atoy! Sorry about that!
- [Atoy] Oh, Kurt!
I asked around where you live because…
This is just my thank you to you.
- Ahh.
- "Kuya Kurt Sarap Pares"!
- Wow! Wow!
- Oh, that is for you.
- This is so delicious. How is it there?
- Yes.
Is it okay now?
- No one is bothering?
- Oh, it is fine.
Well, if you really ask me,
now I have a spot here and--
Well, well, it is nearby.
You should drop by sometime.
- Yes, we will visit.
- Yes, perfect.
There you go! That works.
These ones eat a lot of pares.
All right. I am ready for that.
- [chuckles]
- [Atoy] Okay!
- Thank you so much.
- Kurt, take care.
- All right, thank you.
- If there is a problem, just call.
Just you. All right. Thank you.
Oh, psst. Leave some for me, okay?
- Bro, watch this because, you know… Mmm.
- [phone rings]
[Atoy] Boss…
[Atoy on phone] Mission accomplished.
I told you I would not be embarrassed.
What do you want?
I will return this vehicle to you.
Should I bring it along?
Actually, I am outside now
with the client.
Then maybe just bring it here?
[Atoy on phone, in English] Okay, sir. Uh…
Just text me the address.
I will deliver it to you.
- Okay.
- [Atoy on phone, in English] Okay, boss.
[suspicious music playing]
[chuckles softly]
My man already has your rooster.
You will be reunited soon.
- [in English] Wow! That is very good!
- [Mercado chuckles]
‪[both chuckle]
- [in English] All right, let's go!
- [in English] Okay.
[music continues]
[chuckles grunts]
[Dmitri] This is really good news.
[chuckles]
Oh, they are asking me
to return the rooster.
Thank you again for your help.
- Atoy.
- Yes.
I just want to ask
for forgiveness for earlier.
Let us talk about what you
and Ibyang did when I get back.
Go ahead.
Thanks again. Go on.
Ibyang, leave some for me!
- [overlapping chatter]
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, thank you.
- Take care.
[suspicious music playing]
Who are those people?
What are they doing at Atoy's place?
[music continues]
So, Sister Ame?
I told you, Master is grumpy, right?
His grumpiness is understandable.
You and Tonet are at fault.
I just felt sorry for your sister.
At fault already?
You know, I should have been
the one Atoy brought inside.
If you are jealous, just close your eyes.
[whimsical music playing]
Wait a minute.
Maybe you intentionally
made my makeup thick, right?
That is why I have been itchy.
It is thick because you have many pores.
Of course I have pores.
What do you think my skin is, an onion?
No, sandpaper.
- Hey, stop it already!
- [music concludes]
Why are you fighting?
Is it because of Brother Atoy?
- Hmm? No.
- Oh, no!
‪[whimsical music playing]
Stay here.
You two.
[music fades]
- Padua.
- [Atoy] Sir!
Here it is.
May I see the rooster?
- Mmm.
- Very much alive.
Colorful.
Well, it really is impressive.
I will give this to the client,
and I will just send
the balance later. Okay?
- No problem, sir. Thank you.
- [Dmitri] Colonel!
[tense music playing]
Colonel.
Is this Draco?
[in English] May I see?
[music continues]
- I will go ahead, sir.
- [in English] Hold on.
[Dmitri, in English] Is he the one?
Is this the tracker you are proud of?
[tense music playing]
[in English] I am sorry, Colonel.
I should not have followed you.
[Dmitri, in English]
But I could not help myself.
[in English] I want to meet
the man himself.
[in English] I am Dmitri. And you are?
[music intensifies]
[in English] I get it.
[in English] No name.
[music fades]
[in English] I will just call you
the Master Cutter.
[tense music playing]
Guys…
Do you know the newcomers around Atoy?
You know, the new provincial assistant?
The girl who arrived
in the past few weeks.
- Ohh. Boss!
- I know her.
I have already seen her, right?
What I mean is, the two kids.
Kids?
- Does Atoy have adopted children?
- Hmm?
- [groans]
- That is why I am asking you,
because I do not know!
- Well, that is on you.
- You are unbelievable.
What are you thinking?
[pensive music playing]
I think there is…
Atoy is doing something illegal.
What kind of illegal thing is that, Boss?
- [in English] Child labor.
- [Tukmol] Oh, right.
- [Munggo] Oh…
- That is my hunch.
[Tukmol] That is serious.
[music continues]
I am sure
Atoy is hiding something.
We need to find out.
[music fades]
Chipper Arenas?
[in English] Yes, sir.
That bastard, that demon.
By any chance, do you accept
special assignments?
[suspicious music playing]
Sorry, sir, but… [clears throat]
I only do tracking.
[music continues]
[in English] All right.
I will handle Chipper myself.
- [music continues]
- [phone ringing]
Excuse me. I will just answer this.
Yes, child?
[in English] Hey, Dad!
You are at the golf course, right?
[in English] Why are you asking?
Are you not with
that acquaintance who has…
a known contact who is a tracker?
Master Cutter.
[in English] I want to meet him.
I think he can help me.
He already left earlier.
[in English] Ah, okay. It is fine.
I will just go there anyway.
I already left the golf course.
[in English] No, you did not.
[in English] I am looking at your car
in the parking lot right now.
You are weird, Dad.
[in English] I am on my way inside.
[music continues]
[in English] I have a slight problem.
[in English] My daughter is here.
And it seems she also
wants something found.
[in English] Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Because I told her that you already left.
[in English] Can you just pretend you are
just normal people that I golf with?
[in English] And you are not
the Master Cutter.
You do not want what she wants found?
[in English] I am just
looking out for her.
[in English] It is for her own good.
[tense music playing]
Sir, maybe she is looking
for an ex-boyfriend, right?
Or maybe a man who cheated on her.
[music intensifies]
[in English] Dad!
- [electronic blipping]
- [music intensifies]
[Dmitri] That man is important to Audrey.
What if we made a mistake
in what we did before?
[in English] What is important
is that we protect our secret.
[Audrey, in English] What secret?
Look, there is an issue now on FlipTok.
There are missing women.
The police say they ran away.
But the families say they met someone
on a dating app and then disappeared.
Atoy, Queenie is missing.
[Cita] They need your help.
[Atoy] Where is the usual place
she hangs out?
[Rachel] I only know school and home.
And at Bahay Kayakap.
UP NEXT
[brazen music playing]