♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix this ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
♪ Holding the scissors
One cut, and it's settled ♪
[audience exclaims]
[Janine] Even if she's joined
by her fake father,
the people are still laughing at her.
- [audience exclaims]
- [Janine cackles]
[audience] Ibyang! Ibyang!
It feels like my performance
turned out better.
Thank you, Master. You're the best!
We both know you're the one
who put blue paint on my face.
Don't accuse me!
[Janine shrieks]
Ibyang, what are you doing to Janine?!
She should be the one apologizing to me!
She's a bad kid!
Stop it!
[Ibyang] I grew up in an orphanage.
Master Atoy and Sis Tonet
stand as my parents.
And that's probably
the greatest gift they've given me.
[cheering]
[sobs] Our child is making me cry.
[principal, in English] Our 2026
Little Miss Primary School,
Ms. Janine Ranoy!
[Ibyang] It's okay with me
that I didn't win
because the whole experience was so fun!
[Atoy] So? Did you enjoy?
It feels like this is
the best day of my life!
Can you be my official Daddy Atoy?
PREVIOUSLY
I'd love that.
[music fades]
Dear…
So, where do you want
to display your crown?
It's beautiful.
Just keep it in your room.
It doesn't mean anything to me anyway.
Huh?
How could you say that!
[sighs] Even though I won,
everyone still likes Ibyang more!
Janine, you did well.
It's just that she really had
a lot of people with her.
Did you notice?
It was like the whole barangay was there.
So, why didn't you bring more friends?
[somber music playing]
Um, because, dear. Well, um…
Here's what we'll do.
To end this,
I think I need to transfer you
to a new school.
I'll talk to your teacher tomorrow. Okay?
Right away?
I thought we'll do it next year?
I don't want to transfer schools.
Janine, this fight between you
and Ibyang isn't healthy anymore.
That's why I want to transfer you
as soon as possible.
You're so stubborn, Mommy!
I don't want to!
My friends are there!
Don't talk to me like that.
[in English] I'm still your mother!
[unsettling music playing]
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
[suave theme music playing]
Oh, ma'am!
Why are you still awake?
Nanny, how many kids
do you have in the province?
I have six children.
Two are here in Manila.
Why do you ask?
Because this is all new to me.
Being a mother.
But why… why do I feel this way
about my own child?
What do you mean?
[somber music playing]
I feel so distant from her.
Like she didn't come from me.
Sometimes she just annoys me.
It's exhausting.
Ma'am, it's normal to feel annoyed
and tired with our children.
We, parents, are only human.
And Ma'am Janine grew up
with other people,
so she picked up habits
that aren't like yours.
I know that.
But she's so different from…
[music fades]
[maid] Excuse me, ma'am.
I hate to say it, Audrey, but…
you should be the one adjusting
to your own child.
[in English] You're supposed
to love them, accept them,
and mold them in the right direction.
What you're feeling about
Janine isn't helping.
I wouldn't feel this way about Janine
if you hadn't separated me from my child.
That's still your issue?
[in English] You can't keep blaming
everything on the past.
[in English] Oh my God, Audrey!
She's still your daughter, no matter what!
[sinister music playing]
[in English] Wow! I knew it!
- Can I taste it, Aunt?
- Ah, w-w-wait!
It's still hot!
[in English] Let it cool down first.
[in English] Um, so what's up with you?
You know, Janine won the school pageant.
Yes, I heard. Mommy told me.
[in English] It's nice to hear.
- Amazing.
- I wish you were there.
[in English] Um, what's been
up with you lately?
I'm excited.
At the same time, I feel nervous.
I have an upcoming date.
[in English] Ah, wow!
[in English] That's great news.
[in English] Care to share?
[in English] Hmm, next time, Auntie.
When I actually have something
to share with you.
Okay.
[pensive music playing]
- Delicious!
- [Audrey] Oh!
This is my new favorite.
[in English] Are you okay, Auntie?
Huh?
Are you okay?
[in English] Yes. Of course, I'm fine.
It's just that…
Janine often fights
with someone at school.
[in English] Her name is Ibyang.
Is this the same girl
she fought with at the theme park?
[in English] Yes.
[in English] You know, I don't want
to sound like a bad mother.
[in English] But I can't help but think…
What if Janine really is the one
at fault in her quarrels with Ibyang?
Like at the pageant, they were fighting!
Of course, I'll side
with my daughter, Janine.
But I feel guilty because…
I raised my voice at Ibyang.
[gentle music playing]
I don't know what to do anymore.
It's simple, Auntie.
If you think you were out of line,
then make it up to her.
I'm sure she'll forgive you.
[Cita] Oh, didn't I tell you, Atoy?
Your fatherly instinct
for Ibyang is natural.
She told me she already calls you "Tatoy".
So why don't you make it official?
- [in English] Official?
- Hmm.
You mean, to adopt her?
Yes. Didn't you say your search
for her parents was a dead end?
[mellow music playing]
Well…
Yes. 'Nang,
I really thought about that.
Oh? What's the problem?
But of course…
My work.
If I commit to that,
I can't just neglect her.
I'd have to dedicate my time
to raising her properly.
That wouldn't be possible.
But you did give her time
during the pageant, didn't you?
You even stayed up late making her gown.
[Cita] Hmm.
Just think about it, Atoy, but…
it's good you're considering it.
My concern is…
This is a commitment. Priorities.
And I know you.
If you really want to make it happen,
you can!
[chuckles softly]
[light music playing]
[muffled chattering in the distance]
Dear, um…
[girl twitter]
[in English] I'm sorry about last night.
If you don't want to transfer schools,
that's fine with me.
I just don't want you
always fighting with Ibyang.
I'll just ignore her.
That's better, dear.
All right then. Have a great day.
[in English] I love you.
[in English] Okay.
Okay, Mom?
[sighs]
Okay, Mom.
[Audrey chuckles softly]
[in English] Goodbye, dear.
I'll see you later.
[muffled chattering in the distance]
[sneaky music playing]
[Atoy] What happened to your cheek?
- Huh?
- Ah, nothing. Just scratched it.
Hey, listen to me.
If ever I'm late picking you up,
make sure you never go
with anyone else, all right?
You will only go with me. Wait for me.
Okay.
- All right.
- Tatoy, I love you!
Hmm, love you. Love you.
All right. Okay now.
All right.
Psst! Don't be stubborn, okay?
Yes.
[muffled chattering in the distance]
Ibyang!
[somber music playing]
Uh, s-sorry.
Did I startle you?
Not really.
I just wanted…
to apologize to you.
Because I raised my voice
at you during the pageant.
You didn't deserve that.
It's okay.
I'm sorry too
if I pushed your child.
I have a surprise for you.
[Audrey] Hmm, hmm.
Your favorite!
Are you serious?
It's part of my apology to you.
[in English] I'm sorry.
[light feel-good music playing]
Thank you!
But I don't have porridge to give you.
Don't worry. It's fine.
I just hope…
you and Janine get along.
That's my only wish.
That's what I want too.
All right then!
You might be late!
Thank you again!
[in English] Bye!
[in English] Bye-bye!
[chuckles softly]
[Janine] Take a look at this.
Mommy baked this for me.
We have a big oven at home.
It must be expensive. It's huge!
[in English] Wow!
Looks delicious. Can I have some?
No!
Mommy made this for me,
and you're taking one?
So selfish.
So, are you guys coming later?
- We're swimming at our mansion.
- Of course.
We're excited.
Mabel, if you want some,
I won't share, okay?
Huh? I have some too. Look.
[suspicious music playing]
Huh?
Where did you get that?
- Did you take that from my bag?
- No, Janine.
Ibyang gave this to me.
It looks just like your packed food.
What?!
[tense music playing]
Ibyang!
Where did you get those cookies, huh?
Why?
Your mommy gave them to me.
Do you want some?
What do you mean "want"?
You shouldn't even have that.
Why?
Before you even met your mommy,
we already knew each other.
And she made me taste these first.
I can give you some if you want. Here.
No!
[intense music playing]
Hey-- [gasps]
You're wasting food!
Ame.
[Ame] Hmm?
Can I ask you something?
Of course. I can never say no to you!
[smirks] No!
Do you know or are you familiar
with the process of…
adoption?
For whom?
[somber music playing]
For you!
Of course not. Of course it's not for you!
For… you know who!
[gasps]
Really? You're planning to adopt her?
Well…
- [inhales]
- [sentimental music playing]
Shh. Don't tell anyone yet.
Don't say it to anyone.
Hmm, okay, okay. It's a secret.
- It's a secret. Mmm-mmm.
- Secret?
Oh, she'll be so happy!
[in English] Welcome to our home, girls!
[Janine] See? I told you!
It's a mansion!
There's the pool.
Go ahead.
Nanny, accompany them. Please.
Okay, Auntie. Thank you.
We'll go ahead, Janine.
Janine.
Is something wrong?
You've been quiet.
I thought you'd enjoy swimming
with your friends.
[unsettling music playing]
How can I be happy?
You also gave Ibyang
the same cookies you gave me.
Oh, there's nothing wrong with that, dear.
I only did it as a peace offering.
- Because I want you two to get along.
- There's no way.
I don't want to be friends with her.
I already have friends, right?
And I don't want you to be friends
with Ibyang either,
because I'm your daughter, Mommy!
[in English] Yes, sir.
I can go to you, sir.
[in English] Okay.
Atoy, can I borrow some money
for my commute?
I just want to have Ibyang checked up.
Oh, why? What happened to her?
Well, she got rashes on her face.
Maybe because of the poster paint.
[pensive music playing]
So that's why her face is red.
Oh, that Ibyang.
Why didn't she say anything?
Well, you know that child.
If you don't push her, she won't speak.
All right, I'll go with you.
Oh, no need.
Ibyang's already troubled you enough.
And I heard you have work to do.
So what? I can cancel that.
Don't. Go to your work.
I'll take care of Ibyang.
It's not that serious.
I just want to be sure.
All right then.
Here.
For your expenses.
Thank you.
That Ibyang is really annoying.
I feel like putting blue paint
on her face again.
She's such a pest!
Even meddling with my mommy.
Hey, don't!
She was already humiliated at the pageant.
Well, that's just right.
Come on, help me think
of what we can do to her next.
Janine.
[dramatic sting]
So, it's true what Ibyang said?
That you're the one behind
the blue paint on her face?
[tense music playing]
Mommy…
- You heard it wrong--
- [in English] I heard you, Janine!
Don't lie to me!
I defended you!
And it turns out you're the one at fault?!
[pensive music playing]
Janine.
Janine, where are you going? Let's talk!
What?
You're going to scold me?
You're really siding with that Ibyang?
Child, I'm not siding with anyone!
But I know what's right and wrong!
And what you did was wrong!
It wasn't wrong.
That Ibyang is such a show-off.
So, she deserved it.
[tense music playing]
Mmm.
Good thing you're free today.
I'm not used to you refusing a job order.
Sorry, sir.
I really just needed to attend
Ibyang's school event.
That's good, that you have
another life aside from this.
[in English] Anyway…
let's get to the mission.
[in English] Yes, sir.
A Mrs. Santos came to me.
She's risking half her life savings
just to find and send this man to jail.
Aldrin Galang.
Mrs. Santos's husband met
with Aldrin Galang.
He was supposed to be
the buyer of their car.
But he never came back.
After one week, her husband
was found with his head bound,
his body burned.
Dead.
That Aldrin Galang is the prime suspect.
It's been months,
but the police still haven't caught him.
Based on my intel,
he's been collecting from vendors
at Road 23, Barangay Macario.
Barangay Macario.
[suspicious music playing]
I know where that is.
[in English] Good.
So, Atoy?
Shall we help Mrs. Santos?
[in English] Yes, sir.
I'll take care of it.
I'll start now.
Thank you, Atoy.
Maintain high vigilance on the target.
Very hostile, possibly connected
to the syndicate.
[in English] Watch your back.
Copy, sir. I'll handle it.
[rock music playing]
[Mercado sighs]
- [Audrey] Janine?
- [girl] Yummy.
- Janine?
- [girl] Mmm.
Kids, did you see Janine?
[girl] We've been looking
for her for a while.
Audrey.
[gasps]
[in English] What's going on?
Dad, I've been looking
for Janine all over.
I even asked security to look for her.
But I-I don't know where she is!
What really happened?
I scolded her earlier,
then she walked out.
Now I can't find her.
[door lock clicks]
[maid] Ma'am Audrey.
[suspicious music playing]
We saw on the CCTV.
Janine slipped out through the back gate.
What? My granddaughter ran away?
Why was there no guard at the back?
[tense music playing]
We need to send my men to look for her.
Ah, wait, Dad.
Let me do it first.
I feel like I know where she went.
‪[Audrey sighs]
[Atoy] Tonet.
Deliver that tomorrow.
I need your help.
Can you help me…
[soft rock music playing]
Looks like you've got a mission, Atoy.
That's right.
What's the look you're going for?
This.
Oh. Ah…
This is easy.
Oh, wait.
Why are you waiting on the street?
Who are you looking for?
[rock music playing]
A criminal.
[Mongki] What's up, Boss?
You suddenly called.
I'm short on shipment.
We need to order new stock.
Yes, Boss. What's the hustle?
[Mongki on phone] I'll have some
quality shipment picked up.
Maybe just one or two.
- You're new here, huh?
- [Emerson stutters]
[Emerson] Atoy, is that really you?
[Red] I know you know
what I'm talking about.
You're from the same congregation.
I know your clothing!
[scoffs] Nun--
- [quirky sting]
- Why are you picking on a nun?
Why are you meddling?
Do you want me to pinch you, huh?!
Oh, what, what? Oh, what?!
Son of a thread. They caught on!
UP NEXT
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor… ♪
- [horn honks]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor
Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut… ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias