[brazen music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[Lorna] For now, I need someone
to guard the gold card area.
[Atoy] Ma'am, I'll do it.
You can't. You're new.
You might mess things up there.
The customers there tip big,
especially those betting on fights.
[Atoy] What? Boxing, like that?
[janitor] But the ones fighting
are little people.
It's brutal.
PREVIOUSLY
[Darryl] No one else can help you
get out of here but yourself.
[in English] Red, how are you?
[Vladimir, in English] How about we find
a place where we can meet Manny Pacquiao?
[in English] You know any?
[Red, in English] I actually know a place.
[Vladimir, in English] Oh, let's go.
[Ibyang] I hope he finds Big Sister Ame,
so I can leave this place.
[Vladimir, in English]
What is this place, Red?
[Red, in English]
You're gonna love this place.
[in English] It's a, uh,
battle of mini gladiators.
[Cita] Your Brother Atoy will never stop
until he finds your Big Sis Ame.
- [Cita] That's the kind of person he is.
- [clatters]
- That's been going on for a while.
- [waiter, in English] Sorry, sir!
[waiter] There's someone
messing around here.
[curious upbeat music playing]
[MC, in English] And for our next fight,
it's going to be a rematch
between two rivals.
Now, they are going to settle the score.
It's a fight to the death with
- Tessie Bangis
- [crowd cheering]
versus
The Amazing Ame!
[crowd cheering and applauding]
[MC, in English]
Who will emerge as the winner?
- [curious upbeat music continues]
- [phone keys tapping]
Hello?
Where are you? Are you okay?
Are you out of the hospital?
Boss Red, why?
What do you mean why?
I'm here at Endless. Come here!
Okay, Boss, I'll follow.
I just need to collect something.
Hello?
[crowd buzzing]
[tense music playing]
- [curious upbeat music playing]
- [crowd cheering]
[woman] Sir.
[ref] Are you ready?
Are you ready?
Since yesterday, Boss. Let's do this.
[ref] Touch glove.
- [ref] Box.
- [bell dings]
I'm really going to finish you now.
[brazen music playing]
[whooshing]
[crowd gasps, whistles, cheers]
[in English] Yes! I love it!
[in English] This is good!
[crowd clamoring]
[crowd gasps, buzzing]
[brazen music continues]
[whooshing]
- [in English] This is very, very good!
- [crowd cheering]
[laughs]
That Atoy lives here.
[inquisitive music playing]
I know someone who can make him obey.
Oh, gosh.
Do it, please.
[waiter] Sorry, sir.
[Atoy, in English] Oh, no.
It's okay, sir, we'll help you.
- [patron] Go on, carry him.
- [Atoy] I'll get a mop.
[patron] Go on, hurry up.
[suave music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[brazen music playing]
[in English] Finish her!
[thuds]
[in English] Finish her now!
[crowd cheering]
Agh! [in English] I love it!
I love the Philippines!
[laughs]
Yes! Whoo!
- One! Two!
- [crowd cheering]
Three! Four!
Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine!
- Ten!
- [bell dinging]
[MC, in English] We have a winner!
The Amazing Ame!
- [brazen music playing]
- [crowd cheering]
[in English] Nice win!
Oh!
- [in English] You liked it, huh?
- [in English] I love it!
[in English] I love the Philippines!
- [Red chuckles]
- Whoo!
[crowd applauding]
[melancholic music playing]
[in English] I love this girl.
[in English] Who is she?
[in English] Oh, Amazing Ame, yes.
[crowd whistling, applauding]
[gasps]
[in English] Listen, Red.
[in English] I want to meet
the Amazing Ame.
[in English] Okay, I can
make arrangements. Don't worry.
[in English] Very good, very good.
[in English] It's because I have
a Japanese client.
- [in English] Very, very rich.
- [in English] Okay.
[in English] And he's into midgets!
[laughs]
[in English] We say "little persons" here
in the Philippines, okay?
- [in English] That's the rule, okay?
- [in English] Okay.
[in English] But okay,
let's talk business.
[in English] Okay, good.
[in English] The gameplan…
[in English] If you
can give me Amazing Ame,
I promise you it'll be worth your while.
Because it's very hard to find
a "little person"
with a beautiful, pretty face like hers,
- Right?
- [laughs]
[in English] Don't worry.
I can make that happen.
I'll take care of that for you.
- [in English] This is it. I love you!
- [laughs]
- [in English] Yes, I love the Philippines!
- [in English] Hey, hey, hey!
[in English] Don't forget
my finder's fee, okay?
- [in English] I got you.
- [in English] Good.
- [in English] Cheers!
- [chuckles]
[Vladimir gasps]
[laughs]
- [in English] My man, my man.
- [in English] Yes.
[Paldo] One of those, Miss Siony.
- Just one?
- Just one, just one.
[Paldo] That's it!
- So, bro, you want one?
- Go ahead.
Just soft drinks for me, sis.
How many? What kind of soft drinks?
Whatever is cold. Anything you got.
[phone ringing]
[inquisitive music playing]
[man] Mongki?
Isn't that the guy you sold the statue to?
Why don't you want to answer?
Maybe it's good sign.
Does he owe you money?
I don't want to deal with him anymore.
You know, I regret
ever meeting these people.
Maybe that's another hustle.
It's fine if it's just a hustle.
But if innocent people got implicated…
Huh? What are you saying?
- [tires screeching]
- [thuds]
Boss, that might be Atoy's father.
[Paldo] You might have killed him.
Boss, he had no beef with us.
This imbecile Paldo,
he's really unreliable.
So, what now, Boss?
Tabang Lupa is quite big.
So, what?
You don't want revenge anymore?
Then I'll just look for him myself! Go on!
- Go on, leave!
- [thug 1] It's not like that, Boss.
- We want to make up for it.
- Then there you go!
You talk too much.
Let's go!
[man] Hmm…
- What? You like it?
- [in English] Thank you!
[in English] Good. Welcome.
Now, call Georgia.
I have a gift for her too, okay?
Don't be jealous.
You both have one anyway.
Go on. Go on.
- [in English] Okay.
- [in English] Okay, good.
[in English] Bye.
[inquisitive music playing]
[in English] What the hell?
[in English] Someone stole
my freaking jacket!
Yes, sir? Is there a problem?
Someone took my jacket.
There's a Rolex in the pocket. Goddamnit!
Who? A customer?
[in English] No.
I think it was the janitor
who was here earlier.
The one who wiped the spilled drink.
Which one of them?
We have many janitors here.
[in English] Stupid question!
Of course, I don't know!
[in English] I want my jacket back now!
[in English] I pay a premium
yearly membership here!
Okay, sir. I'll have
the security guys check on it.
- Okay!
- Sorry, sir.
[brazen music playing]
[Atoy] That's good.
[inquisitive music playing]
We're being called to the main room.
Huh? Why?
A customer is complaining.
Something is missing.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Okay, I'll follow.
[foreboding music playing]
- Sis…
- Mmm?
Miss Cita's new bed spacer is pretty.
Oh, you like her?
Just because I find her pretty,
you think I like her?
- I'm choosy, you know!
- [indistinct]
- The green one, cold.
- But you're right, she's pretty.
- They say she's from Cebu. Mmm-hmm!
- [girl] Cebu?
- Isn't Emerson from Cebu too?
- [girl] That's how it works…
Yes, but it's been a while
since I went home.
But you still have relatives there.
Your siblings are still there, right?
[uneasy music playing]
Just asking.
- [woman 1] Ouch.
- [woman 2] Huh? What's that?
Do you know Atoy?
[Mongki] You?
Wait, wait, wait…
You, don't act tough in front of me, okay?
You don't know me.
That's the thing.
You're not from here.
Bunda, who's your enemy?
[Bunda] Well, it's this one--
- [thuds]
- [clamoring]
[cheering] What?! Feels good?!
Huh?! What?! Huh, huh?!
[clamoring]
[thudding]
[intense music playing]
You're so fierce, Ame.
You're terrifying.
Thank you, Darryl.
If not for you, I wouldn't have
learned how to fight in the ring.
I'm happy I was able
to help you, even just a little.
[door clicks open]
[uneasy music playing]
[MC] Get ready.
You have another fight, Ame.
Who will I be fighting?
That one, Darryl.
Do they really do that here?
Woman against man?
We don't have a choice
but to follow orders.
[uneasy music continues]
Don't hold back, Ame.
Knock me down.
I won't do that.
This could be your tenth win,
and if that happens,
you'll be able to leave this place.
You need to win
because your father needs you.
If I win, we won't see each other again.
You have no allies here.
Do this for your father.
Defeat me later.
When you get out of here, find Ibyang.
[stirring music continues]
[suave music playing]
[squelching]
[brazen music playing]
[groovy ambient music playing]
[rich patron] What now?!
- [rich patron] Is everyone here?
- [employee] Yes, sir.
Only one janitor is missing.
Our guys are looking for him.
[employee] Did you see that janitor here?
His name is Jeffrey Matulak.
[janitor] I really can't find him.
Earlier, he was just in the locker room.
[employee] Open your eyes.
He's still inside.
[stirring music playing]
Bro.
- PJ.
- [light music playing]
Do you know where the girl
we played against earlier lives?
Karla, the one who beat us?
Karla? More like Karlo.
You really had to remind me.
We really got crushed.
No, but I know where that one lives.
[dreamy music playing]
Where's my cap?
[Karla] Oh, no, I think I left it
at the court. No cap.
Wishful thinking. It's because
you don't take care of your stuff.
Mom, it's hard to play basketball
wearing a cap, you know.
Sir Delfin gave that to me.
I hope it's still there.
Mom, I'll go out for a bit, okay?
I'll go get my cap.
Make sure that's the only place
you're going, okay?
- [Cita] It's late. Come home right away.
- [Karla] Okay.
There's a rumble at the corner!
Emerson and Bunda Girl
are being ganged up on!
- [Karla] Oh, no! Let's go, let's go!
- [Tonet] Miss Cita, I need to go there!
Stay here, okay? Lock the door.
Don't let anyone in, okay?
Be careful.
Lock this! Lock it now. Go on!
Lock it, Ibyang!
[tense music continues]
- Boss, one order of siomai.
- All right.
What's happening there?
Is there a robbery?
It's chaos out there.
Looks like the new janitor
they're accusing of stealing
from a customer managed to escape.
- [vendor] Oh?
- [security] Mmm-hmm.
Really?
What was taken?
An expensive watch, but it was returned.
Maybe he got scared and backed out.
[vendor] Oh? With so many of them there,
he still escaped?
[security] Exactly. I don't know.
[inquisitive music playing]
- [security] Where, bro?
- [vendor] There.
[security] Okay, that's fine, boss.
[Ibyang] Let's eat first!
We haven't even ordered here yet.
Siomai is my favorite.
Boss, I'll get takeout.
- [vendor] One, boss?
- No, three.
[vendor] Okay, boss.
[bright music playing]
[mellow music playing]
[cheeky music playing]
You're really beautiful, Ibyang.
Beautiful.
But stubborn.
But at least, we're not cruel
like the others out there.
[scoffs]
This suits me.
[clicking and clacking]
[electronic blipping]
[curious music playing]
What is this?
Bat cave?
[curious music continues]
[electronic blipping]
[clamoring]
What's happening here?
Hey! Stop it!
- [clamoring]
- [thudding]
Stop it!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[Cita] Karla! Karla! Karla!
Karla! Karla! Karla!
[clamoring]
Hey!
What's this chaos?!
[clamoring continues]
Hey! That's enough. Stop it. Stop it!
That's enough! That's enough!
- [Paldo] Enough!
- [clamoring continues]
[Paldo] Enough!
[Paldo] Stop it! Stop it!
[clamoring continues]
[man] Karla! Enough! Stop it!
Hey! What's going on?!
You're just meddling!
You're all outsiders!
- [gun firing]
- [Mongki screaming]
What?! Huh?!
Who else is brave here?! What?!
[breathing heavily]
[Cita whimpering]
What?! You think you're tough?!
Where's your cojones?!
I'm only looking
for one person here! Atoy!
So, if you don't want
to get dragged into this,
just answer me!
- Bro, bro…
- [indistinct chattering]
Bro, wait, calm down.
Calm down, calm down.
The person you're looking for
isn't here anymore.
Where is he? Where?
He moved to another place.
I don't know where.
He didn't say anything.
[Mongki] Huh?
He's right.
Atoy hasn't been here
since his father died.
[Peping] It's better if you leave now.
Sorry if anyone got hurt.
The people here are decent.
Leave now, Kuya Mongki.
Sorry for the trouble.
They won't come back here again.
Go now, Big Bro Mongki.
[Emerson] Wait, wait, wait!
What? That's it?
You should have
these troublemakers arrested!
- They just caused us problems here!
- [clamoring]
They even threatened us, didn't they?
- He's dangerous!
- [man] Wait, wait.
If you report that to the police,
they might come after you.
He has a gun.
[man] That's true.
Ah, well… Just pay us instead!
- Oh, yes, just pay us!
- [clamoring]
[Gavin] Okay, okay!
I'll take care of it.
But I only brought a little money.
Ten thousand pesos?
- Maybe this will do?
- [suave music playing]
- Is that too little?
- [Gavin] I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
That's how it is when you're a nepo baby!
Add 5,000 more
because you slammed me down!
[man] You slammed her, huh!
- [funky music playing]
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't want this to happen.
But fine.
- Fifteen thousand.
- [Emerson] Whoo!
[funky music playing]
- Fifteen thousand. I'm really sorry.
- [Emerson mumbles]
That might be enough.
[Paldo] Are you hurt, bro? Huh?
- [Paldo] Does it hurt anywhere, bro?
- [Emerson] Yes.
[Emerson] This 15,000 isn't enough.
No, no, this isn't for you. Not for you.
[Paldo] Father. You take this.
- [Gavin] I'm sorry, really sorry.
- [Bunda] Father, please.
Our goods were damaged.
[Peping] Cita, it's your turn.
[Paldo] Are we okay? Are we okay now?
Please, let's not make this bigger, okay?
They already apologized.
That's enough. I'll send them away, okay?
That's enough, that's enough.
[Paldo] Go now, go now. Leave.
- [Gavin] Sorry.
- [crowd buzzing]
[woman] Our goods.
- [woman 1] It's your fault.
- [woman 2] What about our goods?
[indistinct chattering]
[somber music playing]
Oh, even if what happened
to us earlier wasn't pleasant,
I'm still glad because I saw the unity
of the residents against them.
That's right, Father.
I really don't know any of them.
Most likely, after what happened earlier,
they won't do anything nice
to Big Brother Atoy.
So, it was right that we covered for Atoy.
- Father.
- Oh?
[inquisitive music playing]
What did you cover up?
What's going on?
Big Brother, some outsiders
came earlier, three men.
They were causing trouble.
They were looking for you.
Did anyone get hurt?
Oh, thank God no one was seriously hurt.
Seriously?
‘Nang, do you know them?
I don't know them, Atoy,
but I heard the name of one. Mongki?
[Mongki] I'll take care of this, Boss.
[grunting]
Should we be worried, Atoy?
No.
Don't worry.
It won't happen again.
Is Ibyang here?
Oh, Atoy, you're here.
Manang, I really can't find Ibyang,
- not in the kitchen or the bathroom.
- Huh?
Why? Karla, what?
Did Ibyang escape from you again?
Where is she?
How should I know, Brother!
I didn't see her!
When the commotion broke out,
I told her to stay.
I said, lock the door
and don't let anyone in.
When we got back, the door was locked.
[stirring music continues]
[electronic blipping]
[intense music playing]
Looks like Ame was brought
into underground fighting.
- Poor girl.
- [Atoy] Indeed.
[Atoy] I already have a way to get inside.
[in English] Hi, sir! Good evening!
[in English] Good evening.
A client spoke to me.
Why?
He wants to take me to Japan
for his customer,
but I have a bad feeling about it.
[in English] I want to put all my money
on this fighter.
Uh-huh.
Amazing Ame.
[MC] This time, they will be fighting
two of our most beloved patrons!
We're at a disadvantage.
UP NEXT
You're all disgusting.
Keep quiet.
I'm a friend of Ibyang.
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias