The Mohnyin rebels are invading.
Royal Uncle sent a messenger to Hongsawadi for aid,
- The most suitable man for this task is…
- It is Mingyi Swa, my own son.
- Yes, Your Highness.
- If Mingyi Swa rises to the rank of General, what then?
He is sending his own son straight to his death.
I humbly volunteer to join the campaign with Mingyi Swa.
Prince Nares intervened and took the head with his twin swords.
Would Prince Nares be willing to demonstrate those twin blades?
A sight for us to behold?
The twin sword style of Phra Maha Thera Khanchong.
Never taught to anyone else. I never thought he’d teach it to you.
these twin blades secured victory for Hongsawadi
and saved my very life.
Prince Nares has committed no wrong, Your Majesty.
Learning the Mon style of swordsmanship is no crime.
But it becomes a crime if one uses it to betray his friends.
I ask of you now,
to swear before the sacred relics,
that you will be a loyal friend for all time.
Do you dare to take this oath?
Let us swear this oath together.
If you do not betray me,
I shall not betray you.
Do you agree?
Yes.
- I swear
- before the sacred Shwemawdaw Pagoda.
We, Mingyi Swa
and I, Nares,
- shall be loyal friends,
- bound by true sincerity,
- and never to betray one another.
- Should either break this oath
- let him die this very day or the next,
- and let his soul burn in the depths of hell,
- never to be reborn again.
Checkmate.
Father is furious.
Nares has likely escaped once again.
That death-defying captive is truly formidable.
If I can eliminate him,
Father would surely be pleased.
[The Residence of Princess Suphankalaya]
What was your name again?
You've told me many times, yet I always seem to forget.
The child is nearly a year old, and yet you still cannot remember.
King Bayinnaung bestowed the name,
Phunchi.
But if it is too difficult, just call her
Min A Htwe.
Min A Htwe, my niece.
Mother sent word to say
she wishes to see her granddaughter's face.
We have been away from home for many years now.
I do not know when we shall ever return.
Have you ever tried asking for permission?
I know my place well.
I am a hostage.
To whom should I show my face and beg for mercy?
I will not return…
as a captive of Hongsawadi.
But I shall return to Ayutthaya
as a person of Ayutthaya.
And I shall never set foot in Hongsawadi again.
One day, Sister.
One day.
Come down, brother.
Brother.
Help! Help!
Brother!
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Brother!
Help! Can anyone hear me?
Someone, help me!
Help me!
Help me, I beg of you! I don't know how to row!
The boat is going to capsize!
Mingyi Naung! sit down first!
You will fall into the water. I will go find someone to help.
Hey!
Help! Help!
- Help! Help!
- Mingyi Naung!
Help! Help!
Help.
Mingyi Naung! Mingyi Naung!
Mingyi Naung!
Prince Nares.
Dam, how are you?
Sister.
Be careful.
Who... who was it that pulled me out?
Mingyi Swa.
Good heavens!
What has happened here?
Prince Naresuan fell into the palace moat.
As for how it happened, I am still not certain.
Apply the medicine and watch over His Highness closely.
Do not make a scene or tell anyone yet.
Once Prince Nares has regained consciousness, send someone to fetch me.
Yes, Your Highness.
I went into the water to save Mingyi Naung,
But he struck me with his oar.
It was intentional. He meant to kill me.
Dam, what are you going to do?
I will have my revenge.
You cannot.
You say a ten-year-old boy plotted to kill you?
Who would believe such a tale?
A child could not think of this alone
it was the elders who commanded it!
And who else could be the power behind him?
Is it not his own father, Crown Prince Jaisingh?
Khun Phra Nai.
Go and summon Prince Mingyi Swa at once.
I shall go and petition King Bayinnaung.
I need the Prince to stand as my witness.
- Yes, Your Highness.
- Stop.
Dam.
Think on this well.
To kill within the palace grounds is a breach of the Palace Law.
Will Mingyi Swa truly stand as a witness against his own father and brother?
When the punishment is death?
Your Highness,
if this matter is not brought to judgment,
they may be emboldened to strike again in the days to come.
They will certainly strike again.
You must flee.
I am no coward.
Whoever strikes me, I strike back!
- Why must I flee?
- Not as a coward flees,
But as a man who is free.
You are like a thorn in the side of Jaisingh.
In this lifetime, the two of you can never coexist under the same sky.
Why, then, should you continue to endure this?
Let us go home.
The time has come.
Your reward.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
King Bayinnaung once said to me,
I love to collect gold,
Because your name is Suphankalaya.
How utterly absurd.
Get these things out of here.
Exchange them for weapons,
and transport them to Prince Nares.
[Kuy Village]
The dawn is near. I must depart.
Are you certain that you will not come with me?
In but a few hours,
Hongsawadi will know of your flight.
They will surely send an army to hunt you down.
Battle will be inevitable.
I am but a woman,
and I have a nursing babe.
If I go with you, I will only be a burden that holds you back.
But if His Majesty is enraged by my flight, he will surely punish you in my stead.
Do not worry for me.
I can survive this.
Go now, and go safely.
Prostrate yourself before our parents in my stead.
They are coming, Your Highness.
All the people of Ayutthaya who were taken captive then…
Every one of them shall follow me home.
My brothers and sisters,
we march from Hongsawadi this day,
never to return.
The path ahead is grueling
naught but steep canyons and jagged thorns.
I ask only this
that you stand as one.
United, the difficult shall become easy,
and the heavy shall become light.
Yes, Your Highness!
Everyone, make ready.
As soon as it is light enough to see the lines on your palms,
we move out.
Wait.
Your Holiness has followed us all this way. What is your purpose?
I believe
there are Mon people here in Hongsawadi
who are deeply troubled.
They find no happiness in staying.
They are men of skill and knowledge.
I wish to entrust them to your service, that they may follow you.
And what of you, Your Holiness?
If your heart holds no loyalty to this place,
why linger here in Hongsawadi?
I still have matters to attend to.
I bless you, that you may succeed in all your aims
and be kept safe from every harm.
Amen.
I’ve come to bid you two farewell.
And Muang as well.
Muy.
I'm leaving Muang in your care.
I can care for his body, but not his spirit.
He is already heartsick,
knowing you depart.
Can he not go with you, Your Highness?
That cannot be.
Muang is registered as a royal elephant now, no longer a wild one.
If he follows Your Highness, those left behind will be held guilty.
Our whole house would lose our heads.
Then why stay here waiting for the blade?
Move with Muang and follow me.
Can we, Your Highness?
You can.
The land where I am going has plenty of elephants for you to tend.
Then let us go!
Did you hear that, Muang? We’re going together!
We won't be coming back to Hongsawadi this time.
That fifth-month liquor you buried,
dig it all up for me.
And don't you dare hide a single drop.
Yes, Your Highness!
Sister.
I’ll be back for you soon.
Take care of yourself.
Go quickly.
Go.
Has he herded every last soul from Ayutthaya away?
How dare him!
By doing this, Nares is committing blatant treason.
What say you, Suphankalaya?
Your younger brother
leading people out of Hongsawadi like this. What is his aim?
I do not know what is in Prince Nares’s mind, my Lord.
But I am certain
he harbors no ill will toward you, nor toward Hongsawadi.
I know the reason why.
Yesterday, an attempt was made on Prince Nares’s life.
I believe that is why
His Highness has fled, Your Majesty.
Nonsense!
I crave your royal permission
to raise an army and crush Nares’s rebellion.
I shall bring him back to face judgment,
that he may serve as a warning to all who follow.
By your grace, if that is the case,
I beg leave to lead the army myself and bring Prince Nares back, Your Highness.
This is a small matter.
There is no need for the Crown Prince to lead an army for such a thing.
Mingyi Swa, go after Nares and bring his people back.
I shall not hold him at fault, but if he resists,
I shall deem it treason,
punishable by death.
As you command, Your Majesty.
Do you remember me?
You... elephant child.
Prince Mingyi Swa.
Go and tell Prince Nares.
I will be waiting by the great tree,
near the stream over there.
Tell him to come and negotiate,
so that we need not trouble our men to slaughter each other for nothing.
Brother.
I left in such haste.
I did not even have the chance to thank you for saving my life.
Think nothing of it.
You once saved me, too. Let us consider the debt settled.
Have you truly come to capture me yourself?
I wanted to hear it from your own lips.
Why did you flee?
I was lured into a trap by Mingyi Naung to be assassinated.
And I suspect the Crown Prince Jaisingh is the one pulling the strings behind it all.
But you did not flee alone.
You brought our people with you. To do so,
- is nothing less than an act of rebellion against Hongsawadi.
- I only wanted to go home.
I only wish to be in my own place.
A place to sleep in peace, without the constant fear of death.
If this is what you call rebellion,
then a rebel I shall be.
But the penalty for treason is death.
If you want my life,
then come and take it.
Do you remember our word?
If you stood by me,
I would stand by you.
Now
does that still hold true?
I have come, and I cannot return empty-handed.
The Hongsawadi army will wait until tomorrow.
At dawn, we will storm and destroy your camp.
I will move my people tonight.
I'll leave some weapons and supplies behind.
Take them back with you, as your prize.
Nares.
May you be safe.
Sent for them, yet you return alone. Why?
Prince Nares abandoned camp and fled with his people overnight.
I could not catch him, Your Majesty.
Outpaced? Or did you let him go?
Scouts report Prince Nares heading east,
likely for Phitsanulok.
Since Mingyi Swa failed,
I volunteer to lead the pursuit and bring him to justice myself.
It is well, Your Majesty.
Once Prince Naresuan is brought back,
the truth of his flight
shall be revealed.
Grandfather shall judge for yourself
if an attempt was made on Prince Nares’s life within the palace walls,
what should the penalty be?
Who?
Who dared to attempt Nares's life?
From whom did you hear such lies?
Prince Nares.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Mingyi Naung struck Prince Nares unconscious
and left him to drown.
Had I not saved him,
he would be dead.
How dare you!
To kill within the palace walls,
has the law lost all meaning?
Jaisingh.
Is this how you raise your son?
To eliminate an enemy,
I will do whatever it takes.
After those words,
if I were Naresuan, why would I ever return?
I beg your royal pardon.
What is it?
King Maha Thammaracha has arrived.
He requests an audience.
To discuss an urgent state matter, Your Majesty.
The Junior Queen sent word that
Prince Nares fled after an attempt on his life.
In my distress, I have come at once.
It is nothing.
The children simply do not get along.
My grandson was out of line, provoked Naresuan until he was injured.
It was merely a childish spat.
If he is capable of this at ten,
Nares will surely not survive adulthood.
As a father, I cannot help but fear for him.
If Your Majesty possesses any mercy,
I beg your permission
to let Nares return to Phitsanulok.
There, he can focus on his loyalty to you,
without further cause for resentment or strife.
[Chan Royal Palace, Phitsanulok]
In the auspicious year 933,
the Year of the Goat,
By Royal Command,
Somdet Phra Chao Sanphet Wongkura Suriyodom,
Borom Maha Thammarachathirat Rames,
Pawaret Dhammikarat Dechochai,
Phrommathep Adithep Narubodintra,
Phuminthara Thep Sommutirat Borommapophit,
appoints Prince Narayana
to ascend the throne and rule the City of Phitsanulok.
Long Live the King!
My thanks to you, Phet and Sri, for helping me train the troops.
[Phra Ratchamanu]
[Phet]
It is we who must thank Your Highness,
for never forgetting old friends like us.
[Phra Sri Thamorat]
[Sri]
How could I ever forget? When we were children,
we used to chase chickens together.
As children, we chased chickens. But now?
Now, we're climbing, diving, and wallowing in mud.
Are you training soldiers or bandits, Your Highness?
Our numbers are few.
If the Hongsawadi army marches on us, how could we ever withstand them?
It is by these bandit tactics alone that we will survive.
Will Hongsawadi truly march against us, Your Highness?
If I play the part of a good child,
A humble vassal who bows to their every whim,
they would surely stay their hand.
But as they say, I have never been a good child.
Without me in Hongsawadi,
Mingyi Swa will surely go back to being a good child himself.
The music is so beautiful.
Why have you stopped?
Mingyi Swa, why have you come empty-handed? Where is your lute?
How are we to continue our duet if you've brought no music?
Today, I am too weary to play.
I would rather simply listen to my heart's content.
For who knows how long it will be
before I hear your lute again.
Where do you intend to go?
King Setthathirath of Lan Xang has passed.
Phraya Saen Surintha Luechai, the Grand Minister, has seized the throne.
Furthermore, the Crown Prince of Lan Xang
is still held hostage here in Hongsawadi.
Grandfather deems this an injustice,
so he will march his armies to reclaim the kingdom.
Mingyi Swa.
Do you intend to join the battle as well?
Grandfather has issued a decree.
My father is to stay and guard the city,
while Minye Kyawswa and I are sent to fight in his stead.
I have no love for war.
I loathe the thought of having to take the lives of others.
To be born a man is to be born with duty.
We cannot simply follow the whims of our own hearts.
In this one life I have,
I ask for only one thing.
That just once, I may follow my own heart.
Mingyi Swa.
This campaign against Lan Xang,
it does have its advantages, I suppose.
Grandfather orders Ayutthaya and Phitsanulok to join the war.
At last, I shall see Naresuan’s face once more.
I led my men from Phitsanulok to Nong Bua,
The gateway to Lan Xang,
to await the forces from Ayutthaya.
From there, we were to join King Bayinnong's great army.
But fortune has turned against me.
Sri! Phet! Look, a fire over there.
This was once a village.
Everything is burnt to the ground.
Where have all the people gone?
Help.
Go!
Grandmother.
What is the matter?
The plague has struck. Everyone is dead.
So they burned the village to the ground.
Has the plague struck here, Grandmother?
Grandmother! Grandmother!
- Your Highness.
- What?
Look.
Your Higness.
Move.
Is there any improvement, Phra Ratchamanu?
He is stricken with a high fever; his body is burning up.
His condition has worsened, Your Majesty.
Is it smallpox that has stricken Prince Nares?
Yes, Your Highness.
Smallpox has no cure.
Worse still, anyone who draws near
will surely catch it.
It seems the entire camp is destined to perish together.
Phra Sri Thamorat,
Return to King Maha Thammaracha at once.
Tell him we command his army to halt exactly where they are.
He must not bring his forces to join us.
By your command, Your Majesty.
Use all your strength to care for Prince Nares.
If you lack anything, let me know.
I will provide whatever is needed.
Your kindness is most gracious, Your Majesty.
Bring me my horse.
Are you going to see that captive, Brother?
This does not concern you.
Brother.
If you venture outside the camp
and bring back calamity,
then it most certainly concerns me.
Soldiers!
If General Mingyi Swa goes out,
he will bring the smallpox back with him.
Under no circumstances must he be allowed to leave!
You.
Only one in a hundred
survives the smallpox.
Wait for the news, Brother.
Then, you may perform the merit-making
for your sworn brother later.
My condition has taken a turn for the worse.
My father has ordered the retreat
to take me back to Phitsanulok.
Everyone believes, without a doubt, that I am going to die.
Song Kwae, a paradise between two rivers.
It truly lives up to its name.
Phitsanulok is my home. Hongsawadi is not.
If I hope to see this kingdom live in peace and prosperity,
then you cannot leave it in your father's hands.
The Great Hongsawadi
was built with every drop of my blood and every scar upon my body.
You cannot give it to anyone else. I will not allow it!
Whether Hongsawadi shall know peace,
or be consumed by flames,
that now rests entirely with you.