I beg your forgiveness
about your sister.
Your Highness, we are under ambush.
There is nothing I can do.
Father, Mother, Sister cannot come anymore.
I am my father's son,
the Crown Prince of Hongsawadi.
Crown Prince,
lead the army to reclaim the City of Ayutthaya at all costs.
It is a duty I have carried since birth.
Duty is like the mist
that obscures the sun.
The prayers of us both,
therefore, can never come true.
From this moment forth,
we shall each fulfill our own duty.
I hereby revoke our oath,
that the two of us shall never harm one another.
Should we ever meet,
let neither of us
stay our hand.
I have something important to tell you.
- What?
Is his horoscope truly so fatal?
Phra Maha Thera Khanchong has prophesied that,
between this year and the next,
the Crown Prince shall surely perish on the battlefield.
Moreover,
Prince Ekathosarot has issued a royal command
for me to inform you all.
Since the heavens are now in our favor,
In this upcoming battle, he asked that the three of you
unite your hearts and strength
to slay the Crown Prince by any means necessary.
I am sorry.
This wound has missed your vitals.
It shall only prevent you from wielding a sword in battle.
Consider this wound
a token of goodwill from your younger brother.
You.
No, Your Majesty! Please spare their lives!
Mingyi Swa was wounded
and forced to retreat,
withdrawing his troops back to Hongsawadi.
This incited the ultimate fury of King Nanda Bayin.
Soldiers,
take them both and behead them!
Let me never see their faces again!
Spare our lives,
I beg of you, Your Majesty, please spare our lives.
Mingyi Swa
was also severely punished.
If you were not my son,
I would have your head taken just as they were.
Stay here and face your punishment.
Do not show your face to anyone,
lest they mock you, saying that a crown prince
is as cowardly as if he were not a man.
If you repent, come forth in women's clothing to beg my forgiveness,
and then, I shall pardon you.
How pitiful.
He ordered the execution of the generals
who accompanied the prince.
They were slaughtered in great numbers, Your Highness.
King Nanda Bayin grows more cruel by the day.
If we remain in Hongsawadi,
we shall surely face danger
from the fires of his wrath.
Drag every man in this room out at once.
King Nanda Bayin rounded up the people,
preparing for war against Ayutthaya once more.
Go, get up!
- Get up!
- I will not go!
- Do not cry!
Don't cry! Go!
Do not take my child! Please, do not take my child away!
Causing great suffering
to every citizen across the land.
- Here!
- Go!
Go!
- Come!
- Come with me!
Come now!
- Go!
Wrap yourself in the saffron robes immediately.
Please eat something, Your Highness.
You have not eaten
nor slept for months.
How is the situation outside?
What matter
has caused you such profound sorrow?
King Nanda Bayin
has ordered a mass mobilization for war.
young and old alike have been rounded up,
even the monks living in temples were not spared.
A king wages war
to protect his people,
but if waging war
brings only hardship to the people of Hongsawadi,
for what purpose is it done?
At this hour,
King Nanda Bayin
thinks not of Hongsawadi in the least.
His heart is consumed only by the desire for war
to seek vengeance against Ayutthaya.
Will the empire my father fought to build
truly end in such a way?
Brother.
Hongsawadi does not lack brave men,
but it lacks a righteous king.
You must preserve your life and wait for the day you ascend to the throne.
For only you
can extinguish the fires of war and bring peace to the realm.
May it please Your Majesty,
Crown Prince Mingyi Swa requests an audience.
He seeks your royal audience, Your Majesty.
Tell him to enter.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Mingyi Swa.
Son.
May it please Your Majesty,
I, Mingyi Swa,
Crown Prince of Hongsawadi,
am mindful of my failure and neglect of duty.
Therefore, I humbly ask
for your royal permission
to lead the army into battle against Ayutthaya
to redeem my honor, Your Majesty.
What was that?
You are volunteering for battle?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I volunteer
to fight with all my might.
If I do not return victorious, I shall not return at all.
Mingyi Swa, my son.
this truly gladdens my heart.
For heaven's sake!
The Hongsawadi army is marching once again.
The Crown Prince himself leads the troops.
This time,
Would it be better if I led the army in your stead?
Why?
You and the Crown Prince
have known each other since you were small children.
If it comes to a fight to the death,
will you truly be able to do it?
I am the commander-in-chief. Why would I be unable to do such a thing?
Do you truly believe
that I will die?
Such a matter is not worth the risk.
To go out to battle,
If death comes not today, it shall come on a day to follow.
For us to fall by each other's hands
is better than dying at the hand of another.
Nares.
If I must truly die,
I ask to die by your hand.
Very well.
Come out and fight,
Then let us see how it ends.
May it please Your Majesty,
the King of Prome and the royal tutor Mangjaparo
have arrived with their troops to join the forces.
I pay my humble respects, Your Majesty.
Now everyone is gathered together.
Mingyi Hnaung.
I hear you are now the King of Prome.
I suppose I must pay you my respects.
No need, Brother.
you may speak to me as you always have.
Father must not trust me,
which is why he sent you all, is it not?
Father fears that you may be overexerting yourself,
so he sent us to help with the fighting instead.
And it is not just us,
the army from Toungoo has also arrived.
[Natshinnaung, the son of the King of Toungoo.]
Your Highness.
Natshinnaung.
Did you lead the army down from Toungoo yourself?
I come in my father's stead.
the King of Hongsawadi has commanded
that in this war,
victory is the only option.
Defeat is not permitted.
How is Muang?
He is quite stubborn this time.
Aside from myself, no one can get near him at all, Your Majesty.
If Muang turns unruly during the battle,
Your Majesty will be in great danger.
Please change your royal mount, Your Majesty.
Do you wish to go with me?
My good boy.
[Battlefield of Nong Sarai]
My army
and the army of the Crown Prince engaged in a fierce melee since late morning.
Muang grew enraged until he could no longer be controlled,
bolting away without any direction.
The troops and the four-fold guardians could not keep up.
Only the royal elephant of Prince Ekathosarot
managed to follow closely behind.
And when the dust and smoke cleared,
I discovered that
we two brothers
were surrounded by the soldiers of Hongsawadi.
Let's go, Muang.
Brother.
Since you have wandered into such a circle,
the Hongsawadi forces have bows and firearms.
How will you ever break your way out?
I must simply try.
Perhaps Phra Maha Thera Khanchong’s prophecy was mistaken.
Maybe it is not I
who must die in this battle.
In that case,
I shall congratulate you.
And you?
A warrior dying on the battlefield
is nothing out of the ordinary.
Didn't you tell me that yourself?
From this day
until the days to come,
there will likely be no warrior
as brave as you.
How could I let you die
at the hands of mere common soldiers?
If so,
I invite you
to join me in an elephant duel.
Should I meet my end
at your hands,
I shall have no regrets.
I, Mingyi Swa,
the Crown Prince of Hongsawadi,
shall engage in a royal duel on elephant back
with Prince Nares of Ayutthaya,
so that the honor of this deed
shall remain known forevermore.
Sure.
Enough.
I am tired now.
If you are tired, then surrender.
- I shall not lose.
- I shall not lose either.
Very well.
Fight then, with all your might.
Brother.
No matter who wins or loses,
there shall be no room for regret.
In the past,
I believed that war
was simply about killing strangers
or those not of our kind.
But in the reality of battle, be it a friend,
a brother,
or someone you once knew so well,
if they stand on the opposite side, you must be prepared to kill them.
We grew up together.
I loved you like my own brother.
I, too, saw you as my own elder brother.
We both
were meant to stay on the same side forever.
Was that not the promise?
If you stand by my side,
I shall stand by yours.
This is my solemn oath.
- I pray that our two lands...
- I pray that our two lands…
- May dwell together in enduring peace.
- Bound as brothers, kin of the same soul.
- For all eternity.
From this day forward,
I know not when we shall meet again.
though Hongsawadi and Ayutthaya
may no longer stand as brother states,
you,
you shall always be my brother.
[Brother.]
The death of Mingyi Swa
caused King Nanda Bayin
to be so grief-stricken that he lost his mind.
Afterwards,
Hongsawadi was plunged into great internal turmoil.
King Nanda Bayin
never again led an army to attack Ayutthaya.
Yet the prayer shared between Mingyi Swa and I
has not yet come true.
Humanity continues to wage war,
fighting and struggling against one another.
Even if today,
our dream cannot yet be realized,
in the days to come, people will surely know
that peace alone
will bring about eternal happiness.