[Monday, January 18, 1593]
[11:18 a.m.]
Let's go.
My brother.
Today’s battle
shall be told for generations to come.
But regardless of the legends told,
only I
understand your inner thoughts.
In 1563,
King Bayinnaung of Hongsawadi
leads his grand armada to lay siege to Phitsanulok,
at that time,
a sovereign city-state under the crown of Ayutthaya.
King Maha Thammaracha of Phitsanulok
could no longer withstand the onslaught.
With no reinforcements arriving from Ayutthaya,
he was forced to swear fealty to King Bayinnaung
to save his city,
and was compelled to lead his own men to join the Hongsawadi army
in the invasion of Ayutthaya.
Ayutthaya fell.
Both Ayutthaya and Phitsanulok
were reduced to vassal states,
bound in subjection to Hongsawadi
from that day forth.
[1564 A.D. - Chan Royal Palace, Phitsanulok]
We have captured them, Your Highness.
[Prince Nares]
This one is a feisty fellow, and with quite the pair of spurs, too.
[Prince Ekathosarot]
Catch it!
Prince Nares, where are you?
Prince Nares!
[Princess Suphankalaya]
- Where are you?
- I'm here.
Let the creature go.
Father has returned from Ayutthaya. He has summoned you.
- He has summoned you.
- Father has returned.
How is the situation in Ayutthaya?
[Queen Wisut Kasattri]
His Majesty King Maha Chakkraphat has fallen ill.
[Phra Maha Thammaracha, King of Phitsanulok]
Thus, Prince Mahinthrathirat has been appointed to rule in his stead.
With what ailment does His Majesty suffer, Your Majesty?
It is not serious.
The royal physicians say it was merely a fainting fit.
Ever since Ayutthaya fell
and became a vassal of Hongsawadi,
Father's heart has been consumed by grief.
The King surrendered so that the people might be spared from peril.
His judgment was sound.
- Father.
- Nares.
Look at you. Be careful.
My greetings, Your Highness.
Come to me, my son
Nares.
And where are your siblings?
Khao and I could not keep pace with him, Father.
Dam ran as if he has wings
Suphankalaya said that Father had summoned me.
How could I afford to delay?
When it comes to being headstrong, no one surpasses you.
And look.
Where were you playing? You’ve come back quite a mess.
You are covered in dirt from head to toe, my Khao.
Let them play as they wish.
Soon, they will no longer have these moments together.
Your words carry a strange weight.
King Bayinnaung has sent his royal command.
He demands that we send Prince Nares to reside in Hongsawadi.
He promises to provide for him as his own,
to ensure a lasting peace between our two kingdoms.
The three of you, leave us.
I must speak with your father in private.
What madness is this? To take our son away as a hostage!
It is not only our son.
Every vassal state must offer their young princes and princesses
to the Court of Hongsawadi.
If others choose to surrender their children, so be it.
But my child shall stay with me!
Be careful of your words.
This is a royal mandate from King Bayinnaung.
To defy him
is to be branded a rebel.
Living under their shadow...
it is utterly suffocating.
He is still so small.
Not yet even nine years of age.
To be sent to a distant kingdom,
What if they are cruel to him?
what could he possibly do?
Mother.
Dam.
Please don't cry.
If Father says I must go,
then I shall go.
I am not afraid.
My prince.
[Hongsawadi 1564 A.D.]
Your Majesty, I humbly crave your royal indulgence.
I beg your gracious permission to speak.
- [Binnya Dala, The Grand Minister]
- Bring forth the Princes and Princesses
of the vassal states:
Hsenwi, Jinghong,
Phetchabun, and Phitsanulok
to pay homage to His Majesty.
Princess Waen Kaew, daughter of Prince Hsenwi.
Princess Noi Kham, daughter of Prince Jinghong.
Prince Mahawan,
son of the Lord of Phetchabun.
Prince Nares,
the Princes of Phitsanulok.
[Jaisingh, Phra Maha Uparaja]
[The Royal Son of King Bayinnaung]
Prince from Phitsanulok.
[King Bayinnaung]
Why do you stare at me so?
I seek to witness
the might of the Conqueror of the Ten Directions.
Now what is your judgment?
Your Majesty's stature is no different from any ordinary man.
How did you come to conquer the ten directions, Your Majesty?
All men are born with two arms and two legs alike.
But only those with superior wisdom
and greater diligence than all others
can truly conquer the ten directions.
In that case, if I am equally diligent,
could I also conquer the ten directions?
Is that not so, Your Majesty?
He is but a child, yet so bold.
Who has emboldened him to speak such words?
A sharp thorn needs no sharpening.
Even with a teacher, a coward would never
dare to speak such words.
A sharp thorn should be pruned while it is young.
If left to grow,
it will eventually turn and pierce us, Your Majesty.
Why do you persist with such pestering?
Is it your wish that I punish Prince Nares?
Only enough to teach him a lesson, Your Majesty.
King Maha Thammaracha of Phitsanulok
is a formidable warrior.
That we could conquer Ayutthaya this time
is because Phitsanulok stands by our side.
To strike the son is to wound the father.
Should a few words from a child
cause a rift between us and Phitsanulok?
Is that truly wise?
You aspire to be the King of Kings,
the Supreme Emperor.
You raised these princes,
hoping for their future loyalty.
But this boy is insolent. He dares to speak as your equal.
To not make an example of him
would stain your honor, Your Majesty.
Jaisingh.
To be an Emperor of Emperors,
one must possess both might and mercy.
One cannot rule by sheer force and punishment alone.
If you seek to rule this kingdom after me,
remember this.
To defeat an enemy with the sword
is nothing compared to winning their heart.
[Lord Sapphaphet Phakdi, The Royal Mentor]
Are you sure you want to keep it here, Your Highness?
Lueang must feel out of place here too.
Let him stay here for tonight.
Tomorrow, we shall find a better way.
Yes, Your Highness.
Fear not, Lueang.
I will not keep you locked in a cage.
Tomorrow,
Khun Phranai shall find you a better home.
But you must remain on your guard.
For this place
is vast and grand,
yet it is not our home.
Look, the captives.
[Minye Kyawswa]
This way, Your Highness.
Come here, captive.
You too.
I am no captive.
How are you not?
- My father said you are a captive.
- I am not.
- You are.
I said you're a captive, so you are one!
- Your Highness, please do not!
- Let go!
Teach him a lesson for me.
Let me go! Let me go!
- Let go!
- Stop it!
[Mingyi Swa]
Brawling within the Royal Grounds,
do you not know the gravity of such an offense?
This captive slave tried to strike me.
He hurt me first.
Who are you?
My name is Nares.
I am the son of King Maha Thammaracha, the Sovereign of Phitsanulok.
I am Mingyi Swa.
Son of the Crown Prince Jaisingh.
Grandson of the Great King Bayinnaung of Hongsawadi,
and the elder brother of this foul-mouthed boy.
Minye Kyawswa
If I inform Grandfather
that you have harmed Prince Nares,
you will face a severe punishment.
All of you will.
This time, I apologize on my brother’s behalf.
Can we simply let this matter rest?
Very well.
You are not yet of age for lessons. Go play elsewhere.
I said, leave!
The Royal Tutor has arrived, Your Highness.
Nares.
How is my boy?
Lord Sapphaphet has informed us
that Prince Nares is well and in good spirits.
King Bayinnaung has granted him a residence
equal to those of the Princes of Hongsawadi.
That is a relief.
And what else, You Majesty?
He is taught to read, write, and study semantics.
He masters the Treatises of War and the use of all weapons.
Prince Nares is brillian and learns with great speed.
King Bayinnaung holds our son in the highest favor.
[Mingyi Swa]
[Prince Nares]
Prince Nares has a true warrior's skill.
Truly, he is his father's son.
And what about Mingyi Swa?
Your son is not like you.
In battle, he is no match for Prince Nares.
I shall discipline my son more strictly, Your Majesty.
No two men are born alike.
Prince Nares is brilliant, swift,
and sharp in combat.
He is destined to be a Great General.
As for my grandson, Mingyi Swa,
he is wise, calm,
and broad-minded.
He is destined to be a Sovereign.
A reward for the victor.
You are most gracious, Your Majesty.
And what of the reward for the loser, Your Majesty?
You have lost. Why should you receive a reward?
Where there is darkness, there is light.
Where there is night, there is day.
Without the defeated, how could there be a victor, Your Majesty?
Thus,
the defeated are as vital as the triumphant.
You have a sharp tongue indeed, my grandson.
Here, take it.
Mingyi Swa.
Change your way of thinking.
On the battlefield,
the defeated are as good as the dead.
And the dead possess no importance whatsoever.
Yes, Your Highness.
Hurry, Brother! I must show you something special.
[Kuy Village]
Doctor Suk!
Are you inside?
Who is that? Why all this noise?
[Muy]
Hah! This brat.
[Master Suk]
Your Highness.
Mind your tongue! He is a Prince.
Careful, or your head will roll from your shoulders!
Execution is too swift for her.
I shall lash her to a post instead.
And force her to feast on elephant dung instead of rice for a full month!
Your Highness.
Your Highness, I beg for your mercy on behalf of my daughter.
She was raised in the wild, among the thickets.
I was merely jesting.
I see her as my own sister.
But tell me, how fares my Muang?
Muang.
There are countless elephants in the Royal Stables.
Why come all this way to see it?
Those are the King's elephants. But this one is mine.
Muang went out for some fun
and stepped on a spike.
I have applied the herbal poultice.
He will recover in a few days.
Is this what we traversed all this way to find?
Not quite. The real treasure is yet to come. Just wait.
I am here, Your Highness.
The 'Fifth Month Mead,' brewed by my own hands.
I offer it to you as an apology for my insolence.
Ah.
This is a fine brew indeed.
Believe me, Muy has many more jars hidden away.
Next time, we shall raid her stash once more.
Enough.
Should my father learn that I have slipped away to play like this,
it would mean grave trouble for us both.
What is it that you fear?
Phra Maha Uparaja, whom they say is so fearsome,
has never dared to lay a finger on you.
My father loves me dearly.
But alas…
Had I but half your talent,
my father would be truly proud.
You are capable, Brother, but it is not enough.
Your father wishes for you to surpass all others.
For in the days to come,
you must rule over men.
But I shall not rule my people with the sword.
Others will still use the sword against you.
How will you respond?
Why then should I fear?
With you by my side, I shall simply leave the fighting to you.
And this is your payment in advance.
Payment?
[Ayutthaya, 1568 A.D.]
Is it truly as you say, Phraya Ram?
- [King Mahinthrathirat, King of Ayutthaya]
- Indeed it is, Your Majesty.
Presenting His Highness, King Maha Thammaracha!
King Mahinthrathirat.
We are both Sovereigns of tributary kingdoms,
equal in rank.
Furthermore, I am your elder.
Now that I have come to visit,
why do you show no respect?
And why have you not prepared a seat befitting my station?
A man knows his own deeds in the depths of his heart.
You turned traitor, aiding Hongsawadi,
leading their armies to crush and conquer Ayutthaya.
Do you still expect me to call you kinsman?
Had Ayutthaya not forsaken us first
Never would Phitsanulok have been forced.
You rule Phitsanulok only because
my father bestowed that honor upon you!
Instead of laying down your life to repay his grace,
You saved your own skin by hiding behind our enemies!
Is it because
Bayinnaug now shields your wretched head,
that you dare come here and flaunt your power in my face?
Enough! My presence here
is not to trade words with a fool.
Phraya Ram.
[Phraya Ram, Lord of Chanthabun]
- My Lord?
- You hold the title of Lord of Chanthabun,
yet you linger here in the capital.
- This is highly improper.
- I require Phraya Ram’s service here, by my side.
Leaving him here will only breed discord and lead Your Majesty astray.
The position of Lord of Phichai is now vacant.
I ask that Your Majesty
appoint Phraya Ram as Lord of Phichai,
to assist me
- in governing the Northern Provinces.
- How dare you!
This is the Royal Command
of Bayinnaung,
King of Hongsawadi!
[Border Forest, outside the City of Ayutthaya]
Watch out!
Poison.
[Chan Royal Palace, Phitsanulok - 1568 A.D.]
Go and summon Princess Suphankalaya and Prince Ekathosarot
to my presence at once.
[Princess Suphankalaya]
[Prince Ekathosarot]
King Mahinthrathirat has sent a royal letter informing us
that your grandfather is gravely ill.
His condition is worsening.
And he has commanded that I bring you both to his bedside.
When shall you be leaving, Mother?
Ayutthaya has dispatched a Royal Envoy with five hundred men.
along with a fleet of Royal Barges.
Both the men and the vessels have now arrived.
How could our Royal Uncle expect us all to abandon the city like this?
Father has not yet returned. Will you not wait for him first?
But if your grandfather is truly in grave danger,
And I should delay,
then I would be a daughter most unfilial.
What should I do?
A royal letter from Princess Suphankalaya, Your Highness.
Prince Nares.
Wait. Where are you going in such haste?
I have urgent matters to attend to.
Do not follow me.
Well? Say it.
What is so pressing
that you must disturb me at such an early hour?
I humbly crave Your Majesty’s leave to return to Phitsanulok.
For what reason?
My mother and my siblings were lured to Ayutthaya
and are now being held as captives.
My father went to negotiate with King Mahinthrathirat,
But he has not yet returned, and his whereabouts remain unknown.
From where did you hear such news?
The letter from Princess Suphankalaya arrived this very day, Your Highness.
King Mahinthrathirat bears a deep-seated grudge
for Phitsanulok's shift of loyalty to Hongsawadi.
Now, he may seize this chance to take his revenge.
Phitsanulok is now a vassal of Hongsawadi.
Yet King Mahinthrathirat dares to detain the consort
and the sons of its Lord.
This is a grave insolence.
It challenges my very authority. It shall not be tolerated.
- Jaisingh.
- Your Majesty.
Let Binnya Dala dispatch royal seals to all vassal lords.
Command them to seek an audience with me at once.
Prepare all troops and provisions.
For we shall march our armies to Ayutthaya.
As you command, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
What is it now?
I beg your permission to join this campaign, Your Majesty.
So, you wish to go to war?
I wish to save my mother and my siblings, Your Majesty.
Very well. You are of age now.
Prove your mettle in battle, so that all may fear and respect you.
I shall appoint you as a Commander.
Lead a hundred men and join the vanguard in this conquest.
Your mercy is boundless, Your Majesty.
In that case, I beg Your Majesty's to let my son join the vanguard.
When I was your age,
I fought shoulder to shoulder with your grandfather.
What say you, Mingyi Swa?
In all honesty,
I have no desire for war.
But…
I wish to my help ounger brother, Your Majesty.
I hereby appoint the Crown Prince as our vanguard.
You shall command twenty thousand troops
and lead the march ahead of the main host.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I, myself, shall command the main host and follow thereafter.
The Kings of Inwa and Prome,
Lord Binnya Dala, Lord Saen Luang,
and Lord Pathein,
each shall lead their own provincial forces,
and unite our strength as we march forward together.
By your command, Your Majesty.
For this campaign, I hereby appoint
Mingyi Swa and Prince Nares
as commanders of a hundred-man unit
to join our forces in this conquest.
[City of Ayutthaya]
Move!
Since you refuse to let me pass,
then go and summon your Sovereign!
- Tell him to come and speak with me here.
- I am already here.
My sister is a Supreme Consort,
the glory of both Phitsanulok and Ayutthaya.
Why then do you behave like a common woman in the marketplace?
Since you remember well who I am,
how then do you dare to imprison me?
You hold me and my sons as hostages
to force King Maha Thammaracha into submission.
Does our blood mean nothing to you now?
Originally,
Phitsanulok and Ayutthaya shared no bond.
It was only through your marriage, Sister,
that I forced myself to call them kin.
But once King Maha Thammaracha is gone,
this fragile bond shall be severed forever.
You…
Do you truly intend to kill your own brother-in-law?
I shall reclaim Phitsanulok from the grip of Hongsawadi.
Should King Maha Thammaracha refuse to submit,
then he shall learn the cost of his defiance.
Guards!
Escort Her Highness Queen Wisut Kasattri to the inner chambers.
And see to it that she never steps foot outside again.
Should my sister prove disobedient,
You have my leave to punish her as you see fit.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[12th month , Year 1568 ]
[ Military Camp, Kamphaeng Phet]
Watch your step, Commander Mingyi Swa.
Come then, Nares! I do not fear you.
Brother, Brother.
It is nothing. I merely slipped.
I thought I had struck you, Brother.
This blade is incredibly keen.
Far sharper than the practice swords we’ve used.
Had you not stayed your hand just now, it would have surely tasted my blood.
Fear not, Brother. For my blade
shall taste only the blood of my enemies.
That.
This fabric looks expensive.
It does not belongs to commoners.
Not our own men either.
Then to whom does it belong?
Brother, return to the camp at once.
Tell our men to stay alert and be ready.
Nares.
Smoke.
Father.
I did not expect to find you here.
What has happened? Why are you here, Father?
I have fled from Ayutthaya.
Mahinthrathirat sent men to assassinate me.
They used poisoned arrows, but I survived.
I began my journey only after my wounds had healed.
I have only just arrived in Kamphaeng Phet this very day.
So that is why. Uncle knew his assassins had failed.
He feared your vengeance.
So he took Mother and Khao as hostages.
What did you say?
Mother and my brother are in Ayutthaya. I am going to save them.
I crave your royal permission, Your Majesty.
- What is it?
- We have captured another one, Your Majesty.
- Let me go!
- Walk!
Let go of me!
- Brother.
- Nares.
Let go of him.
I told you to wait at the camp, why did you follow me?
You were gone for so long. I was worried, so I followed you.
This is Mingyi Swa.
The son of Crown Prince Jaisingh, Father.
The King of Hongsawadi has commanded us to march upon Ayutthaya.
We are going to bring Mother home.
I am truly gladdened that you are safe.
Please, do take a seat.
You are most gracious, Your Majesty.
My suspicions were correct.
King Mahinthrathirat seized the chance to assassinate you.
We must teach them a lesson they will never forget.
King Maha Thammaracha,
your arrival here is most opportune.
Mobilize your forces from Phitsanulok
to join with the army of Crown Prince Jaisingh
and strike Ayutthaya from the eastern front.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Mingyi Swa and Nares,
go and reinforce the vanguard at once.
As for the other divisions,
encircle the city from all four directions.
Conquer Ayutthaya at any cost.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, King Bayinnaung leads the grand army himself this time.
Supported by legions from all major provinces,
they have us surrounded on every side.
Our terrain remains strong. We can still hold our ground.
However…
What is it?
The vanguard, led by King Maha Thammaracha
and the Crown Prince of Hongsawadi,
is closing in on our city walls, Your Majesty!
Then hold them back, damn it!
But King Maha Thammaracha and Prince Nares
take turns leading the charge, day and night, without rest.
Their only goal is to reclaim the hostages at any cost.
I believe we should return Her Majesty
and Prince Ekathosarot to them.
Once their fury is appeased,
we may then negotiate for peace.
Your Majesty, if those two reach our walls,
we will not be able to hold them back!
Mother, Mother.
Mother.
Father and Nares have prevailed.
They have reached the city walls, Mother.
Why is that, Mother?
Aren't you happy?
I know not what to feel.
On one side is my brother.
On the other, my husband and son.
Ayutthaya
is my birthplace,
yet Phitsanulok is where I shall rest forever.
Victory or defeat,
for me there is no joy to be found.
And if Ayutthaya falls,
What will happen to us, Mother?
King Bayinnaung will execute your uncle,
and appoint someone else
to rule over Ayutthaya.
And what if Ayutthaya wins?
Hongsawadi would withdraw its forces,
leaving Phitsanulok
under Ayutthaya's rule once more.
But you…
you would lose
both your father
and your brother.
For they would both fight
until their very last breath.
Then, for all the prayers you offer,
for whom do you ask for a blessing, Mother?
I pray
for the protection of this land.
Whichever hands are destined to save this kingdom,
may the heavens
grant them victory.
Wait, Prince Nares! It is I, Phraya Ram.
Do you remember me?
I once attended your court at Chan Palace, when you were a child.
- We have it, Your Highness.
- Wow.
It is so big.
This one is a feisty fellow, and with quite the pair of spurs, too.
Phraya Ram.
My loyalty to King Maha Thammaracha has never wavered.
In the chaos, I failed to recognize Your Highness.
Please forgive me.
Nares!
My master taught us.
When facing an enemy,
be steadfast, and never waver.
You were about to take his life.
Why did you stay your hand?
I knew him once.
When I was but a boy,
Phraya Ram was very kind to me.
But now, you both stand on opposite sides.
He is your enemy.
In the past,
I believed that war
was simply about killing strangers
or those not of our kind.
But in the reality of battle, be it a friend,
a brother,
or someone you once knew so well,
if they stand on the opposite side, you must be prepared to kill them.
Nares.
We grew up together.
I loved you like my own brother.
I, too, saw you as my own elder brother.
We both
were meant to stay on the same side forever.
Was that not the promise?
If you stand by my side,
I shall stand by yours.
This is my solemn oath.
We ask for Princess Suphankalaya
to be my royal consort.
The matter of Princess Suphankalaya is no concern of yours.
Prince Nares is my brother. His sorrow is my own.
Both of you being close to King Bayinnaung could prove to be an advantage.
What is your true intent?
I refuse to be a hostage until my dying day.
You must surpass Prince Nares.
Hongsawadi must never fall to Ayutthaya.
You are the Crown Prince of Hongsawadi.
I am but a captive from Ayutthaya.
How can we ever be brothers?