(Adapted from the novel of the same name
written by Qu Zhongzhi and He Bi)
=Moment of Silence=
=Episode 20=
Wang Shiming.
Long time no see.
- Ms. Su.
Take videos.
It's impossible.
How could it happen?
No way!
You're surprised
when seeing me alive?
Su Xi...
Don't take videos!
Stop!
Stop it!
Get lost!
Stop!
I was kidding you.
Ms. Su and I are good friends.
I didn't kill her!
Believe me!
I'm her brother-in-law.
I didn't kill her, right?
I was just kidding!
You know I was kidding, right?
Xi,
stop it.
Let's go home.
Don't move!
Stay where you are.
Xi,
just stop it.
Come to my office.
Why?
You'll explain how you killed me?
I'll tell you how I survived?
Lingjing,
I didn't kill Mr. Mai.
Wang Shiming did it.
It was Wang Shiming!
Where is the proof?
It's in my house.
OK.
I'll go get the car.
Wait for me.
I knew
you would hurt me.
But I wasn't cautious enough.
You told us to meet at the river bank.
I should've been on guard.
But I wasn't.
Wang Shiming,
you didn't expect
I could survive, right?
Xi,
you shouldn't lie.
When did I go to the river bank?
Lingjing pushed you into the river.
I have proof on my phone.
I've got proof.
See? I've got it!
Mai Lingjing tried to kill her!
It was Mai Lingjing!
I can prove it!
What you've got there...
Ms. Mai?
Ms. Mai is here!
What you've got is fake evidence, right?
Mai Lingjing.
How dare you come back?
Look at him!
He's more like a murderer!
When did you get out
from the mental hospital?
She has a mental problem.
It is true!
Everyone knows about it!
Mr. Zhang,
- you saw her when she went insane,
- I don't know.
right?
I don't know.
You imprisoned me in the mountain
six months ago.
Luckily, I ran away.
I know you're looking for me.
Now I'm back.
Are you happy to see me?
Lingjing, be calm.
We'll be home soon.
Xi!
Lingjing!
Gosh!
Mr. Wang lied to us!
How could he do it?
It's horrible!
He is awful!
No wonder Ms. Mai was never here!
Liar.
You're lying!
Why would I imprison you?
Why would I kill her?
If I did it,
why didn't you call the police?
Am I right, guys?
Why didn't they call the police?
I'll tell you the reason.
We don't have enough proof.
Wang Shiming has got fake evidence.
Now everyone in the company
thinks Lingjing has a mental problem.
We can let him drop his guard first.
We have to destroy his reputation.
I have an idea.
Wang Shiming thinks I'm dead.
We can take advantage of his fear
and make him tell the truth.
Su Xi!
What the heck?
Shiming.
Wang Shiming, you're so scared.
Drop the act.
I'm the CEO
of a publicly-traded company.
You can't just slander me like that.
No one will believe you.
If the police come, they won't buy it!
As you wish.
The police are coming.
Jiang Zhongnan!
You betrayed me!
If I didn't do it,
how could I get the evidence?
What evidence?
You're bluffing!
Here's the security footage
I copied from your house.
You and your mom
had a good conversation.
You didn't know
the security cameras
you installed would catch you red-handed.
You made a rod for your own back.
Wang Shiming,
now it's over.
Honey.
I made a mistake.
Honey, it was my fault.
Please forgive me.
Honey, I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
I love you.
Come on!
Honey, I want to have a baby with you.
Honey, great.
I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
I love you.
Honey!
(Now, all the criminals
are caught and sentenced.)
(Wang Shiming was sentenced to
20 years in prison for fraud and murder.)
(Su Xi was sentenced to five years
for murder and bribery.)
(Li Mei, Wang Shiming's mother,
one year for harboring criminals.)
(Jiang Zhongnan was sentenced to
penal servitude for theft.)
(Zhao Qiang was sentenced to seven years
for the crime of illegal debt and fraud.)
(Yu Hai was sentenced to two years
for assaulting and imprisoning others.)
(Five Years Later)
(In Memory of My Dear Father, Mai Yuanzhi)
Dad.
Please rest in peace.