=The Crow Princess of Fortune=
=Episode 2=
When did I ever say
I was taking you with me?
You interrupted
my attempt to end my life
and ruined my plans.
And now you expect me to thank you?
Move aside.
Move.
(What's going on?)
(I just saved
another ungrateful wretch.)
Well.
Not so cocky anymore, huh?
Why aren't you acting
all high and mighty now?
Done acting tough
with Prince Jing backing you up?
Now that he's gone,
you're
all alone.
What do you mean?
What are you trying to do?
You little jinx,
not a single person
in this world wants you.
You deserve to be burned alive alone
and rot in a filthy ditch.
Your...
Your Highness.
Didn't you already leave?
I've changed my mind.
You're a jinx.
And I'm a cursed star.
Perfect.
I happen to need a daughter.
Do you believe in love
at first sight with a father?
The moment I saw you,
I knew you were meant to be my father.
From now on, my name
is Xiao Suisui.
Since you've acknowledged me
as your father,
then harming the princess
is the same as harming royal blood.
No...
Tell me,
how should we punish them?
Young Mistress,
the Ancestor said
you came down to the mortal world
to change people's opinions of you,
not to kill people and set fires.
Did you forget?
(So annoying.)
(Of course I didn't forget.)
Well, Father...
Killing people isn't good.
We Mystic Crows...
We should do good and build virtue.
But while they may escape death,
they won't escape punishment.
They threw me into
the mass grave for three days.
Then let them experience
the suffering I went through.
Very well.
As you wish.
Your Highness. Spare us.
Three days?
There are wild wolves at the mass grave!
I'll die there, Your Highness!
Let's go.
Your Highness!
Dear.
Dear!
Those crows
followed that little jinx here!
What terrible luck.
What's that great jinx doing back here?
We're doomed to bad luck now.
She's back to bring disaster again.
Princess Xiao Suisui
has returned home with her royal father.
Rise.
(Prince Jing's Manor)
Father,
didn't you say
you had an army of a hundred thousand?
Where are they?
Your Highness!
Watch out.
(Shiwan, Steward of Prince Jing's Manor)
Your servant, Shiwan.
(Dajun, Guard of Prince Jing's Manor)
Your subordinate, Dajun.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Father,
aren't you a prince?
How did things end up this miserable?
Father?
What did you just call him?
As expected of Prince Jing.
Even having a daughter
happens at lightning speed.
Far beyond ordinary people.
Leaving everyone else in the dust.
Exactly.
I picked her up on the road.
I told you long ago,
even the Imperial Preceptor
personally declared my fate.
I am doomed to bring harm
to my loved ones, a lone cursed star.
Because of that,
thirty thousand soldiers were buried
in the northern border,
and my leg as well...
Xiao Suisui, what are you doing?
You're pressing on my leg! Get down.
(It hurts...)
(I can feel my leg again?)
♪Little lucky star,
twinkling with a wink at me♪
♪Every Chinese New Year day brings
the luckiest fortune slip♪
♪The God of Wealth favors me,
the Matchmaker ties red strings for me♪
♪With firecrackers going off,
good things keep coming one after another♪
♪Make a wish on the very first day
of the Chinese New Year♪
♪By the second day,
my belly's already round♪
♪Always talking about dieting,
but the chub never disappears♪
♪Good food brings joy
and happiness every single day♪
♪With lucky stars shining bright,
every year is filled with joy♪
♪I'm bringing blessings to everyone♪
♪Hands clasped together in greeting♪
♪May every family be sweet and happy♪
♪With lucky stars shining bright,
may everything go your way♪
♪Endlessly flowing♪
♪Good fortune♪