A DI DE or 9A B OD AN VL 71 ON 9E.
BAMORO 9ABOBOANVL7ION9E
I think
I still think
it's too early for you to tell Chen Yalu.
The arrow is on the string. I have to shoot.
But to be honest,
I was a bit impulsive.
It's okay.
Anyway, Liu Kaian has taken the bait.
It's not a big problem.
As long as we give out a little bit of small profits,
I believe
he will continue to burn money.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it.
The company is in a mess because of them.
Isn't that a good thing?
The messier they are,
the more likely we'll have a chance to meet.
Stab him to death.
But I started this company together.
It hurts my heart.
You don't want it?
Don't torture it.
Don't worry. Kaixi will get it soon.
Taking over the company is just one step.
What else do you want?
A man who betrays his family
who betrayed his family and his wife,
should have his karma.
Kiki, I'm so happy today.
You saved the company, which means you saved me.
Don't thank me.
I know, men
career comes first.
Kaixi is my hope.
After all,
Is it created with Xu Xi after all?
He can't forget his ex-wife.
and single-minded, right?
No, Chen Yalu.
Why are you talking about this today?
Kiki saved our company.
She's our savior and our precious.
You should thank him.
Fine. How should I thank you?
I'll kneel down to show my sincerity.
Chen Yalu.
Are you kneeling or not?
I'll leave you two alone.
Kiki.
The contract is a success today.
Let's celebrate tonight.
I have plans tonight. Next time.
Okay.
Be careful.
Chen Yalu.
What's wrong with you?
Do you think Jaroe really loves Liu Kaian?
Not necessarily.
She loves herself.
It's not that she can't win.
but she can't afford to lose.
Once you have obsession,
people tend to go astray.
I have obsession too.
That's why I'm here.
I didn't let you run away.
Women are emotional animals. I understand.
You know women so well?
I studied female psychology.
What am I thinking now?
What do you mean?
I know nothing about you.
But I really believed
Because of love.
Go away.
You should thank me.
For what?
Thank me for not being angry in public
and embarrassed you.
You're back.
Mom.
I prepared a table of good dishes
to celebrate your successful signing.
Thank you, mom.
Yes.
We're celebrating the contract.
We might have a banquet next time.
Can you stop talking?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Why are you here?
She asked me out.
It's hard to express her kindness.
I know
you're here to piss me off.
You're half done.
I'm angry.
But after thinking about it,
I didn't want you to be too proud.
So I calmed down.
If you break down at one touch,
I think it's boring.
But your method is too low.
It doesn't matter if it works.
As long as it works.
That's true.
But I'm more confident than you.
I like to be in a daze on the balcony.
Sometimes I think
if I can stay in a corner
in a corner
and enjoy the happiness and romance quietly.
That would be great.
Men prefer the wide sky.
I won't be with you all the time.
That's right.
God has given men the vast world.
But as long as the woman he loves is waiting for him,
he will come back.
Oh, right.
do you think
watching everything?
and watching the man he loves
and everything that happened here.
What do you mean?
Why are you nervous?
Are you scared of Xu Xi?
Yale.
You're prettier than Xu Xi.
But you're not as smart as her.
Actor table.
[Ni Ying Yang as Liu Kaian]
Playing Xu Jinxi
Kei as Yan Jiaying
X Wang as Chen Yalu
Zheng Tuo jiang as Ji Jiang
Anyu as Wu Chun Xiang
Cao Lihua as Xu Mu
Zhang Jianing as Yi Yi.
Liu Weizhou as Lu Wenjun
to perform.
Zhu Asia.
Libin Liu.
Wei Chuan
Wang Jingjing
Wu Yi Yi, Wang Yi, Ma Jing
Jang A-soo.
Lu Cai Yun.
Chen Xin.
Zhao Xin.
Han Chao.
Zhao Yi Cheng.
Wang Tieling.
Xu Zhenbin.
Chen Man-gu.
Staff Form.
Director team.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
The recording team.
Art team.
The styling team.
The production team.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Late production.
Tianjin Jiayi Culture Co., Ltd.
Production Company.
Tientsin Film Pictures Co., Ltd. Ltd. Ltd.
Product Company.
Tianjin Film Pictures Co., Ltd.
[Tianjin Film Co., Ltd.]
Beijing Gaxi Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Wonderful Forest Movie and Culture Co., Ltd.
Beijing Deep Technology Co., Ltd.
Ming Xie Group.
Tientsin Yu Castle International Hotel.
Tientsin Hilton Hotel.
Beijing Handan Steel Hotel.