It's normal for the ring
to go outward like this.
The protruding part is the air bag.
This air bag is filled with semen.
Hold this place and take out the air.
Sex education for someone who's never
dated before is totally useless.
How would it feel if it was useful?
Would it be like a new world?
Contraception is the easiest
way to prevent sexually
transmitted diseases.
It's not an option, but a necessity.
Your bodies are very precious.
My body is precious, so I want my
first time to be with a guy like him.
First love.
First kiss.
First...
Na-eun, I'll protect your precious body.
Let's use all of these together.
Okay, after you open it,
check the front and back.
Check for any tears.
And just like that...
Kang-joon is a member
of Boy of the Month, a
rookie idol group
composed of handsome guys.
He's in charge of cuteness in the group.
Unfortunately, the debut stage
soon became a retirement stage due
to the controversy over the school
violence of the main vocalist.
So they were literally just
the "boys of the month."
But I, Son Na-eun,
became a huge fan of his cute nature
in that short time.
Hey, Na-fatty!
I told you not to call me that!
Wanna go eat after class?
I'm on a diet.
You always say that.
I'm serious this time.
I'm going to be born again after
losing 10 kilograms of body fat.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever.
- Are you kidding me?
- I can't believe this.
Put it on so that it doesn't
rip and push it down.
And that's how you wear it.
(Adult Trainee)
(Yummy Chicken:
Diet Ramen)
Gosh, you eat so well.
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
Sung-mi is gonna set me up
on a blind date next week.
If it goes well, I'll hook you up, too.
We'll be seniors next year.
Why are you dating now?
Seriously? Is that what you think?
What if cutie Kang-joon was your
blind date? You don't be interested?
Look at you smiling.
God, I feel ridiculous
for even saying that.
I think it would be more realistic for
us to get a perfect score on the SATs.
- Hey!
- What?
By any chance, is it just you two?
Yeah.
Then do you want to eat ramen together?
I came with my friend, too,
but there are no empty tables.
There are a lot of empty tables.
He just went to the store.
He's gonna bring a lot of food.
- And you know that Mark Meal, right?
- Of course.
My friend is really good at making it.
It'll be delicious.
I'm a bit uncomfortable.
Just this once.
Hey, let's go to coin karaoke.
- Are you paying?
- Of course.
- Isn't this funny?
- What are they doing?
It cracks me up!
Isn't that Na-fatty?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Right?
- Na-fatty!
It really is her!
It's so nice to see you here!
(Kang Go-eun: God-like
looks, dog-like personality)
Who did you come here with?
- Ja-sun.
Oh, the girl with the weird hairstyle?
- Look at her teeth.
- What the heck?
She's probably saving it for later.
Stop eating, will you?
You're even eating lip tint now?
- Goodness.
- Stop eating already.
If you were gonna do your makeup,
you should've done it properly.
You should contour your jaw line.
You have a huge double chin.
Doesn't she look like Jack Black?
You're right! She looks exactly like him!
- They look so similar!
- Right?
- That's enough.
- Did you see that?
She has a triple chin!
- It's like pork belly!
- How can anyone have three chins?
You'd better now.
I'm on an empty stomach.
"I'm on an empty stomach."
You're on an empty stomach?
- Then what's this?
- Oh my god.
Is it a portable airbag?
Even if you get in an
accident, you won't die.
I said, that's enough, you tramp.
What?
Repeat what you just said.
What did you call me?
Did you know your other nickname
besides "tramp" is "bus"?
I heard all the boys rode you once.
You're not even a countryside bus!
Good for you for being such a huge-ass bus!
- Hey!
Hey, Na-fatty. What are you doing?
- What is she doing?
- Is there something behind us?
Anyway, the next time you do your
makeup, do it properly.
- Contour your jawline, okay?
- Please.
You need some extra contour. Later.
- Bye.
- See you at school.
- Make sure you do your makeup.
- Bye, Na-fatty.
Bye.
I've never seen anyone with a triple chin.
Left three times, right three times.
That way, the sauce can mix well.
Once you eat this, you won't be
able to eat your mom's cooking.
- It smells so good.
- It needs to be microwaved for exactly...
3 minutes and 30 seconds.
- It'll be complete then.
- It looks so good!
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Oh, Na-eun!
- Hello.
- Why is this seat so tiny?
- We should eat somewhere else.
- Where?
Let's go. You saw how I made it, right?
That's how you do it.
- This table is too small.
- What do you mean? It's perfect.
- Wait a minute! Okay, okay!
- Bye!
- Hold on!
- See ya!
- They weren't bad-looking.
- Forget it.
Just look at them. They're not even tall.
Only their heads are big.
They look like lollipops.
They're freaking disproportionate.
Ja-sun, let's raise our standards, okay?
Look who's talking.
You're the one who caked your face.
- Did you put makeup on?
- No!
Gosh!
Hey, I have to go on a diet.
Why did they buy so much?
It's not like we can throw them away.
This is bad for the environment.
Gosh.
This is freaking delicious.
Hey, let's do mukbang on YouTube.
You'll be a hit!
You're home.
Come and eat.
Come on. It hasn't even been a day
since she said she's going on a diet.
She won't even be human if
she eats pork belly now.
Right? Don't you agree?
This is your favorite.
Are you sure you're not going to eat?
You shouldn't starve like that.
You need to eat some greasy
food to be smart and study well.
I know what it takes like.
I already ate it before.
You eat it because you
know what it tastes like!
Honestly,
you only had 1,000 calories today.
No, Son Na-eun! You must hold back!
Don't be a pig!
If you wrap it in organic vegetables,
you won't gain any weight. Here, open wide.
What are you doing?
I'm not going to eat.
If it's delicious, it's zero calories.
Open up. Come on, try it.
Knock, knock.
- It's delicious, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Eat a lot.
- Wow.
I'm jealous of your thick legs.
With one low kick,
you'll be able to break someone's bones.
Shut up, beanpole.
Mom, make her do martial arts.
Look at her arms. She doesn't work
out, but she has mean triceps.
At that rate, she'll be able to bench press
500 kilograms in all three areas.
- I'm done!
- Just eat.
- Once you go to college, you'll lose
weight. - Why didn't you lose weight then?
Because I had you two!
When I was young, I wasn't like you.
Yeah, right. I'm fat because of your DNA!
This isn't the time for
you to worry about dieting.
Just eat and study!
Don't end up skinny and failing
thrice like your brother.
Why are you bringing me into this?
She keeps saying she'll go on a
diet because you keep provoking her.
- All I did was say I'm jealous of her.
- Shut up and go study.
Take a look at her body.
That's enough!
Turn the massage chair off.
Why'd you stop eating? Eat some more.
I grilled all of this.
'Calorie, Calorie, Calorie.'
'Are you eating black bean noodles now?'
'How about a glass of beer?'
'Calorie, Calorie, Calorie.'
'I just stuffed myself with pork belly.'
Darn it.
I shouldn't have eaten it.
(Son Na-eun)
(Na-eun, don't go on a diet.
Your hips are a masterpiece. - J)
Is his name J?
Or maybe his last name starts with J.
Don't tell me it's Jung Joon-ha.
(Jung Joon-ha)
No. He's not my type.
- Kim Sung-joon?
- (Kim Sung-joon)
He looks like a squid.
- (Park Jin-hyuk)
- Don't tell me it's Park Jin-hyuk!
Gosh, he's like an octopus.
All the guys with "J" in their names
look like they came out of the sea.
Gosh, speaking of seafood, I'm hungry.
Wow, are your fingers really that long?
Your hands are really pretty.
What? Are they really?
I do have slender hands.
(Jin Beom)
(3rd place in the high school
fashion audition program)
(Studied abroad)
(Greasy like butter)
Dude, girls don't like flowers or dolls.
Then what do they like?
They like...
perfume.
J?
Don't tell me the most popular and
stylish guy in our school is J!
Then again, since he studied
abroad, he could be more
attracted to glamorous girls
like me than skinny girls.
That's impossible.
(Mid-term practical test:
"Playing instruments that I'm good at."
Next.
Gosh, you should've practiced.
No. 24. Son Na-eun.
She brought a guitar?
That's random.
Did she steal her brother's?
- Does she even know how to play it?
- 1, 2. 1, 2, 3, 4.
Bravo!
She brought a guitar just to show off.
- Then again, she has to be
good at one thing. - Yeah.
Right on!
Yes!
I hate dodgeball the most.
Because it's time for
Go-eun to mess around.
Out!
One more time!
Okay! Nice blocking!
(First J Candidate)
Na-eun, don't go on a diet.
Your hips are a masterpiece.
Give it to Go-eun.
- Her nose is bleeding.
- Poor thing.
Gosh. Kang Go-eun, that awful witch.
I thought my nose was broke.
But did Jin Beom block the ball for me?
Oh my gosh.
How could he look so
cute when he's sleeping?
Look at his skin.
Is he a baby or what?
He looks like he won't even
sweat a bit during the summer.
Doesn't Kang-joon look so cute today too?
Are we allowed to do this during class?
We can't help it if we wanna see him.
Gosh, I don't think my nose
will stop bleeding all day long.
- Let's go!
- Come on!
Are you sure Kang-joon is here?
- What the heck?
- What are you doing?
Huh? Just getting some sun.
- Have you seen Kang-joon?
- No, I haven't.
- Bye.
- Sorry.
- Let's come back next time.
- I thought he'd be here.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
By the way,
you're really popular.
And you're really talented.
- What?
- You're good at the guitar.
No.
I'm not that good at it.
Do you want this?
Huh?
- Why would you give me that?
- Because I liked your guitar performance.
Consider it a gift from a fan.
A fan?
Thanks!
I should thank you, Na-eun.
Kang-joon knows my name!
J?
Isn't it Jin Beom?
- Definitely not.
- Then who is it?
Maybe one of the guys
on the wrestling team?
They really wanted you to join.
They could be approaching you
through this creative method.
But still,
would they give me such
an expensive perfume?
Gosh.
But where'd you get those lollipops from?
It's a secret.
Let's just say a boy gave it to me.
- Kang-joon! You're so handsome!
- Please wear this once!
- Oh my gosh! He's so cute!
- They eventually got him.
- His popularity hasn't died down yet.
- Thanks.
You know it's impossible to close your
left eye and poke your right cheek, right?
Close your left eye and
poke your right cheek?
- Oh my goodness!
- Thanks.
Kang-joon, can you give me your autograph?
- Where?
- Um, here!
- Your PE uniform?
- Yes!
Sure.
What's your name?
- It's Myung-ji!
- Myung-ji.
- Even his autograph is cool!
- Oh my god.
Kang-joon is J?
That's totally impossible.
Could I be so sure?
Nothing is impossible in the world.
Na-eun, don't go on a diet.
Your hips are a masterpiece.
"Na-eun, don't go on a diet.
Your hips are a masterpiece."
Finally, a guy who noticed my
charming hips has appeared!
Guys with poor tastes
would never notice them!
Only sensible guys like Beom
or Kang-joon would know.
(Strong suspects to be J)
(1. Jin Beom
2. Choi Kang-joon)
When you called my name,
I came to you and became a flower.
Kang-joon, I'm already your flower!
A flower that wants to dig
through your nostrils with scent.
Kang-joon.
Na-eun,
don't go on a diet.
Your hips are a masterpiece.
It's good.
You should try some, too.
Not that.
Na-eun,
I don't eat one candy at a time.
I eat two at a time.
I eat three at a time.
We melted all that candy all day long.
Huh?
I'm not ready.
Not yet.
Actually, I've been ready for a long time.
You said you're going on a diet!
- I can't believe you!
- That hurts!
You said you were on a diet,
but you ate a bag of candy at night?
It's because I was sleepy while studying
for exams. I needed something sweet.
Just brush your teeth and go to bed!
Just leave that.
You said you don't get fat
eating organic vegetables.
Go ahead. Enjoy.
Goodness.
- 6, 7. Time for your arms.
- Raise them up.
- 1, 2.
- To the front.
- 3, 4.
- To the side.
- 5, 6.
- Lower them.
7, 8. Time for your arms.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- Hey. Hey!
- You scared me. What?
Don't tell me you think Kang-joon is J.
Come on! That's not even
possible in your dreams!
J... J... It'd be more possible for
the earth science teacher to be him.
- Gosh, what are you saying?
- All righty.
The final evaluation will be a group dance.
- What?
- Awww.
What's up with the reactions?
You know this is important, right?
How will the groups be chosen?
By the order of our numbers?
To be fair, we're going to draw lots.
Four people per group.
But if you're confident, you're welcome
to do individual or couple dances.
God, why are even doing this?
(Drawing lots for the final
performance evaluation)
What's up?
We're totally screwed.
Why the hell does someone like
her need to be in our group?
This is so annoying.
No way! Kang-joon is in our group!
Is fate playing a joke on me?
Jin Beom and Kang-joon?
Both J candidates are in my group!
There's no meat in this beef side dish.
Do they expect us to eat this or what?
Don't you think so?
Na-eun? Hello?
Who am I talking to?
Huh?
What are you thinking about?
I really hate today's lunch.
Did you see him?
Hey, it's Choi Kang-joon!
- Can I join you guys?
- Of course!
Have a seat.
Thanks.
I was thinking about it,
and you know our PE evaluation?
There are two girls and
two guys in our group.
So how about we do a couple dance?
Excuse me.
A couple dance?
I really suck at dancing.
No, it's fine.
I used to suck at dancing, too.
- You?
- Yeah.
No way.
Did you think...
I was born into the world like this?
You're hilarious, Kang-joon!
Or I could teach you.
Okay? Come on, let's do it.
Sure.
Yes!
I think Kang-joon is J.
You saw the way he sweetly looked at me!
Why else would he ask to
do a couple dance with me?
It's because he wants to touch my hips!
Hey, have some conscience and
don't mess with Kang-joon.
I almost hit your philtrum. Gosh.
Then who do you think J is?
That again? I'm sick and
tired of talking about this.
What if this is just a delusion?
You don't hear voices, do you?
You saw the perfume and card yourself.
Did you gift them to yourself?
What?
I'm just afraid you'll take
the SATs in the mental ward.
As your friend,
I'm genuinely concerned for you.
What should we watch?
- Something romantic?
- Yes.
Got it.
- This one?
- No.
No? That one?
What? You don't have a condom?
Not right now.
I'll just take it out before I do it.
- Oh my god! They're going to do it!
- Be quiet!
I'm really good at controlling myself.
You can't even make ramen properly.
I'm out.
Okay, fine. Wait here.
That's Kang Go-eun's voice, right?
Hush!
I guess that's what she always does here.
Last time, I found a used condom in here.
- For real?
- Yeah!
Hello?
Yeah, my boyfriend stepped out.
Let me tell you real quick.
I'm in the same group as Kang-joon.
Yeah! That idol.
The one with the white face.
This Saturday, we're going to get
together at my place and practice dancing.
I'm going to get him drunk and...
sleep with him.
- Keep it down!
- He's not that great.
If I make up my mind to seduce
him, he'll fall for me.
That damn witch!
It's about time I got a new boyfriend.
I've been drawn to cute guys lately.
Kang-joon, who really is your mother?
I want to get on my
knees and bow to her.
That was amazing!
What do you think?
It's not that hard, right?
Not at all.
I'm screwed. I can't pass this evaluation.
You can practice while watching
the YouTube video I sent you.
But we're pairing up for the dance.
We should choose our partner.
Right.
How should we decide?
I want to be with you.
- Um...
- Can't we partner up?
Why the hell is she sticking
out her lips like that?
No matter what kind of
tricks you have up your
sleeve, Kang-joon, my J,
has only me in his heart.
Hey, why aren't you eating?
I can't eat the drumstick
because it looks so pretty.
I'll save it for last.
I wouldn't expect anything
less from a gourmand.
Kang-joon, over here!
Sit with me.
Hey, Kang-joon. Have a seat.
Thanks.
Na-eun, you can have this.
Hey, this is really special.
Eat this and do the couple dance with me.
I'm down! I'm totally down!
But I really suck at dancing, so I
think I'll only cause trouble for you.
I told you. I'll teach you.
Okay?
What? Why aren't you eating this?
Don't tell me you're on a diet.
I am.
Don't go on a diet.
You're perfect just the way you are.
Your hips are a masterpiece.
Kang-joon.
Do you like girls who are fat and chubby?
Yeah, I do like girls who look healthy.
Girls who eat everything well.
I gave up dieting for J.
Na-eun, shall we dance?
I'm talking about the couple dance.
Can you be my partner?
I'm confident that I can do a good job.
Well, Kang-joon just asked me...
What is it?
I like your perfume.
High-five.
(Come to the rooftop after class. - J)
Look at page 34 of your textbook.
It's all in the textbook.
The internal structure of minerals.
1. Crystalline and amorphous.
Crystalline.
The atoms that make up minerals
in an orderly manner...
Na-eun, come to the rooftop after class.
Come to the rooftop after class.
That's it for today.
Make sure you check the major points.
Class is dismissed.
- Thank you.
(Come to the rooftop after class. - J)
Go-eun?
(Adult Trainee)