Ms. Hoshi! Ms. Koyori Hoshi!
He's heading over here.
Kihara...
Ms. Koyori Hoshi.
Yes?
I love you.
Excuse me?
Wait, who are you?
Hey, hey, hey! You're too loud.
What are you doing?
I was loud?
Hoshi, I'll explain to you in the meeting room.
Okay.
My proposal was green-lit as part of our in-house competition?
That's right. The proposal you submitted, and the one by himー
Nice to meet you. I'm Shu Enomoto.
- I became your fan after reading your proposal.
- Too close, too close!
Keep quiet, both of you.
What's going on?
Management was split between your proposal and his. Untilー
I read your proposal,
and realized our ideas and ambitions were the same.
What he said.
Besides, I love all the games you've created so far.
My proposal is nothing compared to yours.
Enomoto, you're a promising lad indeed!
Thank you for the compliment!
- So in short, Hoshi...
- Yes?
You'll be leading this project as the team leader.
I want you to see this game through, with Enomoto as your planner.
Are you up for the challenge?
Yes, sir!
- Sorry for interrupting.
- I started dating my childhood friend, Hijiri.
- I guess it'll be fine if you two stick together.
- Oh, Dad...
Things have been going smoothly in both my work and love life.
- And now, we're finally moving in together.
- Right here.
- It's better to put these on opposite sides, right?
- Yeah.
- The TV.
- Ready, and up.
- Where do I put this?
- Inside here, I guess.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
🎀The bonds of love 💞 Team@Viki.com
Ta-da.
[Koyori, Hijiri]
What now?
We're finally moving in together.
[Changes of Heart]
[Goal: Someday we'll have a cat]
[Holy]
[Hope: Drum-type of washing machine]
Team leader?
[Episode 5]
That's amazing, Koyori.
Thanks for the praise.
What game did you come up with?
I can't be spilling our projects to other companies now, can I?
Ah, right.
Sorry about that.
But this role does come with some pressure.
Yeah, I guess it does.
But even if you hit a wall, don't dwell on it. Make sure to confide in your planner.
Yup, will do.
Things will get busier for me, even though we just moved in. Sorry.
Don't be. I've also just joined a new team, so that makes us even.
If anything, we moved in at the perfect time.
Even if we're both busy, we will still see each other at home.
You're right.
All right. A toast to our first day of living together.
- Cheers!
Let's dig in. It looks delicious.
Bon appetit.
Yummy.
Delicious!
Speaking of, how do we split the chores?
Let's see. For starters, we'll clean our own rooms.
As for the common areas, I guess whoever notices the mess can clean it.
Why are you sighing? Or should we properly assign responsibilities?
I'm just bummed we're sleeping in separate rooms.
Come on, Hijiri...
Oops, I'm sorry!
You're right. It's better for us to sleep in separate rooms.
Since we may go to bed at different timings.
Sorry, I know we already talked about this.
I was also really conflicted about it, to be honest.
But for tonight...
shall we sleep together?
- Hijiri, I'm coming in.
- Go ahead.
Whenever you're ready.
Koyori?
This feels awkward. It's been quite some time, you know?
Huh? What do you mean?
The mood just screams we're going to do it now, so... yeah.
- Huh? We're doing it?
- We're not?
Good night!
Wait, hang on.
Koyori, let's do it.
From now on, we won't have to go home separately on our days off.
Oh no! Hijiri, wake up!
- Oh shit!
- Hurry!
- We're going to be late.
- No...
Koyori, I'll get going first. Make sure to lock up before leaving.
Got it. See you.
- Bye.
- Take care.
Jeez, I wanted to prepare breakfast.
[Idol Buster]
Hoshi, please say a few words.
I'm Hoshi, the team leader for this project.
I look forward to working with you all.
The team may be small now, but more folks will be joining,
so do your best in the meantime.
Will do. If anything, I'm prepared to complete this game with our current team.
I'll follow you all the way!
Don't push yourself too hard, yeah?
I'm so glad you're in this with me, Kihara.
I'm stuck with a clique-ish team, huh?
- Mr. Kawano.
- What is it?
It's my first time being a team leader, so I may trouble you in a variety of ways.
If you have any suggestions, feel free to let me know.
I'll welcome any advice.
Sure.
All right, let me start by giving an overview of the game.
With the development team set up, we've begun working towards launch.
Meanwhile, Hijiri was also busy in his own way.
I'm off to work.
Jeez... the sofa will get moldy if this goes on.
Though we live together, the only time I get to see Hijiri is just before I go to bed.
I'm off.
- Welcome back.
- I'm home.
On days when I get home late, Hijiri will pick me up at the bus stop.
Did you eat already?
- Yeah, a little.
- A little?
I was eating when you texted that you were on your way home.
What? You should have carried on with your meal.
It's fine. I wanted to eat together with you.
Really?
I'm turning in first. Good night.
Good night.
I hope he's not pushing himself too hard just to live together with me.
But why?
I mean, it's just a towel. Whoever notices can hang it back up.
Still...
This happens every day. Does he really not notice?
- Ms. Hoshi!
- D-Don't raise your voice so suddenly like that!
Sorry about that.
I've made a flowchart for the game. Can you review it?
Oh, right. Thanks.
- I'll email it over to you.
- Sure.
[Idol Buster - Battle Mechanics Flowchart]
It's good.
Glad to hear that.
If there's nothing else, I'll take my leave then.
- Sure. See you.
- Bye.
Planners like you sure have it easy, huh?
Always heading home before us.
Guess I'll stay back and do a little more work.
- Just go home, Enomoto.
- But...
Mr. Kawano, don't make your junior feel guilty for heading home.
I'm just stating the facts.
Enomoto is only going home early because he has completed his work during office hours.
Are you saying I wasn't doing work during office hours?
- No, she isn't...
- Mr. Kawano.
You were the one who often said, "I can just stay back", no?
I was obviously joking, could you not tell?
- Then can you explain to me why you're staying back right now?
- Erm...
That's because my team leader,
Ms. Hoshi, was late in giving us the development schedule!
We work according to that schedule.
You keep tweaking around with the characters and specs.
I'm the one doing the programming.
My work will never end if you don't come to a compromise.
Point noted. I'll simplify it further then.
You don't have to compromise, Ms. Hoshi.
What?
The game will no longer be fun if you compromise on the important parts.
Besides, I love the programs that you write, Mr. Kawano.
You make the characters' movements look so sleek.
Say what?
I believe you can build a user-friendly system that will be the key to this game's success.
Well, yeah... That's what I've been trying to achieve.
I knew it! I'm right, aren't I?
Sorry about what I said earlier.
Nah, don't worry about that.
Same to you too, Ms. Hoshi.
No, likewise, I'm at fault.
All right, let's grind, shall we?
Okay...
Koyori, welcome back.
What's wrong?
Did something happen at work?
I see. I've gotten that sort of envy too, about going home early.
But I've finished my work. Of course, I'll leave.
So whether it's your junior or you, don't be bothered by it and head home.
- Okay.
- If you could leave earlier, I wouldn't need to pick you up either.
As long as you clearly explain why such specs are necessary, I'm sure they'll understand.
You've always been frank with me, right?
- So be frank with them, too.
- I can't.
Koyori?
We're behind schedule because I haven't been leading them properly.
I can't be frank, knowing I'm the reason for their stress.
I see.
It's the same with you.
There's no way I can be entirely frank with you.
Of course, I know that.
Oh my god.
Huh? What did Iー
I feel so stupid for getting irritated and worked up all on my own.
You don't have to force yourself to hold back your frustration.
Aren't you the one who's forcing yourself?
I don't think I am, though.
You said you wouldn't "need" to pick me up if I left earlier.
Oh, I meant it as we could leave together from the office instead.
I still feel bad making you come to get me whenever I work late.
Wait. You don't want me to pick you up?
Not that I don't want you to.
But you have early mornings and still come to get me, even if you're in the middle of dinner.
Just like you're worried about me,
I'm also worried about you.
I was going home on my own when I lived alone, so I'll be fine.
I get it now. I won't pick you up anymore.
But promise you'll call if you see anyone suspicious nearby.
- I will.
- Good.
Let's go.
By the way, you always leave your towel hanging on the sofa.
Stop that bad habit, all right?
Sorry, I'll hang it back where it belongs next time.
- So there's nothing else?
- Yup. Everything's good.
As long as we're frank with each other, everything will surely be fine.
How could he forget after just one day?
Maybe we were better off...
"Better off..."?
Hoshi, let's call it here and grab some drinks.
You need to unwind once in a while.
- Huh?
- Or did you have plans with your boyfriend? It is Friday.
I don't have any plans in particular.
Let's do that. It's been a while.
All right!
- Do you want to join us, Enomoto?
- Yes, please!
- Ooh...
- Yay!
I'm working on a personal game, so I'll pass.
Gotcha!
- Thanks for the hard work!
- Cheers!
- Ms. Kihara, when you go "boom" like that, you're really cool.
- You're too loud.
And what do you mean by "boom"? Call me "mature," why don't you?
But I get what you mean.
Hey. Then, Enomoto, what vibe does Hoshi give you?
- Huh?
- Don't bother. Enomoto's sound effects don't make sense.
You agreed with his "boom," though.
For Ms. Hoshi, it's like a "whoosh" feeling.
- "Whoosh"?
And what does that mean?
"Whoosh," as in when you ride a roller-coaster?
It's the excitement before the drop,
the thrill and adrenaline rush when you fall, and the relief when it's all over.
That's how I feel when working with Ms. Hoshi.
I hope to keep having this kind of feeling moving forward.
Could it be that he...
Sorry.
I was the one who invited you guys, but I have to leave now.
- What?
- My share. Let me know on Monday if it's not enough.
- Wait a minute...
- Sorry, Hoshi.
I forgot that my cat is waiting for me.
You have a cat? Since when?
- Ms. Hoshi!
- Y-Yes?
- You see, I...
- Listen!
I have a boyfriend.
I know that.
You mentioned you have a date or something with him. Right?
Gosh, I misunderstood him!
Are you sighing because of your boyfriend?
You've been sighing the entire time today.
- Are things going south with him?
- Wrong.
Sorry.
Have you ever moved in together with a girlfriend?
No.
- You're living with your boyfriend, Ms. Hoshi?
- Yeah.
We moved in together not long ago.
Despite our long history, I'm only now realizing our different habits bother me.
He's my childhood friend, soー
- Your childhood friend?
- Too loud.
Speaking of, who was the one who confessed first?
- Him.
- Wow!
What's with that reaction?
He's your childhood friend?
I'm so envious.
Let's go, shall we?
Do you have any plans after this?
What?
I'm home.
I forgot about it again.
I guess I should stop using my towel in the living room.
I'll apologize to Koyori when she gets back.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
🎀The bonds of love 💞 Team@Viki.com
[I'm heading home soon! No need to pick me up.]
Almost forgot.
I'm so tired.
Do you have plans after this?
What?
Do you normally have supper after drinking?
Huh? No, I don't. I'm leaving.
- But why? Let's go get supper.
- Go home.
Why does being around you always tire me out?
I didn't realize we both lived close by. What a coincidence.
But your home is in that direction, no?
Let's part ways here.
I can also go home by this route.
I'll walk you home on the way.
Is that so? Thanks.
- Mind if I drop by the convenience store?
- Go ahead.
Sorry, Hijiri.
Let's eat it together.
♫ Only you can bring me a love ♫
♫ that will change my life ♫
I can't decide.
Hijiri!
♫ A casual moment makes me wonder ♫
Ms. Hoshi?
♫ But one thing is for sure ♫
♫ Do you wanna be my lady? ♫
Hijiri?
♫ Oh baby, say "I do" ♫