Let's go. Let's go.
It's so mysterious.
What surprise are you going to give me?
Take a guess. It's what you want the most in your heart.
Be careful.
Is it
the house, car, money,
I have all my wives and children.
Then I'll be a salted fish.
What are you daydreaming about?
Let's try something practical.
Staying up late without losing hair
is my lowest wish.
Isn't this my three axes?
Yes.
It was redeemed by your husband.
He even rebuilt the golden body for it.
Oh my god.
Mr. Gu, you are so nice to me.
Don't say anything cheesy.
As long as you like it.
Now the flower cake business is on track.
All your wishes
will come true one by one.
Dear.
I have something to do.
I won't go to the market.
It's already copied?
I don't believe it.
It's definitely not as delicious as ours.
That's right. It's definitely not as delicious as ours.
Sister.
Our Fantasy Flower Cakes are the best.
This is the best flavor.
Our skin is crispy.
The filling will definitely suit you.
Our color is beautiful, sweet but not greasy.
Come on, sister.
Our family uses
pure natural and polluted roses as ingredients.
Yes.
Look at ours
We have lilies.
We have jasmine and silver.
Both.
Let me see yours.
Development a new product overnight.
Do we have to work so hard?
Once something becomes popular,
follow the trend.
But I didn't expect it to be so fast.
It seems
it's time to plan a new way out.
No, we're all waiting.
If you can't find a way out,
we'll go back to our old business
and continue the robbery with me.
Yes.
Gu, have you figured it out?
Not so fast.
Mr. Gu sacrificed his life
for Black Tiger Fortress.
Don't force him.
We are really afraid
to live a poor life.
That's right.
Honey.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Stop talking. There's always a way before the mountain.
Take a good rest.
No one can disturb him.
Be careful.
Mr. Gu is such a handsome boy.
has been tortured.
Brother Hu.
The merchant ship is on the shore.
It's time for me
to save Black Tiger Hideout.
Guys, come with me to do something big.
Come on, let's do something big.
You're back.
I'm in a rush. I'm definitely not.
when you were sleeping.
I see.
Don’t worry. I trust you.
So what did you do?
We’re still investigating.
Investigate what?
Why did you get him out?
I'm not trying to trick you.
You said it yourself.
How do you know what I'm thinking?
Why do you look so pale?
Where did you go?
Sister, Brother Gu.
Come out and have a look.
I finally made it.
You... You went to rob?
Unfortunately, Gu was not there.
I was so brave.
You are bandits.
You can't do pirates' business.
You're all wet.
you must be fishing for goods in the sea.
Did a merchant ship sink?
Stop it.
Besides, you're going to wear my underpants.
Then tell me.
With so many treasures,
we will make a fortune.
Open the box, guys.
What is this?
I risked my life to get these.
Wait.
Since these merchant ships are sinking,
these rouge and powder
can't be delivered in a short time.
It will soon become a delicate object.
I'll go down the mountain to investigate.
You mean this rouge is out of stock?
This rouge is the most sold here.
How long will it take
how long will it take?
I need more than a month.
White clouds. Why is she here?
Make a reservation.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go.
Rouge, top-quality rouge.
Miss, come and take a look at the rouge.
What is Baiyun doing recently?
Gu Jinyu.
How long are you going to hide it from us?
We treat you
as sworn brothers.
How can you do this to us?
Is your identity exposed?
I don’t know what you are talking about.
Stop acting. Please.
Guys, set up the formation.
What's wrong with this?
You're sick, honey.
You don't want the antidote?
You've gone too far.
She didn't even tell us about the poisoning.
She searched all medical books for you these days.
She begged all the witch doctors and used blood as the guide
to create this magical medicine.
Compared to what my husband did for us,
what I did for us is nothing.
Take the antidote.
We've prepared a welcoming ceremony for you.
and officially accept you as our brother.
The poison has been detoxified.
But if one day my identity is exposed,
what should I do?
Dear.
What is this?
It's such a pity to lose it
It's not a pity.
In other people's eyes, it's just rubbish.
Do you know
how to become a qualified Young Master?
to deal with internal affairs and save money.
To protect the city,
You need to be emotionally emotionless and heartless.
Don't let anyone know your weakness.
If you can't bear the mission of Young Master Rong,
don't blame me for taking back all your rights.
Yes, Father.
I won't let you down.
Life would be so boring if there were only missions.
It's because good things are fading away,
That's why I have to save it and take it slow.
If someone sees it as waste paper,
he's blind.
He doesn't know the treasure.