There are so many boxes.
Look.
Open the box, guys.
Mr. Gu is generous.
Heihu Stronghold is powerful.
is really impressive.
It takes a minute to accept a bank.
That's right.
You know them?
So what?
You were the one
was also your doing.
You are stupid and rich.
Don't blame me.
You set up this trap
to squeeze out a large amount of cash.
Zhao Mu heard that I bought a lot of stores
he started to take action.
Did he really stop us?
I've told all the shops owners
to pay Zhao Mu a high price for the acquisition.
Once Zhao Mu has no money,
he'll definitely come after Concubine Liu.
Can the bank have that much money?
Of course not.
So,
We need to feed it.
Send someone to save money inside.
Once Zhao Mu embezzles the money,
send someone to squeeze the money out,
Zhao Mu will be a red ass monkey.
He'll be burnt to death.
Pay me back!
He set me up. Ask him for money.
Zhao Mu.
I advise you to find a way to pay the money back.
Otherwise, if the government finds out,
not only will your bank be confiscated,
you'll also go to jail.
Young Master.
If you beg me,
I can buy your bank
to buy your bank.
your crisis will be solved today.
Bank.
Kneel down and beg me.
and promise not to appear in business again.
Or I’ll make you go bankrupt
I'll make you go bankrupt.
The bank
is yours.
What?
I have no name?
Gu Jinyu.
The bank
is yours.
Exchange the votes.
It's all over.
Here's the money.
Brothers and sisters,
The business of Heihu Stronghold is the top in the city now.
Okay.
I announce
the annual bonus meeting of Heihu Hideout
starts now.
OK.
Line up, everyone.
I'll go first.
Thank you.
Take it.
Here.
Uncle Zhang.
I’m old enough to get money.
Everyone in Black Tiger Stronghold
will get dividends.
Like father, like daughter.
Good job.
Okay.
Here.
Xiao Tian Hu, pay the money.
Catch it.
Why are you here?
Isn’t it your wish
Isn’t that what you’ve always wanted?
But you don't seem happy.
I'm happy.
I just
think of my father.
If my father is still alive,
I can share my happiness with him.
Why?
I want to share your happiness with your father.
Because my father loves me the most in the world.
When I was young,
no matter what I wanted,
my father will try his best to give it to me.
If I did something wrong,
My father doesn't blame me.
He would find excuses for me.
When I'm unhappy,
Dad will always be with me.
But now,
when I was the happiest,
I couldn't tell him.
It's okay.
From now on,
I'll be with you.
Let's go down the mountain and play.
When we have money, we should spend it freely.
Let's go.
Take a look.
Monkey King versus Piggy.
Look.
It's so fun.
Yes.
Can I borrow your shadow puppet play later?
Sure.
Wait for me here.
Where are you going?
I'm going to put on a good show.
Rumor has it that
named Zhu Yingtai.
She disguised herself as a man and entered the academy.
and met her classmate, Liang Shanbo.
Liang Zhu has been classmates for three years.
They study together during the day.
and sleep together at night.
Liang Shanbo saw Zhu Yingtai had ears piercing.
So he asked
Yingtai is not a woman.
Why are there rings on your ears?
There's a reason for the earrings.
Why do you suspect Yun?
There are many temples in the village.
I'll be Guanyin every year.
I don't dare to look at Guanyin anymore.
They fell in love with each other gradually.
I don't know how Zhu Yingtai
explain this lie to Liang Shanbo.
And Liang Shanbo
didn't know Zhu Yingtai was a girl.
Honey, why don't you continue?
Have you ever thought that...
What if
we are the same as them?
You mean hiding your real identity
and deceive each other?
Actually,
I've been wanting to tell you something for a long time.
Yunxi, actually I...
Say no more.
I knew it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect
between us.
Dear.
Why do you think I'm lying to you?
I'm a real woman.
Feel it if you don't believe me.
No, you don't understand.
I...
I know it too well.
No, you really don't understand.
I mean...
Don't be shy. Try it.
I'm not shy. I just want to say
I must prove myself.
I...
Look at the fireworks.
Forget it.
Let's not disturb her today.
and find another chance to confess.
Look at that.
So beautiful.
Six six eight horses
Two brothers are good. Six, six, six.
Honey.
Do you think it's too noisy here?
I just didn't expect
the Spring Festival
It's so lively.
It's New Year. It's lively.
to drive away the Nian.
Nian?
Nian is the loneliness in your heart.
But after you have family and friends,
I won't.
Here, take some food for you.
The Nian in my heart must be very fierce.
So no one can drive him away.
Thank you.
Master.
Uncle Zhang is here.
Uncle Zhang, what took you so long?
I’m not here for hot pot.
I’m here to fulfill the old chief’s order.
Uncle Zhang.
Did my father leave me a gold mountain?
Actually, my real identity is the richest man in the city.
The old chief told me
to give you the secret treasure
I'll give you the secret treasure of Black Tiger Stronghold.
I can finally complete the task today.
A secret treasure.
Uncle Zhang.
Are you serious?
Open it.
The treasure map.