Be careful.
Watch out!
Are you okay?
I smell sulphur.
This is a hot spring.
It's a treasure.
Here it is.
What kind of treasure is this?
Could the ancestors of Black Tiger Stronghold
made a joke for 100 years?
On the contrary,
our ancestors' wisdom is unpredictable.
If there are really thousands of treasures here,
it might cause trouble.
Dear.
You're forcing yourself to save your dignity again.
Let go of me!
Master Rong.
Master Rong, I know I was wrong.
For the sake that I've given birth to your children,
Please forgive me.
Parents love their children.
[they will plan for a long time.]
I understand
I understand.
But don't forget,
Yu is also my child.
Take him away.
Take him to the farm.
Yes.
I'm old.
and my ideas are old.
I used to rule the city with iron wrist.
Everyone was afraid of me,
but they don't respect me.
And you
are kind-hearted
and resolved many grudges.
It's time to take over my job.
Please withdraw your order.
In the past,
living in the shackles of responsibility and expectations.
I've never lived for myself.
Now,
I just want to live for myself once.
and become a woman.
My father is young and strong.
He can inherit the foundation.
In the past,
I treated you harshly
and ignored your feelings.
I never even hugged you.
It's my fault.
Now,
do what you want to do.
Father.
Old Castellan.
These flowers and fruits are only for appreciation.
What a pity.
Why don't we use it
Let's make a deal together.
As the saying goes, you don't make money, king.
Not a good man.
I have to do this business.
Or I won't even be a hero.
God,
The earth is the proof.
Today, we are sworn brothers.
We will be united
and help each other.
Fortune and fortune are together.
We'll live and die together.
This is the second master.
Is it really her?
Is it her?
From now on,
I'm no longer the Young Master of White Dragon City,
but the second head of Black Tiger Hideout.
Please teach me.
Brothers.
The most important thing for us now
to develop the natural hot spring in our village.
It's so sweet.
I've decided.
I'll only marry her in this life.
Thinking about it, I used to hold a grudge against her.
What a sin.
She will be the deity in my heart.
Look at you losers.
You're turning against me faster than you are.
How ungrateful.
You should have principles.
The most important thing now is to change the fortress.
I hope you can work together.
I’ll do as you say.
I’ll do my best.
Don't flatter me.
There was a swing
in the City Governor's Residence.
Unfortunately, no one was willing to play with me.
Then I tore it down.
It's okay.
You have me now.
You won't be lonely with me.
Let me push you.
Sit tight.
Sister.
Let me do it.
Okay.
Sit tight.
Not bad Shooting Tiger, very strong.
Look.
There are two flowers on this one.
These are twins.
They are twins.
They will be together
Live and die together.
That one is called Jinyu.
and the other is Yunxi.
What do you think?
It's all up to you.
Then we won't take this one off.
Let’s take good care of it together.
Let me take care of the Second Master.
And sister.
Put it over there.
Put it here.
Be careful.
Look how nice I put it on.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
It's good for your skin.
Which one would you like?
Please come in.
I didn't expect the poor Black Tiger Stronghold
would be like this.
The business of the fortress is on track now.
Do you have any plans for the future?
I want to travel around the world
around the world.
Fill up
your picture book.
Your life is still long.
We can plan it slowly.