Be careful.
Tiger Shou!
Xiao Tian Hu, how are you?
Run!
Fire!
Put out the fire!
Be careful.
He's badly injured.
Let's go find the doctor.
Hurry.
Let's go.
I've worked hard for many days.
It's like cutting off the way of Black Tiger Stronghold.
Who could
did such a crazy thing?
It's so hateful.
That's right.
No.
Why are you looking at me?
I didn't do it this time.
If it wasn't you,
after the explosion,
everyone came to put out the fire.
Where are you?
I'm really wronged.
I think you won't cry until you see the coffin.
I found these from your room.
What else do you have to explain?
In the future, you'll be able to grow and become stronger.
and become the national champion.
Since you're so cruel,
don't blame me for being unjust.
Who's outside?
How is that possible?
You're slandering me!
Help!
Arrest him!
I did my best for the fortress.
I bled for the fortress.
You can't do this to me.
Kick Wang Hu out of the fortress.
It has nothing to do with Black Tiger Hideout.
Let's go.
I didn't do it.
It was you.
Let's go.
It's not easy to sell.
but it's broken again.
Dear, what should we do?
There's always a way.
Don’t worry. There will be a solution.
Madam. Madam.
The Counsellor is awake.
You are going to die.
Why are you taking medicine?
I'll drink less.
we'll have one more bowl of rice.
It's just a scratch.
You'll be fine after some rest.
Hush.
Don't lie to me.
I know my own body.
I feel a stone on my chest.
I can't breathe.
I don't think I'll live long.
Nonsense!
Leader.
Considering your contribution yesterday,
I asked the kitchen to prepare some food for you.
These are all your favourites.
You're not feeling well now.
It's hard to digest these food.
Not yet.
Then why did you bring it here?
We've been through thick and thin together.
We should share happiness.
Look at us.
I kind of feel a little involved.
Are you here to piss me off?
Don't be so pessimistic.
It's not too late to eat after you recover.
Honey, try this.
The heat is not bad today.
It melts in your mouth.
It's soft and sweet.
I can't eat. I'll just drink some water.
You must be thirsty.
Let me feed you some water.
Do you have any humanity?
It's work injury.
I'm thirsty too.
I want you to feed me.
Okay.
I don't want my hands.
I want it.
You!
You've gone too far.
You're really clever.
Otherwise, the blood stasis can't be removed.
It's hard to heal.
What a beggar!
You want to eat and drink with a broken knife?
Stop pretending to be a hero.
Where is this place?
Get out of here.
Isn't this the second head of Black Tiger Stronghold?
Why are you in such a state?
Did he get kicked out by the fortress?
30 years in Hedong and 30 years in Hexi.
Wait for me to rise again.
I guess I was right.
Since they are heartless,
why don't you follow me?
I'll take you to a good place
to avenge your death.
Thank you for taking me in.
I'm willing to serve you.
Please get up.
It's been a long time
Please.
What should we do?
Cheer up!
We've been through a lot.
This is nothing.
This is all we have left
That's all we have left.
The granary was also in trouble.
It's all barbecue.
Nothing.
It's my turn.
No movement.
It's not suitable.
So,
the fortress is back to the time
I’m poor now.
It's not as good as before.
We're all good now.
We don't even dare to kill pigs.
let alone robbery.
What should we do?
Dear.
Please save Black Tiger Stronghold.
Fortunately, someone in Black Tiger Hideout has skills.
and has connections.
Now,
can only turn the situation around
to change the situation.
By the way,
do you have any special holidays or events recently?
Is there?
It's the 250th anniversary of Heihu Stronghold's establishment.
Got it.
Temple fair.
Got it. That's it.
Guys.
Go down the mountain for business.