Brother Gu made another contribution today.
I feel so relieved.
Mr. Gu, you are really our benefactor.
Thanks to him,
Everyone's life is getting better.
I'm flattered.
Guys, I have something to tell you.
Since my husband came to Black Tiger Hideout,
he has made countless contributions.
The position of the second head is vacant.
I have an idea.
to propose him to be our Second Master.
What do you think?
Okay.
Don't be idle. What about me?
Tiger.
You made such a big mistake.
Don't be a demon.
They won't allow you.
Even if I fail,
even if I can't.
According to the rules,
if you want to sacrifice the pillar for Black Tiger Fortress,
we need a recommendation
and go through hell.
to prove his sincerity.
to join us.
I can protect him.
As for the punishment,
you are so delicate.
Can you stand it?
I’m willing to try.
to take the position of the second head
to get the map sooner.
According to the rules,
we need to cross the sea of fire
and climb the mountain of swords.
and finally get the banner.
Honey.
Don’t worry. I’ll be careful.
Brother Gu.
Please.
Be careful.
Watch out, Gu.
Can you bite yourself?
Sorry.
All I think about is Gu.
Okay.
Honey.
How are you?
Are you okay?
Your hand...
It's cloudy.
I'm glad you're fine.
My husband got the banner
successfully pass.
From today onwards,
he is the second head of Black Tiger Hideout.
Congratulations on your return.
Congratulations!
Second Master.
Fortunately, we prepared in advance.
Otherwise, we would have killed you.
Didn't you expect that you would get hurt?
It's nothing.
I'll do my best
I will do my best.
I'd rather not be the Second Master.
Let me tell you.
Wang Hu's expression today
It's so dark.
So funny.
He's lucky.
If I hadn't rushed back to treat you,
I would have killed him.
Don't be angry.
You.
Who is it?
Show me if you dare.
Please spare my life.
Stop fighting!
How dare you cheat in secret?
Tiger Shou.
I'm not Tiger.
How dare you hit me?
I got you, the kitchen thief!
So you were eating secretly.
Today, because of me,
because of me.
So I came here to get you something to eat.
You made this?
I don't know who did it.
But it's yours now.
Oh no.
The roast chicken is here.
That's strange.
I put the roasted chicken here.
Can it fly?
Where's the chicken?
Well...
Eat this.
It's quality.
The style is new.
It's a batch of good goods.
It can be handed over.
It seems that
we can have a new year
our village will have a new year.
Look at you.
This is nothing.
As long as my husband and I are here,
we can be strong
and dominate the country.
and lead the world.
Right, honey?
Now our goods are in the market.
As long as we keep progressing,
and ensure
will make a fortune in the future.
Who's outside?
I smell gunpowder.