I'm not afraid of anything.
searched
I'm really sorry.
I just looked it up.
It's okay.
Just cut that fat man a bit.
And kowtow.
kowtow to your screen.
I'm afraid you're not the same Wang Fatty.
Uncle Xia,
did you see it wrong?
I didn't see it wrong.
I saw it wrong.
This is a trap.
Third Master!
I'm afraid it's you.
Uncle Xia,
you're not calling me?
Don't be afraid.
I'll wait for you from now on.
No matter it's a day,
ten years,
or a hundred years, I'll wait.
Until you die,
or I die.
Whatever it is, kill me!
Third Master!
Fatty, what are you doing?
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Come on, this is not your game.
This is not your game.
You're a fool.
Why did you invite me to the field?
Why did you invite me?
You're under the spell of the
I don't know either.
Then what is this box for?
This is the silver and silver deer top
in the eight treasures.
I don't understand.
This is the last one
in the eight boxes of the Sheli Zi.
But this thing
is obviously much smaller
than that silver deer top.
When it was a war,
Buddhism had not yet
entered China.
Besides, it's not
Sheli Zi in here.
Could it be that
it's the blood of
King of Lushan?
Then open it and take a look.
Come on.
This key
should be for this box.
Wu Xie.
Why don't you open it?
You're stupid.
There was a female lion
with a female chicken in it.
If we open this box
and run into any kind of mechanism,
we'll all die.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm stupid.
I...
Let's go back and study it.
No.
Okay.
Aomenshimpujing Entertainment City 772772.com
The most exciting PG game on the line.
The mahjong is over.
The mahjong is over 2.
The prize-winning queen
is looking for a golden city.
The super high rate of compensation
for the talented cat,
the prize-winning captain,
and so on.
The prize-winning rate is high.
There are many opportunities for revenge.
Hurry up and join.
Aomenshimpujing Entertainment City 772772.com
I have to find her first
and leave this place.
What's going on?
I don't know either.
Do you two see anything special
in the tomb?
Why should I tell you?
That's right.
There are many dangerous people in this tomb.
If you two want to save Wu Xie,
we can cooperate.
You're dreaming.
How can we
be in the same boat
with you thieves?
We don't steal cultural relics.
What are you joking about?
If I don't take cultural relics,
can we cooperate?
Liu Tai.
The premise is
you two help me save Ning.
Or at least help me repair the equipment
so that we can contact her.
Ning?
Think about it.
Is there anything strange
going on in the tomb?
There are so many holes here.
Every hole
is connected to this big tree.
Where is the way to get out of here?
The blood is coming.
Oh, my god.
He's so bold.
It's Xiaoqi.
What are you doing?
I'm going down.
You can't get out of here.
Go away.
Xiaoqi, you're so good.
You're fighting.
Nice.
Xiaoqi, come on.
Xiaoqi, you're so good.
Come on.
Xiaoqi.
Oh, no.
Xiaoqi, I'll kill you.
Don't go. It's dangerous.
He'll kill you.
Let go.
Go.
Wu Xie.
Xiaoqi, I'll kill you.
Xiaoqi.
Come on.
You.
I'll buy you.
I'm so tired.
Father, I got his Esti second track
on which I could
find out about something ici.
Father,
Where's the recording ofwar?
It's not to me.
You know that, right?
Hmm
Someone is already dead in Seven Stars Calligraphy
Now tell me, what else?
You're not going to steal even your coffin
You're not in the right place
so what are you guys trying to do?
None of your business
You two should use this place to restore the equipment
If not, you could still الحrer
It seems like the fire is made up.
I found the
Okay
The medicine
Look
Can you see
Ah?
You.
I was scared.
You were quite severe.
You can actuallyстаught lyrics nicely.
Killing one's own person is really miserable.
Is it the poison House blood?
The poison House blood?
He vomited blood and woke up.
He should be fine.
Xiao Qi, I am An Ning.
An Ning.
Wu Xie.
Wu Xie, how do you feel?
Xiao Ge.
What should we do now?
Why did you become like this, Xiao Qi?
Dong Zi and I...
We have been in the same room.
But I drank the water there.
I had a hallucination.
Dong Zi is lying on the west side.
Don't go.
It's dangerous.
Xiao Qi.
Xiao Ge.
Don't worry, Qi Lin Jie.
Or I will kill you.
What are you doing?
Stop it, go and drop the gun.
This is Qi Lin Jie.
What is Qi Lin Jie?
Miss An Ning.
What do you want Qi Lin Jie for?
I want to save my partner.
You're crazy. Your partner is already dead.
Shut up!
Use the Qilin knot to exchange your life.
We saved your life.
You haven't paid it back yet.
I'll shoot when you count to three.
One.
Hey, is this woman for real?
Two.
Let her go.
I'll help you find other partners.
I told you.
You're the one who saved us.
You're the one who's the most vicious.
Ming Ping.
Hey.
Ming Ping, where are you going?
Help her find someone.
Don't worry, Wang Guixi. With Xiao Ge's skills,
she'll return safely.
Come.
What did that Ming Ping give me to eat?
Third Master, what is this Qilin knot?
Qilin knot?
Qilin knot is actually a very expensive Chinese medicine.
The longer you put it in, the better it will work.
Qilin knot is used to make a corpse.
The Qilin knot you ate earlier, from the color,
I'm afraid it's been a few thousand years.
Xiao Ge's blood can remove those bugs.
I think she's eaten that thousand-year-old Qilin knot.
It's so deep.
No wonder that woman just now
was determined to grab that thing.
Wu Xie is fine now.
But Cheng Cheng is still in danger.
We should find a way to get out of here quickly.
It's not easy to get out of here.
If we want to go back from the original route,
I'm afraid it's not possible.
Look at these cliff entrances.
They're all connected to the underground maze.
It's not easy to get out of there.
The only way to get out now
is to climb out of this tree.
Look.
The top of this tree should be very close to the ground.
When we get there, we'll just make a hole and we can get out.
And these ten-mantra trees are connected to the top of the cave.
It's just a natural ladder.
I'm fine.
But Pan Zi is injured. He has to climb out of the tree.
I can do it. I can climb.
What about An Ning?
Wu Xie, you're still thinking about that woman?
Let me tell you. You didn't know when you were running over.
That woman was pointing at Pan Zi's head with a gun.
She insisted on changing the Qilin knot.
I think An Ning must have her own reasons.
Forget it. She didn't really want to kill me.
Who said I was a fool?
You two have guns in your heads.
She just wanted to scare us to save her friend.
Okay, okay.
Fatty, I really didn't expect
that you care about my little life.
Because I love you.
Okay, okay.
After all, An Ning has saved Wu Xie.
If she really wants to kill Wu Xie, she won't show mercy.
Yes, yes. You're right.
Fatty.
Why are you all looking at me?
Don't look at me. I'm not helping.
Help, help, help.
An Ning,
go up with us.
Do you really think you can get out alive?
Before I came down,
I was already prepared.
You should plan for yourself.
No.
You have to go up with us.
Because Haishao and Cheng Cheng Cheng are still in your hands.
Miss An Ning,
we saw some mercenaries on our way here.
They should be your people.
Because they have some equipment that we can use,
so we took them down.
I think you're their leader. You should be responsible for them.
Go and take a look.
How is it going, Haishao?
Who told you to chat?
I'm telling you.
If you want to repair the equipment again, I'll throw you all here.
I have plenty of time for you to chat.
You have to give me time to repair it.
I'm working on it.
How much longer?
How would we know?
Big Brother, let me tell you the truth.
We haven't eaten for a long time.
Our brains are slow and need energy.
You can let us do our work,
but you have to give us some snacks.
Drink some water.
How can I get up there?
Who's that?
You already drank water?
You have to show up at a time like this.
You can't just sleep with us again.
These are all good things.
It's a pity.
Even if the equipment is still good,
if you don't have any experience, you can only come here to die.
These are all their guns.
How are they?
None of them are alive.
How did they die?
Miss An Ning, don't ask anymore.
They are all loyal.
Don't be too sad.
Maybe some of them have already escaped.
If you go up there again, don't come to the tomb again.
We are not here to steal cultural relics.
Then what are you here for?
We have other people.
Can we not brag?
You are such a big group of people. You are wearing all the weapons and came to this tomb.
You still say that you are not here to steal the tomb.
Can't you say that you are here to play with me and come to the tomb?
Fatty, don't brag anymore.
This is A1K971.
A1K971 is 74 points heavier than A1K.
It has increased by 15% to 20%.
Everyone's
Hey, don't move.
Third Uncle, what's going on?
So the real coffin is here.
Good guy.
Such a big coffin must be very valuable.
Valuable, valuable.
How come you have so much money in your head?
Can you move such a big one out?
Also, have you forgotten our purpose this time?
Protect the treasure.
Yes, yes, yes.
How many times have I told you?
This thing is called a coffin, not a coffin.
Don't always lose face.
A coffin, a coffin.
I was wondering,
why did they come up with another one?
The seven-star coffin and that one,
how many of them are there?
Which one is real?
The old maid, Lu Shang Wang,
is really a thief.
This tomb is actually in the tree.
How was this machine designed?
Little Third Uncle,
let's not look at this machine first.
Is it really Lu Shang Wang?
Whether he is Lu Shang Wang or not,
we have guns and cannons now.
Even if Lu Shang Wang climbs up,
we can just kill him.
Wu Xie, what is written on it?
I don't understand either.
But I can confirm
that the owner of this coffin
is the Lu Shang Wang we are looking for.
The record of his death
is the same as what we know.
This Lu Shang Wang died at the age of 40.
No child, no daughter.
This hole
doesn't look like it was cracked by itself.
It looks like these chains pulled it out.
Then,
who can tell me
what this is?
This is a piece of paper.
This is not right. This is very strange.
Other people's coffins or coffin
are all targeted from the outside
and not allowed to be opened.
But this is too strange.
Look at the mechanism on the stage.
They directly sent this coffin out.
It looks like the owner of this tomb
deliberately asked the successor
to open this coffin.
These chains are tied so tightly.
It doesn't look like it's used to fix it.
It looks like they didn't want the things inside to come out
so they tied it up.
Look here.
There are words here too.
Little Third Master, what does this say?
This should be a flag.
The record on this is a certain time.
But I don't know what this day is for.
Could it be the time to open the coffin?
Don't talk nonsense.
How could anyone write the time to open the coffin on the coffin?
Did you hear that? What's going on?
Could it be that there's something alive inside?
You're so big. Stop scaring us.
How could it be?
The coffin is so tightly sealed.
There's no air at all.
Even if there's really someone inside, it's been a thousand years.
It's hard to live.
Why don't we just open it?
No, Third Uncle.
Man You Ping said before that we can't touch anything inside.
Not to mention that this is a coffin.
The most important thing now is to hurry up and go up.
Cheng Cheng Cheng and Hai Zhao are still in danger.
Wu Xie, just because of this,
we should open it and take a look.
Actually, I just said to go up. That was just my guess.
If it's different from what I thought,
when we're in trouble, I'm afraid that even Third Uncle can't protect you.
Think about it. There are so many mechanisms here.
What?
This design,
maybe when we open this coffin,
there will be a way and clue to get out of it.
But Third Uncle...
Wu Xie,
I think what you said is right.
You think that we should hurry up and go out.
But if you think like that,
what if we open this thing,
and find the clue to get out of here?
You think that climbing trees isn't a simple thing, right?
Plus,
don't we still have a mall here?
Brother, can you stop looking at us while we eat?
This will affect my appetite.
Chu Bei Liang didn't eat for nothing.
If we can't get the equipment ready after we eat,
you two should know very well
what kind of consequences will come.
You eat, Uncle Wu.
Now we have reached the first floor.
There are still a few floors left.
We must open one or two more floors to see clearly.
Come, count the numbers.
One, two, three.
Why is it so heavy?
Come.
You...
Is it that heavy?
So many people can't even push it.
Come, come, come. Come to the side.
Do you have to force me to do it?
Move aside.
Okay?
Can you do it?
If you can't, don't force yourself.
Let's go!
Fatty is indeed amazing.
You can open the wall and push the coffin.
Shao Ye Zi.
Good job.
What is the price of this tomb of King of Lushan?
The common tomb of King of Zhuhe
is the third floor of the second floor.
If this tree is the first floor now,
we are now at the second floor of the second floor.
So, the bottom floor is the most valuable.
No, the most valuable.
Isn't it?
This jade is too big.
You rarely see it, right?
This jade is the Xinjiang Manas jade.
What is carved on it is the shadow of the sky and the earth.
A jade this big must be complete
to have its value.
Fatty, take it down.
We don't have much time left.
Have you decided what to do?
The vanguard army hasn't been informed.
We can't wait any longer.
There will be villagers passing by in the dark.
We can't stay here for long.
You should think about the evacuation.
Stop talking.
I've decided.
The one that's drawn on this
should be the scene when the official came in.
Then, if it's lying here,
it must be King of Lushan himself.
If you want to know if it's King of Lushan,
there's only one way.
Open it and take a look.
Pan Zi,
this is the last coffin.
Let's be more cautious.
There's a lot of people here.
The coffin is here.
Let's be more cautious.
Be more reserved.
It seems like there's a breathing sound.
Can you stop joking?
That person is your Third Uncle, right?
You're used to scaring me, right?
There's a breathing sound in here.
You think I'm a minor, right?
You're so funny.
You listen to it.
Be careful.
You said there's one, so there is.
There's no other way.
Are we going to drive the coffin back?
Wu Xie,
don't hesitate.
Remember to shoot.
Pan Zi.
Wait.
Put it down.
Do you guys know
what a man's doing?
It's like a stick.
We're going to open
the coffin of King of Lushan.
It's been thousands of years.
You're eating a can of shark fin.
You're going to jump?
You're kidding.
Do as you're told.
I'll do as I'm told.
Move aside.
Move.
Don't think about it.
He's carrying a baby.
Don't destroy it.
I thought it was a seed again.
It may be a baby.
It's just baby.
Can someone put a can of shark fin in it?
We're getting high again.
We don't really have anything else to do.
Useless thing.
I'm a poor guy.
You brothers,
should all be careful.
We won't kill the giant stone tortoise with you.
Why don't you go along with him?
You are so rude.
Are you здесь for recuer
What is the purpose?
It's to put these things on.
Maybe it can help us get back our old self.
You really want this?
Old man, do you know how to take this thing off?
I heard that this thing can't be taken off from outside.
Do we have to take it out?
You're here again?
I told you that you guys don't have any skills.
You can't just carry it or take it off.
Can you think of a way to take it off?
I'm just saying, of course we have to carry it off.
How do we take it off? You take it off from the top.
Aomenshin Peking Entertainment City 772772, Kong.
The most exciting PG game on the line.
The best of the best.
The queen of the prize pool.
The golden city of the treasure hunt.
The golden cat.
The captain of the prize pool.
The high rate of compensation.
The high rate of reward.
Aomenshin Peking Entertainment City 772772, Kong.
What if we sneak over?
Be careful.
Don't move.
What is it, Aomenshin?
She's breathing.
Aomenshin Peking Entertainment City 772772, Kong.
The best of the best.
The high rate of reward.
And the high rate of reward
of the high rate
I'm out of mine
need
Is there any way
yeah
Yeah
it
education
I'll keep carrying on
We had to be strong
Still a long, long way to run
Until I see the sun
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's solve the mystery
And live a dream
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's write our story
Let's make our fantasy
Come true
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's solve the mystery
And live a dream
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's write our story
Let's make our fantasy
Come true