I'm not a good dancer.
The End
I think this little brother
is a real person.
I'll tell you the truth.
In the Qingtong Guwan Realm,
I'm also famous.
If it weren't for the money,
I wouldn't have bought this baby.
You are mixed in the Guwan Realm.
We will meet often in the future.
Please take good care of me.
No, no.
Learn from each other.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's it.
OK.
Please wait.
Take care.
OK, OK, OK.
I don't believe it.
You are fooling me.
I spent 300,000 to buy it.
If you hit me,
you have to pay me.
Fatty, you have a lot of money today.
Do you know what this is?
Isn't this a broken cup?
What broken cup?
I tell you.
This thing is called a foot.
It's a name of a wine in the Shang Dynasty.
The market value is one million.
Really?
One million.
If you don't believe it,
ask an expert.
I'm going to ask an expert.
Let's go eat roast duck.
When did you come to Beijing?
Why don't you say hello in advance?
I'll pick you up.
You are so ungrateful.
You came by yourself.
Fatty, long time no see.
Long time no see.
This is Chen Chengcheng.
He went to the Lujuan Palace with us before.
But he didn't scare us.
This one, this one, this one.
When you fainted,
you gave me a picture in the village.
I was a little impatient.
I didn't have time to say hello.
Hello, Fatty.
Just call me Fatty.
Hello, Chen Chen.
Chen Chengcheng.
Chengcheng.
By the way,
I actually came here this time.
There's something I want you to help me with.
What is it?
I want to see the old lady of the Huo family.
You mean the third lady of the Huo family
who is known as the old lady of the Huo family?
That kind.
Wu Xie,
you're too naive.
Don't say it's you.
Even if it's the son of the old lady,
you have to see him in a good mood.
Why are you like Third Uncle?
You can't say no
even if you haven't tried it yet.
I didn't say no.
You talk to the Beijing people about rules.
As for you,
as for me,
when do you think I'll follow the rules?
But you tell me first.
Why are you looking for him?
When he's online,
I'll tell you.
Delicious.
Thank you, Fatty.
Eat more.
Don't tell Fatty about it.
Don't worry.
It's okay to have him.
Wu Xie,
I
hired an expert
to help me verify it.
Guess what?
It's exactly like what you said.
I can't see
how you're so good
at this antique verification.
Fatty, I'm making a big fortune this time.
Eat whatever you want.
It's just luck.
Come on, let's eat.
The most exciting PG game
on the line of
Aomei New Beijing Entertainment City 772772.
Cheers.
No wonder the
I'm not going to open for three years.
Open for three years.
Yeah.
Fatty made so much money this time.
I guess he can rest at home for three years.
By the way,
how's your help?
Don't worry.
It's done.
So fast.
Of course.
You're not going to be late.
Beijing 49 City.
I'm the number one in the world.
Right?
But I
have to hear your reason first
before I decide whether to do it or not.
Do you remember the gold and silk
we took out from the tomb of King Lushan?
Of course.
Did you donate it or not?
That's fake.
It was transferred by Brother Jia.
What?
Uncle San has already checked it.
The purity is too high.
The craftsmanship when it was taken
is not good.
It's not good at all.
Damn it.
The girl's
back is a shadow.
Don't let Fatty Wang
take her.
If he takes her, he has to spend her.
But I also found
another thing.
Only Old Huo
knows the origin of this thing.
No wonder.
I said, why are you looking for her?
Ning.
Huo is going to a auction.
How about this?
Let's get in there
and have a draw.
We can ask her face to face.
She won't be kicked out.
That depends on
your ability to fool the young master.
I'm going.
It's been a long time
since I saw Mr. Zhang.
I'm going to call him.
Mr. Zhang, you're here.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Brother.
Let's go.
Please come in.
Hey, do you think that fat guy is reliable?
Why hasn't he come yet?
You two don't worry about the fat guy first.
I spent so much time today, I changed my style on purpose.
Do you think I'm extra beautiful today?
Not bad.
I think you two are very handsome today.
The people who don't know really think you are some big young master.
Big young master?
Have you seen any big young master who came by taxi and sat on the side of the road alone?
So pitiful.
Fat guy, are you embarrassed to look in the mirror?
I'm sorry.
Come on, come on.
Brother Fat.
Have you waited for a long time?
Whose clothes are you borrowing? It's quite suitable.
Mine.
I was in the village a while ago.
It's too hard. I'm a little bit tired.
What are you laughing at?
I tell you, I wear a dress today.
That old lady asked me to go in. Do you believe it?
Yes.
Okay, give me the ID.
Okay.
What?
Where can I get you this ID card?
I can find out this place.
Do you know?
Brother Fat, if I don't have an ID card, I can't go in at all.
What should I do?
Don't bother me.
I don't know how I came last night.
You are too unreliable.
Where did you get this thing?
I spent some time last night.
Do it yourself.
Han Shao, I never found you so reliable.
I'm so impressed.
You look good today.
Don't say that.
This useless thing is useful sometimes.
What?
He is a high-tech talent.
Okay, let's go in if we have a card.
Go.
Okay, next.
Please.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Okay, let me do it.
Brother Fat, you are so good.
The auction is about to start.
Hurry up.
What are they shooting?
What else can they shoot?
This is the highest place in Beijing.
Old Huo must come to shoot the treasure.
We have to seize the opportunity.
Let's go.
How is it?
Is it beautiful?
It's so high.
Let me tell you.
Comparing to here,
Panjiayuan and Liulishan are all called land stalls.
So you are a stall owner.
Wu Xie, this girl,
I tell you,
I don't think she is a foreigner.
I would have already paid you.
Wu Xie.
Didn't you say that Panjiayuan is a stall owner?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
The business of the stall is held in three floors of this hotel.
This used to be a place where eunuchs and foreigners often traded.
The trading style here is the style of Chinese and Western.
If so,
the food here should be very delicious.
Why do you think of food?
I'm hungry.
Please come in.
How?
Remember,
you should mix with Panjiayuan.
He will bring you all these good dishes.
Please come in.
This is the young master of Changsha, Wu's family.
You should find a better place later.
Are you going to sit in the seat or the hall?
Look at our dressing.
It's really fate.
This is the person who sold the wedding dress yesterday.
It's really a family business.
Brother.
Why are you so free to come here?
Wait.
Mr. Chen, have we met before?
Brother, you are here too.
What a coincidence.
You two...
You two know each other?
No.
Listen to me.
How can you not know each other?
Did you forget that we met at my store yesterday?
We met yesterday.
Today we are here together.
Is this the hotel?
We have a saying in Beijing.
It's not true.
We are brothers in the four seas.
He is my friend.
You are also my friend.
Who is your friend?
Listen to me.
Give me back the wedding dress.
I won't sell it.
No.
Brother, don't be angry.
Why are you so angry?
You said that you would be angry later.
Brother, someone is arguing here.
Please come and have a look.
I didn't force you to sell your wedding dress.
I will say it again.
Give me back the wedding dress.
Sir, let's not be angry.
Let's talk slowly.
Don't be anxious.
She is a good woman.
Let's not offend her.
It's not up to her.
I ask you.
Will you return it?
Listen to me.
Don't be angry.
I can't return that thing.
I sold it yesterday.
But if you really think you are selling it for nothing,
you give me a card.
I earned a lot of money.
I will return half of it to you.
Everyone is doing business.
You can't see me lose money, right?
You think you are selling flowers.
I don't mean that.
How can you sell flowers?
You wear a suit and tie a tie, right?
No, no, no.
Not necessary.
Do you believe it?
You leave this hotel at night.
I am capable of making you unable to get mixed up in Beijing.
Mr. Li, can you talk to me?
Can you solve the problem like this?
You are not a guest.
I...
How can you talk?
I am sorry.
No loud noise here.
Manager Ma, right?
Actually, we just have a misunderstanding.
We are friends.
Who is your friend?
Give me back the thing.
Guys, let's talk somewhere else.
The card was useful when I entered the door.
Why are you so stupid?
Four cards are useless.
How do I know it will be wrong?
Are you stupid?
Really.
Four.
What's going on?
Your behavior is illegal.
Now there are two ways in front of you.
Either call the police now.
Let the police take you away.
Or leave quickly.
And never enter Xin Yue Hotel again.
Don't be so serious.
Wait.
Do you know who this is?
This is the young master of Changsha Wu family.
Today, I have an important thing to see Mrs. Huo.
Just you guys.
You are disturbing our big thing.
Manager Li, right?
Can you take the responsibility?
We don't care who it is.
We just follow the rules.
Okay.
Since it's like this,
we can only ask Mrs. Huo to explain it in person.
Right?
Let's ask Mrs. Huo.
Manager.
The guest of the Huo family upstairs wants to invite them up.
What's the matter?
Go.
Okay.
This...
These are the guests of the Huo family.
Please give them a chance.
This is a misunderstanding.
Dear guests.
Please come in.
The Huo family?
You are lucky.
Someone is going to support you today.
But don't let me see you again.
I said it was a misunderstanding.
Yes.
Go back to your work.
Go.
Okay.
Let's go.
Fatty.
We don't have to be kicked out.
What's going on?
Fatty has me in Beijing.
Don't be so stubborn.
They won't recognize the wrong person.
It doesn't matter.
We can't go in.
Let's go.
How is it?
Luckily no one came.
Fatty.
Is this the auction house?
It used to be a theater.
They used to perform opera.
But now it's an auction house.
They do perform opera here.
I heard that in Beijing,
people like to listen to traditional music.
That's right.
People in Beijing like this.
You know what?
In Beijing,
it's the old society.
Only Prince and Princess can come in.
But now,
it's a rich market.
Fatty.
Is this the auction house?
It's a character.
Ordinary people can't go in.
That way.
This way, please.
Please.
It's beautiful again.
Fatty.
Hurry up and order something to eat.
I'm starving.
How can you eat so much?
Why do you order?
I'm hungry.
Stop it.
How can you do this?
A good place like this
is so high-class.
If you don't order something,
you'll be sorry for your stomach.
Just let him eat.
That's right.
You're right.
Come on, waitress.
Come on.
Give her the menu.
Order whatever you want.
Thank you, Fatty.
That's great.
Just pay for it yourself.
Order.
Oh my god.
This is for people to eat.
Look.
A plate of bean sprouts.
12,000 yuan.
Really?
Really.
That's called the
It's too bad.
What do you want to eat when he asks me to come?
We're here
mainly to see the old lady.
Don't you want
these kind of things on the menu?
Right.
I'll have a pot of tea.
All right, please wait a moment.
Fatty,
how much is a pot of tea?
1,800 yuan.
It's worth 10% of the cost.
Why are you so mean?
I'm just saying.
It's worth 10% of the cost.
Why are you so mean?
Why don't you order something cheaper?
Keep your voice down.
This is the cheapest.
Here's your tea.
Come on.
I'll do it myself.
Thank you.
100 packs.
It's gone.
Can you pack this?
Why pack it?
It's such an expensive tea.
I'm taking it back to make tea leaves.
I'm so embarrassed.
What's a tea leaf egg?
Brother Sun, you're here.
Fatty, who is he?
Liuli Sun.
Liuli Sun?
Who is Liuli Sun?
You've never been to Beijing City.
Ya is originally a stinky island.
Liuli Zhu.
I don't know what happened later.
It's a big deal.
There are all the treasures in the house.
Ordinary things are not worth looking at.
Only the top-class things are likely to appear.
These years, Ya is a good example of Beijing City.
Where he appears, it means there are high goods.
But it's been years since Ya came out.
Why are you here today?
Didn't you say he was a wind vane?
Maybe there must be something special about this auction.
Where are you going?
I guess there must be a good show today.
Maybe it's a big show.
I'll go get some auction manuals.
See what it is today.
Master Wu, Madam Huo asked you to come upstairs.
You mean Madam Huo?
Miss, you didn't make a mistake, right?
Fatty, didn't you say you didn't find Madam Huo?
I really didn't get the chance to go.
Please.
Fatty, does Madam Huo know we're looking for her?
The Huo family is not a joke.
Maybe she has some connections with your grandfather.
It's a good chance to meet you.
See if you look like your grandfather.
Come to the Sun Siye.
Sun Siye?
Really have culture.
You're so great.
Anyway, thank you for taking care of Madam Huo.
Let's go.
We can't be in the wrong place.
Please.
The golden stone is like a string.
The water is like a hairpin.
The red thread is like a silk.
The green leaves are fragrant.
This is a beautiful painting by Liu Xiaochuo.
Please come in.
You're eating money.
Is Madam Huo here?
It's none of your business.
Don't look down.
Let me tell you.
The New Moon Hotel has not been so lively these two years.
Eat slowly.
Today, it's rare to follow the old lady of the Huo family.
Let's have a look.
Isn't it?
Excuse me.
Here.
Don't look at me.
I'm your partner.
Let's go.
Madam, I'll be there in a minute.
Hello, Aunt Huo. I'm Wu Xie.
I didn't disturb you to rest, right?
You're Puppy Wu?
You really look like that old dog.
It's hard to believe.
So that dog
really has no trace of it.
Uncle, you must be joking.
It's not that I'm joking.
But you're joking.
It's more like it when you laugh.
It doesn't seem like a good thing.
What are the people next to you doing?
They're here with me.
Get out.
You're not staying in Hangzhou.
Why are you going to Beijing?
Granny, I came here this time
to ask you a favor.
Let's talk after I finish eating.
It's so stuffy in here.
This old man from the bed room
is really strong.
He's really a member of the Huo family.
In his eyes,
there's a unique beauty of Eastern women.
Enough.
What are you two fighting about?
Have you seen the world?
What's wrong with you?
Let's go.
I'll take you to another place.
There's a lot of fun here.
You're awesome.
What are you doing?
You asked me to stay in the room.
I didn't.
What are we going to do, Mr. Fatty?
What can we do?
What if Wu Xie is in there?
It's okay.
I'm here.
Sir.
Your jade hairpin fell.
Where's it?
It's not there.
I can't find it.
I'm looking for it.
I'll find it.
I'll bring it for you.
Okay.
Your jade hairpin fell off.
The jade hairpin and the lady's
face-saving appearance
are a perfect match.
Without a step earlier,
without a step later,
the lady happened to pick it up.
It must be a destiny.
I gave this jade hairpin to the lady.
I wonder if the lady can enjoy it
and go to the room to have a rest.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm from a distant place.
I just came back from Germany.
There's something wrong with it.
It's not healed yet.
Sorry for disturbing you.
You're busy.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
I...
I don't know if he's from the second floor.
What's wrong with the second floor?
I told you you didn't remember.
Those who can go to the second floor
are all handsome.
Why are you looking for him?
That's right.
Everyone in Germany is so naughty.
I said are you crazy?
You're so naughty in Germany.
Are you a commoner?
What's wrong with this list?
Did you steal it from the
Panjiayuan's stall?
I didn't say you're a commoner.
You're a secret.
I don't want it.
You're a fat girl.
Can you write a book?
You're a bad girl.
Even the square dance
of my aunt can be seen as fake.
It's embarrassing to be a fat girl.
It means I'm innocent and kind.
I'm not scheming.
Miss.
By the way, Dacheng.
I just saw a few people
with good looks.
Where did they come from?
Madam asked them to come.
Grandma asked them to come.
They came with
the young master of the Wu family.
Young master of the Wu family?
Madam asked you to go in.
I see.
By the way, he's almost here.
You go and pick him up.
I'll wait for him here.
Yes.
Life will always
drop small hopes.
I'm so convinced.
Don't say that.
You have a good eye.
That girl is good-looking.
What are you talking about?
I mean,
Wu Xie is in a bad situation now.
The Huo family is hard to deal with.
That's right.
It's too much to drive us out.
They must think we have no origin.
You don't even look at the Huo family.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
This one.
If you have the ability, say it in person.
Don't say anything behind my back.
What do I say?
It's none of your business.
Brother Pan, forget it. Let's go.
Forget what?
I'm not in a good mood.
The Huo family is so generous.
They are so generous.
They even make a fool of us.
They are really teasing you.
Please step aside.
You want me to step aside?
Our madam is talking for you.
You didn't get kicked out.
Why are you still annoying?
I'm wondering.
Do you think I'm begging you for help?
Step aside.
Han Shang.
Han Shang, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Fatty is too fat.
He blocked my vision.
You scared me.
Wake up.
Han Shang.
Someone, come here.
Come and give us a salute.
What's going on?
It's a sunny day.
Han Shang.
The Huo family is so rude.
They hit people as they want.
Someone blocked my vision.
Don't make noise here.
Keep pretending.
Even if the Huo family is still respectful,
it's not good for them
if things get worse.
Ladies, you're here at the right time.
You give us a salute.
I...
Han Shang.
He grew up in Germany.
I saw him grow up
from such a height.
He's been good at studying since he was a kid.
He's the top three in Germany.
But it's the first time
he's come to study with the Wu family.
You said the Huo family is rude.
They hit people as they want.
Right.
Look at his wound.
If he can't tell you,
he'll be a dead man.
Listen,
I didn't hit him.
Han Shang.
He hit him.
Sir,
we should be polite.
We'll do it.
Just monitor it.
Monitoring is good.
Great.
Come on, lady.
Get up slowly.
You also stand up.
You're just...
Han Shang.
You...
Why are you being polite?
Listen,
everyone is dizzy.
I'm going to the German cinema
to comfort you.
Really.
Han Shang.
Madam.
I'm here to ask you
if you want to
talk about the snake and the copper fish.
Snake and copper fish?
You've come here for nothing.
How is that possible?
Only you know about it
in the Old Nine Gates.
Who still remembers
such a dirty thing?
Nonsense.
You're a doctor now.
You're a doctor.
How can you not remember?
I'm a little more mature
than that old dog.
You're so smooth-tongued.
You're exactly like that old dog.
How can you be so good?
You've inherited
all the bad things
from me.
Is it because your grandma
asked you to meet me?
See how old I am.
Madam, you've misunderstood.
I just want to ask
about the snake and the copper fish.
To be honest,
I haven't seen my grandma for a long time.
Since my grandpa passed away,
she's been in the old house
and never left the house.
That's because she's bad-sighted
and married a short-lived ghost.
How can you think of
asking me about this?
That old dog
knows much better than me.
Didn't he write it
on his old notebook?
The notebook has been destroyed.
How about
I come to trouble you?
You don't dare
or you don't want to?
I don't want to
trouble you.
Come on.
How do you know this thing?
It's with me.
Where did you steal it?
Madam, I didn't steal it.
There's a group of street vendors
who are very interested in this.
I'm afraid that the cultural relics
will be stolen by the outsiders.
So I want to find out
what the snake-tailed tuna
is for.
The Daomu family
has two generations of
dogs who protect cultural relics.
I don't know if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
If I tell the old dog,
will he get angry
and climb out of the tomb?
Okay, I can promise you.
But you can't ask me.
You have to ask your grandma.
Grandma, let's not joke around.
This thing
doesn't have to
disturb my grandma and her family.
Joke?
I don't ask about it.
I, Huo Xian Gu, do business.
I never joke around.
Your grandma and I are childhood friends.
It's been decades.
She never came to see me.
I'm in Hangzhou.
I asked her to come see me.
Is it a joke?
It's settled.
Go back and discuss with your grandma.
If your grandma doesn't want to see me,
you don't have to come to see me.
Song Ke.
You're being unreasonable.
Look.
That's right.
You're too much.
Han Shang.
Is she...
How can you do this?
Han Shang, wake up.
You're too much.
What's wrong with you?
Han Shang.
Are you okay?
Wu Xie.
They pushed Han Shang.
Look.
She's like this now.
My Peng Gu.
Young Master Wu.
You finally love me.
You give a fair review.
These two guys
are from the Huo family.
They're unreasonable.
They want to drive us out.
They hit us.
Look at the kind of people
they hit.
You're too much.
My tailbone.
They hit people in public.
They're too arrogant.
That's right.
Wu Xie.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Young Master Wu is just like this.
Are you serious?
You...
Come on.
Don't touch me.
Stop.
Who are you?
You're Wu Xie, right?
Yes.
I am.
You are...
Yuchen.
Grandma has been waiting for you for a long time.
Why don't you go up?
It's so hot.
Cheng.
I didn't ask you to pick up so many people.
You're the guest who just left, right?
I'm very interested in your conversation.
Can you tell me?
It's just about some history.
And you are...
Xiu Xiu.
He is Wu Xie.
You are indeed the young master of the Wu family.
Why do you all seem to know me?
I don't know you.
I'm Huo Xiu Xiu.
Since Wu Xie is a friend of Grandma's,
let's let the bodyguards leave.
You're wearing a pink shirt.
You're not afraid of finding your old ass.
He didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
Don't take it to heart.
If there's nothing else,
do you want to come and sit down?
Young master of the Xie family.
Could it be that Xie family?
Which Xie family?
Is he famous?
The original Xie family
is also a member of the Nine Gates.
In the ancient world of Beijing,
there is also a number of the Nine Gates.
I heard that the Xie family is in a marriage with the Huo family.
Look at the way the young lady of the Huo family
posted just now.
You all saw it.
This pink shirt
should be her fiance.
Let's go.
I have something to say
to Old Madam Huo.
This way, please.
Hello, Boss Zhang, Madam Zhang.
Granny.
I'm here to see you.
Sit.
Didn't I make it very clear to you before?
If your granny didn't come,
you wouldn't have to see me.
I know a little about
the thing you took.
But now you're old,
you can't remember it clearly.
She said I can't leave.
It's not easy to see this old witch
when you're gone.
What should I do?
Just play with her.
Just forget about her.
What's going on?
Why is everyone like a ghost?
How would I know?
Granny.
This matter is really important to me.
If you don't tell me,
we will kneel in front of this restaurant.
Who told you to sit down?
Stand up.
Cheng.
Take these rascals away.
Aomum Xin Peking Entertainment City
com.
The most exciting PG game on the line.
The mahjong is over.
The mahjong is over 2.
The prize-winning queen
will find the treasure of the Golden City.
The
super high rate of compensation
will get a lot of rewards.
There are many opportunities to get revenge.
Hurry up and join.
Aomum Xin Peking Entertainment City
com.
I've heard that
the Huo family loves to play.
Especially you, Mrs. Huo.
You said you were more popular than the Empress Dowager Siqi.
Today is a good day.
But
if you really let us get these pieces of material,
it will show that you are very careful, right?
But our Young Master Mu
is very popular.
He is very old and young.
But Fatty Wang
is a rascal since he was a child.
He has a bad temper.
If he gets angry later,
and gets hit by this place,
it will be bad for the reputation of the Huo family.
Cheng,
send the guest in.
Please.
Don't come over.
I'll call the police if you come over.
Let go.
You are also good-natured.
You are not as smart as you.
You don't want to play?
Aomum,
don't be angry about this.
Fatty Wang is also talking nonsense.
Besides,
Wu Xie is also the Young Master of the Wu family.
We don't have to
get along with our family.
Aomum,
if you don't agree,
I won't leave.
Okay.
I'm afraid of you.
Young Master Wu,
but don't ask me first.
Even if you ask,
I won't say anything.
You just sit here
until four thirty.
If you can sit,
I won't make it difficult for you.
Okay.
Open your misty eyes
Here comes another fight
There's a stormy night
Before the morning arrives
No matter where you go
I will follow you
Keep careful watch
Of your soul
Smashing through the door
Into another world
Picking up my sword
Nothing I can conquer
I'll keep carrying on
We have to fight
We have to be strong
Still a long long way to go
Until I see the sun
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's solve the mystery
And never dream
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's write our story
Let's make our fantasy
Come true
We have to rock
On our own
Making our fantasy
Come true
On our own
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's write our story
Let's make our fantasy come true
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's solve the mystery
And live a dream
I see the light
I hear the triumph
Let's write our story
Let's make our fantasy come true
Come true