♫ Rumors, some of them are not true ♫
♫ I don't know if you listened to what they are saying ♫
♫ How is this flirtatious? I can't translate it ♫
♫ If you want to know, you have to give it a try ♫
♫ So please please don’t judge me ♫
♫ Just don't believe anyone that I'm bad ♫
♫ Like my manners, it's called being nice. I meant no harm ♫
♫ Be careful or you'll miss the good stuff ♫
♫ Who said that I'm so hot? ♫
♫ Sorry, if my hair looks too hot ♫
♫ What, a womanizer? It's not true!
(Don't believe it, don't believe what he says) ♫
♫ Who said I was a playboy? I just enjoy being with many girls ♫
♫ Do you want to try me for a bit?
Don't you want to know what the real me is like? ♫
♫ What you've heard seems to be negative.
If you try me, you'll be hooked ♫
♫ Don't just believe them, just look into my eyes.
I want you to try to open your mind ♫
[My Dear Donovan]
You're meeting up with her for dinner?
It's about work.
I'm your manager. I should have known about it.
Otherwise, why would you even need me here?
I've also prepared something for you.
My surprise gift for you.
I know what you want from me.
I can't sleep with you in exchange for the job.
But if you think you can get me drunk, you're wrong.
I'm a hard drinker.
If you're a hard drinker, show me.
[Oasis Minimart]
I'm sorry, Miss Pam.
Mickey is not here.
I have to take care of the store, so I can't take you to eat something delicious.
I'll cook something yummy for you, then.
You don't have to, Mr. Aood.
I can just eat those shumai, steamed buns, and sausages.
Anyway,
can you tell me already how you calmed Grandpa down?
Give me 200 THB, and I'll tell you.
Fine. I won't listen then.
Come on. I'm just kidding.
At first, he was angry knowing that you did that job,
but when I said this one sentence to him, everything just ended there.
What was that sentence?
"Miss Pam is adorable."
As expected.
I shouldn't have waited to listen to you.
I'm just kidding.
I told him that you just replaced someone else for that job at that time.
I also said, "Ever since I have started renting Grandpa's house
and have known Miss Pam for many years,
I have never seen her do anything inappropriate."
"Please trust her. Or else, it could affect your heart condition."
And he believed you?
Of course.
I often feel that I have been bothering Mr. Aood since he has helped me all this time.
By the way, does he have to shoot in a swimsuit often?
Oh, nope.
He usually wears regular clothes like we do.
Even if he wears something like that, I'm not interested at all.
I'm serious.
But if it were me, I would look at him.
Mr. Aood!
I'm just kidding.
Miss Pam, please don't stress yourself out because of Grandpa.
Just focus on doing your job. I'll handle that for you.
He is such a nice guy to me.
Here you are.
It looks so yummy.
Not only does it look yummy,
but it also tastes incredible.
You will go like 'Whoa!' after eating it.
- Because it's hot?
- Because you forgot to blow it first.
Since you're onto my joke like this,
what else can I do?
I can't go that way.
- What about this way?
- Hey!
Enough, Mr. Aood. How wicked.
- I'll eat now.
- Please enjoy.
Eat a lot. You can eat a lot more, Miss Pam.
It's super yummy.
Right? It comes with cheese, too.
Miss Pam?
Is it so yummy that you have gone absent-minded?
- Miss Pam!
- What? What is it?
Oh, yes. It's really yummy.
If it's yummy, then why are you making 'that' face?
Huh?
That Pam's cutie face.
But I think you should stop that.
You're funny though.
I'm with him now, but I'm thinking of another guy.
This is not good at all.
Why am I thinking of him?
I guess he must be enjoying dinner now.
Miss Pam.
It's bleeding.
Do you need some ice? I'll get it for you.
It's all right.
It should stop bleeding soon.
Is something wrong? It looks like you're zoning out.
I'm all right.
Do you want to eat anything else? I'll make it for you.
- What about some buns?
- I'm good, Mr. Aood.
I can eat this. It's really fine with me.
Please eat a lot.
Sure.
What is the meaning of your name?
It's an Irish word, which means darkness.
Wow.
Darkness?
That suits me.
Darkness and stars make a perfect combination.
But if I have to pick a name for you,
I'll name you Mr. Google.
Google?
Why?
It's because you have every answer I'm looking for.
Well then, let me ask... something on Google.
What's... your... favorite... food?
No answer?
I'll change my question then.
Which... position... do you like?
Thank you so much for buying me dinner and ice cream.
It's all right, Miss Pam. It's not a big deal.
But to be honest, I want to treat you to every meal every day.
Dude, look at her.
She's carrying heavy stuff. I should go help her.
Hi, there.
- Can I help you?
- Let go!
Help! Let go!
Help!
Miss Pam?
Are you all right?
It's all right, Miss Pam. I'm already here.
Let's go home.
Here you are.
What?
You thought I was trying to make you drunk?
I'm not that stupid.
He keeps worrying that she's trying to make him drunk.
You don't believe me? Let me show you.
But he doesn't know there's something else that can also make him drunk.
This drug makes those who inhale it feel euphoric,
- What's wrong?
- ...and drunk.
Have you got a temperature?
And arouses a strong sexual desire.
That's right. I said "Inhale," indeed.
Do you feel hot?
Because this woman is cleverer than we could expect.
Play in the water with me.
This could be the first time he has tried to take control of his body,
giving it an order, but it's not going as expected.
Or shouldn't he hold it back?
Would it be easier for him to just let it go on?
But no matter what, he still owns a strong survival instinct.
No!
You crazy!
Where are you going?
Come back here.
I'm telling you to come back here!
Come!
Where are you going?
I got this whole place closed.
[My Dear Donovan]
Mr. Aood.
Yes?
I'm all right now.
You thought about what happened that day. Right?
The day I wasn't able to help you in time.
I'm so sorry. I really feel bad about it.
It's all right, Mr. Aood.
Let bygones be bygones.
But actually, you should have been the one holding my hand...
because I can't see anything.
Are you going to say that love blinds people?
Come on.
You stole my joke.
What else can I say?
Is something wrong today? You look unwell.
Apart from knowing me well, he can also read my mind.
He's right. I miss Donovan because I know where he went,
and that makes me quite agitated.
Give me a second.
Sure.
Why is he calling?
Hello?
Hey.
Help.
Help me.
What's wrong?
I almost can't bear it anymore.
Wait.
What's going on?
If it wasn't such a critical situation,
a person like him wouldn't ask for help from others.
I feel something I can't explain.
My body feels hot.
Donovan, I'm here.
Hey, that's such a sweet voice. Are you calling to prank me?
I was worried.
Please rush here.
I really can't bear it any longer.
You're having fun discussing work with Miss Dararai, aren't you?
Why did you ask me to go there?
I have been drugged.
What?
Hey, get me out of here.
Wait. Where? Where are you now?
I'm at the hotel.
The hotel where you discussed work with Miss Da?
Yes.
I'm telling you to open the door!
Where are you? How can I get there correctly?
I'll send you the location.
Okay. Hurry here!
Mr. Aood!
Please help, Mr. Aood.
Donovan will die for sure.
Calm down first, Miss Pam. What's going on?
Donovan was drugged.
Please accompany me, Mr. Aood.
He's sending me the location.
- Let's go.
- Wait, Miss Pam. How do we go?
Why don't we drive?
You're right. The car.
We must drive.
Should we drive my car or yours?
Your car. I'll drive for you.
All right.
- Let's go.
- Wait, Miss Pam.
The car is over there.
Right.
Donovan, where are you?
Are you in this room?
You're not.
What about this one?
Do you want to play hide and seek?
You're not in here.
What about this one?
Or... this one?
I already know where you are.
Open the door for me, please.
You won't?
You're here. Right?
I see you now.
Open the door!
Open it now!
Open it!
I told you to open the door.
You won't?
Fine.
I'm here.
Where are you going?
Where?
Don't stop, Mr. Aood. Go.
- We won't make it, Miss Pam.
- We will. Hurry up. Faster.
Mr. Aood, turn right.
- Here?
- Yes. Turn right.
- Go straight.
- Straight, right?
- Which way do we go now?
- Go straight first.
- All right.
- Here.
- Turn left over there, Mr. Aood.
- Here?
We've arrived.
Yes. This is the right place.
Stop!
He's there. Follow him!
15.
May I know if you have a key card, please?
We're here to see our friend.
This floor is private. You're not allowed inside if you weren't invited.
My friend, Donovan, called us.
He said there's something very important, so we must go to see him.
We'll go together.
- You're not allowed inside without an invitation.
- Hey. Don't you have any other words to say?
I have to ask both of you to leave, please.
Come on, bro.
We can just take it easy, can't we?
Also, we are not doing anything wrong.
We're just here to see our friend, who looks like a westerner.
He is, indeed, a westerner, though. I think you know that. Right?
I really can't let you in.
Please leave.
The faster I want to go, the longer it takes.
The more I want to help, the more problems arrive.
What's all this fuss about?
- What should we do?
- Yes.
I'm coming.
- Miss Pam.
- Mr. Aood.
Let's go!
Mr. Aood, why can't I press on the floor we're going to?
I think it's a private floor. We need a key card.
Let's try this.
I'll try pressing each of them and see which floor we can access.
Then, we use a fire exit on that floor.
All right.
Hey, this one works.
[My Dear Donovan]
He's trying to calm down the burning desire inside his body
by using every defensive instinct he owns.
He's changing it into his strength to survive.
Miss Pam, why don't we call the police?
He's right. Usually, citizens like us can rely on the police. Right?
That's right. Police.
But I think they won't make it in time. It's faster to come and help him on our own.
Also, we can't be sure if they will come or not.
We've arrived.
Miss Pam, that's a fire exit.
Miss Pam, I think the sound is from over there.
Right.
Hey, what are you doing?! Stop!
Pam!
Hey?!
Hey!
Hey, are you all right?
Please get me out of here.
Mr. Aood, please help carry him.
Be careful.
- Are you all right?
- The elevator button, Miss Pam.
Okay.
Where are you guys going?!
Come take responsibility now!
Gosh. Speak of the devil.
This looks like a scene from a zombies movie.
Don't come close. I'm recording a video here.
If you step any closer, the whole world will see you like that.
It's arrived.
Don't come close.
Don't.
Open!
Mr. Aood, you're so clever.
You recorded her video with your phone.
There's no way we can get CCTV footage from here.
It was so loud, but nobody came to see what was happening.
It's obvious all of them here are her men.
- Let's hurry out of here.
- Yes.
Why did you come?
To help you.
I didn't ask for your help. I asked Pam.
Are you saying I'm nosy?
Yes.
Hey, wait. Stop.
Stop! Hey!
Mr. Aood was with me when you called and asked for help.
Mr. Aood, I don't know where the car key is.
The key?
It's here.
What's wrong with you?
Feel burning hot all over my body.
I forgot to mention that this drug's effect lasts for several hours.
Hey!
- Let's hurry up. Here you are.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Hey!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
Hey, I'm trying to help you.
I'm really sorry.
The drug makes me... horny.
Miss Pam, you'd better drive.
- I'll sit in the back.
- Yes.
Let's go, Miss Pam.
Hey, what are you doing?
What's going on, Mr. Aood?
Well, he's just taking his phone out.
I see.
[I know where you live.]
I can't go back to my room.
Miss Da texted me, saying that she knows where I live.
Where will you go then?
Just drop me off at your mom's office.
Nonsense. Look at you now. How can I leave you alone?
Let's go to my house.
Miss Pam, won't Grandpa blame you?
Mr. Aood, since he's like that now,
I think Grandpa will understand the situation.
I think he won't.
All right. Let's go to my house then.
Oh, thank you so much.
Yeah.
Let's go.
I'm thirsty. Do you have some water?
Water?
It's in the back. Please look for it, Mr. Aood.
I found it.
Here you are.
Are you guys all right? I'm sorry.
There's a big hole.
How wicked this drug is.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Mr. Aood, is everything all right?
- He touched my ear.
- Huh?
Miss Pam!
To the left!
I didn't see that.
It's all right, Miss Pam. Just continue driving.
What are you doing?
Mr. Aood, are you all right?
Yes.
I'm not hugging you.
I'm putting a seatbelt on for you.
Let's go, Miss Pam.
Yes.
Miss Pam, floor it!
Sure!
Hey! Don't!
- Miss Pam, go!
- I'm accelerating, Mr. Aood.
Hey, are you all right?
Hey. Should I just leave you here and let mosquitos bite you, huh?
Let me help.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
The drug is still active.
Hey!
Miss Pam!
Hey, pull yourself together!
What are you doing to Mr. Aood?!
Mr. Aood, help me.
What should we do?
No idea.
- Miss Pam.
- Pam, come here.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
One more time.
[My Dear Donovan]
Come.
Spray water on me. It could work.
Let's do it.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Hurry up. Let's do it.
Great.
Come on.
More. Harder.
Like this.
Though he's in a terrible condition now, he still looks good.
He looks really good. How can he do that?
Miss Pam?
Why are you here?
I just came to check.
I was afraid you couldn't handle him, Mr. Aood.
I can. I'm all right.
Hey.
Hey. Are you all right?
What's that look in your eyes?
You still feel it, don't you?
I'm all right now.
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Let's continue.
I'll make it soft then.
You're still up?
Here's some tea.
Hey, let's be frank.
What's the relationship between Pam and you?
Me?
If you want to know, then I'll tell you.
I'm the person Miss Pam trusts the most.
She talks to me about everything.
Everything?
Why?
Did she tell you that she talked to me on the phone last night until she fell asleep?
We talked about several things.
Her favorite color.
Her favorite food.
How she became a kindergarten teacher.
She also sang me a song.
That's normal, isn't it?
The model's manager must talk to the model.
There's nothing special about it.
Also, it's not that important, so there's no need for her to tell me.
If thinking that way makes you feel at ease, then go ahead.
You just talked to her a bit, but you're bragging now?
Let me tell you this.
I'm allowed into her house 24 hours,
and I'm very close to her grandma.
Grandma has already allowed me to hit on her granddaughter.
What a regret I didn't record her voice.
If I did, I could show it to you.
You have to ask for permission just to talk to Pam.
I don't have to ask anyone for permission.
These days, Pam always sticks with me.
This is a Thai culture, you know.
When we want to hit on others' daughters or granddaughters,
we should ask for adults' permission.
If they don't allow us to, then we can't do so.
A foreigner like you...
has no chance.
Pam's grandpa really hates your kind.
He hates them like poison.
Also, Miss Pam loves her grandpa a lot.
I bet she will never displease him.
She's working with you now because she needs money for Grandpa's treatment.
Since you have already heard everything, you should know by now that you have no chance.
Hey? What?
Are you trying to get physical?
Don't.
No.
I'm going to sleep.
Is he sleepy already?
Are you not coming inside?
It's more comfortable here.
As you wish.
Do you need anything else? If you don't, I'll go to bed now.
Please go to bed.
I'm all right. Don't worry about me.
I'm not worried about you.
If it wasn't because of Miss Pam, I wouldn't even care about you.
Please help, Mr. Aood.
Donovan will die for sure.
Don't stop, Mr. Aood. Go.
- We won't make it, Miss Pam.
- We will. Hurry up. Faster.
♫ I don't know why I remember everything ♫
Hey. What are you doing?
Don't move. Stay still.
It's just walking barefoot.
I'll be fine.
♫ The memory of how much we loved each other ♫
♫ is what I can never erase, no matter how much I want to ♫
Who is Maria?
She's my older sister.
Thank you so much.
♫ What do I do when I can't forget I love you? ♫
♫ I wish I hadn't met you ♫
♫ If I could turn back time ♫
♫ I wouldn't look into your eyes ♫
♫ And let you give my heart butterflies ♫
♫ It'd be better if we didn't know each other... ♫
♫ because it's too hard to forget you ♫
I bought some congee for you.
For both of you.
Miss Pam, you also remember that I don't like livers.
Well, the store told me they ran out of livers.
You kept saying you didn't want to do this job,
but you tried to get close to him!
You went beyond the limit of your responsibility. That's why things have gone too far up to now!
Take this. And you don't have to do this job anymore.
I really pity myself now.
Feel free to cry, Miss Pam. No one can see you now.
♫ Who said that I'm so hot? ♫
♫ Sorry, if my hair looks too hot ♫
♫ What, a womanizer? It's not true!
(Don't believe it, don't believe what he says) ♫
♫ Who said I was a playboy? I just enjoy being with many girls ♫
♫ Do you want to try me for a bit?
Don't you want to know what the real me is like? ♫
♫ What you've heard seems to be negative.
If you try me, you'll be hooked ♫
♫ Don't just believe them, just look into my eyes.
I want you to try to open your mind ♫
♫ What you've heard seems to be negative.
If you try me, you'll be hooked ♫
♫ Don't just believe them, just look into my eyes.
I want you to try to open your mind ♫
♫ Don't get me wrong, wrong, wrong  ♫