=Episode 19=
(Let's Fight Side by Side This Time)
Mo Zhenfeng has run away.
I asked him about the factory for you.
He said he didn't know
why there was a surplus of goods.
I guessed it.
Bai Yue and Gu Jiannan
wouldn't let him know.
It's hard for you to investigate
with no clues left.
Who sent you the message?
You're so nervous.
What?
Well.
Just a spam message.
Let me have a look.
(Gu Jiannan)
Are you free to talk?
Am I right?
I received
a spam message.
No.
My husband doesn't let me.
Send it.
=Trick in Love=
Hi.
(Adapted from the novel
"Mr. Intrigue's Love Game" by Yun Qi Mo Li)
What's wrong?
My husband's not happy
about me seeing you.
Spit it out.
When did you
get so mushy?
What's it got to do with you?
I'm leaving.
Wait.
I will sell my shares.
Huh.
What trap are you setting for me again?
With your net worth,
is it still necessary to sell shares?
I'm serious.
I was set up
to owe money.
Yo.
By whom?
Who did justice for God?
Don't gloat about it.
I'm telling you,
Ye Zhongjue doesn't want
my shares,
but plenty of others do.
Even if you really want to sell them,
why don't you just sell them to Bai Yue?
Aren't you on the same team?
My mom doesn't agree.
After all, she is the daughter
of the Ye family.
How come she always
thinks of Ye Zhongjue?
That's really touching.
Can you just stop being sarcastic?
Buy them or not?
Be straightforward.
So what Gu Jiannan said is true?
Yes.
I looked into it.
He got conned at a casino.
Now he's in debt for tens of millions,
and creditors are after him.
Tens of millions.
He's got a lot of guts.
What were you even thinking before?
Being into a man like that?
I wasn't.
It was Mo Zhenfeng who liked him.
You don't have to be so jealous.
So what should we do?
There's no reason to refuse
shares offered to us.
At this shareholders' meeting,
although it pains me greatly,
I have to disclose the largest scandal
in the Jueshi Group's history.
Some time ago,
the company faced a major issue
with excess unsold Health Pots.
After careful consideration,
Mr. Ye planned out
a trade-in promotion event.
Although it involved
much trouble,
all the problems
were solved smoothly by Mr. Ye.
It's known to all of us.
I was glad at first.
After all, the company had a successor.
However...
However, what I never expected was that
behind this trade-in event,
it was nothing
but a complete conspiracy.
Using power for personal gain.
How despicable!
Not only did it harm
our company's interests,
but it also let down
our commitment and investment.
Ye Zhongjue,
even now,
you don't admit what you have done?
Ms. Bai, why don't you tell us
what I have done?
Okay.
If you're so stubborn,
I won't save some face for you.
We all know
about Mo Zhenfeng's counterfeiting.
And the real mastermind
and beneficiary of it
is our new CEO,
Ye Zhongjue.
How...?
How is that possible?
Do you think I'm willing to believe
that he did these crazy things?
Ah?
The evidence is overwhelming.
I have to believe it.
You can take a look.
All these contracts
bear Ye Zhongjue's signature
and his seal.
Everything
is crystal clear.
Take a good look.
Take a close look.
Mr. Ye, today, you will finally face
the consequences of all you've done.
Next,
Mr. Gu will tell us
about the evidence he has collected
in recent days.
These two contracts,
the fictitious contract signed
with the tea factory
and the power of attorney,
bear Mr. Ye's handwritten signature
and seal.
Come on.
Take a look.
Through my visits
over these many days,
I've discovered
a man frequents the tea factory.
And that man
is Mr. Ye.
After all,
that is the Ye family's property.
And both keys
are in the hands of them.
Ye Zhongjue, you used to live abroad,
and once you came back,
you married Mo Suqing,
Mo Zhenfeng's daughter.
No need to say more, right?
So the one behind the fraud
is Ye Zhongjue.
So you have long laid your trap
for me.
The tea factory
is our family's business,
but it's always been
taken care of by a subsidiary
of our group.
There's no way
the keys fall into private hands.
Wouldn't it be too hasty
to determine
that I'm the perpetrator
of this counterfeiting
based solely on the seal
and my personal schedules?
Excuse me, everybody.
I have no right to attend
the shareholders' meeting,
but my husband's name
is at stake here.
So pardon my intrusion.
=Trick in Love=
♪Whispered dialogues
deep within the woods♪
♪Constantly crashing through my mind♪
♪Wake up from a nightmare
with a head full of worry♪
♪Is it a delightful surprise
or an unexpected twist?♪
♪Maybe I shouldn't have♪
♪Got myself involved in a plot
that's carefully designed by you♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪Playing a game of cat and mouse♪
♪Your disguise got me in a whirl♪
♪Fantasizing that one day,
I'll grasp the moonlight♪
♪Even if I got pricked by a rose thorn♪
♪And my wound wouldn't stop bleeding♪
♪I'd still guard you as you grow♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪