=Episode 7=
(Testing with an Ulterior Motive)
I assisted your return
so you can gain the control
of Jueshi Group again,
not for you to be in a relationship.
Do you think Gu Jiannan would help you
just because you gave him some benefits?
So naive.
I did that
out of impulse.
What's your relationship with that girl?
Nothing.
We met in a bar.
Zhongjue,
Bai Yue has more than one man
than Gu Jiannan,
but you only have me.
I hope you can be honest with me
about everything.
Zhongjue,
you crossed the line this time.
You can't do this anymore.
She asked you
to keep an eye on me, didn't she?
The company's situation is complicated.
She's worried about you.
I thought you were my best friend.
Who is this?
(It has nothing to do with me.)
(She made me.)
What are they doing?
This is Mr. Gu!
I didn't know Mr. Gu was into this.
=Trick in Love=
Back to work.
(Adapted from the novel "Mr. Intrigue's
Love Game" by Yun Qi Mo Li)
Ha ha.
Mr. Gu,
about the public crisis
brought to the company by this news,
do you have anything to say?
Sorry
that you see this.
I will ask my lawyer
to deal with such untrue messages soon.
I have nothing to say.
The truth is the truth.
Mr. Gu,
you should say something
when it is needed.
Otherwise, how can you prove
you are innocent?
It is a fake video.
The person in the video is not me.
Ms. Jian,
why do you have to be so aggressive?
Think about the technology now.
Photoshop and face-swapping
can make things look almost real.
Mr. Gu is in a high position.
It's understandable
that someone wants to set him up.
That's right.
Mr. Gu and his girlfriend
are a loving couple.
How could he cheat on her?
The video must be fake.
Since all of you think
it is a fake video,
let's get a professional
to make an assessment.
Well,
I can't trust
the professional you introduce.
What if they are on your side?
How about this?
I will talk to my girlfriend.
Humph.
I will bring her to the business party
a few days later
to meet everyone.
That can certainly prove
I am not a cheater.
(Conference Room)
Hi, Ms. Jian.
Why didn't you join
the board meeting?
I was sorting out some documents.
You didn't see
Gu Jiannan's crafty face just now.
I was almost furious.
He will lose his cool soon.
These are all the contracts of the project
that he was in charge of these years,
The statements from clients.
And the evidence of his self-dealing.
All the important figures will attend
the business party a few days later.
Even Bai Yue
won't be able to save him this time.
If senior Mr. Ye could see
how capable you are,
he would rest in peace.
Jian Jie.
Yes?
About the engagement
my dad made for us...
You mean the child marriage?
Who believes in that in this era?
You are free to love anyone.
I am okay with that.
We mustn't make any mistake tomorrow.
Getting rid of Gu Jiannan
will bring us closer to Bai Yue.
Suqing,
here you are.
How are you doing recently?
Cut to the chase.
What's the problem?
Well,
Gu Jiannan
is canceling all the business
between us.
If that happens,
I will be completely broke.
Suqing,
we are father and daughter.
You have to help me out.
Suqing, I am begging you.
I am kneeling before you.
What are you doing?
People would think I am abusing you.
You...
If you don't help me,
it's the same as abuse.
What did I even do?
Get on your feet.
Only after
you promise you.
Get up!
What's going on?
Haven't you seen
a father kneeling before his daughter?
A father kneeling before his daughter?
How can you do this?
Help your father up.
That's right.
Hey, get up now.
I will get up
only after you say yes.
Hurry.
Alright, alright.
I promise you.
Get up now.
What kind of daughter you are?
I never heard of it.
Just go.
A bunch of busybodies.
The show is over.
We were helping you
and you chased us away.
How could you?
Evil old man.
Suqing,
you agree to help me?
Say it.
What do you want me to do?
You are going to
testify for Gu Jiannan
and your sister
tomorrow.
All you need to say
is that the video of them
is fake.
It's not true.
It is impossible
that they would do it.
Alright?
Why should I?
I won't do it.
Wait,
you just promised me!
What?
Now you just regret it?
You are not going, huh?
Okay.
Then today,
I'm going to jump off the bridge
and kill myself!
Do it if you dare.
Suqing,
I failed you.
I failed your mother.
If there is another life,
I will do my best to compensate you.
I will leave first.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Come down.
Down!
Suqing,
I've lost your mother
and I'm losing you.
If I have no more money,
I will have nothing left.
(Terrible acting.)
(Alright.)
(If this is what you ask for.)
I got you
some anti-inflammatory ointment.
I will apply it for you.
Is your girlfriend pretty?
I don't have a girlfriend.
The HR the other day
was talking about
introducing someone to you.
You are the only one in my eyes.
Does it still hurt?
Yes.
This ointment works really well.
It will get well soon.
Do you use it a lot?
Yes.
I used to get bullied when I was a kid.
It helped me a lot.
You? Got bullied?
Do you ever tell the truth?
What did I do wrong?
Nothing.
What's your plan tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'll go to work.
And you?
Go to work.
=Trick in Love=
♪Whispered dialogues
deep within the woods♪
♪Constantly crashing through my mind♪
♪Wake up from a nightmare
with a head full of worry♪
♪Is it a delightful surprise
or an unexpected twist?♪
♪Maybe I shouldn't have♪
♪Got myself involved in a plot
that's carefully designed by you♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪Playing a game of cat and mouse♪
♪Your disguise got me in a whirl♪
♪Fantasizing that one day,
I'll grasp the moonlight♪
♪Even if I got pricked by a rose thorn♪
♪And my wound wouldn't stop bleeding♪
♪I'd still guard you as you grow♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪