=Episode 5=
(Time to Wake Up)
You're up?
Yes.
Did you sleep well last night?
If you stare at me like this,
I...
=Trick in Love=
(Adapted from the novel
"Mr. Intrigue's Love Game" by Yun Qi Mo Li)
I'm making breakfast
and it's a bit noisy.
Why don't you sleep for a while more?
I'll try to keep it down.
I've already been woken by you.
How am I supposed to sleep?
Sorry.
I'm already so old.
Can't believe I am still having
this kind of dream.
What?
Oh,
I said
since it's spring now,
I should get up earlier.
Okay.
You're jobless.
Why are you staying home
instead of going for interviews?
I have an interview later.
I'm going out in a while.
(Let's see how long
you can keep putting on this act.)
Where will you have your interview?
Can I go with you?
The office
is very very far away from here.
It's fine.
I can take a day off.
Besides, I could use some fresh air too.
Are you sure you can be this impulsive?
I don't really care about my work now.
Work hasn't been going well recently.
I studied administrative management
at university,
so I want to find a job
that matches my expertise.
You don't want me to go with you?
No.
Of course I do.
Let's have breakfast first.
Wow.
Did you learn all these
when you were abroad?
Abroad?
This is a Western-style breakfast.
So I assume you must have
lived abroad for some time.
No...
Not really.
I'll go wash up first.
Okay.
That was close.
Mr. Ye, what is it?
I almost got found out!
Arrange for a video interview
in five minutes.
Interview?
Who are we interviewing?
Me.
What's going on?
I lied that I was going for an interview
and she insists on going with me.
I'm going to tell her
that I'm asked to do
an online interview.
You're the interviewer.
Just put on an act
and brush her off.
No, wait.
But what topics should I cover
in the interview?
No topics need to be covered.
Just remember
that I majored
in electrical engineering.
You're from the company's
HR Department.
The office is located in a remote place.
That's all.
No, this is too difficult!
I...
Who is on the phone?
The company just called me
and said it's changed
to an online interview.
Okay.
Eat first.
Do you like it?
Yes.
If you like it,
I'll make it for you every day.
Oh, right.
You said you wanted to find a job
that matches your expertise.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
Is there a company you want to join?
I want to join Jueshi Group.
I heard Jueshi Group has a new CEO
who is nice and capable.
He also improved employee welfare
the moment he assumed his position.
Everyone respects him a lot.
I think with a boss like that,
this company will be
quite promising.
Who did you hear this from?
Our newspaper wrote
a featured report about them.
This is the kind of image
rich people love to create.
It's just one article.
Not convincing at all.
Do you hate rich people?
Don't you?
It depends.
Not all rich people are bad.
My interview.
Hello.
We've checked your resume
and we're impressed.
If a talented person like you
joins our company,
we would be really lucky.
Honestly,
if you join our company,
you will be really popular.
You'll be a breath of fresh air to us!
Thank you.
I'll report for duty tomorrow.
Sure,
no problem!
But
our company
may be a little far from you.
It will take about two hours
to get here by car.
If there's a traffic jam
during the peak hours,
it will take about three hours.
Is that okay with you?
Of course it is.
Your girlfriend won't mind, right?
I...
I'm single.
Single?
That's a pity.
You're so outstanding.
How could you not have a girlfriend?
I can assure you
that after you join us,
I'll introduce someone nice to you.
Whoever marries you
will be really lucky!
Seriously,
you have outstanding grades,
you're ambitious,
and you can cook well.
Most importantly...
If there's nothing else,
I'd like to call it a day for now.
Bye-bye.
He hung up?
He sure is warm-hearted.
Tell me about it.
Yeah.
Mo Sulian
speaks ill of you
in the office every day.
If you continue to tolerate it,
she'll literally
turn something false into real.
Who said I'm going to tolerate it?
Yes.
You have to teach her a lesson.
I'll find two actors to intimidate her.
No.
This time, I'm going to it myself.
Okay.
Mr. Gu,
the receptionist
just signed a parcel for you.
You can get back to work.
Okay.
(Hotel)
(See you tonight at 20:00)
(Lian)
Alas.
I'm going to propose to Jiannan.
In the future,
you will have no place in this family.
You'll always be inferior to me.
This family is about to become
a recycling center.
I won't go there even if you invite me.
Humph.
(See you tonight at 20:00. From Nan)
(Lovers Hotel)
(See you tonight)
(at 8 PM.)
=Trick in Love=
♪Whispered dialogues
deep within the woods♪
♪Constantly crashing through my mind♪
♪Wake up from a nightmare
with a head full of worry♪
♪Is it a delightful surprise
or an unexpected twist?♪
♪Maybe I shouldn't have♪
♪Got myself involved in a plot
that's carefully designed by you♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪Playing a game of cat and mouse♪
♪Your disguise got me in a whirl♪
♪Fantasizing that one day,
I'll grasp the moonlight♪
♪Even if I got pricked by a rose thorn♪
♪And my wound wouldn't stop bleeding♪
♪I'd still guard you as you grow♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪