=Episode 18=
(Kisses of Forgiveness
and Crimson Bed Sheet)
I've contacted a lawyer team.
They handled Hongyuan Group's case
last month.
We can talk tomorrow
and see if we can cooperate.
I've told you I'll sort out the cost.
I'll keep you posted.
My dear, thank you.
You are amazing.
Thanks to you,
Jueshi Group withdrew
the case right away.
You're amazing.
Excuse me, a cup of water.
Ye Zhongjue
is indeed a nice person.
Way better than
that hypocritical dad of his.
I really need to
thank my good girl.
Without you,
Ye Zhongjue
wouldn't withdraw the case that easily,
right?
=Trick in Love=
(Adapted from the novel
"Mr. Intrigue's Love Game" by Yun Qi Mo Li)
Zhongjue,
you're really in big trouble this time.
Because of the withdrawal,
we paid a huge amount of penalty.
The shareholders are not happy about it.
It's not easy for Ms. Jian either.
Is it really worth it
doing all this for her?
Hello.
Ye Zhongjue, are you insane?
You let Mo Zhenfeng off just like that?
Do you think the board will let you go?
Are you worried about me?
We're getting a divorce.
Now that we've decided to break apart,
why do you have to
make yourself look that bad
because of me?
Who said we were divorcing?
I never said yes.
The woman I marry
is the person
I'm spending my lifetime with.
What a fool.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Why are you being so nice to me?
What do you see in me
that makes you think I'm worth it?
If I'm doing something
that will hurt you,
can you not
go along and hurt yourself too?
You let Mo Zhenfeng off,
do you know what you'll have to face?
Ye Zhongjue,
what I hate the most
is to owe anyone anything.
You don't owe me anything.
I'm being nice to you
because I love you.
No matter what you do,
I will be by your side.
This is my own decision.
It has nothing to do with you.
You don't need to feel burdened.
But it does concern me.
Since my mom died,
no one has ever cared about me,
except you.
How can I not care?
Why would I not care?
Whatever I do,
I do it for your happiness.
If you really feel bad about it,
then don't cry.
Be good.
Ye Zhongjue.
I'm here.
Why did you never explain
what you did when you were a kid?
Why didn't you tell me
the reason why you left?
I failed to help you.
I feel sorry.
Are you stupid?
So,
have you forgiven me?
can you forgive me too?
♪The summer sea breeze blowing♪
♪Arouses the dusk♪
♪In this small town,
we stop and turn around for each other♪
♪Cupid's arrow shoots us
when our eyes meet♪
♪We feel the love as we lock eyes♪
♪In the subtle atmosphere of the moment♪
♪Our souls are getting closer♪
♪We share our emotions
and our lust for each other♪
♪We're both tired of looking for the one
in the massive crowd♪
♪When young, we were eager to love
but didn't know how♪
All good.
Okay. Next, please.
(Jueshi Group Health Pot)
(Old For New)
Big companies really have
good after-sales services.
Next.
It's such a nice pot
and you can even get a new replacement.
I'll probably stick to this brand.
All good.
Mo Zhenfeng left me
a lot of trouble.
Luckily, you came up
with this solution.
Mr. Ye, this is not from our company.
No problem. Next.
It's okay. Chang it for them.
We'll handle it later.
Thank you.
Mr. Ye,
you instructed to let Mo Zhenfeng off.
You also promised the board
you would destroy all the fake goods.
So now,
we need you to answer a question.
Why are the fakes still available
in the market?
I destroyed the fake goods in person.
Technically, there shouldn't be
any problem,
unless someone
transferred the goods
before I got involved,
which caused
the fakes to go into the market.
Mr. Ye, you look pretty certain.
I'm assuming
you've had some clue.
Give me some time.
I'll find them.
We'll wait for you
to find the person behind this.
=Trick in Love=
♪Whispered dialogues
deep within the woods♪
♪Constantly crashing through my mind♪
♪Wake up from a nightmare
with a head full of worry♪
♪Is it a delightful surprise
or an unexpected twist?♪
♪Maybe I shouldn't have♪
♪Got myself involved in a plot
that's carefully designed by you♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪Playing a game of cat and mouse♪
♪Your disguise got me in a whirl♪
♪Fantasizing that one day,
I'll grasp the moonlight♪
♪Even if I got pricked by a rose thorn♪
♪And my wound wouldn't stop bleeding♪
♪I'd still guard you as you grow♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪