=Episode 3=
(My Door Will Always Open for You)
Wait.
Where's my ID card?
ID card?
Ah, wait a moment.
I remember I put it here.
Wait, I think I put it...
I remembered it now.
I forgot to bring it with me
when I left home this morning.
You left it at home?
Yeah.
Do you want me to go home with you?
Do I look like
that I can be easily fooled?
Definitely not.
I left it at home, I promise.
=Trick in Love=
(Adapted from the novel
"Mr. Intrigue's Love Game" by Yun Qi Mo Li)
Alright. I'll believe you one more time.
Let's go.
Okay.
Wait.
I'll drive.
Your car is
too shabby.
With my condition,
it's good enough for me to have a car.
♪In this small town,
we stop and turn around for each other♪
It's here.
♪Cupid's arrow shoots us
when our eyes meet♪
♪We feel the love as we lock eyes♪
Please.
♪In the subtle atmosphere of the moment♪
♪Our souls are getting closer♪
Make yourself at home.
♪We share our emotions
and our lust for each other♪
♪We're both tired of looking for the one
in the massive crowd♪
♪When young, we were eager to love
but didn't know how♪
What would you like to drink?
Water. Thanks.
What do you do?
I...
I am...
an electrician.
I thought you were an artist.
This is my friend's studio.
I just resigned
and don't have a job,
so he let me stay here for now.
(Why does he conceal his real identity?)
Are you an electrician all the time?
To be precise, I'm not one currently.
I didn't really enjoy my last job.
That's why I quit.
By the way,
I majored in electric engineering
at university.
I'd like to find a job in this field.
(Did he lose all the money)
(in the family feud ?)
Then do you plan
to work as an electrician forever?
One can make a living
with their professional skills.
And I don't have to socialize
with others.
It's good to live
a peaceful and stable life.
(Oh, no.)
(He must be kicked out
after failing the family feud.)
Where's my ID card?
Give it to me then.
Oh, the ID card.
Ah.
I forgot about it again.
I'll look for it.
(ID card)
A nice film will be released tonight.
Would you like to watch it?
I've had an appointment.
Give me the ID card.
Thank you.
You said you didn't like
staying in your family, didn't you?
My door will always open for you.
You can stay however long you want.
It's not your business
whether I like my family or not.
You have no right
to judge my life.
I didn't mean it.
What are you doing?
Are you going to play hardball?
What I said was a little reckless.
What I wanted to say
was that I love you truly.
I want to
take responsibility for you.
But I don't need you to do that.
A person like you
simply wants
to get a free girlfriend
to live with you.
Hey.
I just want a chance to look after you.
I never thought
of doing anything bad to you.
Please don't misunderstand me.
The password to this door
is your birthday.
If you don't like me staying here,
I can move out.
I won't be in your way.
When you said taking responsibility
for me,
you meant to let me stay in this house?
Do you get to spend money as you wish?
I don't have much money.
And I just lost my job.
But my friend said
you can stay here however long you want.
We have everything inside.
You can paint
or play video games as you like.
The railway station
is only five minutes away.
And it only takes 15 minutes
to get to your company.
It's convenient.
How do you know where I work?
You were drunk that night
and you said that yourself.
Oh.
Just stay here for a few days.
You can move out
when you find a place
near your company.
Well.
So...
If I stay here,
where will you live?
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
I can find a basement in the suburbs.
One with good ventilation.
Going downtown from there
only takes two hours.
Two hours?
Or
you can use the bed
and I'll sleep on the sofa.
We can make do for a few days.
Alright.
I'll stay here temporarily.
When I manage to rent a place,
I'll move.
Don't bear any ulterior intentions.
No problem.
Rest assured.
Please move my luggage inside for me.
Okay.
(Why would a president
end up to this?)
(A week ago)
Mr. Gu.
What about the matter
I discussed with you a while back?
I told you, no rush.
No rush.
Which of these two words
that you don't understand?
Why do you force me
to marry your daughter now?
It can wait.
I'm just bringing it up
by the way.
Suqing is no longer young.
What's more, your cousin,
Ye Zhongjue,
will be back from abroad soon.
If anything happens
inside the group,
we can cope with it well
after we form the marital bond.
Marital bond?
She wouldn't even let me kiss her
after all this time.
Tsk.
What?
You're going to pick up
the heir of Jueshi Group?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Ye Zhongjue is Gu Jiannan's cousin,
and the real heir of Jueshi Group.
As long as I get him,
I might be able to join the group
and get the things I want,
(so I can make them pay)
(for my mom's accident back then.)
=Trick in Love=
♪Whispered dialogues
deep within the woods♪
♪Constantly crashing through my mind♪
♪Wake up from a nightmare
with a head full of worry♪
♪Is it a delightful surprise
or an unexpected twist?♪
♪Maybe I shouldn't have♪
♪Got myself involved in a plot
that's carefully designed by you♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪Playing a game of cat and mouse♪
♪Your disguise got me in a whirl♪
♪Fantasizing that one day,
I'll grasp the moonlight♪
♪Even if I got pricked by a rose thorn♪
♪And my wound wouldn't stop bleeding♪
♪I'd still guard you as you grow♪
♪That bouquet of roses under the moon♪
♪Is as splendid as you♪
♪Covered in thorns,
with no one to rely on♪
♪But blooming in graceful elegance♪
♪Staying grounded
in this turbulent world♪
♪Isolating myself
and refusing to believe in love♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪
♪I'll support your every decision
and always be there for you♪
♪Three thousand times for you♪
♪Till the ice and snow melt and vanish♪