joking
The second year Class 2 with the strong
runs and a delicious electricity from
Beo 영상
Oh, thank you for the
I'm here.
Yes.
Thank you.
He's Oh Dong-hyun.
He eats all day and eats in his dreams.
Thank you for the food.
He's Byung-ju.
He's the one who sleeps all day, so he dreams the most.
Life follows its name.
What did you dream about yesterday?
You're wearing a red shirt.
Don't pull it too much.
He was a kid who thought Nike and school uniforms were a set.
Why are you wearing a black coat?
Red is the best.
Hey, the red is not coming to Korea.
Hey, is he a foreigner?
Why?
He looks like a jerk.
Is it your first time seeing a red shirt?
Yeah, it's my first time.
Red is the best.
How did you get it?
All four of them dream of first place and transfer to Seoul National University.
There's a route to the front.
The look is over the top.
Look at him.
Hey, you, let's switch to the front.
Come on, let's switch.
Look at him.
Dreams, personalities, and personality.
What's the common ground between them?
It's our class.
Stop it!
All of them like our class president, Seon Ah.
Why do you like her?
She's pretty.
But isn't she a bit tacky?
Seon Ah, it's a big hit.
Did you hear that Park Ji Sung is going to Europe next year?
Park Ji Sung is going to Europe?
I know.
But what class is she in?
I'll go look for her and come back.
How many classes are there between Hyung Pyo and Park Ji Sung?
I don't like her acting like she's good at studying.
She's pretty.
I feel a bit different.
Right? She's not good.
Seon Ah is sexy.
I'm going to beat you up.
You're not going to do it, are you?
Catch him!
Episode 2
Attention!
18.
Back then, we were most thirsty for human desires.
The fattening appetite.
Byung Joo's sleepiness.
The perverted king's sexual desire.
And my fourth desire.
The lust for attention.
Quiet.
I can see everything from behind.
Don't do anything else.
This is your last chance.
Hey!
You bastard!
Teacher's lust for attention?
All of you who have been working hard, get up.
I told you to get up.
You're not getting up?
Byun Tae Hwan.
What did you hide?
I didn't hide anything.
You're hiding something in your hand.
Put your hands away and stand straight.
Stand straight.
This is straight.
Hey, hey.
I'm going to get up even if I sleep because of you.
Stand straight.
Huh?
You're out of your mind because you're a boy.
Can you do that in front of your teacher?
What?
Oh, yes.
See you at your class.
And Son Ahn.
Why are you doing this?
I'm sorry.
You're the class president.
Our class is...
Why can't you stand properly?
Stand straight.
Teacher.
Oh, yes.
This is Korea.
It's a light stick.
Go for it.
Gu Jin Ho, you sit in front of Seon Ahn with your cheek.
Seon Ahn, you watch Gu Jin Ho with your cheek.
You pervert.
Go to the bathroom.
Thank you.
Hey, hey.
Every day, like the day
I've been waiting for.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ha.
I'm going to fall again.
It's much better than last time.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
You don't know what feeling is.
Hey, Doong.
Come on.
One, two, three, four.
Two ants.
Three ants.
Five in all.
Five.
Oh, oh.
Hey.
You're always practicing.
You're worse than the fat guy.
Me?
You're worse than him?
You have to work hard to get that feeling.
Gu Jin Ho.
Have you ever tried to work hard?
I don't do that.
The moment I try,
I'm afraid of what's going to happen to me.
People who have a lot of mouth like you
won't be able to develop for life.
You're a bad guy.
Who are you?
Let's play.
Who plays basketball these days?
Play soccer.
Gu Jin Ho.
Put on some clothes.
Who do you look like?
Huh?
Are you here?
Yes.
I got an interesting call
from the Dongchun
I hope you don't go to the academy anymore.
I saved money because I didn't go to the academy.
Eat as much as you want.
I just want to go back to the academy.
Oh, leave it.
Now you're studying hard with the class president.
Oh, my.
The food.
The food is the best for a countryman.
Wow.
Oh, my.
Attention.
Salute.
Again.
Hello.
Attention.
Salute.
Hello.
Are you ignoring me because I don't have a college entrance exam?
No.
Then you're ignoring me, right?
I'll take a paper exam in 20 minutes.
Oh.
Take out the paper.
There must be someone who didn't bring it to the textbook, right?
If there is, I will accept it as love for me.
No one can handle Mr. Giga's love.
Get up.
A sensitive boss in his prime.
And if you take that love, you can take the exam.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Should I stand behind you?
You're so pissed off about Rudolph.
I know you're doing this.
If you work hard, you'll go to a good university and a good company.
You think you'll succeed, right?
Happiness is not there.
The process of art is the first and foremost element of human life.
Consciousness, consciousness, and the life and existence contained in it.
In order not to become a slave to life, you must have a hobby.
Whether it's dreaming, love, or hope.
I smell good.
Good smell.
It's real.
Right?
Gu Jin-woo.
Thank you for earlier.
Today is the day to get off work.
Anyway, thank you.
But how many leaves?
I brought something if I'm grateful. Why am I empty-handed?
Hey, let's go.
Goodbye, friend.
But you really don't have a dream?
You don't study because you don't have a dream?
No?
Why?
Then why don't you study?
I told you I don't study because I'm afraid.
I'm afraid I'll be too good at studying if I study hard.
I'm a little afraid.
Why aren't you coming?
Why is he so impatient?
Oh, don't be curious about that.
I'm hurt.
Hey, you're all dead.
Come on.
Now the trend is basketball.
Do you know slam dunk?
The left hand is just a
Hey, I won.
Hey, I lost.
We fought well.
What are you fighting about?
Hey, I won.
I won, right?
What is it? Tell me.
Stop bothering Seon-ah.
I'm not kidding.
Tell me before the game starts.
Idiot.
Oh, my God.
Why?
This.
What is it?
It's a prediction problem for next week's test.
It's a type that teachers like.
Oh, this is the type of paper you were talking about?
What else?
This is a reference.
I've never asked for this.
You said you couldn't do it.
I can get half of the test right even if I solve what I gave you.
Why are you so naive?
Because I don't want to ignore it.
Oh, so you've been ignoring me until now because you couldn't study?
Can I just ignore people if I'm good at studying?
No, it's not that.
Just keep ignoring me.
I don't care.
I'm not ignoring people who can't study.
What I'm ignoring is the person who's trying.
You don't even try that much.
So this is how it works?
But why is this so hard?
This isn't it.
That's right.
This isn't mine.
Oh, my God.
The handwriting is pretty.
I didn't even know I read it all the way from that place.
The handwriting is so pretty.
I'm not going to do it.
No, no, no, no.
Open your hands.
That's why it's called love.
That's right. Number three is a little tricky.
Did you solve it by writing?
Yeah, look, I'll tell you.
If you apply the writing solution...
Why do you have to send me a perfect writing?
Move.
I just need to look at one more question.
I have to study, too.
Move.
You study?
Jinho, I'm sorry.
I'll be back later.
That's right.
Actually, I was studying, too.
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Dad, what's the difference between studying well?
Does life change?
A lot of things change.
Honey, what's this?
What did you buy?
I'm going to make some bread.
I told you not to buy this.
Let's just eat.
Study.
If you're going to do it, do your best.
What's this?
How much did you buy?
Come here, guys.
Don't be so rough.
Study to death.
Come on, hurry up.
Hey, Gu Gyeong-ho.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Suna.
Huh?
This is a big hit these days.
S.S. Yujin hairband?
What? Where did you get it?
I sold it out.
I'll try it.
That's right. S.S. Yujin's full version.
You're prettier than Yujin.
That's why I'm giving you this.
Oh, thank you.
But how many times did Yujin get it?
I'll ask Park Jisung.
I'm sorry.
Really?
You?
Why?
Pretty.
It's so pretty.
Jisoo.
Wait a minute.
One, two, two and a half.
That's right.
Here, number four and number six.
It's pretty, but the answer is wrong.
What is it?
Try again.
I'm sleepy. I'll be there later.
I'll give you ten minutes.
I told you I was tired.
So?
I'll solve it in three minutes.
I keep the speed of walking at X, and Suna keeps the speed of walking at Y.
Y, Y.
Why do you do this?
Don't do anything weird.
It's so noisy.
Don't do it.
Why?
It's useless to learn.
Give up math.
It's useful.
I don't give up.
Kim Jisoo.
58 points.
Gu Jin-ho.
86 points.
Look at you.
You can do it.
Your dream comes true.
Teacher.
I'm a genius.
Okay.
I'll try.
I'm a genius.
Okay.
I want to see you for a long time.
I'll go to class A if I do a little more.
I made three mistakes.
Classics helps you focus.
Yes.
Answer loudly.
I'm going.
Figaro.
You're a genius?
Well, that's about it.
You're a genius.
Why didn't you do it before?
I don't know the triangle root, but I'm good at it.
When you buy tofu at the market,
Are you going to say,
Give me three roots and four?
Never.
Give me a handful of tofu.
Three roots and four are six?
Why do you study so hard?
Even if it doesn't look necessary,
I'm just doing it.
Then there's always something to be earned.
You're like an old man.
You're childish.
Have you ever been childish?
Do you know how hard it is to be childish?
Yeah, you're always so childish.
Yeah, you're always childish.
Close your eyes.
Why did something go away so well in those days?
Why did the whole thing reflect on itself every time?
The culprit doesn't even have to raise his hand to confess.
What is it?
Dream concert?
I told you to study.
These guys.
Look at this.
Hey, Ddoong.
How many times do I tell you?
There's nothing in the bag.
Do you only take what you collect?
You know your parents study at school, right?
Do you know you only charge half?
What did you buy all this with?
You stole the school fee, right?
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
Hey, Ddoong.
Mr. Seo.
How much is the school fee?
How much is it?
I'll pay.
Ko Jin-ho, are you having a problem with your teacher?
No, that's not it.
I don't think it's right to do that to Dong-hyun because of the school fee.
How can you do this to your teacher?
It doesn't matter if it's school fees or Dong-hyun's belly fat.
Look at the condition.
The school is going well, right?
Ko Jin-ho, you're having a good time today.
Let's go out and lie down.
Teacher.
I think what you did to Dong-hyun is unfair.
Dong-hyun didn't steal the school fee, did he?
I think he stole it or disappeared.
I think he's looking for it properly.
I'm sorry for the interruption.
I don't remember if I found the school fee that disappeared that day.
But what I remember is...
Don't look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
What's embarrassing?
You're so cool.
But it's fun to show it with us.
Honestly, it's fun, right?
I'm embarrassed.
The hallway we stood on was really hot.
That day's Seon-ah was really pretty.
And as the heat got colder,
I went to the last shopping mall before I became a senior in high school.
Go straight. Go straight.
Hey, look at the second grade class.
I'm going to the second grade class.
Go straight. Go straight.
Second grade class, third class, fighting!
You, you, you.
You stole the school fee, didn't you?
If you tell me the truth, I'll tell you Tae-han stole it.
What?
Byeong-ju, come here.
What Byeong-ju?
So cute.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you eat so little?
Hey, do you want to eat at the horse-dung?
Let's go right away.
Hey, let's eat horse-dung.
Oh, what is it?
Let's eat horse-dung.
Hey, can't you do anything if you're going to eat?
Do it. Do it.
Think about what you ate.
Jong-hyun, Jong-hyun, I'm coming.
Jong-hyun, Jong-hyun.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I won.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Hey, rock, paper, scissors.
Do it right or change it with me.
Sorry.
No, no, no, no.
You can't change it until you change the ball.
Hey, I'm going to win no matter what.
I'm going to win no matter what.
Don't worry.
Byeong-tae, are you bragging?
Hey, do it right.
Do it right.
Are you okay?
It's no joke.
I think I'm going to die.
Can't you stand one person?
It's not even a joke.
Hey, it's a joke.
It's a game. Why are you so serious?
You're a mess, aren't you?
You're a childish bastard.
But what do you want to be in that way?
How do you live?
Let's hear it.
All right.
Hey, Ahn Sung-bin.
Take it.
Hey, is it fun?
Are you having fun?
What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, stop.
Stop, stop.
Hey, you guys, get out of the way.
I'm going to hit you.
Let go of me.
All right.
Make a loud noise.
You guys, come here.
Let's go.
Stop it.
Eat yours.
Hey, Seon-ah, are you here?
Sit here.
Thank you.
Well...
Dong-hyun.
Yes?
Can you give me a minute after class?
Why?
I have something to ask you.
Of course, of course.
Are you introducing yourself?
What is it?
You ask me when you study, right?
Oh, no.
Hey, did you two have a fight?
What?
We played a basketball game.
You're good.
Why?
Did you hear about the Soyang Girls' High School?
I heard that the girls are coming out.
Hey, don't do it.
I'm really scared.
Behind you.
There's nothing.
It rained a lot that day.
It was a day when the Soyang River was blowing.
After the game, the first and second place in the school were still studying.
But the red pen on the floor of the first place in the school...
I shouldn't have died with that red pen.
The first place in the school was the first place in the school.
What is this?
I'm surprised.
So?
So...
I was walking around the school in the country and waiting for the afternoon to end.
Let's go somewhere else.
Okay, let's go together.
And the next one is our school!
Yes, mom.
Now?
Yes.
The final exam is coming soon.
So?
There's only two weeks left.
There's a lot left.
I saw you were a genius.
You don't go to the academy, do you?
No, I don't need that kind of thing.
Then...
Do you want to stay with me and study more from today?
Suddenly?
With you?
Hey, do you like me?
What are you talking about?
I don't like a guy who's dumber than me.
A genius like me is a dumber?
I've been watching you because you're afraid you'll cry if you lose the first place in the school.
I don't need that kind of consideration.
Okay, do it.
Do it.
Let's bet.
Bet?
With the score?
Yes.
I won't let you win.
What do you want?
If I win...
I'll shave your head.
My head?
Aren't you confident?
No, I'm totally confident.
Then...
Let's bet with the score of Gu Kyung-soo.
Okay.
But if I win, you...
You'll be a ghost.
I knew it.
It's because I'm afraid to study alone after school.
You're the apple of my eye.
What's the meaning of apples?
You're a precious person to me.
Apple, apple, apple.
Apple of my eye.
Fuck you.
Apple.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
Learn only useful things in life.
Alcohol.
Technology.
Hey, technology teacher?
Nice to meet you.
I'll tell you I love you.
How much money did you have?
I had a little money.
Little.
I had a...
You have a lot of money.
You have a lot, lot of money.
That's good.
You are the hope.
That's mine.
Go wash your face.
I'll give you ten minutes.
Three minutes.
Go wash your face.
Dad.
Take it off.
On your head.
Wait, wait, wait.
No.
What?
You scared me.
Why?
Did we look too good together?
I kept my promise.
What are you doing?
I'm going to school.
I wish you were popular.
Why don't you choose one of these and go out with someone?
I have to study.
What do you get if you study like that?
I want to go to a good university.
Is your dream a good university?
Dream?
Yes.
What kind of person do you want to be?
It's raining.
I should have brought some clothes.
I'm sorry.
I have clothes too.
Don't.
I'm taking a break.
Try it on.
I don't mind.
The dark
end of the world
was brightened.
We were
shining
in that time.
Why are you half-baked?
You look half-baked.
It's getting cold.
Why are you
half-baked?
Men are not interested in women.
Stop it!
I won the bet, but why did I untie my hair like a ghost?
I was curious, but I couldn't ask.
I'm home.
You're home.
Wash up, son.
What are you doing?
I'm washing the laundry.
Dad, you can't wash this.
Then you just put the smelly thing in there?
Yeah, I'm screwed.
Why?
Did I do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Show hexagon.
It's a sailor's slave, and it's not easy to get married.
You're not only married,
It's also a slave!
It was taken from the sink.
I am a slaves.
He's a slave!
Shut up!
Hahaha Obviously!
You need to get married when her stepfather's swamp rich in wealth couldn't cross English Merchant Episode on multifamily zero?
Hahaha Hopefully!
What is thegren wood?
Shoot again!
It's almost gonna go!
Yeah!
Let's goOooo!
16 years old, 3 years of middle school,
and 3 years of high school.
This whole 12 year long period
was measured with only one day.
I thought it would be over, but it was strangely empty.
So we started playing like crazy.
I was so happy that I didn't even notice it.
You fell for me in the heat of a hot Saturday night.
Be honest with me.
Even if you try to suppress me with your noble eyes,
I'm not good at that kind of trick.
You fell for me.
What are those vague eyes saying?
Even if you dance, come on, come on.
The moment my eyes and your eyes met,
I was so happy that I didn't even notice it.
Oh, stand by me.
If you want, I'll go to the night sky.
Even if you dance, come on, come on.
Hey, who told you to come to the beach in winter?
I'm sorry.
Hey, Jin-ho, Jin-ho.
What's so funny?
What are you doing?
You're more childish than a little kid in the neighborhood.
It's so childish.
I really wanted to ask you after the college entrance exam.
Huh?
What do you think I'm thinking?
Sun-ah, wait a minute.
Jin-ho, you're dead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are we going to be later?
My husband?
Well, I can't go to the same college as Sun-ah.
I'm going to have to pass the law class after school.
I want to get married soon.
Hey, Donghyun, I'm going to make you my girlfriend.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep a lot.
I haven't slept well in a day, so it was really hard.
I'm going to pass the audition and become an idol.
And I'm going to work hard for a few years and then marry Jung Woo-sung.
Wow, Yoon Jin-soo is really big and specific.
It's useless. Ask Jung Woo-sung.
Jung Woo-sung also has a position.
What about Seon-ah?
First of all, a good university.
Then I don't know yet.
Seon-ah has a dream too much.
Seon-ah, take Jisoo's dream. She has a lot of dreams.
Hey, hey, aren't you going to ask me?
What are you?
I have to prove it from now on.
What?
I'm a great person.
A strong person.
What is a great person?
A person who can change the world with just a presence.
Don't overdo it.
What great people are we to you after taking the college entrance exam?
Overdo it. Overdo it. Overdo it.
What if you overdo it? The college entrance exam is over.
Hey, yeah, now you're free. Hey, take it. Take it.
But it's a great day. Is it okay?
Hey, your birthday hasn't passed.
Not only me, but Yoon Jisoo and Seon-ah too.
Cool.
What do you think?
The college entrance exam is over.
Yeah, let's drink.
Hey, fast, slow, normal, it doesn't matter. Let's drink.
Yeah, dreams come true.
Dreams come true.
Our Jinwoo?
Of course. He was always smart.
I'll call you when I get the results.
Ta-da.
Wow, awesome.
Son, what if we go to a college on Line 2?
Do we have to look for a house in Seoul?
Are we all going to live in Seoul?
There's a dormitory in the university.
Oh, Siwon.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Seon-ah.
What's going on?
What should I do?
I think I got a 4th grade answer wrong.
I got 30 points lower than the fake one.
I've never done this before.
I made a stupid mistake in the most important exam.
What should I do?
I'm only good at studying.
It's cold. Let's go to a cafe.
Seon-ah, you know I like you a lot, right?
What?
I'm going to like you no matter what your exam results are.
You really...
You have to understand the atmosphere.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll cancel it.
I thought life would be ruined if the college entrance exam failed.
Now that I think about it, it was just one test.
It wasn't anything.
The first test was to continue the flight from Soyang River to Huncheon and the airport in Gongsan.
The second test was to continue the flight from Soyang River to Huncheon and the airport in Gongsan.
To all the students of Gongchuncheon High School who have continued the flight from Soyang River to Huncheon and the airport in Gongsan,
this test was to continue the flight from Soyang River to Huncheon and the airport in Gongsan.
Sungbin passed the law school in Sinchon.
He applied for a student's school in a safe room, but he's sorry until the end.
Yes, Mr. Choi.
It's Dong-hyun's mom.
Yes, I passed.
Dong-hyun is a Catholic.
It's all thanks to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be born.
The pervert king who went to a place full of stones, wind, and women.
He's in Jeju University.
He was so eager to date, and the sky must have been touching.
It's not Byung-ju, it's Byung-ju.
And I have to graduate now.
Byung-ju, who was always late because he slept a lot, passed late.
120 students in the waiting room missed.
I'm a college student now.
Go to college.
Eun Jong-min.
Hey, hey, hey.
Go to college.
Seon-ah, who was out of her class, passed the law school.
I studied so hard to go to Seoul with Seon-ah,
but I was the only one going to Seoul.
I'm sorry.
I still can't believe I graduated.
Yeah, you're 20 years old.
I should've been a trainee when I was a teenager.
It'll work out. You said you got a second call.
I don't know.
Anyway,
You were the most popular person in school.
How do you feel?
What do you mean?
You're so humble.
You know I'm mean, right?
You're so annoying.
I'm just thankful for everything.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry.
Who's the most thankful?
Who do you want to confess to?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Tell me.
You're the only one who needs to know.
Okay, I promise.
Actually...
Guys, graduation...
is over!
I'm sorry.
In a time when I could just dream,
I was heading to a time when I had to achieve my dream.
But I still believed that our possibilities were infinite,
and I thought our dreams would be realized.
So...
So,
I become a teacher when I graduate?
Yeah.
That's right.
Is that...
a man who's in a school?
I don't know.
You're going to study even when you go to college, right?
I'm going to date someone.
Wait.
That arm...
Why?
Give it to me.
I'm sorry.
I wear this every day.
Why?
Because...
When we break up, our wish comes true.
I've been to the place where the aliens used to live.
It's all thanks to Suna.
The first thing I learned at college was how many games there were to feed alcohol to the world.
I'm going to drink in the room anyway, and I'm going to go to the M.T.
Fighting, school uniform!
Suna, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you disinfecting the school?
Smell the alcohol.
You're doing great.
I'm sorry.
Suna!
This one.
Who is it?
It's pretty.
Let me see.
Okay, okay.
I won't look.
What?
What's this?
Suna, are you okay?
Korean!
Suna and I didn't meet often because we were far away from school, but we somehow found a reason to meet.
Hello?
Oh, sorry.
I was in class.
Really?
Suna!
Oh.
You ordered a couple set, right?
Couple set?
Oh, two-person set.
How long have you been dating?
I haven't been dating yet.
It hasn't been long.
It's a good time.
Have a good time.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
Jinwoo.
Actually, I lose my stuff often, I sleep a lot, and I'm not good at cleaning.
I'm good at making stupid mistakes.
I was pushed to the semifinals.
And I don't know what's trending these days.
What's that?
So, what I'm saying is...
I, who you like, could be in your imagination.
My imagination isn't that rich.
Think about it.
Do you really like me?
I like you.
Why do you say that?
Are you dumped without even confessing?
I should confess properly in the best way.
I was in a hurry.
I, who was still immature, thought that the strong side was the cool side.
What are you doing with the light?
It's okay.
It's just a arm for friendship.
Are you okay?
It's just a ear for love.
Go ahead.
I'm going.
Seon-ah.
Are you hurt? Where?
It's nothing. I got hurt while practicing martial arts with the kids.
Seon-ah.
There's a competition next month.
So, you're going to fight again?
Martial arts is just sports.
Why are you doing such a dangerous thing?
Aren't you studying?
I mean, I'm doing this for my physical strength.
Martial arts is the strongest sport.
It's really cool.
Really?
Can you stop fighting?
It's okay. I'll hang up.
Martial arts is just sports.
I think I can do it with one hand.
Should I come out?
Should I use one hand?
Yes, use one hand.
I invited Seon-ah, but she didn't want to come out.
I'm going to use my hand.
It's okay.
Seon-ah, how was it?
Cool, right?
If I had won, it would have been even cooler.
You really have to do something so dangerous.
What?
There's nothing dangerous.
It's actually relieving stress after a game.
In the end, it's a fight that ends when one person falls.
I'm going to do it.
Don't worry.
I won't fall.
You're so childish.
Please listen to me.
Don't do that.
Listen to me one more time.
If you see me win, you'll think differently.
No, I'm going.
Just once.
Just once, please.
Why do you always do this to me?
Let's just go.
I'm holding it back because of you.
Goodbye.
Make sure to keep an eye on the guy.
Let's go.
Let's just go.
What should we do?
Let's go.
Please.
Hey, you little rabbit.
If you're not satisfied with the anchovy, come back here.
I'll be nice to you guys.
Did you get surprised?
But I'm sure it's because it's a fight.
Maybe it's because there's a match.
It doesn't hurt much.
If I had one person by my side, I'd have won 10 million percent.
Oh, my God.
Let's go.
I asked you to do that.
Let's just go.
Hey.
How can they just go when they say that to you?
Huh? Is it raining?
You could have avoided me at least once.
I wanted to protect you.
But is that such a big mistake?
Why are you so angry?
Didn't you expect this to happen?
You're all grown up, so you're just going to do something stupid.
How long are you going to be childish?
I'm childish?
Yeah, you're childish.
Why do you ignore everything I do?
Is it childish to protect what I value?
You're an adult. You shouldn't have done something so immature.
Yeah, I'm immature.
I didn't have any manners, so I tried to look good.
I was immature and childish, so I fell in love with you alone.
I was just being childish.
Then we should stop.
I told him to stop, but his body was getting away from Seon-ah.
Ko Jin-ho, I don't know anything.
I told him to stop, but he was talking childishly.
Yeah, I'm sorry that a stupid guy like me likes a good guy like you.
I didn't know at that time.
Women grow up faster than men.
The man realizes it after a long time.
Hello?
What? Did you fight?
He doesn't even want to regret it?
It's not the time to do this.
You should have comforted me.
They abandoned me, who was in sadness, on the way, and ran to Seon-ah.
But the re-education was the fastest.
You're a bad guy.
Are you okay?
Tae-hwan, who came to Gimpo Airport and couldn't meet Seon-ah, came to me, maybe he was just sad to go back to Jeju Island.
The person you contacted is only me?
Only me?
This is not right.
Tell the betrayers to take off.
They must be busy.
They are busy.
But I came here by plane to comfort you.
You, a friend like me, you...
Have a drink.
I should have recognized you then.
Stop it.
I love you.
Seon-ah!
Tae-hwan!
I feel better when I see nature.
Thank you.
As expected,
friends are good.
Seon-ah,
Jin-woo and you,
you guys might get back together.
But then,
I thought I would regret it for the rest of my life.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I'm sorry,
but I couldn't miss this opportunity.
I'm sorry.
So, you did 100% wrong.
If it was you, I wouldn't have been able to stand it.
You would have.
If it was you,
I would have run away even if you pushed me to fight.
I'm sorry.
The past love is inside me.
I told you not to die.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Come on.
You are the champion knight, Min Kyung-hoon.
I'll give you confidence in a really good place.
Ye-bi, you too.
Okay, my song.
I'll sing a song and go.
Don't cry, Byung-hoon.
I'm sorry.
Why is it so big?
What?
What is this soldier's welfare?
I don't think it's going to close.
I'm sorry.
My dad said that everyone has a place to go in times like this.
Put your heads together!
Get your heads together!
Attention!
Salute!
This bastard is out of his mind.
Are you going to wear a soldier's bracelet?
My youthful power is gone.
Seon-ah is gone.
Salute!
I'll see you right away.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No!
Then, you call out the name of the person you think of the most and run down.
Salute!
An Jung-bi, you bastard!
How about joining the exchange in Seoul?
I was actually a little disappointed that you failed the college entrance exam.
I think you want to come to Seoul, too.
That's true, but it's a little...
I do want you to be famous in Seoul, not in Gangwon-do.
It might not be a problem now, but if you get a lover and get married later,
one of the two might not be able to work.
Sung-bin, what kind of person do you want to be?
I'm a lawyer.
That's a job, not a job.
I want to be a lawyer.
A dream.
Isn't a job a dream?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
The Chippao typhoon butterfly has passed Okinawa and has been causing damage by spraying
200 millimeters of firewood per hour in Gangwon-do.
The typhoon is expected to spread a strong reaction and firewood at a maximum speed of 47.3 meters
and cause a greater damage.
Hello?
How many minutes?
Three minutes.
Ten minutes.
Sergeant Gu Jin-woo.
I have a favor to ask you.
I heard that the fire in our hometown is also very serious.
But?
I'm sorry, but I'd like to ask you to give me a call from your hometown.
Yes.
Is it your parents?
What?
Three minutes. No, one minute.
You're so slow.
Get down.
Get down!
Gu Jin-woo, are you crazy?
Gu Jin-woo!
I saw it.
Sergeant Gu Jin-woo.
I'll give you three minutes.
Thank you.
I'll call you later.
Yes, please come first.
Hello?
Hello? Oh Seon-ah?
Is Seon-ah here?
Jin-woo?
Where are you? Are you okay?
You're not going to move? You're not hurt?
I'm going to fall over.
Speak slowly.
Are you okay?
I'm not very okay, but
my family is all right.
Anyway, I'm fine.
I'll hang up now.
Thank you.
For caring.
This is it.
If you disappear, my memories will disappear.
You're good at talking.
You didn't call me on vacation.
I was afraid I'd be a hindrance to seeing Sung-bin.
Hindrance?
What kind of hindrance?
Didn't you two go out?
I've never been in a relationship.
Really?
Yeah. Who said that?
Then who else is dating?
Mind your own business.
I should have been nice to Sung-bin.
He's a good guy.
I don't know.
Sung-bin doesn't seem to like me.
What are you talking about?
He liked you so much.
The Oh Seon-ah that Sung-bin likes
seems a little different from me.
It's funny that you're saying this now,
but the person who liked me as I am
is the one who's been waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
I think you're the only one
who liked me as I am.
Jin-woo.
You know so well.
Why didn't you accept me?
I was just
scared.
People say that.
After dating,
the feelings of excitement disappear.
The beginning of a relationship
is the end of excitement.
Maybe I wanted you
to like me
for a long time.
You're so mean.
Wasn't it the same for you?
What about me?
That day in Namsan.
Why didn't you give me
the chance to answer?
I thought I'd be rejected.
So
I was afraid
I wouldn't be able to do what you like.
I was scared.
Jin-woo.
Thank you
for liking me.
Me too.
I like you.
I like
the time when I liked you.
You're my sunshine blue.
Just let me let shine through.
Every little second.
I feel so close to you.
Time flew by after I got discharged.
Most of them were busy with
getting a job, but there were
people who were dreaming.
This is really good.
Should I buy this?
Byung-joo got a job at a furniture company
to save his skills.
I don't know why,
but he became the salesman of the month.
Tae-hwan, who didn't get a chance
to play CC in Jeju University,
lost his dream in the air
in the year of the rat.
After hearing from his father
that the world of prosecutors will come,
he chose to become a prosecutor,
not a lawyer.
He's so unlucky.
I'm not a salesman.
I'm a salesman.
Cut, cut, cut!
Dong-hyun jumped into the K-pop industry
and lost his way.
Jisoo, who was a teacher
at the rooftop of the school,
became a choreographer.
This is the rice.
It's lemonade, and it's refreshing.
It doesn't taste like anything.
It was a girl group's dream,
but they lost their happiness
in a place close to the church.
How is it? This feeling?
I?
I don't know if I've become a great person,
but I started a great company.
Hello. Hello.
People said my webtoon was too childish
and posted bad comments
to increase the number of views,
so I became a popular writer.
D and D.
Great.
I'm a great person.
What is this?
I don't recommend it.
I got a call from the website.
When will it be uploaded?
I heard they'll give you a penalty if you're late again.
Yes, okay.
And I started drawing the next webtoon.
The main character is...
It's not Yang Bo-hyun.
Hello?
It's me.
Who?
Dad.
You should stop being busy.
It's been a while since I got a call.
But why are you so nervous?
What's going on?
Guess.
Are you going to confess now?
You're still the same.
Of course.
I'm a great person.
I can accept it if you want.
Then...
I'll really
confess.
We're going to hold a ceremony in a while.
The guests will be...
Jisoo.
I need a bed.
I'll make it cheap.
Come to Jeju Island.
When will the food be ready?
It's really good.
Let's send it like this.
I'm going to send it when my husband passes by.
Are you an elementary school kid?
You're not going to bless me.
I'm happy because I like you.
I hope you're happy with another man.
There's no such man in the world.
There's no such man.
Now, the most beautiful bride will come in.
Please give her a warm applause.
Today's main character is better than anyone else.
Bride entrance.
The bride is here.
She's here.
If Sungbin is wrong.
If a man truly loves a woman,
When she has a lover,
I sincerely wish you a long and happy life.
Congratulations!
Yes, that's good.
Now, the groom's bride kiss.
Applause for the bride!
Yes, kiss!
The men in the back, aren't you the police?
Your faces are so scary. Smile!
Yes, thank you.
Congratulations!
Let's take a picture together.
Sir, can we take one more picture?
We're friends.
No, we're not.
Okay.
One, two!
Okay, done!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Sir, how do you feel about marrying the most beautiful woman in the country?
It's like a dream.
I'll always live with a sincere heart.
Yes, that's why.
I'm so sorry to send you off like this.
Lastly, I'll give this bride a kiss.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I must be crazy.
But there are conditions.
You can do as much as you did to me.
What's that?
I won't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna stay right here my mind.
I'm never gonna let you down.
I'm gonna let my heart stay for you.
I'm never gonna feel alone.
I'm gonna be there for you.
I'm gonna let my heart stay for you.
Oh, I see it's you.
I wanna be with you.
I wanna be with you my love.
The time I say I need you now.
Tell me everything, cuz I'll be next to you.
I'm gonna stay right here my mind.
I'm never gonna let you down.
I'm gonna let my heart stay for you now.
I'm never gonna feel alone.
I'm gonna be there for you.
I'm gonna let my heart stay for you now.
I'm never gonna be alone.
I'm gonna be there for you.
I'm gonna let my heart stay for you.
I'm never gonna feel alone.
I really like you!
I love you, Oh Sun Woo!
Thank you for liking me.
I really liked you too.
I will.
I hope so.
The boy we liked back then was our dream and youth.
I'm still dreaming of that dream and I will never wake up.
I thought of you.
I thought of you every day.
The feelings that I couldn't tell you.
The feelings that I couldn't reach you.
We will keep our beautiful fluttering feelings.
Your smile in my eyes shined.
I was also shining when I looked at you.
Sometimes like moonlight, like summer night light.
We were colored blue and we liked each other.
Goodbye.
We are now far apart.
I drew you in my heart.
I always drew you.
Goodbye.
I thought of your true self who protected me.
I always thought of you.
I couldn't tell you.
The feelings that I couldn't reach you.
We will keep our beautiful love.
Your smile in my eyes shined.
I was also shining when I looked at you.
Sometimes like moonlight, like summer night light.
We were colored blue and we liked each other.
I know we can't go back.
It was pure then.
All the moments we spent together are precious.
Even if time passes and the future is lost, we will never forget.
If we cried as much as we were in pain, would we have cried it out?
We are like a movie, like the old days.
If we go back, I'll just hold you with a smile.
Thank you for watching!