What are you here for?
Mom, does he not like me too?
No, Dong-seok has just gotten really shy.
He sometimes can't speak at all
even if he wants to.
It's not because he doesn't like you,
so let's understand him, okay?
Hey, wait for me!
Yu-bin looks so excited
for the first time in a while.
She's been down lately.
She's been anxious because she thought
I've been keeping a close eye on her.
And not going to her academy classes
has been making her nervous too.
She stopped going to her academy
for quite some time.
I don't think studying
is her top priority right now.
We came to see a doctor
because Yu-bin kept on lying.
When I scolded her, she started crying
and said she didn't know either.
Then slowly…
she started to believe in her own lies.
That's when I realized
something's gone terribly wrong.
I thought
raising children was all about
standing firm and being strong.
But it turns out that was just hubris.
Nothing turns out the way I want it to.
They said Dong-seok has selective mutism.
I must've…
given him too much stress.
I was so excited
when I learned how smart he was
and ended up pushing him so hard.
I wanted to crush everyone
who used to make fun of my boy.
I never realized
that he was festering on the inside.
Don't you now get
why adults say that raising a child
is the most difficult job in the world?
You and I both…
are learning things the hard way.
EPISODE 12: CAN ADULTS BECOME FRIENDS
WITHOUT MOTIVES TOO?
Don't just play video games
at home just because it's winter.
Make sure to exercise
and don't forget to study either.
-Yes, ma'am!
All right, let's pack our bags.
I'll see you again after the break.
-Okay!
Yes, I was the bully in high school!
-Really?
-Yes, but it's not like I did bad things
or take money from other kids.
I just knew how to fight.
Seriously?
-Really?
-Is that true?
Ladies, look.
My gosh, what is that?
-She's not joking.
-Well…
Are you for real?
There used to be a group of girls called
"Bond Girl" in the school next to ours.
It's a battle scar from
when the two gangs duked it out.
And get this, it was 17 on 2.
-What? 17?
-Please, I don't believe it.
-I wasn't part of the 17. I was the 2!
-Gosh, please.
-You sure it wasn't seven on two?
-You don't believe me?
-No, we don't.
-I swear!
-You were the two?
-I was the two!
Are you serious?
I'm serious. So then I was like…
That school bully.
Does she think being a bully
in the past is something to brag about?
She has no decency.
I know, right?
Why are they even interested in her?
Then who wants to be
the leader of my fan club?
Let me do it.
But honestly, you were quite wild
back then too, weren't you?
You used all kinds of
wild swear words the other day.
Gosh, what?
Hey, if someone is insulting me,
that would piss me off
and I would want to fight back.
I was so shocked that I don't even
remember anything from that day.
But when you spoke in a dialect,
it did come off pretty strong.
Dialect?
Are you prejudiced against people
from the countryside?
You're basically being racist,
do you know that?
-When was I ever racist?
-Yes, I wasn't squeaky clean.
I ranked in the top-tier
university entrance exams in my province.
What did you rank on your exams in Seoul?
Eun-pyo, aren't you coming today?
No, we were planning to go,
but he got scared.
It's going to be the last time everyone in
their class gets together for a playdate.
It must be rough to make him lunch
separately every day.
I don't even know what to make him.
Hey, did the class president go?
Byeon Chun-hui?
Eun-pyo, she hasn't shown up
to places like this in a while.
Jeez, we all voted her, but she's not
even organizing the meet-ups.
Why do you ask?
I was just asking.
Chun-hui, I'm making
fried rice omelet right now.
Do you want to come over
if you haven't had lunch yet?
Sounds great.
You go up the stairs like this
and collect the coins.
Then you can use those coins
to buy new characters.
Got it?
By the way,
why haven't you been saying
anything this entire time?
Oh, he said it's hard
for him to talk sometimes.
It's like how I have
a hard time not telling lies.
It's similar to that.
I see.
Anyway, so if you go up like this,
you'll get to 600.
At 600, you get the spaceship…
It would've been a simple lunch for you,
but it turned into
a big thing because of us.
It's fine. Food tastes better
when everyone shares.
Plus, it's the first day of winter break
and I feel bad for the kids.
Guys, let's all have this
before we have lunch.
-Okay.
-Here you go.
-Don't forget to say thank you.
-Thank you.
-Here.
-Here, Dong-ju.
-Thank you.
You guys are eating so well.
Eat as much as you want.
-Okay.
Thanks for the meal.
Oh, that's right.
Let's try the wine you brought.
Cheers.
This is delicious!
Don't drink too much of it though.
You're a lot to handle when you get drunk.
Mom, it tastes so good.
The sausage is really good, too.
-You like it?
-Yes.
-Eat as much as you want.
-Okay.
Eun-pyo is having a hard time
because she feels so bad for him.
But Dong-seok is not getting any better.
It's rough.
Don't worry, Jae-ung.
Kids get sick and then get better
in just one day
like nothing happened.
Also, kids that give their parents
a rough time turn out better.
How do you know so well
when you don't even have a kid?
Why wouldn't I know? I'm living proof.
My mom used to pray every day
so that I wouldn't become a gangster.
And look at me now.
I'm a government employee.
Gangsters and detectives
aren't that different though.
Your mom never knew that, did she?
-Don't you dare talk about my mom.
-I'm right, though.
You're a total gangster
when you catch bad guys.
At least I don't look like a gangster.
Whatever, forget about it.
Right.
Did you ever check up on that thing?
Oh, that lady?
She works at Red Sun in Daewe-dong.
And there's definitely
something fishy going on.
She was questioned by the police
for some drug charges a while ago.
But she tested clean,
so they just let her go with a warning.
When was that?
It was two years ago
when the joint task force was formed.
They did shake down the entire network.
But it's possible that they have
a new supply chain in place by now.
I told you. I got blackout drunk
and fell down the stairs.
Then why did you run away
instead of getting patched up?
Because the punk I was drinking with
threatened to kill me
and came to the emergency room.
Would it hurt less
if I get stabbed in the emergency room?
Who gave you a ride to the hospital?
Someone who worked there.
A coworker who worked the rooms with you?
Sure, maybe?
I don't really remember.
Why are you guys asking me
all these stupid questions?
Is it a crime that I didn't stay
and get treated?
Ms. Shin.
We're not after the people
who took the drugs.
We're looking for the sellers.
I think you know what I'm talking about.
Sellers are never the type of people
who want to lose track
of their customers.
All right.
Please mull it over.
I hope you make the right decision.
JUNG JAE-UNG
Have a good day.
Go ahead
and investigate everyone
related to that girl.
Yes, sir.
What?
Won-tae!
The cops were just here.
They asked all sorts of questions.
What exactly did they ask you?
They said to call them because they're
after the sellers, not the buyers.
Darn it.
You didn't say anything stupid, did you?
Are you insane?
Hello.
Sit tight for now.
Damn it, you're lucky
I don't stomp you out right now.
Hey.
Hey! Clean that up.
So what do you want?
Well…
I was just wondering what you thought
of laying low for a little while.
-Won-tae.
-Yes, sir.
Is it that hard to get some product?
Sorry?
All I asked you was to get a new supplier
so I could write off
the rest of your debt.
Why the hell are you talking about
what the cops are up to?
Wait.
Are you trying to pull a fast one on me
to try and wriggle your way out of this?
I would never do anything like that.
Then why are you trying
to get out of this?
It's the girl that keeps
coming up with all these excuses.
Jeez, this punk…
How did you manage to
prey on girls when you're like this?
What do you have your brain for?
She has a lot to lose.
What do you think would scare her most?
Your very existence
is the most damage to her.
Are you still not getting it?
I am.
Don't just call her.
Go out there and make things happen.
Yes, sir.
If you're done,
then get going, Mr. Won-tae.
Yes, sir. I'll get going.
Is that as fast as you can run?
Mom, when you spin around really fast,
the crystals on the skirt
sparkle like crazy.
It's so pretty when that happens.
So can you buy one of those tutus for me?
I want one that has even more sparkly
beads than the one that Seo-hyeon has.
Is ballet really that fun?
You literally started learning it.
Yes, of course. I get to be pretty like
a princess and it's healthy for me too.
How about you, Yeong-bin?
Do you like your orchestra class?
It's fun.
If I'm lucky, I might even get to play
a solo pretty soon.
Really?
When did you get so good?
I didn't even know.
Let's hurry up guys.
I'll cook something delicious for you.
Okay.
Yeong-bin really likes playing the violin.
Mom, I like the violin too.
I know you like it too.
You're not going to light that, are you?
You're not trying to
smoke that here, right?
What is it, Mom?
Mom…
And this is a non-smoking area,
so you can't smoke here.
That's all.
-I won't light it then.
-Good.
Put that in your pocket.
You can't smoke here.
I said I won't.
Damn it.
Enjoy.
You can cut it
on your own, right Yeong-bin?
Yes.
I'll cut it for you Yu-bin.
Where are you, girl?
Aren't you coming home today?
Yu-bin, eat up.
Thank you for this meal.
Why are you ignoring my calls?
Is this really how you're going to be?
Should I just go talk
to your old man directly?
I'm on a trip.
I'll call you later.
Mom, where are we going now?
Right…
We're going on a trip.
Then why did we go grocery shopping?
Because we're camping.
Really? No way.
Wake up, Yeong-bin.
Mom said we're going camping.
Aren't you excited?
-Really?
-Yes.
But why are we going camping
all of a sudden?
I don't know. That's what mom said.
Hurry up and eat, Yu-bin.
Eat up.
Okay.
28 MISSED CALLS
17 UNREAD TEXT MESSAGES
The plane is now landing.
Dong-ju, I'm worried you might
spill your milk on the couch.
Oh gosh.
It's okay, we can wipe it up like this.
Mom, we're on winter break,
but how come we're not going anywhere?
We'll go when your dad
gets some time off of work, okay?
When's that?
Dong-seok never plays with me.
Hey, Chun-hui.
Hey.
What are you up to?
I'm just at home.
What's up?
Well…
If you're not busy,
do you want to come here and join us?
Where's that?
We're at a campsite in Gapyeong.
If it's possible,
could you also grab my down jacket,
some underwear for the kids,
and a phone charger from my place?
What do you say?
Mom, we made snowmen!
Be careful.
Okay.
-You did such a good job.
-Right?
We made snowmen
for everyone in our family.
Mom, is Dong-seok's family
not going to join us?
Well…
I'm not too sure. Maybe something came up.
That's Dong-seok!
Dong-seok!
-Hey, guys.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Hey.
-Hey, Dong-ju.
Hello.
We already made some snowmen,
but let's go make it again.
You came.
Hello.
Hey.
We put them over there.
What's with the camping all of a sudden?
I just needed some fresh air.
You can't be dressed like that
in a place like this.
Thanks.
It was a spur of the moment thing,
so I really didn't come prepared at all.
I never knew you had that kind of side.
-Thanks for coming.
-Don't mention it.
The boys were on the verge of
being really bored.
Gosh, it's so nice out here.
And the air is so fresh too.
-We're right over there.
-Oh, right over there?
The kids are going to love it here.
It's so white.
Be careful.
Careful, kids.
Watch your step, guys.
Follow Dong-seok and don't run.
But why did you ask us to come
instead of coming with their dad?
I see.
You guys fought, right?
No.
We never really do
a lot of things together.
We kind of stick to our responsibilities.
You're kidding.
Every time I've seen him,
he looks like such a kind man.
I guess he's just good
at selling that image.
I guess things have a way
of turning out like that as life goes on.
Everyone focuses on their own work,
so they don't burden the other one.
I once heard someone say
that you should never tell your husband
about your hopes and dreams.
Why is that?
Because he's not interested
in them in the slightest.
Gosh.
How did the two of you meet?
I never told you?
No one told you anything either?
Well…
I wanted to get married to a doctor,
so I asked someone to introduce me to one.
You know I'm a materialistic person.
So…
there never was any spark
or anything between us.
We just got married because there wasn't
anything wrong with either of us.
That's why we're still not that close.
Unlike you guys.
Please, we fight all the time too.
Detectives' wives
have all kinds of gripes.
They always work overtime
or have to stay overnight.
That's still a good thing.
You're in a healthy relationship
if you're upset that he's not coming home.
I recently…
went over to Jin-ha's place
because Dong-seok
said that he missed Henry.
I think there was a lot
that I misunderstood about her.
Jin-ha really meant it
when she said she liked me.
But because of
my twisted inferiority complex,
I could never see her true feelings.
I think maybe…
I might've been doing
the same thing to you.
Maybe I had
such a distorted view of things
that I couldn't see anything properly.
That's what's been on my mind lately.
No.
The only person who couldn't see
anything properly…
was me.
My anxiety and greed
are what got you into all that trouble.
I was aware of it,
but I didn't have the courage
to set things straight. I'm sorry.
But the thing is,
I'm still scared.
I'm scared that it might've been me
that made Jin-ha kill herself.
I'm scared that it might've been
those last scathing words
that I threw at her
that pushed her over the edge.
I keep trying to forget it.
But I don't think it'll ever go anywhere.
With that being said…
Do you think
you can tell me what happened
that night?
I want you to come over right now!
I haven't slept in three days.
It's not even that far.
Why can't you come?
Why are you acting like this?
-I told you I don't do that anymore.
-No, you have to come over right now!
Or I'm going to call the cops.
I'm going to tell everyone that
I saw you and Su-in's father at a hotel.
So you better come over right now!
Eun-pyo, the thing is…
In life,
knowing the truth
can be like poison sometimes.
It can be better to live your life
without knowing the whole story.
The one thing
I can tell you…
is that it wasn't because of you.
That's one thing you should know.
Chun-hui, are you sleeping?
No, why?
Thanks for inviting us today.
Don't mention it.
Honestly,
things are starting to
fade little by little.
It felt like things were bound to get
better someday, but at the same time,
I wondered when
and if it would even be possible.
Thanks to you,
I was able to forget about everything
and enjoy myself today like before.
How can our paths
be so intertwined like this?
Even after going through
all those things together,
we're right here next to each other.
I know, right?
Your existence
is the biggest comfort to me
than anyone else's.
I'm really bad, aren't I?
No.
I feel the same way.
Good night, Chun-hui.
Good night.
Chun-hui, did the kids say
there were going somewhere?
They're probably playing out
in the front or something.
Dong-seok!
Dong-ju!
Yu-bin!
Yeong-bin!
Where did they go?
Excuse me, did you happen to see
four kids passing by?
-No, I didn't see anyone.
-I see.
Excuse me, did you happen to see
four kids walking together?
-Did you see anything?
-No.
-We haven't seen any kids.
-Yes, we haven't.
Thank you.
Hey.
Chun-hui, are the kids back?
They're not there?
Okay, I'll start looking around.
-Okay.
-All right.
Enjoy your food.
-The fishcakes taste really good.
-Does it?
I'm going to have another one.
-Can I have more soup, please?
-All right.
Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
What are you kids doing here?
-Are you their mother?
-Yes.
The kids were just staring at us,
so I figured we should invite them in
to have a bite to eat.
Oh, dear…
Were you worried that you lost them?
-I'm sorry.
-No, it's fine.
Come here right now.
Quickly!
-I've been looking all over for you.
-Guys, your mom's here.
-Thank you.
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
-Bye, kids.
You should've told me
where you were going.
Bye, guys.
Guys. Where in the world did you go?
They walked over to another campsite
to get a bite to eat
because we were still sleeping.
Gosh, you should've woken us up.
Kim Yeong-bin!
You're the oldest one here.
You should've told me
where you were going.
I was so scared!
-Hurry up, let's go.
-Let's go.
It's time to head home.
They said we just need to
put this stuff inside the tent.
Okay.
Mom, I can't breathe too well.
What?
Since when?
Dong-ju, what did you eat?
What did you eat?
I told you not to go around
eating candy from strangers.
Yu-bin, where did you get this?
The lady from the other tent
gave it to us to eat.
Did Dong-ju have one of these?
Yes.
Does Dong-ju have a nut allergy?
It's the macarons!
The main ingredient
in macarons is almonds!
Oh, no. Dong-ju!
-Dong-ju, are you okay?
-Dong-ju.
What do we do?
-Did you bring a Jext pen?
-Yes.
Dong-ju, it's going to be okay.
Dong-ju, it's going to be okay, all right?
Don't cry guys, it's going to be okay.
It's okay, Dong-ju.
I switched bags before I came.
What do I do?
-What do we do?
-What do I do?
Call 911.
-Everyone, we have to get to the hospital!
-Dong-ju!
Dong-ju!
Hello, is this 911?
We're located at
Healing Moonlight Camping Grounds,
and my son is having an allergic reaction
and is having trouble breathing.
Please send an ambulance
as fast as you can.
How fast can you get here?
The campground is far from here.
-So it'll probably take about 20 minutes.
-No.
My kid might die
if he has to wait that long.
What's going on?
-Okay, just hold on.
-Let's call the insurance company first.
-Jeez, don't talk nonsense.
-It wasn't my fault, okay?
There's an accident ahead of us.
I don't think
you'll be able to take this road.
Are there any detours we can take?
If you head back,
it's nothing but mountains.
You have to make it
to the bottom of the mountain.
Dong-ju.
Dong-ju! You have to stay with me.
Wake up, Dong-ju!
Chun-hui, what do we do? Dong-ju, wake up!
What do we do? Dong-ju, wake up!
What are we going to do?
Dong-ju, wake up!
Dong-ju!
Chun-hui, what are we going to do?
Dong-ju! What are we going to do?
Dong-ju!
Chun-hui!
Why are you parking the car?
Dong-ju, you have to stay with me!
-Get out of the car right now.
-What are you doing?
You have to stay awake, Dong-ju!
Dong-ju!
Please stay awake, Dong-ju!
Dong-ju. What do I do?
Gosh, what do I do? Dong-ju!
Dong-ju, look at Mommy.
-Dong-ju.
-Hurry and get out of the car!
Dong-ju.
Dong-ju…
Are you okay, Dong-ju?
Have a small snack.
HE COLLIDES WITH THE HIKER
Thank you.
What is it?
Is there something you want to say?
No.
There's just so much dust here.
Goodness.
Why haven't you been going to
Sangkemo these days?
Well…
We just picked a new leader
for the seventh term,
so all I have to do
is sit in as an advisor.
I also figured
that I've been neglecting you lately.
You also need to focus on
writing your script.
I told you I didn't want to succeed
with the sacrifice of others.
I don't need anything from you,
so let's just focus on our own lives.
Sure.
HIKER: IT’S FINE. DO YOU LIKE CANDY?
Gosh, my head.
LIKE I WAS NEVER HERE AT ALL
SCREENPLAY AND DIRECTOR: OH GEON-U
SAVE
SHUTTING DOWN
-Are you leaving, Geon-u?
-Yes, I'm going to be late.
I'm having a meeting with the actors,
so I'll be having some drinks too.
Which actors?
Song Hae-seon.
My goodness.
I hope it goes well.
If they want to meet up in person,
it has to be a good sign, right?
One second.
I wonder if she'll be able to truly grasp
the profundity of your creative world.
Have a good meeting.
Yeong-mi.
I've been really
sensitive lately, haven't I?
I'll be back.
SWIPE THE VIDEO TO FAST-FORWARD OR REWIND
WELCOME
SCRIPT
Jin-ha?
EMERGENCY ROOM
Thank you, Chun-hui.
For saving Dong-ju.
I used to be a nurse.
But I never told anyone.
I didn't want people to gossip about it.
A doctor and nurse…
It's obvious what people would talk about.
I hesitated back there
because I didn't want you to find out.
But that almost got Dong-ju killed.
So you don't have to thank me.
No, I'll be thankful to you
for the rest of my life.
That's already twice now
that you've saved Dong-ju's life.
Eun-pyo.
What happened?
Is Dong-ju okay?
Yes, he's okay.
How did he end up eating peanuts?
And why didn't you tell me
you went on a trip so far out?
Do you know how shocked I was?
Hello.
I'm going to head out first.
Okay. Thank you, Chun-hui.
It's not like I did anything.
I'll see you back in Seoul.
Get inside.
Why aren't you going inside?
Are you now bringing
gangsters into our house?
How much do you owe them?
How much do you owe them
for gangsters to come to our house?
Quiet down, damn it.
How can I calm down
in a situation like this?
I begged you to please…
I begged you to stop gambling!
You're so damn loud.
I can't get any sleep!
Damn it.
Hey.
This is all your fault.
What?
You're the one who killed someone
and cut off a perfect way to make money.
That's how everything you do
ends up though, isn't it?
Is that just
how you were born or something?
Damn it.
Jeez.
Did you…
know about that?
Are you crazy?
If you knew about it this entire time,
how come you acted like
you didn't know anything?
Hey.
How many times have I told you?
You're responsible
for cleaning up your own mess.
Then what about me?
What about me?
Why do I have to be responsible
for your gambling debts?
Why do I deserve that?
You can't even do that for me?
I'm living with a nurse
who killed someone.
You're the one who killed that patient.
You're the one who killed him!
Why are you acting
like it wasn't you all this time?
You're talking nonsense.
Just go get some money, okay?
Because if you don't,
both of our lives are over.
I only gave him the anti-anesthetic.
I double-checked and even triple-checked
before administering it.
Ms. Byeon.
You administered Vecaron, Ms. Byeon.
You mixed the two of them up.
Why are you acting like that?
No, I didn't!
I only gave him the anti-anesthetic!
Aren't you the one who gave him Vecaron
and framing me for it?
You're trying to implicate
a completely innocent bystander!
Do I look like an easy target to you?
Am I some kind of joke to you?
Are you serious right now?
I didn't!
I only gave him the anti-anesthetic!
Somebody say something!
You all know that I really only gave him
the anti-anesthetic.
I really only gave him
the anti-anesthetic. It wasn't me.
It really wasn't me.
Ji-yeon…
What do you want?
Okay, fine.
I'll…
I'll take…
the blame for you.
Instead of ruining the life
of a high and mighty doctor,
the hospital would rather have
a lowly nurse to cover for them
since it's much less of a risk.
But…
I have one condition.
Gosh.
I knew it.
How much do you want?
Marriage.
What?
This is crazy.
Hey.
Do you even want to get married to me?
Yes.
Why?
I want to take this chance…
to take you down with me.
And if you don't marry me,
I'm going to do everything
I can to make your life a living hell.
Hey…
How did you and the neighbor lady
make up all of a sudden?
The kids get along with each other.
Dong-seok?
We ran into them at the clinic.
The clinic?
What clinic?
Apparently, Yu-bin has
a habit of lying all the time.
Oh, I see.
So that's why…
I guess every family has their own
trouble when raising a kid.
It sure isn't easy.
I'm off to bed.
Chun-hui, did you get some rest?
Thank you so much for today.
CHUN-HUI, DID YOU GET SOME REST?
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR TODAY.
In life,
knowing the truth
can be like poison sometimes.
It can be better to live your life
without knowing the whole story.
Jeez.
What are you doing in here?
What are you doing?
You know I don't like you coming into
my office without my permission.
What is it?
I see.
You're wondering what
the actors said, aren't you?
They're all a bunch of idiots!
Of course, they're dying
to play a role in my movie.
They literally begged me like dogs
because they wanted me to cast them.
You should've been there
to see it, Yeong-mi.
That wasn't what you wanted to ask me?
Darn it.
What is it then?
I see.
Is it because of the kids?
Is that really even a big issue though?
Just as you said,
sometimes a dad can get scary
when he's disciplining his kids.
Isn't that the proper way
to raise children?
Why did you lock them in the bathroom?
Why did you throw the cup
and act like you didn't know about it?
How could you do those things
when you know how hard I work
to lay a healthy
groundwork for my children?
A healthy groundwork for your children?
Jeez, I'm really sick of your attitude
of trying to be like a virtuous person.
I've been with you for years
and I'm still not used to it!
Yeong-mi!
Can't you just speak normally?
Who said you could look at my computer?
Is that really important right now?
What in the world is this?
I told you before.
That woman was my muse
and the subject of my articles.
And you're my companion,
compatriot, and support system.
A muse is just a muse.
Something like a spirit
that exists to inspire my work.
And now, you get to be
the wife of a genius director.
Isn't it exhilarating
just thinking about it?
What kind of ridiculous nonsense is that?
What are you saying?
Did you…
sleep with her?
I did.
I slept with her.
Did this woman…
die because of you?
How would I know?
But actually, a woman
like her deserves to die.
You're also forgetting that
all of this is already in the past.
That woman is dead and gone, okay?
And Yeong-mi, can you give up on me?
You're going to be an intellectual woman
who supported the greatest director.
Do you want to give that up
and become a divorcée again?
No.
You could never do that. You know why?
Because the one thing that's most
important to you is your reputation.
Let's look into the period
of Belle Époque in the next class.
That will be all for today's lecture.
Good work everyone.
-Thank you.
-Good work.
-You too.
Do you have any loose change?
No, I don't think so.
That means I can only get one then.
-Oh right, did you hear the rumor?
-About what?
-About Seo Jin-ha, the artist.
-Of course, I heard.
She committed suicide
because she had an affair, right?
Yes. Then did you also see the naked photo
of her that the guy spread around?
I haven't seen it myself
but Seong Min-jun says he saw it.
Maybe the assistant
only let the boys see it.
Gosh, that's crazy though.
How could he do something like that?
Tell me about it.
So nobody knows who he is?
No one knows.
Or maybe they do know
and they're just not telling anyone.
Excuse me…
What are you talking about?
GWANGHWAMUN
Jin-ha's photos are all over the Internet.
You're aware that
this is a serious crime, right?
It's a serious criminal offense that
falls under defamation of the deceased.
Just tell me
where you got that photo from.
Is he her boyfriend or something?
I heard she had an affair.
Please handle this as soon as possible.
I don't want my wife's personal life
to be disclosed any further.
Do you know Lee Eun-pyo?
What's going on?
You said you'd take care of it.
What are you trying to do to the deceased?
Honestly, I don't think you should
get yourself involved in this issue.
Stop. You're the one
who's trying to complicate things.
Don't you think he would want
to keep only beautiful memories of her?