WECHILD COUNSELING CENTER
Do you want to pick out a toy
you'd like to play with?
There are a lot of fun toys.
How about you go and pick something out?
Isn't there anything
that you want to play with?
-Dad, open this for me.
-All right.
PRESSURED, HATE, BORED
LONELY, SAD
Can you take a look
and pick out one of these cards
that best describes
how you're feeling, Dong-seok?
He's a very bright child.
He's in the top one percent
among his peers.
Gifted children tend to be as sensitive
as the level of their intelligence.
So you must have had a much
harder time raising him than most parents.
Usually, many parents of gifted children
overlook their children.
Being intellectually gifted doesn't mean
that their emotional development
is also at an adult level.
It's no easy task to cope
with that kind of imbalance.
So what about Dong-seok?
We can't be sure
what external factor caused this
but it seems that he's suffering from
a conversion disorder due to PTSD.
In his case, it seems to be manifesting
itself as selective mutism.
But ma'am.
Why is this happening all of a sudden?
We're not the type of parents
who abuse our children.
I raise them with so much love.
It may be because he's a gifted child.
Being born with such a gift is not
the same as hitting the lottery.
Gifted children have to endure
the frustration that an adult
might experience when they are forced
to only interact with children.
If they express their frustration,
then they're labeled as being a show-off.
It's hard for them to find
friends that they can relate to.
But how many people do you think
can live without any friends?
Without the proper emotional support
in times like that,
they are emotionally damaged
more than others.
Jae-ung.
Do you think…
I've done something wrong?
What did I do wrong?
Move, Dong-seok.
Mom, hold me instead of Dong-seok.
How come you're not holding me?
Dong-ju, it's dangerous.
Sit properly in your booster seat.
No! Tell Dong-seok to move!
I want you to hold me!
Dong-seok's older than me, and I'm a baby!
So Dong-seok should be sitting by himself!
Your brother is also a baby!
Your brother…
is also a baby.
Your brother
is still a baby to me.
He's a baby.
Your brother is still a baby to me.
EPISODE 11
THE SINS WE DID NOT FIND OUT ABOUT
Father!
Father…
EUNPYO PAINT
Father!
Father…
Father, what do I do?
What do I do?
Father…
Dong-seok!
-Dong-seok!
-Eun-pyo, no!
-No!
Dong-seok!
-Dong-seok!
-It's dangerous!
-No!
-Dong-seok!
Dong-seok!
Eun-pyo.
Hey, Eun-pyo.
Dong-seok…
Lee Eun-pyo. Snap out of it.
Dong-seok.
Eun-pyo, wake up.
Dong-seok!
Were you having a nightmare?
Dong-seok…
What kind of dream was it?
Eun-pyo.
Dong-seok…
was inside a burning paint shop.
And I had…
no idea.
It's all my fault.
I didn't know what was going on with him
and I was just happy about everything.
-It's not your fault.
-Then whose fault is it?
Even you told me
I was pushing him so hard.
Sorry.
But…
no matter how much I think about it,
I can't come up with an explanation.
Could it really be because of
how much I was pushing him?
Is that really it?
Do you think
maybe something happened
to him at the academy?
The kids could've ostracized him.
There's no other explanation
for why he would suddenly
be like this, don't you think so?
I'm positive that there's something
we're just not thinking of.
I'm sure he'll start talking
if we find the reason.
Yes, I'm sure he will.
He'll be right as rain in no time, right?
After his appearance on Genius Kids Show,
he received a lot of attention
and I'm sure that came
with a lot of jealousy.
But those types of emotional battles
are commonplace at academies like here.
I understand that it may be upsetting,
but I'm sure we're not
responsible for this.
He's at a much more
advanced level than his peers
and that sometimes caused difficulties
in getting along with his friends,
but more than that…
Couldn't it be because of his academies?
Maybe they pressured him too much.
I mean, he was always doing
homework even during recess,
so when I asked him why,
he said he'd be in a lot of trouble
with his academy teachers if he didn't.
You're flattering us.
It's not because of us.
It's that Jun-u performed very well.
All we did was point him
in the proper direction.
Yes?
Of course. Come in.
Yes.
He's burned out.
But it happened so fast.
Usually, if it happens fast,
it happens around 5th or 6th grade.
What do you mean by burned out?
As kids start to pick up
the pace of their studies,
some of them start
to lose touch with reality.
That means they're susceptible to stress,
so you'll have to find another plan.
If you run the risk
of the kids burning out,
why would you push them so hard?
We can't tell them not to do anything
just because they could be burned out.
But Dong-seok was following your guidance
and that's how he stopped talking.
As someone who was responsible
for his education,
don't you feel any guilt at all?
I'm sorry, but I think you're getting
something wrong here, ma'am.
Why are you trying to force
that responsibility onto us?
We're responsible for their results,
not for them to build their characters.
And are you saying
that you weren't pushing him?
How about you ask yourself
who is responsible for this whole--
Then are you saying all of this is
the mother's fault for wanting too much?
You said you were an expert!
What you're doing is taking advantage
of parents who are ignorant of education!
All right.
I understand that you're trying
to skirt the responsibility.
Either way, I think you should find
your own way to educate him.
I'd like you to leave now.
I regret being ignorant enough
to have trusted you as an educator.
I hope you start being honest
and start calling yourself a salesman
instead of an education expert.
My mom and dad
both graduated from Harvard.
-Come on!
-Nonsense!
-Don't you know that my dad's a doctor?
My mom's a doctor too,
but she only stopped working
because she had to raise us.
I didn't want to say anything about this,
but my grandpa's actually
the director of Eulju Hospital.
They told me all I had to do was
become a doctor and inherit the hospital.
I don't believe any of that.
All she does is lie.
What?
You guys will only end up
going to community college.
I'm on a different level than you guys.
The driver overheard their conversation
and felt that he needed
to make a recording.
She was obviously coming up with lies
and he was concerned that the other kids
might eventually start to exclude her.
Kim Yu-bin.
When did I ever tell you
that I was a doctor?
Why do you keep lying?
No one is going to be friends
with you if you keep lying like that.
You said you graduated from a good school.
That means you graduated from Harvard.
Then what about grandpa?
Why did you say
he was the director of a hospital?
Grandpa has been
bedridden this entire time!
You saw him yourself the other day!
I don't know.
I don't know why I keep lying.
I want to stop lying,
but they just keep on coming out.
I can't help myself.
Okay, so what is it?
So are you saying she's insane or what?
Watch your words, she could be listening.
Is she a pathological liar or something?
Well, good job.
You pushed them so hard
and now one of them is a liar.
Look what happened
after looking down on me like that.
Is this the result
that you've come up with?
Is putting all the blame on me
going to solve anything?
That's why I'm trying to
talk about it together.
Why are you asking me to help you
clean up the mess you made?
You're pissing me off.
Damn it.
This is so annoying.
PATHOLOGICAL LYING IS THE CHRONIC
BEHAVIOR OF COMPULSIVE OR HABITUAL LYING
Damn it.
Welcome, sir.
You came without getting any sleep?
-Is there still a game going on?
-Of course, sir.
-That's five million won.
-Thanks.
-I hope you win big, sir.
-Thank you.
Mom.
What is it?
Am I going insane?
Come over here, Yu-bin.
It's not like that.
Your dad just got angry and said
some things that he didn't mean.
But…
Let's find out why you keep lying.
There's bound to be a solution, okay?
Okay.
It's fine.
My girl. Come here.
Gosh, my baby.
Can anyone recommend
a good pediatric psychiatrist?
I think my child has tic disorders.
NEWS FEED
WEChild Clinic is the most famous
one in the neighborhood.
Thank you.
It's not easy looking up things like this
and I'm struggling.
I feel like it's all my fault
that my child is having a hard time.
I totally understand you.
When a child runs into trouble,
all of the fingers seem to
point back toward the mother.
Either way,
it's a mom's job to take care
of their children until the very end.
Don't give up.
Dong-seok, what are you doing here?
Jung Dong-seok. Open the door.
Didn't I tell you not to lock the door?
Open the door this instant!
Jung Dong-seok!
What's going on?
Where is he?
Dong-seok!
What do you think you're doing right now?
Eun-pyo.
Dong-seok.
Let's get out of the closet first.
Daddy's going to hold you.
All right.
TOP MATH
When did you finish this workbook?
Have you been staying up
at night to finish this?
I said you didn't have to study
this kind of stuff anymore!
Stop it!
Why are you shouting at him?
He's scared enough.
Everyone stop it!
It's so loud I can't sleep at all!
I want to sleep!
This side.
Yu-bin, do you know
where we're going today?
Yes.
Be honest when answering
the psychiatrist's questions.
Okay?
Let's go.
Mom, I have to pee.
Take your shoes off.
-Hello.
You're just a bit early.
Mom, I want to eat a snack.
Snacks!
Okay.
Mom, let's eat some snacks.
-I want some tasty snacks.
-All right, jeez.
This one or this one?
-Pick one out for yourself too, Dong-seok.
-This one or this one?
-Walnuts.
-You can only pick out one each.
We have an appointment for Kim Yu-bin.
-At 2 p.m., right?
-Yes.
-You can head right in.
-Thank you.
Only pick one.
We have to eat dinner later.
I don't think
this is different from that one.
Do you want something too, Dong-seok?
How about orange juice?
Pick one. Are you done picking?
It seems like he was privately solving
problems from his workbook every night.
That difficult workbook
was solved in its entirety.
He barely slept because of it
and yet he still begs me
to take him back to the academy.
The academy pushed him so hard, but
he wants to go to the academy so badly.
I have no idea why he's acting like this.
It seems like he's been brainwashed
by the academy that he has to study hard.
Trying to stop him does nothing.
What should I do?
It's only expected that he would be
nervous after stepping down the path
he's traveled down for so long.
But I don't think that's the only reason.
What do you mean?
MOM'S WISH
I asked Dong-seok if he enjoyed studying.
He didn't express his feelings
and instead, he wrote this.
It seems like
Dong-seok felt your desperation
on a very deep level
and it's been weighing on him
almost too heavily.
How about we try it just for one day?
And if you don't like it, we can stop.
It's Mommy's wish.
Do you really not want to?
Dong-seok.
MOM'S WISH
Yu-bin has a very strong drive
to seek approval.
The problem is that she only sought
that approval through her good grades.
As people started to stop
showing interest in her,
her anxiety started to grow.
I believe she started to lie
to deal with her anxiety.
Mom, am I really sick?
No, they said you're not that sick.
And they also told me
that you're not alone.
To be honest…
I also do that a lot of the time.
Really?
Adults have a lot of things that
they want to hide from each other too.
And the easiest way to deal with it is…
just that.
Oh, okay.
But Yu-bin.
Lies…
might seem easy at first,
but they end up snowballing
and ruining everything in the end.
So it's better not to start them at all.
Okay?
Let's go.
First floor. Going down.
Dong-seok.
Come over here.
Here's the thing.
Mommy's sorry.
I wasn't thinking about your feelings
and all I did was get angry at you.
To be honest,
I was just as upset as you were.
I have one wish
that I never ever told you before.
And that wish is…
I want you to
smile happily.
I want to see that.
I forgot about that wish
of mine for a moment.
That's the only thing I want from you now.
Okay?
My goodness.
I want a hug too, Mommy!
Get in here, Dong-ju.
My goodness.
My little puppies.
I love you, Mom. I love you, Dong-seok.
I love you, too.
It's Dong-seok.
Dong-seok, what are you doing here?
Why are you being hugged
by your mom like a baby?
Dong-seok said he doesn't
really feel like playing today.
Would it be okay
if he took some alone time today?
-Okay.
-Let's go.
What can we do to get you back
in a good mood, Dong-seok?
What'd you just write?
Can you write it out one more time?
Hen…
Henry?
Dong-seok, do you miss Henry?
-Two, two, three, four.
-Five, six, seven, eight.
All right, now let's switch feet.
-Are we all switched up? All right!
-Yes.
Isn't there anything
you want to do, Dong-seok?
Dong-ju said he wanted to build a snowman.
How do you feel about going sledding then?
Aren't you coming today?
He doesn't like going to places
where there are a lot of people.
I don't think we'll be going for a while.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
That's a problem.
It must be rough for you.
Let me know if there's anything
I can do to help. Whenever.
Thanks for thinking of me.
-Sit down and stand up.
-Jeez.
-One, two, three, four,
-Goodness.
five, six, seven, eight.
One of the moms from
the gifted student's academy told me
that he ran out
in the middle of his presentation.
He didn't even get to
finish his presentation.
She said that it looked like
he even wet his pants.
I heard it looked like
he was having some sort of seizure.
-A seizure?
-Really?
I wonder what got into him?
He was such a smart boy.
They were cutting it really close.
Gosh, maybe I should've said something.
Was there something going on
in that household?
No, it's not that.
His mom's ambition started bubbling up
and started pushing him so hard.
Honestly, it's not like
he decided to participate in
all those competitions and
win every award all on his own.
-You're right.
-I agree.
What's the point of being smart
if you start feeling sick emotionally?
-That's right.
-Right.
-We're blessed.
-Exactly.
-What do you think you're doing?
-That scared me.
Is this amusing?
Is this amusing to you?
Come on, who here
is saying this is amusing?
You have this habit of freaking out
all of a sudden. You need to fix that.
I'm tired of hearing it.
You guys were loving
every moment of it just now.
Who appointed you
as the guardian of justice?
When did that happen?
I actually just started today.
Is she trying to repay Eun-pyo
for all that she's done for her?
I see.
So what you're telling me is
you were getting insanely
jealous of her, is that it?
But in front of Eun-pyo,
you acted all coy and friendly, right?
As soon as she's out of the picture,
your attitude changes just like that.
Coy and friendly?
You think I was sucking up to her?
Listen.
You always stick to one after another
to get all the information, right?
Is there anyone here who doesn't know
about that weird behavior of hers?
And excuse me!
I'm talking to you!
You always hide behind Jae-bin's mom
and gossip about other people
behind their backs.
You need to cut it out
and stop living like that!
What did you just say?
How does every single
one of you choose to do
only the saddest, most pathetic,
and lame things ever?
You're all so pathetic.
Hey!
What?
You couldn't even do
anything to me if you wanted to.
-Darn you.
-My goodness.
Let go.
I can't let go.
You picked the wrong day.
-Hey!
-Goodness.
Do you know who I am?
-Hey!
-Somebody help me!
I used to roll with Chun-hyang's crew
in Bujeong-dong, you brat.
I never lived there, so how would I know?
Goodness me.
-Oh no, just stop.
-My goodness.
-Get back here.
-My gosh!
-Hey!
-Stop it! What are you doing?
-Back up!
-Somebody grab her!
-Stop it!
-Call the police!
Hey, grab her!
Can I have some bandaids
and some iodine please?
-Thank you.
Gosh, that hurts.
Jeez.
-Mom.
-Yes?
Why are you laughing?
Well…
Just because?
I just can't seem to stop laughing.
You know?
People shouldn't try to
suppress their true nature.
Gosh, I should've always
lived my life like this.
-Su-in.
-Yes?
-Should we eat something good today?
-Like what?
What should we have?
Tteokbokki?
I was so pissed off
that I grabbed her hair
and nearly ripped all of it off.
Just let them be, okay?
People are always like that.
Sure.
Either way, thanks for standing up for me.
Eun-pyo.
I still have all that toughness
from my high school days.
I bet she can't move a muscle right now.
By the way, Yun-ju.
Were Dong-seok and Henry close?
What?
Dong-seok mentioned
that he misses Henry.
Gosh, Dong-seok said that to you?
No.
He wrote it on my hand.
Dong-seok and Henry used to
sit together in class, Eun-pyo.
I remember Su-in telling me
how noisy they were.
That's right. He was a gifted student too.
So don't you think
they must've had a lot in common?
I see.
So…
Even if Yu-bin comes up
with strange stories,
please don't think too much of it.
Goodness.
It must've been very hard for you as well.
On one hand, it's quite a relief
that you managed to
catch it earlier on in her life.
If you help her out whenever you can,
then perhaps this may turn out
to be a blessing in disguise.
Thank you.
Hey, Eun-seo. What is it?
Ms. Hwang, I left my math book.
-Is that right? Just a moment, please.
-Okay.
Come here.
-Did you remember it on your way home?
-Yes.
I heard that Dong-seok
from your class has selective mutism.
Here.
Hello.
Why aren't you responding to me?
Tell me whether you can or not
so I can let my guy know.
Do you even know
how dangerous those drugs are?
Gosh.
So what?
-Is that a no?
-Yes! It's a no!
Tell your guy that there's nothing
more coming out from my side.
Don't you need money?
Are you going to keep your kids like that?
Don't you need to pay for their tuition?
I don't need your drug money anymore!
HOW DID IT GO?
There was a setback with the General
Manager in Taiwan due to some issues.
But they will be sending out
a replacement soon.
I'll be there soon. Just hold on.
How've you been doing?
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
Could we meet up in person for a second?
I know it's shameless of me
to be asking this of you
considering you're having a hard time.
But the only person
that Dong-seok will respond to
is Henry.
I'm sorry.
I guess I'm not ashamed
to ask for anything
now that I've become a mother.
No.
I understand.
It must've been really hard.
Jae-suk told me
that you're going to France.
Yes.
That's good.
It'll be much better for Henry
to be there than here.
Henry doesn't seem too fond of the idea.
He told me he didn't want to go.
I've been trying to convince him.
Also…
About last time…
I'm sorry. It wasn't something
I should've gotten angry at you for.
No.
I was wrong.
I was only thinking of myself
and not about how hard you were having it.
If I'm being honest…
I just really wanted to
run away from all the guilt.
I've been feeling inferior
to Jin-ha for a long time.
You know better than anyone
how incredible she really was.
But…
what I still can't wrap my head around
is why such a beautiful, graceful,
and downright gifted girl
would do something like that?
Why…
I'll be leaving then.
Call me.
Hello?
It's me.
Is Henry feeling better?
He's feeling better.
Then can you ask Henry--
How many times do I have to tell you
that he doesn't want to?
Why do you keep forcing him?
Hey, is that punk Oh Geon-u
hitting our kids?
What are you talking about?
Why do they get
more timid every single day?
Do you not notice it?
Do you have any proof
of what you're saying right now?
What did the kids say to you?
They cried saying
that their stepdad is scary!
It's normal for kids to be scared from
time to time when you're raising them.
Are you trying to
nitpick with me right now?
You still have that habit
of whitewashing everything.
I'm warning you.
If anything happens to them,
I'm not going to let it slide.
You better get your act together.
Who is it that you had to
pick up on the veranda?
Oh, it's just Sangkemo.
Yeong-mi, are you seeing
the kids' father by any chance?
Listen, Yeong-mi.
I want our family to be perfect.
But…
why does my loneliness keep growing?
You know how much I hate that punk.
So why do you keep doing that?
-We're back.
Hey, you're home.
Why don't you two
follow me to the supermarket?
I'm trying to make preserves
but we're out of sugar.
Hang on. Put down your bags.
Let's go. We'll be back.
We'll be back soon.
SUGAR
Is everything…
okay with my Sae-bom and Jul-pin?
I want to become the kind of mom
that both my son and daughter
can come and talk about anything
that's on their minds.
The reason why I participate in social
and environmental activities
is because I want you two
to live in a better world.
You know that, right?
Let me know if there's anything
you want to talk about.
Well…
Mom.
Yes?
Our stepdad…
really loves you, right?
Of course.
Why?
But…
I don't think he likes us very much.
Why?
He gets mad at us every day.
Whenever you're not home,
he always swears at us
and he even locked me
in the bathroom last time.
He once picked up a rag
and threw it at Sae-bom.
And even further back then,
it was actually him who broke the cup.
Dong-ju!
I'm just asking you
to check if you have the cup or not.
I'll leave if you check.
He started yelling all of a sudden
and then he just chucked it
out of the veranda.
Hey, we weren't supposed to tell her that.
Is that true, Sae-bom?
Yes.
Your dad only did that…
because he's an artist.
Artists can sometimes be a bit sensitive.
When they have trouble
producing their work,
they have it harder than anyone else
and it can get rough.
So…
that's why he acted like that.
Since we're family,
shouldn't we try to be
more understanding of his shortcomings?
"A warm wind flew in from a faraway sea."
"I could no longer smell
the fishy stink of the dock
or the smell of the people."
"It was the first time
in a very long time that I flew so far."
The end!
That's it for tonight.
Just one more.
No, that's enough.
If you want to meet up with Henry
on the weekend at the kids cafe,
you have to be
on your best behavior, okay?
Dong-seok, are you happy
that you're going to meet Henry?
Yes, I'm happy too!
Gosh.
This is Jin-ha's mother.
I heard from Henry's father.
Call me when you have time.
What is it, Mom?
What?
It's nothing.
Let's go to bed now.
I HEARD FROM HENRY'S FATHER.
CALL ME WHEN YOU HAVE TIME.
HENRY'S GRANDMOTHER
Hello?
Hello, ma'am.
This is Lee Eun-pyo.
I've been waiting for your call.
I heard from Henry's father.
Instead of talking like this,
why don't you come over to my place?
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
Who is it?
Hello, it's Dong-seok's mother.
-Henry!
-Jung Dong-seok!
Did you know we have a huge dog here?
But he's really nice.
He knows "sit," "stand," "paw,"
and even knows how to play dead.
Really?
-Yes.
-Show us.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, wait for me!
But…
What was it you wanted to talk about?
Guys, follow me. I'll show you
a really cool painting. Come this way.
-Boys, don't touch the paintings.
-Wait for me!
Oh, that's what it was.
It's a tiger, right?
I'm going to try
and get the overall shape first.
What?
SEO JIN-HA
Me and other friends were
so envious of anyone
who got to wear
this uniform.
Jin-ha looked so pretty
when she had this uniform on.
To be honest,
I was very jealous of Jin-ha
for a very long time.
She was always better
than me at everything.
She seemed like she had it all
and that made me envious of her.
I felt guilty about those feelings.
That's why
I wasn't able to tell you properly.
What happened between me and
Henry's father was a misunderstanding.
I hope…
you'll believe me.
Did it really seem like
Jin-ha had it all?
You know that
I'm Jin-ha's stepmother, right?
My very existence must've
caused a lot of pain for her.
I guess she didn't mention that to you.
What did you draw, Henry?
Oh, this is the girl
that used to live here.
Then who are these people?
Look, this is her dad
and this is her mom.
And this one is her dad's student.
Did his student live with them?
Yes.
-Okay, I'm going to take the picture.
-Because the girl
-One, two, three.
-begged her to live with them.
Just trust me and try it out once.
Because there was no one
to take care of the girl in the house.
Not at all. You look like a princess.
So what happened?
Did everyone get along?
But why would that make Jin-ha
a child that nobody cared for?
Jin-ha's mother…
suffered from schizophrenia.
So ever since birth,
she was never fully
taken care of by her own mother.
And also,
she was always afraid
that she might take after her mother.
MAY SHE REST IN PEACE
GEOSEONG UNIVERSITY PROFESSORS
There are so many things
that I've done wrong to Jin-ha.
I think part of the reason why
I let out all of that resentment on you
was because I wanted
to be free of some of my own guilt.
I think that's what happened.
You're doing this to me on purpose.
You're trying to make me feel small.
What's wrong, Eun-pyo?
Right.
Ever since you were young,
you had a weird way of messing
with other people's emotions
with that innocent face of yours.
And you always took advantage of me.
You have everything.
Why are you all worked up
to take everything I want as well?
Do you have some sort of mental condition?
You know,
I was thrilled that my dear old friend
became a neighborhood friend.
I couldn't open up
about my feelings to people I met
after becoming an adult.
How is it…
for you?
You know how much I like you, right?
You and I…
are back on good terms now, okay?
Eun-pyo, come on!
MAY THE WAVES OF LIFE
LAST AS ECHOES OF THE HEART…
SEO JIN-HA
Congratulations, Jin-ha.
They're so pretty.
Thank you.
It's nice here.
You get lots of sunlight too.
I was wondering
why they put you up so high,
but I guess this is what it was all about.
I'm sorry…
for everything.
I never thought
you truly liked me as a friend.
I misunderstood you
and hated you.
That was really unfair of me, wasn't it?
I didn't know anything
and said all those things to you.
I'm so sorry.
I did so many bad things to you
without even realizing it.
If I knew they were going to
put this photo here,
I would have bought
the 60,000 won bouquet.
They were prettier.
But you're still the prettiest
out of everyone here.
I'll be back.
Not just in art history,
there were also
many other geniuses in humanity.
They expanded
the limits of human knowledge.
It's thanks to them that we can enjoy
such a rich culture today.
There's a common misconception
that geniuses simply
have to bring out the brilliance
from their god-given talent.
Those so-called "gifted ones."
But is that really the case?
We have a double standard
when it comes to how we treat geniuses.
We revere, yet we envy.
We covet, yet we observe.
We're like spectators in a circus.
We get to sit in the comfort of our seats
and judge them to see
how much they can advance.
But one thing that we can't overlook
is that geniuses endure deep loneliness
than most of us will ever experience.
WECHILD COUNSELING CENTER
He struggled a bit more than usual today.
He barely reacted to the writing exercise
and refused to interact.
Was there an incident that may have
caused him to withdraw like this?
I'm not sure.
Could it be that he's sad that his friend
is going to be leaving soon?
That could be it.
If he felt that he might have to say
goodbye to a close friend for good,
sensitive children like Dong-seok
will definitely have a hard time.
Could it have been
a mistake to go see his friend?
Not at all.
The most important thing is that we keep
building on
happy experiences for Dong-seok.
ART GROUP COUNSELING ROOM, HEART
Excuse me.
You dropped your scarf here.
We came to see a doctor
because Yu-bin kept on lying.
They said Dong-seok has selective mutism.
I must've given him too much stress.
How can our paths
be so intertwined like this?
Mom, I can't breathe too well.
No, my kid might die
if he has to wait that long. Dong-ju.
Dong-ju, wake up! Dong-ju!
-Did you ever check up on that thing?
-Oh, that lady?
We're not after the people
who took the drugs.
We're looking for the sellers.
Are you now bringing
gangsters into our house?
Hey, this is all your fault.
In life, knowing the truth
can be like poison sometimes.
It can be better to live your life
without knowing the whole story.