Are you Korean?
This is a Lautrec.
Eun-pyo.
I'm bored.
Hello.
SAINT-ÉPIANNE BEAUX-ARTS
MASTER
Congratulations, Eun-pyo.
You did great.
Thank you.
-Kiss!
Eun-pyo.
Who would have thought
we'd meet again here of all places?
Doctor Kim Hyeon-jeong,
please come to the
internal medicine department.
Dong-ju, let's go.
Are you okay?
Sit still. Don't do that with your feet.
Put your feet down.
Are you sure you don't need
a more thorough examination?
No, I'm fine.
You should've just left.
We could've taken a taxi.
No, I could never do that.
Jin-ha told me the two of you ran
into each other in the neighborhood.
Yes. What a coincidence, right?
Mom, why are you talking funny?
Dong-ju, put your feet down.
But why are you talking like that?
Gosh, stay still.
Take care of yourself.
And call me if you need anything.
Okay.
Dong-ju, you cutie.
-I'll see you again.
-Okay.
EPISODE 2
ADULTS DON'T MAKE FRIENDS WITHOUT MOTIVES
Dad!
-Hold on, I'm too tired for this.
-Dad.
-How've you been?
-Hey, Eun-pyo.
-Dad.
Where did you go?
I'm so sleepy.
Aren't you guys hungry? Should we eat?
-Yes.
All right.
I'm going to go ask Mom
to cook us something so wait a second.
-Okay, Dad.
-Keep on playing, okay?
Eun-pyo, aren't you going to cook for us?
I'm hungry.
Dong-seok, I want to pull it this time.
By the way, where are my boxers?
I wanted to change,
but I couldn't find them anywhere.
Are you sleeping?
Gosh, we messed that one up.
I want to eat kimchi stew with pork.
In two, three!
Do you think I'm a maid?
What?
You don't even care that I'm in bed
when it's still early in the evening.
The first thing you say after moving in
is "feed me" and "where are my boxers."
What is it? Did something happen?
Forget it. You're not even interested.
Stop pretending you care.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
There's rice in the rice cooker,
and there are side dishes in the fridge.
Fry up some eggs and feed the kids.
But…
-About my boxers…
-Just leave me alone!
Okay, sorry. Just get some sleep.
One, two, three!
OPEN CLASS DAY FOR PARENTS
Hello.
The professor has graced us
with her presence.
I wonder what she'll be teaching us today?
What's going on
between her and Henry's father?
Do they know each other?
Who knows.
That's just ridiculous.
All she did was faint in front of him.
Chun-hui, did she pay you
for the instrument?
She texted me asking
if she could make monthly payments.
Like an installment plan?
She's brazen.
I think we should teach her a lesson.
You don't have to go that far,
you wicked woman.
That's the first time
I've ever heard anyone call me that.
Gosh, I'm speechless.
-Jae-bin's getting out now.
-Dong-seok.
Jul-pin, don't run. You'll fall.
-Your kids are so good at drawing.
-Yes.
Su-in's.
He's good at art too?
He must take after his mother. Jeez.
NAME: HENRY
TITLE: SUNSET
NAME: JUNG DONG-SEOK
TITLE: OUR HOUSE
Your son.
Goodness gracious, look at him.
It looks like he just wanted
to go outside and play.
Oh, my. Hello!
Gosh, you two look great together.
-You made it.
-Hello.
-You guys look great.
-I know, right?
Eun-pyo.
I heard you were ill.
And why didn't you mention
that you ran into Louis?
Now that I think about it,
I never told you
that Louis was Henry's father.
You must've been surprised.
Are you doing all right?
Yes.
Did you go back
for a more thorough examination?
Yes. They said I have something
called pernicious anemia.
Gosh.
How exhausted were you?
I must've overdone myself for a while.
Is it because of all
the lectures you're doing?
Becoming a professor is great,
but you have to put your health first.
Hello, Henry's mother.
I'm Eun-pyo's relative and Su-in's mom.
We were both
the Green crossing guards last time.
Really?
Eun-pyo is a dear friend of mine.
That's what I'm saying!
She's got such a great friend
who she didn't even tell me about.
You're a sneaky one.
Jul-pin.
Today, we'll be learning
how to count bundle numbers.
Okay.
In each of these baskets here,
-there are ten chocolates.
-Okay.
In total, we have three baskets.
And we also have
three chocolates on the floor.
-Isn't that so cool?
-Jung Dong-seok, eyes to the front.
Do your fish sleep
during the night or day?
Jung Dong-seok.
Dong-seok, are you goofing off
because you already know everything?
Let's hear it, Dong-seok.
How many do we have in total?
Dong-seok, pay attention.
There are 495.
Focus, Dong-seok.
Goodness, he's always like that.
Hey, don't be like that.
That's why you need to
pay attention Dong-seok.
Then, can Henry tell us the answer?
Yes, there are 33.
Very good. 33 is correct!
-Aren't our kids just adorable?
-How did we get 33?
How many are in this basket
that already has ten?
-Three!
-Thank you!
-Bye!
OPEN GENTLY
You! I saw everything.
You need to pay attention in class.
Let go of me!
Goodness.
Dong-seok has such a lively personality.
He's like you when you were young.
Right.
How are your parents doing?
Are they still running the paint shop?
You can either click on the link
that says "Afterschool Learning."
Or you can sign up
in the teacher's office.
That's all for the information
I had prepared to share.
Now it's time for us to pick the class
representative for the upcoming semester.
First, I'd like to say
thank you to Jul-pin's mother
for all her hard work
over the last semester.
The next person who'll take her place…
Ma'am.
During the first semester, I spent quite
some time pursuing various agendas.
However, there are still some things
I've yet to accomplish.
We still haven't participated
in the Jungse Chungse debate,
and we have yet to complete
the A Day In The Forest program.
The Let's Eat Clean, Moms on the Scene
program is also still in the works.
So if it's possible, I wanted to ask
if I could serve again
for the upcoming semester.
What?
Well…
Right, I see.
Does everyone else agree?
Well…
I'm Jae-bin's mom.
If I may share my opinion,
considering how hard Jul-pin's mother
worked for us over the past semester,
it simply wouldn't be right for us
to ask her to do another semester.
And perhaps as a way of changing things
up for the next semester,
how about we ask Yu-bin's mother
to be our next class representative?
-Why are you doing this?
-I'm just sharing my opinion.
I see.
Well…
What do all the other mothers think?
-I agree.
-I also recommend Yu-bin's mother.
-It's good.
-That's a great idea.
What do you say, Yu-bin's mother?
Are you interested
in volunteering your time for our class?
Help us out.
Goodness.
Well, I'm not sure
if I'll have a lot to offer
and if I'll do well
but if that's what everybody else wants…
All right. How about we take a vote?
Yes.
Everyone who wants Jul-pin's mother
to serve for another semester,
please raise your hands.
All right.
Now everyone who wants Yu-bin's mother
to be our new representative?
All right, it seems pretty clear.
Yu-bin's mother will be our class
representative for the second semester.
A round of applause, please.
Gosh, thank you. I'll do my best.
Come on.
Thank you all for coming.
-Thank you for coming.
-Congratulations.
-Goodbye.
-Why'd you do that?
I'm really looking forward
to the next semester.
Dong-seok's mother,
can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
The thing is
some kids are late bloomers
and that can't be helped,
but when they can't stay seated
and disturb other students
that's where problems can arise.
Most people in this neighborhood
are rather sensitive
when it comes to issues
such as the right to learn.
He's still young,
so won't things like staying seated
get better as time goes on?
I'm sure.
However, the problem is that
in this neighborhood,
there aren't many kids
that run around like him.
I see.
By the way,
you're making sure
Dong-seok is studying at home, right?
He might be having trouble staying still
because he's having
a hard time keeping up in class.
Dong-seok?
Should we have sent him
to after-school classes?
Enjoy your lunch.
I mean, if his homeroom teacher said that,
it's probably serious.
Why are you blindly believing her?
Me?
What I'm saying is
we need to hold our ground.
Dong-seok is my son.
If he takes after me,
he should be a sharp kid.
I have no regrets that we raised him
based on our principles.
Honestly, our society is abnormal
and there's no reason
we have to follow everyone.
Where's your sense of pride?
And he's still in first grade.
He can start now.
You're right. He can start now.
SANGKEMO
-Excuse me.
-I learned something important today.
Hello, everyone.
What?
The new boy's mother?
A CLUB FOR ENLIGHTENED SANGWE MOMS
SANGKEMO
All right everybody,
she's our new member, "takeitslow."
And as all of you know,
I'm the class representative
for class three
and the highest-ranking member
of Sangkemo, "broccoli."
I'm "keytohappiness."
I'm "withthetrees."
I see.
All of the mothers in my class
are so stubborn and short-sighted
that I was about to lose all hope,
but now that another mom
from the same class has joined our club,
I do feel a bit better.
But may I ask
why you decided to join our club?
I've been so busy with work
that I know so little
about my children's education
and I don't know what to do as a mom.
Right.
I understand.
We sensible moms need to stick together.
We have to protect our children
from all of the fake news.
-Indeed.
-To that end,
Sangkemo has been meeting up regularly
and moving together as one unit.
In particular, we're trying to pass
a new scholastic anti-discrimination law.
So we're trying to organize a meet-up,
but I'm not sure if it'll be at
Gwanghwamun, City Hall, or Yeouido…
"Takeitslow"!
Where are you going in such a hurry?
Did you not hear me?
My mind was somewhere else.
I thought you were going to
stay back and talk with me.
Running off like that hurts my feelings.
As you know,
you and I are very special comrades.
We're true intellectuals who can show
those ignorant, lowly capitalists
what it means to live a proper life.
I heard that you're a professor.
Am I right?
It's important that opinion leaders
like us set a good example.
That's the only way to build
a healthy community.
So, in a few days, to push for
the scholastic anti-discrimination law,
-we're going to try and organize a--
-I'm sorry.
I'm not really that type of mom.
"That type of mom"?
Why are you crying?
Even if you made a mistake,
you should've finished it.
It felt so different
from what it usually feels like!
The instrument was weird!
INCOMING CALL
That's pretty.
SANGWE MOMS ONLINE COMMUNITY
My child is in first grade.
How do I get started
with my child's studies?
CRITICAL THINKING, BOOK STUDIES, AND MATH.
MUST TAKE NOTE OF INCORRECT ANSWERS.
LAZY MOTHERS CAN'T RAISE CHILDREN WELL.
"Takeitslow"?
Why do they want to take things slow?
They'll need to master English
in elementary school
so they can focus on math
in middle school.
TEAM LEADER
Are you playing around with the comments?
You're supposed to discreetly
steer the conversation toward the academy.
If you keep on commenting like this,
I can't pay you 1,000 won per comment.
All right.
I was actually trying to
come off more as a member,
but was that too much?
Just use common sense
and try not to get banned like last time.
She's so annoying.
I'm sorry.
This brat is half my age and
always has to have the last word.
What? 880,000 won?
Classes for gifted students
all start at 800,000 won.
But still, that's insane
for a first-grader.
I told you we shouldn't have
pushed ourselves with the move.
Would I be doing this
if Su-in was just a normal girl?
There was no one who could
teach her in our old neighborhood.
I don't know why
we have to live like this.
I work my butt off
and pour all of it into education.
Stop saying things like that.
Aren't you tired of saying it?
It's what parents are supposed to do.
You think having a baby
is all it takes to be a parent?
I've been slaving away all day.
Is it too much to have some meat?
Look at this.
We had some the other day.
What did we have?
Don't you remember?
There was beef in the seaweed soup.
It wasn't cheap to make that.
Su-in, look at this.
It was all one piece…
Hello.
Oh, hello.
HAVE YOU EATEN?
TRANSLATE
We both got hired
around the same time, right?
Yes.
Our children are also in the same class.
We have a lot in common.
I can speak basic Korean.
Right.
What do you say
we carpool for the commute?
I can learn Korean from you
and you can learn English from me.
Nobody seems to want
to speak to me in Korean.
Does everyone hate me?
Did I do something
to hurt your feelings, Eun-pyo?
NEW MESSAGE FROM LEE SU-HYEON
Jin-ha, how are you doing?
I miss you very much, my daughter.
LET'S STUDY THE NUMBERS 60, 70, 80, 90
Jung Dong-seok.
Sit up straight and don't slouch.
This isn't fun.
Listen to me explain it first,
and then you can tell me what's not fun.
-Do you know what a bundle number is?
-Yes, I know.
Where are you going?
The bathroom!
You just went!
I'm pooping!
My goodness.
Mom!
Yes?
Can I go play outside?
Come on, Mom!
I'm getting a headache.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
-Shoot!
-Wait for me!
Eun-pyo.
If you’re free tomorrow,
do you want to have a cup of tea?
SORRY, I'M A BIT BUSY
Eun-pyo!
Hello.
-Hello.
-What are you doing here?
Su-in, go play. Dong-seok's over there.
Let's play tag, guys!
-Okay.
-I'll be it.
They love running around.
Hurry!
Boys need to run around
to let off all of that extra energy.
Yun-ju.
Do you know
of any academies for Dong-seok
in this neighborhood?
Why?
Are you trying to be
one of those kinds of moms now?
Hello. What brings you to the playground?
I know, right?
-Yun-ju…
-Yes?
Do you mind watching
the kids for a second?
Chun-hui went to search for a new academy
so she asked me to watch them,
but I completely forgot
about the meeting I had to go to.
I just need one hour.
Sure, go ahead.
-Great. I'm counting on you.
-Sure.
-I'll be back soon.
-All right, bye.
Go play, guys.
Gosh, I think I have a serious problem
with letting people step all over me.
I'm sure she's still going to
get all the credit.
This is so annoying.
That woman is the worst
out of all of them.
She's got nothing but she always sticks
next to Chun-hui and bosses people around.
Gosh, so annoying.
Dong-ju!
-My gosh.
-Guys, what's going on? Come here.
-Come here. Dong-seok, come on!
-Quickly, come on!
-Come on!
-Dong-ju.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Something fell from the sky.
What?
Wait, my hairband!
-Yu-bin.
-Yu-bin!
Yu-bin, it's dangerous!
No, stop. Eun-pyo!
No!
Yu-bin, are you okay? Come here.
Yu-bin!
Mom.
Let me see.
Are you hurt? Are you okay?
Yes.
Chun-hui, it's not what you think.
Yu-bin looked so thirsty
so I asked Su-in's mom to look
after her while I went to the store.
-I didn't know this would happen.
-Hey! That's not right.
You're the one who tossed her to me
so you could go run your errands.
Mom.
That lady saved me.
You really didn't have to do this.
The wound is pretty deep.
If it were any deeper,
you would've had to go to a hospital.
You're very impressive.
You're like a real nurse.
I watched my husband treat his patients
and picked up a few things.
-You're all done.
-Okay.
OPEN DOOR
CALL
Chun-hui.
Your place is so nice. This is so fancy.
The furniture is all so nice.
I think I've seen this on TV before.
I saw on the Internet
that a famous designer made it.
It's that one, right?
What did the management office say?
It's hard to see everything
on the security camera.
They moved it to the middle of the complex
last month because they can't
see the license plates when
there are accidents in the parking lot.
They also said they can't show us
anything unless we're the police.
So I made a fuss and asked them to see it.
Maybe it's some sort
of highly intelligent criminal?
Are the only kids that went to
Sangwe Kindergarten from building 901
Henry and Jul-pin?
Yes.
Why? Are you suspecting something?
To be honest,
I took a good look earlier
and the broken shards
were flashing all kinds of colors.
We broke a cup at our place
and it flashed the exact same colors.
It was a cup we got
from a glass art field trip.
We might be able to find the suspect
more easily than I thought.
Also…
forget about the instrument fee.
Sorry?
You saved my daughter's life.
If anything, I should compensate.
It wouldn't be right to take your money.
How could I do that?
It's not a small amount.
If it's really too much,
then just buy me a few cups of coffee.
Lucky you.
Chun-hui!
Chun-hui, you're amazing.
How are you so generous?
I want to be your fan!
I'm so jealous of you.
How did you get Chun-hui
to like you all of a sudden?
You even got rid of
that debt in one swoop.
-Must be nice.
-How could I do that though?
I should pay what I owe.
There it is. You and that pride.
Just forget about it and say "thank you."
You saved her kid.
That money isn't a big deal.
I'm jealous. Lucky you.
Eun-pyo.
It sounds like Chun-hui thinks
Jul-pin might be responsible, right?
Why?
I mean, they've been at each
other's throats for a while now.
Jul-pin's mom actually got remarried.
A married woman with two kids
fell in love with a movie director
and after some scandalous dating,
they got married.
I wouldn't be surprised if the kids
and the step-dad aren't on the best terms.
But why don't you think Henry did it?
Come on, it can't be Henry.
Do you know how much
his parents dote on him?
I mean, you'd know better than I do.
Put your shoes on properly
or you'll end up tripping.
Okay.
Henry, what will you be learning today?
About the origin of languages.
What we learned last class
was that there is an anatomical condition
that had to be met in order
for humans to be able to speak.
The posterior cavity
of the throat needs to drop down
in order for humans
to start pronouncing consonants.
And they surmise that this particular
piece of evolution happened to humans
around 300,000 years ago.
But of course, in addition to
the proper anatomical conditions,
we also need things
to work together with the brain.
-Good job.
-Thank you.
So you think one of my children did it?
-Yes.
-Why?
I just explained it to you.
-The cup resembled the one we received.
-Henry, come here. It's dangerous.
-The only kids that live on the floors
-Okay.
above the security camera that went to
Sangwe Kindergarten are Jul-pin and Henry.
I'm just asking you
to check if you have the cup or not.
I'll leave if you check.
What makes you think
you have any right to treat me like this?
Are you honestly asking me that right now?
If you were in my shoes,
would you do nothing
if your child nearly lost her life?
Are you sure
you're not targeting my children
intentionally because of old grudges?
-What's all that ruckus outside?
-It's nothing you need to worry about.
It's just there's some
half-baked woman out there
who's trying to drag
our family through the mud.
-I was out there arguing with her.
-What did she say?
A cup dropped on the playground
and she came asking if it was our kids.
I'm sick and tired of
these women's habit of getting suspicious
without any evidence.
They're ignorant, low,
and they only care about fake news.
Just don't expect so much
from your fellow humans.
Humans are foolish creatures anyway.
It feels like what little hope I have left
of the human race is dying.
We have Dutch coffee brewed in the fridge.
I just felt like having drip coffee.
Are you hungry?
You want some rice cakes?
No thanks. I can't write anything
if I eat too much.
Dong-seok's mom.
Are you getting back from somewhere?
I was just going to the supermarket.
How are your kids adapting?
They're doing fine.
They say stress from moving is
on par with stress from divorce.
It must be harder for the kids
to move to an unfamiliar neighborhood.
When you have time,
let's go to a kids cafe
so Dong-seok can blow off some steam.
Sure.
By the way…
do you know of a tutor
or an academy nearby?
I don't know much about the area.
Su-in's mom didn't tell you anything?
Then again,
people don't share things like that
even with family in this neighborhood.
Right.
I heard you're best friends
with Henry's mother.
I'm sure both her
and her husband would know a lot.
Right.
Just forget I asked.
HOW TO RAISE A BOY USING YOUR INSIDE VOICE
THINGS PARENTS SHOULD KNOW ABOUT
THEIR ELEMENTARY STUDENT’S EDUCATION
YU-BIN’S MOM
THE TOP 1% MOMS IN SANGWE-DONG COMMUNITY
Are you done chewing?
Spit it out.
How many times did you chew?
You don't remember
how many times you chewed?
Why is it so hard for you to focus
on such a simple experiment?
Are you going to eat your meal all night
and go to bed without studying?
Are you sleepy?
Go eat some ice.
Be quick.
INCOMING CALL
Really?
Really.
All the parents in this area
want to send their kids
to Geoseong University School
of Gifted Students.
Then schools with the Office of Education
and other gifted students schools.
Why?
That's how you get into
the community with all the smart kids.
They have to at least attend
a school for the gifted.
Eun-pyo.
Normal kids will live normal lives.
Mom, I want more rice cakes.
We finished it.
Stop eating.
We're going to have dinner later.
Give me more.
Stop eating.
I don't understand it at all.
Do they really have to do that?
Goodness.
You know,
I don't understand how someone
as innocent as you still exists in Korea.
Eun-pyo.
What's the percentage of kids
that go to top-tier universities in Korea?
-What's this? Is it the sea?
-Yes.
The top three percent.
Then what about gifted schools
and science schools?
The top three percent.
What I'm saying is that
those schools aren't there
to pick out the gifted students.
They select the kids
that will go to top-tier universities.
So all the moms in this area are dying
to get their kids into that school.
From competitions to certificates,
they do it all.
How've you been?
Hello.
Hi.
-Hello.
-Hi.
You must've planned on seeing each other.
I was just here to drop off some food
and got caught up talking.
No. I was just passing by.
Enjoy your time.
No, I should be getting home.
Su-in.
-Rock, rock, rock!
-Jeez, I was close.
Mom, can I go over to Henry's house?
No. What are you talking about?
But Henry has so many
cool toys at his house.
Me too.
Mom.
Can Dong-seok come over to play?
That sounds good to me.
Eun-pyo.
Why don't you come over if you have time?
Miss Nam just baked some apple pie,
so you can try some of that too.
Dong-seok.
What kind of cool toys
does Henry have at home?
I'm so curious.
There are a lot of trains
and there's even a drone.
A drone?
They are a lot of expensive toys.
-And you have a lot of those too?
-Yes.
Chun-hui! Are you just getting back?
Yes, I was picking up Yu-bin
from her academy.
-Hi, Yu-bin.
-Hello.
Is everyone headed somewhere?
We were actually on our way
to Henry's place, so if you have time…
Would it be okay if she came?
This is going to be so much fun!
What should we play?
So you two
went to the same university
and studied abroad in France together?
Yes.
Before I got too homesick,
Eun-pyo would always give me kimchi
and other pickled side dishes.
She helped me out so much.
Goodness.
What a heart-touching friendship.
I…
I have an upset stomach.
Could I have a cup of latte?
Of course.
So Dong-seok's mom finished
her undergrad in France,
and finished her doctorate in Korea?
She's quite the talent.
Where do you hold your lectures?
-Let me take that for you.
-Thank you.
Eun-pyo…
left France before she completed
her doctorate program.
At the time, everyone was talking about
how she was on track to become
the youngest to complete the program.
We were all looking forward to it.
I don't think I ever heard
the whole story either.
Why did you drop out?
You were on the verge of completing it.
Henry's mom.
Perhaps you're pressing a subject
that Eun-pyo isn't too keen on sharing.
I'm going to the bathroom.
LEE EUN-PYO
Eun-pyo, hurry up.
Hey.
What's that smell?
What?
It smells like some kind of oil.
Oil?
Oh, you mean the linseed oil
and the turpentine?
I use this to help mix my oil paint.
It smells really bad, doesn't it?
My dad's actually an oil painter.
He's a professor at Geoseong University.
Hey, Lee Eun-pyo!
Get some paint thinner and pour it in!
That's good.
Gray.
Pour the whole thing in.
That's enough.
What are you doing in here?
Oh, I just…
Do you want to get back into art?
I figured.
I'd expect as much.
I think it's such a shame
that you stopped.
You had
all the talent.
But you know…
I don't know how this might sound,
but…
you should be careful around Yu-bin's mom.
Why?
She sort of has a dark side to her.
I'm also doing my best
to not get involved--
-What makes you say that?
-What?
Are you close to her?
No.
Then what makes you say that?
You have no ground to stand on.
No, I was just
looking out for you.
Mom.
Yes?
Let's go home. It's not fun anymore.
Dong-ju, did you not enjoy the movie?
I can't understand
anything they're saying.
Oh, dear.
Is that why?
-Yes.
-Goodness.
Let's go.
Guys, it's time to go home now.
Stop watching cartoons.
Su-in, let's go home.
I want to go later.
It's time to go home.
There aren't any subtitles--
He fell.
How did he fall in there?
How do you fall in like that?
Did you know? Is he…
So they do listening in the mornings.
Then do you do that every morning?
-Everyday.
-I see.
Would you by any chance
have an easier list
or a fun list to recommend?
This is all stuff
you can find after a quick search.
I was wondering
if there's something that Yu-bin likes.
I'm sorry…
about earlier.
I never should've brought up France.
The conversation
just kind of led that way.
I think…
you must've been pretty taken aback.
But there's no reason
for you to feel bad about it.
You came here, finished your doctorate,
and are giving lectures now.
That's not something
everyone is capable of.
I'm so proud to see you
living your best life.
On that note…
Here.
I made these to sell
at my upcoming exhibition.
I only made ten of them.
I thought it'd be nice
for you to wear it to your lectures.
It suits you so well.
I knew it would suit you.
It's so pretty.
Do you like it?
You know,
I was thrilled
that my dear old friend
became a neighborhood friend.
I couldn't open up
about my feelings to people I met
after becoming an adult.
How is it…
for you?
Seo Jin-ha!
Why are you doing this to me?
Doing what?
You're doing this to me on purpose.
You're trying to make me feel small.
What's wrong, Eun-pyo?
Right.
Ever since you were young,
you had a weird way of messing
with other people's emotions
with that innocent face of yours.
And you always took advantage of me.
How could you…
say that?
You think I don't know your true colors?
Acting like you care.
Acting like you feel sorry.
But in reality,
you dig up on others' sore spots--
I'm sorry, Eun-pyo.
I was just--
We're even now, right?
I heard he's on the blacklist
in the class.
Please help me, Yu-bin's mother.
It's up to you to find
what's right for your kids.
Seeking advice won't solve it.
I'm going to transfer
Dong-seok to another school.
You didn't know?
I didn't like her back then.
Why was she jealous of me?
I'm nothing to be jealous of.
Can you pretend you don't know me?
If you ran into your ex-boyfriend
in the neighborhood…
I wanted to make up before I leave.
Blame it on my inferiority complex.
What's your name?
Eun-pyo.
Lee Eun-pyo.