Detective
Please, save my daughter
The Wang family wants to kill her
Don't worry, I'll save her for sure
Who is it
Since Shuang'er died
My son has been losing his mind
We invited Master Cao to collect Shuang'er's bones
To ward off disaster for my son
My son Sanming was harmed by this woman
Hurry and collect the bones
Don't let this woman harm our Wang family again
Drive out evil, break the ground
So-called bone collecting
Means taking up remains buried for years
Then rebury them in a new blessed grave site
That way, disaster can be dispelled and blessings sought
So the family may prosper
Hold up the umbrella
Smash the tombstone
Open the coffin
All of you Wangs deserve to die
You all deserve to die
Shuang'er
Master
A right hand bone is missing
A sign of great calamity
Take him away, now
Take the young master away, now, quickly
None of you Wangs will die well
Even as a ghost, I won't spare you
With one right hand bone missing
Can one be added to avoid disaster
No
Using another dead person's hand bone instead
Will bring a wronged spirit's deadly claim
And make the calamity even worse
Master, snow in June signals a great injustice
Shut up
Master
Since Master Cao says dead bones won't do
Then living bones should do, right
You cut off an innocent person's arm
It goes against heaven and human morals
You will surely suffer Divine retribution
I can't collect these bones
I'm telling you, in Nanwan Town
I am heaven
I'd like to see what heaven cannot tolerate
You must collect these bones
Otherwise
Shuang'er, the Wang family's vengeful spirit, will kill again
A third severed-hand case strikes Nanwan Town
Another severed hand
A missing right hand bone is a dire omen
Ow, ow, ow, it's numb, numb, numb
Zheng Yu
It's been three years
I was only joking with you
Why'd you hit so hard
So you do know it's been three years
I told you to come find me, and you never did
I was busy
Busy with what, exactly
How's the information I asked you to check
Do you even need to ask
After all, I am Nanwan Town's one and only
great swindler
great detective
Hand over the file
The three severed-hand victims were all tied to the Wangs
The first was a Wang family thug
The second delivered goods to the Wang family
The third was a mailman
He wasn't one of the Wangs
But he and Shuang'er, the Wang family's daughter-in-law, were from the same hometown
Oh, right, Zheng Yu
Why are you so certain
This severed-hand case is tied to your master's affair
Three years ago, the Wang bone collecting failed
And then Master disappeared
He only left this behind
Th-this is
Master's right hand bone
Back then, Master left me this letter
Telling me to leave Nanwan Town
And never come back again
In these three years
Many Vengeful Spirit's Claim cases happened in Nanwan Town
The times are in turmoil now
The police station is already in utter chaos
They have no time to deal with the Wang family
The Wang family has dominated Nanwan Town for years
Aren't you afraid
Master died a wrongful death for no reason
And there are countless wronged souls in Nanwan Town
This time back, I will uncover the truth
And restore peace to Nanwan Town
Come quick, come look
A wedding procession, a wedding procession
Master Wang is marrying again
Her elder sister was the last wife
The sister died, so he married the younger one
Come to think of it
In the Wang family, a concubine dies every three years
That is damned eerie
Xu Nan
Dearest
No... wh-what is going on?
How did Dearest become Madam Wang?
No, what is going on?
My sister died right here
For my sister
I gave up almost everything
My future, my freedom
Even the man I loved
That bone collecting boy has been missing for three years
You should forget him soon
Now the Wang family has come with a proposal again
I have already accepted the betrothal gifts
This time, you must marry
What is happening?
Th-this is...
What is it? Wh-what is this?
Give me back my right hand
I died so miserably
Master, what did you see?
It is Shuang'er's wronged spirit here to claim a life
Everyone, quiet down, quiet down
Someone is pretending to be ghosts here
Everyone, do not panic, do not panic
Steward, go see what is going on
Shuang'er is claiming a life
The Wang family truly has some unspeakable secret