Why has Xu Nan come?
Matriarch Lü and the Madam of the Wang Family are distant kin
The Wang Family had to send someone for Matriarch Lü's funeral
Wang Shengchang has vanished without a trace
Things with your sister-in-law have gone nowhere
You're in no hurry at all
Why not take this chance
and quickly leave the Wang Family with her
I know her temperament
No one can stop what she wants to do
All right, all right
It is our honor to receive the Fifth Concubine of the Wang Family
A true honor indeed
Third Madam, my condolences
My master had to go out on business
So I have come on behalf of the Wang Family to mourn your matriarch
They are truly so alike
The Fifth and Fourth Concubines truly are twin flowers
Forgive me, my loose tongue spoke out of turn again
It's no matter
I heard the Eldest Young Master has fallen ill as well
I specially brought fine medicinal herbs to visit him
Our Zhao Family is a lineage of perfumers and herbalists
I know a little medicine
Then many thanks indeed
In that case
take the Fifth Concubine to see the Eldest Young Master
Yes, this way please
I can go in by myself
Go attend to your work
Yes
It's you
A ghost!
Fox paw prints and fur
Could the curse of the fox spirit be real?
This...
What use is making a rubbing of these prints?
An adult has 206 bones
A child has a few more
About 217 to 218
From the bones' size and age
you can tell how old the person was
It is the same with animals
Then what have you learned from these prints?
Nothing for now
I am not a ghost
The one who died was my elder sister
Zhao Xujun
I was discourteous
Your reaction just now made it seem you feared her greatly
I did not
Afraid my sister's vengeful spirit would come for your life?
No
She once came to the Lü family for help
You and Matriarch Lü drove her out
What secret are you hiding for the Wang Family?
I...
Speak
It was not me
It was Lü Quan
Eldest Young Master, save me! Your sister sought help from Lü Quan
It was not me
He and the matriarch were the ones who abandoned your sister. Save me!
Eldest Young Master, it was them, them!
It had nothing to do with me!
They did it all
They did it
Do not come for me
I have truly never heard of such a strange thing
When he just went mad
a strange, eerie odor came off him
As if he had been poisoned by some rare toxin
What is it?
It is actually a fox spirit
Eldest Young Master
The Lü family has met with misfortune
To prevent more mishaps
We earnestly ask Mr. Zheng to hold the bone-collecting ritual at once
This is my first time collecting bones for an animal
Though it is not human
it was once still a living creature
and should be treated seriously
Break ground
Open the coffin
These fox bones are hard in texture
They have not weathered away
It has been dead no more than one year
This is no fox spirit the Lü ancestors killed by mistake a hundred years ago