Hello everyone
I'm back
Please don't trust them
trust them
What they said are all fake.
I have never done anything.
Then
Thank you guysf who trust me.
The anchor's price
is listed
The anchor Zhi
could date with you offline.
the following vidoe
Only 5 Yuan
Ruanzhi is the best.
Ruanzhi Fighting
Protect the best Ruanzhi.
Welcome Ruanzhi back
黑粉注意Anti-fans Be careful
Don't throw stones.
Protect the best Ruanzhi.
Ruanzhi is the best.
Ruanruan is the best.
Guard angel
I trust Zhi
Yes
Ruanzhi is the best
Guard Ruanzhi
Thank you guys
Thank you guys for trusting me
I still believe
这个世界in this world
Most people believe me in this world.
So now byebye everyone.
Really thank you guys
So I keep it all the time.
If I run out of tune,what to do?
If my voice cracks,what to do?
I will become a laughing stone
among the whole school.
Don't be nervous about the competition in the afternoon.
I am here
Uh
Um
Well
Orange is your lucky color,isn't it?
I trust zhi.
At the same time for tomorrow,
Continue to boost popularity and give gifts
give more oranges
Yep
Ten thousand rockets more
Open the door,Qizhan
Are you there,Qizhan? Open the door
Open the door
Ok
What are you doing?
Uh
You
Um
What are you doing here?
I just wanna know what you are doing
Well
I
am cooking
Well
You didn't eat yet,right?
between Ruanzhi and Bailu in television drama
I
Sure.Let me have a look. I cooked some noodles.
Hey
How hungry you are.
Eat up then
Thank you
Wow
Instant noodles are so delicious.
what's wrong?
Mmm
How did you know that I didn't have dinner?
You don't have time to eat because you just finish the live.
Hum
I know it must be you.
Tell me
Are you the one who just gave me the gift?
So you come here, just wanna ask me this question
Don't indulge in sophistry
I know it is you
It's me
Mr.Yan told me
that you will live broadcast this afternoon
So I stopped by and had a look.
I didn't expect
to see those
so I would help you definitly.
Ruanruan
I will always guard by your side
Let me show you something
Whenever I shoot these things,I always think
whether I have a chance
to show you these sceneries
or not
In the past two years when I travelled
Sometimes it's for visiting some famous buildings.
visiting some famous buildings.
Sometimes it's for understanding local customs and practices
local customs and practices
When I see something funny
I'll think of you.
When I see some delicious food
I'll think of you
When I see some beautiful sceneries
If you were by my side
I'm sorry Qizhan
If I hadn't been
so impulsive at that time.
Ruanruan
Those lonely days
Tough days
passed away.
Woukd you like to see the future sceneries with me?
see the future sceneries with me?
I remember when you asked me this question at that time
when you asked me this question at that time
My answer?
Actually
After you left,
I feeled really sad.
It's Mr.Lilan
He was always by my side
and help me out of the trouble.
So
I don't know
I am grateful to him
or
some other emotions
exactly
Ruanruan
But after today's live broadcast
I know that
For Mr.Lilan,
I'm respected and worshiped in career
I really appreciate his help.
but
These gratitude
won't affect my mood.
But you are different
Do you know
When I think about
he person who are opposite the camera
is you
My heart beats faster.
I can't sit for a second.
So Qizhan
I
Why you eat jelly in the morning?
This is my breakfast.
That's all you have for breakfast
You don't know
I'm on diet recently
Eating a jelly
is just fine
No way
I prepared breakfast for you.
You have prepared so much.
Wow
Please stop here
I got off first.
It's not good to let colleagues see us later
Ha ha ha
We need be careful in the office.
What's wrong?
Mr.Qi
Good morning
Uh
Morning, Mr.Yan
Are you walking?
Yes, we are walking now.
I saw  that someone was driving
in your passenger seat just now.
Uh
Was it?
Ah
Ha ha
Nobody
Uh Mmm
I'll go first.
I will park the car
See you later in the company
Uh Haha
Alright
Take care, Mr.Qi
Ha ha ha ha
Byebye
It's unusual
Absolutly right
Something different
Get up
Nobody's here
Ouch!
My neck
Ah
I have to go now
Five minutes
No
Ten minutes later, you come to the company
Why?
Keep it secret
You promiesd
I'll go
Ruanruan
Ten minutes
I have something to tell you guys
You didn't see it before
Look at Mr.Qi's face
I promise
there is another person in his car
So
Who is in his car?
It must be a woman.
Wow
Ha ha
Hello
Ah Haha
Yes, it's me. Haha
Mr.Qi
According to the current progress for >
Three episodes a day
By next week
we could complete the whole dubbing mission
The completed part
has already transfered to the producer.
Uh Besides, Mr.Li
has already started the two projects ahead of schedule.
ahead of schedule.
And it's a little rushed.
Well
Zhi
What are you looking at?
Why the big smile?
Nothing
Especially >
It's rushed for trial
to joint International Film Festival for this year
We redrafted
an expedited contract
The other company's legal affairs are being audited.
It's said that they will give feedback this afternoon.
If there are no questions
We will start it at all
Well It's end
Mr.Qi We
Well
Ok Break up
You don't leave?
What do you want?
But you need find it by yourself
Alright
Ruanruan
I can't believe
we are already together now
Well
Yes
What are you
doing?
I thought you are
strange recently
Zhi
We browse your Moment for a long time
Uh
Well
I gotta take the phone
Hey
Taotao
You...
When did it happen
Tell us the truth
Uh-uh
It's just happened recently
Who is he?
Do I know him?
Out with it Out with it
Uh
I'll talk to you after everything stabilized.
Alright
Talk to you later
I have to work now
Byebye
So exaggerated?
Say it
Did you love someone before?
So you refused me
No
It's just happened recently
I am disppointed in love
but
看你笑得这么开心when I see you are so happy
I feel better now
Congratulations
But you need buy me a meal
To make up for
my broken heart.
You...
Enough is enough
I don't care
Buy me a big meal
big meal
Alright
Took a shower?
Yes
I saw your calling when I was on bed.
Have you finished your work?
Almost
Prepare to go back to hotel
What's going on?
Do you like the gift?
So many people like me in the Moment
So you would prize me, wouldn't you
Sure
What do you want?
Let' go to the Art Exhibition which you talked last week
Really?
But you said you should stay there for three days
Because the negotiation is smooth going
We could sign the contract tomorrow
So I sould pick you up tomorrow
Nice Love you
kiss to you
Ok Thank you
Off work now
Let's go
Zhi It's time to go home
Let's go. Uh
Uh-uh
You guys go first.
I need write something
Ok.Don't be too late.
Ok. Bye.Bye.
Bye
Go Go
Well
Hi
Zhi
You finised? So fast
Mr.Yan
You guys didn't go?
Yep
There were too many people to use the elevator.
We waited for a long moment
Then wo went down stairs
to take exercises.
哦 那个 严哥Uh. Well. Mr.Yan
I
forgot my charger
So i need go back to take it
You guys go first.
Let's go
Look
Is that Mr.Qi's car?
Yes
it is
Where are you going?
Say hello to Mr.Qi,of course.
Mr.Qi
You come back to fast
Is everything ok?
Yes
Almost done
We go fist.
See you later.
See you Mr.Qi
Hush
Let's go. Zhi
What are you about there?
Uh-uh OK
What?
Oh
Don't come here please
please
阮芷
wait
Uh-uh
well
Bailu has some suggestions
She needs addictional recording
Um
Uh
Ok Go Go
See you. Byebye
Bye
Qizhan
Yes
Something wrong with my belly
How about we go first
What's wrong with you
I buy you some hot drinks
Sure
Let's go to buy it
Ok
Look
Is she Zhi?
Wait me for a moment
I ask for the hot drink
Ok
Ruanzhi
Hi
HI
Aren't you staying in the company to do the addictional recording?
What?
Steal away and see the art exhibition
Um
Was there a boy?
Your boyfriend?
Everyone is here
So introduce him to us
Yeah
Introduce more details about him
We are curious about him for a long time
Yes
We meet him first this time
Introduce him to us quickly
Let's talk together.
Uh
Umm
He has some other things to do
Maybe it's too late when he come back
Don't you want to see the art exhibition?
If you are late, it will close soon
Hurry up Hurry up
We could see your boyfriend next time
Uh
Um
Yes
We will dubbing tomorrow.
Let's talk about something about that
Are you angry?
Oh
How to see the art exhibition in that instance
How about going there one more tomorrow
Mr.Qizhan is handsome
Mr.Qizhan is my love
Are you happy now?
This is man.
What's wrong?
I always hurt.
Why I feel you are wronged
What
did I do something wrong?
Why are you guilty?
About our relationship,
You are so scared that others know that
It's not Scared
I don't prepare to face it.
Ruanruan
I don't wanna force you
I wanna stay with you in any time
It's just like this.
We didn't see the art exhibition and then went home.
He didn't answer me even when I tried to tickle him
Taotao
Am I excessive?
Ruanzhi
I don't know
You are a bad girl
What?
You even think I'm a bad girl
Of course
About you
You agreed with him
Then announced it in the Moment
In the end, you want to hide him and wanna nobody knows he is your boyfriend.
You make a true love
become secret fling
Unless
Unless what
You treat him as a back-up.
Oh,what are you saying?
Mainly
You know each other
It's a little bit Embarrassed
We know
He is Qizhan?
Ruanzhi
You still fall in love with him, right?
When is it?
Is it on my birthay?
At that night
Did you
combined viciously
act in collusion with each other
work with thieves?
Whoops No
It's just happened recently
Mainly
I don't how to tell you guys about it.
It's easy
Let me tell you a good idea
At the singing party
you annouce Qizhan is your boyfriend.
I promise
Evrything will be OK
Nice
Taotao is so clever
You are so smart
Why you have a such clever brain
What a good idea
Are you Ruanzhi?
That is not a fact.
It must be someone who wanna trap her
She is a little Internet celebrity
Why do they trap her
Yes
You are right
Yep
Zhi
Yes
Mr.Qi wanna talk to you
Ok
Uh
Zhi
Eerything will be better
What?
What happened?
Come to see it
What's the meaning?
When I see that
It's already on the second in the trending topic list
Arguably
It's usual to dubbing for Bailu
But why it is in the trending topic
According to the source
Ruanzhi admit to
sing the Bailu's new song.
Replacing is a truth.
Then compared voices
It is found that the voices are same,they are from one person.
So
That's the point
In that afternooon
I saw you in the Sunny Recording Studio
You were recording that song,right?
Yes
Ruanruan
You
singed that song?
I'm sorry Qizhan
I
really don't
want to see things like this way.
What does it affect on Bailu?
For Bailu, It's ok.
Her studio just need to release a statement.
What I worry about is
her followers will hurt you.
For me, it's ok.
When it calms down, everything will be ok
Maybe several days later
After all,they won't oppose the person
who is a little unknow dubbing actor
Right?
Don't worry
I'm always by your side
Yes
Uh
Are you still angry now?
I am not angry about you
You shoudn't accept the work like this
Yes
Bailu's followers like idol followers
are so young
and so impulsive
So I 'm worried about you
Something wrong
There are many Bailu's followers at the company's gate
They wanna see you
Go
I send you home first
Ok
Ruanzhi
Make a public statement for apologizing
Uh
Taxi
Mr. Driver
Drive at full speed.
Qizhan
Where do we go
Go for Bailu
I'm sorry,Miss Ruan
We don't mind the followers will go to your company to bother you
Are you ok?
Miss Ruan and us are old frieng for many years
Because Lulu is more popular these days
Someone wanna trap her
But Idon't know they are so extreme
I stand for Lulu and her followers
To apologize for you
Ok
As Miss Lin saying
I think you already
have a Public Relation Plan for it.
Right?
Of course
But
We need Miss Ruan to coordinate with us
Ten million
We buy your voice
Ten million?