=The Double=
=Episode 10=
Sis,
yesterday, I was cleaning up
and found your bag left here.
Come by and pick it up
when you're free.
(She left this.)
(There might be clues from Li Ziyu.)
(I need to find a way to go back.)
This one looks pretty.
I'll try it on.
It does look nice.
Alright.
We'll have it dry-cleaned
and delivered to you.
Wait.
Do you have other sizes?
This one is already your size.
Our models are chosen
to match your body measurements.
I've recently gained weight.
The size doesn't fit.
If possible,
I'd like to go to the store.
Of course.
We'll be waiting for you, Miss Li.
I want to go shopping.
What?
Am I restricted from that too?
Mr. Zhao,
Miss Li wants to go shopping.
Got it.
Send a driver to go with her.
Understood.
Miss Li,
please get in the car.
Miss Li, let me drive.
Miss Li, Miss Li.
Let me drive.
Hello? Mr. Zhao.
Miss Li drove off.
Where to?
I don't know.
(Secretary Tian)
Wu Baohui ran away.
Mr. Zhao, I...
I'm heading back now.
What about the meeting?
Instead of worrying
about postponing the meeting,
you should worry about yourself.
(Zhang Shunyang)
Zhang Shunyang?
How could Li Ziyu know him?
(Zhang Shunyang)
(Zhang Shunyang, Swipe to answer)
Ms. Li,
you finally answered the phone.
What's up?
The course in Bin City has ended.
I've booked an evening flight back.
Before I leave,
I was wondering if I might have
the chance to meet you in person.
Hello?
Ms. Li, are you listening?
Ah.
Alright.
I'll come to see you.
Great.
Ms. Li?
It's me.
Oh, I didn't expect
to meet you in person before leaving.
Is that so?
This place is beautiful.
Yes.
I fell in love with it
the first time I came.
Thanks for providing
such a perfect spot.
Actually,
my connection
to Bin City is
thanks to your sponsorship.
My sponsorship?
Originally,
I hadn't planned on coming to Bin City
until I received your call.
You said
you hoped I could come here.
Oh, by the way,
there's a question
I've always wanted to ask.
Why did you set the course fee
at this price?
Is there an issue with the price?
If ordinary people can work hard
to afford it,
art becomes less of a luxury.
My stay in Bin City was enjoyable.
I have a plane to catch,
so I won't disturb you anymore.
I hope we can meet again sometime.
Alright.
(Special Price)
A price that ordinary people
can strive to reach.
A once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
My idol,
the painting master Zhang Shunyang,
is actually coming here to give a class.
Really?
That's wonderful!
With his guidance,
you'll definitely improve a lot.
Come on.
Ordinary people like us
can't afford his class.
Well.
(Shunyang Art Studio; Special Price)
Why is it so much cheaper?
An unprecedented price.
Maybe heaven is favoring our Baoting.
Definitely not.
Even at half the usual price,
it's still close to 900,000.
I can't afford that.
Forget it.
Maybe in the next life, I'll be rich.
Wu Baohui,
you're about to make a fortune.
A client has their eye
on your big house in the east of town.
They requested you to handle it.
No way.
Did the client check carefully?
That house is priced
way above market value.
Of course.
The client already paid the deposit.
The deposit has been paid?
Who is this client,
paying the deposit
without even seeing the house?
Don't ask.
You wouldn't understand
the ways of the wealthy.
I'll give you her number.
Follow up on it.
You get a percentage.
Got it.
Thanks, boss.
Baoting,
when does registration
for that Master Class close?
Today.
Why so soon?
Maybe because of the big discount,
lots of people signed up.
(Wallet)
(Calling Mr. Liu)
Hello, Mr. Liu.
Can you lend me 900,000 more?
I'll pay you back next week.
The interest
will go with what you said.
Sorry.
The number you're dialing
is temporarily unavailable.
Sorry.
The number you're dialing
is temporarily unavailable.
Please wait...
You brat, you promised to pay us back.
After paying such a big deposit,
she suddenly disappeared.
Could that big client also be Li Ziyu?
(Premium Client)
Why is it you?
Go home.
♪The blizzard came♪
♪It was when we first met♪
♪Yet you made me promise♪
♪To become her double♪
♪The heavy rain beyond the umbrella♪
♪You shielded me from the world♪
♪Love has no second chances♪
♪I overrated myself♪
♪When our stars cross paths again♪
♪Perhaps it's destiny♪
♪A thousand encounters♪
♪All lead to you♪
♪My unreasonable demands♪
♪Are precious emotions to you♪
♪I'm sure I am your♪
♪Only one♪
♪I almost missed you♪
♪No one can replace you♪
♪Let me hold you tight again♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)