=The Double=
=Episode 14=
Here.
Ginger soup.
Come here.
♪The blizzard came♪
♪It was when we first met♪
♪Yet you made me promise♪
♪To become her double♪
♪The heavy rain beyond the umbrella♪
♪You shielded me from the world♪
♪Love has no second chances♪
♪I overrated myself♪
Actually, there's no need
to go through all this.
Is the temperature still fine?
♪In the pouring rain, it was you♪
♪Braving through hardships♪
♪Lying awake, it was also you♪
You're so good at this.
Have you done this for others before?
What?
I said, you're so good at this.
Have you done this for others before?
♪Double♪
No.
You're the first one.
♪When our stars cross paths again♪
♪Perhaps it's destiny♪
♪A thousand encounters♪
♪All lead to you♪
♪My unreasonable demands♪
♪Are precious emotions to you♪
♪I'm sure I am your♪
♪Only one♪
♪I almost missed you♪
♪No one can replace you♪
♪Let me hold you tight again♪
Is it still raining outside?
It's stopped.
Are you free tonight?
Do you want to go for a walk?
I have a meeting later.
It might end very late.
Okay.
We'll talk when you're free.
Sure.
♪Am I her♪
♪Double♪
Hey, Lulu.
I remember you were classmates
with Mrs. Xu Jiaming, right?
Could you send me her contact info?
Okay, I'll wait for your news.
Mr. Zhao.
What's wrong?
Mr. Han has canceled the meeting.
Hello?
Mr. Han,
this is Zhao Jize from Qinghe.
Ah.
You're not feeling well?
If it's convenient,
I'd like to visit you.
Oh.
It's nothing.
We'll reschedule.
Hello?
Mr. Lin,
this is Zhao Jize from Qinghe.
Oh.
You're not in the country?
Okay.
When you return,
I'll treat you to a meal.
Hello?
Mr. Zhang,
this is Zhao...
Mr. Feng...
Ms. Ma...
Mr. Ming...
Those people are clearly doing this
on purpose.
Prepare a list of companies
that have collaborated
with Qinghe in the past five years.
Okay.
Come in.
Do you still want to take a walk?
Are you done with your work?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's go for a walk.
Do you like walking?
It's okay.
I like to walk when I'm stressed.
When my body is tired,
my heart doesn't tire so easily.
How about now?
Are you stressed?
A little.
What about you?
I'm fine.
You're quite stubborn.
Of course,
someone like you who can do anything
wouldn't be scared
by this small setback.
Thanks for your trust.
Would you like
to have candy to ease the anxiety?
Is it sweet?
Try it and you'll know.
Quite sweet.
Do you want to try it?
This is the last...
Is it sweet?
(Lulu)
I've sent you
Mrs. Xu Jiaming's contact info.
(Xu Jiaming: The money is ready for you.
Come to my place tomorrow.)
You look so pretty
even while sleeping.
You look just as good when you wake up.
Why are you pretending to sleep?
If you want to keep looking,
I can pretend a little longer.
I'm going out.
You can sleep.
Where are you going?
Just going out for a walk.
I'll drive you.
No need.
You rest a little longer.
Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
Sure.
If I had known,
I would have pretended a little longer.
(Wu Baohui)
Where are you?
I'm coming to find you.
(New recording)
You really didn't disappoint me.
Come in, and we'll talk.
Where is Miss Li?
She went out at noon.
She hasn't come back yet.
Did she take a car?
No.
(Wu Baohui)
Your home still feels the same.
It gives me a strange feeling.
Stop pretending.
You once looked down on it,
and you won't change your mind.
This is the money you wanted.
Don't come looking for me again.
We're so familiar with each other now.
Occasionally seeing each other
is fine, right?
You keep coming to find me.
Does your wife not mind?
What could she possibly mind?
But,
compared to her,
I care more...
Wu Baohui.
I regret it.
What do you want?
Wu Baohui.
Let's start over, okay?
Xu Jiaming, you're crazy.
Wu Baohui,
did you already plan
to impersonate Li Ziyu
and inherit Qinghe Group?
No wonder you didn't cause a scene
when I dumped you.
So, you've found your next target.
Let go.
Wu Baohui.
Let me tell you.
You'll never get rid of me.
If you dare get any closer to her,
I have a hundred ways
to make you wish you were dead.
Aren't you afraid of your secrets
being exposed?
Want to offend me?
Go ahead, and try me.
♪The blizzard came♪
♪It was when we first met♪
♪Yet you made me promise♪
♪To become her double♪
♪The heavy rain beyond the umbrella♪
♪You shielded me from the world♪
♪Love has no second chances♪
♪I overrated myself♪
♪When our stars cross paths again♪
♪Perhaps it's destiny♪
♪A thousand encounters♪
♪All lead to you♪
♪My unreasonable demands♪
♪Are precious emotions to you♪
♪I'm sure I am your♪
♪Only one♪
♪I almost missed you♪
♪No one can replace you♪
♪Let me hold you tight again♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)