=The Double=
=Episode 17=
(High-end whole-house ceiling)
Hey, be careful.
There are fragile items inside.
Are we leaving just like this?
Buying the old house back
has always been our mother's wish.
What's wrong?
You don't want to go back?
No.
I just feel that after living here
for more than ten years,
I've unconsciously come
to regard it as home.
A rented house is never truly a home.
Don't think too much.
You'll leave with the luggage first.
I'll finish up with Bai Qian
and come to find you.
Take care.
Mr. Zhao, I don't want it.
Take it.
It's what you deserve.
If you need anything,
just call me back anytime.
I hope we can meet again.
([Bank of Communications]
Dear Mr. Zhao Jize, it's your birthday.)
What about you?
Do you have any wishes?
I never make wishes.
Make one on your birthday.
Birthday wishes often come true.
I'll take you to the rooftop
of my house.
The breeze is lovely there,
and the night view is beautiful.
You'll definitely like it.
Alright.
Safe travels.
Today, standing here on this podium,
I truly feel undeserving.
As everyone knows,
(Qinghe Group Press Conference)
Qinghe Group
is facing an unprecedented crisis.
In order to save Qinghe,
we had no choice
but to let go of many divisions.
We've failed the trust
of many employees.
A few months ago,
when the crisis of Qinghe first broke,
the group faced a devastating blow.
Someone asked me,
"Are you stressed?"
Are you stressed?
A little.
What about you?
I'm fine.
Still being tough, huh?
Of course,
someone like you who can do anything
wouldn't be scared
by this small setback.
Thanks for your trust.
I said I was fine.
It's not about being tough.
I just believe
that many people who believe
in Qinghe and me are supporting me.
It's because of your trust
that Qinghe has been able to rise again
and start anew.
Zhao Jize,
this isn't a dream, right?
(Zhao Jize's birthday)
Stop the car.
Driver, stop the car.
Letting Wu Baohui take the brunt
is the only way
to protect Qinghe and you.
Is there a better way
to protect Wu Baohui?
Mr. Zhao.
Answer me.
Make a statement
that Li Ziyu is dead,
and any problems that occur after this
will be your responsibility.
Let's do it that way.
I'll handle the rest.
Mr. Zhao.
Then I wish you
a safe journey.
Zhao Jize,
I've made up my mind;
I'll take this with you.
It really is snowing, Zhao Jize.
Yes. It's snowing.
I want to make a wish.
Has your wish come true?
It's you.
♪The blizzard came♪
♪It was when we first met♪
♪Yet you made me promise♪
♪To become her double♪
♪The heavy rain beyond the umbrella♪
♪You shielded me from the world♪
♪Love has no second chances♪
♪I overrated myself♪
♪When our stars cross paths again♪
♪Perhaps it's destiny♪
♪A thousand encounters♪
♪All lead to you♪
♪My unreasonable demands♪
♪Are precious emotions to you♪
♪I'm sure I am your♪
♪Only one♪
♪I almost missed you♪
♪No one can replace you♪
♪Let me hold you tight again♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)