(Lawless Lawyer)
(Lee Joon Gi)
(Seo Yea Ji)
(Lee Hye Young)
(Choi Min Su)
(Lawless Lawyer)
(Police)
My gosh. Hello, Officer.
You know why I stopped you, right?
Let me see your license.
Sure thing. I should cooperate.
Let's see.
What are you doing now?
Oh, these bills are a bit too crisp.
Are you trying to bribe
a police officer now?
No, it's not that.
Stop trying to be sneaky. Get out.
Wait, hold on.
Gosh, this man...
I said, get out.
Goodness,
cut me some slack, will you?
Come this way, please.
Gosh, I'm sorry about that.
There's a traffic monitoring camera
up there.
This spot should be safe.
- What is this?
- Come on, you know what it's for.
You tried to express
your gratitude toward me just now.
When?
I couldn't close my big fat wallet,
so I was taking a few bills out,
that's all.
Gosh, seriously.
Are you kidding me right now?
All right, then. If that's the case,
I'll be sure to give you
the highest penalty.
Give me your license.
Oh, my driver's license.
Sure, no problem.
Let's see.
Here you go.
(Attorney Bong Sang Pil)
I see that you're a lawyer,
but so what?
Sergeant Park Mun Seong
in Traffic Enforcement...
at Northern Gyeonggi
Provincial Police Agency.
Who are you?
A client hired me for a bribery
case, and I just obtained...
evidence number seven,
which I'll use for the litigations.
No, not that one. Over there.
This evidence proves
that you've been...
demanding bribes in return for
letting traffic violations slide.
The excessive regulation and
threatening requests for bribes...
made my client shed tears.
I'll make sure he's compensated
monetarily for the tears he shed.
My goodness.
Please don't be like this.
I'm a busy man.
Please issue the ticket quickly.
The one with the maximum
demerit points.
Sang Pil, where are you now?
I'm coming to rescue
the gangster accountant.
Please don't kill me.
You want to live? You jerk.
I've been telling everyone that
you're such an amazing accountant.
How many buildings did I buy
with the tax money...
you saved me?
Think about it.
How can I not be attached to you?
You made it.
Yes, what's the situation now?
Don't you hear the scream?
Wait, hold on. Just a second.
Wait for me.
- Who's that?
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- Who's that guy?
- What does he want?
- Hello.
Please just be natural.
Why are you guys just
standing around? Get that rat!
- That jerk!
- Come here! You little...
If you lay even a finger on me,
you'll regret it.
I'm that man's...
See this guy beaten up to a pulp?
I'm his legal representative.
He's a lawyer, Boss.
Why would a lawyer
set foot in this place? How gutsy.
I'm aware that there's a problem
between you and my client,
and I'm here
help you two solve the issue...
step by step
through my legal guidance.
Stop going on about the law,
will you?
Do you think this is court?
Whack him!
I knew that it'd be hard
to talk to you guys,
but go easy on me, please.
Well, if that's the case...
Yes, you over there.
Let me start with you.
What did you just say?
You piece of...
How dare you punch him? You jerks!
- You little...
- Wait!
All right, everything I do from now
will be considered self-defense.
That will be the case only if you
can walk out of here in one piece.
What are you waiting for? Whack him!
Wait, hold on.
I guess you guys don't know.
This suit is
from a high-end Italian brand.
I wouldn't want it
to get wrinkled up.
Now that I've taken it off, you guys
can come at me all you want.
- I'm ready.
- You little...
You scum.
What did you just say?
Listen up. If you use that,
you'll get locked up for five years.
If you drop it now,
it'll be reduced to two years.
Dropping it...
will be considered
a mitigating factor.
You'll end up with a lighter
sentence than even those...
who never used their tools
from the beginning.
What on earth are you doing now?
Whack him already.
Wait!
Have a look at this.
What's your problem...
This shows...
the financial records of tax evasion
you've committed...
while running your company
for the last five years.
Take a look at this evidence here.
You'll be charged with assault
and harassment,
which can put you behind bars
for 7 years and 3 months.
If attempted murder
is added on top of that...
It'll depend on the judge,
but the minimum would be 17 years.
If I report you to the National
Tax Service for tax evasion,
they'll collect two million dollars
from you.
The total amount of money
you lost because of my client...
is 800,000 dollars.
Do you really want to lose
two million dollars...
and end up in jail
because of the 800,000 dollars?
You've had to forcefully
take money...
from many people and do other
shady things to earn your money.
You'll give it all to the government
when it's done nothing for you?
How can we trust that
he'll not report us to NTS?
Who's going to guarantee it?
I'll guarantee it.
What's going on?
Hello, Boss.
What? "Boss"?
Dae Woong, were you...
behind all of this?
That capable accountant told me
that he wants to work elsewhere,
so I just introduced him
to a smart lawyer, that's all.
I'll announce the verdict.
What the defendant did...
to protect herself and her child...
from domestic violence
doesn't fall...
within the range of what is
considered appropriate.
What she did can't be
accepted socially,
and therefore,
it can't be considered self-defense.
Therefore, the defendant...
is sentenced to 20 years in prison.
Ms. Ha.
Ms. Ha!
Your Honor.
20 years?
That's more than
what the prosecution asked for.
How dare you question the verdict?
She was beaten and treated horribly
throughout her marriage of 10 years.
But she killed her husband,
didn't she?
It makes me so furious.
She ran away to a shelter,
but he tracked her down...
and trampled on her
until her ribs broke.
Then he whipped her
with his belt too.
She deserved that!
Which law firm are you from anyway?
She was stabbed with a knife too.
It happened while she was
trying to defend herself!
Are you taking her side
because you're a woman too?
Are you? Answer me.
This is precisely why you women
can't go far in this field.
All you do is show up in court
reeking of your perfume.
Why are you just standing there?
Get her out of here.
It's not because I'm a woman.
This verdict is wrong.
Hey.
I'm way above your league.
No one can challenge...
my verdicts...
It's not like...
judges are always right!
Attorney Ha Jae I...
is suspended for six months.
My gosh. Look at you!
Your condition is worse
than I heard it was.
A suspension isn't enough.
She should lose her license!
Her law firm must
be held responsible too.
I get that I was wrong to punch you,
but...
your judgement was way off,
so I don't regret my actions.
Attorney Ha!
I was going to go easy on you
since you're a girl,
but you asked for it.
I'll put you jail
for assaulting a judge!
- Sir, please reconsider.
- Attorney Ha!
Write an apology...
on the Lawyer's Association website
under your real name.
- Hold on.
- That day...
Don't.
Sit back down.
Look at her!
I did...
nothing wrong.
As a lawyer and as a woman,
I'm...
really annoyed.
Understood?
Are you the attorney, Bong Sang Pil?
Yes, that's me.
Here you go.
Who sent this?
I don't know.
I'm just a delivery guy.
(Your employment
has been terminated.)
(April 2, 2018, Daehan Law Firm)
The trial of Detective Oh,
a murder suspect...
in the killing of
mayor of Kiseong Lee Hyun Soo,
will be held at
the Kiseong District Court.
The presiding judge will be
Judge Cha Moon Sook,
who is known to have turned down...
the appointment for
Supreme Court three times.
Detective Oh has been
denying all allegations.
Boss, it's me.
I...
want to open a law firm in Kiseong.
Is this the time
you've been referring to?
Someone sent me this.
Is this why you're going there?
No,
that's not the only reason.
Then what?
Is it because of her?
Yes.
Take the boys. I'll keep funding...
I appreciate the offer,
but I'm going alone.
You sure are stubborn.
Like mother, like son.
I'm sorry, sir.
It really hurts to
hear you call me that today.
Sang Pil!
Yes, Uncle Dae Woong.
Let's drink.
I want to be as just as you,
but it's too darn difficult
to live like that.
What do I tell him?
I'm sorry, Dad.
"Time cures everything."
That's said by those
who haven't suffered in life.
(Episode 1)
(Welcome to Kiseong.)
I've never seen
fog like this before.
It's like I'm up in the skies.
After my mom died,
my clock stopped.
Listen to me...
very carefully, okay?
Don't ever...
come back to Kiseong.
Don't trust anyone from here.
Do you understand?
Don't trust anyone.
The world of judges
has been dominated by men.
According to a newspaper in Asia
that's the equivalent of "Dimes",
there's a female judge
of worldwide reputation...
in Kiseong.
She's Judge Cha Moon Sook,
and she's joining us today
for the first time in a while.
Hello, I'm Cha Moon Sook.
- Thank you for having me.
- I didn't know...
she was acknowledged
by the newspaper.
What's wrong?
Does hearing it in Kiseong...
make her name carry more weight?
Oh, gosh.
It's an honor.
I think of it as encouragement...
for me to devote myself
to the law and justice.
This train will arrive...
at Kiseong Station shortly.
To those getting off
at Kiseong Station, have a nice day.
Thank you.
(Daeho Stationary)
The office on the fifth floor
is occupied by a loan shark.
They've been preying on locals.
Gathering from the tricks they use,
they're low-class thugs.
Look at this! What a sweet ride.
It's shiny.
With a fresh coat of wax,
we could get 40,000 dollars.
- Let's take out that loan.
- Nice!
What can we throw
to cold, hungry wolves?
Sorry?
Are you thinking about
driving them out?
This is where
I'm setting up my office.
But this is a 40-year-old building.
It could collapse any day.
Sang Pil,
I'll get the tools and follow you!
Where should we go?
- Haeundae!
- Hawaii!
You're also going to...
- Jeju Island!
I'm also going to...
- Hawaii!
We have a customer.
Enough already.
- Hawaii!
You are all crazy.
So,
you're our first customer today.
How much do you want?
I don't think you're not
that desperate.
Well, everyone has their
own little story anyway.
Geum Kang...
Is it your name?
Nothing has changed here.
(Bong Sang Pil)
(Bong Sang...)
Why did you engrave my name here?
I'm...
going to come back here
at any cost.
I'm sorry, my son.
Because I have no money,
we have to move again.
It's okay.
I heard it's a life experience.
My son!
I almost forgot.
- Mom!
- Yes?
Look at this!
Sang Pil, what's this?
You're a lawyer,
and lawyers must always win.
Bong Sang Pil, you're so smart.
When I grow up,
I'm going to be a lawyer too.
Are you sure?
But, how can a lawyer fight?
A lawyer has no sword or gun.
If you're a lawyer,
you have to fight with the law.
With the law?
In court,
a lawyer is a person
who has to fight only with the law.
That's what a lawyer is.
- With the law?
- Of course.
With the law.
You in a suit!
What are you here for?
Didn't you come here for money?
You all need to move out
from this place.
"Move out"?
Be quiet!
Where do you want me
to move out from?
Move out of this office.
"This office"?
(Daily installment loan)
Did you see ghosts
or something at sea?
Why are you acting up in my office?
I hoped you could understand me
at once.
But it was not that easy.
Don't you agree?
Close the door!
What's this?
Are you kidding me?
(Ha's Photo Studio)
Welcome.
Look who's here.
Are you Attorney Ha?
What were you doing?
I was doing what I always do.
Goodness.
The noodles are so soggy.
I don't know how you eat it.
When you reheat it,
it's even more tasty.
And it's quite filling too.
Aren't you curious why I came
home in all of a sudden?
No, I'm not.
Dad...
Even if I got fired from my job,
you wouldn't mind that much.
Jae I...
Later, there will be a trial
by Judge Cha Moon Sook.
Do you want to go with me?
Should I?
What did you do with Sang Pil?
I'm still constipated.
I might have to get an endoscopy.
Mr. Tae!
Sang Pil.
- You were so slow.
- Are you okay?
- We worked everything out already.
- Really?
Sir...
What should I call him?
When I'm absent,
talk with Mr. Tae, the director.
"The director"?
Is he that famous...
director?
What's going on?
Mr. Bong decided to
hire all of us.
Dae Woong Gang,
the Kiseong Branch!
From today, I'm going to serve you,
Mr. Tae.
What?
Welcome to the city of fog,
Kiseong!
- Welcome!
(Daily Installment Loan)
I know why you came home.
Dad, what happened was...
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to meet Judge Cha.
She'll understand me.
Good for you.
Do you still have bitter feelings
about Yeon Hee?
I heard dads love their daughters
so blindly.
But how unfortunate to have you
as my dad.
We don't need another blind lover
in our family.
I guess so,
since I love you so blindly.
Please stand for the judge.
Please be seated.
I can see that many people came
today too.
This city is the most righteous city
in the nation.
Because the citizens of Kiseong
have a lot of interest in the law,
I'm always nervous.
Today's case is about
a married woman,
who feared for her life after
putting up with...
years of domestic violence,
and killed her husband.
I've been a judge in Kiseong
for 30 years,
but the moment of announcing
a verdict is still very difficult.
I will announce my verdict.
The legal interests that are
infringed by domestic violence...
can't be superior to life.
Any violence can't be obstructed
by murder.
However, I have a different ruling.
Because of violence by men,
whose physiques are superior,
women can't find any ways
to deal with such violence.
A woman, who has been tamed
by constant violence,
usually gives up her life...
for the sake of her children.
To get away
from inhumane violence,
the defendant had to make
such a radical decision.
And I'm not capable of
finding her guilty.
This case is about a human being,
who feared for her life...
and had no other choice
in order to stay alive,
thus deeming this as self-defense.
Therefore, I find the defendant...
not guilty.
It was impressive as expected.
Judge Cha is like the Mother Teresa
of Kiseong.
I knew it.
She's incredible.
She hasn't changed at all
for such a long time.
Dad, talent must be important
in this area.
Who are you getting a call from?
No one.
There'll be a customer
in the photo studio.
You should meet Judge Cha
to say hello.
On the way home, get some
groceries and take your time.
- Dad!
- I heard about you.
I heard you've been disbarred.
I wasn't disbarred.
Unfortunately, I was just suspended.
As a lawyer, you should've
legitimately dealt with misjudgment.
- I didn't know you'd use violence.
- I know.
I should've dealt with it elegantly,
but I guess I'm too energetic.
It's a good thing
that you're energetic.
It means you have a pure heart.
Judge Cha,
you were inspirational today.
When did you get here?
Is it because of that incident?
She was daring enough
to punch a judge.
I believe that
the judge made a mistake.
Don't feel defeated
just because you were suspended.
Holding back when you shouldn't...
is the same as losing.
You know that, right?
Of course.
Ma'am, we should go.
- That's right!
- Run along!
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking the photos down.
They're not in business,
so move along.
- What do you mean you can't?
- Dad!
Darn!
- Pay back the loan.
You can't hold out.
Stop it!
Girls should step outside.
Despite my looks,
I'm known as a gentleman
in this line of work.
"Girl"?
What...
Do you want to get beaten up by one?
You have me trembling.
Lady, step outside.
My concern is only with
this nasty debtor.
"A nasty debtor"?
Are you thugs or loan sharks?
I get that spicy food
has its appeal,
but due to tighter laws,
some details can't be
discussed with third parties.
- "Laws"?
- Yes.
You see,
I'm a lawyer. Get it?
"A lawyer"?
That means you understand the law.
Then you should step outside.
I don't want to violate
the information privacy law.
Dad.
Did you borrow money
from those jerks?
- It's...
- Tell me!
Since you're a lawyer,
you can explain to your dad
what's going on.
We'll be back soon.
Pay your interest.
Let's go!
- Sure thing.
- I got myself a radish.
Dad.
What's going on?
What on earth is this?
(Daily installment loan)
- Good job.
- We're throwing these away.
Sure thing.
Be careful over there.
- Hurry up.
- What is all this?
- Over here.
- You should've cleaned them sooner.
I'll do it right away.
- Shut up while you work.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll clean this up.
- This is unbelievable.
Darn.
Why is it so dirty here?
Focus, will you?
Check if you have them.
Put those up there.
Sir!
Wait!
You can't just barge in here!
Are you the owner of this place?
Your first words to me
seem to have thorns in them.
Unpaid interests...
doesn't justify
vandalizing or larceny.
Darn it.
I can't file charges for
assault with a few pieces of paper.
You're very clever
with your use of violence.
The law was revised this year.
An interest rate of...
a financial contract
can't exceed 24 percent.
Did you think you could
get away with 45 percent?
Fine.
Article eight of registration
of credit business...
and protection of finance users.
I will revise it.
An interest rate could be unfair,
but that doesn't
give you the right...
to not meet the repayment deadline.
I bet this isn't
a registered business.
Should I call the police?
Call 1332.
Call the contact center of
the Financial Supervisory Service.
All advisers are busy at the moment.
Not willing to repay money
that was properly lent...
by accusing it of being illegal...
is audaciously immoral.
In this case,
you're also blackmailing us.
What?
I heard you got suspended
for punching a judge.
Don't add to your charges,
or you'll get your license revoked.
How did you know that?
Did you do a background check on me?
I only do that...
with women I'm interested in.
Why you obnoxious jerk!
Be a bit gentler.
I'm not one to step
into this place easily.
The victim won't settle.
Detective, wait!
I want to press charges
on that loan shark too!
You lot!
Is this how you've been
doing business?
You guys have nothing, but you
leech onto those who are worse off?
What else could we do?
We had to make a living.
Also, Ha's Photo Studio...
That's enough.
They only wanted
to feed their mouths too.
I'm sorry.
We only agreed to become
members of this gang...
because you promised
that we'd make a living.
Do you know...
what this is?
She's the lady in a blindfold.
I saw her at my trial.
Bingo.
Sit down.
This place will no longer be
a loan office.
We will be a law firm.
"A law firm"?
That's right. He's a lawyer.
- What a joke.
- That's hilarious!
Hold on.
It's the truth. He's not kidding!
From this day on,
you'll be living
completely different lives.
You, who have been
breaking the law,
will join me and go around it.
Simply speaking,
you'll now defeat the law.
We've been ignoring the law
for quite some time now.
Don't ignore it any more.
Beat it.
- Yes, sir!
- From now on,
he's Attorney Bong.
- Yes, sir!
(Choi Jin Ae Law Firm)
Mom, where were you?
Sang Pil?
What are you doing here?
I told you to stay home.
I came because I missed you.
You can't be here.
Listen to me...
- very carefully, okay?
- Mom?
This...
is your uncle's address.
This is him.
Since when did I have an uncle?
If...
anything happens to me,
go find your uncle in Seoul. Got it?
What about you?
Listen to me...
very carefully, okay?
Don't ever...
come back to Kiseong.
Don't trust anyone from here.
Do you understand?
Don't trust anyone.
Remember...
what I said.
Don't ever come back here.
All right?
(Daeho Stationary)
Hey, Ms. Lawyer.
Just do your job...
and focus on your trials.
Why would you overstep your
boundaries and risk your life?
Shut your mouth.
Where's the memory card?
There's no such thing.
You don't have it? Are you sure?
- Answer me.
- I don't have it!
All right, okay.
If you say so, I should...
believe you.
Are we good now?
It's all right.
But I'm wondering...
It looks like there's
someone else here.
Kiddo.
Kiddo, come on out!
Your mom will be in trouble
if you don't come out.
Shut it! My son isn't here.
I said your mom will be in deep
trouble if you don't come out.
I can't promise you
that she'll be okay.
I'll count to three.
Just to three, okay?
One.
Two.
Three.
Leave my mom alone!
Sang Pil.
No, let go!
No, don't do this!
Stop, please!
Let go of me, you jerks!
- You're a good boy.
- Don't lay a finger on my son.
- You're cute.
- Don't touch him!
Don't touch me.
Let me ask you one last time.
Where's that memory card?
I don't know.
Really?
Well, if that's the case...
This kid didn't even do
anything wrong,
right?
No. No, don't.
Don't! Don't hurt him! Please, no...
Okay, I'll give it to you.
Yes, sir. Where are you now?
I found it.
What would you like me to do
about the lawyer and her son?
Hey, kiddo.
Did you swallow it? Open your mouth.
Open your mouth! You little...
Look at this kid.
I must say, your son is... Goodness.
I'm an impatient man.
I can't wait until he poops it out.
- Hey, give me a knife.
- No.
- Hurry up.
- No, don't. You can't do that!
Let go of me, please. Don't do that!
Let go!
Please... Don't hurt him!
- Let go.
- No, don't hurt him!
No! Sang Pil, run. Run away!
- No, Sang Pil. Run!
- Gosh, this woman...
Mom.
Mom!
Hey, turn on the lights.
(Daeho Stationary)
He's gone!
I think he just slipped out.
- Just now...
- Come on.
Let's go find that kid.
Look in every nook and cranny!
Yes, sir!
Detective, those men killed my mom.
What? Some men killed your mom?
Who are they?
That man!
Did you see that man...
killing your mom with your own eyes?
Yes, I did. I saw everything.
Hyung Man, grab a hold of that kid.
I need to get something out of him.
Detective Wu, did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
Go. Continue along.
Hey, I can't find it anywhere.
Where did he hide the memory card?
That kid swallowed it.
Get it out before I take care
of him myself. It's important.
Then what about the woman?
Bury her with the kid.
All right.
Hey,
did you guys tie her limbs properly?
Yes, we did, sir.
Hey, it's over there. Make a left.
What's this?
Let go!
You little brat.
You're so dead.
Run.
Get back here, you rat!
- Hurry!
- Stop!
- Run!
- Stop...
Come at me all you want, you jerks.
- Mister.
- Hey, wait.
Take this and buy yourself
something to eat.
Choi Jin Ae!
What did you just say?
Say it again. Who?
Choi Jin Ae.
How do you know Jin Ae?
She's my mom.
Your mom and I...
cut all ties with each other
a long time ago.
Leave.
My mom died.
Those men...
killed my mom right in front
of my eyes.
All right.
Let's eat.
Uncle Dae Woong.
Yes?
You're a gangster who earns money
by beating people up, right?
Yes, you're right.
Then, please teach me
how to fight like you.
Why?
Do you want to get back at the guys
who did that to your mom?
Your mom has been keeping away
from me because I was in a gang.
But you want me to make you
a gang like me?
I'll never do that.
I promised my mom.
I told her I'll be a lawyer
when I grow up.
That's a good idea.
Try to be a lawyer and
don't think about anything else.
But my mom told me...
not to come back to Kiseong
whatsoever.
But I'm...
going to come back to Kiseong
when I get stronger.
All the truths...
are here inside.
Sang Pil!
You promised me.
You told me you'll be
a good lawyer like me.
You have to keep that promise.
I'll be watching over you.
I mean it.
(Kiseong Police Station)
(Homicide Team 2)
Let go of me!
- Mr. Tae!
- Yes.
What's this?
Why are you here to see me?
I'm not visiting you.
(Interviewer)
I'm here to interview you.
You're interviewing me?
What for?
It's an interview for
the position of a paralegal.
I chose you as the prime candidate
for the position.
Hey...
Do you know what kind of job
a paralegal does?
Can you see this?
I'm a lawyer too.
Your father is liable to me
for debts.
But, there's no way for him
to pay the debt.
One option is to make you sign the
disclaimer of your body.
That's too ungentlemanly of me
though.
So, work hard as a paralegal,
and settle your debt
fairly and squarely.
What did you say?
You want me to be a paralegal?
- Hello, I'm a lawyer.
- I see.
You got suspended
by knocking out a judge,
and now you're jobless.
You run an illegal loan company,
and you do illegal
background checks.
You're trash.
It might be refreshing
to punch a judge out of anger...
because you didn't do your job
as a lawyer and lost your case.
But what happened to your client?
Watch what you say to me.
You don't have the right to judge me
as I have no idea...
whether you're a lawyer
or a gangster.
I saw many lawyers like you,
those who regard their clients
as not human beings,
but as their meal tickets.
I'm not a good lawyer,
but I'm a lawyer that
someone might need.
You must be helpful to those
who are wealthy and guilty.
They're the people who are likely
to need the best legal service.
Why did you become a lawyer then?
You should've become a gangster.
Why did you study law?
You need to know the law
if you want to violate the law.
Didn't you know that?
Well, I'll be the one to ask
questions from now on.
I'm here not to visit you,
but to interview you.
And I might become your employer.
I'll give you an option.
If you do a good job as a paralegal,
your suspension will end.
Then I'll hire you as a partner
in my firm.
Me? Why?
Why would I become your partner?
A woman who has a loud voice
and is as violent as you,
is perfect for the position
of my paralegal.
I'll inform you with the result
of the interview right away.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Ms. Ha... Okay. You may go.
You have quite the backer.
Where did you find him?
Congratulations! You got
the position as my paralegal.
What the...
Darn.
My gosh.
You told Judge Cha?
At a time like this,
who can help us...
except Judge Cha?
Why did you do that?
Goodness.
Because of that photo studio,
I sent my daughter to jail.
And I had to tell such an
embarrassing story to Judge Cha.
Let's close the studio.
I won't agree with it.
I'll close it.
So, I can pay all the debts.
What about Mom?
What are you going to do
about Mom?
You said you wouldn't move
the studio...
because if we do,
Mom won't be able to find us.
Jae I...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
In order to make sure
you graduated from law school,
I loaned some money.
This is what a father should do
to his daughter.
I'll take care of everything.
So, don't worry.
Ha Jae I!
Go away.
I don't want to talk to you now.
Then, you might not
want to hear this news either.
I vouched for you.
- What?
- Judge Cha asked me to do it.
It was her request to me.
If that is true...
- I want to...
- Don't thank me.
I had no choice
because Judge Cha asked me.
All right. Bye.
- Dad! We're home.
- What?
We're here now, Dad.
That was fast.
That's good enough.
(Lawless Law Firm)
- Goodness...
- Hello.
Congratulations with
your first day of work.
Your first day was supposed to be
a week ago.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Well then, are you prepared?
I'm going to work as much as
the debt that my dad has.
Reduce the debt
according to my daily wage.
What about the overdue interest
accumulating even at this hour?
I'll pay everything
as soon as possible.
You're so quick.
When do you think this work
makes me scared?
I'm sure it's when someone
takes out a loan and disappears.
It's when a debtor is too
motivated like you right now.
Is that so?
"Lawless Law Firm's
king of lawyers".
It suits a lawless person like you.
You shouldn't say such things
to someone who does legal service.
- Geum Kang!
- Yes, sir.
Well...
Follow me.
I'll tell you about the first case
that our law firm will take.
Okay.
"Paralegal".
See you later.
Take care.
Hello.
Here you go.
Thank you.
(We trust in you,
who is starting a new life.)
We're here. Get out.
Are you seeing anybody?
Is that what you want?
Seeing your reaction,
I guess you aren't.
Investigating the case
must be an excuse you made.
You're showing your true colors
as we're left alone.
We're here for an outside duty.
I'm here to pay off my dad's debt,
and I'm against dating my coworkers.
Dating your coworker?
That's uncomfortable.
I guess you decided to consider
our law firm as your workplace now.
Personally, I hate lawyers like you.
I hate those who
pretend to be lawyers.
What's with
the casual language though?
Maybe it's because you punched me,
but I feel comfortable with you.
I see you're keeping it up.
Fine then, Attorney Bong.
Ms. Ha,
we already seem
to be on the same page.
This trial will be
a piece of cake for you,
except for three things.
Ms. Ha?
First,
the client already has a lawyer.
It's called professional courtesy.
I don't steal clients.
It won't be easy...
since the lawyer used
to be a respected judge.
I'm surprised you know
some big words.
Second,
the prosecutor on this case...
is one of the best
Kiseong has to offer,
Prosecutor Kang Yeon Hee.
That doesn't give me an excuse
to reject this case.
What's the third?
The presiding judge...
- is Judge Cha Moon Sook.
- Really?
So it's her case.
What is the client
being accused for?
Murder.
He's being accused of
killing Mayor Lee Young Soo.
Here. Read it.
(Daeho Stationary)
We're here.
We're employees now.
Sir, how have you been?
I called to notify you
of my arrival...
in Kiseong.
Gwan Dong.
What brings you by?
I came to teach a lawyer a lesson.
What?
"A lawyer"?
(Mayor Lee Young Soo Murder
Case Report)
Why do you want
to defend this client?
The prosecutor's office
have definitive proof.
You said you weren't interested,
but it seems you got a handle
on this case already.
Do you owe the client a favor?
Do I owe him a favor?
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Attorney Bong Sang Pil.
Do you know me?
Don't we all start off as strangers?
Attorney Bong Sang Pil?
I want to represent you,
so you should switch lawyers.
Is this how lawyers
get clients these days?
I see you're in
desperate need of work.
I was quite famous in Seoul.
It's a shame...
because I already have
a decent lawyer.
Did you see that man...
killing your mom with your own eyes?
Hyung Man, grab a hold of that kid.
I need to get something out of him.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Detective Wu Hyung Man,
let me make you a free man.
(Lawless Lawyer)
Hand over Detective Wu's case.
I guess I was wrong.
You're actually...
a lot worse than I thought you'd be.
Tell Bong Sang Pil...
that he has two options.
He can either forfeit the trial
or give up breathing all together.
Bong Sang Pil
doesn't follow the basics,
but it's hard to ignore him.
Are you cut out for the job...
of mayor of Kiseong?
I'll do my best, Judge Cha!
I'm her son.
I'll kill you...
from outside the prison walls.