Oh! My Emperor Season 2
Production company: Horgos Wajijiwa Entertainment Co., Ltd
Episode 17
Why do you want to get into the Palace with me?
Anyway, it's my wedding.
All of a sudden, you care about the wedding?
You aren't trying to scrutinize the topography here, are you?
So it's convenient for you to do something bad?
You suspect me?
I am just kidding.
Don't be mad.
Besides,
in your present body,
it's a little hard to do bad things.
No, hold on.
What's wrong with my present body?
It's because of you.
You make me eat so much every day.
Of course I gain weight.
Okay, I dare not to say are fat.
What's more,
no matter what you become,
I will always like you.
Sweet words.
I mean it.
Not just sweet words.
Moreover,
I am holding your hands right now,
which means you are my wife.
Okay, I believe you. Just let my hands go.
No.
You don't want your hands, do you?
Do you know that spicy gluten sticks?
Your place doesn't have that, you know.
Here they come.
Spicy slices, you know?
That is...
Prince Tang,
today is for discussing about the wedding things of Your Majesty.
Why do you bring this vicious woman here?
What vicious woman?
She has a name, which is Xia Bing.
And she is a peace-making marriage princess from the Orion State.
My fiancee.
Prince Tang,
though in that situation,
a private meeting like this,
you bring such a beautiful foreign female here.
Is it a little improper?
She is going to be my wife.
I bring her here
is to eliminate misunderstandings you have to her.
Well, an outsider or an insider, both are okay.
But I have to make it clear first.
Messing around is fine. Do not steal money.
The national treasury is really empty.
Shut up.
All right, okay, okay.
Turn around, come on. All turn around.
An outsider or insider, it doesn't matter.
You are one of us when you get married.
Missy knows best.
You are worthy of being a friend, Missy.
Lord Luo,
I know you have a good relationship with Prince Tang in private,
but it concerns important issues of our state.
It must be taken serious.
I know,
Miss Xia Bing has done evil things
to us before.
But it was because
we didn't stand on same side.
But now...
Now...
As the saying goes,
one false step brings ever-lasting grief.
Then a girl who takes a false step...
Wrong, a girl who made a mistake.
Why can't she be forgiven by you?
If we don't forgive her,
what to do if she continues making mistakes?
You notice that Dragon Egg is not talking.
You guys are talking so much here.
A girl from far away come here to marry.
What harm can she do to the Zodiac State?
Feifei is right.
Missy, you are so great.
Before,
you isolated me just because
I belong to Ophiuchus.
Try to kill me.
But I am still standing here
to discuss major issues with you.
So just give her a chance.
Misunderstandings will be solved in the end.
That's it.
I invite Miss Xia Bing
to prepare my wedding together.
Do you agree?
Hold your disagreements.
Applaud if you agree.
Applaud.
Your Majesty,
this is the ultimate madness medicine
that Orion State developed using Black Pearl.
I hand it over to show our sincerity.
I hope you can live with each other peacefully
and give times of peace and prosperity to the masses.
Exactly, Your Majesty.
Come on.
Beautiful, right?
Why do you bring me here?
What do you wanna know?
What does that mean?
I bring you here
to make you relax.
I know you don't want to be with them.
See?
Is it amazing?
What?
This clothing is
beautiful, right?
Weird.
Just like you.
I harmed you and Ophiuchus's people.
I am the enemy of the Zodiac State.
To my surprise, you helped me to persuade others.
In this world,
it's normal that so many things are weird.
I came here in a weird way,
with no ideas.
And I became the Constellation Lord of Ophiuchus,
and fell in love with
that nerd.
Though there are many strange things,
enemy can't be the enemy forever.
Right?
Not the enemy forever.
I tell you what,
Beitang Tang really likes you with his whole heart.
Just think about it.
Don't always think about the past.
Lots of people are together.
One more person just adds a pair of chopsticks.
Two more persons, we...
add four pairs of chopsticks.
Only need to add two pairs of chopsticks.
You are good at counting.
Anyway,
Your wedding clothing, consider it done.
I definitely will
make friends with you.
Stay here. Don't go out.
Xia Bing.
Bingbing.
Who is being weird for a day?
Stop.
Who are you? How dare you assassinate?
Grandma-Empress?
Xia Bing, you get the balls to prevent my plan from carrying out.
How dare you.
Imperial Archbishop.
I dare not.
I don't mean to stop your plan.
If Luo Feifei
is killed by others,
it will obstruct your big plan.
That's why I took moves rashly.
Please forgive me, Imperial Archbishop.
Xia Bing,
you grew up beside me.
Your temper is really like mine.
The future destiny of the Orion State
is on your hand.
I must follow your orders.
Then I will act according to your plan.
Just...
Hope Imperial Archbishop could spare Prince Tang's life.
As long as he behaves as he told,
his life
is yours.
Thank you, Imperial Archbishop.
Feifei,
you were assassinated again.
Are you okay?
I am good. It happens a lot.
You know it.
Don't worry.
There is a saying goes
the good live a thousand years,
the bad live not too long.
I feel I probably have done
few good things in recent days.
I should pay attention to it.
Can't do that few.
It looks like the Orion State doesn't give up.
Dragon Egg,
do you figure it out?
They already use a peace-making marriage
to resolve conflicts between.
I don't think there will be more conflicts.
Perhaps they does one thing under the cover of another.
But Bingbing saved me.
If not her, I already became a hedgehog with a arrow on me.
And you know it, Dragon Egg.
I truly don't want the tragedy of Ophiuchus happen again.
Is Bingbing okay?
Just relax, she is fine.
She probably come back home with Beitang Tang.
I think Bingbing likes Big white tooth.
You think?
My excellent Intelligence Quotient.
Being fond of a person,
the expression in one's eyes is different.
You do pay a lot of attention to her.
Of course.
Their marriage is also a major event.
Oh, I got another thing to tell you.
You..
No.
It's us.
Our wedding customs of the Zodiac State
is really out of date.
I don't want it arrange like that at all.
How about you handing all over to me?
You arrange?
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
What's wrong? Are you feeling sick?
No, I am not.
I feel you have something on your mind
after you get out of the Palace.
Did they scare you?
They are good people.
Just have a weird temper.
Come on.
It's nothing.
I don't mind.
That's right.
Missy stood up for you.
I believe they will accept you soon.
So it's not because of them.
Yea.
Did Missy ask you something?
Nope, Feifei is nice.
I think so.
Her words are always surprising,
but some of those are true
and break common customs.
Maybe it's the reason why
my brother and Uncle Chen
were so into her before.
You?
I only like you.
Sweet words again.
But
Feifei told me earlier today.
She said there are no permanent enemies.
Even though two persons are on the different stands,
they may be together in the end.
Yea.
The Ophiuchus
was deadly enemy to the Zodiac State,
and was the enemy who killed my father.
But they eventually are together.
Sometimes, I kind of envy her.
Ignoring the masses' thoughts,
no matter how others slander,
she doesn't care at all.
Beitang Tang,
let's leave here, okay?
What's wrong? Bingbing.
Is it not good here?
No.
What are you worried about?
You don't understand.
Bingbing, I don't know what you are thinking,
but
trust me.
Whatever happens to you,
I will protect you.
I am afraid I can't protect your safety.
I am afraid you will hate me then.
Yours.
It's a spring and autumn haute courture.
Beautiful, right?
For me?
I was wondering whether it suits me.
Doesn't suit?
How could be?
I am gonna prepare
the most perfect wedding for the four of us.
Feifei,
could you tell me
our wedding procedure?
It's my first time to get married
and I don't have much experience.
Sister,
do I look like I get married for the second time?
Nope.
Nope, right?
We all get married for the first time.
Tell you what,
on wedding day,
in the early morning,
Dragon Egg and Big white tooth will ride on their imperial horses
to gallop.
Start from their imperial room
to our boudoir.
At this very moment,
Shengnan and Yanran
will stuck in the doorway.
For what?
No red packets, no way to enter.
After that,
they will come inside to look for our shoes.
Will it be too complicated?
Complicated.
It's quite simple.
Men
won't cherish if they can get you easily.
It's true.
Then the four of us will be under people's attention,
with lots of cheers and applauses,
then we will step into wedding hall together.
After that, we will buy everyone in the city a drink. The whole world joins in the jubilation.
boom-bang-boom-bang.
Applauses are everywhere.
People are touched.
So blessed.
What do you think?
Xia Bing.
Huh?
What's going on?
Nothing.
Finish?
Yea.
Why are you absent-minded the whole day?
This is so important.
Nothing, I am good.
I know.
Does Big white tooth...
He must bully you, doesn't he?
-I will beat him for you the other day. -He doesn't.
This kid is...
No, Prince Tang is good to me.
Chongchong, wait for me, Chongchong.
Hurry up.
Here you come, Chongchong.
Lord, what you don't know
is that Master Mei is so stingy.
This one can't give, that one can't give.
Even these bamboo barrels of gunpowders
are solved by us.
Master Mei,
you don't even spend this little money!
you don't even spend this little money.
I turn you in.
Do you believe I search your house and confiscate your property?
Make you become a poor wretch.
It's not me being stingy.
The national treasury is empty.
It really has no money.
No money, right?
I suppose your money is in your belly.
Do you have other instructions, Lord?
Not a big deal. We could raise money by ourselves.
And we will never let you wronged, Lord.
You are so great, Chongchong.
Well, however,
I just want everything be simple.
Anyway, food and clothing in the Palace cost money.
Only the housekeeper knows how high the cost of living can be.
You see,
Your Majesty could have an empress like you,
which is really a fortune to state.
Shut your mouth.
What are you doing here?
According to the national law,
Both of you will be drawn when you get married.
Be drawn.
Meaning wedding pictures.
What pictures?
Nothing.
With your brain and your Intelligence Quotient,
can you understand?
Just know to ask questions.
You guys could stay here. I will go find him.
Okay, you go ahead.
Chongchong and I put gunpowders away for you.
Your pose is kind of weird.
Not at all.
The weird part is you unexpectedly find Su Xunxian to draw it.
What's weird is that you choose Su Xunxian to draw this picture.
So I thought,
you may think drawings of Master
follow too many rules.
Then I specially found Su Xunxian for you.
If you say Su Xunxian is good at drinking and making money,
I totally trust you.
But you say he can draw.
I truely don't believe it.
As the saying goes, methods may vary while the principle remains the same.
I can comprehend by analogy.
Don't question my painting skills.
My mother taught me that personally.
Do you know who my mother is?
Who is his mother?
His mother is the top timber dealer in Zodiac State.
A timber dealer?
And you are drawing us there.
What's wrong with the timber dealer?
Arts are interconnected.
Like making a profit, it is a kind of art
isn't it, Master Mei?
I can't agree more.
What a big profit you are making.
Just this picture
can help you earn thousands of constellation coins.
Okay.
Alright.
You are all artists, aren't you?
Then let me check how
you work.
I just draw it roughly.
Still need more details.
Then it is finished.