Oh! My Emperor Season 2
Production company: Horgos Wajijiwa Entertainment Co.,Ltd
Episode 21
Gragon egg,
Now I have to say goodbye.
♪I'm not perfect.♪
♪Will you accept me and stay with me?♪
I've told you,
you'll be a good emperor.
♪Will you accept me and stay with me?♪
Definitely.
♪Simple isn't humble, there's no wrong and right with love.♪
Well, I
sing a song to you.
♪Simple isn't humble, there's no wrong and right with love.♪
I remember I said
I  can sing.
♪Simple isn't humble, there's no wrong and right with love.♪
♪I'll hold your hand without flinch.♪
Especially the high level songs.
You know,
♪I'll hold your hand without flinch.♪
just like
higher or lower octave.
Up and down suddenly.
I choose one for you.
♪The world of you.♪
♪I'll not afraid even the lights off.♪
Twinkle twinkle little star.
How I wonder what you are.
♪I'll not afraid even the lights off.♪
♪The world of you.♪
Up above the world so high.
♪Even the stars all close the eyes♪
♪Even the stars all close the eyes,♪
♪I still can see you in my dream.♪
Like a diamond in the sky.
The world of you.
You'll miss me, right?
♪I still can expect tomorrow before the short absence.♪
Do you?
♪The world of you.♪
♪Even the dream is far away from me,♪
♪at least you still stay with me.♪
♪You still stay with me.♪
♪I'm not perfect.♪
♪Will you accept me♪
♪and stay with me?♪
♪Simple isn't humble,♪
♪there's no wrong and right with love.♪
♪I'll hold your hand without flinch.♪
♪The world of you.♪
♪I'll not afraid♪
♪even the lights off.♪
♪The world of you.♪
♪Even the stars all close the eyes,♪
♪I still can see you in my dream.♪
♪you stay with me.♪
♪I still can expect tomorrow♪
♪before the short absence.♪
♪The world of you.♪
♪Even the dream is far away from me,♪
♪at least you still stay with me.♪
♪You stay with me.♪
♪I still can expect tomorrow♪
♪before the short absence.♪
♪The world of you.♪
♪Even the dream is far away from me,♪
♪at least you still stay with me.♪
♪You stay with me.♪
It drives too fast in the midnight.
The girl was bumped to fly.
Help her first! Hurry up!
Too fast! Oh my God!
She hurts seriously.
Come on, help her! Help her!
I don't know it is a dream or not.
But I remember all of them.
And it's so real.
Feifei,
recently you read more constellation books
than professional books.
You wanna find a new job?
A new job?
Who gonna accept me?
Do you believe time travel?
Yes.
I also believe the returns of White Snake.
I knew it.
Right.
Nobody believes time travel.
It's incredible.
All accidentally is inevitable.
The rest of them
have something undiscovered causality.
Like fate.
They will meet each other by mutual attraction.
For example, the stars.
They have their own orbits,
but they will meet the other stars one day.
I believe,
one day, I will meet my Mr·Right
accidentally.
All accidentally is inevitable.
Good gal.
Not a stuff.
I have a friend who writes novels.
He said the structure of theater
can explain lots of things in life.
Something looks complex, but actually it's easy.
No matter how do you think about it, it's just a circle.
I can't understand.
I'll sing a
Little Star to all of you!
Boss, you've got a few customers here.
A little bad business these days.
But I think,
lady, your friend got a bad day, right?
Bad?
I'll give you some money.
You may take your friend
to try that one opposite.
Let your friend teach them a lesson.
What?
Please! Please help me!
Please take her away.
The other customers left because she's singing.
Twinkle twinkle little star.
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high.
Dragon egg,
I miss you.
Dragon egg!
According to the observation of astronomers.
Tonight, it's the nearest distance between Ophiuchus
and the earth in recent years.
Because it's so close to earth orbit,
that's why it's so obvious this time.
It's rare
to see that.
Because Ophiuchus just need a little time to cross the Milky Way.
So that the center direction of the west of the Milky Way
which nears the stars beside Ophiuchus.
Tonight! 8:00 pm.
You can expect to see Ophiuchus
in our Jianlong mountain.
Now,
there are many astronomers
arrived there.
I hope all of you pay attention to your safety.
Be sure not to stampede.
Feifei.
In China, the official name of Ophiuchus
mainly belongs to Heavenly Market Enclosure, Housing accommodation and Tail accommodation.
Xiaoyu.
I heard that Ophiuchus is the only one constellation
which can connect with Cancer.
Master! Master! Please stop!
Stop!
Wait, I've remembered it.
Okay, thank you, doctor.
Where?
Workers stadium, please.
Got it.
Don't move! Don't move!
Cold?
You're here.
I thought you'll come here.
Do you know how long I've been waiting?
Bad dragon egg!
I'm not dragon egg.
You are talking about other person.
Talking about other person.
You can just tell me you want my signature.
Is it funny?
Is it funny to masquerade someone's boyfriend?
What are you still looking at?
Jiacheng! Jiacheng!
Jiacheng, I'm a big fan of you!
Quickly! Jiacheng! Take some pictures quickly!
Jiacheng! Jiacheng! Jiacheng!
Jiacheng! jiacheng! Jiacheng!
Feifei,
do you remember I've said
if you mention the other man's name again
then I will punish you.
♪I wanna move to your heart.♪
♪The greater gravity you have.♪
♪I wanna travel into space with you.♪
♪We get in the time machine to see the galaxy.♪
♪Just you and me.♪
♪I undertake you indifference and arrogance.♪
♪You need to accept my unreasonableness.♪
Jiacheng
♪Your faintly smile♪
♪sweeten the air.♪
is my male god.
He's handsome and talented.
.♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪Whether you have expectation?♪
♪I wanna feel your breathe frequency,♪
♪and experience all your emotions.♪
♪Please hold me in your arms.♪
Don't mention any man's name in front of me.
Or I'll punish you.
But Jiacheng.
♪I wanna move to your heart.♪
♪The greater gravity you have.♪
♪I wanna travel into space with you.♪
♪We get in the time machine to see the galaxy.♪
♪Just you and me.♪
♪I undertake you indifference and arrogance.♪
♪You need to accept my unreasonableness.♪
♪Your faintly smile♪
♪sweeten the air.♪
♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪Whether you have expectation?♪
♪I wanna feel your breathe frequency,♪
♪and experience all your emotions.♪
♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪Sing a love song for you.♪
♪Use all the best metaphors for you.♪
♪Keep them in my mind.♪
♪Just let me fall into the Aegean sea.♪
♪The greater gravity you have.♪
♪I wanna travel into space with you.♪
♪We get in the time machine to see the galaxy.♪
♪Just you and me.♪
♪I undertake you indifference and arrogance.♪
♪You need to accept my unreasonableness.♪
♪Your faintly smile♪
♪sweeten the air.♪
♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪Whether you have expectation?♪
♪I wanna feel your breathe frequency,♪
♪and experience all your emotions.♪
♪I feel like fell into the Aegean sea.♪
♪Sing a love song for you.♪
♪Use all the best metaphors for you.♪
♪Keep them in my mind.♪
♪Just let me fall into the Aegean sea.♪
You're still a silly gal.
Can't believe you can't recognise me.
Dot not throw things everywhere afterwards.