Oh! My Emperor Season 2
Made by Horgos Wajijiwa Entertainment Co.,Ltd
Episode 15
I'm so tired.
Pay respect to me and go.
Grandma-Empress,
You can't let His Majesty marry with that bitch.
I can't?
Why?
I know you.
I gave you a chance,
but,
you disappointed me.
Grandma-Empress,
I'm not begging for myself.
Luo Feifei is too restless.
There will be so many troubles if you keep her.
You may go.
What do you want to say?
Grandma-Empress, you might be stay here too long
to forgot our country's mission.
You mean I'm old and confused?
I need you to remind me?
Grandma-Empress, I dare not.
Grandma-Empress, you have your own way to do things,
I'm nothing compared to you.
How dare I guess your godly thoughts.
I just can remind something small around you.
I hope you can forgive me cause I want to protect you.
Nowadays, His Majesty and the Lords get together.
If the trends continues,
It's impossible that shake the foundation of the Zodiac
and replace them.
Grandma-Empress, I hope you decide it as early as possible.
Bilian,
You're more and more capable.
Now you can teach me how to handle things.
I dare not.
Of course Grandma-Empress decide all of the things.
If you have no other things,
Grandma-Empress, I shall leave.
Dehai,
How are my cottonrose hibiscus?
Your Majesty, it's not full of bloom.
Take good care.
It's hard to get them.
It's for Feifei.
Your Majesty, you're so thoughtful to Miss Luo.
Well, I'm concerned.
I need to take a look.
Miss Luo is so lucky.
Missy.
Big white tooth.
What're you doing here?
I came for you.
Let's play outside.
Nope.
I can't. Go yourself.
I'm about to get married with dragon egg.
Grandma-Empress doesn't like me all the time.
At this important moment,
I'm won't touch the tiger's ass.
Alright.
I'll spend more time with you.
Walk around with me.
When does the flower bloom here?
Is it a ordinary flower?
Nothing special.
But it's alone here.
And it looks have good smell.
Let me smell it.
Yeah, not bad.
No, it have no aroma
Your Majesty, look at that!
Who broke my cottonrose hibiscus?
Big white tooth!
He just said it smells good.
and he broke it. Then I said,
Big white tooth, stop! Stop!
He doesn't listen to me! And ignored me!
He broke it here.
Missy.
Brother.
It's my fault.
Missy.
He will not blame you! It's okay.
Every time
I am forced to be the scapegoat for you.
Egg!
Gragon egg!
Beitang Yi.
You may leave.
You know, Beitang Tang did it is not on purpose.
It's unintentional.
You thought I'm silly.
Beitang Tang is not interested in flowers and plants.
I know you did it.
Well,
I was afraid you would mad at me.
I care about you.
You know I spend a lot of time
on it.
Just because I want to give it to you when we marry.
For me?
You need to told me.
Actually, no matter later or early, it's the same!
How it can be the same!
I got it!
Heart!
Beitang Yi.
You're upset?
The last time thing I haven't talk to you!
Now how dare you be mad at me!
I'm just a girl!
In order to marry with you,
I went to the Grandma-Empress by myself.
You?
You just like a nerd and you know nothing!
Now you blame me.
Feifei.
I don't  blame you.
That's right.
I've already sent you a betrothal present,
so where's your dowry?
Dowry?
What?
How can I give you dowry?
I'm HERE!
Well. You wanna get something from nothing?
I'll
give you! Give you! Give you!
Is it what I've sent you before?
Your Xiaomihu is my Xiaomihu.
It belongs to us!
You keep it!
Dowry! Take it!
Okay! After we marry,
II'll give it back to you.
Luo Feifei,
I'm gonna kill you today.
There's poison in the dart.
Your Majesty.
What?
There's a pattern.
Turn-back.
There isn't! For real.
I remember there was a pattern.
I saw it wrong?
What wrong?
Obviously, you wanna take advantage of her.
Okay. Stop it.
I'll handle this.
Also,
Recently you should visit Grandma-Empress less frequently.
Why?
Although Bilian belong to her,
she doesn't suppose to know this thing.
Listen to me.
You mad at me again?
By the way,
you ask Su Xunxian and Shang Yu
come to me tomorrow, I got something.
Missy, you alright?
I heard you were assassinated again?
I'm okay.
Not a big deal.
And besides, Every day, I'm so uncomfortable
if it doesn't happen.
Missy, you have such a special hobby.
Take it easy, Bilian was dead.
My brother is handling her funeral.
Why don't you help your brother?
I'm concerned about you.
They're there.
Why are they here?
Of course somebody invite us.
Prince Tang,
You have such a beauty at home,
why are you not going back?
I'm curious, you're a businessman,
Are you tired with speaking poems all day.
Give me.
Well, good liquor.
You also know liquor?
Nope.
It's impossible that Su Xunxian owns low quality liquor.
Besides,
I smell money in so far away.
Where's Shengnan?
Dali doesn't feel well recently.
She usually wanna throw up
and she likes eating something sour.
Is it heatstroke?
What are you laughing about?
You're still a kid.
You don't understand.
I feel like it's that.
You mean?
I'll go first.
How do you know I can't understand
if you don't tell me.
It's hard to say; it's about growing up.
Alright, stop it.
His wife is pregnant.
She's gonna have a baby.
Hurry up.
Go! Go!
The flour is made by mixing fish and powder.
You make dumplings first, this is stuffing.
Sedan?
Jiao
The three levels. Jiao.
Jiaozi.
Dumpling!
Dumpling. Pawnshop.
What's that?
It's a delicious food.
Delicious!
Hurry up! Do it!
I want a thousand first, okay?
Okay?
This might be more than I need.
I believe I can finish them quickly
with my speed.
If you finishes then you can begin another round.
Round and round.
I got it.
Iet's make it clear,
I
will not do these physical work.
Neither Bai Wuchen
nor Shengnan come.
You don't wanna do that! Well,
Big white tooth.
No!
I just play here.
I'll do all of it! Okay?
Master Su, would you mind chopping the stuffing?
Not bad. Not bad.
I've learned some new skills of
swordsmanship these days.
It's so fluent when I use it.
When I move with the skill,
it's like a dragon flying in the sky.
Shut up!
Can you stop talking?
And do something?
You're such a chatterbox.
Look? Still just looking at me?
There's nothing special!
Brother.
Your Majesty.
Where's Feifei?
After she finished making dumplings
she went to visit Grandma-Empress.
So why are you still here?
I wanna take some dumplings to Xaibing.
You just said
where did Feifei gp?
Grandma-Empress's chamber.
She didn't listen to me.
Go on.
Lord Luo, Grandma-Empress may see you.
Let me see, it hurts deeply.
Luckily, not a lot of blood.
You're worrying me?
You flatter yourself.
I was worrying His Majesty will blame me
if I hurt you.
You okay?
Maybe because there's a lot of blood.
I feel a bit giddy.
You okay?
You're insatiable.
Bingbing, you know,
the first time I saw you in the desert,
I was think it's unreal there will be such a pretty girl in the world.
And I also thought
who will be the lucky guy to marry you.
It will be the luckiest thing in his life.
You did such things to me and Shangyu
as I know you are the people of the Orion.
You don't know how angry I was.
At that time, I just wanted to catch you
and teach you a lesson.
It's all because of you
acted like an idiot when you saw the pretty girls.
Okay! Okay! Done!
Please stop being angry.
I still have a lots words to talk to you in the my rest of life.
By the way, I took some dumplings made by Missy.
It's really delicious!
Sit here.
Dumplings?
Take it here.
This is unique vinegar.
I made it by the Chinese wine
from Su Xunxian.
And added some garlic.
It's so good. Try it.
You don't scared me?
I need to afraid you'll trouble me?
Or afraid you're an Orion's people?
You know I come from the Orion?
I've saw Bilian's pattern.
There're plenty of signs pointing at you
demonstrating you came from Orion.
Everyone knows.
So why you still here?
You wanna kill me here?
Don't you think that's too obvious?
You think you can go safely?
Threaten me?
No, I'm not bold enough.
And you're Grandma of the emperor.
I also wanna be good to you.
And you can give us the best wish.
One more thing,
Grandma-Empress,
Don't you think
it's so strange
that the Ophiuchus assassinated predecessor that year?
I hate the Ophiuchus all the time.
But I also doubted.
My original country.
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Try it.
It's been too long. You'd never tried it.
Have a try.
I haven't ate
such comfortable food for so long.
What's the stuffing?
Pork and cabbage.
But I can taste fish?
The skin of the dumpling is made by fish and powder.
It's expensive!
There's a bit one! Did you see?
You can eat more the big dumplings.
I put much meat in them.
I don't feel I waste them.
Look at the big
Grandma-Empress?
Somebody help? Help!
Lord Luo, what a clever and ruthless trick.
Seems like Grandma-Empress doesn't dare to
bother you for a while.
I really don't know she can't eat fish.
What's our meeting about today?
Today.
I'm sorry.
Today is
Did my words make you feel so disgusted?
Shengnan is pregnant.
Pregnant?
Whose child?
No!
Everyone keeps this matter under your hat,
otherwise people will laugh at me.
Dali,
you yell too loud.
Everyone knows now.