Oh! My Emperor
Production company: Horgos Wajijiwa Entertainment Co.,Ltd.
Episode 6
Brother, Missy is preparing.
Are you...
Can you stop talking?
Brother, I can see that she really likes you.
Why not take a try?
If you don't I'd like to take a try.
You guys are crazy.
You're still so coy.
If you didn't like her
you could have given her to me.
Miss Luo, It's time to change clothes.
Just a minute.
We're adults.
You should know.
OK, whatever you say.
After all, this is a first time experience
for His Majesty.
Miss Luo, please be gentle to His Majesty.
First time?
It seems his thoughts have gone awry.
Brother, relax.
Let's put it this way.
She likes you.
You are just going to help her dream come true.
She helped you out after all.
Get out.
All right.
Brother, remember she likes you.
Don't be afraid.
Be gentle.
Get out of here.
Brother, be gentle.
She likes you.
Jiacheng, let's go home together.
Jiacheng,
Why
don't you answer?
Do I need to recover the scene?
Jiacheng, I want...
Stop thinking!
No, I mean I want all the people
that were here that day to come now.
Take a shower together.
Why?
I remember there were Prince Chen,
Eunuch Hai and...
What are you trying to do?
I just wanna...
Jiacheng, where's your scar?
Even if you like me,
you shouldn't be too impudent.
You're not Jiacheng.
You're not Jiacheng!
Who are you? What's wrong with you?
You are such a lovelace!
Liar! I want to go home!
I think I should have my fill first.
Hello.
It's me.
You! You! You!
You thief!
You haven't paid for the room.
How dare you come back?
I owe you?
Boss, tell you what,
it is a misunderstanding.
A big one.
I told you
I was going to take a tour,
and now I am back!
Pay it.
No money, I'll take you to the authority.
What did I tell you last time?
The most important thing is your health.
Take care of your blood pressure,
lung and heart.
Now I'll seek money for you.
I will soon be back with money, boss.
No, stop!
It's just job hunting.
I'm an adult.
How can I be afraid to look for a job?
I'll find a job.
These are completed products.
Send them to Mr Wang.
Hurry up!
Boss Li placed the order yesterday,
Have you finished it?
Look at this.
Niuniu, come here.
What's up? Mom.
You embroider a character "Luo" on this.
Go ahead.
Wait a minute.
Mom, I did it,
Good girl.
Look at this.
You have been embroidering from this morning,
and this is what you got.
Not even as good as a five-year-old girl.
Five years old?
It's no big deal. My work was just a bit slow and ugly.
Pick one.
Miss.
One day has gone, and I haven't found a job.
Do I have to sleep on the street?
Too bad.
Hold on! Miss.
You're so beautiful.
And you've been hovering around for so long.
Are you in some dilemma?
I am Yuanniang. I can help you.
Yes! I want a job.
No problem.
Just a job.
Follow me, your life necessities will be guaranteed.
Are you working in pyramid selling?
Come with me.
Girls, sing and dance!
Amazing!
Yoga?
I know how to do it.
There are a lot of pretty girls dancing and singing.
What are you doing?
No, I was too excited.
They are professionals
while I'm only an amateur.
I think the show is so good,
and they're so beautiful. I am going...
What?
You wanna leave?
Follow me upstairs obediently.
Change! Change!
Be quick!
Where are you from, bumpkin girl?
Your taste for clothes is so out of fashion!
If our dancers and singers dressed like you,
We would have gone bankrupt.
We're the top class of Donan City.
The competition here is fierce.
You need to improve
your professional and learning abilities.
Start with your demeanor.
What are you looking at? Go ahead!
Come out immediately!
Be quick!
What are you doing?
Smile, come here.
Bring me a cup of tea.
What are you doing?
Why are you so stupid?
You can't do anything well!
Do it sincerely.
Sit down!
Let me show you
what is professional.
Lordling, it's been a while!
Drink up this cup of tea when it's still warm.
Or
shall I feed it to you?
Lordling.
I'll drink it.
This tea
will be beneficial to your health.
Yuanniang.
Yuanniang, I'm sorry!
Sorry! It's my fault!
Yuanniang, I know I shouldn't have done this!
I would like to learn the next trick!
Yuanniang,I would like to learn the next trick!
Yuanniang, we're in trouble!
There's a nasty guest.
Please come here quickly!
What are you shouting about!
Such terrible sound you made!
Bad singing and awful dancing!
Get out!
I want the most beautiful one!
Otherwise, I'll pull down this place!
What is wrong?
What makes our lordling
so angry like this?
Fuck off!
Keep in mind.
You have to use all the tricks
that I have just taught you.
Did you here me?
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Fuck off!
All of you!
OK! You dare bully me,
then I'll make you regret
and I will destroy this place.
Drunkard?
Look at her and learn from it.
Fuck off!
This one...
Stop drinking!
Get up!
What is she doing?
You...
What?
I'm damned! I'm damned!
I just like this.
Let me go.
Put me down.
Let's get in.
This is terrible!
What do you want?
You will know immediately.
Get out of here!
The day for the test.
You old woman of Ophiuchus
stole my beans and wanna escape.
Give it to me!
It's mine!
It's mine! Give it to me!
You've wronged me!
Give it to me!
My beans!
You wanna escape with my beans! Give it to me!
Mine!
You've wronged me!
Get off!
Are you okay? Granny?
I'm fine.
Miss, thank you.
I'm not a thief! This is mine!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
You bullied an old woman in broad daylight.
What's wrong with you?
She stole my things.
That's it!
This old woman of Ophiuchus
keeps stealing from others. It serves her right.
Hit her! Kill her!
It serves her right.
You guys.
Have a heart,
Will you?
Can't you see she is down on the ground?
Why don't you lend a hand?
Why there are so many people?
They've blocked the road.
Follow me.
Do you have any sympathy?
The Ophiuchus people are born to be vicious.
It can't go wrong to keep away from them.
Am I right?
Yes! Just kill her!
She also stole our things!
Nonsense, you are lying.
She's the thief!
She really stole our things.
Let's go!
I didn't steal his things.
Just ignore him. Let's go!
Stop!
Give me my beans!