Make way.
Coming through, coming through.
We're bringing in a washing machine!
A washing machine!
Mom.
I'll go find a place to put it.
Okay, okay.
A washing machine.
Why did you suddenly buy a washing machine?
It's so expensive.
We bought it specifically
to prepare for later
when people come to propose a match
so we can find a well-off girl.
Why prepare for the second son so early?
This is for our eldest son.
The amount of money our eldest makes
is beyond your imagination.
Minjiang...
Anyway, in the future, our family
will have a washing machine, a fridge...
the three, six, and eight major items.
We'll have them all eventually.
Your Minjiang is so capable.
If you know any
girls from good backgrounds,
hurry up and introduce them to us.
If they're too late,
they won't get through our door.
For sure, for sure.
Definitely.
A while ago,
weren't they so poor they were being chased for debt?
Putting up a front.
Wang Shulan.
You're always muttering over there.
What are you saying?
I didn't say anything.
Didn't say anything?
I clearly heard you.
Some people just can't stand seeing others do well.
Zheng
Min
jiang.
I think he's actually quite nice.
Sis, there's nothing going on between Zheng Minjiang and me.
I didn't say it was Zheng Minjiang.
Yingrong.
I've been there before.
If you want to settle down,
I think
he really is a decent guy.
No, no, no.
Zheng Minjiang doesn't like me.
And in his eyes,
I've always been a troublemaker.
How could that be?
Sis, don't you know?
Zheng Minjiang has always liked you.
He even wrote you a love letter before.
Oh, that matter.
I know about it.
But that love letter
wasn't written for me at all.
It was written for you.
Sis, stop joking.
He gave it to me personally to pass on to you.
Why would I lie to you?
He told me himself.
He said he finally
worked up the courage to give you the letter,
but you just took it and ran off.
He was afraid of a misunderstanding,
so he asked me to tell you.
But then
something happened to his dad that very night.
You know what happened after that.
Our families were at each other's throats.
I saw that you two never got along,
so I never mentioned this.
Wait a second.
I'll show you something.
Good thing I didn't lose it.
Look here.
On this...
although he didn't write a name,
look at the content of the letter.
Here.
Cheerful, sunny.
And here.
Independent and strong.
This...
what does this have to do with me?
See for yourself.
Those girls,
seeing my family's situation,
all want to marry in.
And those
who are breaking their necks to get in.
And those matchmakers,
seeing I have ten thousand yuan,
no matter the match,
they can talk it into happening.
Our eldest,
second, and third sons' marriages,
were settled in a snap.
Mom,
look.
Isn't that Minjiang's runaway wife?
Mom, I'm back.
Yang Liu, why have you shown up again?
Mom,
what are you saying?
I married Minjiang, after all.
This is my home.
Didn't you take the money and run?
Mom, what kind of talk is that?
Getting married,
doesn't the groom's family have to pay?
Besides,
I went back to my parents' for so long,
didn't you miss me at all?
Mom, Minjiang missed me a lot.
He wrote every day asking when I'd return.
From now on,
we'll live a good life together.
You're still willing to live with Minjiang?
Of course I am.
I'm not.
Minjiang.
What are you doing here again?
Didn't I make it clear
not to come looking for me?
Minjiang, are you still angry?
We are not husband and wife.
We never registered the marriage.
You are not legally my wife.
But the villagers all attended the banquet.
I don't believe
that every single one of them is blind.
Minjiang.
Young couples fight, but lovers' quarrels are soon mended.
Mom,
this matter,
don't get involved.
Minjiang.
I don't care what you came for this time,
but I advise you,
don't try to scheme against our family.
Get out.
Minjiang,
I know we had misunderstandings before.
The past was my fault.
Look, I...
Minjiang!
What are you looking at?
If it weren't for your money,
who would want to come back to you?
It doesn't matter if you don't admit it.
As long as others think
I'm the Zheng family's daughter-in-law, that's enough.
A woman like this,
whoever marries her is unlucky.
Minjiang,
that Yang Liu,
she was wrong before.
But now that she's back,
if she settles down with you,
it might still be okay.
Mom,
ever since Dad passed away,
I've listened to whatever you said.
Because I'm the eldest,
I have to set an example for my brothers.
But this obedient Zheng Minjiang
is not the real me.
Mom
I've figured it out
I can't be like I was before
You say you're arranging a marriage for me
and I just get married
Whatever wife you arrange for me
I just accept it
And I certainly can't just listen to you
telling me to get back with Yang Liu
and just get back with her
Mom
My own path
I decide for myself
I...
I did that for your own good
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong
The fault isn't yours either
It's that Yang Liu and I aren't right for each other
On the wedding day
she ran off with all the gift money
Now that she's back
it's just because she sees our family has money
How could I possibly act
like nothing ever happened
and keep living with her?
Is it that you...
now that you're making money
want to find a better girl
and look down on her?
Yes
That's exactly what I think
That's fine then
Yang Liu as a daughter-in-law
if you don't accept her, then don't
You're right
You haven't registered the marriage yet
so you aren't officially husband and wife
Even though we held the banquet
and the neighbors all saw it
but if there's a good girl
it doesn't matter what others say
Mom will block those rumors for you
But you have to promise Mom
if you look again
you must find a very, very good girl
a hundred times better than Yang Liu
Definitely better than her
That's good then
But I have something to tell you
You're at that factory now
working as a technical consultant
You still need to bring your two brothers along
Ask that Factory Director Tang
to arrange jobs for your two brothers
Mom
after all this talk
you still want to arrange things your way
Whether it's me
Haiyang, or Xiaochuan
we are all the same
We can all be responsible for our own actions
How can that be okay?
Can't let those two mess around
You work pretty hard
Reliable
You're not bad for a creditor
You practice what you preach
not just ordering me to work
You're putting in more effort than me
Because
I always want to find something to do
Working is better than being idle
Exactly
I feel at peace when I'm working
Fair enough
Here.
I was just thirsty. Thanks.
Wang Yingrong is seducing men again.
You still want to look at that Wang Yingrong, don't you?
Look, who is that man next to her?
Is this the one who went to the labor camp?
The Zheng family's second son.
Zheng.
Zheng Haiyang.
That Wang Yingrong.
She's even hooking up with an ex-convict.
A shameless woman and an ex-convict.
They're actually a good match.
She caused me to lose my job.
I'm not done with her in this lifetime.
Then let's not make life easy for her.
My fish isn't fishy.
Unlike some people.
Who are fishier than the fish.
You know that Wang Yingrong, right?
Heard she's now with that ex-convict.
Hooked up together.
Wang Yingrong, the second child of the Wang family.
Exactly.
Isn't the ex-convict the Zheng family's second son?
The two of them hooked up.
Exactly.
I think they both smell just as fishy.
Anyone who sees them would turn away.
What rumors are you spreading here?
My second son.
Would never hook up with that Wang Yingrong.
Whether they hooked up or not,
I'm afraid you'll have to go home and ask to know.
Exactly, exactly.
Go back and ask.
Don't be unaware of the situation,
And say "no" so decisively here.
Wait until I go back and ask clearly.
I'll tear your mouths apart.
Wang Yingrong.
You come out here.
Did you seduce our Haiyang?
Wang Yingrong.
Speak for yourself.
You homewrecker.
Why are you seducing my Haiyang?
Mom.
What are you doing?
I heard people outside saying.
That you and Wang Yingrong are hooking up.
It makes me angry just hearing it.
They are ruining your reputation.
If it's about what they said,
Why come back and scold Sister Yingrong?
I'm an ex-convict anyway.
Am I afraid of others ruining my reputation?
Getting involved with the Wang family.
Is worse than being an ex-convict.
It won't do.
I'm going to find that Wang Yingrong today.
And make her give me an explanation.
Mom.
You heard wrong.
The point of what they said was me.
But.
But they clearly said.
You and Wang Yingrong.
Do you think Wang Yingrong is stupid?
What do you mean?
Do you think with her conditions,
She needs to find an ex-convict?
Our two families are so close.
It's perfectly normal to exchange a few words when we meet.
Just don't worry about how others spread rumors.
Anyway, there is one fact in what they said that isn't wrong.
I am just an ex-convict.
Son.
Don't think so much.
Even if I'm out, it doesn't change the fact.
If I can't make something of myself,
I can't blame others for talking about me like this.
Forget it, forget it.
Don't worry about what those gossips say.
Don't take it to heart.
I won't take it to heart either.
Let's go, let's go home.
Whose daughter lacks upbringing like that?
It's indecent.
Alright, alright.
Mom.
Little Sister.
Come back with me.
Hey.
Ying Tang.