I really like you
I...
Help!
Zheng Haiyang, Zheng Xiaochuan
Hurry up
Quick, quick, quick
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Big Bro
He...
He's jealous
He drank too much
He's a bad drunk
You guys hurry and take him away
Take Big Bro away
Just take him back if he's drunk
Let's go
Let's go, Big Bro
Big Bro, let's go
Which one of you is Zheng Minjiang?
Who's looking for me?
Who are you guys?
We're workers from Boss Tang's factory
We'd like to ask Master Zheng to come take a look at a machine
I am
No
Big Bro, should we go?
Go
Let's go
Master Zheng
This way, please
You must be Master Zheng
Master Zheng
I've been waiting for you for a long time
Anyway, the money for breaking the machine...
I definitely can't afford to pay it
Might as well let Zheng Minjiang fix it
Brother, what is the meaning of this?
Why did you send people
To tie us up and bring us here?
It wasn't kidnapping
Let go, let go
I just wanted to beg you, brother
To save my factory
My men don't know how to handle things
They were a bit anxious
You want
Me to help you fix the machine?
Yes, yes, Master Zheng
Uncle Tang, he can't do it
Look at how drunk he is
He doesn't look like a skilled worker at all
If he breaks your machine
It won't be worth the loss
Yang Liu
You don't understand Zheng Minjiang at all
He has the skills and the ability.
He's not worthless like you said.
Are you a skilled worker?
Is it your place to speak up here?
It's not your place to talk either.
Stop talking.
My dad hasn't even said anything.
Just think about it, everyone.
If he really had that kind of skill,
how could he fail to even get
the position of Director?
His family is poor as dirt.
Uncle Tang,
why don't you just wait for the German expert?
Don't get scammed by this guy.
Boss Tang,
he's just drunk right now.
Once he sobers up,
he can definitely fix it.
Li Guangming,
tell me, this Master Zheng,
how are his skills and ability, really?
Boss Tang,
that position of Director...
it originally belonged to Zheng Minjiang.
I got someone
to take his spot.
But he really has talent.
Minjiang,
if you just fix the machine,
I'll give the Director position back to you.
I don't care about that.
I just hope
to work and live with a clean conscience.
You think I'm like you,
obsessed with being an official?
If you can't fix it,
just admit it and be done with it.
Making excuses, pretending to be drunk...
Aren't you ashamed?
Dad,
he simply can't fix it.
We've definitely been tricked by him.
Second Brother,
what if Big Bro can't fix it?
How about I help Big Bro back home first?
Even if he waits to sober up tomorrow to fix it.
You have a point.
Big Bro really drank too much today.
Don't let him do anything stupid.
Hurry up and drag him back.
If they won't let him go,
I'll take the heat.
Hurry up.
Big Bro,
this machine is extremely precious.
If you don't fix it, you'll have to pay damages.
Let's not take on this mess.
Let's go.
You haven't asked him yet.
How do you know he can't do it?
Zheng Minjiang,
look at me.
You are a rare talent,
and now you just need a good judge of talent.
This is the most important moment of your life.
Tell me, can you do it?
Of course.
Are you drunk too, Sister Yingrong?
Encouraging my brother like this.
Boss Tang,
my Big Bro really drank too much.
He's talking nonsense.
I'm not talking nonsense.
I can fix this machine.
And,
I can do it right now.
Good, good!
Zheng Minjiang, I support you.
Big Bro!
If you don't fix the machine,
we'll have to pay for it.
Our whole family
won't be able to pay it off in two lifetimes.
Don't worry.
Hey.
Can you actually do this or not?
If you can't, just admit it.
Don't waste everyone's time here.
Exactly.
Look at him.
Fixing a machine,
and he's sweating all over.
He doesn't look like a man at all.
Quiet down.
Can't you see he's fixing the machine?
What are you looking at?
This machine...
is indeed a bit complex.
See?
I told you he was a fraud.
Zheng Minjiang,
how could you be like this?
If you can't do it,
don't try to be a hero.
If you break it,
can you afford to pay for it?
Stop talking nonsense here.
Zheng Minjiang,
I believe in you.
Wang Yingrong,
are you defending him that much?
The two brothers...
haven't even said anything yet,
and here you are, chattering away.
If you ask me,
you two must be in cahoots.
How about this?
You apologize to me,
and in front of everyone,
admit that you two are frauds.
Pay us back the money,
and I might just let you off.
Pay money?
Can money make up for our losses?
I want him in jail!
Done.
Is it really done?
How is that possible?
When I fixed it last time,
didn't it short-circuit and burn out?
The machine's central control system...
the inverter was burnt out.
As for how I fixed it,
I don't need to explain the details to you.
You are Director Li,
my superior.
Just now,
you should have seen it clearly.
Boss Tang,
start the machine and take a look.
Okay.
Master Zheng really is Master Zheng.
I can't thank you enough, Master Zheng.
I knew you could do it.
Is this Zheng Minjiang actually a talent?
How come I didn't see it before?
Master Zheng.
Here is ten thousand in cash.
It's to thank you...
...as a reward for fixing the machine for me.
Boss Tang.
This is too much.
Not at all, not at all.
I also want to sign an agreement with you.
Not a liability agreement.
It's that I want to invite you...
...to be a Technical Consultant at my factory.
About the Technical Consultant position...
...let me think about it.
But don't worry.
If the machine has any more problems...
...contact me anytime.
Good, good, good.
Then I'll have Xiao Huo send the agreement over.
You think it over carefully.
But this money...
...you must accept it.
You have to believe...
...you're worth it.
And you're worth even more.
Boss... Boss Tang.
Zheng Minjiang fixed that machine.
I don't have to pay that 500,000, right?
The agreement you signed...
...what does it have to do with him fixing the machine?
Boss Tang, I...
You have to pay what you owe.
Boss Tang! Boss Tang!
Zheng Minjiang! Zheng Minjiang!
Put in a good word for me!
Minjiang.
Let's go.
Minjiang!
No...
You think just because I'm down on my luck...
...that you'll be better off?
At worst, we'll both go down together.
You... are truly useless.
If you had found Master Zheng earlier...
...would all this have happened?
You...
...idling around all day long.
Someone like you...
...still wants to inherit my assets?
Keep dreaming!
Boss Tang!
It's fixed!
A little less, please, Boss Tang!
Honey...
I don't know how Zheng Minjiang did it.
He must have pulled some trick.
Go to hell.
Do you have any idea...
...because of your nonsense...
...how long our factory's production was delayed?
How much loss it caused our family?
He...
...how could he possibly know how to fix this machine?
He grew up here his whole life.
He's never even been anywhere.
How can he compare to that German expert?
Did you hear that?
My dad called me useless!
Said I'm not qualified to inherit the family fortune!
Are you satisfied now?
No, Tang Yan...
Listen to my explanation.
I definitely wanted to help you.
Get off.
I knew you two had something going on.
I heard that kid call you Sister-in-law the other day.
Don't follow me anymore.
Tang Yan!
Are you dumping me?
Don't follow me!
Tang Yan!
There really is ten thousand.
There really is ten thousand!
There is!
Big Bro, you scared me to death just now.
I didn't know if you were really drunk in there
or just faking it.
Made me worry all night.
I broke out in a sweat.
You see.
As I was fixing it,
I sobered up.
It's all good now.
Now that we have this money,
we're the new rich.
We're the new rich!
Also,
didn't that guy just say
he wants to hire you as a Technical Consultant?
He'll definitely give you lots more money later.
I'd like to see
who dares look down on us now.
I really didn't expect it.
Master Zheng isn't great at drinking,
but his skills are pretty good!
Half the credit
goes to you too.
What's it got to do with me?
What's it got to do with you?
I...
If it weren't for you
giving me that push forward,
I wouldn't have taken this step.
Anyway, I'm happy for you.
We drank tonight,
and we drank happily.
That's right.
Let's go back and keep drinking.
Keep celebrating.
No, no, no. Just kidding.
Time to go back and sleep.
Gotta keep working tomorrow.
Your brother succeeded.
We still have to keep working hard.
Exactly.
We need to succeed too.
Succeed.
Let's go.