[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 11]
[Planning for College Life]
Chen Miren.
I heard that you and Zhong Wei
walked around the playground for five loops
and listened to music for two hours with the same pair of earphones.
He even fed you ice cream?
How did you know?
The lucky girl is with the campus heartthrob. It's big news.
The school forum broadcasted it live.
Chen Miren.
You're a lucky star in the school now.
Everyone wants to know
what he likes about you.
Your face
is barely above the average level.
Your figure
is not that good.
Not to mention your academic performance.
I can only say
beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
Why is Zhong Wei more lovesick than me?
They had an appointment since high school.
Yes.
Was it possible that Zhong Wei wasn't handsome
and had bad grades back then?
Check the school forum.
Hurry.
[Makka Pakka]
Chen Miren conquered the campus heartthrob for the second time, once again earning the title of the lucky girl.
Huang Xiaoyue cleared his name and regained his innocence.
[Makka Pakka]
Put this on.
Do I have to?
Otherwise, don't get in the car.
Huang Xiaoyue,
you're still single after all this time?
Yes.
I was wondering why someone abandoned Zhong Wei
for Huang Xiaoyue.
It's totally unreasonable.
You can talk about it.
But don't launch personal attacks.
I, after all, have been a rival in love with Zhong Wei.
A rival in love?
Does Zhong Wei take you seriously?
I'm the one who doesn't take him seriously.
How about this?
Good.
Get in.
This is an unofficial competition.
Isn't it easy to win an award?
Our Ziqi
just got a fifth-level piano certificate.
Last month, in the piano competition
held by the International Piano Association last month,
she won a gold prize.
Tianci
participated in the recitation competition last week
and won the first prize in the city.
He won the award in the composition competition yesterday.
We don't even have enough space for the trophies.
In the future, Tianci
will go to Hanhai University.
Right?
Sorry, I'm late.
Greet the aunties.
Hello, Aunties.
Let me introduce.
My son Zhong Wei
is a top student in the Business Management Department of Hanhai University.
You know Hanhai University, right?
A top university in China.
Your Tianci and Ziqi
can also enter that university
if they work hard for more than ten years.
By the way,
he is also the school ambassador.
He is even on the poster.
Isn't he handsome?
Look at him.
He can rely on his looks,
but he insists on relying on his talent.
Mom.
Come, have some tea.
Bai Ran.
Bring Zhong Wei out more often.
Zhong Wei.
Help my Tianci with his studies
when you have time.
My son is very busy.
Not only is he going to school,
but also starting a business.
He doesn't rely on his father,
but on me.
Let's have tea next time.
Every time we drink tea, they show off their child,
as if they are the only ones with a son.
You've earned dignity both on the surface and at a deeper level.
What about the thing I asked of you?
Isn't it just about additional investment?
I'll transfer the money to you in a few days.
Well.
I want to ask you for money for some emergency.
What for?
I'm in a relationship.
I don't have money.
Zhong Wei.
You're running out of money because of dating?
You made up such a terrible lie.
I'm really in a relationship.
Look.
She's not as good as me,
but she's quite cute.
Much prettier than you.
Is this your attitude to ask for money?
No.
I mean
you two are different types.
But both of you are at the top level
among your type respectively.
That's more like it.
Take the money.
Thanks.
Wait.
Let's go.
It's all here.
Keep it in mind. I need to go to the restroom.
Look at this.
I have exclusive news.
Where did Zhong Wei go?
To the restroom.
Chen Miren.
I have something to tell you.
What?
The truth is cruel.
But we have to face it bravely.
Haven't you grown taller?
Go away.
Although you curse me,
as your
best friend,
I must tell you
Zhong Wei is a fake rich second-generation.
I saw him today...
Huang Xiaoyue, don't talk nonsense.
What's that look on your face?
Did you see it too?
Zhong Wei must have his reasons.
And I think
it's no big deal.
No way.
You have no bottom line.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Chen Miren.
Let me tell you.
As your best friend,
let me remind you.
You must have a bottom line.
Take care of yourself.
Better late than never.
What happened?
Tell me.
Exactly.
What did Huang Xiaoyue tell you?
What else can he say besides gossiping?
Well,
I'll bring you the clothes tonight.
What clothes?
The clothes you asked me to wear that day.
That piece of clothing?
Did you remember it
while I was in the bathroom?
This is my school.
It's not very big.
But the scenery is pretty good.
Thank you for inviting me to your school.
Everything is beautiful.
You're beautiful too.
I should thank you
for practicing English with me.
You speak very well.
It is a long way to go.
Let's continue to learn from each other.
I may not be able to.
What do you mean by that?
I have to go back to America to deal with some troubles.
So I may not go to the oral language school
for a long time.
But I'll be able to chat with you every day
and supervise you to practice oral English.
We'll see.
Honey.
Why are you here?
I'm here to tell you some good news.
What is it?
The eyebrow razor pen
that we invested in
became popular as soon as it was launched.
It's almost sold out.
Really?
I knew my wife
has a good investment sense.
Thank you for your support.
By the way, Honey,
the founder
launched a new project.
The powder box game console.
This looks like a powder box,
but it's not an ordinary powder box.
The back can be a game console.
If we take it with us when we go shopping,
we can reapply makeup and entertain ourselves.
And there are many games inside.
Look, Super Mario,
Islands of Adventure,
and Tetris.
What do you think?
Not bad, right?
Good.
Would you like to invest in it?
Chen Miren.
[Boys' Dormitory]
My bike broke down.
I was delayed on the way.
It's okay.
It's clean.
You cleaned it?
I cleaned it with the washboard.
The quality is good.
[Boys' Dormitory]
You cleaned it very well.
I put some conditioner when I washed it.
Smell it.
It does smell good.
I'll get going then.
I put the same conditioner on my clothes.
[Boys' Dormitory]
Zhong Wei.
Is this the love token
between you and Chen Miren?
Such a long thread.
Could it be a knock-off?
Huang Xiaoyue.
Smell it.
Can't you tell?
Nothing special.
There's a smell
that bachelors can't smell.
Let's see how long you can show off.
[Yao Weijing]
I look ugly in this photo.
No.
You're the most handsome.
[Fang Mao: I look ugly in this photo.]
[Yao Weijing reminds Fang Mao: No. You're the most handsome]
How can you bear that?
Let me scold her for you.
No need.
[Followed]
It's a smurf account.
Zhong Wei is a fake rich second-generation?
Revealing the true color of Hanhai's campus heartthrob.
He's not a real rich second-generation.
Zhong Wei
is a campus heartthrob who sweeps Hanhai University
and wins many girls' hearts
and a legendary rich second-generation
with countless wealth.
But why
does he only ride a bike or take a bus for traveling?
Why would he
go through the hard labor of construction work
during his holiday
just to earn three times the hourly wage of 60 yuan?
What made him
[Construction Area
Mind Your Safety]
sacrifice his dignity
and be kept by an upper-class society's wealthy woman?
The truth is
Zhong Wei
is just a fake rich second-generation.
Working on the construction sites?
Doing labor work?
Being kept?
What're you talking about?
That's his sister.
Chen Miren. Don't worry.
Look at Zhong Wei's sister's style.
Zhong Wei doesn't look like a fake rich second-generation.
I mean it.
But
this photo of him working on the construction site doesn't look fake.
Was he experiencing life?
Actually, Zhong Wei
is not a rich second-generation.
Chen Miren.
You knew it?
Yes.
Then it's fine.
Right.
It doesn't matter if he's rich or not.
But
if he pretends to be a rich second-generation while he's not,
it's a matter of character.
Right?
Right, Zhao Gu?
Boring.
What character?
Zhong Wei never said
he's a rich second-generation.
Besides,
even if he pretended to be a rich second-generation,
it's just that he has strong self-esteem.
What does it have to do with his character?
Yes.
Zhong Wei
has strong self-esteem,
but his character is guaranteed.
I still think we should observe more.
Are you done talking?
I'm going to bed.
Have you read the campus forum?
Yes.
Zhong Wei seems to be a fake rich second-generation.
Turns out it's all fake.
I thought she was really lucky.
However, it's all fake.
Yes.
As to Zhong Wei,
people say he is the descendant of a powerful political and business alliance,
with a substantial overseas inheritance,
hailing from an artistic family.
None of these is true after all.
He even rode a bike in the name of low carbon
and environmental protection.
Is it possible that he can only afford a bike?
Do you think
that everything he's wearing
is counterfeit?
Are you done?
What's wrong with doing manual labor?
Is labor shameful?
What's wrong with making money with his own hands?
You're making up stories based on the few photos
that are even blurrier than the ones taken at the photo studio when I was three.
Is it fun?
Besides,
Zhong Wei has never labeled himself as a rich second-generation.
His excellence and brilliance
have never come from others.
You are jealous.
You don't want others to be good.
How pathetic.
Shameful.
Chen Miren.
I admit you made an excellent speech.
But can you give me back my chopsticks?
[Jinshi Rice Noodles] [Hui's Pastry]
Come down.
Let's go.
Your mouth is for eating.
[Recharging]
Thank you.
I'll recharge it with 50 yuan.
At least 100 yuan.
I used to recharge it with 50 yuan.
The recharge system has been upgraded.
At least 100 yuan.
Will you recharge it?
[Recharging]
Take this.
Hurry up. Ten yuan short.
100 yuan.
This one is damaged. It can't be used.
[Canteen culture Line up voluntarily]
The area of damage hasn't exceeded
20 square millimeters.
Why can't you use it?
I said no.
Are you going to recharge?
[Canteen culture Line up voluntarily]
Can we recharge it first?
Right.
Recharge it.
Actually, we can eat better.
It's okay.
I just want to eat this today.
[Southern Rice noodles and Northern Noodles]
Eat up.
I'm starving.
Eat more.
You work so hard.
You need more nutrition.
We study the same thing.
Why do you say I'm tired?
Eat up.
Leave me alone.
Here.
You not only have to study
but also teach me.
You must be tired.
Zhong Wei.
Even if you eat noodles,
can't you add some chicken drumsticks for Chen Miren?
I'm on a diet.
Do you eat three meat buns in the morning when you're on a diet?
Zhong Wei.
Is what's said on the school forum true?
Are you really a fake rich second-generation?
What fake rich second-generation?
Well.
Have you heard?
In our school's agricultural department's
experimental field,
a giant hybrid custard apple has grown.
It was stolen.
They checked the CCTV footage.
The culprit was a monkey
which escaped from the zoo.
It has been sent back to the city zoo.
Monkey?
Why haven't I heard of such big news?
Who caught it in the end?
It seems to be Mr. Wang, the cleaner of our school.
He chased the monkey with a broom
and ran around the school several times.
Chen Miren.
Can you stop changing the subject?
Zhong Wei.
Now everyone says
you're not a rich second-generation, but you pretend to be one.
Is it true?
Does it matter if he's a rich second-generation or not?
He makes money with his own hands.
He's much more glorious
than those who can only feed on their elders.
Besides,
as the saying goes...
That's right.
I'm just a fake rich second-generation.
My parents got divorced.
Then my dad found me a stepmother.
My monthly living expenses
are only along the poverty line.
I study during the day and work as a bricklayer at night.
This is my first time eating meat in half a month.
Chen Miren.
Zhong Wei is so pitiful.
Although he's pitiful,
he has a good character.
Eat more.
Enough for me. You eat too.
We're finally going to watch
[Yao Weijing]
Listen, Love is Crying.
[Fang Mao]
Let's watch a movie tomorrow.
I have something to do tomorrow.
Maybe another day.
[Oh]
Zhong Wei.
Let's watch the ball game tomorrow.
I'll buy wine. You buy duck necks.
Sure.
You're not free tomorrow.
We're going on a date.
I'm not free tomorrow.
Date?
Zhong Wei.
Are you going to take Chen Miren to the east street of the school
for a barbecue worth 18 yuan per person
on your date?
Huang Xiaoyue.
Did you give me the money we split for the barbecue last time?
Han.
Wait for me.
Leave the date to me.
Okay.
You plan. I'll pay.
No problem.
Miaomiao, sit here.
No.
I don't want to be a third wheel.
I'll sit here if she wouldn't.
I can explain.
The second chapter
is about simple income determines theory.
We divide it into
the
output changes with investment.
Xu Miaomiao.
As to the acceleration module for investment needs...
I still want to explain it.
No need to explain.
I'm not a pervert.
I know.
Then why did you hit me?
Inertia dictates.
Do you really dislike it when people touch your hair?
Very,
extremely,
absolutely dislike it.
Let's make an example.
Let
Y represents output,
with Y1 and Y2 being output for two different periods.
K represents the capital stock.
[The food list for the fifth live broadcast]
K1 and K2
represent the capital stock for two different periods.
[Fourth Lucky Pastry Shop]
Let K be the capital-output ratio,
which represents the amount of capital required per unit of output.
Then
there must be
K equals KY.
Here...
Hello?
Hello.
Why didn't you reply to my messages?
I was in class.
What's the matter?
Nothing serious.
Your brother is about to have his holiday.
Your dad and I plan to
take him to the big city to visit you
and travel around
to broaden his horizons.
What's the name
of your university?
And
is it far from the museum?
What are you going to do here?
I don't have time to show you around.
Why are you so indifferent?
Your dad and I
also want to visit you.
No need.
I'm fine.
That's it. I have things to do.
This kid...
Hello.
Bodybuilding?
Yes.
I just finished skiing with my friends.
I'm working out in the gym in London.
See?
Yes, it's gorgeous.
That's not enough.
When you come to London,
I will show you
the real charm of this city.
Okay.
That's a deal.
By the way,
I'd like to introduce my friends to you.
This is Lisa.
Hello.
Hello, Lisa.
My name is Zhao Gu.
Weijing.
Fang Mao.
I was delayed on my way here.
It's okay.
Is there still time?
Sure.
Gosh.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Fang Mao.
Luo Si.
Why are you here?
Aren't you busy today?
Are you following me?
What?
Am I interrupting you?
[Movie guide]
I'm here to give her the keys.
Whose keys?
My keys.
Why do you have her keys?
She's the daughter of my supervisor.
[CFTIDE CINEMA]
Fang Mao.
Explain it to me.
What else do you want me to say?
Why do you watch a movie with her?
I just said
I'm here to deliver the keys.
Who is she with?
How would I know?
Weijing.
[CFTIDE CINEMA]
Sorry, I'm late.
Let's go in.
Why didn't you report to me
that you're sending keys to your supervisor's daughter?
Luo Si.
Don't I have
personal freedom at all?
Do I have to report to you when I send the keys?
Aren't you going too far?
I...
[Patriotism, law-abiding, integrity, and courtesy]
Luo Si.
Didn't you go to watch a movie with Fang Mao?
Why are you back so soon?
The movie is boring.
So I came back first.
Miaomiao.
Can you lend me a piece of your clothes?
Why?
Tomorrow is my first date with Zhong Wei.
I bought some clothes
on the Internet urgently yesterday,
but the seller sent me the wrong ones.
I couldn't wear them.
Come with me.
Elegant style.
It's a must for a date in a Western restaurant.
Lady style.
It's the classic style for afternoon tea in the cafe.
And
the cute style.
It's suitable for you to watch a movie or a play.
You won't go wrong with it.
You choose.
Anything else?
I've already considered all the dating locations for you.
What else do you need?
Look.
This is my date place tomorrow.
Dear.
Wear more tomorrow.
Just make sure you don't get bitten all over by mosquitoes.
Do you think Zhong Wei's face
[Do you think Jongwei's face is also plastic surgery?]
went through plastic surgery?
I don't have money. I can't afford it.
How can you bear this?
What's wrong?
I think it's fun.
They all said you're a fake rich second-generation.
[Heng Chang]
I am.
My dad gave me so little money every month.
I can only struggle along the poverty line now.
That's to cultivate
your frugal ethics.
Your dad still loves you.
No.
My dad doesn't love me at all.
[Heng Chang]
Right now, I'm just
a pseudo-rich second-generation who has to work every day
to earn a living, barely making ends meet.
Are you coming tomorrow?
[Heng Chang]
No.
I have a date.
How much is your celery?
Eight cents.
It's expensive.
Look at my celery.
I bought it from the shop on the eastern side of the agricultural trade market.
It's only 65 cents.
It's cheap and has good quality.
So cheap.
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Let me tell you.
In this season,
Chinese yam is the best for the stomach.
Young man,
you look pale.
Is your kidney not good?
You should eat more Chinese yam.
How handsome he is.
Eat more Chinese yam to nourish your stomach.
I bought one kilo
of this celery.
This park
seems quite quiet.
Although this place is a bit remote,
according to my investigation,
this is the place in Hanhai voted by netizens
as the most suitable
for couples' dates.
Don't worry.
They said
this park
is beautiful and has fresh air.
There are also many rare wild animals.
Most importantly,
it's free.
Let's go.
[Looking for traces in White Sand]
The famous attraction that you must visit in this park
is right ahead.
The big, clear, and beautiful Bibo Lake.
Next attraction.
The ancient meteorite.
This is strange.
This is the place on the map.
[Ancient Meteorite]
Chen Miren.
We should have arrived.
[Ancient Meteorite]
Let's go to the next one.
[Wildlife Reserve Area]
The wildlife protection zone is right ahead.
Is this the wildlife protection zone you mentioned?
This...
Yes.
They're wild.
Look.
It's so fierce.
I heard that up ahead, there's a stunning landscape
known as the Crooked Butt Canyon, which rivals the Grand Canyon
in the United States.
Do you want to go?
No need.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
Okay.
I've booked a table.
Next, we'll
have our candlelight dinner.
Hello?
Ms. Li?
Yes.
Is the place I booked
still available?
Candlelight dinner, right?
It's available.
The store at the entrance of the village
doesn't have red candles.
How about white candles?
Sure.
Remember to cook the goose for me.
More salt, more chili.
We have a strong taste.
Okay.
This is the best food in Li Village.
Sister Li's Stewed Goose in an Iron Pot.
Just go out this door, and we'll be there.
Let's go.
Wait.
Okay.
Let's go.
Chen Miren.
Where's the goose stewed in the iron pot?
Who knows that the restaurant suddenly moved?
The spicy hot pot is also good.
It's cheap.
[Spicy hot pot, 5 yuan each]
Why is it so expensive?
If you think it's expensive,
you can eat something else.
I didn't force you to eat.
Boss,
another skew of quail eggs.
Okay.
Thank you.
Five yuan for one skewer.
I'm starving.
Even if it costs 50 yuan, I'll have it.
Boss.
The bus is about to finish its service soon.
Do you know any other bus
to go back to the city?
Why don't we take a taxi?
It's expensive.
The bus is about the same.
It's spacious.
I'll send you there later.
You might catch the last bus.
Okay.
Okay, eat.
Hurry.
[Baiyun Pavilion] [Second Xinhe Village] [North Jiangdongmen Road]
Wait.
Please stop.
Chen Miren.
Zhong Wei, what's wrong?
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫