[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 16]
Lin Miaomiao told Bao Zhendong
"I said what I said out of anger".
"Don't take it seriously".
Bao Zhendong said,
"I know".
Then he turned around and got in the car.
Through the window,
Bao Zhendong looked at Lin Miaomiao
and smiled.
The misunderstanding between them has started to be addressed.
It's time
to start his next plan of pursuing her.
Plan?
What plan?
What?
I can buy you one later.
Huang Xiaoyue,
let me ask you a question.
What question?
Well,
what kind of boys do girls usually like?
It depends.
For example, your mom
and your cousin who is in high school
definitely don't like the same type.
What about the girls in our class,
such as Zhao Gu?
Zhao Gu doesn't like boys.
Zhao Gu only likes studying.
What about...
Luo Si?
A mama's boy.
He has to be someone who can't take care of his own life independently
and is very irresponsible.
What about love experts like Xu Miaomiao?
That's easy to know.
You'll know
after you know what kind of the male lead is in the novels she has read.
[Cao Jia'er]
I had fun today. Good night.
Don't forget our appointment on Friday.
[Cao Jia'er]
Okay.
The male lead's Plan A:
being a romantic and tender boy who is destined to meet his girl accidentally.
[Literature]
Plan B:
being domineering and cool.
Hey.
That ugly girl in red.
What are you looking at?
Throw me the ball.
Listen.
Bao Jiaguo has been really weird recently.
He dresses up like a leading actor in an idol drama every day.
I think
either he has joined a cosplay club
or he has read too many online novels
and wants to be a leading actor.
Really?
Hello?
Well,
he has a new style today.
But I have to say
he looks good in it.
As expected,
being cool and cold is the most classic.
I've ignored her and been indifferent to her.
Next,
I should play cat and mouse.
Look at Bao Jiaguo.
He looks handsome today.
That's not what I meant.
Who does he dress up like?
Professor Do Min Joon.
What happened to Bao Jiaguo?
According to scientific research,
male creatures would dress themselves up
when they want to pursue female creatures
in order to win their hearts.
Why are you looking at me?
[Zhong Wei]
[I want to drink milk tea.]
[I'm not coming today.]
Did you oversleep?
Chen Miren,
I have secret information to report to you.
What information?
Zhong Wei went out last night
and didn't come back.
Huang Xiaoyue, what's that look?
I'm warning you. Don't talk nonsense.
It must be because he had something to do in the company
or he went home.
Didn't you see the message I sent you?
I didn't have time to read it.
I was in a hurry.
I'll buy it for you after class.
Let's go together.
Well,
Huang Xiaoyue said you didn't go back to the dorm last night.
I was too busy last night,
so I didn't come back.
Have you heard
that there was a serious traffic jam at Lanshan Park today?
Lanshan Park?
What is that place?
You don't know?
Couples go there to watch the sunrise or have a date.
And it is said that today
is the best day in a year to watch the sunrise.
[Lanshan Park]
That's why it was crowded there.
Don't these people
go to work or go to school?
Class begins.
We are going to talk about tomorrow's final exam.
It will be the first official exam
since your enrollment.
You must attach great importance to it.
If you fail,
you'll have to retake the course.
Okay, let's begin.
The geometrical significance of derivative
is similar to physics.
It moves from the secant line to the tangent line.
This is the secant line.
The line formed by the two dots on the picture
is the secant line.
The tangent line is...
[Class Summary]
Let's go shopping.
I'm tired.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm not hungry.
You two go.
Let's go.
Bye.
Chen Miren,
I bought canned food for Xiaomeng.
Let's go feed Xiaomeng.
I also bought canned food for Xiaomeng.
Then use the canned food you bought today.
Then put the canned food you bought at my place.
You two are showing your love publicly.
So romantic.
You can do it too.
Let's go.
The bread in the bakery you mentioned last time
is quite delicious.
Do you want to go with me?
I'm sorry.
I'm busy.
Zhong Wei,
do you like Xiaomeng
because it looks like Cloudy?
Xiaomeng is Xiaomeng.
Cloudy is Cloudy.
They're both cute.
Right?
What about me?
If what happened in childhood hadn't happened,
would you be with me?
I'm with you
only because you're Chen Miren.
It has nothing to do with what happened in childhood.
Eat slowly.
Hello?
Why didn't you come to class today?
I'm sick,
so I asked for a leave.
Sounds like you are very sick.
Yes, I've taken a lot of medicine.
I'll visit you. How about that?
No, no.
I'll be fine after I get some sleep.
Okay.
Have a good rest.
Okay, baby.
I'm gonna get some sleep.
That's ridiculous.
What's wrong?
Bao Zhendong, the new male lead,
is the new boyfriend of the heroine.
Originally, he would be by her side
whenever she is in need.
But now,
he told the heroine he was going to the company.
But he went into a strange hotel instead.
The male lead lied to the female lead.
The plot is going to collapse.
Now the key is
who the person in the room is.
I wonder
how A Caged Bird will write the plot.
But according to the plot development,
she is either a spy sent by the stepmother
or the male lead's first lover.
I think if you are together,
no matter what happens,
you shouldn't lie.
What if there's a reason?
Since you chose to lie,
it must be the best solution.
And the truth
is definitely much crueler than this.
I'd like to see
what the truth will be.
Is it so hard to reply to my message?
Unreasonable.
Rest early.
We'll have an exam tomorrow.
Chen Miren,
aren't you going to sleep?
Soon.
Chen Miren,
what's wrong with you?
You should trust Zhong Wei.
Don't be suspicious.
Stop writing.
Time's up.
You don't study hard usually.
Now you are trying your best in the exam.
[Final Exam] [Cao Jia'er]
Cao Jia'er?
Chen Miren,
how could you take the exam in someone else's name?
You fake!
I'm not. I'm not.
It was a dream.
Oh no.
I'm late.
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
[Chen Miren]
Have you forgotten the exam today?
Chen Miren, the exam has started.
Put away your phone.
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
Luo Si. Luo Si.
Give it to me.
Why did you throw it there?
How would I know it would go there?
Xu Miaomiao.
Xu Miaomiao, what are you doing?
I... I...
Sorry, sir.
It's mine.
Come out with me.
Zhong Wei,
what's wrong with you lately?
You're late for the exam.
Sorry, sir.
Go take the exam.
Bao Jiaguo,
you have to retake the course if you cheat in the exam.
Wait in my office.
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
Students in the last row, pass the papers forward.
Sir.
Bao Jiaguo...
Bao Jiaguo cheated in the final exam.
He has been disqualified.
He has to retake the course.
Miaomiao,
I thought Bao Jiaguo is the class monitor,
so that the teacher would spare him.
I'm sorry for getting him implicated this time.
If you want to apologize, apologize to Bao Jiaguo.
I'm going back to the dorm to apologize.
Are you angry?
No.
I don't think so.
You are not even looking at me.
Have you been busy lately?
I won't be busy tomorrow.
What about today?
Today is the last day for me to be busy.
I'll take you home tomorrow.
What have you been busy with?
Things in the store.
I promise
that after today,
I'll always accompany you.
Think about where we will go during the vacation.
But...
I promise.
You promise?
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
It hurts.
I'm leaving.
Go.
I'm really leaving.
Just go.
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
Don't be upset.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
[Advanced Math Final Exam]
[Listen, Love Is Roaring]
[Hanhai University Bulletin Board]
Sir, is there no one inside?
No one is in the office.
Who are you looking for?
Nothing, sir.
[Campus Bulletin Board]
[Next Friday]
[Are you okay?]
Recording a demerit and retaking the course
are both serious.
[Campus Bulletin Board]
[Zhong Wei]
There's a new movie recently:
Listen, Love Is Roaring.
Do you want to watch it together?
Right, he's busy.
Chen Miren.
Aren't you watching a movie?
What movie?
The new movie
called Listen, Love Is Roaring.
I'm not.
I'm right here.
It's strange.
We just watched a movie in the cinema
near the campus.
When we came out,
we saw that Zhong Wei bought two movie tickets
and went inside with a girl.
It was not you?
Maybe you were mistaken.
How is that possible?
Who would mistake Zhong Wei for someone else?
Maybe we were really mistaken.
[Zhongying Taide Cinema]
[Be civilized and polite]
Chen Miren,
what are you thinking?
Trust is the most important thing for couples.
You're here.
Cao Jia'er,
I've fulfilled your three wishes of going to Nanchizi Park,
watching the sunrise, and watching a movie.
What else do you want?
I want to eat the berry cheesecake here.
Okay, I'm going to order it for you.
Okay.
Please come again.
We're offering a discount for couples today.
Miss,
we are offering a discount for couples today.
[Chen Miren]
[Reject] [Answer]
Hello,
Zhong Wei.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Are you Chen Miren?
I'm Cao Jia'er.
Zhong Wei is buying berry cheesecake for me.
If you have something to tell him, I'll tell him when he comes back.
Nothing.
This is our menu. Please take a look.
We're offering a discount for couples today.
Ask your boyfriend to have a taste now.
Boys and girls,
take your loved one here to have a taste.
Thank you.
The spoon.
Cao Jia'er,
when will you go back to America?
Soon.
Why do I feel like
you don't want to see me?
No.
Don't think I don't know this.
You don't want me to visit you in your campus,
so you came to me whenever I called you.
No.
That's not true.
Liar.
Do you have a secret that you don't want me to know
in your campus?
What secret can I have?
Fine.
I'll let it go.
Tell me when you go back to America.
I'll see you off.
Okay.
We just watched a movie in the cinema
near the campus.
We saw that Zhong Wei bought two movie tickets
and went inside with a girl.
Why are you back so late?
There were a lot of work in the company.
Zhong Wei went out last night
and didn't come back.
I was too busy last night,
so I didn't come back.
There was a serious traffic jam at Lanshan Park today.
[Lanshan Park]
Lanshan Park?
What is that place?
Couples go there to watch the sunrise or have a date.
[Lanshan Park]
If what happened in childhood hadn't happened,
would you be with me?
I'm with you
only because you're Chen Miren.
It has nothing to do with what happened in childhood.
8.5 points?
Zhao Gu,
did you oversleep or eat something bad?
Why did you significantly underperform in the exam?
The total points of IELTS are 9 points.
Zhao Gu, you're really amazing.
You passed IELTS so easily.
Where do you plan to go for vacation?
Fang Mao and I plan to go hiking.
Come to London during your summer vacation.
[Dylan]
I will take you to travel to this city.
That would be great.
My store exploring livestreaming show is not over.
I plan to travel around Hanhai
in this vacation
and let more people know Hanhai's food culture.
Chen Miren,
where will you and Zhong Wei go?
I don't know.
Maybe we'll just stay at home.
Zhao Gu, what about you?
I will go to the U.K.
Come in.
[Planning for College Life]
What took you so long?
Girls have a lot of stuff.
You know that.
Wait for me.
Okay.
[Planning for College Life]
Luo Si,
if my boyfriend treated me like that,
I would have broken up with him long ago.
[Planning for College Life]
He's sharp-tongued but soft-hearted.
Since childhood, when I went to school,
he has never let me carry my suitcase.
As long as this tradition exists, our love exists.
Miren,
when will Zhong Wei come to pick you up?
Maybe later.
He said he would send me a message.
Luo Si,
your requirements for love are so simple.
Being simple is the essence of life.
Otherwise, why is your romantic boyfriend
useless now?
We have different understanding of being useful.
Why?
Let me tell you.
Fang Mao
made tofu in the lab today.
Isn't he amazing?
Zhao Gu, wait for me!
[Bao Jiaguo]
[Future Elites of Hanhai Business Administration]
I need someone to help carry the luggage at the Girls' Dormitory.
The class monitor has left long ago.
Xu Miaomiao, how about letting me help you?
Chen Miren, I'm leaving.
Bye.
[Cao Jia'er]
We finally didn't miss each other.
My waiting has paid off.
I haven't been so happy for a long time.
[Zhong Wei]
I'm downstairs.
[Girls' Dormitory]
Let's go. Let me take you home.
I heard that the cape jasmine in Mount Su in the east of the city is blooming.
We can go hiking someday.
And we can go to the Xiaobo River in the west of the city
to watch the sunset together.
Oh right.
Your favorite popular milk tea shop
will soon open a branch
near the campus.
How about going to Nanchizi Park?
Why?
I heard that they are renovating it.
It's not a good place to go.
What about going to Lanshan Park to watch the sunrise?
I heard that the No. 5 observation deck
is the best location to enjoy the scenery.
Or we can go watch a movie.
There is a new movie
called Listen, Love Is Roaring.
I heard it's good.
Well,
let's go to the cinema near the campus.
It has the biggest and most comfortable seats.
And it offers more popcorn.
What do you think?
Chen Miren.
You don't want to go?
Or you don't want to go with me?
You know everything?
Should I keep pretending that I don't know?
Don't misunderstand me.
But it's all settled now.
Have you been with Cao Jia'er all this time?
Yes.
But she's going back to America soon.
I just want...
We should break up.
Chen Miren,
say it again!
Zhong Wei,
now you know
I'm a fake.
I knew you got the wrong person long ago.
I've been lying to you
to be with you.
I don't mind.
I do.
Being with you is too stressful.
I feel like a thief
taking someone else's place
and stealing someone else's love.
But now it's good.
Cao Jia'er is back.
I can give you back to her.
You think I'm something
that you can just give back?
Sorry.
I used wrong words.
Can we break up?
No.
You won't break up with me,
but you went on a date with Cao Jia'er.
Do you want to be a two-timer?
What do you mean?
Am I that kind of person to you?
Aren't you?
If I wanted to be a two-timer,
I wouldn't have waited until now.
Right.
You are popular.
You can have many girlfriends.
I don't deserve you.
Why are you talking about that again?
Can you let me finish?
Why are you so unreasonable now?
Now you know.
It's not too late.
Chen Miren,
I'm gonna ask you one last time.
If you break up with me this time,
I won't wait for you again.
Don't regret it.
I don't.
I don't want you anymore!
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫