[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 15]
You stayed up all night. I brought you breakfast.
Thanks.
Zhong Wei,
you're in a good mood.
A little.
[Call from a Stranger]
[Reject] [Answer]
Hello?
Are you Zhong Wei?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Cao Jia'er.
Cao Jia'er?
Who is Cao Jia'er?
You called me Heroine in childhood.
In Nanchizi Park and the taekowndo gymnasium.
I looked for you in high school.
A student called Chen Miren in your class
said you transferred to another school.
So we didn't see each other.
Later, I found you on Weibo.
But you didn't reply to my messages.
I asked many friends to find you.
Where... Where are you now?
I'm in your campus.
Okay, I'll come to you.
[South Garden Store]
I'm here, Hanhai University.
Are you Cao Jia'er?
There are different phases
for sewage treatment.
Do you understand?
Okay, class is over.
Zhong Wei, look.
I have something to do. I have to go.
Don't you think it's good?
Chen Miren, what are you looking at?
[Zhong Wei]
Xiaomeng has gained weight again.
Zhong Wei.
Why are you back so late?
I...
You must have been busy in the company today.
Um... Yes.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
I knew it.
Go upstairs and eat.
It's still hot.
Chen Miren.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
My girlfriend is so nice.
So is my boyfriend.
Zhong Wei,
do all boys love the new and loathe the old?
Don't you know if I'm nostalgic?
Right.
I have something to do in the company. I have to go.
Go ahead.
I'm okay on my own.
Hold on to it.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
This is for you.
Why are you so nice?
Bye.
No.
All of these are not good.
According to our previous plan,
we need to provide sale volumes for three months.
We need at least 5 categories and 15 units
for updating.
Chao,
you have to hurry up.
Zhong Wei,
you know our actual situation.
Plus you, there are only five of us in our team.
We've been working overtime to finish the drafts.
We submitted so many drafts,
but you only chose three.
If this continues, there is no way we can achieve our goal.
You can't want both quantity and quality.
Providing enough products is the basic requirement.
It's also our responsibility towards the brand
to meet the quality standards.
I don't think there is a problem with that.
Actually, I think the ones you ruled out
are not that bad.
With a little modification, we can make them new...
No.
Every product of OHH must be special
and meet high standards.
Otherwise, what would we have to compete with Yu Dawei?
You are right.
But you should consider
our actual situation.
You should consider
what survival of the fittest means.
Then eliminate me.
I've revised the drafts seven times.
If you don't like my creations,
I can just join another team.
Yi, calm down.
I didn't say anything about eliminating anyone.
Qi Chao.
There is no need to ask a designer
who can't submit satisfying design creations
to stay.
[Heng Chang]
Zhong Wei,
actually, I think the most important thing now
is to increase the speed of product updating.
But quality is also important.
Of course quality is important.
What I mean is
under the current situation
and with limited time,
we should ensure the speed of product updating first.
At the same time, we should recruit people
to improve quality and expand production capacity.
We need to explore
our potential to the greatest extent.
[Heng Chang]
I think there's still a lot of room for us to improve.
We can do it.
Done.
Green Mountain Cafe.
Guo's Pig's Large Intestines.
[Winter Olympics-Themed City Exploration Plan]
Wang's Ginger Duck.
Miaomiao,
you made such a detailed list just for a meal.
Aren't you on a diet?
All you care about is eating.
I plan to make an urban adventure plan
under the theme of Winter Olympics.
Traveling around Hanhai within two months,
promoting city culture through livestreaming,
popular online stores, and lesser-known attractions
are all included in my plan.
Chen Miren,
what are you doing? Sit down.
My design draft
is on the new product list for the third quarter.
Really?
Great.
I'm going to find Zhong Wei
and tell him this good news.
You forget your friend when you have a boyfriend.
Zhong Wei.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Chao kept talking.
It doesn't matter even if I have to wait longer today.
You are so happy.
Is there good news?
Guess.
I guess
someone's design draft has been selected.
How do you know?
At least I'm Mr. Zhong Wei of Heng Chang.
Order whatever you want.
It's the treat of the greatest designer in the future.
I have a gift for you.
The Westward?
I've always wanted this.
It's out of print.
I specially got this for you
from my dad.
If you give it to me, it's mine.
You can't take it back.
Don't worry.
It's all yours.
[Cao Jia'er has sent you a friend request.]
What's wrong?
My phone is dead.
Then I'm gonna take a photo.
I'll send it to you.
Excuse me, is Zhong Wei in this class?
Yes.
You are...
Which is his seat?
He's attending a physical education class.
Why don't you...
Cloudy.
It's her.
Since he's not here,
I'll come another day.
I have plenty of time anyway.
Right.
Please keep this a secret for me.
I want to give him a surprise.
Is she the Heroine Zhong Wei mentioned?
I heard a student will transfer to our class.
I heard about it too.
It seems she is rich and beautiful.
She'll be here in a few days.
She will come here.
Should I confess to Zhong Wei?
Zhong Wei,
someone is looking for you.
Okay.
I'd better tell him.
There will be a basketball game next Saturday.
Zhong Wei, you must come.
Sure, no problem.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
I...
Dad.
Mom.
I want to transfer to another school.
Why do you suddenly want to transfer to another school?
I just do.
[Cao Jia'er]
[I've accepted your friend request. Let's chat now.]
[Today's delicious food]
[Another new member]
[Past, memories that can't be forgotten]
I've been wanting to buy the same dress as your friend's for a long time.
Chen Miren,
ask her to send you the link.
Miaomiao,
I want to ask you something.
If a person
has gained love using the identity of someone else,
and they really like each other,
but many years later,
the true owner of the identity came back,
what should that person do?
Chen Miren,
I didn't expect you to read romance novels too.
Stealing
other people's life
is exactly a plot in romance novels.
Then... how does it end
for the substitute?
Of course it doesn't end well.
No matter how proud and happy she is at the beginning,
as long as the true owner of the identity appears,
she'll become nobody immediately
and become a catalyst for the love between the hero and heroine.
Chen Miren,
if you like this kind of novel,
I'll recommend you more.
The heroine takes revenge on the evil substitute in the latter part.
It feels so good.
That villain
has a miserable ending.
Her family breaks up.
Everyone leaves her.
And she gets sick.
I don't like it.
You don't like it?
I think it's good.
Okay. The third one is
the radical expression and trigonometric substitution
are very obvious substitutions.
So we need a change of variable
to get upper and lower limits.
The fourth one is
functions with upper limits in integration.
The fifth one is
upper limit functions are antiderivatives.
[Cao Jia'er]
The last one is
the reciprocal of upper limit functions.
What are you looking at?
I'm purchasing girls' products.
You want to take a look?
No.
I hope you can review after you go back.
[Cao Jia'er]
If the crystal shoes don't belong to you,
you'll only get hurt if you insist on wearing them.
Have you heard of this story?
I came to look for my crystal shoes.
Okay, class is over.
What...
What do we eat for dinner?
I...
I need to receive training with Miaomiao in the cheerleading team.
Go by yourself.
What are you doing?
Based on my experience,
they must have had a fight.
Is Zhong Wei also a scumbag? Did he cheat on her?
Huang Xiaoyue,
study hard.
Chen Miren.
What's wrong with you today?
You look absent-minded.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Did I ask her where she is going?
Could it be Cao Jia'er?
[Men's room]
Chen Miren,
why did you go into the men's room?
[Men's room]
What's up?
Is this your student ID card?
Yes.
I tried to catch up with you,
but you ran really fast.
Thank you.
[Men's room]
Chen Miren,
it's irresponsible if you just leave like this.
What... What should I be responsible for?
You just saw...
[Men's room]
Don't talk nonsense.
I saw nothing just now.
Fine.
Do you... have a boyfriend?
Of course I do.
My boyfriend is tall and handsome.
And he's cruel.
So stay away from me.
Really?
I don't believe it.
Chen Miren.
Chen Miren,
who was that?
I don't know him.
I just met him.
You haven't eaten, right?
No.
I'm free this afternoon.
Let me accompany you.
No need.
What's wrong?
The coach always scolds me.
I don't want you to see it.
Fine.
Tell me after you finish your training.
I'm leaving.
Chen Miren,
did you borrow money from a loan shark
or are you the one who snuck into the orchard
in the middle of the night to steal the hybrid peach
newly cultivated by Agricultural College
and got publicly criticized yesterday?
Why would I do that?
It's just I'm having
some love issues recently.
No wonder you've been avoiding Zhong Wei lately.
Chen Miren,
you have a boyfriend like Zhong Wei.
Are you still not satisfied?
It's not me.
It's Zhong Wei.
What?
He dares to flirt with another girl behind your back?
Then he should be the one hiding.
Why are you hiding?
It's hard to explain.
In short, there is a small problem
between me and Zhong Wei.
What problem?
Tell me.
Let me analyze it for you.
It's too complicated.
I...
Miaomiao.
Chen Miren.
It turns out Yao Weijing
is the daughter of Fang Mao's mentor.
Fang Mao's mother
thinks she is from a scholar family.
She thinks only a girl from a scholar-gentry family
can match him.
So she wants to be the matchmaker of them.
What did Fang Mao say?
Of course he didn't agree.
But
his mother has a strong desire for control.
He can't persuade her.
So he has decided to play along with Yao Weijing.
You mean
there is nothing between Fang Mao and Yao Weijing?
They are just acting to deceive Fang Mao's mother?
You believe that?
There is no proof. Of course I don't believe that.
But Fang Mao showed me
his chat history with his mother,
some screenshots of them discussing
how to deceive their parents,
and a photo of Yao Weijing and her boyfriend.
I have to say
she has a bad taste
since she likes a man like that
instead of Fang Mao.
Fine.
When it comes to love, only those in love know if it's good.
Do whatever you want as long as you're happy.
[Zhong Wei]
Come downstairs in 5 minutes.
I brought you barbecue.
I have no appetite. Maybe another day.
[Midnight Barbecue]
Has Zhong Wei really been dumped by Chen Miren?
Why?
I heard it's because Zhong Wei is bad at kissing.
This is new.
Chen Miren.
[Midnight Barbecue]
Hey, your skewers.
[Planning for College Life]
How many men and women?
Where is the party?
At what time?
We'll just have dinner
in a restaurant near the campus.
Plus me,
there will be 5 men and 1 woman.
A woman?
My mentor.
Her child is 8 years old.
Fine.
Go.
Don't forget.
When I go out,
I shouldn't talk to any women under 40 years old
or have any eye contact with them.
When I go to a party, I should send you three videos
of at least 10 seconds.
Besides,
I should send my location every 30 minutes.
Have you received the package?
Yes.
Then use it.
Okay, bye.
[This is his girlfriend. You should go away.]
So this is Chen Miren?
It's her boyfriend.
She's Chen Miren.
She's Chen Miren?
Chen Miren, here.
[Shanghai Buns]
Huang Xiaoyue,
have you spread rumors about me again?
Why would I?
I have principles.
I only spread true gossip
in order to find out the truth.
Of course,
it's inevitable
to exaggerate properly.
Don't look at me like that.
It's scary.
Tell me.
Is Zhong Wei bad at kissing?
Zhong Wei is bad at kissing?
Really, Chen Miren?
No.
Huang Xiaoyue,
why did you say that?
Then why have you been avoiding Zhong Wei lately?
So
how is Zhong Wei's kissing skill?
Bao Jiaguo.
Stay away from me.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Which class are you in?
I'm going to criticize you publicly for wasting food.
What's wrong with him?
You're avoiding Zhong Wei because of love.
He's afraid of being slapped.
[Xu Miaomiao, the livestreaming show hasn't started.]
At 8 o'clock tonight,
I'll go explore Green Mountain Bakery.
The theme is nostalgia.
Remember to come and watch.
[Change Your Hairstyle]
[50% off for perming and dyeing]
[Your hairstyle, your call]
[It only costs 20 yuan to wash, cut, and dry the hair.]
[Senior Design Director will design a style for you.]
[The one you love will fall in love with you easily.]
The look today reminds me of puppy love.
Wel-
Thank you.
come.
This strawberry pudding
is pink and sweet.
It tastes like puppy love.
Is he a livestreamer too?
I don't think we invited him, right?
[Xu Miaomiao]
The taste of puppy love
is just like this caramel sea salt cake.
Thick
but nostalgic.
Through the elapse of time,
there will only be pure love and nostalgia left.
A caramel sea salt cake, please.
Okay.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
This strawberry pudding
is pink and sweet.
It tastes like puppy love too.
[Xu Miaomiao]
Nothing
can stop us from being together.
Even death
can't do us apart.
Bravery, immaturity,
and fearless love
are what this lemon cake gives us.
Next, I'm going to introduce
tiramisu.
[Mom]
Bai has left.
[Xu Miaomiao]
Do you know the origin of tiramisu?
Once upon a time, an Italian soldier
was about to go to the battlefield.
But he had nothing to eat at home.
His wife who loved him prepared food for him.
She put all the dim sum and cookies
in a cake.
And this cake is called tiramisu.
It means
"take me with you".
Tiramisu indicates the reluctance to part
and sadness.
[Xu Miaomiao]
We are all on a journey
where we may say goodbye anytime.
You don't know
where he will get off.
But
as long as we've been together
and accompanied each other,
that's enough.
Your experience together
will become a shining memory in your life
in the future.
[Xu Miaomiao]
I want to eat tiramisu.
Miaomiao, don't cry.
That's all for today.
See you next time.
[The livestreaming show is over.]
What's wrong?
Is it because our tiramisu tastes terrible?
Nonsense.
Impossible.
Sorry.
The cake.
Stop crying.
Xu...
Five yuan.
Together.
Xu Miaomiao,
I didn't do it on purpose
last time.
If I had known it, I should have
carried shredded cucumber.
Even stir-fried spicy chicken
would be better than pig's large intestines.
Anyway,
it was all my fault.
I have inescapable responsibility.
How about this?
I'll pay for your shampoo
over the next year.
Two years.
Four years.
If you don't agree,
how about paying for your shampoo
before you become bald?
Bao Jiaguo,
you'd better stop talking.
You're a language genius.
Don't be angry then.
Last time, in the cafe...
I was not following you.
I...
I found the dessert shop
on an app.
So I wanted to try it.
Meeting you was purely a coincidence.
Fine.
I went there because I saw your livestreaming announcement.
But don't worry.
I won't tell anyone
you cried and had snot bubbles.
Bao Jiaguo.
Thank you.
Thank you
for accompanying me when I was crying that day.
And
I said what I said at Shuangling Mountain
out of anger.
Don't...
take it to heart.
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫