[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 19]
Today's game had a huge gap in strength.
In less than a minute,
Bao Jiaguo made a spike
that left the opponents completely helpless.
Chen Miren, you're back.
Let me tell you.
Bao Jiaguo won the table tennis championship today.
What's wrong?
I just ran into Cao Jia'er.
You ran into Cao Jia'er?
And then?
She asked me to return Zhong Wei to her.
She talked like Zhong Wei belonged to her.
Ignore her.
Miaomiao.
Chen Miren and Zhong Wei have broken up.
So what?
They can get back together.
Chen Miren transferred schools once
because of Cao Jia'er.
I think Zhong Wei and Chen Miren
lack trust in each other.
Zhong Wei is afraid that Chen Miren will be troubled
when she sees Cao Jia'er again,
so he wants to handle it himself.
But Chen Miren doesn't believe
that Zhong Wei just wants to resolve the issue.
I think Zhao Gu is right.
But
right now, we can't be sure
if Zhong Wei
wants to resolve things with Cao Jia'er
or just rekindle old feelings with her.
What are you talking about, Luo Si?
What old feelings did they have?
Zhong Wei just wants to make sure
that Chen Miren doesn't feel uncomfortable seeing Cao Jia'er
and he wants to minimize any potential issues.
That's right.
Exactly.
Chen Miren.
Don't overthink it.
You don't have to comfort me.
Zhong Wei and I have already broken up.
You will make up.
I think so too.
Girls.
Chen Miren has been feeling down for several days.
We need to keep her busy.
Yes, especially to make sure she doesn't lose to Cao Jia'er.
Luo Si, do you have any idea?
Not yet.
I can take her to study hard during classes.
Zhao Gu.
Are you trying to rub salt in Chen Miren's wound
about her breakup?
I'll dress Chen Miren up tomorrow.
She can't lose her momentum,
especially in front of her love rival.
♫Summer party, you are my destiny♫
One is called "manager",
and the other is "agent".
♫Sweeter than a strawberry ice cream cone♫
Both of them mean
"broker" in Chinese.
♫Can I move into your heart?♫
But today, we are going to learn the difference between them.
What does "manager" represent?
♫How can I get closer to you?♫
♫Hey girl, please don't cry anymore♫
Usually, it refers to...
♫I want to invite you to dance♫
♫Holding your slender waist♫
♫Don't be afraid, today is Friday♫
♫As the night falls, fireflies dance in the sky♫
♫Let's leave our worries behind and step into the land of romance♫
♫I would like to be with you♫
♫I want to soar with you in the sky♫
♫Explore the mysteries of the paradise planet that no one knows♫
♫All problems are no longer problems♫
♫How to speak words of love gracefully♫
♫Huh?♫
♫Summer party, you are my destiny♫
♫Sweeter than a strawberry ice cream cone♫
♫Can I move into your heart?♫
♫How can I get closer to you?♫
♫When I don't see you for a moment, I feel anxious♫
♫I'm addicted to the fragrance you emit♫
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
♫Hey girl, please don't cry anymore♫
♫I want to invite you to dance♫
♫Holding your slender waist♫
♫Don't be afraid, today is Friday♫
♫As the night falls, fireflies dance in the sky♫
♫Let's leave our worries behind and step into the land of romance♫
♫I would like to be with you♫
♫I want to soar with you in the sky♫
[Chushan Rice Balls]
♫Explore the mysteries of the paradise planet that no one knows♫
♫All problems are no longer problems♫
♫How to speak words of love gracefully♫
♫Huh?♫
♫Please, please be with me♫
♫Just you and me♫
♫I only want to gaze at you all the time♫
♫Expressing the most sincere love♫
♫Summer party, you are my destiny♫
♫Sweeter than a strawberry ice cream cone♫
♫Can I move into your heart?♫
♫How can I get closer to you?♫
♫Summer party, you are my MVP♫
[Wednesday Membership Day]
♫When I don't see you for a moment, I feel anxious♫
♫I'm addicted to the fragrance you emit♫
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
Thank you.
If you want to thank me,
buy me dinner.
Maybe
I'll just do it myself.
Just kidding.
Milk tea is fine too.
What?
You don't even want to buy me milk tea?
Okay.
Have you noticed
that Chen Miren has become prettier lately?
Most people become more attractive due to the power of love,
but Chen Miren has become prettier due to the power of heartbreak.
We're just having a cold war.
We haven't broken up.
Is that so?
Less ice, full sugar, with coconut milk, right?
I want milk tea too.
Me too.
You all have one.
I'm leaving.
As expected,
the way to get over a breakup
is to start a new relationship.
See you on the basketball court.
It's time to start our plan.
What plan?
The plan of destroying Qin.
I bought them for you.
Again?
This milk tea shop
has been exposed for failing food safety standards.
How dare you still drink their milk tea?
Here, drink mine.
Huang Xiaoyue.
Are you that kind?
I...
I just want to thank you
for cheering for me in the basketball game last time.
Who cheered for him?
You did?
Chen Miren.
This is for you.
This is my favorite.
Chen Miren.
Let's exchange.
Here, have some vitamin C after the meal.
It helps with skin whitening.
Give it a try.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay for it.
Huang Xiaoyue.
Tell me the truth.
Are you Cao Jia'er's spy?
She's fat, so she doesn't want me to be thin, right?
Of course not.
Then why have you been making excuses
to bring us food?
Tell us.
What are you up to?
Well...
I'll tell you.
The mastermind is Zhong Wei.
Did you just expose me like that?
But I've explained
that you did this
to be good to Chen Miren.
But Xu Miaomiao said
that you hated Chen Miren so much
that you wanted her to get destructively fat,
and end up lonely.
You can't blame me.
I told you
that your trick was so lame
that you would get exposed sooner or later.
What did Chen Miren say?
Chen Miren...
I don't want to
argue with him on such boring tricks.
Zhong Wei.
I finally found that
your enemy is not only Qin Mengxuan.
Who else?
Xu Miaomiao, Luo Si and Zhao Gu.
Then what should I do?
Turn enemies into friends
and clear the obstacles.
So you mean
there's nothing between you and Cao Jia'er,
and it's just a misunderstanding?
You went on a movie date with Cao Jia'er
because you were afraid that after she showed up,
Chen Miren would break up with you again.
So you wanted to meet her requirements
and send her back to America?
But unexpectedly,
Cao Jia'er transferred here.
Yes.
So do you believe in
what Zhong Wei said?
I believe Zhong Wei.
After all,
the more handsome a man is, the more devoted he is.
My Fang Mao is just an example.
I just simply think
that from the perspective of input and output ratio,
the only possibility for Zhong Wei
to win back Chen Miren
is true love.
Let's vote.
Raise your hand if you believe Zhong Wei.
We decided
to believe you.
We'll explain this to Chen Miren for you.
I've explained everything.
It's useless.
I originally thought
that over time,
Chen Miren would realize
that there's nothing between me and Cao Jia'er.
But I didn't expect
Qin Mengxuan to come out halfway.
What if before Chen Miren finds out about the truth,
she and Qin Mengxuan were together?
How could it be?
Why would she choose Qin Mengxuan instead of you?
Why not?
Now there's a Cao Jia'er standing between you.
Chen Miren has already misunderstood Zhong Wei.
At this moment, Qin Mengxuan
launched a fierce pursuit,
who can withstand it?
Let me be frank.
Qin Mengxuan's pursuit
is indeed hard to refuse.
Right?
You think so too, right?
Don't worry.
You have us.
Yes.
We'll help you.
Thank you.
Let's watch a movie tomorrow.
The movies that are in cinema recently are so lame.
Whoever watches them will regret it.
I heard that
Qin Mengxuan
is dating Guo Haomei
from the broadcasting class.
Recently,
Huang Xiaoyue saw them
going to the woods together.
Chen Miren.
The exam is coming.
Are you prepared for it?
Look! Look!
He's so handsome!
[Literature]
[Warm hint]
What're you doing?
Reading.
There are so many empty seats.
Why do you have to sit here?
The library is a public place.
I can sit wherever I want.
Excuse me.
This seat is taken.
Please leave.
But...
I came here first. Didn't I?
Are you done?
As long as you two shut up,
I'll be done.
Zhong Wei.
Chen Miren has broken up with you.
Please keep your distance.
Don't make trouble.
Who is he?
We didn't break up.
We're just having a cold war, right?
Come with me.
Where are we going?
Go away.
Aren't you childish?
I'm not as childish as you.
You asked someone to act with you
to persuade me to quit.
You should at least rehearse.
He's so bad at acting.
How can I get into the role?
Can't you be reasonable?
Be reasonable?
When two people in a relationship are arguing,
how can they can be reasonable?
We didn't just fight. We broke up.
Zhong Wei.
I'll tell you again.
We've broken up.
You announced it unilaterally.
Did I admit it?
I don't want to talk to you.
It's fine.
Let me talk to you.
You didn't study hard in class.
You read for leisure during class.
You looked up four times in ten minutes
and played with your phone eight times.
You even spent three minutes drawing on the textbook.
Don't think that just because the teacher praised you,
you can become careless and proud.
Listen.
Without me by your side,
and tutoring you,
and you fail,
you'll regret it too late.
It's none of your business.
Of course, it is.
Think about it.
If you fail the exam and get retained,
I don't want to date a junior.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
There's a limit to revenge.
You want me to gain weight, and I've endured it.
Don't disturb my studies.
Well.
I disturb your studies?
How dare you say that as a poor student?
Well,
I was afraid you might lose something,
so I stayed to watch them for you.
Thank you.
You two
are still together?
[Hanhae University Open Day]
The scenery is nice there.
Let's go over there.
The school is so beautiful.
She loves taking photos.
Tell me, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Don't forget.
When you were in high school,
your mother didn't allow you to buy action figures.
I
secretly sponsored you with a lot of private money.
What?
You have made changes on your path to pursue your dream.
Even your dad doesn't have the right to know?
I've entered Heng Chang.
Really?
That's too...
I was fired in less than two months.
Too pitiful.
Dad,
I don't want to be a designer anymore.
Do you remember
when you were in kindergarten,
you fought for watermelon
at the sports day?
You fell
and got mad for several days.
We advised you that participation is what matters most,
but it didn't work.
Suddenly, one day,
you came home happily
and told me,
"Dad,
this afternoon,
I had a big watermelon in kindergarten."
Actually,
you didn't care about the result
of the game.
You only wanted to eat that big watermelon.
Chen Miren.
Come and take a photo of me.
Mom.
That's the lawn. Don't step on it.
Come out!
Can't I step on it?
No.
I told you
that a key university
is different.
Look.
This campus is like a 5A-class spot.
It's beautiful.
Our daughter
entered the Department of Business Administration at Hanhai University.
What an excellent girl!
Come on, take a photo of us.
But I still want to eat the watermelon.
My daughter wants to eat the watermelon.
Mom, I'm taking the photoes.
One, two, three, make a heart.
Come on.
Look at this. It's so beautiful.
So beautiful.
Chen Miren.
Your school is so nice.
There are fruits to eat.
These are models made by the Sculpture major students.
Put it down.
It looks real.
I really like that painting.
Take a photo of me.
Dad, Mom.
Don't run around.
Otherwise, I won't be able to find you later.
Distinguished leaders, teachers,
parents,
and fellow students,
[School Open Day]
hello, everyone.
I'm Zhong Wei from Class 22
of the Department of Business Administration.
I'm honored to speak here
[School Open Day]
on behalf of the students.
I sincerely thank the parents
for coming here.
Our parents are our mentors
and also friends who will accompany us in our whole lives.
Hanhai University is a key university in China.
It has a strong faculty...
Mr. Zhong.
Zhong Wei is really
excellent.
Yes.
Most importantly,
he's handsome.
They are the main force
in cultivating outstanding talents.
They're also...
Isn't he handsome?
Social service
and culture heritage...
Just so-so.
Backbone force...
Wu Dabo from the Department of Foreign Trade
is more handsome and has a better figure.
His arms are thicker than Zhong Wei's thighs.
He can do 80 push-ups in one go.
Have become the best in all walks of life...
You like Zhong Wei?
Used to be my dream...
How is that possible?
I like that type of boy Wu Dabo is.
Again, I warmly welcome
and sincerely thank
all the parents for coming.
We will study hard and be positive
and give you a satisfactory answer.
[School Open Day]
I believe that
we will have a bright future.
He's really amazing.
The top student
on the Glory List
is him, right?
He's someone else's kid. It's none of your concern.
Can't you learn from him?
Chen Miren.
What a coincidence.
You know each other?
Yes, we are classmates.
Uncle and Auntie. Nice to meet you.
I'm Zhong Wei.
Hello.
I'm not familiar with him.
Zhong Wei, right?
Miren
always talks about you.
She told us that you always care about your hair
and you're a livestreamer, right?
That shouldn't be me.
Whether it's you or not,
you are classmates.
That's Xu Miaomiao.
Uncle, Auntie.
Are you here
solely to attend the open day?
I saw you three
harmoniously together.
You're so happy.
Unlike me.
I haven't seen my dad for a long time.
I haven't had dinner with him for a long time.
Your parents aren't here?
No.
We're going to eat.
Let's go together.
He's busy.
I'm free.
I just don't want to trouble you.
Not at all.
Why do all excellent kids
belong to others?
Kid, why are you
walking away so quickly?
Zhong Wei.
Listen.
She's good.
But we spoiled her.
Please don't mind.
[Longan Osmanthus Soufflé]
Today, after Zhuo Wei finished his speech,
I saw him talking to Chen Miren in the audience.
[Fresh Tea Meets Sweet Longan]
Are they still connected?
They are classmates.
It's normal for them to talk to each other.
But you have to be careful,
especially about Chen Miren
who is like a clingy plaster.
Yes.
Jia'er, hurry up
and establish a relationship with Zhong Wei.
Don't let others have the opportunity to interfere.
The ambiguous phase is the sweetest.
No hurry.
[Osmanthus oolong]
Chen Miren.
I was eating with my parents.
You called me here
just to feel this tense atmosphere?
Auntie. Thank you.
Let him help himself.
Why are you helping him with the food?
I should have
gone to the basement mall to buy long johns.
No.
If you leave,
this meal will be strange.
Why aren't you eating?
Eat more.
You are in the same dorm.
Thank you
for taking care of Miren.
That's right.
We didn't take care of her the most.
Zhao Gu.
Eat more.
Here, you too.
Thank you. Auntie.
Zhong Wei.
I heard that you are the top student in the grade.
In the future,
please help Miren more
and help her with her studies.
Auntie, don't worry.
In the future,
I'll sit next to Chen Miren.
If she has any questions,
she can ask me anytime.
That'll be great.
Thank you.
Great.
No need.
I have Zhao Gu to help me.
I like sitting alone in class.
Chen Miren.
He was kind enough to help you with your studies.
Don't be so picky. You don't know what's good for you.
Hurry up.
Thank him.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's what I should do.
Miaomiao.
Can you tell us
if Miren
has a boyfriend?
Do you?
No.
Uncle, Auntie.
Do you
support her to date someone?
We do.
Of course, we do.
Speaking of which,
it's a sad thing.
Well.
Miren is
lively, cute,
gentle, and kind.
But since young,
she has never received a love letter.
Zhong Wei.
You are a boy.
You have a wide circle of friends, don't you?
What about
introducing a healthy boy
to Miren
so that she can go on dates
and go out for a walk
so that she won't sleep in all day?
Her limbs are about to regress.
She can't be able to go on dates after that.
Uncle, Auntie,
don't worry.
In terms of finding Chen Miren
a healthy boyfriend,
you can count on me.
Great. Thank you.
Uncle, Auntie.
Eat more.
Of course.
Your auntie likes taking photos.
What's going on?
Are they Zhong Wei's parents
or Chen Miren's parents?
Are they meeting each other's parents?
Zhong Wei.
Cao Jia'er?
Why are you everywhere?
I'm also surprised to see you here.
Hello, Uncle and Auntie.
Hello.
You know each other?
Hello, Auntie.
I'm Zhong Wei's classmate.
No.
Uncle, Auntie.
Excuse me.
I'll go out for a while.
Enjoy your meal.
What's wrong?
I'm so angry.
[Watch the steps]
Cao Jia'er.
Didn't I tell you
Chen Miren is my girlfriend?
But I heard you broke up.
We didn't break up.
Besides,
Chen Miren is very narrow-minded
and she tends to be jealous.
I hope you can
keep an appropriate distance from me as a friend.
What is the appropriate distance?
A distance that doesn't make Chen Miren jealous.
Is that so?
[Watch the steps]
Let me send you back.
Let's go.
[Watch the steps]
He is excellent,
but he has a girlfriend.
Chen Miren.
He has a girlfriend.
No matter how excellent he is,
you can't steal him.
What are you talking about?
The car is here. Get in.
Okay, we're leaving.
Let's go.
If you meet someone suitable,
you should date.
Okay, okay.
We're leaving.
Bye.
Don't forget to eat watermelon.
I didn't expect Zhong Wei to be such a person.
We've actually been helping him all along.
Seeing may not be true.
I don't think we should get involved.
They should solve it themselves.
Miren, you're back.
Yes.
Chen Miren.
You've occupied Zhong Wei for so long.
You should give him back to me.
What?
You have made changes on your path to pursue your dream.
Even your dad doesn't have the right to know?
My life goal
is to become the chief action figure designer.
I passed the interview at Heng Chang.
Really?
Congratulations, future designer.
[Clearance Sale for Action Figures, Don't Miss It]
[Posted]
I don't believe
that no one would like my action figures.
Hello.
I'm an action figure designer.
I want to design an action figure about animals.
Can I observe
their movements here?
[Remote experts support]
Yes, follow me.
[Cao Jia'er]
[Decline] [Answer]
Hello?
Zhong Wei.
I found an injured cat.
It was badly injured.
I need to send it to the hospital.
Come and help.
I'm on the Yilin Avenue.
You'll see me if you come over.
I'll wait for you.
[Girls' Dormitory]
Xiaomeng.
Are you an action figure designer?
Amazing.
Can you give me a set
after you finish your design?
Of course.
This is Pudding.
Pudding likes being petted on the head the most.
So cute!
This is Bobby.
It's very prone to jealousy.
If you pet Pudding's head,
remember to pet its head too.
Otherwise, when you leave,
it will fight with Pudding.
Suit yourself.
I'll get back to work.
Bobby.
Don't worry.
I just checked.
Well,
it's just a scratch.
The bones are fine.
If there's nothing else,
you can go back.
It can't get wet.
Thank you, doctor.
I'm here to treat Xiaomeng.
What happened to Xiaomeng?
Nothing big deal.
Zhong Wei and I have taken it to the doctor.
Chen Miren.
Cao Jia'er called me
when she saw the kitten was injured.
Xiaomeng.
Xiaomeng is fine now.
It's just a scratch.
The doctor just took care of it.
I have to go.
I won't disturb you.
Chen Miren.
I want to take a walk alone.
Don't follow me.
Chen Miren.
Cao Jia'er.
You were indeed
a ray of hope in my grey childhood.
That's why I tolerated you.
But I was only grateful to you.
Even if I met you
in high school,
I wouldn't be with you.
What do you mean?
I like Chen Miren
just the way she is.
That's enough.
Zhong Wei.
Let me ask you one last question.
Is it that no matter what I do now,
you won't like me?
Yes. I won't.
Chen Miren.
I have something for you.
I saw you liked the action figure on Weibo last time.
I thought you would like it.
This is for you.
Thank you.
But this can only be given to the one you love.
I can't take it.
You are the one I love.
Qin Mengxuan.
I'm sorry.
I did it on purpose
to provoke Zhong Wei before,
so...
I know.
I don't mind.
So,
you still can't forget Zhong Wei.
I don't want to date now.
I just want to focus on my career.
Shouldn't you be
comforting me in times like this?
Qin Mengxuan,
you are a good person.
You're excellent, considerate,
sunny and handsome.
You'll find a better one.
I think so too.
Chen Miren.
Chen Miren!
You scared her away.
Qin Mengxuan,
can you stop hitting on her?
Okay.
Okay?
Anyway,
I'll find a better one.
Did she reject you?
You two are so boring.
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫