[English subtitles are available]
♫I'm fascinated by your every move♫
[Miss Lucky Go!]
[Episode 5]
You're back.
How did it go?
Not at first.
But then I met Zhong Wei.
He solved it for me.
Zhong Wei? Why did he go to Linzhou?
He went to shoot a promotional video.
Miaomiao, you know what?
Zhong Wei is really good at negotiating.
How could he be so good?
He's good at communicating as well as studying.
Chen Miren.
You look
like Zhong Wei's fan.
Do I?
Look in the mirror.
Zhong Wei, where have you been these days?
I've had three meals of stewed goose by myself.
I had something to do.
What did you do in Linzhou?
It was a private matter.
Well, let's dine together today.
[Safety Production Rules]
Come in.
Mr. Ye.
Okay, go ahead.
Mr. Zhong Wei.
The sample is ready. Take a look.
This is the special price we agreed on.
I've also applied it for you.
[Quotation of Linzhou Huateng Toy Factory Co., Ltd.]
Thank you, Mr. Ye.
Don't mention it.
It's you who is excellent
and didn't disappoint Mr. Zhong.
My dad?
Yes.
When I called Mr. Zhang,
he was talking business with Mr. Zhong.
Mr. Zhong said
you deserve
the first place.
Why don't you take a look first?
In my opinion,
it has to be Mr. Zhong at the crucial moment.
You didn't say that before.
Without you, how is there Mr. Zhong?
I mean,
without you,
Mr. Zhong wouldn't have helped us like this.
This is not my business.
It's the company's business.
Also,
my dad just did me a favor.
Killing two birds with one stone.
A son knows his father the most.
Wait for me.
Chen Miren, hurry up. It's time for the roll call.
Why didn't you call me?
Didn't you ask us to leave without you?
Have you forgotten?
I made a mistake.
Chen Miren, listen.
Hurry up.
The class is about to start.
Run! Run!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
I can't run anymore.
Since I was young, I've always been
in the audience at school sports meetings.
Morning.
When did you come back?
This morning.
We're going to be late.
I'll give you a ride.
Okay.
Zhong Wei, Chen Miren.
Cao has always prohibited lateness and absence.
Don't you know?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Hurry up.
Okay.
You go first.
I'll ask Xu Miaomiao to cover for me.
I'm leaving.
Chen Miren, why haven't you arrived yet?
Cao prohibits absence.
I heard that if one gets caught this time,
his average score will be zero.
Please buy me some time.
I'm on my way.
Chen Miren, Cao is out.
We can only mourn for you.
[There's love in the world. Please help the poor.]
The three of you...
I'm here.
Are always late, right?
We'll be roommates in the next life.
You even sleep in class.
Did you do well?
How many marks did you get?
Sir, I have a question for you.
Set the origin X0 and Y0,
then the tangent equation passing through the origin is...
Y equals two times the square root of X0 minus one-half.
Then, I concluded that X0 equals 4Y0,
which equals the square root of 2.
I see.
The answer is three halves times the square root of two.
Thank you. Sir.
Okay, that's good.
The three of you, go stand behind.
Okay, let's start the class.
Open your textbook.
Let's learn the parameter equation today.
What is a parameter equation?
Chen Miren, what about the new shade I bought?
Isn't it attractive?
Look at these symbols.
I recognize them by looking at them separately.
Why do they look like the Book of Heaven when put together?
You mean her, right?
How could she...
Can't you talk openly?
We didn't talk about you.
Right.
But you kept pointing and whispering.
I'm sure you didn't say anything good.
Don't you know?
There's a thief in your dorm.
Are you talking about me?
I didn't say that.
You said it yourself.
What did I steal?
As to what you stole,
you know better than we do.
Do you have any proof that she's a thief?
I didn’t say that.
Shi Hou from Grade 3 said it.
Who is he?
This is about our dormitory, and I don't know anything.
How could he know?
Shi Hou is Zhao Gu's boyfriend.
Zhao Gu has a boyfriend?
You don't even know that as her roommate.
It seems that
you really don't know
what happened in your dorm.
Zhao Gu.
You told others
that Chen Miren is a thief?
I said it.
What evidence do you have?
Luo Si lost something too.
Those are worthless, Zhao Gu.
This must be a misunderstanding.
Let's go back and talk.
Luo Si.
Let's make it clear.
Zhao Gu.
Chen Miren just
unwrapped your package by mistake.
Do you have to be so petty?
This has nothing to do with the package.
Chen Miren.
Don't regret if I tell them.
Tell us now. We're not afraid.
She's not that kind of person.
Chen Miren.
Do you dare to swear that you never took my stuff?
Zhao Gu, you've gone too far.
Just get to the point.
How can you make her swear?
And about what happened between you and Shi Hou,
if it wasn't Chen Miren who didn't let me say it,
the whole school would have known it.
Chen Miren, tell her
you never took her stuff, right?
I believe in Chen Miren.
She won't steal other people's things.
I'll borrow it.
Zhao Gu, can we go back first?
Okay.
Why can't you talk here?
Why do you have to go back first?
Feeling guilty?
Looks like it's true.
Chen Miren, don't go.
Tell them.
Chen Miren.
Stop asking.
What's going on?
Zhong Wei, how come you spoke for Chen Miren?
Chen Miren even yelled at Zhong Wei.
She must be desperate.
He treats her so well.
But she is not grateful.
Indeed.
[Girls' Dormitory]
Did you tell other people
that Chen Miren took my stuff?
Yes. Didn't you tell me that?
That's our dorm business.
It's none of your business.
[Girls' Dormitory]
Zhao Gu.
[University Life Plan]
Zhao Gu, I'm sorry.
I did borrow your sanitary pads.
I bought new ones to return to you.
But I lost it.
Then I forgot.
It's just a pack of sanitary pads.
You're overreacting.
That's a terrible excuse.
I really didn't lie to you.
Do you have evidence?
No.
Any receipt?
I lost it.
I only believe in evidence.
Zhao Gu, forget it.
It's just a pack of sanitary pads.
It's normal if she forgets it.
I really bought it.
Chen Miran said she bought it, she's bought it;
If she loses it, it's lost.
It's just a pack of sanitary pads.
Do you want the person who picked up the pack of sanitary
to return it to you?
Help me give it to Chen Miren.
Bao Jiaguo.
I didn't expect you to be so perverted.
I know where the pack of sanitary pads is.
[Boys' Dormitory]
What can I do for you?
Give it to me.
What?
Sanitary pads.
You, you... Are you having your period?
I don't have it.
You shouldn't have asked me for it.
You rascal.
What are you thinking?
Let me ask you.
Did you take Chen Miren's sanitary pads?
Don't slander me.
I just picked it up.
The same thing.
Do you know
that pack of sanitary pads
was bought by Chen Miren to return to Zhao Gu?
Now Chen Miren is framed as a thief.
You have to return it to her to prove her innocence.
I threw it away long ago.
Go buy another pack.
How much is it? I'll pay you.
You need to buy it yourself.
Me?
I'm not going.
You girls should sort things out
among yourselves.
Hey, Bao Jiaguo.
You can't leave if you don't go today.
I...
I'll go with you.
Let go of me.
[Boys’ Dormitory]
Bao Jiaguo, you dare not admit your mistake.
What kind of man are you?
Xu Miaomiao is really...
Was she kidding me?
I'm a man.
How can she ask me to buy that thing?
About Chen Miren and Zhao Gu?
Exactly.
A few days ago, I met Chen Miren at the supermarket.
She left a pack of that thing.
I wanted to return it to her out of kindness.
But Xu Miaomiao thought I was a pervert.
Now she asked me to buy it.
She said I have to buy it and return it
to clear Chen Miren's name.
Tell me, what is this?
I'm speechless.
The one who started it should be the one who ends it.
Don’t make a big misunderstanding
and affect our class's unity.
Besides,
the result of the excellent class evaluation
is coming out at the end of this month.
Our class is the only one selected in our department.
Besides, you are targeted by Xu Miaomiao.
She won't let you go.
Bao Jiaguo, you dare not admit your mistake.
What kind of man are you?
If it weren't for the honor of our class...
It's okay.
There are surveillance cameras in the supermarket.
Send the video to Xu Miaomiao.
What else can she say?
Bao Jiaguo.
Don't tell them it was me who said it.
What a coincidence.
What are you buying?
Nothing. Just some nonsense.
Remember to attend the monitors' meeting of the department
tomorrow afternoon.
No problem.
Have some water.
It's 68 yuan in total.
I'll hold it for you.
Let's go.
How much is it?
You bought it?
You can check it later.
Now you want dignity?
If you hadn't taken Chen Miren's sanitary pads,
she wouldn't have been accused of a thief.
I'll emphasize it again that I just picked it up.
Also,
I sent you the surveillance video of the supermarket on WeChat.
You'll know after you see it.
Whatever you say.
Anyway, you should make up for your mistake.
If you hadn't misunderstood me for being a rascal,
I would have returned it to her.
It's not a misunderstanding. It's the truth.
Rascal.
Bao Jiaguo!
What?
I was right.
You are a rascal.
I... I...
I don't know where it came from.
You saw the supermarket surveillance footage.
Now the truth is out.
You wronged a good person.
What else?
What're you talking about?
Where is my watch?
What watch?
This is an accident.
What about the watch?
I didn't take your watch.
Where is my watch?
How would I know?
You...
Come in.
Zhao Gu.
Is Zhao Gu in this dorm?
Yes.
Zhao Gu.
We caught the thief who broke into the girls' dormitory.
The security office wants you to claim your watch.
Zhao Gu, you accused Chen Miren without evidence.
Zhao Gu, you went too far this time.
Zhao Gu.
Don't call her.
She was so fierce just now.
Why is she humble now?
I believe in Chen Miren.
She won't steal others' things.
Chen Miren.
Stop asking.
Did I go too far to Zhong Wei just now?
I don't know what Zhong Wei thinks.
But if someone yells at me in public,
I will never talk to him.
So serious?
What do you think?
I think
Zhong Wei treats Chen Miren differently.
What's the difference?
I think Zhong Wei just
wanted to say something for Chen Miren
because she helped him draw the poster.
Zhong Wei doesn't seem to be a nosy person.
But why did he
stand up for Chen Miren?
If you hadn't yelled at him just now,
maybe the next second
Zhong Wei would hold Chen Miren's hand
and walk out of the classroom in public.
Dream on!
Luo Si, wake up.
Chen Miren.
I'm sorry for wrongly accusing you.
I apologize.
I noticed you often bought this.
Zhao Gu.
I like the spicy flavor.
All right.
We are roommates.
We are family. What grudge do we have?
Things are cleared up.
The truth is revealed. So isn't everything fine now?
Wait.
What do you mean?
Zhao Gu, you should make it clear in the class group chat
that the thief has been caught
and you misunderstood Chen Miren.
As for her borrowing your sanitary pads,
it's up to you.
Tell everyone if you don't feel embarrassed.
I'll make it clear.
I'm glad you know.
It's okay.
[Future Elites of Hanhai Business Administration]
All right, the thief is caught.
Chen Miren is innocent.
I misunderstood her.
I'm here to apologize to her.
Look at the group chat.
I told you
Chen Miren is not that kind of person.
Everyone is happy.
Go to sleep.
No, I can't forgive her.
Unless she apologizes.
[Zhong Wei]
Zhong Wei, don't be angry.
As long as you're not angry,
I can do anything.
[Zhong Wei]
Alright, don't be angry.
I've deleted the boy who liked
my posts on Moments.
[Zhong Wei]
Alright, don't be angry.
It's so cheesy.
Chen Miren.
Get me a coupon.
It would be fine if she could coax me.
[Chen Miren]
Although it's a little perfunctory,
for the sake of your sincerity...
[Chen Miren]
[Chen Miren withdrew a message]
This is good.
Even my mom bought it,
it will work on Zhong Wei.
[Don't be angry]
At the critical moment,
family group chat is quite useful.
Take a look.
Come here.
[Welcome to the Cartoon Club]
Have a look at the baking club.
[Baking Club]
You've been eating for ten minutes.
Are you joining our club or not?
I'll think about it.
Have a look at the baking club.
A unique platform
leads to a unique brilliance.
Have a look at the baking club.
[Recruitment of Music Club]
Take a look.
Welcome to the travel club.
[Recruitment of Basketball Club]
Welcome.
Fill it out.
[Recruitment of Basketball Club]
Zhong Wei.
[Zhong Wei]
Are you joining the basketball club?
[Recruitment of Street Dance Club]
Get me a form.
Okay.
[Recruitment of Street Dance Club]
Okay, thank you.
Senior, please give me a form.
Sorry, Junior.
We don't accept girls.
I'll apply for my friend.
Okay. Here.
[Recruitment of Street Dance Club]
Zhong Wei, you're perfect for the basketball team.
Have you eaten?
How about I treat you to dinner?
What do you want to eat?
Grilled fish in the canteen or spicy hot pot?
How about this? I'll treat you to a nice meal.
Let's eat out.
Pick whatever you want.
[Recruitment of Street Dance Club]
Done.
Okay.
[Welcome to the Needling Club]
Has he listened to the "Don't be Angry" song?
Why is he still angry?
[Recruitment of Basketball Club]
[Cheerleading Club]
Chen Miren, you're finally here.
I signed up for Huang Xiaoyue.
Can't Huang Xiaoyue walk?
Why did he ask you to sign up for him?
What happened?
Zhao Gu isn't here.
I have a feeling that a war will be triggered soon.
We agreed to come together.
Where did Zhao Gu go?
I just sent her a message in the group chat.
She should be here soon.
Don't wait for her.
Let's go...
Isn't that Zhao Gu?
Congratulations
[Welcome to the English club]
on becoming a member of our English club.
I hope we can have fun together.
Thank you.
But I'm not interested in making friends.
Zhao Gu, didn't we agree to come together?
Why are you here alone?
The English club has limited vacancies.
If I wait for you,
I'm afraid I have to join the Thai club.
You should have told us.
Are you afraid we'll compete with you?
You don't have such high aspirations.
I have nothing to be afraid of.
You...
Let's check out other clubs.
Needling Club?
[Recruitment of Street Dance Club]
Fang Mao happened to be in need of a scarf.
[Needling Club looking forward to your participation]
Zhao Gu is right.
She really has no aspiration.
Chen Miren, which club do you want to join?
I want to join the cheerleading club.
Chen Miren.
You're the only one
[Recruitment of Literature Club]
who shares the same interest with me in our dorm.
You want to join the cheerleading club too?
It's not that I want to join the cheerleading team,
but the cheerleading team needs me.
[Recruitment of Literature Club]
[A different charm of cheerleading club]
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
Thank you for your support for the cheerleading club.
Since there are too many applicants,
our registration has ended.
Come next year.
Has it ended?
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
Take it.
Don't you want to join the cheerleading club too?
I can't take it.
Watch me.
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
There's no place left. Come next year.
Hello, Senior, I'm Xu Miaomiao.
So?
Am I not worthy of an extra spot?
You want me to make an exception for you?
No. If I make an exception for you, what about others?
If you want to join the cheerleading team, you can either wait until next year
or take the place
of someone who will quit.
Why are you so stubborn?
How could you say that?
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
I...
Miaomiao, forget it.
You have the application form.
I don't really want to be a cheerleader.
I have poor coordination in my body.
I always turn in the same direction when I walk.
No.
What's wrong?
[Recruiting]
Nothing.
You want to join the cheerleading team, right?
[Recruiting]
Not really.
Wait for me.
[Recruiting]
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
Who is he?
Zheng Ze.
He's so enthusiastic.
Is he one of your pursuers?
No.
My senior in high school.
Looks like it.
[Dance Youth Enthusiasm]
I talked to your seniors in the cheerleading club.
[Recruiting]
They said they could only give one more place.
One is perfect.
We already have one.
Okay, take the second exam at the gym at 2:30 p.m.
Don't be late.
Thank you.
Come on.
[Recruiting]
Not bad.
You don't want to join the cheerleading team
just because of him, do you?
What about you?
I...
You did it for Huang Xiaoyue, right?
I'm not doing it for him.
Who is it then?
The ones who play basketball in our class
are only Zhong Wei and Huang Xiaoyue.
Is it Zhong Wei?
Let's go.
[Cheerleading Club]
Zhong Wei or Huang Xiaoyue?
[Baking Club]
She danced so well.
She's really amazing.
She's amazing.
I'm nervous.
What if I can't dance well?
Next, Chen Miren.
You can do it.
Go.
Her dance is weird,
but it's so appealing.
Okay.
Next, Xu Miaomiao.
Here.
Come on.
It's so funny.
[Club Recruitment Registration Form]
Dong Lili.
Here.
Why can't I do a vertical split?
What do you think of Fu Tiantian?
Just so-so.
Do you think you can pass?
I didn't do well today.
It's okay.
We still have a chance next time.
But it's enough to be a cheerleader.
If...
I mean if.
If you fail...
That's impossible.
Chen Miren.
If we don't succeed, we'll become martyrs.
Now I'll announce the final result.
Wei Ruxuan is out.
Guo Yini passed.
Xu Miaomiao...
Wait.
What are you doing?
Your performance just now was too normal.
It can't show your skills.
Let's show the coach our real strength.
If you do well,
you'll be the center.
That makes sense.
So funny.
Coach, you don't have to be so picky.
That girl is amazing.
Great!
I announce that you're accepted.
Thank you, Coach.
Coach, what’s going on?
It was a group performance.
Besides, even if only one of us will be accepted,
it should be Xu Miaomiao.
To be honest,
with her level,
if I accept her,
I'll lose my job.
You're different.
You are the base position talent we need the most
right now.
Well, I...
If Xu Miaomiao joins the cheerleading team, I'm in.
Or I'll quit.
You mean
buy one and get one free?
You're making things difficult for me.
I can only lift her.
Well...
Also, congratulations to Xu Miaomiao.
Welcome to join the cheerleading team.
Buy one and get one free.
It's okay.
We are teammates from now on.
I’ll protect you.
Yes.
Coach.
Since I'm a member of the cheerleading team,
I have to say something.
I think
our team uniform is too ugly.
I suggest finding a professional designer
to design a new uniform for us.
Xu Miaomiao.
We won't disturb the coach.
Who disturbed the coach?
Am I right, Coach?
♫I don't need to doubt that I've fallen completely♫