[Tsukumoyacho - First Year of the Showa Era (1926)]
[Iwai Detective Agency, Tsukumoyacho 99th Street]
Mother...
Mr. Iwai, please wake up.
Morning, Ms. Kanoko.
Breakfast is ready.
- Sir.
- Ouch!
No sneaking bites.
Looks delicious as ever.
- Mr. Iwai.
- Yes, ma'am.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
- Let's dig in.
Yum...
Yum, indeed.
Mr. Iwai, mail.
I'll go grab that.
Good morning.
This would be everything.
Thank you very much.
They're all addressed to you, sir.
Are you expecting something?
No, sir.
Breakfast turned out great, I'd say.
Kanoko, are you going to ask Santa Claus for anything?
Santa Claus?
It's almost Christmas.
Here, Santa Claus.
You don't know Christmas?
You decorate a tree, and eat fancy food!
I've only read about it in books.
Oh...
What did you ask Santa for Christmas?
Bye!
Morning, Taro.
A Christmas party?
Kanoko's never celebrated Christmas before.
My, are you suggesting we hold a Christmas get-together?
But keep it a secret from Kanoko.
- Then this has to be a surprise party for Kanoko.
- Yup.
What a wonderful idea.
I'll tell your father to cook a feast.
Tell Mr. Iwai about it, too.
Of course. Let's make sure he helps with the preparations.
After all, Mr. Iwai would be utterly lost without that girl. Right?
Yeah.
My gut says someone is talking about us.
Hopefully it's because they have a job for us.
Well then, I'm off to go post these up around the neighborhood.
And I have a shrine to go clean.
I'll see you later, sir.
Careful out there.
Right then.
Ouch...
Ms. Kanoko? Are you alright?
I'm fine.
[Usotoki Rhetoric]
[Episode 10]
Please come to us if you need anything at all.
Will do.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
[Tsukumoyacho - East Mountain, 65th Street]
65th...
99th...
Come on, put your back into it.
I already am.
You cheated, didn't you?
What?
You won "rock-paper-scissors" ten times in a row.
Nonsense.
- There.
- Thank you.
Rent please.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Could you direct me to 99th Street?
Pardon?
I'm searching for the Iwai Detective Agency.
Do you have trouble?
No, rather...
I'd suggest you turn back, ma'am.
That detective is poor, and unreliable.
- But...
- He only works for money or food.
- Well...
- The cold weather has him unmotivated as well.
That being said, hot summers don't motivate him either.
Spring and autumn are especially prime time for lazing around.
In short, he's a difficult fellow.
My daughter is in his care.
Could you perhaps point me the way -
That was...
Sorry about that, ma'am.
In that case, I can guide you there.
Would you really?
Of course.
[We shall solve your troubles - Iwai Detective Agency]
Call on us anytime.
Of course.
Thank you again.
- Good luck out there.
- Good luck!
Thank you!
Perfect.
[A Christmas Gathering]
Christmas...
Thief!
Someone catch that boy!
Sorry, I'm gonna need a hand!
Right!
He's not in his office around this time.
Let's head over after a snack.
Please, sit. You must be tired after traveling.
Go on.
Thank you.
These Tsukumoyaki's are a Tsukumoyacho specialty.
Would you like a seaweed, or sauced one?
Then...
I shall take this one.
Thank you again.
This is delicious!
Then we're lucky.
These things taste differently every day.
I see.
I wonder if my daughter had one of these as well.
Maybe.
She has quite a love for food, you see.
Though I must say, your daughter is absolutely heartless.
She's left her visiting mother to navigate these streets herself.
You knew her address, so clearly she knows you're coming.
Youngsters these days just don't respect their elders.
No sir, you misunderstand.
Then did you come all this way without telling her, ma'am?
Yes.
I understand, I'm also quite forgetful.
- It's not too late to -
- No, no.
I didn't forget to send word of my visit.
Then you came without telling her on purpose?
I do not intend on meeting my daughter face-to-face.
I only wish to see her doing well.
I see.
She must never know I have come to see her.
Sounds like a troublesome daughter to me.
Oh, she's no trouble.
My daughter is a sweet girl.
She has an incredibly kind heart.
And yet you cannot bring yourself to go see her?
Mom, try this one too.
Thank you, dear.
She is my treasure.
I cannot go to see her...
Because she is so kind.
Hey!
Wait up, you thief!
Hey! Stop right there!
Stop!
Someone, get that boy!
Give me back my money!
Wait!
You rascal...
- Say...
- Yes?
Have you ever met this "Mr. Iwai"?
I know of him.
He's a lazy man, with a real obsession for money.
How curious. My daughter described him as an intelligent man,
with a magnanimous heart.
She has him in high regards I see.
My daughter's letters never included an address of any sort.
That is, until her most recent one.
[Iwai Detective Agency, Tsukumoyacho 99th Street]
This place has become somewhere my daughter feels welcome.
I wonder, what sort of individual is Mr. Iwai?
Last I heard, an assistant he hired several months ago
has been putting in good work.
Is that so?
Yes.
I also hear she helps him solve cases, or perhaps not.
Either way, I'm sure that dirt poor detective owes her plenty.
- There he is!
- Wait up!
You ain't getting away, kid.
I won't allow you through.
Fine.
You can have your money back.
Sorry about that, folks.
We've got it from here.
What's your deal, man?
Come with me.
- Thanks again, Gramps.
- That was delicious. Thank you.
See you around.
Detective Iwai's a real troublesome fellow, I'll tell you that.
I have to give her credit for dealing with a man like him.
Ma'am?
Sorry, I was simply mystified.
Mystified?
See, my daughter...
Never mind.
At least it seems like they get along well with each other.
Why is this "Mr. Iwai" able to get along so well with Kanoko?
I work at Suou's Sandals, doing odd jobs around shops.
What's your name, kid?
Kasuke.
- What was that?
- Kasuke.
Tell me, Kasuke. Why'd you trick me?
The Suou kid's book got torn.
So I went to go buy a new one, before Mr. Suou found out.
There you go.
[Children's Encyclopedia of Bugs]
How much?
That book costs 80 sen.
Dear, come over here.
Sorry, I'll be right back with you, son.
Yes?
I was short on money.
[Children's Encyclopedia of Bugs]
Excuse me, could I get the book written on this note here?
I took on this errand but I can't read, or write for that matter.
I assumed you had mistaken me for a clerk.
Sorry, were you a customer?
So...
Nope, I work here.
We just sold the copy we had on display.
I'll grab another from the back.
Thanks a bunch.
- Could I get the payment first?
- Right.
Here's 30 sen.
Perfect.
I'll be back with you shortly.
Just give me a minute.
Thanks for waiting...
[Sugaya Bookstore]
Son?
H-Hey! Thief!
First things first, you gotta apologize for tearing the book.
It wasn't me.
A stray dog got to it.
Then just say so.
'Cause no one will believe me.
And why's that?
My dead dad was caught as a robber.
The first store I worked at always blamed me for their problems.
No one ever believes me even when I'm telling the truth.
So I gotta lie my way out of it.
What an angsty lad.
So, how much are you short?
- Huh?
- I can't cover the whole bill, but I can pitch in a bit.
You can't be serious.
What if I was lying just now?
You weren't lying.
It feels great to hear that, even though I was.
You weren't.
Listen here, Kasuke.
I often find myself in a similar situation.
But the reason I still manage to scrape by
is because there are people who are willing to help, and forgive.
There are people who are willing to believe.
Without them, I don't know where I'd be now.
It's when I think back on these kind folk,
that I realize I can't just wallow, you know?
So just think of it as your lucky day, and take my change.
Let it overwrite the bad vibes.
I don't need your pity.
You're making me look like a brat.
That's because you are.
Mr. Suou...
He's a nice guy.
Do you think he'll believe me if I explain myself?
I wouldn't know.
I'm not this "Mr. Suou", after all.
Whatever.
Even if he doesn't believe me, I'll tell him everything.
I just want to try.
Sounds good.
Will you truly leave without actually meeting your daughter?
Yes.
I only want to see how she is doing.
Are you really this girl's mother?
Pardon?
Your story reminds me of a common fraud.
A mother comes to "visit", only to rob an empty house clean of all its valuables.
I am no thief.
They convince strangers that they don't wish to see their child, only to -
That is not the case.
But then this is strange.
Strange?
You have her address, but didn't send word of your visit,
and now you're trying to leave without even a "hello".
That doesn't sound like you cherish your daughter at all.
I'm terrified.
Of meeting your daughter?
But she is your treasure, is she not?
She is, and I cherish her deeply.
But I am afraid my words will only hurt her.
In that case, simply don't say anything that will.
Although, if your daughter was somehow able to detect lies,
I can understand why you would worry.
Pardon?
"What if there was a lie mixed within my words?"
"What if she had to hear it?"
Yes, I can see why you would be fearful.
- Sir?
- Like parent, like child.
It seems your experiences resonated with Kasuke, Mr. Riichi.
Don't give me all the credit.
It helped that you believed in his story too, miss.
That kid had lost his faith in people,
because people lost faith in him.
My claim that he "wasn't lying", isn't exactly the same as believing in others.
Drat.
I forgot to buy the book.
Still, I understand the importance of belief and believing.
Because having that sort of trust
makes a person feel stronger at heart.
Excuse me, are you...
Even your expressions and mannerisms are similar.
Especially the way you both worry yourselves into a twist,
and the way your stomachs frequently rumble as well.
You are Ms. Kanoko's mother, no?
- Huh?
- We've arrived.
Welcome to my office.
"Iwai Detective Agency"...
Mr. Soma Iwai?
As for why "Mr. Iwai" is able to get along with Kanoko...
It's because I'd rather have someone expose my lies,
than deal with someone who doesn't believe in me, when I speak the truth.
After all, the fact that she's able to perceive lies,
also means she's able to see the truth.
She's able to see the truth?
I've never thought of it that way before.
All my life, I've only focused on how not to hurt her feelings.
I'd speak carefully, to not lie.
But I was afraid that effort too, would sound like a falsehood.
It was a dilemma I could never find a solution for.
Don't overthink it, and complicate things further.
Tell her everything that's on your mind.
Will that child forgive me?
After all these years?
I don't know. I'm not Ms. Kanoko, after all.
Nevertheless...
The Ms. Kanoko I know
will listen to your story.
You won't insist on leaving without seeing her now, will you?
I forgot to lock up again.
Ms. Kanoko will nag at me again.
Come on in.
Kanoko gets mad?
Quite often.
Welcome.
Please, have a seat.
She reprimands me when I try to sneak a bite of food.
She wasn't forgiving when I suggested we take a lost cat as hostage, too.
Ms. Kanoko also laughs and eats plenty.
She's actually even sung and danced with me before.
She dances?
She does indeed.
Excellent timing.
Kanoko...
Mother?
I'm so glad you look well.
Why have you...
What about Dai?
Your father has come home from work, and is looking after him.
Mother...
I missed you, my dear.
Thank you very much, Mr. Iwai.
Thank you for dinner.
Yes, thank you again.
Come visit again any time now.
Mrs. Yoshie. Please continue to take great care of Kanoko.
You won't be returning with them, Soma?
You inconsiderate fool.
I don't want to intrude.
Kanoko looked so happy tonight.
Did Kanoko go home?
Yes, she just did.
- Mom, tell them.
- Hm?
Kanoko's not here!
Right!
Mr. Iwai, Mr. Hanasaki.
They're all such nice folk.
There are plenty of others you haven't met too.
There's Mr. Roppei, Mrs. Lily,
Mr. Kanji... and Ms. Chiyo!
Ms. Chiyo is the daughter of the Fujishima family.
She's an energetic, and fun individual to be around.
Is this person your friend?
Yup.
I see.
Mr. Iwai is...
He's an exceptional person, really.
I know he has that unpaid tab...
But he's truly kind.
I can tell from the way you talk about him.
When you left the village,
I said you were welcome home any time, remember?
Yes.
You know you're welcome home anytime, right?
I know. Thank you.
I have always been worried about those words.
If you came home to the village, you would only suffer.
And if that were so, perhaps it was best you never returned.
It was an honest thought I had. I couldn't help myself.
But then...
What if my words only sounded like a lie?
I tried penning a letter about this.
But a letter is...
I know.
I finally had it up to here, and found myself in Tsukumoyacho.
Yet until I met Mr. Iwai...
I didn't even have the courage to speak with you.
I'm so sorry.
In my fear of a slight lie...
I failed to tell you everything I truly feel.
I love you, Kanoko.
I love you.
I love you, my dear.
Mother...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry.
Mother...
What? You ate a Tsukumoyaki?
It was delicious.
I'm glad.
Because sometimes, it's not.
- Really?
- Yup.
Talking about food is making me hungry again.
It's time for bed.
Good night.
A surprise Christmas party?
Something to show our appreciation for Ms. Urabe's hard work around town, I suppose?
Indeed. We shall begin preparing tomorrow
for the party two nights from now.
Mr. Iwai, you will help my husband carry in the tree tomorrow.
He'll be leaving first thing in the morning, so be ready.
Wake up.
- I'm not lifting a finger.
- Mr. Iwai.
Soma. No one is more indebted to Ms. Urabe than you are.
You're always preaching to me about sincerity, but look at you now.
How dare you lie to Ms. Kanoko?
Personally, I'd hate to keep anything from her.
Why don't we just spill the beans?
You don't get it, Mr. Iwai.
We're going to surprise her.
Keep complaining, and there will be no more meals for you.
Now Taro, it's off to bed with you.
This spells bad news...
Good morning...
Huh?
Good morning.
Mr. Iwai?
Mr. Iwai doesn't seem to be around.
Is that so?
I had hoped to say farewell, but alas.
My train is coming soon.
Yup.
Give Mr. Iwai and the others my regards, alright?
I will.
Hold on, I'll walk you to the station.
Kanoko.
I will head to the station alone.
Otherwise my sadness will become unbearable.
You know, Kanoko.
I had actually asked Mr. Iwai how he could remain at your side,
what with your powers and all.
Really? What did he say?
He had said, to perceive lies
also meant seeing the truth.
To him, your ability is a solace.
It gives him the relief that someone believes in him.
Even now, I feel guilty that I couldn't protect you
when I was right at your side.
But I'm glad you met Mr. Iwai
after leaving our village.
I truly am.
Kanoko.
I'll see you again.
Mother.
Thank you...
for coming to visit me.
I'll write to you when I return.
Okay.
- Thanks again.
- Of course, come again.
Thank you.
Come again now.
Welcome back -
- Ma'am.
- Kanoko!
Have you see Mr. Iwai?
Mr. Iwai? He left early this morning. Said he had a job to do.
That was...
I recall he said he would be back by this evening.
A lie.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Why did Mrs. Kurata lie?
She must have her reasons.
- Are you alright?
- Ms. Urabe!
I mean -
Please, do not touch that.
- What?
- I'm alright, really.
- Sir, thank you for visiting yesterday.
- Yesterday?
Ah yes, it was an honor to meet your mother.
I've got that.
Have you seen Mr. Iwai?
Soma?
Oh, erm...
I have nothing to say on the matter.
Well then.
Good day.
He definitely knows something.
That surprised me.
She almost found out.
Will we manage to hold out until tomorrow night?
We should just tell -
This is for Kanoko's sake. We just want to surprise her a bit!
- It's a secret, Mr. Iwai.
- A secret.
A secret.
Mrs. Kurata lied,
while Mr. Hanasaki is hiding something.
What exactly happened to Mr. Iwai?
No, it's okay.
Those people would never hurt Mr. Iwai.
Even though I don't know why they lied,
I trust that it's nothing bad.
Right then.
[We shall solve your troubles - Iwai Detective Agency]
- Mr. Iwai.
- Welcome back, Ms. Kanoko.
I just returned as well.
Sir, where were you today...
Did you visit the Kurata's?
Is this about Mrs. Kurata's lie?
Mr. Hanasaki knows something as well.
I knew you'd worry about it.
It's okay.
I'll pretend I haven't caught on.
I see.
When I first hear a lie, I still end up assuming the worst.
It's not an easy habit to break.
You're not alone though.
People who can't detect lies go through the same experience.
They doubt the truth,
and grow anxious.
You've seen people lie for this very reason, no?
Sometimes what seems like a lie, turns out to be the truth.
And that makes situations even more troublesome.
Even if you didn't have that ability of yours,
I assume you'd be worrying just the same.
You just pick up on these lies more often than others do.
Which, in turn, leaves you less room to doubt the truth.
I'd say it's a fair trade-off.
Mr. Iwai always opens my eyes to a new perspective I was unaware of.
Let's go.
Sir, it seems they're closed already.
[We are closed for the night - The Kurata's]
Kanoko?
Ms. Urabe?
- Should I help?
- No, no need!
This has nothing to do with you, Kanoko.
Yes, this is... for a job Mr. Hanasaki has taken on!
- Isn't that right?
- I see.
- Mr. Iwai, let's head back.
- Oh darn!
I forgot they were secretly prepping for a Christmas party,
because Taro wanted to surprise you.
Mr. Iwai!
- Soma!
- Oops, let my mouth slip.
Mr. Iwai, our secret!
- Sorry about that.
- He...
He revealed the truth in front of everyone on purpose.
All so he wouldn't lie to me...
Unbelievable!
And so I wouldn't have to lie to all these people.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Please do not blame Mr. Iwai.
He has given me so much, I would never be able to repay him.
Not in my life.
He has?
What I mean to say is...
Alright, alright. If Kanoko insists.
Right, folks?
We'll be holding a Christmas party here tomorrow.
Look forward to it, okay?
I will.
Alright. Back to work! Mr. Iwai, you help Mr. Hanasaki.
Go on now.
Here.
See you tomorrow?
Yup.
Kanoko, we're ready!
[The next night]
I can head over now?
Yup. Let's go!
- Ready?
- Yup.
Kanoko.
Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas!
Go call them in.
Kanoko, dinner is ready.
Come eat it before it gets cold.
Okay.
- Alright.
- Come on in.
Welcome in, folks.
Mr. Iwai.
Me...
Merry...
Merry Christmas, Ms. Kanoko.
Merry Christmas, Mr. Iwai.
Kanoko, Mr. Iwai, hurry.
Sorry about that, Taro.
Hurry!
[To be continued]
Your landlady said I could stay a while.
[The finale is upon us!]
This is my office.
[A mysterious freeloader arrives at the agency?]
- My, do you have a guest tonight?
- This is my wife.
- Ron.
- You have got to be kidding.
- Inari's not here!
Kanoko, you must like Mr. Soma dearly.
You're lying to us, are you not?
[What exactly is this woman's end goal?]
I'm a liar.
I'll be adding her tab to your growing bill.
- Soma, come here.
- Is everything alright?
I wouldn't mind sleeping with you instead, Mr. Soma.
That's another lie.
Mr. Iwai.