Kanoko was being weird again.
She's so creepy.
Be quiet, she'll hear you.
Who cares? It doesn't matter if she hears you.
She's a monster.
See ya, Monster!
- Get lost, you freak!
- Ew, it's Kanoko.
Mom told me to stay away from her.
- Take care now.
- Mine too.
She said Kanoko brings bad luck.
So that's when I told him, the devil's out to get him!
Quiet. Kanoko's here.
Close call. She would've called me a liar again.
- The girl can't even take a joke.
- What a real pain, that one.
Did you hear? Kimi's folks are having another quarrel.
That girl must've run her mouth again.
How can she act like she had no part in this?
It's like she can read our minds. Unsettling, I'd say.
Missy, you got a minute?
We've got a bet we can't lose.
Your "powers" would really help us out.
Ignoring us? The nerve.
[Monster]
[Harbinger of Bad Luck]
Mother...
Welcome home, Kanoko.
[Leave our village]
Oh, this? This is nothing.
That's the tone of a lie.
For as long as I can recall,
I've had a certain knack for detecting lies.
Mother.
Promise me you'll stay in good health, Kanoko.
I will.
I'll make sure to send word via letter once I settle down.
Write as soon as you do so, and not a moment later.
Don't worry about me, Mother.
I'm not the youngest to have left the village.
I know I've caused you a fair share of trouble growing up.
But I have a better handle on my ability now.
I promise I'll be fine.
Yes, I'm coming.
There, there now.
There, there...
If anything, with this skill of mine,
no bad folk will get the best of me.
So...
I promise I'll be fine out there, Mother.
Kanoko.
If you ever find yourself in a tough patch,
you know you're welcome home anytime, right?
I know. Thank you.
[Tsukumoyacho - First Year of the Showa Era (1926)]
I find myself in a far away town.
Yet where there are people, there are also lies.
- Good morning.
- Shopping?
- Yes. I plan on making sukiyaki for dinner tonight.
- My! So do I.
Lies.
You're a lucky man, my good sir.
Buy this elsewhere, and it would've cost you twice as much.
- Really?
- I'd never lie.
Lies.
Miss.
Miss!
Your knot there is coming undone.
- Let me fix it for you.
-Lies.
- Now, come this way.
- I'm fine, thank you -
With this ability of mine,
I should be able to avoid most immediate dangers.
- Come again.
- Yes, come again.
[Cafe Rose]
[Now Hiring Waitresses]
Good morning.
The head proprietress will be with you shortly.
Here, have a seat.
Are you aware of the sort of store you've stumbled into, Missy?
Erm...
Gosh, you must be nervous.
- How about a smoke?
- Stop that, she's a child.
- But she wants to work here, doesn't she?
- You bully.
Leave it at that, girls.
I'm terribly sorry, dear.
We just hired a new girl.
In fact, you caught me as I was about to take that poster down.
Is that so?
Come again when we're calling for new hires.
We'll be waiting.
A country girl like her could never replace Maria.
Especially since her customers were there for her beauty.
Really, who thought she would run off with a mystery man.
I only hope she found herself a good one.
Isn't that right, Madam?
Enough chatter. This shop won't clean itself now, will it?
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry, miss. Try another place, yeah?
I'm starving...
[Tsukumoyacho]
We're "cleaning"? Cleaning what?
The ol' Inari shrine up ahead.
[T/N: Inari is the Japanese god of foxes, fertility, rice, etc.]
It needs a good sweep.
We're coming here to clean a shrine.
Exactly.
We're here to clean.
- - To clean.
Looks like your ears need cleaning too, Kaoru.
Soma.
If you really wanted me to arrest you, you only needed to ask.
I cannot believe you called me out here to clean.
Cut me some slack, it's tough work for one guy.
Soma, I am a police officer.
Hey, wait up.
A person's life is on the line here.
On cleaning this Inari shrine?
The modernization of our era has left this shrine to be forgotten,
with visitors dwindling by the day.
Even the old lady who used to care for this shrine
entrusted her duties to her youngest daughter, before passing on.
If you're just trying to scare me, stop it.
However, this daughter of hers
had long forgotten about the shrine in favor of her work.
And you see, this youngest daughter is actually...
- Enough.
- My landlady.
- Huh?
If I tidy up around here, she'll lower my rent for the month.
- Hey.
I might actually make rent -
The only thing "on the line" here is your livelihood.
- But I'm broke!
- Yeah?
And without money... Without money...
- I don't give a damn, you fool -
- Shush.
I hear something.
What was that?
- Leave it.
- H-Huh?
Leave it.
Woah - hey!
Leave it. Leave it, I say.
Please, leave it.
Leave it, I beg you.
Leave it.
Just leave it!
I already gave you the tail.
The head is mine.
Please, have mercy.
I haven't eaten a thing since yesterday...
You there! Miss!
Are you alright?
- And where do you think you're going?
- I'm not dealing with that.
You heartless bastard!
Miss, are you alright?
Miss?
Now then, I've got rent to save on.
[Usotoki Rhetoric]
[Episode 1]
[Tsukumoyacho]
[Kurata Eatery]
Welcome, welcome.
Come on in.
- There you are.
- You better help me clean that shrine.
That could take days.
- Here's our charcoal grilled salmon. Enjoy.
- I could care less about your rent.
Thank you so much. This looks absolutely delicious!
- Eat your fill, alright dear?
- And don't worry about the tab.
If anything, that guy there has eaten far more free meals than you ever will.
- Ain't that right, Mr. Sleuth?
- Come on.
You didn't have to rat me out, Pops.
He stuffs himself every day, and hasn't paid a single cent.
- Exactly.
- Seriously, Soma?
- "Mr. Sleuth"?
- Indeed.
That man there is a private detective,
while the other is Kaoru Hanasaki, a detective for the police.
They both carried you here.
They did?
Then pay your bill already.
Excuse me, sirs.
Thank you both for saving me.
My name is Kanoko Urabe.
I played no part in this. It was all him.
The name's Hanasaki. I'm relieved to see you are well.
- I'm terribly sorry for causing you trouble.
- It was no trouble at all.
More importantly, aren't the meals here delicious?
Just relax, and eat your fill.
Hypocritical bum.
I'm just speaking for Pops while he's busy cooking.
It's so homely here.
- These people speak to one another as they would a friend.
- Thank you.
And the meals they serve... warm me to the core.
He owes me that much? Damn.
- Do you feel no shame, taking advantage of such kind people?
- These people are honest folk.
How nice.
They're all cheery, and clearly get along.
If only my own life was like this.
- I'm home.
- Welcome back, Taro.
Thank you for grabbing those groceries.
I'll take those.
Running errands? Good going, Taro.
Here to eat free meals again?
- Taro, I'll teach you a lesson.
- Yeah?
Nothing's more expensive than something you get for free.
Says you.
Oh?
Taro, did you get any more change? I'm not counting enough.
That's all I got.
- No...
- That damn Rokuhei, taking my kid for a fool.
This means business.
Dear, I'm sure it was only a mistake.
No.
You shouldn't lie like that.
People will lose their trust in you,
and you'll be making a villain of that innocent storeowner, too.
What?
You should never lie to make someone else the bad guy.
- Miss.
- Ms. Urabe, I wouldn't be so hasty.
We cannot say for sure the boy has lied yet.
I'm sorry.
I... see.
Taro!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Thought you could best me?
Dear, there are customers!
- Come with me, son.
- Dear!
- What are you doing? Get the rag!
- I'm so terribly sorry, sirs!
- Ma'am!
- Yes?
Ma'am...
What's the matter?
Did you get new table kerchiefs?
Is now really the time?
Yes, we needed new ones.
Soma, I swear I'm putting you behind bars.
What have I done?
Taro. Go upstairs.
Folks...
I'm so sorry.
Kanoko was being weird again.
See ya, Monster!
The girl can't even take a joke.
- What a real pain, that one.
She's so creepy. Creepy.
I've made everyone miserable with my ability. Again.
Thank you for the meal. I must get going.
Kanoko?
Good night.
I've had it with my power.
You ought to stay the night.
I'll take shelter at the shrine.
Why? You've got nothing to apologize for.
Besides, I hear wild dogs are running amok up there.
We promise you're no bother at all.
The fault is Taro's, not yours.
Stay with our Sleuth tonight.
No, I mustn't. Sorry again for the ruckus I've caused.
At least finish your meal before you go.
And hey, my place is right there.
Though it might be messy, I've got a clear guest room on the second floor.
- Don't I?
- That, he does.
You have no need to brave the outdoors, really.
Now, come back in and have a seat.
There you go.
Feel free to come back for breakfast as well, dear.
Score! Thanks a million.
You ought to learn some humility.
Taro. I said upstairs.
Come on, Pops. I think Taro's reflected on his actions plenty.
Don't be too hard on him, alright?
Remember, he has his side of the story too.
Yes, sir.
- Sorry for the ruckus.
- Pops?
- I know, I know.
- Wrong. I'm asking for seconds.
- Seconds?
- Learn humility, indeed.
Thanks for dinner, Pops.
Take care now.
- See you tomorrow.
- You must be exhausted.
Take care, and rest plenty.
That is, if there's even room to stretch your legs.
Rude. Don't worry, the guest room is clean.
- Ms. Urabe, do not hesitate to call the police -
- Good night.
Then I shall leave you two.
Thank you for your help today.
My place is close. Follow me.
Here we are.
See? Told you so.
- "Iwai".
- Huh?
You were wondering how that was read, right?
It's my name. "Soma Iwai".
Oops, I forgot to lock the door -
- A-Are you alright?
- Come on in.
And close the door.
- How about we eat out tonight?
- Really?
Then we can actually chat a bit.
That sounds wonderful.
- Good evening.
- Evening.
She was whisked away because you wouldn't make your move, Mr. Moto.
Oh, Maria!
Without you, this place is full of hags and nothing more!
- What? Rude.
- You're a withering old man yourself.
I hear Maria left the place without a word to any of you ladies?
Of course not, she would never.
- That's what Rosanne said.
- I did not.
Don't you lie to me now!
Oh goodness, he'll kill me! Help!
He'll kill me, I say!
- Ouch!
- Are you alright?
Watch your step.
I've seriously got to clean up already...
Are you alright, Mr. Iwai?
- No.
- Huh?
Did something happen?
She cut off my electricity.
W-What?
It was only a matter of time. I wasn't paying my bills, after all -
One moment.
[Iwai Detective Agency]
Mr. Iwai, are you perhaps dirt po -
Do private detectives not receive much work?
Found it.
Listen up, Kanoko Urabe.
Yes, sir.
Have you ever once in your life thought,
"My, I sure could use a private detective right about now"?
- No, sir.
- Exactly.
Most people don't.
Which means detectives rarely get any work.
I wish people were lining up outside my door.
- I wish I had lines for days -
- Sir, calm down!
In any case, that's that.
Don't worry about water. There's a well out front.
These weeds are edible...
- Here.
- Thank you.
The guest room's the one all the way to the back.
Watch your step.
The stairs are especially messy.
Will do...
Well then, good night.
Good night.
Say...
How'd you catch onto Taro?
How did you know he was lying?
It was only a hunch.
I lied.
A hunch?
And here I thought you caught on like I did.
Nothing. Good night.
Good night.
♫  ♫
The lies I tell sound just as grating as any other lie I'd hear.
I spoke big about not lying to Taro,
yet I lied to all those people there.
♫ ♫
Although, I guess it doesn't matter.
The status quo won't last.
It's like she can read our minds. Terrifying, I say.
I know I'll be chased out of this town too.
♫ ♫
Take care now!
Mrs. Kurata!
Where's your husband?
He's searching across the river.
And we're certain no one saw him around these parts?
Absolutely, we've been looking all morning.
- So have I.
- Can it.
"Can it"? Learn some respect, you son of a gun!
- I'm back.
- Mr. Noppe!
Dear!
- Did you find him?
- He wasn't by the station.
I see. Then maybe he's by the piers.
- The piers?
- I'll go check.
Great, thanks.
Goodness, where did that boy go?
We'll find him, Ma'am. Stay strong.
Your help means the world, thank you.
Of course.
Have you tried contacting the school?
You absolute buffoon. It's a Sunday!
Right, sorry.
Taro will be fine, he's a strong lad.
- Indeed.
- Stay strong, Ma'am.
Where else would Taro go?
Excuse me, did something happen to Taro?
Truth be told, he wasn't in his room this morning.
None of us have seen the boy either.
Maybe he got caught up in something bad?
This is no joking matter, you dunce.
Go home already.
I'll help search for him.
Who was that?
Taro?
Maybe he's over there.
- Mr. Iwai?
- Good morning, Kanoko Urabe.
What are you doing?
Gramps, are you almost done?
I can't believe you've made me open shop bright and early...
Mr. Iwai, Taro has gone missing!
Which means I'm not getting breakfast at the Kurata's today.
This may be my fault.
- One seaweed, and one glazed mochi please.
- Yeah, yeah.
- If I only I didn't...
- Hm?
If only I didn't run my mouth yesterday...
- Now, now.
- Please let me go!
Follow me.
Gramps, I'm in a hurry. Put it on the tab.
- Again?
- This way.
You know where Taro went?
Probably.
Seems like you really hadn't caught on.
Coming...
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Have you checked the nearest station?
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Understood.
We'll call if we have any update on our end.
- Great, thank you.
- Sergeant Hanasaki.
We received report this morning of a child that has gone missing.
- A child?
- Yes, sir.
The child is Tatsuzo and Yoshie Kurata's son, Taro Kurata, age 6.
He was not found in his room this morning,
and his sandals were also missing.
Kurata, of the Kurata Eatery?
Yes, sir.
- Sato, search by the station.
- Yes, sir.
- Okuda, I want you to check the park.
- Understood.
- Ask around for eye-witnesses, anything will help.
- Yes, sir.
- Fujimoto, you're with me to the Kurata Eatery.
- Copy that.
- Let us make haste.
- Yes, sir.
A cat, you say?
[Tsukumoyacho]
Yes, the one you were fighting a fish over.
Taro probably went to check up on it.
- Want one?
- No, thank you.
If I'm on the mark, I think he was keeping the cat at the shrine.
A family working in food service can't keep a cat, let alone a pet.
He must have been feeding it leftovers from his school lunch.
I mean, you saw the evidence.
What evidence?
That cat wore a bandanna that had the same pattern as the kerchief the Kurata's used.
A bandanna?
But today is Sunday, which means no school and no leftovers.
Taro wanted to secure some food for the kitty,
which was why he tried to keep some pocket money for himself.
Don't be too hard on him, alright?
Remember, he has his side of the story too.
Is that why you...
- What was that?
- Nothing.
He had already picked up on the reason behind Taro's lie.
That was why he asked the Kurata's to go easy on him.
- "Iwai".
- Huh?
You were wondering how that was read, right?
He was able to answer me from my line of sight alone.
I didn't even have to speak a word.
He must be very observant of others.
But of course. I am a detective, after all.
See? He could easily tell I was amazed.
Now then, just a bit further.
Right.
Taro left the house last night because he got worried.
He thought the kitty might get attacked by wild dogs.
The very ones Pops mentioned last night.
- Wild dogs?
- Exactly.
Then I'm especially worried for Taro as well.
I doubt there are any wild dogs around.- Pardon?
And I think you'd know.
Because I've certainly heard growling around these parts.
- Me!
- Probably.
Oh, me.
Which is why Taro is here.
Taro?
Someone seems to be up there.
A visitor?
Good morning.
- Morning.
Sir, have you seen a small child wandering this area?
Can't say I have.
Is that so? Thank you, sir.
Huh? Did he just...
What's the matter?
That man knows something.
Woah, where are you going?
Let me go!
That man, he...
- What of that man?
- He...
I can tell.
Tell what, exactly?
Creepy. Creepy. Creepy.
I can tell when someone is lying.
That man says he knows nothing, but he's lying.
- What?
- Please, let me go!
You can detect lies?
Yes. I can.
I...
[Monster]
I am...
a monster.
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
What are you doing?
Stay back, it's dangerous around here.
I said, what are you doing?
Yes or no.
Ask him something that can only be answered with yes or no.
Get solid proof that he knows something.
For example...
Hey you!
Isn't there a kid in there?
No, of course not.
Liar!
Mr. Iwai!
Quit meddling!
I've got breakfast for you, Taro.
Mr. Iwai...
Let's split this later, yeah?
I need you to hold your breath for a bit. Got that?
Great job, kiddo.
Mr. Iwai...
Impressive.
Taro!
Taro, I'm so sorry.
You must have been terrified.
Taro had gone to the Inari shrine
to check on the cat last night.
Except,
he also happened to witness this man burying a body.
Go, run!
The man kept Taro locked up,
and had planned to kill him off as well.
Okay.
Everything's okay now.
That was loud, wasn't it?
It'll all be okay, I promise.
What's wrong now?
My Tsukumoyaki's gone...
"Tsukumoyaki"?
I'm sorry, Mr. Iwai.
I dropped your mochi.
I suppose that'd happen.
Come eat at our place instead.
Nah, I'm not blaming you, Taro.
But since you offered, I think I will.
Taro. Look.
Inari?
Inari!
So that cat's name is Inari.
Say...
Why did you decide to believe me?
Liar!
You dove into that fire,
despite having practically no evidence.
You could have died in there.
That's because I didn't think you were lying.
Someone who is against making a bad guy out of others
would never lie in a situation like that.
The other reason was because
the police may compensate me for a job well done.
I see you seriously believe it.
Thanks.
I'm glad he believed I can detect lies.
I'm glad Taro is safe, too.
Still...
I really didn't want Mr. Iwai
to find out about this skill of mine.
After all,
now he won't treat melike he used to.
He won't see me as a "normal" person ever again.
[Tsukumoyacho Police Department]
I went through what they call a "questioning" at the police department,
and after I told them
they explained to me the specifics of this case.
If I may ask, why exactly did you decide to tail that man?
Why did you think
I had a sort of hunch,
Thank you for your time.
Once we get your signature downstairs, you're free to go.
The one who was killed by that man,
was a waitress who worked for Cafe Rose, named Maria.
Ms. Kiyo Tabuchi, please come on in.
The poor girl.
She was played for a fool by an awful man.
Isn't that right, Madam?
Our livelihood is built on falsehoods.
Yet Maria was murdered, no thanks to another lie.
What an earnest fool she was.
I am able to detect lies.
It's almost like a supernatural power.
But I kept the truth behind my abilities a secret from the police.
Mr. Iwai must have kept the secret as well,
since the officers made no note of it."
Taro?
Taro!
You alright? Must've been a rough night.
- Taro?
- Taro!
He's back! Taro's back!
I'll be taking him home.
- Great!
We'll leave you two at that.
The Kurata's are waiting for you both with a feast prepared.
Mr. Iwai...
So you were awake.
Do you think Inari will be okay alone?
Ms. Urabe!
That must have been a harrowing experience. Are you alright?
Yes, I am fine.
That's good to hear.
And Soma?
I believe he's currently taking Taro home.
I see.
Ms. Urabe, is it true?
Will you be leaving town?
Yes, sir.
Was it rough, residing with Soma?
I suppose he is dirt poor.
He cannot clean either.
Yet he feels no shame for his faults,
and is an absolute bum at times.
I wouldn't...
Even so, he isn't a bad man.
He's incredibly observant,
almost to an uncanny degree.
Which is why he understands people.
Indeed.
My boss recently had his second child,
and they were looking for a nanny.
I had hoped to introduce you to them.
You wouldn't stay in Soma's garbage heap, of course.
We would arrange an abode for you.
- Sir...
- You should stay here, in our humble Tsukumoyacho.
Although...I suppose that doesn't sound appealing,
considering what just happened to you.
But this town is a good one, I guarantee it.
Thank you, sir. But I have places I must be heading to.
With this ability of mine,
I should be able to avoid most immediate dangers.
That is why...
I'll head someplace new, where no one knows me.
These weeds are edible...
♫ ♫
Thank you, for everything.
Stop fighting!
[The store is closed for the day. Thank you for understanding.]
I feel bad for Mommy.
Taro! How could you?
You don't feel bad for Daddy?
Did the police finish badgering you?
You're certainly carrying some baggage.
Did the police give you a hefty reward?
No.
Rather, what are you doing?
Mr. Hanasaki was looking for you -
- There, eat it while it's hot.
- Thank you.
I'm working off this morning's tab.
Besides, I don't want him nagging me for another unpaid meal.
Kaoru said he wanted to recommend you as a potential nanny.
Yes, I just turned down his offer.
Thought you would.
I could never let him introduce you to his boss,
especially with those powers of yours.
After all...
You're better off working for me.
- Pardon?
- Not that I have much to offer in terms of a salary, though.
- Erm...
- I mean, come on.
You can detect lies? That's incredibly useful for a detective.
- "Useful"?
With your powers, and my *cough*...
And your what?
Hot! Never mind the details.
Together, we could help so many people.
My power could...
And we could make absolute bank.
...help people?
I...
Yes?
I'd like to stay with you folks, if I could.
But...
But?
Creepy. Creepy. Creepy.
What's stopping you from staying?
Is it how broke I am?
Or maybe... how broke I am?
Because I'm definitely short on money.
Stop teasing me.
I mean...
Mr. Iwai.
You don't feel...
disturbed, having me around?
Not at all.
I'm an honest man, after all.
That was a lie, wasn't it?
Busted.
Huh?
Just now, he...
Not at all.
And you know that, right?
Because you can tell I'm not lying.
Are you alright?
Watch where you are going!
How absolutely clumsy you have been.
Do you hope to make a murderer of our wonderful chauffeur?
- Enough of that, Chiyo.
- Sir!
I apologize for my daughter's crude...
Crude attitude.
Are you unharmed?
Yes, sir.
That is an absolute relief. Well then, good day.
- Kokichi.
- Yes, my lady.
♫ ♫
Good morning, Kanoko.
Good morning, Taro.
Good morning, Inari.
Here's breakfast.
Taro, are you good on time?
See you later.
See you.
Travel safely.
Good morning, Mr. Iwai.
Good morning, my assistant.
And a good morning to our newest resident, Inari.
This marks the start to my life as a detective's assistant.
That's freezing!
[To be continued]
Kokichi? Kokichi!
[The rich lass gets kidnapped!]
Is something on your mind, ma'am?
Dear!
- A kidnapping?[The rich lass gets kidnapped!]
Matsutakes...
- You mustn't be tempted!
[Matsutake mushrooms, and mysteries galore]
Thanks a million.
I cannot miss "The Beheading".
[Matsutake mushrooms, and mysteries galore]
The beheading?
"I have your daughter."
[A case for this back alley detective, and his assistant to solve]
- Chiyo...
- There are several mysteries within this "kidnapping".
♫ ♫