[Hideyoshi Mayume]
Okay.
I have the ability to detect lies.
Sorry little guy.
And thanks to Mr. Iwai's acceptance of my quirk,
I feel welcome in this town,
without need to live in fear of my power.
At least, that is what I've come to believe.
Which is especially why I want to hurry and prove my worth to him.
- Hey there, Kanoko.
- Good morning.
Here, Inari's breakfast.
Thank you again, sir.
Take these stewed eggplants we had as leftovers, too.
Mr. Iwai loves this stuff.
As do I.
- May we really?
- Of course.
Thank you so much.
Must be hard work, being that guy's assistant.
Well, I still have a ways to go.
I wouldn't say that.
Speaking of, where is he?
He's out on a job.
That's a good omen.
Next thing it'll rain cats and dogs tomorrow.
Quit raining on our parade.
[Tsukumoyacho - First Year of the Showa Era (1926)]
- A cold?
- If only.
- What?
- My gut tells me trouble is on the way.
I only hope I'm wrong...
That's what you get for roping a poor bystander in to clean the shrine again.
You make me sound like a villain.
I told you the Inari shrine was littered, wasn't it?
Littered with dry leaves.
I'd say cleaning the area makes you a model police officer.
Get your act together and pay rent already.
I ought to arrest you.
This goddamn chill.
Morning, Gramps.
We're back.
That miso soup smells divine.
- We have returned.
- Welcome back.
Thank you for your hard work.
Stewed eggplant!
Mr. Iwai!
Wait for the table to be set.
I worked like a mule today.
Don't lie.
You're too serious for your own good.
Learn to relax already.
- Ms. Kanoko, some warm tea please.
- Sure.
Those are two separate matters.
Make sure you get your nutrients.
Says the man who eats weeds.
Wake up.
Wake up, I say.
Up!
Mr. Hanasaki, would you like to join us for breakfast?
Thank you, but I shall pass.
- I'll eat at the office.
- Please do.
We wouldn't have anything for you anyway.
- Sorry, sir...
- You have no need to apologize, Ms. Urabe.
The fault lies in Soma's incompetence and -
Bye now.
I shall visit again.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
Let's have breakfast, shall we?
At least put away your basket first...
What's all this?
Stuff I picked up to sell at the pawnshop.
I see.
I almost forgot. A letter from the landlady came while you were out.
From the landlady?
She wants me to go to her place.
I shall head out after preparing breakfast.
Something she can't tell me, the owner of the place directly...
No, am I finally getting kicked out?
This is bad!
But I just cleaned the Inari shrine!
I knew trouble was on the horizon...
[Usotoki Rhetoric]
[Episode 6]
Found you.
Okay...
Easy now...
Kanoko?
Wait up!
Please, don't run...
- Kanoko!
- What are you doing?
No!
Wait, please!
- That way!
- That way?
- T-That way!
Slow and steady...
Smells so good, even the kitty is tempted.
Indeed.
Mr. Iwai?
Where have you been? You could have helped!
Now, Ms. Kanoko.
- Go!
Right!
This cat is definitely the one?
- Yes.
- Glad to hear that.
I would have appreciated any help -
This was a task the landlady asked you to complete, right?
- I suppose.
- And for free?
Yes...
Her neighbor was cat-sitting for their boss, and let the cat slip.
Right, but sir...
If she directed those neighbors to me, this could have been a paying job.
I wonder if the landlady will take this job as next month's rent.
I doubt it, sir.
It's not her cat, after all.
- Say, Ms. Kanoko.
- Yes, sir?
Are those neighbors of hers rich?
Her neighbor's boss is the rich one.
Then we could keep the cat as a hostage,
and demand ransom money from those bigwigs.
If you do, I'm telling the landlady and Mr. Hanasaki.
Yes, what a terrifying prospect indeed.
I knew it, a catnapping would have made us hit the jackpot...
You're still going on about that, sir?
Chiyo Fujishima...
Ms. Chiyo!
- Mr. Soma, Ms. Kanoko! How do you -
- Nope.
That's just trouble.
Mr. Soma? Please do not run!
Mr. Soma!
Have you seen this man?
"Secrets", "Secrets"!
Come see our show at the Wakadake Theatre!
Act inconspicuous.
Yes, sir...
Mr. Soma?
Mr. Iwai? What're you doing here?
Now is not the time, really.
There you are, Mr. Soma!
- Mr. Soma!
- Thank you.
Ouch...
Ms. Chiyo!
But sir...
Sorry about that. You alright, miss?
There goes all the pain, right out your nose.
Did I miss a spot?
Are you alright, Ms. Chiyo?
Lemme see.
What?
Right, left,
back, and front.
Yup, not a scratch in sight.
Well, I'm in a hurry.
Farewell, miss.
Ms. Chiyo, are you able to stand?
Yes, but what ever was the matter with that man?
Do I look that young?
Goodness, I have embarrassed myself in front of Mr. Soma...
Your bag.
Ms. Chiyo.
Your kimono has come slightly undone.
What ever shall I do?
- Mr. Iwai.
- No.
- I haven't even -
- I refuse.
Sir.
I owe you much, Ms. Kanoko.
It was no trouble.
We're done, sir.
Great.
Though I must say, I am floored!
It is an honor to be welcomed into your office, Mr. Soma.
I never did.
I shall make some tea.
She's probably not thirsty.
I'd love tea.
We only have roasted silvergrass, so I hope that will suffice.
Silvergrass?
I must say, today is full of many firsts for me.
Say, may I take note of your office space?
Oh?
This does not belong to me.
What beautiful craftsmanship.
The individual from earlier must have dropped it.
- This reeks of destiny.
- Pardon?
- Trouble.
- Let us deliver this.
I knew it.
I've read about this sort of happenstance before.
Our protagonist is on the hunt
to find the owner of a lost item.
Yet as they uncover more and more of this mystery person,
they fall madly in love!
Love?
The protagonist's efforts also spark a flame within this owner, and...
My, what a romance!
To find clues, trace that trail,
and uncover the hidden truth.
Indeed, this is what being a detective is all about.
- So it's about the romance...
- She just barrels on, doesn't she?
First, we must see what sort of clues lie in this mirror.
I bet that man was a plasterer​.
You were acquainted with this individual?
Not at all. But he had plaster on his right arm, remember?
Did he now?
His towel had a store name embroidered on it too.
"Fujimitsu Plastery" is what it said.
How observant.
I expected nothing less from you, Mr. Soma.
Then let us make haste.
I don't do work for free.
Mr. Soma...
Besides, you'll be fine if Ms. Kanoko accompanies you.
I suppose we ought to be called the Girls Detective Club then?
Indeed.
I shall enjoy tea another time.
Let us depart, Ms. Kanoko!
R-Right!
Come back before dinner, you hear?
Yes, sir. See you later!
Have fun.
A young lad?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeowch!
Tome's the youngest guy here, right?
- Yeah.
- Then you've got the wrong store.
- Tome, bring us tea.
- Yes, sir.
If he doesn't work for the plasterer...
Then we've run dry of clues.
What a conundrum indeed.
Red hair!
- Red hair?
- Maybe they're talking about Riichi.
Does he have a sort of rattail?
- Yes, that man exactly!
- That guy's not a craftsman here.
He does easy, odd jobs around town.
Says it's 'cause he can't read.
Wasn't he working the mortar with you earlier, Tome?
Yeah. I believe he lives at that store full of knick-knacks
over on Marudera Street.
So his name is Mr. Riichi.
Thank you for the information.
- Let us make haste.
- Yes.
Do we have the right place?
- Excuse us.
- Yes, dears?
Would there happen to be a "Mr. Riichi" here?
Yes, one moment.
Riichi, you've got customers.
Coming.
The ladies from earlier?
- Apologies for intruding.
- Don't be, what's up?
We have come on business, as the Girls Detective Club.
Does this look familiar to you?
Oh hey, I was looking for that!
- It seems like it.
- Thanks for making the delivery -
How very suspicious.
Yes, indeed.
For why would a man have a pocket mirror on hand?
Actually, it's not suspicious at all, Ms. Chiyo.
You cannot deceive this detective, sir.
But he wasn't lying,
he was definitely searching for it.
Ms. Chiyo, this mirror belongs to him.
What?
This mirror was my mother's memento.
Thank you, really.
Huh?
That was a lie.
I've made an insensitive remark.
I'm truly sorry.
An honest apology. Very good.
Please do not treat me like some child.
Ms. Kanoko, let us be off.
R-Right...
Please excuse us.
I crave something sweet.
Riichi, don't munch on food when dealing with customers.
I have to eat it while it's hot.
- Still...
- He lied about that mirror being a memento.
But he wasn't lying when he said he had been searching for it.
Surely that mirror belongs to him... right?
Are you coming, Ms. Kanoko?
Yes.
I'm starving.
- Welcome.
- Hey, Pops.
- Full house today?
- Yeah, busy day.
- Alright.
- Sorry again.
- Excuse me.
- One grilled fish, coming up.
Could I get seconds?
Yes, right away.
Looks like it's another Tsukumoyaki day for me.
Gramps, two sauce please.
Grannie...
Welcome dear.
Welcome.
Where's Gramps?
We have done a fine job today.
Allow me to treat you
for going along with my antics.
Oh hey, I was looking for that!
This mirror was my mother's memento.
What ever is the matter?
Are you feeling unwell?
- No...
- Is that so?
A snack will perk you right back up.
Shall we partake?
Yes.
- Thank you again.
- Of course.
Soy sauce, vinegar, and mustard is a must for tokoroten*.
[T/N: a gelatinous side dish/dessert]
The clementines add a nice touch to this mitsumame* as well.
[T/N: dessert; mixture of beans, agar cubes, fruit, and syrup]
A thief got your bag?
Along with my favorite pocket mirror, too.
The silver one?
Yes, it was terrifying.
Thankfully, they tossed my bag aside.
My, what a harrowing experience.
What sort of pocket mirror?
- Pardon?
- We're the Girls Detective Club.
Might you tell us more of this mirror of yours?
We're no one suspicious!
We may have seen this mirror of yours.
It's quite the small thing,
but has a fine emboss of various plants.
That matches the mirror we saw.
The handle is also engraved with the name "TATUE", in English.
Could you write that down for us?
Was there any sort of engraving on the handle?
I'm not sure...
So the inconsistency within his lie...
Can you recall the thief's face?
No, it was all too sudden.
Was that he stole the mirror.
That mirror is definitely the one.
Yes...
Yes, it must be.
I believe that man is the thief.
Let us visit his place once more, and see for ourselves.
I would never forgive myself if I assisted a common thief.
You're really out of everything?
Yeah, sorry about that.
Looks like I have no choice but to eat this then.
So you do have food to eat.
Gramps was manning the stall in the morning,
so I thought it was a safe day.
But Grannie was the one at the stall when I went.
- So you bought Grannie's recipe?
- Yup.
I've been too scared to eat it,
even though I'm downright starving...
Where's Kanoko?
She's off searching for someone.
Is that right?
Sounds like she's doing more detective work than you are.
She sure is.
That's all you've got to say about it?
Here.
Thank you.
Still, that Kanoko's an absolute waste on you, Mr. Iwai.
I certainly owe a lot to her.
Say, Mr. Iwai.
Hm?
You've got to get yourself out of this poor state, and fast.
It's not like I'm not poor by choice.
Has my unpaid tab finally reached its limit?
That's not my point.
You'd best keep your eye on Kanoko.
Or else she'll find herself a better paying job,
and leave you for them, that's what.
Well we can't have that happen now, can we?
Yeah, especially since you've taken an unusual liking to her.
What?
I mean, you're not one to let someone stay close to you this long.
Make sure to treasure the lass, yeah?
Let us check the mirror, and ask for his mother's name as well.
If he is illiterate, his answer will not match the handle's engraving.
There's no need,
I'll be able to tell either way.
Excuse us.
My, what brings you ladies back?
Is Mr. Riichi still around?
I just sent him to Cafe Rose, on an errand for Lily.
Cafe Rose?
Let us make haste.
- See you.
- Thanks again.
Riichi!
Could you lend me a hand?
Sure thing.
Is Cafe Rose this way?
Yes, we are almost there.
Ms. Kanoko?
Sorry.
Watch it, kid!
Are you alright?
Can you stand?
Yeah.
My pain flew right away.
My, you're a strong lady. How commendable.
Say, where did you get that pocket mirror?
This? My brother gave it to me.
- May I see it?
- No.
I only wish to see it.
This is Mommy's mirror.
My brother told me to treasure it.
This girl...
- She isn't lying.
- I will return it.
- No.
- Yaeko.
Brother!
Hey! Give it back! Give it!
Hold on, have I...
- Ms. Chiyo, that is...
- Give it back, give it back!
Huh? There's no engraving on the handle.
Brother...
Here.
What are you people doing?
What is going on?
I...
I've made an awful mistake.
- We're so sorry.
- We're so terribly sorry.
You thought I was a thief?
We had jumped to conclusions.
Given the circumstances, I guess I'd look pretty darn suspicious.
But an honest apology is the sign of any good kiddo.
I see now.
Your habit of treating us like children is because of your younger sister.
Maybe so.
This here especially reminds me of Yaeko.
See? That, right there.
Come here!
Me?
Play with her, will you?
- Why, of course.
- This way.
Yaeko ain't my younger sister.
She lived above that store of knick-knacks with her mother.
Two years ago,
Yaeko's mother disappeared on her, leaving the kiddo behind.
I took it upon myself to look after her
since the same sorta thing happened to me.
But recently, she's been asking about her mother again.
I had no idea what to tell the kid.
That was when I found the mirror, in a sewer I was cleaning over the summer.
I gave it to Yaeko, saying it belonged to her mother.
So that was why you said it was your mother's...
I was coming back with it from the repair shop today
since Yaeko broke the thing.
Anyhow, that's the story.
Keep it a secret from Yaeko, will you?
I'm so sorry for the mistake.
Don't be, that ol' thing used to belong to someone else anyway.
Here, chin up.
Don't take it to heart, yeah?
Yaeko, it's time we head home.
- Brother, look at this!
- People tell all sorts of lies.
They lie out of ill-intent.
For show.
To be considerate.
And...
To keep a secret.
That's Grannie's recipe.
Ms. Kanoko sure is late, isn't she?
We did fine work as detectives today.
Isn't that right, Ms. Kanoko?
While that sounds marvelous, it is past your curfew, my lady.
I'm terribly sorry for causing worry, Mr. Kokichi.
Cheer up, Ms. Kanoko.
Although we made quite the blunder,
we must be glad Mr. Riichi is very forgiving.
Indeed...
My lady, we must be going.
I still have plenty to talk about with Ms. Kanoko.
Perhaps another day.
If you'll excuse us, Ms. Urabe.
My lady.
Please give my regards to Mr. Soma.
Ms. Chiyo misunderstands.
I didn't suspect Mr. Riichi, like she had.
Instead, I made an assumption.
I had assumed he was guilty, upon hearing his lie.
I can detect the lies people tell.
Yet that is exactly why there are things I've become blind to.
[Iwai Detective Agency]
Mr. Iwai...
Mr. Iwai.
Am I truly allowed to be a detective's assistant?
Am I worthy enough to be at your side?
All my life, this ability of mine
has only come to hurt others.
My father bought this doll for me.
You're lying!
- Kimi, you're lying again.
- I'm not!
I'm not lying.
I'm not!
Kimi!
You forgot your hat!
- There!
- Oh my!
You've gotten much better at that, haven't you?
I have to get going.
It's too bad. You only just arrived home...
Sorry. I don't know when I'll be back again.
Work has gotten busy, you see.
Uncle, you're lying!
And since you're lying, you can stay home with Kimi.
Is that true, Father?
- Father?
- Kimi.
Let's play over there with Grandma, okay?
Kanoko exposed his lie to the whole family.
It seems he had a lover elsewhere.
He was married into the wive's family, right?
I hear it became a whole ordeal over there.
We're so terribly sorry.
Do not step foot near our home, nor Kimiko ever again!
Yes ma'am, I am so sorry.
My daughter still hasn't woken up from the shock of it all!
I'm so sorry, Kimi's grandmother!
I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- Kanoko...
So what if you can detect lies? Devil's child!
We are so sorry for the trouble.
That was when I finally understood what my powers were capable of.
Mother...
The only way to avoid hurting others
was to stay alone.
So I made an effort to stay alone, without speaking to anyone,
because that was all I could do.
- And even then...
- He did it.
It wasn't me.
Believe me, sir. I'm telling the truth.
- Then who did?
- I couldn't just stand by
and watch people lie,
while they placed the blame on others.
I'm telling you, I didn't do it.
Really?
Are you telling the truth?
He's lying.
She spoke.
- Creepy.
- Matsuo is lying.
We need to talk, young man.
Mother...
Welcome home, Kanoko.
[Leave our village]
So long as I have this ability of mine,
it's only obvious people ostracize me.
I won't forgive you.
I can't believe you'd spread my secret.
You told everyone I'm receiving aid for my tuition.
What are you talking about?
I never told anyone anything.
Really?
But that's what I heard.
Lies!
She says I'm lying.
How terrifying.
Kimi, it wasn't me.
I'm telling the truth!
You're telling the truth?
How do we know you're not lying?
Kimi!
Must be nice.
You can hear our lies,
but no one can hear yours.
Right.
I ought to just lie.
I should lie, and keep all this a secret.
I'll leave the village,
and live my life pretending I can't hear these lies.
Promise me you'll stay in good health, Kanoko.
I will.
I'll make sure to send word via letter once I settle down.
Write as soon as you do so, and not a moment later.
I know I've caused you a lot of trouble growing up.
But I have a better handle on my ability now.
I promise I'll be fine.
Yes, I'm coming.
There, there now.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad my mother can't hear lies like I do.
If anything, with this skill of mine,
no bad folk will get the best of me.
So...
This power isn't all bad.
I promise I'll be fine out there, Mother.
I now understand why my mother hugs me
without a word.
It's because she's afraid.
She's afraid that a lie will be mixed in to her words,
and that I'll pick up on them.
After leaving my village,
I lied, and kept these powers to myself.
I vowed never to hurt another soul with this ability again.
But then I met Mr. Iwai,
and I realized my ability could help people.
I was happy.
This means your powers can't verify any unknown factors.
You'd best keep that in mind, if you're to be my assistant.
Mr. Iwai made that fact clear.
Yet I almost hurt someone again despite it.
Ms. Kanoko.
It's me.
Mr. Iwai?
The Hannya mask depicts jealousy and envy.
Come again?
It seems you don't get it.
First, eat this.
Eat up.
Amazing, right?
Amazingly horrible.
- Yes, sir.
- Grannie was manning the stand today.
- Erm...
- You know, Ms. Kanoko.
Yes, sir.
I visited the Fujishima residence earlier
because you still hadn't returned to the office.
What?
You only left my magnifying glass behind. Of course I'd worry.
And while I was there, I asked about this afternoon.
So...
I hear you had a nice bowl of mitsumame today.
Pardon?
Ms. Kanoko, why?
Mitsumame?
Why do you get to enjoy mitsumame,
while I was waiting, worried sick, with only a nasty Tsukumoyaki
to satiate me?
- Huh?
- And that is why I am here, looking for you with this mask.
Hence the jealousy and envy...
I had a feeling today would be nothing but trouble.
So?
What really happened?
From the looks of it, you're worrying yourself in circles again.
We've sat here to look at the moon before.
Remember?
I wouldn't forget it for the world.
Because your words that night made me so happy.
Sir...
I've decided I will no longer be your assistant.
I don't want to cause him any more trouble.
Today...
I made a mistake in judgement.
I almost hurt someone deeply.
There are things I've become blind to,
because I can detect lies.
And I know, deep down...
I will hurt someone eventually.
This ability of mine is not something to use for a profession.
I've always hated being alone.
But that's what was needed of me all along.
Even if you quit, you'll still hear those lies.
Yes.
- I'll simply ignore -
- Nope.
- I'll ignore-
- Not happening.
- I'll -
- You're asking the impossible.
How would you know?
Because you couldn't ignore Taro, Kaoru, or Shinako.
You had to say something.
Hence, impossible.
Even so, it's something I must do.
I don't want this power to hurt people.
I'm sick of it all.
Okay.
If anything, I practically forced you to become my assistant.
I wasn't exactly paying a salary either.
You might be better off working elsewhere after all.
He lied.
Farewell.
I'm the one who rejected him.
Mr. Iwai has never once disapproved of my power.
Yet I made him lie.
I...
I've...
I've hurt him?
You'll be fine if Ms. Kanoko accompanies you.
See?
A person who deeply hurts when others are hurting
could never ignore someone in pain.
Now resign to your fate.
- But...
- Alright.
Listen up, Ms. Kanoko.
If there's something you're blind to because you hear lies,
then it's something I'd be privy to, as someone who can't, no?
You're allowed to stay.
Mr. Iwai...
Let's go home.
Yes, sir.
I heard your stomach growling, Ms. Kanoko.
But I'm the one who's really starving, got that?
Sorry, sir.
All my life, I have been alone.
I always believed the solution to not being alone,
was to be allowed by someone's side.
Achoo!
Sir, should I give you back your coat?
It's fine. I just sense more trouble...
- Huh?
- Welcome home, Kanoko.
Good evening.
You forgot to lock up again.
Even if I may never believe in myself,
I am able to believe in Mr. Iwai.
And so, I finally feel like I understand
what it truly means to "not be alone".
Hungry?
Yes,sir.
[To be continued]
A Haunted Manor?
[The Haunted Manor of 33rd Street]
It's said to be haunted by a ghost.
- Let's go, Ms. Kanoko.
- Go, where?
To find us a ghost.
A ghost?
[The murderer is a ghost?]
Don't scream.
If you do...
[The murderer is a ghost?]
The identity of this woman lies within the Haunted Manor.
[Uncover the lies hidden within this ghostly activity!]
Who is this?
- A ghost!
- The correct answer is... Mr. Iwai!
This is me?
This is you, isn't it?
His sketch is so realistic, it's terrifying.
It's almost as if someone's will was pulling the strings.
It's sort of cold.
I'm starting to get chills.