Come on.
And then you snatch his phone.
Snatch it from that side.
Yes.
Face recognition.
Let me see first.
No, he didn't...
It's not locked.
Straight to it... Wow, a princess carry!
Princess carry and then toss him over there.
Where do I toss him?
Toss him over there.
Huh?
Toss him on the sofa.
Oh my god.
To think there'd be a day I'd be princess-carrying someone else.
How are you going to princess-carry him?
Just scoop him up from under his legs.
This isn't my dominant hand.
So strong.
I feel like I was lifted up in an instant.
Yes, one scoop.
Scoop him over there.
Go.
First...
You walk over first.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Don't move.
Let's just start from here.
No need to start over.
Are you okay?
Did you hit yourself anywhere?
It hurts a lot, stop pulling me.
I feel like you're about to rip my ribs out.
Let's just hug then.
And then kiss.
Kiss as soon as you lift him.
This should be fine, right?
It's fine.
This is fine.
Hey!
Careful, careful.
Right, stop messing around.
This is too dangerous.
I didn't dare to move much.
Right.
Let's see.
Just a forceful kiss like this.
Are you shy?
Come on, you resist.
First, try out the posture for a forceful kiss.
Let me see.
Forcefully kiss me.
Come on.
Where?
Where do I forcefully kiss from?
Just yank him onto the table and kiss him.
Just grab his head and pull it over.
Mhm.
Yes.
And then you turn your head away.
Look at the window.
Look outside the door.
You say, "No."
"No."
Then you turn his face back again.
"Don't worry."
This...
Yes, yes, yes.
Turn his face back.
"I've already locked the door."
Then things should proceed downwards from here.
That's why he has that...
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
How do we proceed downwards?
You have to flip him over and pin him down first.
Yes, this posture is very suitable.
This table.
Kissing, kissing, kissing, and then flip him over.
Right, just yank him.
Yes.
That's the idea.
The kind of master who turned you gay?
Look, it's so late.
Let's wrap up and go home.
Do you think I'm blind?
Hey, this shot is super cool.
Let me see.
Right.
And I can't even fight back.
I can only clamp his leg between mine.
Because I can't use any strength.
And then continue.
Hey, no.
Hey, right.
Practice this move.
Practice this move for a bit.
After you've kissed him,
besides kissing,
you must have some hand movements.
Slowly, slowly move down.
You can't be so aggressive.
Right.
Like dry tinder and a raging fire, sir.
Touch his hand, touch, slowly touch his belt.
And start unbuckling his belt.
No.
It's a bit itchy.
Don't get the wrong idea.
No one is getting the wrong idea.
What are you doing?
My knee hurts.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Failed at trying to look cool.
Holding his face.
I just like you wearing flowery boxer shorts,
clumsily making sugar figures,
and picking your feet while reading comics.
Can you not cover my ears?
You are my...
I just like you.
Who covers someone's ears when holding their face?
Okay.
I'll take you back to the clinic.
Every minute I'm with you,
I'm not myself.
I was going to ask, can my butt sit down?
Oh, that's true.
Actually...
Then it feels a bit like sitting just for the sake of sitting.
Like you want to sit but then suddenly stand up.
Actually...
Right.
Do you think this is how you look in my heart?
Hey.
Pause for a moment.
After the kiss.
"You think this is how you look in my eyes?"
Is there anything else you want to say?
I don't think so.
I'll take you back to the hotel.
Back to the clinic.
Action.
There are people outside.
Let's do it again.
This take wasn't intense enough.
The rhythm in the middle was very good.
I think the beginning wasn't intense enough.
Right.
The rhythm in the middle was very good.
The beginning needs to be more intense.
Like this.
Yes.
Stop.
Hey, that was intense.
That's good enough.
This take was very intense.
Very intense.
Right, just act according to this.
Should this be recorded too?
Cut.
I think you can move your position.
It's so weird.
What's up?
Turn over.
Come on.
Cut.
The moment he goes for your neck, you have to panic.
This is the office.
Right.
I should be more panicked.
Yes.
And then you pull him again.
The door is locked.
Come on.
Alright.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
These pants...
The pants button.
What would happen if I undid one more button?
It's hard to unbutton.
Every time you rip my clothes off...
it feels like you're peeling off a layer of my skin.
Undo a couple more buttons.
You're about to peel my skin off.
It's hard to imagine what it'll be like when we really let loose later.
That's good enough.
Very good.
Looks good.
Looks very good.
Okay.
Come on, get your clothes back on.
Get dressed.
Alright, we're going to start shooting the dialogue scene.
After the action scene comes the dialogue scene.
I have a feeling of having been "played with."
It looks so damn good.
"However simple you want it to be, that's how simple it is."
"That's the philosophy my mom told me."
My mind is full of you.
My heart is full of you.
I'm not leaving.
I'm calling a designated driver.
Let him finish his scene.
I don't care.
This is fine too.
Yeah, it works.
This move is pretty good, right?
"Can we, can we ever meet again?"
"I pleaded before the Buddha for thousands of years."
"Willing to trade lifetimes for our one life of love."
"Hoping to move the heavens."
I'm not leaving.
I'm just making a phone call.
Don't go.
Don't worry.
Then I'll sing a song for you.
Go on, sing.
"The ends of your dark hair are coiled into a circle..."
"entwining all my attachment to you."
"Through the translucent door curtain..."
"the words spoken from my lips hold no deceit."
"The gray tiles on the roof coiled into a circle..."
Okay.
So sweet.
So, so sweet.
So sweet it's killing me.
I was screaming.