Do you want to...
take things a step further?
How is it?
Delicious, right?
Okay.
Is it necessary to walk that far away?
You're about to fly away.
A medium close-up or what?
Do you want...
a deeper relationship?
Okay.
Cut.
That was great.
Great.
See?
Awesome.
The way we interact in real life...
is actually more like these two in the show.
Like, I'm always teasing him.
You two can just be yourselves then.
He was definitely nervous for the first scene.
But it's okay, because this scene itself is...
I just told him,
I said, "I would fall for you in real life."
Just imagine it.
He imagined it and got scared to death.
Just kidding.
Oh, so that's the feeling.
No.
OK.
He washed his hands, they're very clean.
Right.
Even if I didn't, he wouldn't mind.
Right. Come on.
I've already placed two pillows.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Give me some personal space.
Okay, that works.
Don't move your head.
Right, where's your position?
Now you're lecturing me, huh?
Lower it.
Hey, you.
Xiao Shuai, come forward.
Xiao Shuai, forward.
I feel like I have Parkinson's.
Lower it a bit.
Slower.
I don't want to eat it.
Don't rush, hold still.
Try your best to hold steady.
Good take.
You're laughing at me here, aren't you?
Laughing again, huh?
Come on.
Give me some pillow.
Woke up?
Not yet.
Why are you putting your leg on me?
And then hold back from kissing.
He moved out of the way.
Let's do it.
I finally get to be on top of him for once.
Put the folding screen here and...
the bedside table back in place.