Take a bite.
One bite.
Just one bite.
These two are different things.
Let me try.
It's not cooked, sir!
Did you eat the skewer from his hand?
Yes.
I didn't eat that one.
I'm done for.
It's over for me.
Quick, protect me!
Shuai Shuai.
Director: Everyone's quieting down.
Director: Slowly settling down now.
Settling down...
Stop hitting me!
What's this?
This is a designer brand.
I don't care.
That outfit costs a fortune.
It holds its value well.
You two good-for-nothings.
Button it up.
I can't seem to button it properly for you.
My hands are too slippery.
You guys, stop fighting.
If you're going to fight, go do it in the dance studio.
Hey!
Give it to me.
Don't play.
What are you doing?
Okay, come on.
Come to hit me.
Come to hit me and annoy me.
I'm tired.
So tired.
You can put it inside.
Smaller.
Chi Cheng.
Ouch!
You almost scratched me.
Hey, it's surprisingly not that scratchy.
I shaved today.
I have a standard
V-shaped face.
Ah, so you're like this.
Right.
Okay, come.
Let's do the next take.
Wu Suo Wei, turn your face a bit more.
Turn and get closer to him.
Yes, like that.
Now look back here.
Right.
And then, a big smile.
Broad shoulders.
I drew
the costume that you often wear.
The deep V-neck.
I'm done drawing.
Come and show it to everyone.
Can we have a "BE" song?
Do you still love me?
Why are your eyes reflecting light?
Because you are in my eyes.
How did you do that?
How should I know?
Don't stand on your tiptoes.
We need a bit of a height difference.
It's not like I...
What's your height?
I don't know.
Guo Cheng Yu, your hand a little lower.
Yes, yes, like that.
Good, hold that pose.
Let me see.
Do you still love me?
How come there's another camera here?
I'm a cool and aloof person.
Please edit this part out, thanks.
Ta-da!
We're rolling!
Stop with the "ta-da."
Let's try it.
Right.
Okay.
Guo Cheng Yu, come on.
Bring your face over a bit.
Higher.
Tip of the nose.
Right.
Good.
Losing all of this is a sin.
But I can't watch you leave.
He's getting shy.
I can't look at you.
Xiao Shuai, don't move.
Xiao Shuai's gaze...
Guo Cheng Yu, move a little closer and up.