The whole universe shines because of me
Episode 16
Only you?
One more.
I'll break his finger.
Senior, Mr. Ma,
wait here.
I'll go in alone.
Okay.
The
Yi Ran.
Ye Wu Miao,
I know you're good at fighting.
If you dare to fight,
he'll go down.
Listen to his order.
Let Yi Ran go.
If you have any conditions, just say it.
It's a good thing to talk to a smart person.
It seems that this little star
is very important to you.
I'm talking about the point.
Sign this contract.
Give me the 20 billion.
Sign it.
Take her away.
If you don't sign it,
I'll take you down.
I'll sign it.
You only know that I'm competing with you for 20 billion.
But you don't know
that 20 billion is for her.
20 billion?
Isn't 20 billion better than a woman?
You have everything with 20 billion.
Yi Ran.
Wu Er Ping.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
They're a team.
Miss Song,
I'm really sorry.
I didn't tell you the truth.
I asked you to cooperate in this play.
Play?
For the sake of friendship,
I gave up interest without hesitation.
Congratulations to Ye Wu Ming.
You passed the last test.
Junior,
this is the most important part of the test.
The most important thing about the successor of the Eight Immortal Sect is the character.
You took over the contract of 20 billion.
If you hesitate,
the contract will be invalid.
Mr. Feng, Mr. Zhu,
what do you think?
Ye Wu Ming did pass the test.
Mr. Ye,
we admit that you passed the test.
Greetings, Senior Brother.
You call me Senior Brother?
You look much older than me.
I'm a disciple of the Eight Immortal Sect who is abroad.
Now your identity has been confirmed.
Of course you're the Senior Brother.
Please allow me
to follow everything.
No, no, no.
You can follow me if you want.
But don't call me Senior Brother anymore.
Mr. Ma,
when can I use the 100 million?
Anytime.
The penalty of 100 million has been passed.
The previous thing was a deal.
From today on,
I have nothing to do with you.
You took the money?
For a playboy,
you took 100 million to protect her.
Is it worth it?
First, she is not a playboy.
Secondly,
is it worth my words?
Don't be touched.
I haven't said I'll take the money.
You took 200 million.
You took 100 million.
Are you planning to
send a drug dealer?
Mr. Li,
people are not good enough to swallow their own image.
You have a big appetite.
I'm afraid I'll choke you to death.
I'm not a snake.
You may not be a star.
Besides,
you dare not make things big.
Mr. Li,
as the biggest shareholder of the company,
I have a word to you.
Sometimes,
you have to learn to let go.
You can take it when you see it.
Mr. Su,
I'm doing this for the benefit of the company.
Although you are the biggest shareholder of the company,
you don't have the right to make decisions.
The risk is greater than the profit.
Although I don't have the right to make decisions,
if I withdraw shares from your company,
do you know what it means?
You have the right to make decisions for your own.
All my colleagues
have their own standards.
Mr. Su,
tell me,
is there something that Mr. Li
wants me to do instead?
If I become a?"
Mingtian, Governors this post,
send an issued note to Fish Village for matchmaking box with cards of 50,000 aoa arm.
Before opening the box,
have Yuanyuan say herself,
Correct on both leading and revoked justice.
Yuanyuan!
Mr. Ye.
Such a big office.
Is it comfortable?
You did it as my car.
Fine.
Done.
Congratulations, A Song Yi Ran.
From today onwards,
you're a real nobody
and an
I'm still your bodyguard.
Is that how you like to be a bodyguard?
I like you.
People
must be a little secretive.
But since I've officially broken off the contract with Mr. Li,
I don't think I need to be a bodyguard anymore.
No.
Although Li is stupid,
his father is hard to deal with.
I think he was too polite to you before.
He will definitely change in the future.
Come on.
Think about it.
You were his artist before.
You still have a bad credit card in your hand.
Maybe
you can kill him.
Really?
I'm so scared.
Don't worry.
I'm a professional bodyguard.
I think you're right.
Then please continue to protect me.
Then I have to think about it.
Let's have dinner together tonight.
Mr. Man says
this is our family's last meal.
Ms. Ye will be our guest tonight.
I'm home.
Come here.
It's not Mr. Ye's place.
It's not Mr. Ye's level.
It can be my stomach.
You're so massageful.
Move it.
This place smells good.
I usually come here.
Ladies.
Donation.
Guests.
Coupleै
처럼rzazoiangkyoucheng.
g y m z y
You two are
lovers?
Boss, you have a good eye.
We're a couple.
This is it.
Okay.
A couple set meal.
Are you too overbearing?
I'm overbearing.
Girls like me.
You're so ugly.
I don't want others to think I'm a loser.
No matter what others think of you,
just be happy.
You're right.
Anyway, I want to
take more acting lessons.
I want to make up for the past one
and shut others' mouths.
Listen, I'm not in a hurry to pay you back.
But you have to pay me back, right?
Here comes the couple set meal.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
Hurry up.
I'm not hungry.
You eat first.
Are you afraid of being photographed?
Of course.
If my fans know I'm a meat-eating animal,
I'll be ruined.
Why didn't you think of it?
What if your fans like the real you?
Hurry up.
Or else all the Geraldine is warning you.
I don't want results.
lack of experience
In the company
You keep saying you eat but have a bad appetite?
Come on, quick, quick
I need to have Opera Ten
I'm not eating.
No.
I won't eat if you don't eat.
Why isn't the beer here yet?
I'll pour it myself.
A healthy life and a beautiful morning.
It's a bit hypocritical.
Those on Weibo are just people.
People, you know?
They're all fake. You believe that?
I think
one should be reasonable.
You can't be like the usual.
You're just creating characters.
Then why can't I create
a sincere character?
I'm not that tired.
If those fans
don't like you because you eat meat,
then they only like your personality.
It has nothing to do with you.
Just one bite.
Wang Ming, thank you.
Birthday, Keyiks.
I'm the last one to deliver it.
Do you want to leave now?
You're already on my diet.
How can a Milwaukee Fried Chicken
taste as good as this in showbiz?
Showbiz does no Parent's Day.
Do you have time to prepare for it?
Birthday, Keyiks,
you're raising a baby.
Then…
words never lines don't contradict each other
you have gone out so long
I
raise your hand
how about William
I
take it
you
good
Life won't ever be the same without you
Please pay the round
Once I save the world
I will find my heart
I hate being alone
I hit you when you slept
I liked to sleep when you in dominated
but now you hateU
If you know
Say we're sorrows
Change another one.
Be ambiguous with me.
Get out of my way.
I'm ambiguous with you.
I'm joking with you.
Don't be angry.
I'm sorry.
You just want to say sorry?
You're not sincere at all.
You can't make up for my hurt heart.
Then tell me.
How can I make up for it?
I'm sorry.
How about this?
I've been thinking about
the rival drama between me and the leading actor for a long time.
I can't control my emotions.
It's action drama.
Take this opportunity
to practice for me.
Action drama?
Okay.
How can I cooperate with you?
I'll think about it.
Close your eyes first.
Stand still.
Feel the environment.
Are you ready?