[Men's House]
[Before they know it, the night deepens]
[Min Seong is the last to come back]
[Cho Yun Jae: Can I borrow a pen?]
[Oh Min Seong: What pen?]
[Cho Yun Jae: To write a letter. Not a letter.]
[Oh Min Seong: Write what?]
[Cho Yun Jae: My diary.
I didn't write it yesterday.]
[Cho Yun Jae: How was your date?]
[Oh Min Seong: I had a great date.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Did your feelings change?]
[Oh Min Seong: We had our date...]
[Oh Min Seong: I told him everything.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah, at the bar.]
[Oh Min Seong: I asked him
why he did that, and everything.]
[Cho Yun Jae: And then? What happened?]
[Oh Min Seong: Going on the date,
I was no longer angry.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Wow, so crazy.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah, I must be crazy.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I know, right?]
[Oh Min Seong: I was no longer angry,
and I was having so much fun]
[Oh Min Seong:
that I didn't want to bring it up.]
[Oh Min Seong: I was very angry
about what happened yesterday,]
[Oh Min Seong:
but after a night's sleep, or a day later,]
your anger sorta subsides, right?]
[Cho Yun Jae:
Is Hyeong Jun still your first choice?]
[Oh Min Seong: Well, for now.]
[Oh Min Seong: Ha... Why?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Sorry?]
[Oh Min Seong: Why?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm just curious about others.]
[Oh Min Seong: What about you?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's a secret.]
[Oh Min Seong: Seriously?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hyun Jun?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know yet.
I don't know anything.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's so interesting.]
[Oh Min Seong: What's interesting?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Just.]
[Oh Min Seong: The dynamics here?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: The more I know,
the more interesting it is.]
[Oh Min Seong: I agree.]
[Oh Min Seong:
How did things develop like this?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hello.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Did you have fun?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yes, I did.]
Sorry.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: How long did it take?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Must've been a long commute.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I went to Seoul.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What did you do there?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I did a lot.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm so jealous.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What about you, Taichi?]
[Taichi: I went to Sokcho Beach.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Right,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
I heard you went to the beach.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You went with Han Gyeol, right?]
[Taichi: Yes.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: How was it? Satisfied?]
[Taichi: I made it clear to him.]
Really?
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What did you say?]
[Taichi: That I don't feel that way about him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I expected that.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You told Han Gyeol that?]
[Taichi: It's not that I don't like him.]
[Taichi: It's not that.
But it's just not romantic.]
[Taichi: He's a good friend.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: He's a good person,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but there are no sparks?]
[Taichi: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm going for a smoke.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'll join you.]
[Taichi: Will you come to Block A after?]
[Kim Sun Wook: OK.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What'd you say?]
[Taichi: Will you come to Block A after?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Of course.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Take a rest.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What?]
[Hyeok Jin goes to Block A with snacks]
I'm so tired.
[Looking around]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Sleeping so soundly.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Where have you been?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I was resting in my room.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
And I came here after smoking.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Home-run Ball choco puffs!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Bought it at the convenience store.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My favorite snack.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm so tired.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: So tired.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Oh, this is your side, right?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I secured it.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I secured this side.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Good job.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Lie down for a while.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What've you been doing?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Just playing with my phone.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: There's nothing on it.]
[Romance persists deep into the night]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What's the text about?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's call time.]
[Oh Min Seong: You got a text?]
[Taichi: It's call time.]
[Time for your Phone Room calls.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[With the return of the call time,
have there been any changes of heart?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Honey.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah?]
[Kim Sun Wook: What's wrong, honey?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Who'll you call?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Like you don't know, honey?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I've only been waiting for your call.]
Since the first day I came here.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You know
you're my only one, right?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What's going on?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Honey,
you've never called me once!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I only said I'm waiting
for you to call me. I didn't say I'd call you.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
The three of us has clear paths.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Very certain.]
[Oh Min Seong: What if he doesn't call me?]
[Taichi: I know, right?]
[Oh Min Seong: What do you mean?]
[Taichi: I understand you're worried]
[Taichi: that he doesn't call.]
[Oh Min Seong: But really,
what should I do if he doesn't call me?]
[Oh Min Seong: I won't forgive him.]
[Taichi: Hmm?]
[Oh Min Seong: I'll destroy him.]
[Taichi: He'll call you.]
[Oh Min Seong: Who are you going to call?]
[Taichi: I'm still thinking.]
[Oh Min Seong: Between two guys, right?]
[Taichi: No, three.]
[Oh Min Seong: Three?]
[Taichi: It's because...]
[Taichi: I'm not
particularly interested in anyone.]
[Oh Min Seong: Don't call me.]
[Taichi: I won't.]
[Taichi: Can I not make a call?]
[Taichi: Honestly, I was a bit pissed off
when he told me not to call him.]
[Taichi: I'm sure it was a joke.
But we're roommates after all.]
[Taichi: I don't even like him that much,
but he told me not to call him.]
[Taichi: That kinda hurt my pride.]
[Taichi: And I know things are going well
between him and Hyeong Jun.]
[Taichi: Nothing will come out
of choosing Min Seong.]
[Taichi: That's why
I didn't want to make a call.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You must be really sleepy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I hate this time the most.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why? You're at your sleepiest?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
Go out... I guess I'm first.
[Kim Han Gyeol: Good luck.]
[Yun Jae is the first
to convey his feelings]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Ah, I'm getting hot already.]
[Hyun Jun goes to the living room
to be alone]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I thought he might call me.]
[Yun Jae, who's been
focused only on Hyun Jun]
[What will Yun Jae convey to Hyun Jun?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hello?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hello?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hello.]
[Want to go for a walk later tonight?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Tonight?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, if there's time.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
OK. Let's go if there's time.]
[Cho Yun Jae: OK. See you later.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: OK. See you later.]
[Cho Yun Jae: OK.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I still chose to call Hyun Jun, for now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: After holding hands
during our conversation,]
[Cho Yun Jae:
and after thinking things through,]
[Cho Yun Jae: I still liked him the most,
so I called him.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I decided
to be more proactive]
[Cho Yun Jae: and talk to him more,]
[Cho Yun Jae: so I wanted to
make some time for the two of us.]
[Hyun Jun has his head lowered]
[Yun Jae goes straight back to his room]
[Hyun Jun looks really troubled]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I wanna finish my call early too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Huh?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I wanna finish my call early.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Or not?]
[Cho Yun Jae: What do you mean?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Near the end,]
[Kim Han Gyeol: you'll get to choose
between those who've called you.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What if I don't get any calls?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Just have to accept it.
No other choice.]
[Kim Su Min,
please head to the Phone Room.
Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Kim Su Min:
After bowling, I was in a great mood.]
[Kim Su Min: Just seeing him having fun]
[Kim Su Min: and being all happy,]
[Kim Su Min: my mood improved too.]
[Kim Su Min: The slight physical contact
also made my heart flutter.]
[Kim Su Min:
So I decided to convey these feelings.]
[His heart is still burning for Sun Wook]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello?]
[Kim Su Min: Hello.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello.]
[Sun Wook answers the call with a smile]
[Kim Su Min: Thanks to you, today's been
the happiest day I've had in four days.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Really?]
[Kim Su Min: I hope that tomorrow...]
[I'll get to laugh and have fun
with you again.]
[Kim Sun Wook: OK.
Thank you for everything too.]
[Kim Su Min: Got it.]
[Kim Su Min: I've become more sure
of my feelings for Sun Wook.]
[Kim Su Min: He seemed to be
having so much fun at the bowling alley.]
[Kim Su Min: When I saw that,
it made me really happy.]
[Kim Su Min:
When I think of how happy I got]
[Kim Su Min: just from
from seeing someone else happy,]
[Kim Su Min: I thought that
I might really like him.]
[I realized I really like him.]
[Kim Su Min: So, Sun Wook
is the clear number one in my heart.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
What should I say on the phone?]
[Cho Yun Jae: When will I
have an experience like this again?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: There's a huge mountain.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't think I can cross it.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: But you're trying right now.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
Because that mountain is too high.]
But I don't want to make a Plan B.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: There's been
drastic changes to my plan lately.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
Is it Hyeok Jin or Taichi for you?]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
It keeps going back and forth.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What's making you waver?]
[Cho Yun Jae: So I can use that trick.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: As they say,
you have to put in the work.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
It's really what's effective.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Should I do that too?]
[Cho Yun Jae:
But I've been giving it my all.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: There's actually a change.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: My ranking has changed.]
[Cho Yun Jae: OMG. Seriously?]
[Cho Yun Jae: What a dopamine spike.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: You have to
keep it a secret. Promise.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: You must keep it a secret.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I won't tell anyone.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I got it.]
Good luck.
[Eum Hyeok Jin,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Yesterday was the interest ranking.]
He said if it was a call time,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: he'd have called me.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: So I knew he'd call me.
And I would call him first too.]
[Making his way towards Han Gyeol]
[Is Han Gyeol's heart really
aligned with Hyeok Jin's?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hello?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hello.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hello.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
We should go on a date tomorrow.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I hope so. Please.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I want to go out with you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Tomorrow,
no matter what it takes,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: we must go on a date.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yes.
Please work your magic.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'll see you later.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: OK.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: He showed
that he felt the same way.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: We must go on a date.
Even if we don't get to,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: we'll still go out.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I'll grab him and run away.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: My dopamine's spiking.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
My first choice is Hyeok Jin.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: My interest in him has grown
a lot. Since we had many long conversations]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
and also talked about our feelings.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You know,
my first date was with Taichi.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It was nice, but...]
[Cho Yun Jae: After talking,
I felt like he was too much of a kid.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
That's why I told you on the first day]
[Cho Yun Jae: that Taichi is like a kid.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
But after observing him for a while,]
[Cho Yun Jae: he's not just a kid.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah, he sounds mature at times.]
Right?
[Oh Min Seong,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Min Seong, the only participant in Men's House
who's making a call for the first time]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Min Seong is growing on me too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But anyway,
I think Min Seong and Hyeong Jun...]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I think he'll call Hyeong Jun.]
[Conveying his feelings after
spending an entire day with Hyeong Jun]
[Oh Min Seong: I was thinking about what to say.
30 seconds is really short.]
[What will Min Seong say to Hyeong Jun?]
[Oh Min Seong: So cold.]
[Min Seong is so excited that he's smiling]
Hello?
[Oh Min Seong: Hello.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hello.]
[Oh Min Seong: They say to
convey my feelings. So I called you.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Go ahead.]
[Oh Min Seong:
It's beyond interest. I like you.]
[Oh Min Seong: That's more accurate.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I see.]
[Oh Min Seong:
Is that all to your reaction?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I don't know.]
[Oh Min Seong: What do you mean—]
[30 seconds flew by]
[Oh Min Seong: After his first "hello,"]
[Oh Min Seong: he dropped his voice.]
[Oh Min Seong: That frustrated me a little.]
[Oh Min Seong: But anyway,
I had to convey my feelings.]
[Oh Min Seong: I've made up my mind
to be proactive.]
[Oh Min Seong: Actually,
these are things you just think about.]
[Oh Min Seong: But this time,
I decided to say what I was thinking.]
[Oh Min Seong:
I think that's why it's been working.]
[Oh Min Seong: I've been consistently
showing my affection to him.]
[Oh Min Seong:
Even if I tell him I like him now,]
[Oh Min Seong: I thought
he wouldn't find it strange.]
[Oh Min Seong: But there's the thing about]
[Oh Min Seong:
how he wouldn't be forthright with me.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm doing all this now,]
[Oh Min Seong: so why won't he
give me an answer?]
[Oh Min Seong: Why is he being so vague?]
[Oh Min Seong: Because I like him more?
I'm sure that's it.]
[How does Hyeong Jun feel about Min Seong?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Bye, I'll wait for you.]
[Kim Sun Wook,
please head to the Phone Room.]
OK.
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
"OK," huh?
[Who will Sun Wook convey his feelings to?]
[Who is Sun Wook drawn to today?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello?]
[Hello?]
[Kim Sun Wook: When we were bowling,
you looked cute when you smiled.]
[Who is Sun Wook
conveying his feelings to?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Thank you for
always enjoying the food I cook.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: See you later.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It was my first time
calling Hyun Jun,]
[Kim Sun Wook: so I was very nervous.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It was a time
for me to convey my affections.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I think I've
shown him even more that I like him.]
[Kim Sun Wook: He seemed happy]
[Kim Sun Wook: that I called him.]
[Hyun Jun's expression is different
from what Sun Wook expected]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I was quite conflicted.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I got his call
after I had a conversation with Yun Jae.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: So I was quite conflicted
when I answered his call then.]
[Who is the person in Hyun Jun's heart?]
[Kim Han Gyeol,
please head to the Phone Room.]
I'll be back.
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Han Gyeol's emotions have been
fluctuating left and right today]
[Who will Han Gyeol
convey his feelings to?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hello?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: It's me.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Thanks for the Melona ice cream.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It was good.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Let's have B.B.BIG next time.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Sure.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm getting shy.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: OK. Bye.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yeah, bye.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
We've talked a lot in Men's House,]
but we've never been on a date together.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Hyeok Jin's been frustrated about]
not getting to go on dates,]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
so I thought it was the right timing.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: In my current situation,
Hyeok Jin came in at the right time.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I hung up the call myself.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: After calling?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah, there was time left.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
You really rapped on the phone?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Are you Yoon Mirae?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I had 6 seconds left.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But for me,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
even if I had nothing else to say,]
I wouldn't have wanted to hang up.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: OMG.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is it too... What's wrong?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What's wrong?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is it a turn-off?
Am I too romantic?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is it too romantic?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yes, it was romantic.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Didn't expect this from me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah, totally.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
"Wouldn't want to hang up"...]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Don't you feel so?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: My head hurts.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Don't you get shy?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Isn't that what's exciting?]
[Kim Sun Wook: When I'm shy, I run away.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I know what you mean.
But I hit people when I'm shy.]
[Punch]
[Kim Sun Wook: You're not shy now.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I was happy (I got his call).]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: He's cuter than I thought.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
He started off with "It's me!"]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Even through the phone,
I could tell he was shy.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It felt like]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: when you have nothing
to say, but you don't want to hang up,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
so you two just keep laughing.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Something like that.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: What's wrong?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's so funny.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Seriously, don't tell anyone.]
[Taichi: Is it my turn?]
[Taichi,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Taichi: Who should I call?]
[Taichi heads toward
the Phone Room undecided]
[Cho Yun Jae: Taichi just went out.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I think he'll call you again.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: No way.]
[Cho Yun Jae: He doesn't know
if you've made your call yet.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Of course.]
[Cho Yun Jae: So he'll call you.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
I don't think he'll call me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Does it look like
Taichi likes someone else to you?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: No.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right? No one else.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Just wait for the call.]
[Cho Yun Jae: This is freaking funny.
Why am I so nervous?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: He won't call me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: He just left.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: He won't call.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Now.]
[Yun Jae's phone rings]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hello?]
[Taichi: Hello?]
[Cho Yun Jae: What's this?]
[Taichi: Well, we didn't talk much
after the first day, but after talking to you]
[Taichi: yesterday and today,]
[Taichi: I don't know
if it's romantic or not,]
[Taichi: but I want to talk to you more.]
[Taichi: That's what I feel right now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really? Thank you.
See you later.]
[Taichi: OK.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: See?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: But I didn't expect him
to call you.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Wow, what day is it today?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I just...]
[Cho Yun Jae: We are like comedians.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I know.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But I've only talked
about funny stuff with Taichi.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Did he call me
because I was funny?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Who knows?
He's quite quirky.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: But I was right.
He wouldn't call me.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hey! Why are you hiding?]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
What do you think of Taichi?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know about Taichi!]
[Cho Yun Jae: I told you he's like a kid.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I know.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What happened between
you two, that all this is happening?]
[Cho Yun Jae: You both had a change of heart.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
What kind of dates did you have?]
[Taichi: Why didn't you answer your phone?]
[Oh Min Seong: I heard
the phone ringing downstairs.]
[Oh Min Seong: Even if you called me,
I wouldn't have picked up.]
[Taichi: Oh, really?]
[Taichi: I wanted to call Min Seong.]
[Taichi: But I couldn't get past the fact
that he told me not to call him.]
[Taichi: I was also afraid that
it'd become awkward between us.]
[Taichi: Things are going well with
the one he's interested in.]
[Taichi: I wasn't confident
I could defeat him.]
[Taichi: I was quite confused.]
[Taichi: I also didn't feel as confident.]
[Taichi: Anyway,
I didn't get a call until then.]
[Oh Min Seong: Who did you call?]
[Taichi: It's a secret.]
[Oh Min Seong: I heard a phone ring
on the first floor.]
[Taichi: Hmm?]
[Oh Min Seong: A phone downstairs rang.]
[Taichi: You don't know who he is.]
[Oh Min Seong: I've got it.]
[Taichi: Did you get a call?]
[Oh Min Seong: Me?]
[Taichi: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: No, I didn't.]
[Oh Min Seong: I said I didn't get a call.]
[Taichi: Wait a little longer.
It's not over until it's over.]
[Oh Min Seong: I said I didn't get a call.]
[Taichi: I heard you!]
[Oh Min Seong: Why do you sound so fed up?]
[Taichi: There's still a chance,
so don't give up.]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't get a call.]
[Oh Min Seong: I thought I'd get his call.]
[Oh Min Seong: Or I'd storm to his room.]
[Oh Min Seong:
But it was a really long wait.]
[Oh Min Seong: "What if..."
I got a bit worried.]
He looks sturdy and good in this photo.
[Staring]
[Hyeong Jun is just staring at his phone]
To be exact, it's when he grabbed his knees.
Oh, yeah?
[He finally gets the text]
[Lee Hyeong Jun,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[A day with Min Seong
that washed away his pain]
[Will Hyeong Jun
convey his feelings to Min Seong?]
[Taichi: See? I told you.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hello?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hello.]
[Oh Min Seong: Who are you?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hmm...]
[Oh Min Seong: 30 seconds is short.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You're the only one
I could call, so I called you.]
[Oh Min Seong: What was that?]
[Oh Min Seong: You sound so uncool.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Wait, I think
I called the wrong person.]
[Oh Min Seong: What?]
[Oh Min Seong:
Please convey your feelings.]
[Oh Min Seong: It was cut off.]
[Taichi: I told you you'd get a call.]
[Oh Min Seong: 30 seconds is too short.]
[Oh Min Seong: I had mixed feelings.]
[Oh Min Seong: "You were the only one
I could call" can mean]
[Oh Min Seong: he had no other options,
or that he only has feelings for me.]
[Oh Min Seong: Why's he being like that?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: If I don't joke around,
he'll go even further with the jokes.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
So I beat him to the punch.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: He must be
really comfortable with me now,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: because he was
not serious at all during the call.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It made me speechless.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I thought,
"What should I do with him?"]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Sigh, I'm really tired.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
I'm sleepy, and my back hurts.]
[Sun Wook looks exhausted too]
[Kim Sun Wook: I was slowly getting angry.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
More than anger, I got anxious.]
Even if he's interested in me,]
[Kim Sun Wook:
feelings can change anytime.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's not weird
for feelings to change at this time too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I started worrying
and having doubts.]
[Lee Hyun Jun,
please head to the Phone Room.]
[Within 30 seconds, convey your feelings
to the man you are drawn to today.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Has Hyun Jun called yet?]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
You should pray for this now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm sure he won't call me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: We talked today.]
[Cho Yun Jae: He said he's 70%
leaning toward Sun Wook.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
So he'll call Sun Wook today.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
But he might call you too. 30%.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
But I don't want to have false hope.]
I'd just end up getting hurt.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I feel better
thinking he won't call me.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
But I'll try to change his mind today.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I asked him out
on a walk tonight, if there's time.]
[His heavy steps
mirror his heavy heart]
[Who will Hyun Jun convey his feelings to?]
[Between Sun Wook and Yun Jae,
who will Hyun Jun choose?]
[Hello?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hello?]
[Yes.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yes?]
[Sun Wook gets shy
after getting Hyun Jun's call]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It'd have been better
if we got to hang out alone today.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: But it was still fun.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.
We can hang out together next time.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I enjoyed the food too.
Thank you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: OK. See you later.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: See you later.]
OK.
[Sun Wook regains his smile]
[Kim Sun Wook:
He's not the type to say all that.]
So he must've given it much thought.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That was
very thoughtful of him.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I know he means no harm,
but he habitually gives very short responses.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Having to
initiate the convo in the call,]
[Kim Sun Wook: it must've taken him
much thought and courage.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought
it was very thoughtful.]
[Kim Sun Wook: And I was very happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: He's the person
I like the most right now.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: So I called him.]
[The call time is over]
[Taichi didn't get a single call]
[And another person...]
[Su Min, who's been waiting endlessly
for his call]
[Kim Su Min: I didn't get his call.]
[Kim Su Min: I didn't expect much,]
[Kim Su Min: but I can't help feeling sad.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Taichi.]
[Taichi: Hmm?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Come here.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I have something to ask you.]
What is it?
[Cho Yun Jae: You chose me on the first day.
Then you never chose me again.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What's the reason?]
[Taichi: I tend to get interested in people]
[Taichi: who I feel relaxed with
and have fun with, regardless of looks.]
[Taichi: On the first day, to be honest,]
[Taichi: we were both nervous,]
[Taichi: and I didn't see you feel relaxed.]
[Taichi: So I felt uneasy too.]
[Taichi: Compared to the first day,]
[Taichi: it's much more fun
to talk to you.]
[Taichi: Should I say
we share the same sense of humor?]
[Taichi: So I've been a bit...]
[Taichi: Like I said on the phone,]
[Taichi: I'm still not sure
if it's romantic.]
[Taichi: Right now, I'm unable to]
[Taichi: say I like you with conviction.]
[Taichi: And for you, on the receiving end,]
[Taichi: it's hard for you to accept]
[Taichi: that I'm sincere right away,]
[Taichi: since we've been
a lot like buddies so far.]
[Cho Yun Jae: To be honest,
I like that I'm relaxed around you, but...]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know if it's romantic
or just because it's fun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: To be honest, on the first day,
when I went on a date with you,]
[Cho Yun Jae: I was grateful
that you chose me,]
[Cho Yun Jae: so I was quite fond of you.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But after the date,]
[Cho Yun Jae: I felt like
you weren't interested in me anymore.]
[Cho Yun Jae: So I saw you as a friend,
but you called me today.]
[Cho Yun Jae: To be honest, I was happy.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But anyway, we already]
[Cho Yun Jae: know a lot about each other.]
[Taichi: That's right.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Like how
I've been interested in Hyun Jun,]
[Cho Yun Jae: and...
Since Han Gyeol and I are roommates,]
[Cho Yun Jae: I know that
you two were a thing.]
Yeah.
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know what to think.]
[Taichi: Me too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: So I wanted to talk to you.]
[Taichi: Today...]
[Taichi: In this brief time, I was quite
surprised by our similar sense of humor]
[Taichi: and how fun it was
to hang out with you.]
[Taichi: It's rare for me to feel this way.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Taichi: I'm...]
[Taichi: I'm more picky than you'd think.]
[Taichi:
I don't get along with people easily.]
[Taichi: It takes me a long time
to feel close to others.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Me too.]
[Taichi: But it was different for us. So...]
[Taichi: This could be
a kind of attraction.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Taichi: But... So...]
[Taichi: The person
I want to talk with now is you.]
[Taichi: I think we can have a good chat,]
[Taichi: so I thought
it's right to choose you.]
[Taichi: Right now, to be really honest,]
[Taichi: since you came to me,]
[Taichi: I must tell you I'm not sure.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right?]
[Taichi: I'm used to
having a crush on others.]
[Taichi: If I like someone,]
[Taichi: I'll keep liking the same person.]
[Taichi: That's how it's been.]
[Taichi: But on this shoot,
I've yet to feel]
[Taichi: that kind of
intense attraction so far.]
[Taichi: Anyway, right now I'm just]
[Taichi: amazed that we got close so fast.]
[Taichi: You seem interesting,
and fun to hang out with.]
[Taichi: If I had someone I liked,
I wouldn't have]
[Taichi: read into these feelings.]
[Taichi: Because when I liked someone,]
[Taichi: I've always only been
focused on that one person.]
[Taichi: I can't say I'm certain right now.]
[Taichi: I'm sorry about that.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's OK.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But it's great
that you're honest with me.]
[Taichi: I should be honest.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I've been honest too, ya know?]
[Taichi: "Ya know"?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Ya know.]
[Taichi: Me too, ya know?]
[Will Yun Jae's feelings change?]
[Who set your heart ablaze today?
Record it in your Love Diary.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is the thought of
writing your Love Diary getting you excited?]
[Hahaha.]
Oh my goodness...
[Staring]
What?
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What?]
[Sun Wook is
looking through his past entries]
[Kim Sun Wook: Wow, from the first day,
I've only written about Hyun Jun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's been the same for me.]
[My heart is: Sunny
Most drawn to: Lee Hyun Jun (❤️⁠x6½)]
[Kim Sun Wook: All I've written is Hyun Jun.]
["I'm happy I got to talk a lot with Hyun Jun.
I got a call from him for the first time.
Feels like a dream!"]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah, just about Lee Hyun Jun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My heart was partly cloudy.]
["After I missed the chance yesterday,
I got prepared first thing in the morning.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I was a bit relieved,
and it was a therapeutic day too.]
[But I couldn't go on a date again. And it
had to be Taichi, who chose Han Gyeol.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I was a bit comforted,]
[What's wrong with me? I was so sad that I
cried in front of Han Gyeol. I felt energized
by the group date, my first time out of the dorm!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: so I feel refreshed.]
[Most drawn to: Kim Han Gyeol (❤️⁠x6½)]
[Hyeok Jin's Mind = bowling was super fun
+ must have a date tomorrow + first time
getting his call; sincerity wins hearts?
+ Am I warm? + craving Melona]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Bowling was fun]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: and I felt better.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Han Gyeol said I'm
now his priority. Persistence paid off.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My no. 1 is Han Gyeol.
No one's my least favorite.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm happy today,
so everything seems beautiful.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: The date was fun,
but it was a busy day,]
[Most drawn to: Min Seong (❤️⁠x4)
Least drawn to: Han Gyeol (x1)]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: so I'm tired and sleepy.]
[My heart is: Rainy
"Glad I decided to go out today!"]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I just want to go to bed.]
[Oh Min Seong: December 7.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hyeong Jun chose me for a date.]
[My heart is: Sunny
Most drawn to: Hyeong Jun (❤️⁠x7)]
[Min Seong's Mind = photos
+ couple items + date + Hyeong Jun
+ Hyeong Jun + Hyeong Jun]
[Oh Min Seong: Because of what I saw yesterday,]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't think I'd enjoy the date.]
[Oh Min Seong: but I was no longer angry
once the date started.]
[Oh Min Seong: But I didn't want any
misunderstanding, so we had a honest talk.]
[Anyway, I just like Hyeong Jun.]
[Taichi: My heart was rainy today.]
[Most drawn to: Yun Jae (❤️⁠x3)
"Went to Sokcho Beach by car. I was troubled
when I got the chance to choose my date.]
[Taichi: It was a confusing day.]
[The fact that I was troubled clarified how I feel,
so I was determined to tell Han Gyeol, who's
been showing interest in me, how I really feel.
Looking at the sea, I think I was honest."]
[Taichi: But I have no regrets.]
[Taichi: At a nice place, I could]
[Taichi: convey my feelings properly.]
[Taichi: I could seriously talk to him 1-on-1.]
[Taichi's Mind = Unsure if it's romantic,
but I want to talk more with Yun Jae,
since it's fun to hang out with him]
[Taichi: It was the best way to handle it.]
[Taichi's Mind = scallops + beautiful sea
+ cigarette… + feeling guilty]
[Taichi: The sea was beautiful too.
That was the most memorable.]
[My heart is: Partly Cloudy
Most drawn to: Kim Sun Wook (❤️⁠x5)
Hyun Jun's Mind = Sun Wook + bowling + Yun Jae?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The group date was]
[Lee Hyun Jun: the most memorable.]
["The group bowling date was fun.
I feel relieved after having an honest
conversation with Yun Jae."]
[Lee Hyun Jun: We had fun together]
[Lee Hyun Jun: and relieved stress.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Whenever I bowled,]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
Sun Wook kept meeting my eyes.]
He also reacted to what I said and did.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I grew fonder of Sun Wook.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
As for Yun Jae, I'm not sure.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I had an honest talk with Hyun Jun.]
[Most drawn to: Hyun Jun (❤️⁠x6)]
[Cho Yun Jae: so I feel relieved and happier.]
["I felt better after having an honest
conversation with Hyun Jun."]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I felt relieved, and I should]
[My heart is: Sunny
"I felt a weight lifted off my shoulders after
talking to Taichi. It's like I knew how it'd end.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: talk more with Hyeok Jin]
[Now I'm thinking about Hyeok Jin, who's
been proactively showing me affection.]
[I'm thankful to Ichi too. If it were me,
I might not have been as honest
as he was. I got closure."]
[Kim Han Gyeol: and go on dates.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: A new beginning.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: My no. 1 is Hyeok Jin.]
[And Su Min who honestly
expressed his feelings to Sun Wook]
[My heart is: Sunny
Most drawn to: Sun Wook (❤️⁠x4)]
["I was feeling down the whole day, but when
I saw him happy, I became happy too, hehe."]
[Su Min's Mind = conversations]
[Sunny to some, cloudy to others;
what will tomorrow bring?]
[It's now the fifth day in Men's House]
[Who is the first to welcome the morning?]
[Hyeok Jin,
the diligent one with no exception]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If I can't go out, I'll riot.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If I can't get
one 1-on-1 date in five days,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: am I not a total idiot?]
[Focused on blowing his hair for the date]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Sir, I have a request.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What is it?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want my hair to
go this way, but my hair won't listen.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Let me help you.
It's not hard at all.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's not hard?]
[Kim Sun Wook: If your hair's parted like this,
just blow on both sides to give it volume.]
Right, yes.
[Kim Sun Wook: Do this, gather them,
blow on it, and then let go.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Nice.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Thank you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Are you ready?
Are you ready?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Whose song is that?]
[Kim Sun Wook: IZ*ONE.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Instant answer.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Of course.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
Rollin', rollin', rollin', yeah!]
[Kim Sun Wook: When I see you,
shake it, shake it, shake it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I want to dance.
I want to dance.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You've become
someone who wants to dance.]
[Thinking carefully]
[Careful deliberation]
[Can the man who can't go on a date
finally have his first date?]
[Gets up]
[Hyun Jun is the first
in Block A to get ready]
[What's next?]
[Wake up the guys on the second floor
who are still sleeping]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Time to get up.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You're late.
It's already 10 AM.]
[Oh Min Seong: Ah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Blinding lights.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Sunshine.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Get up. Go wash up.]
[Hyun Jun is heading to Block B]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hi.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hello.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You're here early.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Did you sleep well?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I practically fainted.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why are you so cute?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I didn't want to wear this.]
[Kim Sun Wook: The hoodie suits you.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Your hoodie is so cute.
You look like someone who's in love.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: So many hearts today.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Oh, you're right.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I don't usually]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: plan what I wear,
or what accessories I wear.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I stood for 3 minutes
in front of the pink hoodie,]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
contemplating if I should wear it.]
[Last night]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I've never worn this,
nor this, nor this. You know the vibe, right?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Wear this and this.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I told him to wear
his pink hoodie and white pants.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Since I was wearing
pink pants and a white sweater.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But he didn't wear it.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You can't wear it?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Why?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Don't know. I've never worn pink.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But it's his style.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: He needs to wear
what he wants. I can't force him.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Will you go out today?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I hope I can.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yeah.]
[Another guy in pink, Su Min, is ready too]
[A day date and a night date awaits you.
Choose a guy you've never dated,
and a guy you're most interested in.]
[Kim Su Min: Sun Wook was my first choice.
Because we haven't had a date yet.]
[Kim Su Min:
I really want to go out with him.]
[A day date and a night date awaits you.
Choose a guy you've never dated,
and a guy you're most interested in.]
You didn't get the text?
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If it's not mutual,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I wouldn't be able to go out.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I got slightly worried.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
But I've talked with Han Gyeol,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: and he said
he wanted to go on a date with me.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
So I just trusted that he'd pick me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: We've never dated,
so I don't know what he's like,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: and what he thinks.
I was curious about his true feelings.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I chose a friend
I'm comfortable with for the day date.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
I chose Min Seong for the night date.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
I didn't need to think about it.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Among those
who haven't went on a date,]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I was curious about him.]
[Cho Yun Jae: For the day date,
I chose Hyun Jun, who I haven't dated]
[Cho Yun Jae: and want to date.]
[Cho Yun Jae: So I chose Hyun Jun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: For the night date,
I chose Taichi, who I'm still]
[Cho Yun Jae: unsure about.]
[Taichi: I wanted to express my gratitude.]
[Taichi: I wanted to go out with him]
[Taichi: and express it.]
[Oh Min Seong: It was easy
to choose a date for the night.]
[Oh Min Seong: I had to think about
who to pick for the day date.]
[Will their dream dates come true?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Come here.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hmm?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's too quiet there.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What did you say?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's so quiet.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What's wrong?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What's wrong?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What's with that look?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No reason.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Who did you choose?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Huh?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Did you choose me and Hyun Jun?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: No, why?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: He said it so firmly.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What about you?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's a secret.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Who did you choose?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I chose you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: And the other person?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I chose Su Min.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But it needs to be mutual.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's true.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: So?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I chose Sun Wook.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Other than him.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yun Jae.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yun Jae...]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
You like the cute type, huh?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Is that so?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Have a good chat with him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You must dislike me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: No, you two stay here.
Why are you doing this to me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Who'd you choose?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Who else could it be?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hyun Jun.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hyun Jun chose you too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I know.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But that's not the point.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Steal him! Steal him!]
[Cho Yun Jae: How? I can't do it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: That's not who I am.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: No, you can do it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I can't do it.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You can do it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've lost my courage.]
[Oh Min Seong: You haven't even tried.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah, that's not good.]
[Cho Yun Jae: We talked yesterday.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: About what?]
[Oh Min Seong: That you like him?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, but I'm sure he
already knew anyway. He's observant.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Don't think about it
as stealing. He chose you too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But he won't choose me in the end.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Who knows? Give it a try.]
[Cho Yun Jae: From the 2nd day, Sun Wook
and Little Hyeok Jin have been proactive.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I wasn't aware.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Anyway, he said he's
70 to 80% leaning toward Sun Wook.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
80% means it's missing 20%.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Easier said than done.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What about Sun Wook?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What about him?]
[Cho Yun Jae: About Hyun Jun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm sorry to Sun Wook too.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why are you sorry?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Of course I'm sorry.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Since we've gotten close.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I can't help but
think about such stuff.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Anyway, Hyun Jun
is the one who will make the choice.]
[Oh Min Seong: Do as you deem fit.
You'll be fine.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You can do it.]
[Will the day and night dates
alter their affections?]
[An outdoor sauna enjoyed in winter]
[Which couple will enjoy this unique date?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Wow, amazing.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: There's water.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's fascinating.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Looks warm.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's like a scene in a movie.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The water's heated up.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I think it's like this in Japan.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's transparent.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: There's a scent. Or not?]
[Cho Yun Jae: No, I smell it too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It looks warm.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do you like saunas?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yes, I do.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I feel like it relieves fatigue.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Let's get changed.]
[Cho Yun Jae: OK.]
[What will unfold in this special place?]
It's fascinating.
It's cold.
[Cho Yun Jae: Where should we leave this?
Can we drink in the tub?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah, they said we can.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I've never had a date like this.
And it was with someone I've never dated.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
It was a novel date, so I liked it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Oh!]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's a bit hot.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's really hot.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Are you OK?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, I'm fine.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm hot.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You're hot?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's hot.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's warm for me. Just nice.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: When was the last time
you had a sauna?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Sauna? It's been a long time.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really long. Years ago.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That long?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I had a sauna sometime last year.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Where did you go?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: In my neighborhood.]
[Cho Yun Jae: A sauna in the neighborhood.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I've never been
to an outdoor sauna.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Me too. It feels like Japan, right?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: How do you feel being out here?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How I feel? It's fun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I need to stand up.]
Oh, lean like this?
Sit there.
[Cho Yun Jae: You must work out a lot.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Work out?
I just do simple stuff.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
I used to go 5 or 6 days a week.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Now I'm lazy and go 4 days.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I've been lazy.]
[Cho Yun Jae: The weather's too good.
I'm so hot.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Wipe with the towel.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, I should.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do you need it?]
[Ha...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How do you feel
being out on a date?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's nice, but first of all...]
[I'm happy because I'm with you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What did you want to do?
Bungee jumping? You kept mentioning it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I want to do extreme sports.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: There are
other things besides bungee jumping.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've tried most of the scary stuff.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What have you tried?]
[Cho Yun Jae: There are many scary
theme park rides in Southeast Asia.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've tried them all.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
So you've been to Gyeongju World too?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've been there.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But I don't think
the rides in Korea are scary.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Gyeongju World rides are scary.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Rides abroad, there are]
[Cho Yun Jae: like roller coasters
that go backwards.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I saw it on YouTube.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Keeps going backwards. It was fun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I went with a friend,
and they threw up after.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It makes you really dizzy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Did you try it too?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I did, but I was OK.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Really? I'm curious.
I want to try it too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's getting cold.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do you travel a lot?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I like traveling.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Really?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I actually like active stuff.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
I don't think you're an introvert.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Interpersonal relationships
and being active are different.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I feel uncomfortable and shy
when there are many people around.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But...
I think they're different.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I get too lazy to travel.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's nice once you get there,
but the process is troublesome.]
Right?
[Cho Yun Jae: Booking tickets and hotels.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: And there's also waiting in line]
[Lee Hyun Jun: at the airport and stuff.]
[Cho Yun Jae: That's troublesome.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The line is too long.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: At the immigration counter.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do you talk a lot with friends?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm quiet when with friends too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right? You seem quiet.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I just listen
and speak from time to time.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I've always been quiet.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No, I changed.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You did?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: When I was little,]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
I talked a lot in elementary school.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I changed after puberty.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I see.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: They say
I suddenly became quiet.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I stopped talking after that.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's troublesome.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Or should I say
I just don't like speaking unnecessarily?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Oh.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I guess
I thought it was better to]
[Lee Hyun Jun: talk only when necessary.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Did you say
you've never been in a relationship?]
[Cho Yun Jae: No, just not many.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How many times?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Twice after turning 20.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Twice? How long were they?]
[Cho Yun Jae: One was around 6 months,]
[Cho Yun Jae: and the other was long-term.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I met him for a few years.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I think it's a reason
I don't date much.]
[Cho Yun Jae: After dating someone long-term.
What about you?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Twice too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: After 20?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah, I've never
been in a relationship before 20.]
[Cho Yun Jae: None before 20?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: My first time was
after coming to Seoul.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What kind of relationship
do you want?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Where we're like friends.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Like friends?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Relaxed but nice.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I see.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What about you?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Same for me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: When we're together,
I'd like to feel like I'm having fun.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I see. Fun.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Actually, I...
I also like the quiet vibe too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: The silence when we don't talk.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You get me?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Being comfortable with each other?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yes, when
we're comfortable even in silence.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I think I get it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Oops, sorry.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Was that a challenge?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'll win if we fight.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You're right.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Every time you move,
this wobbles too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Nah, not to that extent.]
[Cho Yun Jae: No, it is.]
[A conversation that is
slightly smooth and slightly choppy]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Want to go into the sauna?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, let's go in.]
[Cho Yun Jae: How do you make this again?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: A towel sheep head?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right, I remember now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But it might not look good.
Do you want to try it on?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No, I'm good.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Try it. Just try it.]
-Try it. -I'm good.
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't really like sheep.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why not?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Sheep?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why? Sheep are cute.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
They are, but I prefer goats.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why do you like goats more?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Goats are cuter.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really?]
[Cho Yun Jae: This is...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Try it on.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You try it on.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't want to.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Try it on.]
Here.
[Cho Yun Jae: Is this how you wear it?
It doesn't fit.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
You probably made it too tight.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You look like a sheep.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do I?
Don't you dislike sheep?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: But you look like a sheep.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do I?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Didn't you say
sheep aren't cute? That you prefer goats?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I did.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: With the towel on,
you look like a sheep.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It suits you.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It looks nice from here.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The scenery?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I liked it from the outside too.
Since the weather's great today.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I find it
more beautiful looking out from here.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Like it's being framed.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I see,
framed by the window.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It feels like Finland.]
[Cho Yun Jae: R-R-Really.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Though I've never been there.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It feels like I'm abroad.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do you want to go?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Finland?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Why?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's a long flight.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Can't stand long-distance flights?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Regular seats
are too narrow for me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right, they should be.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Even flights
to Jeju Island or Japan are tough.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I can't sit for too long too,]
[Cho Yun Jae: so I go to
the bathroom area to stretch.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
Stretch a little and come back.]
I usually do that.
[Lee Hyun Jun: But I can't keep doing that.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I keep doing it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's why
I don't like going abroad.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't like plane rides.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The whole process is
inconvenient and troublesome.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, packing luggage too.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
But it's exciting too. For me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Packing luggage?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I find it troublesome.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Oh, really?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Although we
talked more than usual,]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I don't think our conversation]
[Cho Yun Jae: flowed well.]
[Cho Yun Jae: The romantic excitement
I felt at the start]
[Cho Yun Jae: has been decreasing.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
On my first date with Yun Jae,]
the conversational flow wasn't bad,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: but I can't say]
[Lee Hyun Jun: it was smooth either.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I strongly felt
that we'd be better as buddies]
[Lee Hyun Jun: than romantic partners.]
[Are they losing interest
in each other for good?]
[The sun shines brightly by the river]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The weather is so nice.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I like walking, so I've
always wanted to come to places like these.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yeah, you said that
in the first meeting.]
Yes.
[Kim Han Gyeol: For the person
who I've never dated before,]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I chose Eum Hyeok Jin.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I chose Han Gyeol,
who I've been wanting to go on a date with.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I was really excited
to be alone with him.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: How do you feel on your
first date? Your first time leaving the dorm.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm excited
because it's my first date,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: and also
because it's with you.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Let's lean here for a while.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: To be honest,
I'd been feeling really down.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I wanted to go out with you,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but the timing was never right.
Like I wasn't granted a chance.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It felt like
I just kept missing out on everything,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: so I was really stressed out.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But yesterday, you said
you wanted to go on a date with me.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: So I'm grateful.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Now that
I'm out on the date, I feel good.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm glad you're happy.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Are you satisfied
coming out with me?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yes, I'm happy.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Your hands must be cold.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Thank you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Honestly, you're the only one
I want to go on a date with.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
That's why I'm so happy today.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I kept saying
I wanted to go on a date and take a walk,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but I could never do it.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm doing everything
I wanted to do today, all at once.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: So I'm really happy.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Whatever. I'm shy.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: That's good.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm not good at saying such stuff.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The frustration of feeling like
I was cursed has all been released instantly.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: That's great.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
All washed away by the river.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Though we talked a lot in
Men's House, it's the first time being outside.]
That's right.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Anyway, it's different
chatting alone in the dorm]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
and chatting outside like this.]
I wanted to talk to you like this.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
I also think I know you better now.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: How do you feel,
now that you know me better?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Gosh, I don't know!]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm very grateful to you.
You've been doing so much to woo me.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But you didn't know at first.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah, I didn't.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I had to tell you directly!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You know
how hard it was for me?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I was so shy.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm a little slow.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yeah.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Want me to take your photos?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: OK.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I brought a Polaroid camera.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
And I'll take photos of you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: 1, 2, 3.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It was really fun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
I can look him in the eyes now.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: His eyes are very pretty.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
The date itinerary was nice.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: After spending time
together outside, I think we have]
[Kim Han Gyeol: different dating styles.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: On the date,
I think he was too deliberate.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
That style doesn't really suit me.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Especially outside.]
[After a walk, they move on
to the next dating activity]
[A tarot date to get to know each other
through tarot divination]
[What fate awaits them?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm so excited.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm nervous.]
-Nervous, right? -Yes.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's my first time.]
[Nervous]
[Heart thumping]
First, I'll shuffle the cards properly.
[This is the basic card formation.
Starting from here.]
[It's a Queen.]
Kingdom.
[Han Gyeol got many King cards]
It's a King.
It's a bit…
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's all similar.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Interesting.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: What do you think you'll get?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I don't know. I'm nervous.]
[Many of Hyeok Jin's cards
feature people and the sun]
I got a lot of people.
Seems different from mine.
And a lot with the sun.
[Hyeok Jin's cards] [Han Gyeol's cards]
[This is the basic card formation.]
[The cards here represent who you are.]
This is about love.
[Love Card]
[Fortune Card]
This is about money.
[Unlike Han Gyeol's,
I'll start with Hyeok Jin's.]
[There are a lot of people.
And a lot of sunshine.]
Yes.
[You have many people around you.]
[But his is
completely different from yours.]
[Rather than people,]
[there's a lonely queen with a long face.]
[You may be fine normally.]
[But when provoked or enraged,
you might become]
[quite tough.]
[Kim Han Gyeol:
Don't you think it's interesting?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: You have a lot of people,
but mine are all alone.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yeah.]
[It actually ended up being
divided into two categories.]
-It's really fascinating. -So fascinating.
[Fascinating]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You'd think it'd be a mix.]
[As for love, you got The Hierophant card.]
[He's preaching to the people below.]
[With love, you're quite tolerant.]
[But you could be a bit
bossy and old-fashioned.]
["Hey, listen to me!"]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Bossy and old-fashioned?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: No.]
[You tend to tell your partner
to listen to you, that you're right.]
[But you are also very benevolent.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Interesting.]
[You've got The Lovers card, representing
your love life in the next 3 years.]
[You might meet someone you get along with
and get into a relationship.]
[Your dating style is
completely different from his.]
[Unlike yours, he got a King card.]
[He's in a confrontation,]
[while you're proactively seeking love.]
[The person you like will appear.
You'll be surrounded by people.]
[With this card, there's praying.]
Right?
[And angels appear with fanfare
as you wished.]
[You are the one praying.]
[Please let me date someone like him.
You're praying like this.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Mine was the total opposite of his.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hmm...
I don't think the results were ideal.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Just through the tarot reading,
I could see that we're totally different.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Then...]
Yes.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If we were to date...]
[Oh, you two?]
Yes.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to know
how things will turn out for us.]
[Will things go well if you date?]
Yes.
OK.
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm curious. Since the type
of our tarot cards are totally different.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I know, right?]
[Brainiac, if they get into a relationship,
will it go well?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Brainiac,
please give us good cards.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: What will it be?]
[One card...
Wow, it's The Hierophant card!]
[This is a King card.]
[Rather than
getting into a relationship right away,]
[it's better to
coordinate your thoughts first.]
[For a relationship to go well,
you'll need a lot of time.]
[Slowly adjust to each other.]
[If you let nature take its course,]
[things can develop smoothly
between you two.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Don't be impatient.]
[Don't rush into it.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: What Brainiac said
sounds plausible.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I thought
we weren't compatible.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: If we want to date,
we need a lot of time to adjust to each other.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I think
that made sense to me.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Personality-wise too.
Although he's older than me,]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I didn't get that vibe
when we were on the date.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I felt a little pressured.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: We asked about whether
we could be in a relationship,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: and how we should
navigate things as a couple,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but the result wasn't good.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Of course,
it was just for fun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But the reading was
that we weren't compatible,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: so I was disappointed.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: There's still time left
for us here. Why did we get those cards?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I can't help but]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: overthink things.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If our conversations
don't flow well,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: or maybe
when we face some friction,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I think I'll be
reminded of this tarot reading.]
[How will Hyeok Jin and Han Gyeol's fate
pan out?]