[After the date with Taichi]
[Who is Min Seong waiting anxiously for?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hello.]
[Oh Min Seong: You're here.]
[Oh Min Seong: What did you do before this?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I just had a chat at home.]
[Oh Min Seong: With whom?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: With everyone.]
[Oh Min Seong: I see.]
[Oh Min Seong: He had his bangs pulled back.
I thought it really suits him.]
[Oh Min Seong: With his eyebrows showing,]
[Oh Min Seong: he looks more manly
than his usual cute image.]
[Oh Min Seong: It really suits him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I look very different
when I pull back my bangs.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I wanted to
show him a different image.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Min Seong said
he likes black the most,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: so after only wearing
bright colors, I dressed in black for the date.]
[Oh Min Seong:
This date is only for 30 minutes.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's short.]
[Hehe]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why are you smiling?]
[Oh Min Seong: This hairstyle suits you.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Really?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Are you still feeling unwell?]
[Oh Min Seong: It hurts so much. I'm dying.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
And you're having a cold drink?]
[Oh Min Seong: Are you worried about me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I don't want to be infected.]
[Oh Min Seong: You always say uncool things.
Just say you're worried about me.]
[Oh Min Seong: This is the last date
before we make our final choice.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's our last date.
So we should talk.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Wow, it ends tomorrow.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm just curious.]
[Oh Min Seong: The way you think about me...]
[Is it just for this show,
or will it extend beyond the show?]
[Oh Min Seong: I want to talk about this.]
[Oh Min Seong: You don't want to answer?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: No, that's not it.]
[Oh Min Seong: I came into this show]
[Oh Min Seong: hoping for a relationship]
[Oh Min Seong: that goes beyond the show.]
[Oh Min Seong: Coming on this show,
I made my choices based on whether]
[Oh Min Seong: we could
continue dating after the show.]
[Oh Min Seong: So of course I chose someone
whom I want to continue seeing after the show.]
[Oh Min Seong: If we are fond of each other,]
[Oh Min Seong: I think
we can become a real couple.]
[It's fate after all.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm not good
at expressing myself in words,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: but I always chose you.
I called you too.]
[Oh Min Seong: And?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm shy.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Anyway, if we become a couple,
the relationship will be public.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I was
worried about those things.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But I don't want to
worry about those things anymore.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I did miss you today.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Today?]
[Oh Min Seong: It's your first time missing me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Well...]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I don't know.]
[Oh Min Seong: So cold.
A cold and shrewd Seoulite.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I've never been
good at expressing myself. I was shy too.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I tried my best, though
it was indirect. I hope he saw my efforts.]
[Oh Min Seong: It was cute. I liked it.]
[Oh Min Seong: He's unfathomable.
Can't figure him out.]
[Oh Min Seong: But he also knows how
to be cutesy and affectionate. It's cute.]
[Oh Min Seong: So how should I interpret this?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What do you mean?]
[Oh Min Seong: How should I interpret this?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Do I have to spell it out?]
[Oh Min Seong: I have no idea.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You don't?]
[Oh Min Seong: You always have a poker face,]
[Oh Min Seong: and you never say much.]
[Oh Min Seong: Although I'm a shy person,]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm like a clown in front of you.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I put in a lot of effort too.]
[Oh Min Seong: I know.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I gave you the heart.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's cute.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's cute, right?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I have one too.]
[Oh Min Seong: You're wearing it.]
[Oh Min Seong:
I have both the star and the heart.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I wanted to
give it to you at the end,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: but you said you were
going on a date with another person.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: So I got anxious.]
[Oh Min Seong: That's why I'm wearing it.
So everyone can see it.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun:
I kept mine hidden, though.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It made me so happy.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I was really happy that
he wore the keychain I gave him right away.]
[Oh Min Seong: I like it.]
[Oh Min Seong: In the morning, when I
told him I was gonna go on another date,]
[Oh Min Seong: he gave me this.
That's cute of him too.]
[Oh Min Seong: Why are you so quiet?]
[Oh Min Seong: I like you
even if you don't say anything.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm always quiet.
Didn't you know?]
[Oh Min Seong: No, I knew.]
[Oh Min Seong: But I still like you.]
[Oh Min Seong: What'd it be like
seeing each other after this show?]
[Oh Min Seong: I can't really imagine it.]
[Oh Min Seong: On this show,
we're in a setting away from real life.]
[Oh Min Seong: When we go back
to our daily lives and see each other...]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Wouldn't it be similar
to the date we had in Seoul?]
[Oh Min Seong: I really enjoyed that date.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It was very comfortable.]
[Oh Min Seong: I had a great time.]
[Their Seoul date that was
blended into everyday living]
[Moving forward, will they
be able to share their daily lives?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Pour it for me.]
[Oh Min Seong: Don't you have hands?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I like it
when people pour it for me.]
[Oh Min Seong: What about me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hmm? Yours is full.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm asking if you like me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You're not bad.]
[Oh Min Seong: For goodness' sake!]
[Oh Min Seong: Say if you like me or not.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I like you.]
[Oh Min Seong: You're really
bad at expressing yourself.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah I'm bad at it.]
[Oh Min Seong: You're really bad at it.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'll accommodate it.
That's how you are, right?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah, OK.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm happy to be with you.
That's all I need.]
[Oh Min Seong: I feel relieved.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why?]
[Oh Min Seong: I just feel relieved.]
[My worries have been resolved.]
[Before they knew it, their feelings
for each other have gotten stronger]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm leaving.]
[Oh Min Seong: Bye. See you at home.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Though it's a pity
the date was really short,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm glad we could completely
clarify how we feel about each other.]
[Oh Min Seong: When I first came here,
the first person I met]
[Oh Min Seong: was Hyeong Jun.
From then on,]
[Oh Min Seong: we spent every day together.]
[Oh Min Seong: So, from then to now,
everyday with him felt like destiny.]
[Love that came like destiny,
may it be forever]
[Waiting for his next date]
[Who is Su Min waiting for?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello.]
[Kim Su Min: Hi.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hi.]
[Kim Su Min: We meet often.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I know.]
[Kim Su Min: Our eyes met
when he walked in. He was all smiles,]
[Kim Su Min: waving the camera at me.]
[Kim Su Min: So he knew it was me
and brought it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I expected to see him.
So I was relaxed when I went on the date.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought it was
the last time we could talk alone]
[Kim Sun Wook: on this show,]
[Kim Sun Wook: so I went on the date
without any worries.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's good to see you often.]
[Kim Su Min: It's good?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
[Kim Su Min: That's good.
Did you take a lot of photos?]
[Kim Sun Wook: No,
I haven't taken any since then.]
[Kim Su Min: What a pity.]
[Kim Su Min: It's the last day.]
[Kim Sun Wook: We're having
the last date together on the last day.]
[Kim Su Min: Did you go on a date just now?]
[Kim Sun Wook: No, no.]
[Kim Su Min: No?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: This is my first date today.]
[Kim Su Min: It's my honor.]
[Kim Sun Wook: No, no.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's nice to
have a peaceful date like this.]
[Kim Su Min: You're right.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
Such a date has its advantages too.]
[Kim Su Min: How was the week?]
[Kim Sun Wook: The week?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I really enjoyed it.]
During the last shoot,]
[Kim Sun Wook: it was
getting to know strangers.]
[Kim Sun Wook: This time, I got to
know everyone on a deeper level.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I enjoyed it more.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What about you?]
[Kim Su Min: I've been... ah,
feeling all sorts of emotions.]
[Kim Su Min: Right now too.]
[Kim Su Min: I realized I'm really bad at]
[Kim Su Min: expressing myself
to the one I like.]
[Kim Sun Wook: In the past? Or now?]
[Kim Su Min: I still feel that way.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It doesn't apply now.]
[Kim Su Min: Really?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah,
you've been really cool.]
[Kim Su Min: On one hand, I still have regrets.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Why?]
[Kim Su Min: I thought
I could've been more proactive.]
[Kim Su Min: Other than
talking to you alone like this,]
[Kim Su Min: I always felt
shy and nervous for no reason,]
[Kim Su Min: and stopped myself
from making moves.]
[Kim Su Min: So, a part of me]
[Kim Su Min: still wishes
I were a bit more courageous.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's possible.
But I really felt your sincerity.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You should not have regrets.
As the one on the receiving end,]
[Kim Sun Wook: I completely felt your effort.
And I'm very grateful for it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I don't think
you should have any regrets.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
I felt your efforts as they were.]
[Kim Su Min: I was a little jealous.]
[Kim Su Min: I did get a bit jealous.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's human nature.]
Right?
[Kim Sun Wook: I really enjoyed
all the time I spent with you.]
[Kim Su Min: When we're talking alone,
I have no problem looking into your eyes.]
[Kim Su Min: But for some reason,
it's hard when we're in the rooms.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Really?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Why?]
[Kim Su Min: That's how I felt.]
[Kim Su Min: Before you came in,]
[Kim Su Min: I thought that since
we've talked a lot and had a date yesterday,]
[Kim Su Min: I could treat this casually.
But somehow I got nervous again.]
[Kim Sun Wook: The last date
is always like this.]
[Kim Su Min: I got nervous for no reason.]
[Kim Su Min: Want me to take photos for you?]
[Kim Sun Wook: So suddenly?]
[Kim Sun Wook: All of a sudden?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Let's do it together after.]
[Kim Su Min: OK.]
[Kim Su Min: I hope you'll use up the film roll.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I think I will.]
[Kim Su Min: I hope you can
take photos with everyone today.]
[Kim Su Min: Still, I'm very happy
to talk to you like this]
[Kim Su Min: for the last time.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's not the last time.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But like this... Anyway,
it may be the last time of significance]
[Kim Sun Wook: on this show.]
[Kim Su Min: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: For the two of us
to spare the time to do this.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But I'm
always grateful to you]
[Kim Sun Wook: for always
thinking of me in a positive light.]
[Kim Sun Wook: If I were you,
I'd probably have some negative thoughts.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But you didn't. You always
thought highly of me and took good care of me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm very grateful.]
[Kim Su Min: There was someone else
I was a little curious about,]
[Kim Su Min: but I couldn't help]
[Kim Su Min: that my mind always
ended up landing on you.]
[Kim Su Min: Even when I got
curious about that other person,]
[Kim Su Min: the curiosity died out quickly.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I must be very charming.]
[Kim Su Min: Immensely.]
[Kim Su Min: Overflowing with charm.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What do you like about me?]
[Kim Su Min: Your words are
warmer than I expected.]
[Kim Su Min: When I talk to you,
your responses are]
[Kim Su Min: usually
much warmer than I expected.]
[Kim Su Min: That's one reason
you stood out to me.]
[Kim Su Min: I don't know if
I feel that way because I like you,]
[Kim Su Min: or that's
how I'd felt from the beginning.]
[Kim Su Min: I like that.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's a compliment.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I don't usually talk warmly.
I don't usually speak with care.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But you're older than me.
But even if you weren't,]
[Kim Sun Wook: you're someone
who's always treated me warmly,]
[Kim Sun Wook: so naturally
I reciprocate that.]
[Kim Sun Wook: And it also means
you're valuable to me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I spoke to you
with more care and more warmly.]
[Kim Sun Wook: After six days together,
is there anything you're curious about?]
[Kim Su Min: You say I've expressed
myself enough, but from my perspective,]
[Kim Su Min: right now,
I think I could've done a little more.]
[Kim Su Min: To leave without regret,
I thought I should've worked a little harder.]
[Kim Su Min: So I regret that a bit.]
Do you have any regrets?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Me?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I don't think so.]
[Kim Su Min: Are you really happy?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Happy... I'm happy.]
[Kim Sun Wook: As you said,
I've been happy, and still am now.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm also happy and grateful
that I got to spend time with you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I think it's because
you've worked hard to spend time with me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So, thank you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You must be happy too.]
[Kim Su Min: I will be happy.
I'll only be happy.]
[Kim Su Min: I could feel him
establishing clear boundaries,]
[Kim Su Min: so while I was smiling outside,
I was crying inside.]
[Kim Su Min: I hope we can
have fun together after this show too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: We should all meet again.
I'm glad to have met everyone here.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I hope we can create
more nice memories together after the shoot.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Because Su Min
has moved me in many ways,]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm happy to have
had a pleasant chat]
[Kim Sun Wook: with him today.]
[Kim Su Min: Let's just take two photos.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Shall we?]
[Kim Su Min: Let me take one for you first.]
How?
[Su Min and Sun Wook
making their last memories]
Like this?
-Move a little outward. -Like this?
1, 2, 3!
[Kim Su Min: Nice.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Shall I take one for you too?]
OK.
[Kim Sun Wook: Oh, it's pretty here.]
[Kim Sun Wook: 1, 2, 3. Smile!]
[Happy memories that will linger on]
[Sun Wook is waiting for
a date with another man]
[Who did Sun Wook choose as his date?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Just seeing him come in
from a distance made me happy.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I seldom say
that things make me happy,]
[Kim Sun Wook:
but everything about him made me happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Did you wait long?]
[Kim Sun Wook: No, no.]
[Kim Sun Wook: About... 40 minutes?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's a long time.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I did something else.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What did you do?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Had a chat.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
Why do you think you're here?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Because I chose you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hmm?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Isn't it because I chose you?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I chose you too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Right. It's mutual.]
[Kim Sun Wook: When they said to choose
someone I want to express my feelings to,]
[Kim Sun Wook:
I looked through my text history,]
[Kim Sun Wook: and it was all your name.]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
I think mine's like that too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So...]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought,
"Ah, so this is how I feel."]
[Lee Hyun Jun: So how do you feel?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm happy to see you again.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You're really easy to read.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Why do you say that?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Like an open book.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't think I am.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Why? It's obvious to me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How is it obvious?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's just obvious to me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What's obvious to you?]
[Kim Sun Wook: How you feel?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Is it obvious?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Feelings can't be hidden.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I bet everyone except you knows.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Really?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: To me,
he's always been proactively]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
expressing his interest in me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: If I was
about 50% drawn to him at first,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: it's been constantly increasing
as we spent time together in Men's House.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I like this.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You're so cute.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm not cute. How am I cute?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You smile a lot.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Seeing you makes me smile.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do I look funny?]
[Kim Sun Wook: A little?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Really?]
[Kim Sun Wook:
I'm someone who smiles a lot,]
but I smile more when I see you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hm!]
[Kim Sun Wook: What's that reaction?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What?]
[Kim Sun Wook: What's that reaction!]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It means I'm in a good mood.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What do you think of
Min Seong and Hyeong Jun?]
[Lee Hyun Jun:
I think they're hitting it off.]
-Yeah? -Why?
[Kim Sun Wook: They're always in my room.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So when I watch them,]
[Kim Sun Wook: they're cute.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What's cute about them?]
[Kim Sun Wook: How they hang out together?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What do they do?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hmm...]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hyeong Jun's like a cat.
He's always still. But Min Seong is...]
[Kim Sun Wook: always clinging onto him.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Really?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Is he a cicada?]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I thought
they're cute when they're together.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Are you jealous?]
[Kim Sun Wook: What?]
[Kim Sun Wook: A little?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Want me to cling onto you?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You don't say such things out.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Why not?]
[Kim Sun Wook: We need to
overcome a lot of obstacles.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Is there a lot?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Just saying.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But you're charming
as you are. I like it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's good.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's good that you like it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Is that all?]
[Kim Sun Wook: My goodness.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Isn't that enough?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yes, that's enough.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
You're my first and last date.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Oh, right.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So...]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm very happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What is it?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You look so cute.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I said I'm not cute.]
[Kim Sun Wook: No?]
[Kim Sun Wook: What should I do?]
[Kim Sun Wook: How do I
turn this robot into a real human?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Try to change me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Slowly.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'll do it gradually.]
[A little clumsy,
but it's what makes this love more exciting]
[Kim Sun Wook: What's the most
important thing in a relationship to you?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Not lying.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What about you?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Me? I think...]
[Kim Sun Wook: Not lying is important,
but trust is the most important to me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Got it. I'll keep it in mind.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'll keep it in mind too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Lying...]
[Kim Sun Wook: I didn't expect you
to be so talkative.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yes, I talked a lot.
Since Yun Jae said he wanted to talk.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Did this and that in secret.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I see. In secret.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
Don't hold hands with Yun Jae again.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How did you find out?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Don't do it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: There are so many spies.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I won't.]
[Kim Sun Wook: You actually held hands.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Are you freaking serious?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: So assertive.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So funny.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: My first thought was,
"How did he find out?"]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The conversation
and interactions were between me and Yun Jae,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: so I first
wondered how he knew.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Your hands aren't shaking today.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought a lot
about what I should do.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: About your hands shaking?]
[Kim Sun Wook: No.]
[Kim Sun Wook: When I heard you held hands.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Ah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I thought,
"Wow! How should I bring this up to him?"]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought
it's better to talk about it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Message received.
I won't hold his hand again.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm just kidding.
No, I'm not kidding.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I won't hold his hand again.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm actually
quite a jealous person.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Seems like it.]
[Kim Sun Wook:
I try not to show it, but I am.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'll be watching you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm scared.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Ah...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What's wrong?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's like I'm talking to a robot.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I think
even ChatGPT's more empathetic.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: ChatGPT's ChatGPT. I am me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It was trained to be so.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So you can do it too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Train me to be so.]
[Kim Sun Wook: OK.]
[Kim Sun Wook: How do you feel?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: About?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Today is our last date,
and it ends tomorrow.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What do you think
about your time here?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm satisfied. I did well.
I think I had a good time.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What about you?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Me? I really enjoyed it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do I look that funny?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You're so mean.]
[Kim Sun Wook: "You're so mean"!]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hmm?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Your response was funny.]
[Hyun Jun and Sun Wook's date
with endless smiles and laughter]
[Taichi: What's going on? Only you here?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Did your date go well?]
[Taichi: Well.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Who did you date?]
[Taichi: Guess.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Ah, tell me.]
[Taichi: Who will you date?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'll tell you after you tell me.]
[Taichi: Min Seong.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Min Seong?]
Yesterday was blah.
[Kim Han Gyeol: You are all here.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You're back.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Isn't (Yun Jae's) jacket nice? It suits him.]
[Taichi: You changed?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah, I was dressed too casual.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I really like the back.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Give it to me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Haha.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Isn't he cute?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I feel cuteness aggression.]
[Taichi: What do you think of Hyeok Jin?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Taichi, you're really...]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Why aren't you answering?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What do you think of me?]
No.
[Cho Yun Jae: You're great! Wanna go on a date?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Come on!]
[Cho Yun Jae: Wanna go on a date?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Wanna go? Do it?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'll do it if you do!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Sure. Let's do it.]
[Taichi: No. Han Gyeol, let's go out.
Leave them alone.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Want to build a narrative?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
We'll turn into a romance movie.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Wanna do it? I'm game for it.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My back hurts. Give me a massage.]
[Taichi: Aren't you hot?
Why don't you take off your jacket?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Trying to undress me, huh?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'll take care of that.
Taichi, stay out of it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: When can I go on my date?]
[Taichi: Just now, I heard that]
[Taichi: one of us can't go on a date.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It must be me. Really?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Want to go for a walk?
To the convenience store nearby.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But they said I'm going to a cafe.]
[Taichi: I lied to you.]
[Taichi: Everyone's going on a date.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: You actually believed him?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yes, I did.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You must have chosen someone.
So you'll go on a date with him.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What'd you do? Just a cafe, right?]
[Taichi: No, no. I went hiking.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Damn you.]
[Chatting non-stop]
Kick it like this.
I guess I'm old. My body's been aching lately.
[Among them,
Han Gyeol seems particularly silent]
You're not young anymore.
-I saw these yesterday. -Wearing these shoes.
[Kim Han Gyeol: I was calming myself down
after all the exhaustion I've experienced.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What'd you talk about? 30 min?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
-You too? -Yeah.
[Kim Sun Wook: I told him
not to hold his hands.]
What?
[Kim Sun Wook: I told him not to hold his hands.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What do you mean?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You don't know? Oh, you don't.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah. What is it?]
[Kim Sun Wook: He and Yun Jae
held hands while talking.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Who did?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hyun Jun.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What? Why?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why hold hands?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I don't know.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: There must've been
something between them.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I said...
"Don't hold hands again!"]
[Kim Sun Wook: I said I'm a jealous person.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: So you got jealous?]
[Kim Sun Wook:
So I said I get jealous easily.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Of course you got jealous.
They held hands.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So I said I get jealous easily.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Who held hands?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hmm? I said I'm like that with
the one I like. And he said he'd be careful.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: And what did he say?]
[Kim Sun Wook: He said
he'd be careful; that he was sorry.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
He held hands with Yun Jae?]
Who?
[Kim Sun Wook: Well, it's understandable.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: How'd they end up holding hands?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why? I won't accept it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's a special environment here.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's what I thought.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: But it still bugged you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah, so I thought]
[Kim Sun Wook: I should tell him how I feel.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: That's right.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I have to make it clear.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah. So I told him.]
[Hyun Jun is waiting for another date]
[Who chose him as a date?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hello.]
[Cho Yun Jae: How have you been?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I've been good. You?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Me? I've been good too.]
[The atmosphere is a little awkward]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's ending. How do you feel?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: About it ending?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I just feel like,
"It's finally ending."]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's a bit of a pity too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What about you?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Me? Well...]
[Cho Yun Jae: Let's say,
if I could do it again, I'd put in more effort.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't think
I expressed my feelings well.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
I had a lot of chances to do so,]
[Cho Yun Jae: but I didn't.
So I feel a bit regretful.]
[A conversation that is hard to continue]
[Cho Yun Jae: Shall we say
3 of each other's strengths?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: All of a sudden?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Want to go first?]
[Cho Yun Jae: You...]
[Cho Yun Jae: Ha... Your strengths?]
[Cho Yun Jae: First of all, hmm...]
[Cho Yun Jae: You don't seem it,
but you're actually very considerate.]
[Cho Yun Jae: You're very thoughtful.]
[Cho Yun Jae: And kind. You're kind.]
[Cho Yun Jae: What's wrong?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Aren't you being too generous?
Even if it's about strengths.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't know if he wanted to
ease the mood, or if he prepared it beforehand,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: but right off the bat, he said
to mention 3 of each other's strengths.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: To be honest,
all 3 strengths he said about me]
[Lee Hyun Jun: really moved me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: As for you...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You have really good skin.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm so jealous.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: And you look really young.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: When I first met you,
I thought you were the youngest.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Really?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I thought you were the oldest.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I hear that a lot. It's OK.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You're really kind.]
[Cho Yun Jae: This is nice, hearing 3 strengths.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It was a nice time.]
[Cho Yun Jae: All this while, I'd been
too nervous to talk with him]
[Cho Yun Jae: and express myself.]
[Cho Yun Jae: In our last conversation,
I tried my best to ease the mood,]
[Cho Yun Jae:
so it wasn't tense or awkward.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But recently
we've been talking more too,]
[Cho Yun Jae: so it's OK.
It's not that awkward now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Compared to the first time we met.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: We were really awkward then.]
[Jo Yoon-jae: I'm really shy with strangers.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me too. So when you first came in,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I had no idea what to say.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I really
resented my personality for a bit.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Why? There's nothing wrong
with your personality.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Well, everyone...]
[Cho Yun Jae: It feels like everyone's
doing a good job being proactive]
[Cho Yun Jae: but me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's not true.]
[Cho Yun Jae: So it got to me a bit.]
[Endless self-blame and regret inside]
[Cho Yun Jae: Also, did you see my letter?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I felt bad after reading it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: But I couldn't
show it then and there.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: In any case,
I felt sorry after reading the letter.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I wondered if I even
deserve all this affection from various people.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
When considering who to choose,]
[Cho Yun Jae: since I still...]
[Cho Yun Jae: I thought it's better
to choose you. That's why I'm here.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you.]
[Cho Yun Jae: No problem.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: For taking the initiative.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've really challenged myself here.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I think
I've used up a lifetime's courage here.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But I've also learned a lot.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I wonder if
I've been living too comfortably.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've grown in a better way.
I understand now.]
[Cho Yun Jae: If we could go back to
the beginning, what do you think would happen?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Back to the beginning?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't know.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Right.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Who knows what would happen?]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's a bit of a pity.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
During my stay here for a week,]
[Cho Yun Jae: my regret that
I couldn't be more proactive]
[Cho Yun Jae: will stay with me for a bit.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I've said
everything I wanted to to Hyun Jun.]
[Hope that there are no more
regret and guilt between the two...]
[Min Seong is waiting for his last date]
[With the Super Date right,
who's the second guy he chose?]
[Oh Min Seong: Please have a seat here.]
[Kim Su Min: Hello.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hello.]
[Kim Su Min: I was so surprised
to see Min Seong sitting there.]
[Kim Su Min: I didn't expect it at all.]
[Kim Su Min: I was very curious
about the reason. Why me?]
[Oh Min Seong:
I chose him once last time too.]
[Oh Min Seong: I thought it'd be nice
to go on a date with him once.]
[Oh Min Seong: I had to choose someone else,
and I wanted a relaxing date.]
[Oh Min Seong: Was I being too selfish?]
[Oh Min Seong: This is where you repent.]
[Kim Su Min: Repent?]
Yes.
[Oh Min Seong: Well, anyway,
I chose you today.]
[Kim Su Min: I was surprised.]
[Oh Min Seong: Surprised? Why?]
[Oh Min Seong: Wondering if I like you?]
[Kim Su Min: No, no.]
[Kim Su Min: I was a little surprised
when I came up the stairs.]
[Oh Min Seong: Of course it's surprising.
You couldn't have expected this.]
[Kim Su Min: Yeah.]
Right?
[Kim Su Min: We knew each other before.]
[Oh Min Seong: That was during "His Man 2."
Who knew we'd meet again in Season 4?]
Yeah.
[Kim Su Min: I was a huge fan.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Oh Min Seong: Of "His Man 2"?]
[Kim Su Min: Yeah, and also your fan.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really? Why?]
[Kim Su Min: Because I...]
[Kim Su Min: I like people
with strong facial features.]
[Kim Su Min: That's why
I was a huge fan of yours.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm so thankful.
You like plumper people?]
[Oh Min Seong: Do you like plumper people?]
[Kim Su Min: No, that's not it.]
[Kim Su Min: I don't care about size.]
[Oh Min Seong: Thank you so much.]
[Kim Su Min: I was a huge fan of yours.]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't know. I didn't know.]
[Kim Su Min: So when you first appeared,]
[Kim Su Min: I was so happy.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Oh Min Seong: I was happy to see you, too.
I didn't expect to see you here.]
[Kim Su Min: But how you're like now is
different from what I saw in Season 2.]
[Oh Min Seong: I don't remember
what I was like then.]
[Kim Su Min: You were quiet.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, I was quiet then.]
[Oh Min Seong: Anyway,
it's my second time on the show.]
[Oh Min Seong: I was
determined to act differently.]
[Oh Min Seong: When I watched the show,
I didn't like how I appeared.]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't seem sincere.
Though I was being honest and sincere.]
[Oh Min Seong: But when I watched the show,
I didn't like how I acted.]
[Kim Su Min: Your attitude in this season
has been really cool.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Kim Su Min:
That's why I voted for you today.]
I see.
[Kim Su Min: Mr. Popular with 5 votes.
Have you had your Super Date?]
[Oh Min Seong: This is the Super Date.]
[Oh Min Seong: Because I chose you.]
[Kim Su Min: Ah...]
[Oh Min Seong: This is it. Nothing special.]
[Kim Su Min: Yeah?]
[Kim Su Min: It's an honor.]
[Oh Min Seong: Oh, please. Don't say that.]
[Kim Su Min: You used
your Super Date right on me.]
[Oh Min Seong:
Did we choose 2 dates yesterday?]
[Oh Min Seong: For Day and Night dates?]
[Kim Su Min: Yes.]
[Oh Min Seong:
I chose you for the Day Date.]
[Oh Min Seong: But the date didn't happen
because, I guess, it wasn't mutual?]
[Kim Su Min: I chose you for the Night Date.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Oh Min Seong: Day and night. I see...]
[Kim Su Min: You were the one
I was curious about, your thoughts and stuff.]
[Kim Su Min: So I chose you for the Night Date.]
[Oh Min Seong: I chose you for the Day Date.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm shy.]
[Oh Min Seong: So after we first met...]
[Oh Min Seong: We haven't met in private,]
[Oh Min Seong: so when I first met you,
I thought you have a great personality.]
[Oh Min Seong: You're very likeable.]
[Kim Su Min: Like I said before,
"His Man" should be about 2 weeks long.]
[Oh Min Seong:
I agree. A week is too short.]
[Oh Min Seong: How could you
know someone in a week?]
[Kim Su Min: It should be 2 weeks long.]
[Kim Su Min: Then, I can make an impression.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, 1 week is too short.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's near the end...]
[Kim Su Min: Yes, it's too late...]
[Oh Min Seong: It's almost over.]
[Kim Su Min: Ah, I'm all about the face.]
[Oh Min Seong: So you like Sun Wook's looks?]
[Kim Su Min: I like his personality.
I also like his looks.]
[Kim Su Min: As I got to know him,
I found that he's warm too. I like that too.]
[Oh Min Seong: Right, he's quite considerate.]
[Kim Su Min: Like with the ranking
for the elimination voting,]
[Kim Su Min: I ranked based on who I liked.]
[Kim Su Min: You were in my top three.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's an honor. I'm so shy.]
[Kim Su Min: I liked how
you were truly following your heart.]
[Kim Su Min: I think it was a great attitude.
I was even a little jealous.]
[Oh Min Seong: You got jealous...]
[Kim Su Min: I was impressed, but also...]
[Kim Su Min: What kind of
relationship do you want?]
[Oh Min Seong: Where we're like friends.]
[Kim Su Min: Like friends? I see.]
[Oh Min Seong: Like friends.]
[Oh Min Seong: But he should also...]
[Kim Su Min: Make your heart flutter?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, that too.]
[Kim Su Min: Romantic excitement.]
[Kim Su Min: Watching you two, I think
you'll have the relationship you want.]
[Oh Min Seong: If so, I'd be beyond happy.]
[Kim Su Min: He says you're very cute.]
[Oh Min Seong: Who?]
[Kim Su Min: Hyeong Jun.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Kim Su Min: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Why can't he say that to me?]
[Kim Su Min: He talked about considering
if he should be more expressive.]
[Oh Min Seong: Consider?
No, he should be expressive.]
[Kim Su Min: He says you're very cute.]
[Oh Min Seong:
This is fun, chatting with you.]
[Kim Su Min: I'm more suited
to be with someone I like more,]
[Kim Su Min: rather than
someone who likes me more.]
[Oh Min Seong:
The person you like more. Right.]
[Kim Su Min: To be honest, on this show,
it's not that I didn't get any attention.]
[Kim Su Min: During the last shoot,
someone showed affection to me first.]
[Kim Su Min: But I really realized that
I'm more suited to be with]
[Kim Su Min: someone I like more.]
[Oh Min Seong: Right now,
I also prefer the one I like more.]
[Oh Min Seong: That's right for me.
Isn't it more fun?]
[Kim Su Min: Did you like him at first sight?]
[Oh Min Seong: Hmm... Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, at first sight.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hyeong Jun was
the first person I met.]
[Oh Min Seong: Others came from outside.
Only Hyeong Jun came from his room.]
[Kim Su Min: You two were there first.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: He sat in front of me.
So I met him first.]
[Kim Su Min: Getting with the one
you fell for at first sight must be really...]
[Oh Min Seong:
I didn't expect any of this.]
[Kim Su Min: You must be really happy.]
[Oh Min Seong: How did it turn out like this?]
[Kim Su Min: You must be happy.]
[But everything went well.
Maybe it's luck.]
[Kim Su Min: I hope you
give it your best shot. And have a long...]
[Oh Min Seong: Lasting relationship?]
[Kim Su Min: And happy relationship.]
[Oh Min Seong: I hope so too.
It depends on both our efforts.]
[Oh Min Seong: I hope you get to
do couple vlogs soon too.]
[Oh Min Seong: We can do it together.]
[Kim Su Min: A double date?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, invite us
on your YouTube show.]
[Kim Su Min: I'll do my best to plan that.]
[Oh Min Seong: Invite us too.]
[Kim Su Min: I had fun. We talked a lot.]
[Kim Su Min: I had a deep discussion with him.
That was fun.]
[Oh Min Seong:
It was fun chatting with him.]
[Oh Min Seong: So the date felt short.]
[The date that seems
both breezy and meaningful ends]
[The men who have gone through
an unpredictable emotional tunnel]
[Taichi: We're swimming!
To the pool! To the pool!]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Should I wear a tank top?]
[Kim Su Min: I'm wearing shorts. Oh no.]
[Party time for the nine men]
[Kim Su Min: Those two look so excited.]
[All gathering by the heated pool]
So cold!
[Min Seong is lying in bed alone]
[Oh Min Seong: I suddenly got sick.]
[Oh Min Seong: After the Super Date,]
[Oh Min Seong: I suddenly had a fever,
so I couldn't join the rest of the shoot.]
[All brimming with excitement]
[Kim Su Min: Get in quickly.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Wow, it's hot!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Going in like that?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is it hot?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's hot here.]
It's not cold.
Come in.
[Kim Su Min: Take off your shirt.]
[Kim Su Min: Wow,
y-your... back muscles are crazy.]
Nice.
[Kim Su Min: I'm like a mom
taking pictures of my kids.]
[Kim Su Min: I'm afraid of water.]
[Kim Su Min: I fell into the water once
when I was little.]
[Kim Su Min: So I became afraid of water.
I just soaked my feet a little.]
I can do it too.
[Like a fish in water,
Taichi is so excited]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: This is a dating show.]
[Taichi: I go to the beach
with my family every year.]
[Taichi: It's a family tradition.]
[Taichi: I also go swimming
in Korea once a year.]
[Taichi: But this year, I had the shoots,
so I'd been too busy to go.]
[Taichi: I was sad about that.]
[Taichi: But I got to swim here.
I had a lot of fun.]
[Taichi: It's more fun
to swim with everyone.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I can't go forward!
Why am I so slow?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Because you're too small.]
[Cho Yun Jae:
It's the most carefree I've been]
[Cho Yun Jae: since I got here.
I had a lot of fun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin:
Woah, he took his shirt off!]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Take yours off now!]
[Kim Su Min: Show us quickly.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Are you a man or not?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Even if you sit here, it'll show.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Wow,
his muscles are really big.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Your face's changed.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hey, why are you looking
at him like that? What's with your expression?]
[Kim Su Min: Wow, my eyes are so happy.]
[Kim Su Min: I like looking at them.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Go in there.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You go.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: After you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No, it's too cold.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Aren't you a man?
You're big and burly.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: From afar, one is super tanned
and the other is super fair.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Go in!]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Rock, paper, scissors.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Who will it be?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Go in.]
It's really not cold.
I think it's cold.
Stay here for a while. Come on.
Move one leg over first.
The way you climb over is dangerous.
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Ah!]
You come down too.
[Ah!]
What was that?
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What was that sound?]
Did something come out of you?
[Kim Sun Wook: It's so cold!]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Sorry, but are you having
a swimming lesson? He's like a swim instructor.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I had a lot of fun
in the heated pool.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I love playing in the water.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I laughed the most then.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I also saw more smiles
on everyone than any other time.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I had a lot of fun.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It was really fun.
I think I had the most fun.]
No!
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I didn't do anything.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Why does he look so haggard all of a sudden?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's different.]
Yes.
It's cold.
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's going to be a good memory.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Everyone playing together was so fun.]
[Kim Su Min: The kids are so cute and playing with them is fun.]
[A happy time where they set aside
their heavy thoughts]
No!
[His Man]
[After playing in the water]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do I just grill it?]
[Kim Su Min: I need to prepare in there.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Let's go out to grill it.]
[The last night's barbecue party]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Wow, the meat is amazing.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Your reaction is much more intense.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm so happy now.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Why are you happy?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: 'Cause I want to eat meat.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Me too.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Hello, Taichi.]
[Taichi: Hello.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I should heat up the rice too, right?]
[Kim Su Min: Heat up some first. There might be people who don't eat rice.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Shall I?]
[Taichi: Hyung only started the fire in the middle.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's burnt.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's burnt.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It tastes better when it's burnt.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Is that so?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Give it to me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm crying.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Don't cry. Why are you crying?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Sad thoughts came to mind.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What is it?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: That someone is sick.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Who? Ah.]
[Min Seong who caught a cold
is already dreaming away...]
[Kim Sun Wook: The meat might get cold. You should eat first.]
[Kim Su Min: Is it cooked already?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You eat first.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: The meat is ready so soon?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: They already sent us a plate of meat.]
[Kim Su Min: It looks good.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Have a bite first?]
[Kim Su Min: No, that's rude. They're already eating, right?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Probably.]
[Kim Su Min: They must have eaten.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: That's right.]
[Kim Su Min: Let's sit down and eat.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Sounds good.]
[Taichi: Mm!]
[Kim Sun Wook: Is it good?]
[Taichi: Because of this, I want to be in charge of the grilling.]
[Taichi: Because we can eat first.]
[Hyeong Jun and Hyun Jun
are roasting marshmallows]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I don't think we can eat that.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I grilled it well.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You've never done this before, right?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: No, I have in the past.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's been a while. The fire is too strong.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yes, the fire is quite strong.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's warm though.]
[Kim Su Min: Sit down and eat.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: We have to eat meat standing up.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: No?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Mm! It's delicious.]
[Kim Su Min: This is the brightest expression I've seen on you today.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: It's really delicious.]
-Really? -Yes.
[Cho Yun Jae: How delicious is it?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Mm!]
[Kim Han Gyeol: It's delicious, right?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: This charcoal grill aroma is amazing.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Is it that good?]
This charcoal grill aroma is amazing.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Mm. It's good.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Pork belly with skin is really delicious.]
[Kim Su Min: Mm!]
-Right? -Delicious.
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Is it good?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I want one too.]
[Taichi: But I sprinkled too much black pepper.]
It's a bit salty.
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Mm!]
[Kim Sun Wook: You came out to eat, right?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: No.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Is it obvious?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yes.]
[Taichi: I'll send this one inside too.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: If there were another pair of tongs, I could help grill. What a pity.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Are you crazy?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Ah, my eyes hurt.]
[Sun Wook takes a break,
passing the tongs to Hyeong Jun]
[Taichi: I'll do it. It'll take some time anyway.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Okay.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's really hot.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Is it roasted like this?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yes, but it'll catch fire if you get too close.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Let me grill it for you. It might get burnt.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Oh, just right.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Delicious.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Is it okay?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yes.]
[Kim Sun Wook: We didn't get to have it on Nami Island.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah, we were just playing.]
[Somehow, the pork belly and collar
have already been roasted]
[The army stew is ready too]
[Kim Su Min: Cheers!]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: How do we cheer?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: WiFi.]
Cheers.
It's good.
[Everyone is satisfied with the dinner]
It's been a long time since I drank.
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Ichi, there aren't any bowls left, right?]
[Taichi: I'll go get them.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Ramyeon?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: He's like the cafeteria auntie.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The way you say things...]
[Taichi: I don't want that much.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: The student.]
What?
[Eum Hyeok Jin: A student for real.]
[Cho Yun Jae: But I want some too.]
What's going on?
[Kim Su Min: You have to eat more today.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm hungry.]
[Kim Su Min: You didn't look well just now.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I mean it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Pour it for me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Oh?]
[Taichi: Sorry.]
[The happy last dinner]
[Cho Yun Jae: Ah, I want to put on some songs.]
[Taichi: Yeah.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Sing for us.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hahaha.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: There was something really funny.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Let me tell you something funny.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's really funny.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What is it?]
[Curious]
[Cho Yun Jae: Do you know BLACKPINK's "Bet you get it now"?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Well...]
[Cho Yun Jae: My friend heard it as "plant some cabbage."]
(T/N: Sounds like that in Korean.)
[Kim Su Min: Shall we have a toast?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hey!]
[Cho Yun Jae: Plant some cabbage. Plant some lettuce.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Why are you so happy?]
[Kim Su Min: The key to comedy is repeating it.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's really funny.]
[Taichi: What do you think of the shoot?]
[Taichi: Tonight is the last night.]
[Taichi: Especially the newcomers. How do you feel?]
[Kim Su Min: Yes.]
-I want to know. -I'm really curious.
[Taichi: I'm really curious.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm sad.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Why?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Because it's the last day.]
[Taichi: Are you drunk?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm drunk.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Anyway, I'm sad.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I feel like I rode a really scary roller coaster.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm almost there. Getting ready to get off.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: The moment where you're catching your breath.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Are you a liberal arts student?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm 100% a liberal arts student.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's so abstract.]
[Kim Su Min: So emotional.]
Yeah.
[Kim Han Gyeol: It was fun. I feel calm now.
I drank soju. Everyone looks closer.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: It's the end. That's the feeling.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Shouldn't you cry?]
[Kim Su Min: I'm numb now.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Seems like it.]
[Kim Su Min: My first shoot was a bit hard.]
[Kim Su Min: This shoot was quite fun.]
[Kim Su Min: It was fun.]
[Kim Su Min: The preparation was fun.]
[Kim Su Min: I also met a lot of good people.]
[Kim Su Min: Yes, it was very fun.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's different from last time,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but it's time for me to accept another me.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Something like that.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: That I've found a different me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's right.]
Right?
[Lee Hyun Jun: I think I saw three of you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I think it's four.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It was nice that Han Gyeol expressed
his thoughts to me the other day.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I didn't get to take the initiative at the start—]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: that was a pity.]
[Taichi: It was a time when I got to think more about myself.]
[Taichi: I realized that I need to think about more things.]
[Taichi: This shoot was fun for me too.]
[Taichi: I'm so happy to have met so many good people here.]
[Taichi: The happy time I'm spending with them]
[Taichi: is ending soon—I find that sad.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Firstly, I]
[Kim Sun Wook: learned how to treat people with sincerity]
[Kim Sun Wook: and how to give and accept love—
through this experience.]
[Kim Sun Wook: The way to express love and how to accept love—]
[Kim Sun Wook: I seem to know them better now.]
[Kim Sun Wook: This week has been a meaningful time.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm most curious about his feelings.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It was fun.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Again.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: That's terrible.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The atmosphere got cold so quickly.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It was a fun time.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I don't want to go home.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I'm happy to have met many good people.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Let's go on a trip next time.]
[Kim Su Min: That'd be great.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Some recreation stuff.]
What do you think?
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Screaming in the silence.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It was fun, but it was also tiring.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But I'm happy]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: to have met so many nice people.]
[Oh Min Seong: I wanted meat too.]
[Oh Min Seong: I mean, we have to return to our normal lives.]
[Oh Min Seong: I've made good memories,
and have met nice people.]
[Oh Min Seong: I was happy but reluctant to leave.]
[His Man]
[The last night when countless emotions intertwine]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What should I write on my Love Diary?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Today is the last day.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Min Seong is still sick, what should we do?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Right.]
[Oh Min Seong: Mmhmm.]
[Taichi: Do you want something to eat?]
[Oh Min Seong: Hmm?]
[Oh Min Seong: Maybe later.]
[Taichi: There's meat and army stew. You can't have those, right?]
[Taichi: Okay.]
[Oh Min Seong: Ah...]
[Cho Yun Jae: Compared to the date time, what left a deeper impression was...]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday]
[What's your love forecast today?]
[What kind of day was today?]
[Cho Yun Jae: Was it just a burst of dopamine]
[We played board games yesterday and we played in the water together today. We've gotten a lot closer.
Now I feel like we're more than friends.]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Taichi]
[The person I'm least interested in is:]
[Cho Yun Jae: or am I really feeling something?]
[Cho Yun Jae: We played board games in Block A.]
[Cho Yun Jae: We had fun playing in the water too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I also had a drink with Taichi.]
[Cho Yun Jae: It was a time we got along well.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I feel relaxed. But it's time for the final choice.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I feel I've been worried for nothing again.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday]
[What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[What kind of day is today?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: If I have to choose something I regret,]
[I don't even know what I did, but it ended so quickly.
I'm also very conflicted about who to pick for the final choice.
The person I'm most interested in is: Eum Hyeok Jin
The person I'm least interested in is: none]
[Kim Han Gyeol: it was maybe I was too passive.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny
What kind of day was today?]
[Today is the last day at Men's House. Although I'm happy, I also feel a bit reluctant to leave.
But I'm very glad to have found out who likes me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I didn't get to chat with many people.]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is:]
[Lee Hyun Jun: This part is a bit of a regret.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I should've talked to Yun Jae more.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: But I don't have any regrets now.]
[Taichi: I wrote what I was thinking.]
[Taichi: I wrote it every day. The space given was too small.]
[Love Diary
Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
Swimming was really fun! The hyungs, staff members, I'm really, really, very, very grateful to you all!
Shout it out! A date that felt like a real date, and it still made my heart flutter. The space is too small, I'm writing on the next page...]
[Taichi: I just wrote down my thoughts briefly]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday]
[What's your love forecast today? Cloudy]
[What kind of day was today?]
[Today is the day of the final date.
Today was a chance to go on a brief date with the person I wanted to date.
Actually, until now, I haven't had anyone I've successfully developed a connection with.]
[Taichi: since today is the last day after all.]
[I haven't felt a strong romantic attraction to anyone either.
I was really worried about who to date. While I was worrying, I thought of what Min Seong told me yesterday.
"In the end, you have to be honest with your heart so that you won't have any regrets."
So I thought of the only moment since coming here that I was afraid of regretting.]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Oh Min Seong]
[The person I'm least interested in is: none today either]
[Taichi: Starting from the reason I chose Min Seong]
[Love Diary
Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
It was a bit heart-fluttering, a nervous and formal date that made me very happy!!
Although I'm not confident about making the final choice tomorrow, I think in the end I'll be able to make a choice that I won't regret.
Today's filming was fun. Good job, TAICHI!!]
[Taichi: I also wrote that I feel some regret about not being able to make a choice]
[Love Diary
What's your love forecast today?
What kind of day was today?
Actually, when it was time to make the phone call on the fourth day, I wanted to call Min Seong.
But he joked and said "Don't call me,"
so I got scared and didn't call. I actually feel a lot of regret about it.]
[Taichi: I also wrote my thanks to the hyungs.]
[In the end, I decided to follow my original way of thinking—not thinking too much and just going directly to the person I'm attracted to. To approach him without leaving any regrets, I went on a date with Min Seong.
This was the first time since coming here that I felt nervous before a date, and even during the date
The person I'm most interested in is:
The person I'm least interested in is:]
[Taichi: I wrote quite a lot of things.]
[Kim Su Min: He used his Super Date right on me.]
[Kim Su Min: He's someone within the top 3 in my mind.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[Kim Su Min: If only I could have known him better sooner,]
[What kind of day was today? A day where I candidly expressed my heart.
And I was the popular guy today... I also have regrets; if only I had been candid from the start.
The person I'm most interested in is: Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Kim Su Min: maybe the result would have been different?]
[Kim Su Min: I should've been more honest on the first three days.]
[Kim Su Min: I think I lacked courage.]
[Kim Sun Wook: This week means a lot to me.]
[Love Diary
Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
The meat was delicious. It's almost over! Let's do well
Lee Hyun Jun: His Man 4, so cold! I was happy that we went swimming.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Must be sincere, no matter the words or actions]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny
What kind of day was today?
Everyone, be happy! His Man 4]
[Kim Sun Wook: It was a time for getting to know each other]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Lee Hyun Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Kim Sun Wook: and I've become happier,]
[Kim Sun Wook: so I will never forget this.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Rainy
What kind of day was today?
Today is the last day. The moment I received the text message, the only name I could think of writing down was "Kim Han Gyeol."
The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Han Gyeol
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It feels like it's really ending, so I feel quite relieved?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Things didn't go as I expected,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: but I don't regret it now.]
[Hyeong Jun came to see Min Seong]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: He didn't eat either.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hmm?]
[Oh Min Seong: Have you eaten? Was it delicious?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I did.]
[Oh Min Seong: Well done.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You need to eat something.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, I'll eat later.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Do I smell like barbecue?]
[Oh Min Seong: No, my nose is blocked.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Is that so? That's good.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You need to take some medicine.]
[Oh Min Seong: I will later.]
[Oh Min Seong: My fever is gone.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You're still hot?]
[Oh Min Seong: It's just that my body is hot.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I brought snacks.]
[Oh Min Seong: What snacks?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Cookies.]
[Oh Min Seong: Where did you get it?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I saw it downstairs.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'll eat later.]
[Love Diary: Now that the day is over,
Please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
A fun day. Hyeong Jun. It's so painful.
Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday]
[Oh Min Seong: Because I was sick, he came to take care of me again.]
[What's your love forecast today? Sunny, Snowy
What kind of day was today?
I was very lucky today and got first place, so I received a Super Date ticket.
Actually, I wanted to go on a date with Hyeong Jun, but I was told to pick two people.
After worrying about it for a long time, I chose Su Min, and it was very fun.]
[Oh Min Seong: He even brought me cookies, I was so happy.]
[But because my throat was sore, I couldn't get my energy up after that... I miss Hyeong Jun!
The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun.
The person I'm least interested in is:]
[Oh Min Seong: Who else could ever be this good to me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You don't have an appetite, do you?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes, but I'm much better now.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Stop lying.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: How weak.]
[Oh Min Seong: I'm not weak.]
[Love Diary
Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
Thinking of you.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: When we were on our date, he wasn't that sick.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Cloudy]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Min Seong was lying on the bed with a high fever]
[What kind of day was today?
How did you get sick? You make me worry.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: and his body was burning up.]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Min Seong
The person I'm least interested in is: everyone besides Min Seong]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I was a bit worried, he must be feeling very unwell.]
[A deeper feeling for each other]
[The night before the final choice
gets darker...]
[The last morning that felt like
it wouldn't come]
[Men's House]
[After 7 emotional days]
[Block C, Su Min's room]
[A space where smiles and tears coexisted]
[Su Min is preparing for the last day]
[Kim Su Min: The 3rd and 4th day felt very long.]
[Kim Su Min: After I figured out my feelings,]
[Kim Su Min: I started to enjoy it.]
[1F, Block A:
Hyun Jun & Yun Jae & Han Gyeol's room]
[Cho Yun Jae: Did you sleep well?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yeah.]
[Cho Yun Jae: My head's going to explode...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How much did you drink?]
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know. I drank too much with Taichi at the start.]
[Block B:
Hyeok Jin & Hyeong Jun & Sun Wook's room]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Put on eyeshadow for me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Got it.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Make it perfect today.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Today?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's an important day.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What day is it today? What day is it today, Mr. Customer?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Today? It's an important day.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But it can't be too exaggerated.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'll draw you like Kim Sun Wook.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: A natural look, please.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's Kim Sun Wook. Please raise your head.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What day is it today?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Today is an important day]
[Kim Sun Wook: Are you going to confess to someone?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yes.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Do you think you can succeed today?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: In what?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Anything.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Ohoho.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I...]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Do we really have to pack?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Yeah.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Shall I take out my luggage?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Where should I start from?]
[Kim Sun Wook: How do you feel about sharing a room with us?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Wasn't it nice to live in the same room?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I had a good time actually.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yes.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's nice that we shared a room.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to hang out with my roommates.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Now we're really close.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: We have interesting chats and they're good at listening.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to meet them (even outside).]
[It's time to pack my luggage and my feelings]
[Cho Yun Jae: I haven't actually decided on]
[Cho Yun Jae: who I should choose yet.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Honestly speaking, can I really pick someone]
[Cho Yun Jae: in such a short time?]
[Cho Yun Jae: That's what I think.]
[2F, Block A: Min Seong & Taichi's room]
[Taichi: I've reflected a lot.]
[Taichi: There were a few times where my pride was hurt.]
[Taichi: But this time, I did my best with no regrets.]
[Oh Min Seong: That it's finally over.]
[Oh Min Seong: I think there are fruits—]
[Oh Min Seong: of my labour, and the partner.]
[Can the men
make a choice they don't regret?]
[It is the day of the final choice.
Please put your Love Diary into the mailbox of the person
you want to become a couple with to convey your heart.]
[Kim Su Min: Ha...]
[Kim Su Min: They look too careful.]
[Kim Su Min: Challenge, courage, honesty—words like this.]
[Kim Su Min: To show someone]
[Kim Su Min: my diary is too...]
[Kim Su Min: It's embarrassing.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Ha...]
[Kim Sun Wook: Put the diary in the mailbox?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Ah...]
[Kim Sun Wook: My raw emotions are in there.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Pfft.]
[Kim Sun Wook: This?]
[Kim Sun Wook: But Hyun Jun might find it cute.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I wrote "Lee Hyun Jun is so cute" way too many times.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's embarrassing.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I know there will be one,]
[Lee Hyun Jun: but I don't know if there will be two.]
[What is Yun Jae's choice?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What was that?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What text was it? I haven't read it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Huh?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The text.]
[Kim Sun Wook: To put your Love Diary]
[Kim Sun Wook: into the mailbox of the person you want to be a couple with.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: That's terrible.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Why? Did you cuss?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: No.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I don't know.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's better to let him see it,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: 'cause I only wrote about one person in there.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Did I write everything?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: You?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I can't remember.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I want to tear a few pages out.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: No—shouldn't we be showing it
only if we both pick each other?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If that isn't the case, what do I do?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It's terrible.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's embarrassing.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Min Seong wasn't there on the 1st day,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: so I wrote my thoughts about others.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Thinking about when he reads that
makes me feel embarrassed.]
[Oh Min Seong: He can see all of it. I have been honest.]
[Oh Min Seong: Hyeong Jun will give it to me too, right? But after all,]
[Oh Min Seong: there were other things that happened to him,
and he had some difficult times too,]
[Oh Min Seong: so what he wrote may not all be positive stuff.]
[Oh Min Seong: But the latter parts should be filled with better stuff, right?]
[Oh Min Seong: As the diary goes on.]
[Taichi: I just want to make a choice honestly.]
[Arriving at the mailbox first;
the men's final choice]
[Be it unwavering feelings]
[Or a shaken heart]
[They are all put into the mailbox
one after another]
[Men's Love 4: Love Diary]
[All the men have made their choices]
[It's time to confirm
each other's choices]
[Through a very long choice tunnel,
go towards the destination]
[At the end of the road, what kind
of relationship is waiting for them?]
[Taichi: I want to date someone I like after all.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I was waiting for him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I was thinking when will he come?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I've already made up my mind. So it's easy.]
[Hyeok Jin is no longer afraid
of the pain that love could bring]
[He makes his final choice
in the last moment]
[The man that Hyeok Jin chose
in the end is?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My final choice was Han Gyeol.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: The reason is because I don't want to regret.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I put the diary in.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: To be honest, I thought, since the person I choose]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: will get to read the diary,]
[Kim Han Gyeol]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to, once again, tell him what I couldn't say.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: My emotions were recorded in that diary.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I wanted him to confirm it again.]
[Hyeok Jin still looks at Han Gyeol]
[Will Han Gyeol accept Hyeok Jin's heart?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Yeah.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hello?]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hello.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Hmm...]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I really have a lot to say.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm sure you know why I chose you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Come to think of it,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I always had my eyes on you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Also...]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I'm sure you know—I've said this before.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: When my thoughts were a mess,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: you were like a calm ocean after the waves are gone.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hyung, I...]
[Kim Han Gyeol: didn't choose anyone this time.]
[He had a particularly hard time
when having to choose]
[After careful consideration, Han Gyeol's choice is...]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I didn't choose anyone.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I can't pick anyone among the 8 here]
[Kim Han Gyeol: whom I think I can build a long-term relationship with.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: And I've already expressed
my thoughts the day before.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: So we know what we feel.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I told him I'd think about it and give him an answer,]
[Kim Han Gyeol: but Hyeok Jin seems to have already expected it.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I've told you many times—you also know—]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I really like you, and I think you're really cool. You know that, right?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yes, I know.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: There were many moments I was confused whether]
[Kim Han Gyeol: this was out of romantic interest
or out of admiration.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: You've seen how conflicted I was.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: My conclusion is that it's not out of romantic interest.]
So...
[Kim Han Gyeol: But I hope even outside of here,
we can be close friends.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I learned a lot from you.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I learned how to accept love.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Thank you so much for liking me.]
[He made Han Gyeol
experience new things]
This should suit you.
-It's very thick here. -Right.
-Does it look good on me? -Yes.
What's this?
My nickname!
[There were also moments
Han Gyeol was touched]
-They didn't have crushed ice. -Really?
So I bought ice cream.
-I suddenly wanted to buy Melona. -Is that so?
-Are you happy to come out with me? -Yeah.
-Your hand must be cold. -Thank you.
[Hyeok Jin takes good care of Han Gyeol]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I know how you are interested in me
and take very good care of me.]
["Thank you so much, really..."]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Okay. That's enough.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I had a good time.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Yes, there were fun times.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I'm hanging up.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Okay.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I feel relieved. I do feel a little disappointed.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It was mostly disappointment.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: What if I did better? What if I showed my interest earlier?
How would things be different?]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: If I had more chances, what could be changed—
regrets like that.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to be loved once.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: When I'm in a relationship, I'm always the one who loves more.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I want to meet someone who loves me more.]
[We hope Hyeok Jin can find his love soon]
[At the intersection of choices]
[Who will be the next to choose?]
[Taichi's final choice is?]
[Taichi: But I have something I want to tell you first.]
[Taichi: At this stage,]
["I don't think
I'm interested in you romantically..."]
[He's not romantically interested
in Yun Jae]
[Oh Min Seong: Who are you calling?]
[Taichi: I'm still thinking about it.]
[Oh Min Seong: Don't call me.]
[Taichi: I won't call you.]
Don't call me.
Can't I give up?
[Min Seong makes it hard
for him to approach]
[Taichi is still not sure about love]
[Where is Taichi's heart
pointing towards?]
[There's another man
who's finding it hard to make a choice]
[Who is Yun Jae's final choice?]
When did you get here?
[Since the first time they met,
Hyun Jun left a deep impression on him]
-Here? -Yes.
Since I've been here?
I don't know.
[Cho Yun Jae: What do you think I should do
to get Hyun Jun's attention?]
I think he's quite slow.
[He has a lot on his mind about Hyun Jun]
No. He reads the room quickly.
-Hyun Jun? -Yes.
He's actually observing everything.
[And for Hyun Jun,
he tried to muster up his courage]
["Hold my hand."]
[Cho Yun Jae: It's been so tiring.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Actually, I'm really tired.]
I don't know.
[Cho Yun Jae: I don't know. Anyway,]
["I think I still like you the most.
Even though I said those things."]
I don't know what I was thinking.
[In the end,
Hyun Jun didn't understand his feelings]
[To him, love is a wall
that can't be crossed]
[Will Yun Jae muster up his courage again
and fight for Hyun Jun?]
[Taichi: I didn't choose anyone in the final selection.]
[Taichi: In Men's House, I wasn't really]
[Taichi: romantically interested in anyone here.]
[He put his love diary
into the nameless mailbox]
[Taichi: I came to this show to find someone to date,]
[Taichi: yet I made this choice.]
[Taichi: It's a pity, but]
[Taichi: I made this choice which is true to my heart.]
[Q. Do you feel any regret
for your final choice?]
[Taichi: Of course, it was a pity.]
[Taichi: I came on this show to find a real partner.]
[Taichi: To get this result, it's quite a pity, but]
[Taichi: I tried my best. So I want to tell myself I did well]
[Taichi: and that I did well.]
[Taichi: At the same time it's quite a pity. I felt fifty-fifty in that sense.]
[Taichi: But I was really determined]
[Taichi: to not leave alone.]
[Another man
has given up his final choice]
[He put his 7 days of sincerity
into the nameless mailbox]
[Cho Yun Jae: I can guess the result.]
[Cho Yun Jae: The person I am interested in was very obvious about it.]
[Cho Yun Jae: When he feels burdened, he'd take the initiative to move away.]
[Cho Yun Jae: He probably wanted to draw a clear line.]
[Cho Yun Jae: And I also know that
Hyun Jun wouldn't choose me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: In any way, I might put him in a tight spot.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Hyun Jun and Sun Wook took the initiative
to come and talk to me.]
[Cho Yun Jae: Seeing them trying so hard,]
[Cho Yun Jae: I think I've met very nice people.]
[Cho Yun Jae: I'm most grateful to Sun Wook,
and I feel sorry too.]
[Cho Yun Jae: With Hyun Jun...]
With Hyun Jun.
Yes.
[Short but passionate heart flutters]
I think this is when his heart flutters the most.
This.
[Putting all the moments into his memories
and saying goodbye...]
[Sun Wook comes to the final choice place]
[Who's the man walking to Sun Wook?]
[Su Min chose Sun Wook]
[Kim Su Min: I really want to cheer for him.]
[Kim Su Min: Because I still like him.
So I think I should choose him]
[Kim Su Min: with my feelings.]
[Kim Su Min: So I chose him in the end.]
[Kim Sun Wook]
[Kim Su Min: I kept smiling awkwardly.]
[Kim Su Min: I felt lost.]
[Kim Su Min: Seeing him smiling in front of me made me very happy.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello?]
[Kim Su Min: I had a lot of fun these days.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Me too. Thanks to you.]
[Kim Su Min: Yes, you look so happy.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Seeing you here, I'm surprised.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Because of you, I had a lot of fun.]
["Yes, be happy..."]
[Kim Sun Wook: Okay.]
[Kim Su Min: I think we should follow our hearts.]
[Kim Su Min: So I called you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I see.]
["I'm going to keep
showing my interest in you..."]
["Will he get hurt?
I was worried about that."]
["Let's go on a date."]
[Kim Sun Wook: A proper date?]
[Kim Su Min: I want you to be happy no matter what.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm happy now.]
[Kim Su Min: Shall we take some photos?]
[Kim Sun Wook: Shall we?]
[Kim Su Min: I'll take one for you.]
[Su Min hopes that Sun Wook
will always be happy]
Like this? Like this?
-A little to the front. -Like this? Like this? Like this?
[Kim Su Min: Bye.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Bye.]
[Su Min leaves no regrets whether coming to
show his love or turning to leave]
[Kim Su Min: I feel relieved now.]
[Kim Su Min: Because this was a big challenge in my life.]
[Kim Su Min: I made many attempts.]
[Kim Su Min: It was a period of time]
[Kim Su Min: where I could get by with more courage.]
[Kim Su Min: I feel great.]
[Kim Su Min: I think I've done something. So I'm proud of myself.]
[Kim Sun Wook: First of all, when I was waiting alone,]
[Kim Sun Wook: I was sure he'd come.]
[Waiting with confidence]
[Hyun Jun showed up as Sun Wook believed]
[Kim Sun Wook: He walked with big strides from afar.]
[Kim Sun Wook: My heart fluttered and I was happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Hello.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Do I still look funny?]
[Kim Sun Wook: A little?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Me?]
[Kim Sun Wook: A little.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hello.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Did you wait long?]
[Kim Sun Wook: A little.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I chose you in the final choice.]
[Lee Hyun Jun]
[Chose Hyun Jun with no doubt]
[Kim Sun Wook: I chose Hyun Jun. Because]
[Kim Sun Wook: as soon as I came here,
I was interested in him.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's how it was from the beginning.
Then, the more I know him,]
[Kim Sun Wook: the more I think he is a good person.]
[Kim Sun Wook: And I like people who are shy]
[Kim Sun Wook: and reserved.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Because most of them]
[Kim Sun Wook: are actually filled with emotions on the inside.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I prefer this kind of people.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That's why he's attracted me more.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I chose you too.]
[His interest leaned towards Sun Wook
bit by bit]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I chose Sun Wook because]
[Lee Hyun Jun: we've confirmed each other's feelings.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Right from the start,
he's also showed a lot of interest in me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: He cared for me too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: That's why I chose him.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What's wrong? Do I look like a robot again?]
[Kim Sun Wook: No, I'm just happy.]
["I like you a lot."]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you for liking me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Hey, what's with that reply?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Am I wrong?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You're doing this again.]
[Kim Sun Wook: At times like this...]
[Lee Hyun Jun: How about times like this?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I got it. Thank god.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Why are you laughing like that?]
[Kim Sun Wook: I'm laughing because I'm happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Thank you.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Thank you, too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I can feel it all.
Though you put it this way in words.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'm glad you can feel it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But I have something for you.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What is it?]
[Lee Hyun Jun: "Hyun Jun, I like you a lot"?]
[12/9—Hyun Jun, I like you a lot.
-Sun Wook]
[How Hyun Jun acts when he gets bolder]
["I like you too."]
[Lee Hyun Jun: My heart fluttered and I was really happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: He was standing above looking at me.
He's so small and he's so cute.]
[Kim Sun Wook: My heart fluttered, of course. That he did that in the open.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought, "Oh, he's mustered up some courage,"
and thought that's cute.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It's cold. Let's go in.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Let's go.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Yes, I was happy.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: To be able to become a couple—a match—
with a friend I like.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I thought we should get along well.]
[Kim Sun Wook: When we became a couple, I was really happy.]
[Kim Sun Wook: That this person's final choice is me—
that his final conclusion is me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But this is not the end but the start.]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's different out there
as compared to being in here.]
[Kim Sun Wook: So, we need to adjust to each other.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I thought about things more realistically.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I think we'll get along well.]
[Kim Sun Wook: We will overcome it bickering with each other.]
[Shy]
[Kim Sun Wook: Let's take photos together.]
[Making memories together]
Like this.
It's going to break.
Be careful.
[Lee Hyun Jun: Not bad, right?]
[Kim Sun Wook: You look good on camera.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: You too.]
[Kim Sun Wook: But I can feel it too.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: What?]
[Kim Sun Wook: That you think of me positively.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Oh, so you felt it.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I thought you didn't feel it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I can feel it all.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Smile.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: 1, 2, 3!]
[Lee Hyun Jun: Say something before you take it.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Okay, I'll tell you next time.]
[I hope you can be happy together
every moment...]
[Many people are enjoying happy moments]
[Among them, the person waiting for
the last man is?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I chose Min Seong.]
[Oh Min Seong]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Because I like Min Seong. So I chose him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What should I say to Min Seong?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I've been thinking about it.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: So before I came here, in the car,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I used my phone to jot down what I should say.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I thought a lot too.]
[Oh Min Seong: My final choice's got to be Hyeong Jun.]
[Oh Min Seong: Because I like him.
Who else should I choose?]
[Oh Min Seong: Of course I should choose the person I like.]
[Walking towards Hyeong Jun without any concerns]
[Oh Min Seong: I just think it's good. Everything is good.]
[Oh Min Seong: So he chose me. That's what I thought.]
[Oh Min Seong: I don't know either. It was an interesting feeling.]
[Oh Min Seong: But it's a good feeling.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's a good feeling.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's great.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I thought he would come.
I was happy to see him coming.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Mm... I was really happy.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I missed you so much.]
[Oh Min Seong: I missed you so much.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Quite a lot?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Why are you dressed so thinly?]
[Oh Min Seong: I have to look cool.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I missed him a lot,
so I couldn't help but hug him.]
[Oh Min Seong: I thought my heart stopped beating.]
[Oh Min Seong: His actions like this are so cute.]
[Oh Min Seong: How could this be? Don't you think he's cute?]
[Oh Min Seong: Don't you think he's cute doing things like that?
He doesn't seem like someone who'd do something like that.]
[Oh Min Seong: Your hands are so cold.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I've been waiting for a long time.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Your hands are too cold.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Do you like me a lot?]
[Oh Min Seong: Of course.]
[Oh Min Seong: That's why I'm doing this to you. All this time.]
[Oh Min Seong: What's your name? Sorry.]
My name is Lee Hyeong Jun.
[Min Seong fell for Hyeong Jun
even before remembering his name]
Send the name of the person you want to go on a 1:1 date with.
As soon as I saw that, I wrote Hyeong Jun's name right away.
More than saying I'm interested in him, I like him.
[His interest that he expressed
only towards Hyeong Jun]
I think that is the right expression.
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I have something for you.]
[Oh Min Seong: What is it?]
[Oh Min Seong: What is this?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's shaking its tail at you.]
-Isn't it cute? -It's shaking its tail.
[Oh Min Seong: So cute.]
-Isn't it cute? -So cute.
[Oh Min Seong: Is it wagging its tail to me?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: So cute. Where did you get this?]
[Oh Min Seong: You brought things like this, and then things like this too.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: You look like a fish.]
[Oh Min Seong: I don't look like a fish.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Just take it.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: There's something I want to say to you.]
[Oh Min Seong: What is it?]
["Do you want to go out with me?"]
[Oh Min Seong: I was going to say that.]
[Oh Min Seong: Of course I do.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I've never confessed before.]
[Oh Min Seong: Really?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Yeah.]
[Oh Min Seong: Ever?]
[Oh Min Seong: It's an honor.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Is that how you do it?]
[Oh Min Seong: Yes.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I know Min Seong is not good at expressing his love.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But he's been working hard for me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It would be a pity to just end up as a final couple,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: so I thought to make a clear decision.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: So I confessed my love to someone
for the first time in my life.]
[Oh Min Seong: I was going to say that.
But he got ahead of me.]
[Oh Min Seong: He asked me out. That was nice.]
[Oh Min Seong: I was going to say that.]
[Oh Min Seong: I want to date him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Didn't you say you like to kiss?]
[Oh Min Seong: Mmhmm. But you said you wouldn't kiss me.]
[Oh Min Seong: Didn't you say you wouldn't kiss me?]
[Oh Min Seong: Ah, so warm.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Let's meet outside every day.]
[Oh Min Seong: Yeah, this is really amazing.]
You're flirting, aren't you?
[They dated on the first day Min Seong joined]
No, that's not it.
It's really small.
[The two of them stuck together
every single day]
You have to take photos from the top.
If you don't edit it, I'll kill you.
[Oh Min Seong: Meeting him here—]
[Oh Min Seong: I think it's fate.]
[Oh Min Seong: I want to spend the rest of my life with him.]
[Oh Min Seong: After leaving here, in our daily lives,]
[Oh Min Seong: I hope we can spend every day happily together.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's finally over. I want to go back quickly]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: and go on a date with Min Seong.]
[We hope your love that came
just like fate can last forever...]
[The men's story that hasn't ended yet]
[Men's House]
[Kim Sun Wook: Can I read it now?]
[Love Diary: 4 December, Thursday
What's your love forecast today? Snowy
What kind of day was today? When I received the phone call?
The person I'm most interested in is: Cho Yun Jae
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[The Love Diary sent to the other half of the couple]
[Love Diary: 5 December, Friday
What's your love forecast today? Cloudy]
[What kind of day is today? I didn't expect to receive so many gifts. It's amazing.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What is this?]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Love Diary: 6 December, Saturday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny
What kind of day was today?
Going to Nami Island with Sun Wook was so much fun. A boat date felt so novel.]
[Kim Sun Wook: His interest in me kept rising.]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Love Diary: 7 December, Sunday
What's your love forecast today? Cloudy
What kind of day was today? Group date, bowling was fun. I felt so relieved after having a sincere talk with Yun Jae.
The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Kim Sun Wook: Oh, from this point on he stopped writing my last name.]
[Love Diary
Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.]
[Kim Sun Wook: What's up with this question mark? Yun Jae question mark.]
[Sun Wook] [Bowling] [Yun Jae?]
[Kim Sun Wook: So cute.]
[Love Diary: 8 December, Monday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[Kim Sun Wook: His interest rose bit by bit.]
[What kind of day was today? I’m so happy I found out how Sun Wook feels. I also cleared things up with Yun Jae Hyung, so I feel much better now.
The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Kim Sun Wook: Oh, was I just not expecting much?]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[Kim Sun Wook: Whoa, I thought we still had to write down our interest rankings on the last day.]
[What kind of day was today? It's the last day at Men's House.
I'm both happy and sad to leave; I'm so glad I got to meet someone who likes me.]
[Kim Sun Wook: He intentionally didn't fill it all out]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Kim Sun Wook
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Kim Sun Wook: There's half of it left.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Surprisingly, it's similar to mine.]
[Kim Sun Wook: I felt yet again that Hyun Jun is someone easy to read.]
[Kim Sun Wook: He wrote down the things he told me]
[Kim Sun Wook: through letter or speech,]
[Kim Sun Wook: so it's more touching than I thought.]
[Kim Sun Wook: Is he watching mine downstairs too?]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's over.]
[Love Diary: 6 December, Saturday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[What kind of day was today? Went on my first date. It was so much fun.
What kind of fun date should we go on next time?
The person I'm most interested in is: Lee Hyun Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: None]
[Love Diary: 7 December, Sunday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny
What kind of day was today?
I talked a lot with Hyun Jun today, and I'm so happy.
He called me for the first time. It feels like a dream...]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Lee Hyun Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Lee Hyun Jun: His handwriting is really ugly.]
[Love Diary: 8 December, Monday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[What kind of day was today? Had a pleasant date with Su Min. I'm so happy I shared what was truly on my mind.
I also told Hyeon Jun Hyung how I felt. This is great, I feel like I'm going to like him even more!
The person I'm most interested in is: Lee Hyeon Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Love Diary: Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
The meat was delicious, let's get along well. Lee Hyeon Jun. It's over now!
His Man 4: It's so cold! I was so happy while swimming]
[Lee Hyun Jun: It was almost all about me.]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I'll remember everything.]
[Love Diary: 4 December, Thursday
What's your love forecast today? Cloudy]
[Oh Min Seong: The person he's least interested in is Jae Ha?]
[What kind of day was today?
The person I'm most interested in is: Han Gyeol
The person I'm least interested in is: Jae Ha]
[Oh Min Seong: The person he's most interested in is Han Gyeol?]
[Oh Min Seong: Gosh.]
[Love Diary: Now that the day is over, please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words.
So sleepy, so annoyed, so annoyed, so annoyed, the food was good.]
[Oh Min Seong: He was annoyed on the 5th day.]
[Love Diary: 5 December, Friday
What's your love forecast today? Rainy
The person I'm most interested in is: Min Seong
The person I'm least interested in is: Jae Ha]
[Oh Min Seong: What is this star?]
[Love Diary: 5 December, Friday
What's your love forecast today? Rainy
The person I'm most interested in is: Min Seong
The person I'm least interested in is: Jae Ha]
[Oh Min Seong: Is that star for me?]
[Oh Min Seong: So cute.]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Cloudy
What kind of day was today? Why isn't he feeling well? It's weighing on my mind
The person I'm most interested in is: Min Seong
The person I'm least interested in is: Everyone except Min Seong]
[Oh Min Seong: It seems like he cares about me quite a bit?]
[Oh Min Seong: He's really transparent.]
[Oh Min Seong: So cute. Very good.]
[Oh Min Seong: As we get to the back of it, it's all about me.]
[Love Diary: 8 December, Monday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny]
[Oh Min Seong: He was thinking of me after all; he let me know that.]
[What kind of day was today? His hands were so warm
The person I'm most interested in is: Min Seong
The person I'm least interested in is: Han Gyeol]
[Oh Min Seong: He said my hands were warm.]
[Love Diary: Now that the day is over,
Please leave behind the thoughts filling your heart through drawings and words. Missing him]
[Oh Min Seong: He said he missed me; this is great.]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't expect him to care so much about me.]
[Oh Min Seong: He didn't show it on the surface.]
[Oh Min Seong: He always has a poker face. That's why I think so.]
[Oh Min Seong: It's nice. This is another twist.]
[Love Diary: 5 December, Friday
What's your love forecast today? What kind of day was today?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Ha]
[Today is the first day moving into Men's House. I'm nervous and excited.
The one who caught my eye at first sight was Hyeong Jun. Why am I attracted to him?
I guess I like that kind of look, haha.
The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: None]
[Love Diary: December 6, Saturday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny, Thundering]
[What kind of day was today? Had a 1:1 date with Hyeong Jun today.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Ah, I totally didn't expect this.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: From the first day?]
[The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: Jae Ha]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Amazing.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What should I do?]
[Love Diary: December 7, Sunday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny
What kind of day was today? Hyeong Jun chose me today, so we went on a date
To be honest, after what happened yesterday, I didn't think we could have such a happy date.
After the date, all my bad moods swept away. But because I didn't want any misunderstandings,
we had a sincere talk. Anyway, I just like Hyeong Jun!
The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Love Diary: 8 December, Monday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny. What kind of day was today?
I held hands with Hyeong Jun today.
And then he took the initiative and told me to hug him; my heart almost stopped beating.
The house date was wonderful. After the date at home, we went out for dinner in the evening.
The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun
The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Love Diary: 9 December, Tuesday
What's your love forecast today? Sunny. What kind of day was today?
I was very lucky today and got a date chance. Actually, I only wanted to go on a date with Hyeong Jun,
but I had to pick two people, so I also chose Su Min. Because I wasn't feeling well,
I couldn't participate enthusiastically, but I missed Hyeong Jun so much!
The person I'm most interested in is: Hyeong Jun. The person I'm least interested in is: X]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What? It's all about me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: What should I do?]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's the first time I'm crying 'cause I'm so happy.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: He was very naughty around me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: But reading the content on here,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: rather than it being naughty,]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I feel warm.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I did a good thing confessing to him.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I will express myself as much as]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Min Seong has been trying his best to.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I have to say more nice things to him. That's what I think.]
[Men's House]
[The true feelings of the men after a passionate week]
["A place where the love cells are awakened."]
[Kim Su Min: To be able to express my feelings to someone?]
[Kim Su Min: That courage, honesty—]
[Kim Su Min: be it being apologetic, thankful, or happy—]
[Kim Su Min: I can express them more.]
[Kim Su Min: I want to fall in love the way I want—]
[Kim Su Min: slowly seeping into one's heart.]
["The door to another opportunity."]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: This is the first time I've come out]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: through such a huge platform.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I've got all kinds of opportunities here.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: I think I'll have more opportunities in the future.]
["Power"]
[Kim Han Gyeol: With "His Man," I've grown.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I've always thought I was not good at]
[Kim Han Gyeol: the important part of love.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: I learned a lot communicating with various people]
[Kim Han Gyeol: coming here.]
In various aspects...
["It's a big step"]
[Taichi: I had a lot of conversations with myself.]
[Taichi: I thought a lot too.]
[Taichi: Thanks to that I gained a lot of experience]
[Taichi: and I learned more about myself.]
[Taichi: I'm really happy to have been on this program.]
["Not 'His Man', but 'My Man'"]
[Kim Sun Wook: It's not "His Man" anymore.]
["It's 'My Man'"]
["Love and hate, love and hate"]
[Oh Min Seong: To be honest, it's a lie if I say it's not tough here.]
[Oh Min Seong: But after time passes, it will become a good memory.]
[Oh Min Seong: I didn't expect to come back.]
I met my fate
and found a good person.
["A good fate, a good person"]
[Lee Hyun Jun: I think I had a good time through this program.]
["A huge energy that helped me
become an adult."]
[Kim Sun Wook: When we are out of here,
we should still meet.]
[Kim Sun Wook: We must meet.]
[Taichi: It was very nice to meet someone I get along so well with like Jae Yun here.]
[Taichi: To be able to meet a nice friend makes me very happy.]
[Taichi: Although it was a little difficult, I had fun.]
[Taichi: Jae Yun was a big part of that.]
[Taichi: I want to thank him.]
[Kim Su Min: I think I'll remember it for the rest of my life.]
[Kim Su Min: It was a big challenge.]
[Kim Su Min: It was also a group of good people too.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Hyeok Jin, I learned a lot about accepting love.]
[Kim Han Gyeol: Thank you.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: In Men's House which we call a typhoon,]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: when I talked to Han Gyeol, it felt like
I was in the eye of the typhoon.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: It was really quiet.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Thank you for letting me rest even for a moment.]
[Eum Hyeok Jin: Thank you for helping me calm down.
I want to say something like this.]
[Oh Min Seong: A romantic relationship that's like friendship.]
[Oh Min Seong: A sweet one too.]
[Oh Min Seong: I want to have a relaxing relationship. With Hyeong Jun.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: It's the same for both Min Seong and me.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: Don't be too tired. Lean on each other.]
[Lee Hyeong Jun: I hope we can have a good relationship.]
[Kim Su Min]
[Eum Hyeok Jin]
[Lee Hyeong Jun]
[Oh Min Seong]
[Cho Yun Jae]
[Lee Hyun Jun]
[Kim Sun Wook]
[Kim Han Gyeol]
[Taichi]
[Park Jae Ha]
[Lee Hyeok Jin]
[His Man 4]