(Minseok) ⟨I was chased out of a South Korean chaebol family after being accused of embezzlement→
In despair, he met Momoko, a doctor at the clinic, and fell in love ⟩
⟨Meanwhile, my Korean mother and brother suddenly came to Japan⟩
>> Korean
(Minseok) ⟨He has announced that he will close the hotel in Tokyo⟩
(Minseok) ⟨To protect the hotel→
I decided to quit on my own, but...⟩
(Minseok) Everything is okay now.
⟨Thanks to my brother who believed in me→
I thought everything was resolved ⟩
⟨but…⟩
(Momoko) Minseok-san, stay strong!
Mr. Minseok!
(footsteps)
(sound of door closing)
(Momoko) Hahaha...｡
(footsteps)
(Takuto) Momoko!
Are you okay?
(Momoko) Min-seok... Min-seok was stabbed and his mother told him.
I was unconscious and couldn't stop the bleeding...
(Takuto) Calm down and take a deep breath.
(Momoko) Minseok was stabbed by his mother.
My brother was also taken in for questioning.
(Takuto) What's going on?
(sound of door opening)
(peach) Mr.
>> We are doing everything we can, but the wound is deep and there is significant damage to the liver.
I urgently need a living liver transplant →
Do you have family members who can help?
Preferably a blood relative.
(Momoko) Blood relatives...｡
(Doctor) If you are waiting for a donor other than your family →
Procedures may also take some time.
Until then, I will be connected with a liver support device →
We cannot guarantee that you will be saved.
(Momoko) That's it...
(Takuto) It's okay.
I'll do something.
Momoko, stay by Minchok's side.
(Peach) Takuto.
♪～
(Doctor) [We cannot guarantee that you will be saved]
(Peach) Takuto.
♪～
>> \I'm coming in/ \Please/
(All) Ichi ni San.
(Sound of electrocardiograph)
(Doctor) The entire liver will be removed for transplantation.
Thank you very much. (All of us) Thank you.
(Doctor) Cooper Sessi. >> \Sessi Gauze/
♪～
(sound of door opening)
The surgery was completed successfully.
(Momoko) Ah, thank you.
>>The rest depends on your own efforts.
(Momoko) Ah, good!
>> Excuse me. (Momoko) Ah...｡
Ah...｡
(Takuto) Momoko It's from here.
There's no point in it if you collapse.
(Momoko) Yes.
(Sound of electrocardiograph)
(Momoko) Huh. (Sound of electrocardiograph)
(Momoko) Minseok-san.
Teacher, I woke up!
(Doctor) Kim Min-seok, do you understand?
Kim Min Seok.
I had organ transplant surgery →
You will be staying in a private room for severe cases for a while.
Because the hematoma is pressing on a thick bundle of nerves →
I think it will be difficult to walk at first →
Let's do our best in rehabilitation.
trying to say something
what?
(Minseok) She is...
Was it okay?
>> It's okay.
You were by my side the whole time.
(Minseok) Good.
>> Korean
(sound of handcuffs being removed)
(Eri) Poor person.
Me and you too→
I couldn't get what I wanted most.
So somewhere→
I felt like I understood how you felt.
(Eri) But you did something that can't be undone.
Even though you've come this far, you still haven't noticed.
A really pitiful person.
Goodbye.
Korean
(Momoko) Also, an eye mask and towel.
Oh, and this is the required smartphone charger.
This is from the director.
A crossword puzzle to kill time.
(Minseok) Even something like that? thank you.
(Momoko) It seems that having this will make your stay in the hospital a lot more satisfying.
(Minseok) Momoko-san, are you okay with taking time off from work?
(Momoko) The director was also worried and told me to stay by Minseok's side.
Everyone is waiting for Minseok.
Me too, until Minseok regains consciousness →
I didn't feel like I was alive.
(Minseok) While I was sleeping, I had a dream about my father.
(Momoko) Korean? (Minseok) Yes.
When my father collapsed, he was trying to say something to me →
Even though I'm desperately trying to convey something →
I didn't understand.
A dream at that time.
In the end, what do you want to say even in your dreams?
I didn't understand though.
(knock)
(Momoko) Yes.
(Takuto) Yo, you look good.
Mincheok's brother →
They say things like “Get the best room”→
I prepared it specially here.
(Minseok) Ah... (Takuto) It's me.
(Minseok) Thank you.
(Momoko) Takuto is so condescending.
(Takuto) Desa→
Actually, there's someone I need to meet.
(Takuto) Sorry to have kept you waiting.
(Excellent) Photo.
(Minseok) Why?
(Takuto) The person who transplanted organs to Minchok was →
It was my father.
(Minseok) Huh?
No, it shouldn't be like that...
Because at that time...
〔father! father! ]
〔father! ]
(Takuto) 23 years ago, Mincheok's parents →
I realized this when I looked at the medical records from the time of the accident.
(Takuto's voice) Dad's medical record states the hospital he was transferred to.
Mincheok didn't even attend the funeral →
I was worried that I didn't even know where the grave was.
At the hospital I was transferred to, I was asked to tell me the story of that time.
(Minseok) Why?
>> Can we talk for a moment?
♪～
It was bad to stay silent.
I know that I'm not allowed to come out and apologize now.
(Minseok) I'm a little confused...
(Minseok) What do you mean?
>> 23 years ago →
After being seriously injured in an accident...
I can no longer walk →
Pretend you're dead →
I wanted to let go of Teru.
(Minseok) Why?
>> To live with light→
I didn't know where to turn for help.
I also had my own weaknesses.
(Minseok) So→
Did you leave me with my father?
(Yu's voice) If it's Jeonghoon who I trust the most →
I thought I could entrust the light to you.
It was really bad.
I've wanted to visit you many times.
Two years have passed since the accident →
I've been to Seoul.
But I couldn't call out.
Teru is in a new place →
Trying to live as Kim Min Seok...
Because I was desperately trying to live as Kim Min-seok.
I thought I couldn't get in the way.
Whatever you say will be an excuse.
But →
Not even a day, not even a second →
I am Teruno...
(Minseok) I am →
This is Kim Min-seok.
I can't go back to Teru Aoki now.
You are my little self →
How much I wanted to see my deceased parents...
How lonely I felt→
Have you never thought about it?
♪～
(Minseok) Thank you for saving my life.
But now...
(Minseok) I don't know what to say.
Sorry.
♪～
(cry)
(sound of door opening)
(Momoko) Minseok-san.
(Minseok) Thank you, Takuto-san.
(Takuto) Who is your father?
(Minseok) I talked.
But my father is a Korean father.
My life was saved by everyone.
I will do my best in rehabilitation and get well soon.
(Physical Therapist) I'll bend it slightly.
(Physical therapist) Do you feel uncomfortable?
(Minseok) It's okay. (Physical therapist) Yeah.
(Kazami) Would you like to eat the pudding I gave you?
(Momoko) Ah, I'm going to Yamashiro Memorial Hospital.
(Mika) Huh, Momo-chan-sensei, how about some pudding?
(Momoko) Ah, Mika-chan, you can eat.
I was thinking of delivering the children's letters to Min-seok.
>> I'll bring it later because I'm on my way home.
(Momoko) Ah, no, but...
(Kazami) Ah, Momo-chan, then she was transferred to Yamashiro→
Could you please ask me how my patient is doing?
(Momoko) Okay, then I'll go!
>> Even I can do that much.
Mika-chan.
It's a stable insensitivity. >> Huh, what do you mean?
Do you want to take a break?
(Minseok) Ah, it's still okay.
Are we causing any inconvenience to you?
(Natsume) No, after the deputy manager left →
Who do you think is the least energetic?
(Minseok) Who is it?
>> I'm the manager. (Minseok) Huh?
(Mizushima) Well… Look, manager.
In Korea →
I heard that this kind of thing is common for visits, so yes.
(Minseok) Thank you.
>> Yeah, I'm in trouble if you don't fill that hole in my job as soon as possible.
I don't know.
(Physical Therapist) Se-no.
(Minseok) Ah...
(Physical Therapist) Put your butt out in front of you right away.
Ah! (Minseok) Sorry.
>>Okay, let's finish here for today.
♪～
Korean
(Kyunhua) Huh…｡
Ha!
♪～
〔Yeah〕
(Junghoon) [Hahaha…]
(sound of closing diary)
(cry)
The wound is healing well.
(Minseok) It's all thanks to you, teacher.
thank you.
>> I would like him to continue to work hard on his rehabilitation even after being discharged from the hospital.→
There's one thing I have to tell you.
As the pressure is prolonged and the paralysis is becoming fixed →
Recovery of walking may be difficult.
(Minseok) Huh?
>> In that case, it can also be used in daily life such as excretion and bathing →
I think you will need assistance.
(Minseok) But if you do rehabilitation, you'll be fine, right?
>> Honestly, looking at what's going on now →
The situation is indescribable.
(Takuto) Momoko, can you open it? (Momoko) Yeah, OK.
Please be careful on the stairs. (Takuto) Thank you.
Let's go, Minseok. (Minseok) Yes. (Takuto) Good.
(Momoko) Yay!
Yes, OK. (Takuto) Well then, I'll put down the minchok.
(Minseok) Thank you. (Takuto) Okay, I'll go slowly.
Se-no.
Good.
(Minseok) Thank you.
(Takuto) OK. (Minseok) Thank you.
(Knock) (Momoko) Konkonkon Can I come in?
(Haru) Shi~!
(Takuto) It's good.
Mincheok, don't look behind you yet.
(Minseok) Ah.
(Takuto) Not yet, not yet.
Good.
Se-no! (Momoko) Let's go!
(All) Minseok-san, welcome back!
yeah? >> Mr. Minseok?
(Minseok) Ah...｡
I was surprised and happy.
(Takuto) Great success everyone!
(All) Yay!
(Child) Is your foot okay? (Minseok) Yeah, it's okay.
>> Wheelchair looks cool. (Minseok) Eh, really?
(Takuto) That's cool. (Child) Yeah.
(Kyoko) This much? (Chica) Kyoko-chan is a little normal.
(Kyoko) Normal? (Momoko) Ah, I understand, Chika-chan.
Do you want me to do it like Minseok?
(Chica) Yeah.
(Momoko) Minseok's presentation is special.
(Takuto) Whoa, is it finally my turn?
(Yusuke) Takuto is no good because he has no sense!
(Takuto) Hey, what is NG?
(Minseok) Ah, I'll do it.
Can I come by for a while? Sorry for the back.
(Takuto) Then everyone will pass through Minchok, so spread out.
(Minseok) Take care of your feet. >> Yes.
(Takuto) Let's go.
(Takuto) It looks like it's going to be difficult to get inside.
(Momoko) Ah, then should I have you do it from your side?
I mean, it's about time we redecorated this place.
I originally thought it was small.
>> Yes, that's right.
(Minseok) Sorry for making such a fuss.
(Takuto) What are you talking about? I'm so NG.
Please, Mincheok.
(Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) Yes, Minseok-san. (Minseok) Thank you.
(Momoko) Where should I start?
Ah, is this it?
(Minseok) Oh, sorry. (Momoko) Yes, please.
(Minseok) Thank you. (Momoko) Yes.
(Minseok) Then... >> Ah, is this it?
(Minseok) Oh, sorry.
(Child) It's home!
(Minseok) Sorry it took so long.
>> It's okay, it's okay, I don't care because I'm the main character! Hey.
Then I'll have it!
(All) Itadakimasu!
(Kyoko) Please do this too. (Momoko) Ah, thank you.
Hey, sister.
Mika-chan, could you please help me out?
(Child: Kazami) Yes, thank you for the meal.
Well done.
(Takuto) This is suspicious.
(Minseok) Should I put down the dishes? >> Yeah.
I will lower it for Minseok-san.
(Minseok) Is it okay? >> Yes!
(Minseok) Thank you.
>> Do you need water for your medicine? I'll bring it to you.
(Minseok) Thank you. (Yusuke) Yeah.
Momo-chan, please add some water. (Momoko) Yes, yes.
(Takuto) He's more considerate than me.
(Momoko) Yes, please. >> Yes. (Momoko) Thank you.
(Minseok) Ah. (Takuto) Yusuke!
(Momoko) Huh!
(Takuto) Is Minchok okay too? Please show me a little.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
(Minseok) Ah. (Momoko) Minseok! OK?
(Minseok) Yes, Yusuke-kun?
>> It's okay.
(Minseok) Ah... (Momoko) Minseok, I'll move it.
(Minseok) Excuse me. (Momoko) Se~no Ugh!
(Minseok) Ah, are you okay? >> An-chan, hold the wheelchair.
Ah, yes. (Takuto) Let's go.
Se-no.
(Minseok) Ah...
Sorry, please grab me.
(Takuto) I'll grab some clothes. (Minseok) Yes.
(Takuto) Se~no. (Momoko) Se~no.
(Takuto) Ah!
(Minseok) Ha ha ha.
Huh… hah hah…｡
I'm sorry.
>> Korean
(Kyoko) What are you looking at?
(Momoko) ``Summary of places you can go with a wheelchair.''
There is something like this.
Clinics also need to be barrier-free.
Ah! It's already that time! Hey~
I was asked to come up with a menu for the children's cafeteria by tomorrow.
>> Momoko.
(Momoko) Huh?
>>If you have any trouble, let me know.
>> Big sister, I'll help you.
(Momoko) Yes, thank you.
(sound of door closing)
♪～
(Momoko) That's all for today.
>> Please take care.
(Momoko) Take care.
>> Momo-chan sensei. (Momoko) Ah.
>> I'm amazing.
I had a friend that I was close with in high school →
We always played in groups of three.
Two people other than me have been dating for a long time →
I didn't realize it until they announced that they were getting married.
(Momoko) Um...｡
>> In other words, I'm extremely insensitive.
Momo-chan-sensei was so insensitive that I noticed it→
It's obvious that he's dating Minseok.
It was written on my back that I wanted to go on a date early today.
(Momoko) Sorry.
>> Please go, I'll be back eventually.
(Momoko) Thank you. I will definitely repay this favor...
>> With strawberry daifuku! (Momoko) Thank you!
>> Strawberry Daifuku!
(Kazami) You finally noticed!
This is the limit of insensitivity.
welcome.
(Momoko) Good evening.
(Salesperson) Please excuse me.
(Momoko) Sorry to have kept you waiting. (Minseok) No.
(Momoko) Thank you. >> Please take your time.
(Momoko) Is this a restaurant where the menu is all in French?
(Minseok) Japanese is also available. (Momoko) Good.
(Minseok) What do you want to eat?
There are also many wines.
(Momoko) Wow~ Is it okay?
(Minseok) Of course.
(Momoko) Hmm.
It's a combination of flavors that I've never had before.
What's in this sauce?
Children may also like the taste.
delicious.
Ah, but this is a little too mature.
(Minseok) That was difficult.
(Momoko) I really have to be careful hahaha...｡
Hey, if the earth were to be destroyed tomorrow...
(Minseok) Huh? (Momoko) Minseok finally →
What do you want to eat?
(Minseok) That's sudden.
(Momoko) I always think about this.
(Minseok) Do you have the answer? Momoko's.
(Momoko) Could you please not laugh?
(Minseok) Of course.
(Momoko) I have my sister's usual money-saving recipe.
Come and try this delicious food →
I'm not talking about doing that though. (Minseok) Ah.
(Momoko) The tofu was falling apart and the bean sprouts were falling apart.
It also contains green onions that I grew.
I want to taste each and every one of those things at the end.
Does Minseok have that kind of food too?
(Minseok) Ah, I...
(Knock) (Salesperson) Excuse me.
(Minseok) Ah, it's the main thing. (Momoko) It's the main thing.
(Staff) It's grilled beef fillet Chaliapin style.
(Peach) Foreword withdrawn.
This may be the meal you will have on your last day on earth.
(Momoko) This is also really delicious.
(Minseok) I'm glad you like it.
(Momoko) Next I will take care of Minseok →
I'll take you to a delicious restaurant.
(Minseok) Momoko-san.
I came here today because I wanted to talk to you about something.
(Momoko) Yes, what is it?
(Minseok) It's about my body.
I'll be here forever→
You may not be able to walk.
(Minseok) Returned to Korea and continued rehabilitation →
I'm thinking of working at a company.
(Momoko) That's...
(Minseok) I won't be able to see Momoko again.
(Momoko) Huh?
(Minseok) When Yusuke fell down at the children's cafeteria →
I can't prevent or help in advance →
It was frustrating.
I also fell down and couldn't get up →
I've caused trouble to everyone.
(Momoko) That wasn't Minseok's fault.
(Minseok) That's not all.
Entering the clinic and setting up the food →
I had to borrow everyone's help.
There were many things I couldn't do and I just apologized.
(Momoko) It's a bad situation to have to apologize for something like that.
Minseok isn't bad.
(Minseok) I am now→
I can't even change my clothes by myself.
Even today, my brother helped me →
I was finally able to get dressed.
(Momoko) That's how prepared I am...
(Minseok) Even in the toilet→
I can't go alone.
But if I go back to Korea →
Still for me →
There are things you can do for the company.
(Minseok) Just now →
The last time we talked about what we wanted to eat →
There was something that came to mind.
(Momoko) What?
(Minseok) Cup ramen I ate by the river with Momoko.
(Minseok) It was a taste I don't want to forget.
But →
I have to take Momoko out →
You can also eat cup ramen and lie down by the river →
You can also ride a jet coaster at the amusement park →
You can't just drop by the children's cafeteria.
(Momoko) It's not like that...
Not because I can do that...
I just→
I want to be with Minseok.
(Minseok) When I meet Momoko-san →
There are only things I want to do but can't do →
Floating in my head→
I'm afraid I'll cause trouble for Momoko.
(Momoko) I don't think so.
(Minseok) I am →
Momoko's life →
I want to support your dreams.
But I can't do that.
(Momoko) Minseok-san, that will never happen.
(Minseok) If you came here today, this is the store→
Because even I was able to enter.
(Minseok) Lastly →
Eating delicious food with Momoko →
It's because I wanted to laugh with you.
(Momoko) I don't want to be separated from Minseok-san.
(Minseok) When I'm with Momoko...
(Minseok) I can't stand myself.
(Minseok) I think it's now.
We can go back to our respective paths.
♪～
>> Are you sure you can go home?
(Minseok) Yes.
What I learned here →
I will utilize this information in the future management of Fungum.
>>Not yet→
I told you that there are many things I haven't taught you.
(Minseok) It was a pleasure working with you all →
I won't forget.
Hope you're well.
>> Come with me outside. (Minseok) That's all for the manager.
>> But…｡
(Minseok) Farewell→
Because it will be difficult.
♪～