(Minseok) ⟨I lost my Japanese parents when I was young →
I was adopted by a Korean chaebol family→
Just as I was about to take over as president after my father...⟩
>> Korean
(Kyonhwa) Get out!
(Minseok) ⟨I was chased out of Korea after being accused of embezzlement⟩
⟨In despair, I met Dr. Momoko, a doctor at the clinic...⟩
(Momoko) There are words that I have always cherished.
``There is no tree that will not fall even after being cut 10 times.''
(Minseok) ⟨I learned that she values ​​the same words as I do⟩
(Takuto) Momoko also lost her father in an accident.
(Minseok) A spell to cheer you up.
There is no tree that will not fall after being cut 10 times.
⟨Those are the words I told her 23 years ago⟩
⟨but…⟩
(Momoko) Takuto taught me this.
That's why I'm grateful to Takuto.
(Momoko) What's wrong?
(Minseok) Ah... Ah, no.
(Momoko) I'm sorry I had to send it to you.
(Minseok) No.
(Momoko) Good night then.
(Minseok) Good night.
♪～
(Momoko) Minseok-san.
(Momoko) Thank you very much for today.
(Momoko) See you at the children's cafeteria.
(Minseok) Yes again.
(Momoko) Be careful.
♪～
(Minseok) Huh…｡
(Apricot) Peaches!
(Momoko) \Yes! /
Good morning sister.
(Kyoko) It's not "good morning."
Are you already a 5 year old?
(Momoko) Huh?
>> Make it so muddy!
(Momoko) I'm sorry.
>> What on earth did you do to make it so dirty?
Oh, I even got hurt.
No... So what were you doing there?
(Momoko) [Ah! ]
(Minseok) [Are you okay? Let's go together]
(Kyoko) Hey Momoko, are you listening?
(Momoko) Yes, I'm listening.
Ah, I'll take out the trash!
>> Hey Momoko!
♪～
(Minseok) [“There is no tree that will not fall after being cut 10 times”]
[I have lived my life valuing those words.]
(Momoko) I see...
(Momoko) [To cheer me up when I was in despair→
Takuto told me]
(Minseok) Take the elevator to the 3rd floor and turn right.
(Female) Thank you. (Minseok) Please take your time.
welcome.
(Minseok) Takuto-san.
(Takuto) Oh, as expected, he's so cool looking so stiff.
(Minseok) Ah, no...｡
Why are you here?
(Takuto) Minchok!
What time do you work today?
(Minseok) Huh?
(Takuto) It's almost there, it's almost there, it's almost there.
Good.
(Takuto) Wow, look at it, Minchok.
That's amazing.
The sunset you can see from here is the best.
copper? Did you like it?
(Minseok) Yes.
(Takuto) Doesn't it sound like you were forced to say something?
(Minseok) No...
(Takuto) But Momoko often gets mad at me for being too pushy.
But it's really amazing.
When I look at this sunset, I can't forget what happened.
That's why I really wanted to show it to Mincheok.
(Minseok) Takuto-san.
Did something happen?
(Takuto) You know...
(Takuto) You said you lost your parents at our hospital.
(Minseok) Yes.
(Takuto) What are your parents' names?
Aoki?
(Minseok) Why did you do that?
(Takuto) I still have my old medical records, and I noticed this when I looked at them.
>> [Sound of keyboard hitting]
[Mouse click sound]
(Minseok) Originally, my name was Teru Aoki.
My parents died →
I was adopted by someone who was my biological father's best friend →
I went to Korea.
(Takuto) I see.
(Takuto) Then that must have been Minchok.
(Minseok) Huh?
(Takuto) ``There is no tree that will not fall even after being cut 10 times.''
(Takuto) 23 years ago→
Who taught this word to Momoko?
(Minseok) [Hey, do you know? ]
[Character that will cheer you up]
[There is no tree that will not fall after being cut 10 times]
(Takuto) Actually, me too →
I was there that day.
(Minseok) Huh?
(Takuto) That day I was →
I heard that Momoko's father was taken to our hospital...
(Momoko) [crying]
(Takuto's voice) But...
Look at Momoko crying →
I just couldn't get close.
(Takuto) Until then, I had only seen Momoko smiling.
(Takuto's voice) While I'm doing that→
A boy around the same age came →
I sat next to Momoko.
(Momoko) [crying]
[Thank you] (Minseok) [Yeah]
(Nurse) [Teru-kun, I'm sorry, but could you hurry up and come here please? ]
(Takuto's voice) After a while, a nurse brought the boy away.
(Takuto's voice) Then...
(Momoko) [Sound of falling]
(Takuto) [Peach! peach! 〕
(Momoko) [Haa haa...]
(Takuto's voice) Momoko developed a fever and collapsed.
(Takuto's voice) He continued to sleep like that for a long time.
(Momoko) [Haa haa...]
>> [Sound of door opening]
(Female) [Kyoko-chan, are you okay? ]
(Kyoko) [Yes]
[Sound of door closing]
(Takuto) [Peach? 〕
(Peach) [Takuto...]
[Did you stay for a long time? ]
(Takuto) [Yeah]
(Momoko) [Thank you]
[Hey Takuto]
(Takuto) [Hmm? ]
(Momoko) [“There is no tree that will not fall even after being cut 10 times”]
[I'll always remember these words]
(Takuto) [Yeah]
(Takuto) The shock of losing my father →
Because I had a fever and was in bed →
Momoko's memory was confused.
but….
I thought I would remember it someday.
I wasn't the one who taught you those words.
But it remained the same even when I became an adult.
[Kampai! ] (Momoko) [Kampai! ]
[Mmmm, delicious]
(Takuto) [Wow, the training was tough]
(Momoko) [Yes, but finally →
It felt like I was standing at the starting line to become a doctor.]
(Takuto) [Of course] (Momoko) [Yeah]
(Takuto) [Hey...] (Momoko) [Takuto: Do ​​you remember? ]
(Takuto) [Hmm? ]
(Momoko) [Words that my father said to me when he was in an accident]
[“There is no tree that will not fall after being cut 10 times”]
[Because of these words, I did my best without giving up.]
[I'm embarrassed to say something again, but→
Thank you, Takuto]
〔what? what up? ]
(Takuto) [No]
(Takuto's voice) Momoko always thought those were my words.
(Takuto) You know...
(Takuto) Could you please shut up?
(Takuto) I don't want Momoko to go through the trouble of reminding me.
The sadness of losing my father that day.
(Takuto) I want Momoko to keep smiling.
(Minseok) I understand.
(Minseok) Me too, Momoko-sensei→
I want you to smile all the time.
(Takuto) Thank you, Minchok.
(Takuto) And what if it turns out that it's actually Minchok?→
I'm sure Momoko will blame him.
Have you been deceiving me all this time? That's it.
So please, Mincheok.
(Minseok) Yes. (Takuto) Hehe.
(Mio) Momo-chan sensei!
(Momoko) Hello! (Mio) Hello!
(Momoko) Are you home? Now. (Mother) That's right.
(Momoko) See you again, Mio-chan. (Mio) Yeah, goodbye!
(Momoko) Be careful.
(Minseok) 《Just seeing you again is like a miracle》
♪～
(Minseok) Huh? 📱(vibration sound)
📱(vibration sound)
(Minseok) Yes.
📱 Are you Kim Min-seok? (Minseok) Yes.
📱 This is Tomoyama Real Estate. (Minseok) Ah.
📱 Regarding the rental apartment you inquired about, →
very sorry.
📱 We already have a contract with another customer.
(Minseok) Ah, is that so?
📱 If I have another chance.
📱(Sound of call being disconnected)
📱(Real estate agent) Kim Min-seok. (Min-seok) Yes.
📱 Sorry, the property you asked about →
It's already decided.
(Minseok) Is that so?
📱 I'm sorry.
📱(Sound of call being disconnected)
Korean
📱(notification sound)
♪～
(Minseok) Huh…｡
📱(notification sound)
(Kazami's voice) ``Tomorrow is Children's Cafeteria Day.''
♪～
(Momoko) Good evening.
(Minseok) Ah, good evening. (Momoko) Good evening.
Please come up.
(Minseok) Ah.
(Mika) Minseok-san, thank you for coming early.
(Momoko) That's right.
Ah. (Minseok) Huh?
(Momoko) The string. (Minseok) Ah.
(Momoko) Please stay still.
(Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) Yes, this is fine.
(Minseok) Ah. (Momoko) Huh? Did it hurt?
(Minseok) Ah, no...｡
My back has been feeling a little tense lately.
(Momoko) What happened?
(Minseok) Ah, that...
I'm currently sleeping in the break room at work.
(Momoko) At work? You won't be able to rest at all if that's the case.
(Minseok) Ah...｡
(Momoko) But why?
(Minseok) It's hard to find a house.
(Momoko) Home? it is….
(Mika) Yes, Momo-chan, please help me here.
This way, this way... (Momoko) Huh?
>> No, don't ask me any more.
It might be about money.
(Momoko) Ah.
>> Prices are really high right now →
It may be very difficult.
(Momoko) That's right.
Ah! >> Huh?
(Momoko) Mr. Minseok, would you like to move here?
(Minseok) Huh?
(Momoko) There's a room on the second floor that I don't use and a bed.
(Minseok) Ah, no, I think you can find it if you keep looking.
(Momoko) Do you not like it?
(Minseok) I don't dislike it, but...
(Momoko) You don't have to worry about the rent.
I wish I could help out at the children's cafeteria instead.
(Minseok) Ah, but... (Kazami) I'm home!
(Momoko) Ah, welcome back. (Mika) Welcome back.
(Kazami) Get half price ham! (Mika) Thank you.
(Momoko) Hey, Director, it seems that Mr. Min-seok is in trouble because he doesn't have a home to live in.
>> Oh yeah, then you should just move here.
There's a room on the second floor that I don't use and a bed.
I don't need rent.
If you could help out at the children's cafeteria instead.
(Mika) I'm saying the same thing.
(Kazami) Same thing? With whom? (Momoko) It's me.
I'm sure the director would say that.
Hey.
(Minseok) No, but... (Momoko) It's okay.
When you're in trouble, we're there for each other.
>> That's right.
(Minseok) I'm really happy, but isn't it a nuisance?
>> It's not a nuisance at all!
The children will be happy if you come.
(Momoko) This is everyone's big home.
(Momoko) Minseok-san said that, right?
♪～
(Kazami) Itadakimasu!
(All) Itadakimasu!
(Child) This looks delicious.
(Kazami) Ah, that's right.
Hey everyone, next time Minseok-kun→
I'm moving here.
Huh? Is that so? >> Really?
Are you a happy person?
(All) Yes!
We can play together anytime.
(Momoko) You can't do it anytime. >> Yeah~｡
(Minseok) It's always okay.
>> Really? (Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) I'm happy. (Child) Yeah.
(Kazami) Yes. This way~ (Minseok) Haa... haa...
(Kazami) Is that all you need?
(Minseok) Yes….
That's cool.
(Kazami) It's here. (Minseok) Sorry.
(Kazami) Come on, please. (Minseok) Sorry to bother you.
>> This is the room used by my daughter who went to art school a long time ago.
Sorry, but it's small and dirty.
(Minseok) It's a nice room.
>> Really? good.
It's time to get rid of things like this.
(Minseok) Wow, that’s amazing. >> No, no…｡
I have to see it.
You are free to use the kitchen downstairs for meals.
Let's eat together on Children's Cafeteria Day.
(Minseok) Thank you.
(Momoko) Conconcon enters.
Good morning. (Minseok) Ah. (Momoko) Today is moving day, right?
(Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) Well, let's celebrate later.
(Kazami) That's right.
(Minseok) Celebration? (Momoko) Yes.
(Kazami) Yes, I'll take it.
(Minseok: Momoko: Mika) Itadakimasu.
(Minseok) Soba?
>> In Japan, soba is a great way to go when moving.
I hope we will have a long relationship.
(Minseok) Ah~｡ >> Yeah.
(Momoko) Is there anything going on in Korea?
(Minseok) Ah, toilet paper for moving.
(Momoko) Toilet paper?
(Minseok) Life and things are a standard gift for housewarming →
Smooth like toilet paper→
It's a wish that everything goes well.
(Momoko) Hey, that's right.
>> It's fun to learn a lot about Korea when Minseok is around.
(Mika) Yes, that's right, Minseok-san.
I heard about it from a friend of mine the other day.
(Minseok) Nun friend? (Kazami) Nun friend?
Friends enjoying afternoon tea together→
I'm Nuntomo for short.
Hahaha...
So, I heard from that child →
The heir of Hwang Geum is now Min Seok →
Apparently he's coming to Fangum Hotel Tokyo.
(Mika) Have you talked to that person yet?
(Minseok) Ah, um...｡
No, not yet.
>> I see, but people from chaebol →
I may not be able to speak normally.
I'm a person above the clouds.
(Kazami) What kind of things do people like that usually eat?
Isn't it a full course every day?
Wow! So I guess the place you live in is amazing too.
It's a very spacious house with a nice view.
There must be a lot of helpers.
I guess it's like I've never held anything heavier than chopsticks.
(Momoko) Hahaha... But well→
The world we live in must be completely different.
(Kazami) Look, Minseok's chopsticks are still.
(Minseok) Ah, I'm sorry. >> Eat, eat.
(coughing)
(Momoko) Water, water. >> Are you okay?
(Minseok) Sorry. >> Hahahaha…!
I'm surprisingly panicked.
Ahahaha…｡
(Kazami: coughing)
Director! (Momoko) Director.
>>Yes, yes...drink.
Because I'm already laughing at Minseok-san.
(Kazami) Ah...
(Momoko) Hahaha...｡
(Mika) Already.
♪～
Korean
(Knock) (Momoko) Minseok-san.
(Minseok) Ah, yes, please.
(Momoko) Excuse me.
Have you finished organizing your luggage?
(Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) Um...
If you like this.
These are the green onions used as a condiment for lunch.
If you do this, it will grow again.
(Minseok) Ah. (Momoko) Green onions are the best economical vegetable.
Minseok-san: I'm thinking of moving and getting a lot of things.
(Momoko) You didn't need it? (Minseok) No, I need it.
(Minseok) Oh, sorry.
(Momoko) No.
Please change the water every day.
That way it will stretch well.
(Minseok) Ah yes.
(Momoko) See you then.
(Minseok) Again.
(Sound of door opening and closing) (Momoko) Excuse me.
(Mika) [Well, it's hard to find people from chaebol →
I may not be able to speak normally.]
(Momoko) [The world we live in is probably completely different]
♪～
(Momoko) Okay!
>> Hmm.
Your fatigue will be blown away.
This dumpling is really delicious.
(sound of door opening)
(Mika) Welcome back. (Kazami) Welcome back!
(Minseok) Is it a bun?
>> I have Minseok's too. (Minseok) Ah, thank you.
>> Hmm, mitarashi is the best!
(Minseok) Huh? What about Momoko-sensei?
>>I went home early because I had something to do.
(Mika) I made sure to bring the mitarashi with me.
(Momoko) Hmm, delicious!
Well, next...
Ah, ah!
yeah….
Wow, I did it!
(Momoko) It's delicious.
♪～
>> English
(Staff) What happened?
(Natsume) It's like a double booking for a suite room.
You are an important customer who uses our service often.
(Jones) Minseok.
(Mizushima) Minseok?
English
Huh?
(Minseok) I used to stay at a hotel in Seoul before.
>>Ah, is that so?
English
Ah...｡
english conversation
(Takuto) Ah, it's finished!
tired.
(whistle)
>> English conversation
(Takuto) Ah.
(Takuto) Fangmu Air?
♪～
(Takuto) The heir of a conglomerate?
(Staff) Looks like you were humiliated in front of the manager.
(Staff) It doesn't seem like anything bad will happen if you get involved.
(Staff) What does it mean to be the heir of a wealthy family?
(Staff) Hey.
(Minseok) Excuse me.
(Staff) Thank you for your hard work.
(Staff) Thank you for your hard work. (Staff) Thank you for your hard work.
Korean
(Minseok) 《I would rather feel the same way again...》
(Mika) [It seems that the heir of Fangum is coming]
[Have you talked to that person yet?] ]
(Minseok) [No, not yet]
(Momoko) [The world we live in is probably completely different]
(Momoko) [Minseok-san, would you like to move here? ]
>> [I look forward to a long relationship]
(Momoko) [This is everyone's big house]
(Minseok) 《I am...》
(Momoko) Huh? what happened? I'm going to get dazed and cold.
(Takuto) Ah, okay, eat.
(Momoko) Eh, what's wrong? What is doctor's malpractice?
(Takuto) Huh? What did you say?
The most important thing for beauty is health.
I'm careful about my health as well as my beauty.
(Momoko) That would be fine.
Hmm, delicious! Delicious, delicious.
(Takuto) Eat well as always.
(Momoko) It's my favorite delicacy.
Ah, do you like Minseok here?
Let's invite him next time.
yeah?
(Takuto) No, I already brought you Minchok.
(Momoko) Oh, is that so? So how was it?
Did you like it?
(Takuto) Well, yeah.
(Momoko) Well, I guess it's delicious here.
I see...
You have to try the yakitori here.
>> English
(Takuto) [Heir of a conglomerate? ]
That's Momoko.
(Momoko) Huh?
(Takuto) It's about Minchok.
(Minseok) Good evening.
(Momoko) Welcome back.
(Minseok) Um...
(Momoko) I've been waiting for Minseok.
(Minseok) Did something happen?
(Momoko) This.
(Minseok) What is this?
(Momoko) This is a saving recipe.
(Minseok) Huh?
(Momoko) These are all side dishes that can be made for less than 100 yen.
My sister's recipe.
(Minseok) Your sister? (Momoko) Yes.
My sister is amazing.
Everything is cheap, delicious, and healthy.
(Kyoko) [That's right, all that's left is...] (Momoko) [Yeah]
(Kyoko) [Simmered deep-fried tofu? ]
(Momoko) [Oh, that's nice.]
[Atsu-age (deep-fried tofu stew in minced meat)]
Minseok →
How to save money on green onions They were happy.
Please save a lot of money with this.
Good night then.
(Minseok) Thank you very much. (Momoko) Yes.
Ah, I'll turn off the front light.
(Minseok) Good night. (Momoko) Good night.
(Minseok) Take care. (Momoko) Yes.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
♪～
(Minseok) Momoko-sensei! (Momoko) Huh?
(Minseok) To Momoko Sensei→
There's something I want to talk about.
(Momoko) Yes.
(Minseok) My...
(Minseok) Korean families...
(Mizushima) Oh my goodness.
This is this.
(Minseok) Manager.
(Mizushima) Is it here? This is my new home.
Manager: Sorry, I had some alcohol.
I was surprised.
Even if the heir of a wealthy family lived in a place like this.
(Tao Zi) Yu Caoji?
>> Heir On...
Huh? Didn't you know?
Yes, this person is→
Korean conglomerate Hwangeum Hotel Group →
He’s the heir of the family. Hahahaha…｡
Wear it under an umbrella→
I quickly became the deputy manager of my hotel.
Well, I guess it's because of that margin.
I want to start from scratch as a bellman →
You started saying something special, haha.
Well, I guess the same goes for living here.
Because he is the heir of a conglomerate →
Do you want to experience the life of common people?
Haha.
I'll bother you for a moment.
(Natsume) Manager! (Minseok) Manager.
>> Ah, sorry.
Oh, that's cute.
I'll bother you for a moment. (Minseok) Manager.
(Mizushima) It's okay, it's okay... (Minseok) Manager.
(Mizushima) Just a moment... (Minseok) Please pick it up.
(Mizushima) Eh, children's cafeteria.
Oh, just a little bit... (Minseok) Manager.
>> It's okay, it's okay.
(Minseok) Manager. >> Oh no.
Hahahaha... The children's cafeteria is disgusting.
Ahahaha Oh my gosh.
Is it a charity?
Ah, that's amazing →
It must feel good, huh?
Live a life without any inconvenience →
"I'm kind →
I'm amazing.''
It's all a rich man's debauchery.
You look down on us normal humans.
Stop fooling around!
You...
You're such a hypocrite.
(Minseok) Manager... (Momoko) What are you talking about?
You don't know anything about Minseok, right?
>> You're probably the one who doesn't know.
You probably didn't know that this person was the heir of a conglomerate.
(Momoko) Even if I don't know that, I know about Minseok.
Mr. Minseok →
He is a kind person who naturally extends his helping hand to those in need.
(Minseok) [Help this person]
(Momoko) Even the children know this very well.
That's why everyone loves Minseok.
(Child) [Amazing]
(Momoko) For us→
Where was Minseok born and raised?
It doesn't matter.
♪～
(Mizushima) At most →
So that you won't regret meeting this person later.
I don't know.
Let's go, Natsume-kun. >> I'm very sorry.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(Minseok) I'm sorry.
(Minseok) I can't say it →
sorry.
(Momoko) Um...
(Momoko) Maybe I just don't understand it well.
Even if people say that Minseok is a chaebol...→
I don't get it at all.
Even though you say that someone lives in a different world than you do →
I don't think so at all.
Minseok here →
Because Minseok is everything to me.
(Minseok) Momoko Sensei.
(Momoko) I didn't need this. (Minseok) No.
(Momoko) Huh? (Minseok) I need it. (Momoko) No, I don't need it.
(Minseok) I definitely need it. (Momoko) I definitely don't need it.
(Minseok) I definitely need it, no, no... (Momoko) I definitely don't need it.
Minseok, wait.
(Takuto) [Anosa Momoko] (Momoko) [Hmm? ]
(Takuto) [It's about Minchok]
(Momoko) [What's wrong with Minseok? ]
(Takuto) [Ah, no, it's nothing]
(Momoko) [Ah, that's right, you didn't know that, Minseok-san →
I've just moved above the clinic.]
(Takuto) [Eh? ] (Momoko) [So, I want you to take a look.]
[I was thinking of giving this to Minseok]
[Look, it's pretty expensive right now.]
[So I thought the best way to save money would be to cook for myself.]
[You worked really hard, didn't you?]
[My sister came up with all this recipe...]
♪～
(Minseok) My real parents are →
I was running a small coffee shop.
(Momoko) A coffee shop?
(Minseok) It was a place for people from the neighborhood to gather and relax.
[When I grow up, I will protect this store]
(Minseok) But after my parents died in an accident →
I lost my family →
I was taken in by my father's best friend.
That person was the president of Hwangeum Group.
I went to Korea→
I started living as Kim Min-seok.
(Momoko) That's right.
(Minseok) Yes.
(Momoko) I also lost my parents when I was young.
Even with new parents →
Even if I had a life without any inconvenience→
I think I can at least understand the loneliness that cannot be filled.
(Momoko) You have lived a strong life.
♪～
(Minseok) Welcome. Would you like to check in?
(Male) Yes. (Minseok) I'll bring your luggage.
(Female) Thank you. (Minseok) Please come here.
(Kazami's voice) The heir?
But Minseok is Minseok.
I'll keep it a secret from my friends.
I'm sure you'll be jealous.
(sound of door opening)
(Mika) Welcome back. (Kazami) Oh, welcome back.
(Momoko) Welcome back.
(Minseok) I'm home.
Looks delicious.
(Kazami) Do you want to eat? (Minseok) Ah, I'll have it then.
I'll wash my hands before that.
>> Ah, Minseok may have said "I'm home" for the first time.
(Momoko) Ah. (Kazami) Ah, that's certainly true.
Hahahaha…｡
(sound of door opening)
\Excuse me/ (Momoko) Hmm.
(Mika) Sorry, it's over for today.
(Momoko) It's okay. What happened today?
(Eri) I'm not a patient.
I →
Kim Min Seok →
I'm my fiancé.
♪～