(Ko Hyun Jung)
(Ryeo Un)
(Yoon Sang Hyun)
(Lee Jin Woo)
(Namib)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Children were filmed under production guidelines.)
What happened?
Hey! Are you crazy?
- You didn't call anyone, did you? - No.
That's good. You guys go inside.
Go inside!
My goodness.
Hey. Who are you?
Come out.
Come out, you punk.
My gosh.
(Mom)
Are you out of your mind?
Are you trying to ruin my life?
Get up.
Get up, you jerk!
- I'll take him to the hospital. - Let go of me!
I don't know who you are,
but don't tell anyone what you saw here.
Got it?
Let's go.
Jin Woo.
What happened?
Jin Woo...
I saw...
what he did to himself.
I didn't mean to see it.
I was just...
worried about him.
That's why I came here.
Jin Woo told me to cover him.
But I couldn't do that.
(Namib)
(Episode 10: The Best Kid)
(Lost Property)
It's going to be all right. Don't worry too much.
This is my second time...
to wait for a doctor outside after my family got into an accident.
This is my second time.
Are you Ms. Kang Soo Hyun's guardian?
Yes.
There are no fractures or organ damage.
She passed out from the shock of the accident.
She still needs to be hospitalized for several days of treatment.
Please get a check-up before being discharged.
Thank you.
My gosh.
(TA Entertainment, Mr. Cha)
Ms. Kang.
This is her husband.
- I'm listening. - It's about Yoo Jin Woo.
Did you know he has been doing something like this?
"Something like this?"
We went to an emergency room.
We cleaned up the mess.
- What on earth... - Okay.
I'll admit her to the hospital.
You go home and pack what you need.
Stay by her side when you come back.
(Health Products)
(Anxiety, tension, and depression due to neurosis)
(Sleep improvement and relaxation for insomnia)
(Relief from anxiety disorders, psychological stability, )
(For improved sleep)
What happened? What's this on your clothes?
Dad. Jin Woo...
Have you...
met Jin Woo?
Mom was injured.
I'm going to the hospital.
I won't take long. So please wait at home.
Let's go.
What?
You said Mom was injured. I should go.
Okay.
Go and get changed.
(Patient Room 1005)
(Kang Soo Hyun)
Please don't abandon me. Please don't avoid me.
Please.
Please. I swear I'll do my very best.
- Please. - This is the best for us both.
I'll do all I can, so please.
Mom.
Honey.
Are you okay?
I had a dream.
What dream?
Jin Woo.
Which Jin Woo?
Yoo Jin Woo.
- What? - What happened to Jin Woo?
- Jin Woo... - I checked.
He's fine. He's in the dorm.
No. Then why...
No. He's doing fine.
Please take a rest today. Okay?
(Yoo Jin Woo)
Is someone throwing stones?
What's going on?
Hey, what's this sound?
Hey, did you get stalker fans?
No, I didn't. Isn't it Do Ha?
It's not me either.
- Is it him? - Why is he sleeping over there?
Mr. Cha didn't allow him to sleep in his room...
because he might do something.
It's so loud. Who is it?
Hey, don't open it. They might take pictures.
Are they reporters who heard about it?
He's doing all sorts of bad things.
Guys, let's go to bed.
We should practice tomorrow.
Let's not care about someone who will leave soon.
So...
Well...
I mean...
Don't just follow the company's orders.
Always speak up for yourself.
And say no when you need to.
Even when everyone doubts you,
you should always...
Why did you come?
Are you going to take me again?
The factory you bought after selling me.
Can you sell it again?
No.
Please don't come back.
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight.
- What is he doing? - Don't talk to him.
- My goodness. - Hey, don't look at him.
Why are you not practising? What are you doing?
Mr. Cha.
I don't think it's right for us to suffer because of him.
Do you think you guys are the only ones who are suffering?
The entire company is a mess.
Thinking about what happened yesterday,
he might be putting on a show.
What do you mean?
He wants people to pity him because he's in a bad situation.
He did that on the audition show as well.
He puts on a show in an urgent situation.
Jin Woo.
I told you to admit to your wrongdoings.
Does this mean you can't admit to anything?
People are criticizing the entire company...
because of you.
And this is what you want to do?
Is that right?
- Did you come to make fun of me? - No, it's not like that.
I don't have another intention.
Is Jin Woo okay?
What?
Don't you have to ask if the company is okay...
before asking about him?
People are criticizing all of us because of him.
It's because you were sitting on your hands.
What did you say?
Did you handle the controversy...
over him appropriately?
Just like people on the Internet, didn't you believe all the rumours,
force him to take responsibility,
and tell him to beg and apologize no matter what?
How dare you blame us when you're the one at fault?
And who are you to say something like this to me?
You're Kang Soo Hyun's husband, nothing more.
But I agreed to meet you,
thinking you might give me a refund.
Do you understand?
If you're not going to give me a refund, get out.
Get out.
I can't reach Ha Na. She hasn't come to practice either.
Ha Na.
Why did you do that?
What the reporters are saying is nonsense.
Don't listen to them.
Did you not believe in me?
Did you think I wasn't good enough?
Hang in there.
Hang in there just for a moment. It's going to be over.
Ha Na.
Okay. This is the first term. And this is the last term.
It's multiplied by the number of terms.
The one before this asks for the middle term...
between the 1st term and the 19th term, right?
Then what goes in the middle term?
It should be "a ten."
Eight multiplied by nineteen...
Eighty plus seventy-two...
is 152. That's the answer.
Did you get it right?
Don't forget to review it.
- Thank you. - All right.
Hey.
Oh, yes.
- You don't have to give it to me. - Why not?
It's from Yoo Jin Woo.
He's a little weird.
- What's weird about him? - I saw it on the Internet.
There were many controversies over him.
What controversies?
Manipulation. His personality.
And he's a bully.
What did you see?
- What? - You observed him closely.
You were in the same class as him.
- And you did this with him. - We're not close.
Hey, even if you're not close,
even though you're not close,
why do you believe people who don't know about him...
instead of what you saw and experienced?
Jin Woo. Can we talk for a moment?
I feel sorry for Yoo Jin Woo.
He created the class assistance system.
I thought he was different from others.
Do you also believe them?
Do you think what they say about him is all true?
No.
But people don't care, you know.
When something comes up, they gather around, gossip, and destroy you.
They don't even care to know what the fact is.
He was just unlucky.
Well, the truth is...
A little while ago...
We lost!
- Is it that hard? - I'm sorry.
Do it properly.
- Hey. - What? What is it?
Yoo Jin Woo from "Star Rise."
What? Yoo Jin Woo?
You mean, the Yoo Jin Woo we know?
He used to go to an adult entertainment place.
"Yoo Jin Woo..."
"has a nasty personality."
"He used to hit kids at school."
Hey, is it okay to write it?
Why?
It's not a lie.
You guys!
- Hey! - Hey!
- This is good. - Can I try it?
Hey, Jin Woo. Don't.
Hey.
What if they deny it? Then what will you do?
- Come on. - Me?
Here.
- Hey. - Oh, nice!
- Hey, well done. - My gosh.
- Come on. - Hey, open your mouth.
- Let me try once more. - All right.
Mom, I found out who posted the stuff about Jin Woo being a bully.
Those guys at the anti-bullying committee hearing.
It was them.
Mom.
We have a witness too. Jae Hyun said...
That company will handle everything related to Yoo Jin Woo from now on.
"That company?"
There is nothing I can do now.
Because you sold him?
Be honest with me.
The factory...
Didn't you buy it with the money from selling him?
That's right.
Did you think it'd make me happy?
Earning a future by selling a friend.
Did you actually think it'd make me happy?
Jin Woo.
I couldn't see that far.
I've seen it so many times.
Kids who have no future fall apart so quickly.
But I destroyed your future with my own hands,
so I wanted to do whatever it took to create a future for you.
That was all it was about.
"Future?"
So, you sold my friend to create a future for me?
Yes.
I didn't even do it on my own. You built that so-called future for me.
That's right!
Sir.
I need to talk to you about something.
What is it?
I'd like to settle my account.
Bill me for the breach of contract penalty for the ad too.
- What? - I'm sorry.
I'll take responsibility for the situation and leave.
Well, I was going to give you this anyway.
Why should we take care of this for you?
You'll have to cough up a lot of money.
I know.
Hey.
No funny business...
until your contract is terminated.
A suicide attempt, for example.
I wasn't trying to kill myself.
I wanted to live.
That's why I did it.
What are you doing?
There's food in the fridge, and your medicine is in the cupboard.
You know, I never asked them to rig the results on "Star Rise."
Mr. Jang just went ahead and did it.
I've booked a practice room for you at Pandora.
Rest up today, and start practising again tomorrow.
I'm doomed anyway.
It's all over now.
The final round has been postponed anyway.
It's a good thing.
You said you'd die if you lost.
You didn't lose yet, so why do you look like you're dying?
Keep your promise.
You can think about it once you lose.
(Yoo Jin Woo)
(CEO Kang Soo Hyun, Pandora Entertainment)
Hide me.
(CEO Sim Jin Woo)
Mom.
What are you doing here?
I can't sleep.
What?
It's weird. I didn't drink any coffee.
You're probably just tired.
It happens.
No. I didn't get any sleep last night either.
What?
Mom, I can't stop thinking about it.
About what?
That day, Jin Woo...
While you were coming to me,
I went to Jin Woo.
I opened the bathroom door,
and he was sitting on the floor.
He was bleeding from his wrist.
That moment, Jin Woo asked me...
to cover him.
So, I...
I covered him,
but people suddenly showed up and...
It's okay.
He will be okay.
Tomorrow is a new day.
It'll be a new day.
Have a good day.
(Flavia)
(Reject)
- How are things at the agency? - How's the factory?
You look tired.
Come on. Look who's talking.
What are you doing here? Shouldn't you be at school?
What about you?
What's that bag for?
You said you were used to being abandoned.
That was a lie, wasn't it?
Yes.
I lied.
What's with your face?
- I'm sleep-deprived. - You too?
Yes.
Me, Kang Soo Hyun, and Sim Jin Woo too.
Oh, boy.
What are you guys going to do?
Send her away.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about Soo Hyun.
Send her on a trip or something.
She always comes here and watches videos of the sea.
Why don't you give her a vacation?
Vacation?
(Recommended Tour Packages)
Tell Ha Na to withdraw voluntarily.
Don't make things get out of control.
No, she can't withdraw.
The company's image is being destroyed as we speak!
Will you let the controversy get out of hand?
When I kicked out Kang Soo Hyun...
and appointed you as the new CEO of the company,
I took into consideration that you were harbouring a grudge against her.
I don't know why you two had a falling-out,
but I needed that grudge.
In the beginning, you didn't seem...
to hesitate when you had to fire people.
Do you think you'd never end up like Kang Soo Hyun?
I bet everything about this company looked promising at first.
You thought...
you'd make a lot of money if you kicked out Kang Soo Hyun...
and replaced her with an obedient CEO.
- What? - I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I put poison in this company.
If you drink that poison, we'll both die.
It all comes down to money, right?
I refuse to lose a single penny.
Pandora's financial statements.
I'll make them look really good so you can just wash your hands of it,
so just...
watch what I do.
How will you do that in this situation?
I'll get Yoo Jin Woo back.
Yoo Jin Woo?
People are drawn to stories like this.
A story of someone who comes from nothing...
working himself to the bone to move up in the world and succeed.
Do you know what people like even more?
Seeing someone successful like that hit rock bottom from the top...
and roll down an endless slope...
because of one mistake.
In this world, there are people who enjoy that.
A member of the most popular idol group 20 years ago.
He lost everything because of a scandal.
Do you know what he does as a streamer these days?
He dances, sings,
and puts on a show for money.
There's a ridiculous amount of money in that industry.
Are you saying you'll get Yoo Jin Woo...
and make him do stuff like that?
You see,
I know that industry.
Everyone who was rooting for Yoo Jin Woo...
will come and hurl stones at him.
And every single one of those stones is money.
This way, you can recover your investment,
and I can destroy what Kang Soo Hyun created...
and what she'll go on to make.
- You know what I mean. - Right.
- It's not that it didn't go well. - I was just kidding.
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
- Really? - Yes, this is nice.
Good choice.
(Infinite Continent)
(Infinite Continent TV)
(Ladies, help me.)
(Infinite Continent: Ladies, help me.)
Oh, my. Jeongsuni. A hundred thousand stars?
Thank you so much!
A sexy dance move?
(Gift from Jeongsuni)
(Today's goal: 10,000, Currently 1,218, 15 percent)
(Today's MVP)
(My Family Care Home)
When will they get here?
Mom. Let's play something else.
"Play?"
What are you talking about?
Your sister's bringing her boyfriend...
No.
She's bringing your future brother-in-law over.
How does she remember what happened decades ago?
Let's go. I should wait for them outside.
No, Mom.
I'll check with them.
Put this down and use this instead.
It's a lipstick. Make yourself look pretty.
Hold this in this hand...
and the lid in this hand.
Darn it.
Eat this.
(Incheon to Zurich)
- Incheon Airport, 4pm. - What?
The beaches there are fantastic, apparently.
Take a few days off and enjoy a hot spring.
I booked you a hotel too.
What do you mean? Why would I suddenly travel?
I've done everything you asked so far.
Do as I say for once.
None of us can sleep, and we're losing our minds.
At least one of us has to relax, okay?
That's a pretty scarf.
Here.
Don't think of anything over there, ignore your phone,
and eat lots of nice things. Okay?
What is this?
(Joo Hyun)
- Hi, Joo Hyun. - Jun Seok.
I'm really sorry,
but could you come over today?
- Today? - Yes. Right now if possible.
Can you?
I'll tell Soo Hyun about it.
- No. Don't tell her. - What?
I'll come over. Don't tell Soo Hyun.
- Okay? - Thanks, Jun Seok.
Can you come dressed in a suit?
A suit?
Have fun.
Eat lots of nice food.
My gosh.
I haven't worn a suit in over ten years.
I wonder if it still fits.
It fits.
(My Family Care Home)
Thank you.
Jun Seok.
Hey. Who's this new guy?
Where's Mother?
In her room.
She thought we were in school a few days ago.
Today, she's in meet the future son-in-law mode.
Okay. Let's do this.
- Good luck. - Thanks.
Mother. I'm here.
(Check-in Counters)
From audition star to scandal-maker.
Everyone's talking about "Star Rise" contestant Yoo Jin Woo.
Despite allegations he worked at a shady club and was a school bully,
neither he nor his agency has released a statement.
Yoo Jin Woo participated in the televised audition "Star Rise,"
and he reached the main round which was broadcast live.
He transferred to TA Entertainment as soon as he left the show,
and joined a boy group expected to debut soon.
Mom. Enjoy your break.
Get me a souvenir.
Recently, word got out that he worked at a club,
and that a meeting was held to discuss his bullying.
Soo Hyun told me a lot about you.
I see. I heard a lot about you too.
You're going to start a company together?
What was it called?
- Pan... - Pandora?
Yes.
There's a guy called Dong Jun. Us three will work together.
You're still young. Good for you.
- Thank you. - But...
why did you choose Soo Hyun of all people?
Pardon?
As a future spouse and business partner,
why did you choose my Soo Hyun?
She's more trustworthy and reliable than anyone...
when she's in my corner.
I thought...
she was someone I could face any obstacle with.
You're right. My Soo Hyun...
is like that.
I'd like you to work together...
and make her dream come true.
Soo Hyun's dream?
Yes. You know what...
her dream is, don't you?
She told me about it one day.
That one day,
she'd like to meet them.
Hyun Bin, you slow down a bit at the bridge.
Can you keep with the beat?
You're doing well.
You nailed the tone and melody,
so let's work on the time and details and try again.
He's getting better and better with your feedback.
Thanks.
Let's try again.
I want to meet them one day.
In my lifetime.
The best...
The best kid.
Mother. I'll visit you again.
Okay. Let's meet often.
Sure.
I'm Reporter Han from Joypic.
I couldn't reach Ms. Kang, so I called you.
You know Yoo Jin Woo's press conference is up soon, right?
(My Family Care Home)
The call cannot be connected.
Tell the reporters yourself.
(My Family Care Home)
Taxi!
Incheon Airport, please, and fast.
I shouldn't have told her to ignore her phone.
- Hey. - Are you ready?
What will he say?
I don't know. We'll see.
(Republic of Korea)
(Information)
Kang Soo Hyun!
What's going on?
What will you do about Yoo Jin Woo?
"What will I do?"
To sell him to buy our son a factory.
- It was your idea. - Right.
You made that decision because you thought...
Yoo Jin Woo was worth it.
- Yes. - There's something...
I really want to ask you.
Yoo Jin Woo.
What is he to you?
What if...
that accident hadn't happened?
If our son hadn't gotten hurt.
If you never dreamed of buying a factory.
If you hadn't been replaced as Pandora's CEO.
If you were an ordinary producer.
If I hadn't...
nagged and tormented you.
If you had no burdens...
or guilt to live through.
If you didn't have a husband like me who bothered you.
What if that were the life you had...
and you met Yoo Jin Woo?
Mom, can we check that out too?
Hang on.
Mom's a bit busy. Give me a moment.
- Mom. Let's go over there. - What?
- Shall we? - Honey!
The restaurant crowded, and we have to wait.
Let's eat somewhere else.
- I thought that was a hammer. - No.
If that hadn't happened...
He'd be the best kid of my life.
Let's go to Yoo Jin Woo.
Yoo Jin Woo's here.
Read word for word. It's all on you.
(It stemmed from my past mistakes.)
(It happened before I joined TA Entertainment.)
(I was deprived when I grew up.)
(I had depression for a long time, )
(and I started to self-harm when I was young.)
The issues we know of so far...
is that "Star Rise" was rigged, you worked at a club,
and you were a bully when you attended Sewoon High.
We'd like to know what's true and what isn't.
Your being seen at the club.
Is it related to the producer of "Star Rise" who was bribed?
Witness accounts of your bullying days...
are surfacing online.
Is that true?
Yoo Jin Woo. Will you apologize?
(I hung out with people I shouldn't have, )
(and disappointed fans with my actions.)
(I take full responsibility and will leave the boy group.)
(I apologize sincerely to all who believed in me.)
Yoo Jin Woo.
Look up.
Sit up straight.
I'll answer all the questions.
Don't you say a word, okay?
I'm Kang Soo Hyun. Direct your questions to me.
How much of the issues are true...
and how much is false?
They're nothing but groundless rumours.
Is it a groundless rumour that he was at a club?
A close friend Yoo Jin Woo met...
when he was a trainee currently works at a club.
That's all.
There's talk that he bullied students at school.
That's...
My son was involved in a bullying incident.
Yoo Jin Woo helped my son who was a victim.
That's all.
Would he consider apologizing?
No.
Making vague apologies...
about unclear rumours just to move on.
I think that's the worst you can do to deceive fans.
We won't apologize at this moment.
Yoo Jin Woo. You did nothing wrong.
Look up and come with me.
What's your plan, Ms. Kang?
Do you deny all the suspicions?
- What about the bullying... - Is this it?
- Comment on that, please. - Look over here!
Tell us the truth.
- Why won't you answer? - What are you thinking?
(To press conference)
Wouldn't it have been nice...
if you'd held Yoon Hee's hand like that too?
Yoo Jin Woo.
I'll take him.
Yoo Jin Woo. Do you think you deserve to be in the light?
I'll take you.
To a world that suits you.
(Namib)
You all but ruined an agency...
and will take just the kid?
I'll hand him over to whoever brings the money first.
Mom will sell the place to get you back.
Half the price?
Help us out. We're a bit short.
Pandora will get him. It has been decided.
You'll just abandon them. Now you say this?
I get the feel I can never come back if I leave now.
I'm at the police station.
Our story is that Yoo Jin Woo did it all.
I can't sing anymore.
I'm of no use if I can't sing, right?
You don't need me anymore.