[Go Hyun Jung]
[Ryeo Un]
[Yoon Sang Hyun]
[Lee Jin Woo]
[Namib]
[Characters, locations, incidents, groups, and occupations are fictitious.]
[Child actors were filmed safely with their guardians present and consulting with experts.]
Jin Woo.
Kang Su Hyeon...
is sincere about you.
Listen to her well.
Hyung, why are you like this?
And you coming to Muse, and what we did together- no...
knowing me and everything else...
That never happened.
Understand?
What do you mean?
Why would you say that?
Jin Woo.
Take care.
[Seoul Euncheon Police Station]
Hyung!
[Namib - Episode 12: A Long Journey]
Thank you for everything.
Jang Hyeol Cheol was responsible for everything?
He brought in people he had grudges against to Muse
and had them take drugs.
Then, in that process, you also...
I transported it and also used violence.
Do you know that statement is disadvantageous to you?
Regardless of what Jang Hyeon Cheol testifies,
the truth is in this USB.
I hear an attorney is here. You should talk to him.
I am Attorney Han Dong Jun
from JL Law Firm.
[Attorney Han Dong Jun, JL Law Firm]
CEO Kang Su Hyeon sent me.
Mom even gave me some money to hang out with you.
No, this is enough.
One of my dad's friends is a really famous attorney.
Since he's on his case, don't worry about it too much.
Yoo Jin Woo didn't speak more on that matter.
I couldn't tell if he found his solution,
but his face seemed much more at ease.
And...
another person who needs to solve a problem...
Are you looking for something specific?
- This one.
- One moment, please.
I will show you the product.
Thank you.
Is this a present?
- Yes.
- Your wife?
The CEO.
The CEO?
Wow, it's pretty.
I found it on my way here.
Gosh, no, this isn't it, either.
Let's be close.
Gosh, I don't think that's it, either.
[Email]
[Kang Su Hyeon - Dear Composer SJS]
You enjoyed it?
[I enjoyed listening to the demo track. It's a good song.]
Nice!
Okay!
[Let's meet.]
You want to meet?
What do I do?
This makes me look like a taxi driver.
Gosh...
I think she'll recognize me.
Kang Su Hyeon.
She won't recognize me, right?
SJS?
Take it off.
- You recognized me?
- You thought I wouldn't?
I don't know what to say.
Because the song was good.
Really? It's not bad?
I'm almost taken aback.
The lyrics especially.
Anyone hearing this song
will feel that it's Yoo Jin Woo's story.
Why do you think that way?
Why do you think it's only Yoo Jin Woo's story?
♫ Amidst the passing crowd ♫
♫ I'm still alone pretending to be fine ♫
♫ Brushing past another painful day ♫
♫ Where are you headed? ♫
Jin Woo told me
that I'm a desert.
A desert?
But...
Yoo Jin Woo is an ocean, right?
Supposedly, there's a country like that in Africa.
Namib.
Namib?
It's fascinating, right?
The desert and the ocean meet directly there.
They just meet together like this.
What a great combination.
Yoo Jin Woo.
Lift your head.
A stubborn woman
and a boy who really doesn't listen!
You two are a great combination.
- Who knows?
- Straighten your shoulders.
Maybe you two might achieve something together.
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Cheer up and take one more step ♫
These lyrics...
are your story.
And...
I want to apologize
for saying we should get divorced.
♫ Without worries, without worries ♫
♫ It's okay to smile ♫
It's pretty on you.
Let's start over.
I don't want to.
- What?
- I don't want to accept your apology.
- And if you won't?
- Bring me the papers, so I can sign it.
Gosh, why are you being like this?
Are you really going to be like this?
Then, give me back the ring.
I refuse. There are no take-backs.
You said you won't accept my apology!
You want to get divorced?
Well, that's not what I mean...
Hey...
Goodness.
- Accept my apology.
- No.
Shall we get started?
Yoo Jin Woo, how about you give it a go?
Okay.
Please turn off the MR.
Why aren't you singing?
I'm sorry.
Come out.
Well... I just...
whenever I try to sing,
I keep hearing my heartbeat,
and I keep remembering how...
people yelled at me.
Do you think everyone's like that?
- Pardon?
- Do you think everyone was like that?
All the school bullies have posted letters of apology
and all the incorrect articles were straightened out.
[I know all these rumors are false. I am proof that this is all slander...]
See yourself objectively,
instead of becoming a tragic figure.
[Late Jang Yoon Hee]
Jang Hyeon Cheol.
Audition program Star Rise ended in the midst of controversy.
In particular, many people are curious as to whether contestant Gyeong Ha Na,
suspected of having her results manipulated, would win.
Her agency, Pandora Entertainment, revealed that Gyeong Ha Na has been released.
- Gyeong Ha Na was a trainee...
- Let's go.
from Pandora Entertainment, who appeared on Star Rise.
She reached the finals of Star Rise and ultimately got second place.
Lee Han Young testified that the drug distribution and violence
at nightclub Muse was carried out under Jang Hyeon Cheol's leadership.
We will hold a cross-examination regarding this matter.
Are Lee Han Young's claims true?
Jang Hyeon Cheol?
Why did you do this?
If you did what I told you-
Before Yoon Hee died,
I asked her.
Why, of all places...
Why, of all places, is she training at this company?
Kang Su Hyeon dragged Yoon Hee into the company-
No.
Yoon Hee said she trusted her oppa.
She said she would follow you wherever.
All right, all right. Jang Hyeon Cheol.
Please respond to Lee Han Young's claims.
He will exercise his right to remain silent.
Oh, Yoo Jin Woo. Let's go to school.
What? I have a recording session today.
My mom said you should go to school today.
Change into your uniform.
- What?
- Your uniform.
Yeah.
In-je-jin.
Ji Young.
What are you doing?
- I'm studying.
- Studying what?
Yoo Jin Woo, there's a world that only students know that celebrities are unaware of.
Let's go.
[I hope all your pen strokes become the answer.]
[Yoo Jin Woo, I hope you only walk down a flower path!]
He's here, he's here!
Hurry, hurry!
Come here!
He's so handsome!
Congratulations!
Let's take a picture together.
Come to the center!
Hurry up and get in!
Okay, okay! We're taking the picture!
One, two, three!
Okay!
Hey, smile!
One, two, three!
Congratulations!
Oh, you're here, Yoo Jin Woo.
Shall we get started?
Yes.
Yoo Jin Woo, people are very curious about your song.
We are, too.
Let's do it.
Well, CEO Kim said he would resign.
Gosh, Kang Su Hyeon got kicked out, Jang Hyeon Cheol got fired,
and CEO Kim resigned.
Gosh, who should I hire as CEO for this company?
Chairman, how about you personally-
What, what? Are you crazy? Personally, do what?
Trying to make me experience disaster, too?
If things keep going like this, it will become a worthless burden.
I have to bring the trajectory upward somehow.
Well, do you have any candidates in mind?
Him.
Who do you mean?
Him!
We're not so close that we'd have chicken and beer together.
Is this your restaurant, too?
Yeah.
- Really?
- Obviously not.
It has good food. I'm a regular here.
Try it. It's good.
Wow, this is so good!
- Take some to go.
- I'll take three chickens to go, please.
Okay.
There are two boys living in my house.
Thanks.
For firing Hyeon Cheol.
I didn't do it for your benefit.
Hey.
Hey!
Gosh!
Do you want to be Pandora's CEO?
♫ Baby, we were so happy ♫
Me?
♫ Baby ♫
♫ Don't you love me anymore ♫
I've taken too much time off. I don't think I can.
Gosh, seriously.
Gosh, that's such a relief.
I mentioned it impulsively,
and I was actually worried that you might say yes.
I happen to be a bit impulsive.
Sorry.
This bastard.
Hey, though I'm not interested, I have someone to recommend.
- Who is it?
- She's worked in the field for a long time
and she's well-known for producing results.
She's got charisma, so she can bring order to a chaotic company.
Who is it?
Kang Su Hyeon.
Bringing Kang Su Hyeon back to Pandora is the best solution.
Kang Su Hyeon...
just doesn't listen.
- You're right.
- She does whatever, and she's stubborn.
- Very accurate.
- She's a very burdensome CEO for investors.
Sometimes, I find her burdensome as well.
If I were to make Kang Su Hyeon the CEO,
someone will need to keep her in check next to her.
She can't be CEO by herself. We'll need at least a co-CEO.
Co-CEO?
Who would do it? Who?
Someone who will keep Kang Su Hyeon in check
and let the board of directors and me know about Kang Su Hyeon's actions.
Oh, you mean a puppet CEO who acts like a treacherous minister?
You think such a person exists? Goodness.
He does exist.
You. How about you become co-CEO with her
and report everything Kang Su Hyeon does?
Are you telling me to become a spy monitoring my own wife or what?
- You're perfect.
- I won't do it!
You really want to right now.
I said I won't do it.
Yes. Please do so.
Yes.
[11/3: Check physical albums, check progress of pre-orders...]
[11/7: Album Release]
- Honey.
- Yeah?
Did you confirm that the song has been registered with the distributor?
- Yeah.
- You've also confirmed the press release
that will go out on the release date, right?
Of course.
What's with you?
No, it's nothing.
What am I doing right now!
If a casting request for Yoo Jin Woo comes in, let me know immediately.
Oh, okay!
What are you going to do?
Since tomorrow is the song release, I've got tons of things to do.
I'm talking about after that.
When you first brought Yoo Jin Woo,
and when you brought him back after selling him,
you've had a plan.
After releasing Yoo Jin Woo's song, what is...
your plan going forward?
♫ Even still, smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Get up again ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
[Yoo Jin Woo - "Smile Again". November 7th, 2024. 6 p.m. (KST)]
What's wrong?
I'm just worried.
- About what?
- If the song isn't successful after doing all this,
Ahjussi...
no, Producer Shim will get hurt, and...
The song is being released at 6, right?
What rank does the song need to be considered a success?
It will be a big success if the song is anywhere near the top 100.
If it lands in the top 10,
then he'll get casting request calls from all over.
He can even potentially get first place on a music show.
If he gets first place on a music show, he can look forward to end-of-year awards shows.
But...
that's pretty much impossible.
It'll work out.
Yoo Jin Woo, you aren't speaking pessimistically for once.
I just get that feeling.
I get the feeling that
I'm on the right path regardless of the results.
[010-1220-9846]
- Hello?
- Yoo Jin Woo?
Yes.
Yes, got it.
- Did something come up?
- Huh?
- It's the police station.
- Why? Is it about the Muse situation?
No, it's about a different issue.
I'll be going first.
Do you want me to tell my mom?
I'll take care of it myself.
So, it's not just one person but a total of 14 people
say that they were scammed.
How is this a scam!
I will pay them back when there is a profit!
I'm telling you that is a scam, lady!
Are you sure your son knows about this?
Is that true?
Yoo Jin Woo? Oh, you're here.
Your mother received investments from many
saying that she was preparing your concert.
Did you know about this?
No.
In the end, the concert didn't take place,
and the investors reported your mother for fraud.
I called him to let him know.
It's just that he didn't pick up.
Is what she's saying true?
Could I talk with my mom for a second?
Go ahead.
Mom.
My song is out.
What?
My song.
I'm really becoming a singer now.
Here.
Mom.
This was our dream.
♫ Amidst the passing crowd ♫
♫ I'm still alone pretending to be fine ♫
Me becoming a singer was also your dream, Mom.
My dream?
When I was little, you took me around to turn me into a singer.
So,
we've achieved our dream.
♫ Even still, smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
Mom.
Help me...
keep going down this path.
♫ Even brighter than the stars in the night sky ♫
♫ You've lived brilliantly today ♫
♫ Don't hesitate and lift your head ♫
♫ Get up again ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ Even still, smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Hunched-up shoulders don't suit you ♫
♫ Passed over as if unnoticed ♫
♫ My smile etched with thick callouses ♫
♫ Without worries, without worries, ♫
♫ It's okay to smile ♫
[173rd]
What's this!
This song only hit 173rd place?
Was the song not good?
No, I think I just didn't sing it well.
173rd place isn't bad.
It's not bad?
Did you think you'd get first place?
Prepare for your schedule.
Okay.
She says it's not bad. By next week,
- it'll probably make it into the top 100.
- Okay.
Your song "Smile Again" is so good.
Please introduce the song to us.
"Smile Again" is a song with a positive message to many people,
saying that we can smile again
even if we are facing hardships and difficulties.
Yoo Jin Woo, you probably faced hardships and difficulties as well.
How did you overcome them?
I have people who place a lot of faith in me.
And when I look into their eyes,
I was able to cheer up and sing again.
Star Rise received a lot of love from the public.
Among all the contestants, I liked you the most, Jin Woo.
Jin Woo, when did you start dreaming of becoming a singer?
I think...
it happened quite naturally for me.
For me...
I am the happiest when I sing.
That's great. With that happiness in mind,
let's see Yoo Jin Woo perform his new song
"Smile Again" for the first time here at Lulu Live.
[Every Wednesday, a Wednesday Market]
♫ Hunched-up shoulders don't suit you ♫
♫ Even brighter than the stars in the night sky ♫
♫ You've lived brilliantly today ♫
♫ Don't hesitate and lift your head ♫
♫ Get up again ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ In the swiftly passing time ♫
Producer, Producer.
How about we use this song as the background music?
- What is it?
- Yoo Jin Woo's song.
Let me hear it.
♫ Pretending to be confident ♫
♫ Brushing past my lonely day ♫
- It's good, right?
- It's good.
Did you listen to the song "Smile Again" yesterday?
- Hey, that's Yoo Jin Woo's song.
- Wait, you knew?
Of course!
It's so good. I listened to it all day yesterday.
I got hooked on this song, too.
I've been listening to it on repeat!
Guys, guys!
The charts, the charts!
[57th: "Smile Again" by Yoo Jin Woo]
It's daebak, right?
Tomorrow?
Okay. He is available.
Okay.
CEO.
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- For what?
- Pardon?
What are you thanking me for?
Oh, my song landed in the top 100 charts.
Did you top the Billboard charts or something?
Why are you getting all emotional about it?
Oh, I guess you're right.
You'll be appearing on Music Sketch tomorrow.
The live music show. You know it, right?
Tomorrow?
One of the cast couldn't make it, so there was a slot.
Get ready for it.
Okay.
Hello?
CEO Kang Su Hyeon?
[Mega Entertainment]
In the end, we meet like this.
Congratulations.
Yoo Jin Woo's pretty good.
He's only getting started.
I've seen how you've developed Yoo Jin Woo, CEO.
How you left Pandora together
and you sold him to TA but then brought him back.
You made a big sacrifice to do so.
I can't imagine why you would do so.
Why would you make such a decision despite facing losses?
It's not possible to explain it
if you think about losses.
I'll ask you one more time.
Does your offer to me still stand?
Your offer to sell Yoo Jin Woo to me.
- Yes.
- After releasing Yoo Jin Woo's song,
what is your plan going forward?
I will send him to the best company in our nation.
You will send him away?
Great.
The potential he's shown in the audition process,
and how he's produced results despite hitting rock bottom...
We've been won over by Yoo Jin Woo.
Please hand over all the rights to Yoo Jin Woo.
We will compensate you for your losses, CEO.
Please write down how much you want for him.
Are you sure?
Yes.
[Party B will hand over all rights and receive 0 won as compensation.]
If I receive money, your company will feel pressure
to recoup the investment and the burden of having paid a large sum.
I will hand over Yoo Jin Woo to Mega Entertainment for no compensation.
The money you would've given me, give it to Yoo Jin Woo in the form of time.
Even if he loses his way for a bit,
give him time and wait for him.
This is my condition.
[Party B will hand over all rights and receive 0 won as compensation.]
Jang Hyeon Cheol.
You distributed 1,000 mg of opioids, right?
This pertains to the possession, trafficking, and facilitation of drugs,
as well as aiding and abetting drug use.
Do you know that?
We have evidence and the victim's testimony, so there's no point in denying it.
Yes, I did it.
Can I go now?
Jang Hyeon Cheol?
You are Jang Yoon Hee's older brother, right?
You know this man, right?
Is he also claiming to be a victim as well?
- No.
- At B Club in Cheongdam-dong,
a female college student lost consciousness.
You won't be able to catch him.
Even if he kills someone,
even if he's found with drugs all over his body,
he always gets away.
Things will be different this time.
The victim is a former trainee from Mega Entertainment.
The CEOs of entertainment agencies made this incident public
and requested prosecutors to investigate it.
CEO Kang Su Hyeon, in particular, led this effort.
She told me to meet with you,
saying ten years ago,
you lost a family member from the same method.
I heard she told your attorney that she's requesting an investigation.
I guess you didn't hear about it.
Please tell me...
what happened back then.
[Ga Young, Kim Bo Ra, Yoo Jin Woo]
[Music Sketch. Every Saturday at 10 p.m. Upper Art Hall. Live Broadcast.]
I heard Yoo Jin Woo is appearing today.
Really? His song was pretty good.
Should we buy some flowers?
Let's go.
[Music Sketch: Yoo Jin Woo]
Well, I met Oh Bong Gyu.
He wants you and me
to return as co-CEOs.
The procedure is complete,
so all we need to do is make the decision.
I won't go back.
It's the company we built.
They're waiting for you.
I met my best protege
and did my best.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Excuse me, your flowers are ready.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yoo Jin Woo.
Okay, just give me a second.
Now, I already know, even if you don't tell me.
It would have been so great if we had met a bit sooner.
Going on a few YouTube channels, doing a few interviews,
and filling in as a replacement for a music show. That's all I can do for you.
- Pardon?
- I'm a small world for you to demonstrate your talents.
I received a call from Mega Entertainment.
They want to scout you.
You've given me a good song,
and things are going great right now.
Things worked out this time, but what about next time?
Not too long ago, a singer from Mega Entertainment topped the Billboard charts.
You definitely have the potential to do the same.
You are the best protege I've ever seen.
I want to know how you will develop and grow.
Aren't you curious?
Aren't you curious about what world awaits you
when you meet an even greater ocean?
An even greater ocean...
Lee Jin Woo.
You will watch me, right?
Wherever it may be.
I'll do well and will be back.
Yoo Jin Woo.
Goodbye.
♫ I walk this path over and over again ♫
♫ With the beautiful tears of the season ♫
♫ I am happy even if it's slow ♫
♫ I live dreaming of you ♫
♫ Will I obtain it after leaving you behind? ♫
♫ I'm always enough for today ♫
♫ Though I can't know, live tomorrow as today ♫
♫ When the wind blows, it will be nice ♫
- Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
♫ I steady my heart ♫
♫ The heart-throbbing moments ♫
♫ Muttering thank you to myself ♫
♫ I erase the wounds, too ♫
♫ I coldly say that I'm lonely again ♫
♫ I look at myself in the mirror ♫
♫ How you held me saying I did well ♫
♫ I embrace this moment even more ♫
♫ I cross the stairs of my memory ♫
♫ I swallow my tear eternally ♫
♫ I remember my dreams ♫
♫ Will I obtain it after leaving you behind? ♫
♫ I'm always enough for today ♫
♫ Though I can't know, live tomorrow as today ♫
Mom.
♫ The words that made my heart flutter every day ♫
♫ Forget it now ♫
[I'll be taking a journey. I told Dad already.]
[I know it's an important time for you, but I'll trust you now.]
[Call Grandma sometimes. I have a lot to say, but I'll stop here.]
[I'll return by Christmas. My son, I love you.]
[My son, I love you.]
♫ I'll dream again tomorrow, too. ♫
Though Mom said she would return by Christmas,
she didn't return even after two years.
[Pandora Entertainment]
Fail.
[2 Years Later]
Pass.
My eye drops.
CEO.
I guess I have no luck with CEOs.
Kang Su Hyeon said this is how you find stars.
Hey, when did we start choosing kids who win staring contests
rather than kids who will be loved by the audience?
Gosh, why are you doing this?
Shut up. Stay outside.
Damn it.
You also pass!
[Joongyoung Prison]
- Let's go, Lee Han Young.
- Where?
Wherever.
♫ Let's soar, fly away ♫
♫ Higher ♫
♫ To chase your dream ♫
I guess you're busy.
I'm just a cosmetics company employee.
Do you want some water?
Unni, it's me.
What is it?
Are you still considering our previous offer
of becoming Pandora's vocal trainer?
I don't sing anymore.
CEO Shim Jun Seok said to let you know that he's been waiting for you for two years.
Let me think a little longer.
Okay.
Why would you lie about not singing anymore?
Because she keeps calling me.
I don't want to go to that company.
- Why not?
- Every time I was at that company,
things went wrong for me.
What will you do now?
Someone once told me
things won't end by running away.
Regardless of what I do,
I will face things properly from now on.
I mean,
if it's hard for you to go alone, I can give you a ride there.
No. I'll drive there myself.
It will soon be Christmas Eve, and Mom is looking for you.
I see. Okay.
Did you prepare presents for the kids?
Yes, I did.
All right.
Here.
My daughters will be so happy.
Look at this.
This is a present for the kids?
- Why?
- Seriously, Honey.
Will eight-year-old kids like something like this?
I'm sorry.
You should be more attentive to the kids.
Okay, okay.
All right, this is Mom's present.
So pretty.
Mom, put them on.
Yeah, they fit nicely.
It's warm.
[How do I draw this part?]
Oh, here?
[Teacher, what's it like to listen to a song?]
You can feel various vibrations in your body.
In the end, it feels like a huge wave crashing over you.
[Wow...]
You should try going to a concert, too.
[Okay!]
You didn't forget about the Christmas gathering today, right?
[CEO Shim Jin Woo]
- Oh Bong Gyu?
- Yes, Hong Jung Hwa.
Why did you come here? You've got no sense.
What do you mean, no sense?
The CEO and an employee of the company I invested in are here.
And a singer I like is also here.
- Have a glass.
- Okay.
By the way, you heard about Yoo Jin Woo, right?
He's returning tomorrow.
From his overseas tour?
I hear things were crazy this time, too.
Right now isn't the time to be happy about Yoo Jin Woo's success.
Look at the state of our company's kids!
That's what I mean!
When does Yoo Jin Woo's contract end? Can't you sign him?
What about Su Hyeon? Is Su Hyeon coming this Christmas?
I don't know. When Mom left, she said she would come by Christmas.
I thought she meant that Christmas coming up in a month,
but it's already the third Christmas this year.
Gosh, what is Kang Su Hyeon doing these days?
Unni, you're here?
The music teacher is here.
Aigoo, her boyfriend is also here.
Hey, we'll need to bring two more glasses!
You're here to eat this time, right?
Yes, I'll be eating.
- I also brought a guest.
- What?
Merry Christmas!
Yoo Jin Woo!
Hey, Yoo Jin Woo!
Hey, your face is just shining nowadays.
- Hello.
- Hey, go and ask him about his contract.
Shut up.
Hey, you bought our presents, right?
Hey, you look more fit!
- Come on. Hello, hello.
- When did you get back?
- Hey, what's this?
- How are you?
His face has gotten so much more handsome
- after going overseas.
- How did you come here?
Oh, it's snowing!
How did you come today?
My schedule got canceled, so I came back early.
You sure it wasn't because you missed us?
A little?
But where's the CEO?
Wasn't she supposed to come back for this Christmas?
Yeah, I came here to see the CEO, too.
I don't know, either.
- You don't know?
- But I guess she is alive at least.
She calls me sometimes.
Not too long ago, she said she was in Southeast Asia.
What are you saying?
Not too long ago, she said she was at Mt. Everest.
- What!
- That's weird.
She said she was studying in a library when I talked to her recently.
What is she really up to?
I'm the only one she didn't call...
I'm sure you'll hear from her at some point.
Let's have a drink.
Yeah, let's have a drink.
All right, let's drink!
These guys are drinking it up.
You two should get married already.
You guys look good together.
What are you saying!
Today is the last supper, the last supper!
Let's just eat, drink, and forget about the rest.
I guess Mom changed so much
that she still has a lot to fill.
Why do you guys act like you're not that close?
Is it because you were an idol trainee?
We have a special guest, Yoo Jin Woo, on set with me today.
We've discussed how his ten years as a trainee,
his audition program appearance, and his debut.
This is the final question.
What is one thing you heard that encouraged you the most to reach this point?
I think hearing that I was her best protege
encouraged me the most.
Who are you referring to by "her"?
[International Arrivals]
[Yoo Jin Woo's Fan Signing Event]
[To Hyeon Jeong. Yoo Jin Woo.]
Thank you.
Hello.
What's your name?
Yoo Jin Woo.
Lift your head.
Straighten your shoulders.
Look at me straight.
♫ Even still, smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Hunched-up shoulders don't suit you ♫
♫ Even brighter than the stars in the night sky ♫
♫ You've lived brilliantly today ♫
♫ Don't hesitate and lift your head ♫
[To my best protege]
♫ Get up again ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ In the swiftly passing time ♫
♫ We lose our way ♫
♫ Pretending to be confident ♫
♫ Brushing past my lonely day ♫
♫ What lies beyond this? ♫
♫ Is this the right path? ♫
♫ Will we find happiness at the end? ♫
♫ Even still, smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Hunched-up shoulders don't suit you ♫
♫ Even brighter than the stars in the night sky ♫
♫ You've lived brilliantly today ♫
♫ Don't hesitate and lift your head ♫
♫ Get up again ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ Even when you fell countless times ♫
♫ Even on days when tears welled up ♫
♫ You endured it all ♫
♫ You are stronger than you think ♫
♫ Smile again ♫
♫ Once more, stand up again ♫
♫ Cheer up and take one more step ♫
♫ Passed over as if unnoticed ♫
♫ My smile etched with thick callouses ♫
♫ Without worries, without worries ♫
♫ Smile for me ♫
♫ It's okay ♫
[May today be the day you meet a bigger ocean and face a wider world.]
[Thank you for watching Namib.]