Aren't you happy to be out here?
I am.
You always talked
about wanting to relax somewhere,
-and you're finally here.
-Yes, I am.
Do you often go on trips?
I do.
Any memorable trips?
Which trip was the most memorable?
Despite not wanting to remember,
there's one trip that I just can't forget.
Did you not hear the question?
And it's also…
Hey, Ung.
TWO DAYS BEFORE UNG'S DEPARTURE
…with Yeon-su.
Ung.
Are you ignoring me?
Didn't we break up?
Really? Did we?
How could you tell me
to just go so easily?
Because you should.
The school is covering the costs.
Are you fine
with being apart for six months?
This is a great opportunity for you
to learn many new things.
Of course, you should go.
Let's go on a trip.
You can go alone.
I'll be going on a long one soon anyway.
Hurry. We need to leave.
Where to?
You wanted to see the sea, so let's go.
Right now?
Just like now, I had no say on this trip.
Yes. I bought the bus tickets already.
Come on.
Why didn't you tell me about this sooner?
SUWON, JANGAN, HOGOK-RI
Don't you smell the sea already?
It was barely a trip.
Who is this trip for?
There's no time. We need to hurry
if we want to catch the bus back.
Is this what I think it is?
Our final trip together?
How could I forget that trip?
Let's hurry. We need to get a move on.
Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-Thanks.
Check this out.
Doesn't it look scrumptious?
It's my treat, so eat up.
Here.
Is thisThe Last Supperor something?
Look at how plump this is.
I've never had this before.
Are you going to treat me to a nice meal
then leave me here?
Just eat.
Eat up. Today is going to be a busy day.
She did whatever she liked.
I'll take it now.
By myself?
Smile. They're all waiting.
-Why aren't you taking it with me?
-All right.
Is this really our final trip?
Before we break up?
I could never read her.
One, two, three.
Done. Let's go.
Can't I just appreciate the view?
You need photos to reminisce.
I want to ponder a bit.
About what?
About our future.
Come on. Why bother
thinking about that while on a trip?
I was thinking about it at home,
but then you dragged me here.
Look at this. You look like a wild deer.
Are you ignoring
everything that I'm saying?
What a shame.
It would have been better during the day.
She never listened to me
Hey. Smile, will you?
I feel like I'm talking to a wall.
We're running out of time.
We need to go to the market.
Hey, let's go.
Take a look.
-What would you like?
-It's a long arm octopus.
-Gosh, they're very fresh.
-Can I touch it?
Of course.
Stop that.
-Goodness. He's such a scaredy-cat.
-Where are you going?
Let's go.
And…
Look at the crabs.
SUWON, JANGAN, HOGOK-RI
Wasn't today fun?
Are you sleeping?
You always frown in your sleep.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Next time, let's take a longer trip.
I took up an extra part-time job,
so I've been way too busy.
I was going to take
the morning shift off but I couldn't.
It was hectic, wasn't it?
This was my first trip,
so I'm still new to it.
Next time, let's stay longer
and go farther away.
Do you want me with you next time too?
Who am I supposed to go with?
Should I go by myself?
She was always like that.
Hey. Are you really stupid?
Why would we break up?
Then you should have told me
instead of making me feel anxious.
Must I say it out loud?
Can't you tell?
I can't. I still can't.
Unless you tell me, I can't read you.
Choi Ung.
Ung.
Look at me.
We're not going to break up.
If we fight or break up again,
just come to me like you did today.
-And then?
-Then…
You could have smiled like this
for the photos.
I need to look at them while you're gone.
Is that why you took them?
You know what? Let's take one now.
-Here?
-Yes.
Okay. Smile.
At times, she'd feel extremely distant.
Other times, she'd pull me closer…
Why aren't you taking it?
What's wrong? Do I have an ugly smile?
I think I love you.
…and make time stop.
Did you know that?
No.
I don't.
So remind me every time.
So how could I forget that moment?
I had no idea then.
I'm not sure.
I don't really enjoy going on trips.
That the promises you make on a trip…
There's nothing memorable.
…are all lies.
EPISODE 8
BEFORE SUNSET
Honestly, I don't know what's going on.
I tagged along just in case.
I do suspect that something's going on
between those two.
Ung has always been irresponsible,
so it's normal for him
to run away or not pick up my calls.
But Yeon-su ran away too.
That made me think
something was going on between the two.
Anyway, I'm not here to relax.
How do I put it?
I'm here to keep an eye on them.
It's my duty as his manager
to take care of his mental health.
They'll figure it out.
After all, they're adults.
But seeing how childish they still are,
I guess I'm the only one
who's growing old.
Oh, my. I didn't know I brought this.
Is there someplace I can swim
around here? Perhaps, an indoor pool?
Anyway, you guys were smart
to lock them up in here.
They're extremely irresponsible.
I'm sure I brought some hangover medicine.
I heard you've known them
for a very long time.
Would you say
that they have changed over time?
To be honest,
they haven't changed one bit.
They were a headache back then,
and they still are.
They're a nuisance
to everyone around them.
By the way, where are they?
Don't tell me they're arguing.
Things have gotten worse.
Why now? Why did we have
if you were going to run away,
you should have gone farther.
That's rich coming from you.
You were caught too.
So? Have you given up?
Are you going to keep filming?
What choice do I have?
You said you were sick of me.
How can we be in the same place
if you're that sick of me?
We really came on another trip.
Next time, let's stay longer.
And it's longer.
And go farther away.
And farther away.
What?
Isn't it the same for you?
You must be sick of this too.
We fight, avoid each other, and run away.
That's what we do.
And now, here we are.
What can we do though?
Do you want some privacy?
No, I'll leave.
Why did I have to remember that now?
Gosh, what a nice view.
Why are you breathing down my neck?
I look forward to learning
many things from you on this trip.
I'll observe every little thing you do.
You better step back
unless you want to be let go.
I already told you, but I'm truly glad
to be a part of your team.
Both you and Ms. Jung
are incredibly talented.
I'm very eager to learn.
I don't like repetition.
I see.
You have two jobs.
Anything, sir!
Number one. Always be ready
to give Chae-ran what she needs.
-I can do that.
-Number two. You shouldn't block my view
when I look around.
What should you do then?
That's it. Simple, right?
Anyway, I'll do my best.
I know you're being cold
because you think I'll quit too.
But I'm not going to quit
and will do my best.
I can assure you
that tenacity is my forte.
I want to become
a competent producer just like you.
Mr. Park said you also made
many mistakes as a rookie.
But thanks to his guidance,
you were able to grow.
So I--
What are you doing?
I will also learn and grow.
My heart flutters the most before filming.
I mean it.
This is the most exciting part of my life.
Don't you feel the same way?
Hey, cut this nonsense
and go help Chae-ran.
-Yes, sir.
-Leave that here.
Yes, sir.
Why would his heart flutter?
My gosh.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
May I take a few more photos here?
-Here?
-Wait, sir.
Is this building in the drawing
the one we're in front of right now?
SEOUL HARDWARE
Yes, you're right.
See? I told you.
He apparently drew many places
in this neighborhood.
Then sir, do you recognize this place?
Hold on.
That's the flower shop over there.
-Let's stop by. Thank you.
-Thank you.
By the way, what is this?
Ho.
WITH UNG
MEALS WITH RICE
Hey, Chang-sik.
Didn't you stop by this morning?
Once a day will do.
Ung must have really put on quite a show.
-I told you it's not that kind of a show.
-No, listen.
Tourists came by
the hardware store and took photos.
They said they came because they saw
my store in one of his drawings.
Oh, that?
"Oh, that?"
What was that? Why aren't you surprised?
-Come here.
-What?
-Gosh, enjoy the food.
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
-Enjoy.
-It's really good.
What would you like?
Don't stare
when they're eating. It's rude.
I thought it was weird
that we had
a lot of young customers recently.
My goodness.
It seems Ung has become quite famous.
Speaking of which, I'm thinking
about hanging his drawings here
and also in the alley.
Then this alley
will become a popular tourist site.
Honey, don't just stand there.
Help me out.
Coming.
Also, I'm thinking
about wearing a name tag.
It's going to say "Ung's Father".
Or maybe a cap with the same writing.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
Can you give me…
SEOUL HARDWARE
…one of his drawings?
Our latest project was a big success.
Good job, everyone.
Soen is very pleased.
It's all thanks to Ms. Kook.
I agree. Ms. Kook, thank you.
Ms. Kook, have a great vacation
Right. Did you read the news?
Everyone loves Go-oh. Here's the link.
GO-OH AND SOEN'S SYNERGY
WHO IS GO-OH?
NJ AND GO-OH'S SPECIAL RELATIONSHIP
GO-OH RECEIVED FLOWERS FROM NJ
I doubt it's special.
What are you mumbling to yourself?
What? Were you filming me?
Well, filming is a part of my job.
But I don't do it in secret,
so don't worry.
As I said before, I'm ethical.
How ethical of you to kidnap me.
You would have run away
had I told you beforehand.
I've lost trust in both of you.
At least I explained everything later.
You're getting very annoying these days.
You should make things up for going AWOL.
You shouldn't have run away.
I wouldn't have
had I known this would happen.
Since you're here,
just relax and take your mind off things.
In front of the camera? How relaxing.
Was there anything
you wanted to do on a trip?
I'm not sure. I never thought about that.
Think now. I'll make it come true.
I know this is all for the documentary.
Geez.
So? How's it going?
What do you mean?
That artist you're interested in.
What? Is it already over?
Don't be absurd. It hasn't even begun.
I'm still working on it,
but I did tell him how I feel.
Again? It doesn't surprise me anymore.
What's with the reaction? How could you?
Can you always act surprised?
With your face,
I would have seduced
every single man out there
and made them ask me out.
Why do you always end up
telling them how you feel first?
What's wrong with expressing my feelings?
This is exactly why you're still single.
Speak for yourself.
Were you ever in a relationship?
Well, I just told him how I feel for now.
He must be taken aback.
He needs some time to think.
He must be confused.
One call from me right now,
and he'll be swayed.
MR. CHOI UNG
The person you have called
Please try calling again later.
What? Is he not picking up?
Look at that. You confessed to him,
and he's not picking up.
This is fascinating.
Hey, you're not done here.
Where do you think you're going?
Why isn't he picking up my call?
This will be the end of your interview.
Now, you can spend the time
however you want, and we'll film you.
Tell me what you'd each like to do.
Can I just lie down?
Of course, you can.
Eighty percent of your footage
is of you lying down,
so keep at it.
What difference will it make?
Just lie down and don't ever get up, okay?
Hey, it took ages to reach downtown.
Imtern, how much
of our company's money did you spend?
She said we needed these.
There are many of us.
This isn't much.
Sol-i is an excellent cook.
I don't get why her business is failing.
Shut up and eat your ice cream.
What is this?
Gosh, we paid
for someone else's stuff. Geez.
-What? Did you want this?
-Yes.
It's my favorite.
You're going to draw?
Yes. What else can I do here?
Where are you going?
Not too far, so don't worry.
I saw many beautiful trees.
Put some more clothes on.
It's cold in the mountains.
I'm not going with you.
What? Then who is?
Chae-ran will.
What about you?
I'm going to visit the village
with Yeon-su.
I see. Suit yourself then.
-Are you ready?
-I don't need to get ready.
Can I do whatever I want?
Sure. Whatever you want.
Hey.
What time do I need to be back by?
Well, there's no set time.
This is a rural area,
so it'll get dark soon.
You should come back early.
Let's go, Ung.
"Ung?"
They were never that close.
I'm speechless.
I'm Ung.
I've been feeling frustrated lately.
But now that I'm here,
I feel a little more liberated.
Also, it's been ages
since I've gone on vacation.
Honestly,
I've never really taken any breaks.
So I don't know how to relax.
I think that's why I always work.
I've only gone on one trip
in my entire life.
Don't you think
I'm born to be on camera?
I was just talking endlessly on my own.
Gosh, I did you another favor.
I have a question.
What is it?
How will you film me
if I get on a bicycle?
I can drive, fly a Helicam,
or set up a camera far away.
In any case, it won't be easy.
I see.
Are you going to?
Okay. Let me call the others--
No, don't. Let's make this simple.
-That'll be a headache for me.
-Exactly.
-You were never this childish.
-Is that a no, then?
What are you doing? Go over there.
Hey.
-Are you done?
-Yes. Let's go.
This is boring, right?
It's okay.
He told me to do whatever I wanted.
I'm always this boring.
I know. I saw all the footage
from ten years ago.
I was boring back then too.
That's why I had no expectations.
Stop hanging out with Ji-ung.
You sound just like him right now.
That's a compliment in my line of work.
How was it?
The footage from ten years ago.
Did you not watch it?
There were parts that didn't air.
That was actually the fun part.
If it was up to me,
I would have re-edited the footage.
Why?
They only showed the lives
of the top and the worst students.
There's a lot we missed out on.
Like what?
You're playing dumb.
After watching the footage,
I could tell exactly when you started
developing feelings for her.
Are you teasing me?
Yes. A bit.
Let me repeat myself.
Don't hang out with Ji-ung.
Then what about now?
How do we look from where you're standing?
I think…
I've said enough.
I shouldn't get involved.
That's how this job works.
-You're quite interesting.
-Thanks.
In return, it'd be nice if you
made things more interesting.
I'll do my best.
Why am I the only one who's exhausted?
Why aren't you tired?
Yeon-su, good stamina is a must
if you want to be a producer.
You sicken me.
Right, you used to be
in the track and field team.
-You remember that?
-You were always running under the sun.
But Ung caught my eye even more
since he was always lying in the shade.
This is nice.
I could totally fall asleep right now.
You must be tired
since we left early in the morning.
I never understood people
who took naps under the shade.
So this is how it feels.
Get some shut-eye. We have a lot of time.
If I nap now,
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
Goodness.
I haven't seen you around before.
Are you visiting?
Yes. We'll be staying for a few days.
I see. You two must be on a trip.
Why would you come here
when there's nothing to see?
But the scenery is nice, right?
Yes, it's a beautiful village.
It's quiet and the air is fresh.
There's a small hill over there.
The view from up there
looks marvelous during sundown.
Go take a look with your girlfriend
when she wakes up.
I will. Thank you.
Goodness. It's good
to be young and in love.
Tell me about it.
So I'm your girlfriend.
And we're young and in love.
Are we?
Well, I didn't feel the need
to correct them.
They were just being nice.
You're back.
I've brought the lighting equipment.
Hey, you're back.
By the way, did you see Eun-ho?
Why? Where did he go?
We went out a while ago,
and I abandoned him.
Well done. But why?
He talks too much.
I just can't take it.
Gosh, he nags so much too.
I get it. Well done.
By the way,
are Ji-ung and Yeon-su not back yet?
No, they're not.
I didn't see them during my drive either.
They must have gone far.
It's getting late though.
I'm sure they'll come back.
Gosh, I'm tired of resting here.
I already miss Seoul.
Sol-i.
How could you abandon me?
I walked 7km in these sandals.
Gosh, Eun-ho is back and in tatters!
Hey. I'll give you a piggyback ride.
Forget it. Go away.
Do you even know how much pain I'm in?
-Let's go.
-Gosh.
WITH UNG
MEALS WITH RICE
-Let's go.
-We've never closed this early before.
Gosh, we're out of ingredients.
Let's wrap up the other shops too
and call it a day.
-Goodness.
Are you closed?
I'm sorry. We've closed early today.
We ran out of ingredients.
So it's empty.
Yes.
That's better for me.
What? Hold on.
She looks familiar.
Is Mr. Choi Ung not here?
I see. Are you a fan of his?
I am, but I'm also here
because he owes me.
-It's good. Try some.
-What?
-It's a bit bland.
-Is it?
This is bland? Is he serious?
Gosh.
Yeon-su, try this.
This is bland? Gosh, that's infuriating.
-Do we have salt?
-Yes, it's in there.
What are you doing? Come out.
Let's eat dinner and call it a day.
-You must have had a lot to film.
-I guess. Why do you ask?
Well, it's just that you came back late.
With Yeon-su.
Never mind.
Also, don't let your juniors
take after you.
Chae-ran must have done well.
Geez. You're a bad influence.
Gosh.
Here. Eat up since it was
a tough day for you.
Sol-i, I can't feel my legs. Am I okay?
It's okay. Rest up, and you'll be fine.
My hands are trembling too.
Why won't it stop?
It's just your imagination. Dig in.
Should we drink later?
You guys better not sleep early today.
We'll be drinking all night, so eat up.
Right. Where did you guys go?
What took you so long?
Somewhere nice?
Well, we biked around the village
and took a nap.
A nap? Outside?
Yes. Why?
Didn't you think
people who took naps were pathetic?
I'm on a trip. I can do whatever I want.
I don't know about that.
Don't you like having
a tight schedule when you're on a trip?
Not every time.
And it also depends on who I'm with.
-You must have gone on many trips.
-I've had my fair share.
-You're getting a call.
-He is?
It's your dad.
What? It's a video call.
I didn't know he could do this.
He's never done it before.
It must be important. Answer it.
-Go on.
-Okay.
The reception is poor.
Hey. It's Ung.
Hi, Ung. How are you?
Did you arrive safely?
You should have called us to let us know.
Dad, who taught you
how to make a video call?
How is Ji-ung doing?
Sure. Your other son is doing fine.
Ji-ung, hi.
Are you having dinner?
Is Yeon-su there too?
-Well…
-Yes, I'm here too.
Did you have dinner?
Of course, we did.
How is it there? Is it nice?
I love it here. The scenery is beautiful
and the air is fresh.
You should take a break
and come here for vacation too.
Of course. We'll ask Ung
to take care of the restaurant
and we'll go on a trip.
Right, Ung. Your friend is here.
My friend?
But all my friends are here.
I'm disappointed.
What? NJ! Why are you there?
What? NJ?
Are you holding a memorial service?
Pull it out.
You haven't run away from me, have you?
Gosh. Goodness.
Hey, I'll be back.
-Me too. Let's go.
-Sit down.
I…
Why did I avoid him like a fool?
Hi, Grandma.
Were you sleeping?
I must have woken you up.
But you sound half asleep.
What is it?
Nothing. Just go to bed early
since we have to shoot tomorrow.
You're being cruel by telling me
to sleep when it's not even 10 p.m.
-What about your pills?
-I had no time to pack them.
Do you want some hot milk?
That's fine. Where are you sleeping?
We got our own place.
We'll come back here tomorrow morning.
Okay.
What is it?
Just say it already,
unless you want to be here all night.
We decided to change the angle
and focus more on you
and Yeon-su's emotions
And?
It confuses me the more I film you two.
Your feelings towards Yeon-su.
Whether it's because of
your past relationship, or…
Or?
Ms. Jung told me today
that people behind the camera
shouldn't get involved.
What are you curious about?
That only applies…
when I'm filming.
I have many questions,
but I'll ask next time. Good night.
It really feels like you're back, Yeon-su.
I'm really sick of this.
Isn't it the same for you?
You must be sick of this too.
We fight, avoid each other, and run away.
That's what we do.
And now, here we are.
What can we do though?
I'm disappointed.
Hey, I'll be back.
It's none of my business now.
Let's forget about it.
Any memorable trips?
I'm not sure.
I don't really enjoy going on trips.
There's nothing memorable.
That hurt.
It confuses me the more I film you two.
Your feelings towards Yeon-su.
Whether it's because of
or…
Is it the past
That's exactly what it is.
But here's the problem.
Despite being in the past…
It was hectic, wasn't it?
This was my first trip,
so I'm still new to it.
Next time, let's stay longer
and go farther away.
If we fight
or break up again,
just come to me like you did today.
I think I love you.
…it's all too vivid.
Did someone tranquilize me last night?
My gosh. I haven't slept this well
in a very long time.
Sol-i, how could you
fall asleep after dinner
when you said we'd party all night long?
By the way, what's wrong with your face?
Were there a lot of bugs last night?
This is how I look in the morning.
Did you sleep well? Where are the others?
Right. If your schedule
isn't too hectic today,
can you let Yeon-su sleep in?
She probably hasn't slept in
like that in ages.
Ung too.
He must have gone to bed late
after drawing all night.
Why would he work during the trip?
It's heartbreaking.
Sure. Let's take it easy.
They're on vacation after all.
Let's check out the site.
But don't you worry about your footage.
You have us.
Right. We'll let you film us instead.
-Let's wrap it up.
-Okay.
Sol-i.
What? Where is everyone?
Are you in there?
Did he have trouble sleeping again?
Was he awake?
Yeon-su.
Yeon-su?
-Yes?
-What distracted you so much?
I'm sorry. What did you just say?
Let's finish the interview
on our way down.
A villager told us about this place
that's beautiful during sundown.
Okay. Sure.
-Let me change the battery.
-Sure.
What? Why aren't you with Chae-ran?
She told me to stay with you instead.
Who do you think you should listen to?
But it seems I came at the right time.
Gosh, she always
makes me do things instead.
Goodness. You're that man from yesterday.
Hello. We meet again.
You must have come in a group.
You're all handsome.
-Where are you going?
-Home, of course.
Right. Did you visit that place
with your girlfriend yesterday?
She's probably
on her way there as we speak.
Geez, not today. It's going to rain soon.
I doubt it will.
Goodness. Can you not tell?
You should hurry back
before you get soaked.
You should have gone there yesterday.
It's a marvelous place. Goodness.
Let's do our final interview here.
Tell me your thoughts on this trip.
Okay.
Wait. I'm low on battery.
I think it'll turn off midway.
I should have packed extra.
I think this has happened before.
Is it a déjà vu?
Should we just go back
to the village and finish up there?
Well, let's just do it here.
You said the view was beautiful.
Then let me go get
some extra batteries and lighting.
Please wait here.
Lately, it feels like I've been spending
Sol-i.
Yes?
I have a question.
Okay. I'm listening.
What are we…
having for dinner?
I see. You're always curious
about the most useless things.
It's actually quite important.
-Light a fire if you're that hungry.
-It's cold.
You spat at me.
You're disgusting. Go away.
Geez. You have a knack
for saying the rudest things.
-Hey. My spit would land on me, not you.
-Gosh.
Gosh, that's cold.
-What?
It landed on me too.
-What is this?
-What?
Is it raining?
-What? Just out of the blue like this?
-Gosh.
-Darn it.
-Come on.
I spent an hour doing my hair!
I told you we should have stayed inside!
What's going on?
Is it raining?
They didn't say it'd rain.
This is definitely a déjà vu.
How refreshing.
I wish the rain would clear my head
of all this needless worrying.
It really is him.
What are you doing there?
Thinking.
About what?
About why I've come to you once again.
How can I explain this?
I must be cursed.
You shouldn't have said that then.
Is it me again? It's my fault?
Yes. It's you again.
I'm sick of it, but it's you again.
Then just go. Don't just stand there.
Am I really cursed?
Then I'll go.
Or has this ridiculous trip bewitched me?
Should I leave or stay?
Or maybe…
I knew all along…
that this would happen
We're not going to break up.
If we fight or break up again,
just come to me like you did today.
-And then?
-And then…
I'll grab onto you and never let go.
JANGAN, HOGOK-RI, IHWA-RI, GOON-RI
BEFORE SUNSET
I must be losing my mind.
But he hasn't called me since then.
Ms. Kook.
What's going on between you and Ms. Kook?
Are you worried that Ung might say
that it was all a mistake?
Do you like Ms. Kook, Ji-ung?
I have no idea what you're thinking
Can I stay over?
I have something I want to hear from you.
So I want to hear you say it now.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim