SEPTEMBER 08, 2011
50 DAYS OF DATING
Yeon-su asks strange questions
from time to time.
What if…
-What?
-I get into college, but you don't?
-I will.
-At this rate, I doubt it.
Do you want me to fail?
No, it's just a what-if question.
What if I get in
but you have to resit the exam?
What will happen to us?
Well…
First, that won't be the case.
But if that happens,
I'll study somewhere near your school.
And I'll pack lunch
and study by your side.
Do you like me that much?
Hey. Why aren't you answering me?
Hey.
Just focus on sweeping, will you?
-You're slacking off.
-I said do you like me that much?
-What's the matter with you?
-Hey.
340 DAYS OF DATING
-What?
-What if…
She'd ask out of nowhere.
What is it this time?
What if you secretly go on a blind date?
Don't be ridiculous. Why would I do that?
Then what if I do?
You're going on a blind date?
No.
-It's just a what-if question.
-Ji-ung will spy on you.
Ji-ung? As if.
I'll stay by your side
at all times to make sure you don't.
What? I'm serious.
I know you finish class at 5 p.m. today.
I'll see you soon.
But we met yesterday.
-Ung, you must really like me.
-Class is starting.
-Bye.
-Hey.
750 DAYS OF DATING
What if I never get better?
What? Don't exaggerate.
Your fever went down a lot.
No, it's just a what-if question.
What if I never get better and--
What? Don't be ridiculous.
I think Yeon-su enjoys watching me suffer.
You're all better.
Get up and have some porridge.
There was a specific answer
that I wanted to hear from him.
1,565 DAYS OF DATING
Ung was strange.
-Hey.
-What?
Are you done? Do you want to switch?
What if…
-Again?
-Yes. What if…
I don't care. Enough with your what-ifs.
What if I go abroad
as an exchange student?
Did you sign up for that?
No, it's just a what-if question.
That would be horrible.
All my friends broke up
after going abroad.
I could feel that he liked me a lot.
What if I get a job
and have to move to someplace far away?
Then I'll follow you and find a job there.
Or I'll just follow you.
Why? Why do you want to be
by my side at all times?
Aren't you tired of our long relationship?
Aren't you?
Do you like me that much or not?
How should I put it?
He never said the most important thing.
-You're annoying.
-How could you hit me?
-Whatever. I'm going home.
-No, wait.
Hey. Why are you suddenly so upset? Hey.
-Hey, don't.
-Don't follow me.
-Hey, what's the matter with you?
-I don't get why she keeps asking me that.
He can't be that dense, can he?
1,670 DAYS OF DATING
And it was when I asked him
that question for the last time…
How peaceful.
What if…
-I told you you have to stop.
-This is the last time. I promise.
I don't get why you do this.
What if we break up?
-We won't.
-It's possible though.
Not for me.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I could leave you.
What if I abandon you?
It's just a what-if question.
Then what will you do?
-I won't see you.
-What?
-I won't see you ever again.
-Ung. You're pretty heartless.
-You'll never see me again?
-Never.
What if I go see you again?
I'll spray water, throw salt,
and kick you out.
I'm not some demon
you need to drive out, you know?
So…
you better not leave me.
He had never looked at me that way.
But maybe
that wasn't a what-if question for her.
You…
What about the salt?
Seeing her here right now…
How did we cross paths again?
EPISODE 2
1792 DAYS OF SUMMER
-Hello.
-Hello. It's just us two today.
-I see. A group of two.
-Hello.
I always come outside
and greet our customers.
Many of them are regulars here.
They're pretty much family…
Hello.
Please go inside.
What is this?
We're filming right now. Be natural.
Don't look at the camera. Look at me.
-Am I being filmed too?
-Just act normal.
Go inside. Go on, sir.
Go inside. Don't look at the camera.
You must be a regular here.
-Ji-ung, what is this?
-Cut!
Chang-sik, please. Come on.
Consider him a producer.
Just be natural and answer his questions.
Stop calling him by his name.
-Okay. I'll watch you.
-Okay.
-Do what you need to do.
-Let's do it again. Action.
-How fascinating.
-Someone watch the counter.
-Excuse me.
What a hectic day.
Ji-ung, where in the world is Ung?
I told him to wake up early today
and help out as the cashier.
That little brat.
-Gosh.
-He has trouble sleeping these days.
Why is that?
He's still struggling?
I thought he had gotten better.
Is he pulling all-nighters
because of his drawings?
Unbelievable. It's all because
he never goes outside.
-Ji-ung, you should--
-No.
I should buy some tonic for my boy.
Honey, call Yong-tae and ask him
to concoct a tonic for him.
-Okay.
-Goodness.
He's not a little boy.
-He's a grown man. Don't exaggerate.
-Be quiet.
Ji-ung, what is Ung up to right now?
He must have just fallen asleep.
I'll visit him after filming today.
Thanks. That'd be great.
Thanks.
-Come here.
-Yes?
I'll visit Yong-tae later
and ask him for the best tonic…
-Have you--
-I'm sure
you didn't come here
to ask me how I've been doing.
-You look--
-I doubt you're here
to tell me that I seem to be doing good.
Seeing how you're not getting upset,
this must be something very important.
How has he become even more unlikeable?
You see…
Hold on.
Are you getting married?
No.
Fine. Keep talking then.
He seems to have changed too.
This is you, isn't it?
-No.
-You didn't even look at it.
I can tell that you're lying.
You're Ko-o.
-I said no.
-I didn't believe it at first.
Because there was no way
you would have worked this hard.
But the places you drew
looked quite familiar.
You don't go to many places.
-They're nothing special.
-And the interview.
You once told me
that you never draw people.
It's common for artists
not to draw people.
Fine. Let's say these are just suspicions.
And this…
is proof.
NJ's manager posted this
on his social media.
Do you see that blurry guy in the back?
That's you no matter how I look at it.
You recognized me?
Ko-o never shows up to his exhibitions
or even when he sells his paintings.
But he met NJ in person
when she bought one from him.
-I'm her fan.
-Okay. Sure, you are.
Anyway, I'm here to see Ko-o,
not Choi Ung.
I have a proposal.
Is that so?
All right.
Make your pitch.
I guess everyone changes
when they become successful.
He's so cocky now.
Sir, we'd like to do a collaboration
between Soen Shop,
a premium lifestyle boutique,
and your work.
We were thinking if you could draw live
on the opening day of Soen Shop.
What do you think?
I refuse.
-Sorry?
-I don't want to.
May I ask why?
I just don't want to.
But still,
if you tell us why you don't want to,
we could make--
No. There's no need for that. It's okay.
-Hey.
-Who are you speaking to?
The artist or Ung?
Are you going to keep being so childish?
I'm not. That's why I'm hearing you out.
Why won't you do it then?
It's because of me.
I don't like being in front of people.
You'd know if you did your research. And…
it's also because of you.
You've changed quite a bit.
I doubt it. I don't feel any different.
Can you please stop being so immature?
Anyway, read this again.
If you change your mind--
Who are you talking to now?
-Ko-o? Ung?
-Hey.
I shouldn't have visited him.
All he did was humiliate me.
-Why are you here, Yeon-su?
-What?
I told you I won't ever see you again.
I wouldn't have come to see you
if it wasn't for this.
So you're here for work?
This is very important to me.
Well, It doesn't seem important enough
to come find me after five years.
How are you still so upset
after five years?
How are you so indifferent
only after five years?
What are you doing?
Am I dreaming?
That woman looks very similar to Yeon-su.
He hasn't changed either.
She even sounds like her.
I can't believe I'm dreaming of you
meeting your ex-girlfriend.
I think we're done here,
so you should go home.
That annoying jerk.
What is it?
Is this not a dream? Is this real?
Why is Yeon-su here?
Come on. Open the door.
Okay.
Who is it?
Seeing how crazy everything is,
I must be dreaming.
-It must be.
-What are you on about?
This has to be a dream.
-What?
-Good morning.
It's okay. That's normal for me.
It's been a while.
Yes, it's been a while,
but you didn't even call.
You rarely pick up at this hour.
-Can I come in?
-Sure.
Who are these people?
-Your employees?
-Yes.
Bye.
Does he think he can look down on me
just because he's successful?
Since when was he so great?
What?
Bye.
I checked one thing off
my bucket list today.
How dare she come here?
What are you doing?
Don't keep her waiting.
You must have had a guest over.
Yes. I didn't expect you to come.
I tend to be welcomed
even when I'm not expected,
so I was a bit thoughtless. Sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
My name is Gu Eun-ho.
I'm Ung's manager.
You can ask me about his exhibitions,
purchasing his work,
and anything else.
Ung? Is that your name?
Yes. I'm Choi Ung.
I see.
Did I come too early today?
Not at all.
Feel free to come whenever you want.
That's why the studio
is open all year round.
-This is my studio--
-If you have any questions,
barge in whenever you wish.
We're honored someone as shabby
as you came to this precious… No.
You're precious. Someone as precious
as you came to this shabby place…
I'm sorry.
It's okay. People tend to stutter
when they talk to me.
Can I see your studio?
Of course, you can. Right?
It's okay, right?
Let me show you around. This way.
I'll never forget this gratifying day.
Sir?
Coming.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
Your food is always delicious.
Gosh, thank you so much.
I hope your business flourishes.
Thank you. Have a great day.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Keep walking. Just go.
-You gave me a free fried egg today.
-Gosh.
You never do that. Thank you.
Just leave. Go.
I own Seoul Hardware.
-and my name is…
-Kook Yeon-su?
How dare you let me look this ugly
in front of her?
You traitor.
This has to be
a gratifying moment, right?
Sir.
This was the moment I've been waiting for.
Sir?
She's calling you.
-Yes?
-Can you draw something for me?
-What is it?
-There's something I'd like you to draw.
I see. But I don't draw people.
I usually draw backgrounds
such as buildings or trees.
It's a building. My building.
-Sorry?
-Please draw the buildings I own.
-Make them look pretty.
-She's incredible.
I find no joy in my life these days.
I'm bored no matter what I do.
This isn't why I worked so hard
all throughout my life.
Oh, dear.
But when I look at my buildings…
How should I put it?
It feels refreshing.
I feel more lively, have an appetite,
and sleep well at night.
Looking at them gives me
a sense of reassurance.
I'm glad.
That's how I feel
when I look at your work too.
I see. Thank you.
I find peace and balance.
Buildings are the only things
that remain the same.
Do you own properties too?
Of course not.
He's paying monthly rent for this place.
So what do you say?
Can you draw one for me?
It'll benefit you if they find out
that I bought another work of yours.
Well, do you think it'll be okay?
You're an idol.
It may tarnish your reputation if people
find out that you own properties.
I don't care.
I couldn't find any joy in life
because I had to maintain
this image people had of me.
I'm going to do
whatever I want from now on.
I see.
Then let me think about--
I'm sure he can do it.
By the way,
didn't you say you were a fan of mine?
Yes, I did.
You don't seem like one today.
Are you already sick of me?
What do you mean?
It just seems like
you're distracted today.
I tend to notice things like this easily.
Oh, that's not why--
I should get going. See you next time.
Let me escort you.
Why does it keep bothering me?
How childish of him.
I don't need him to do me this favor.
I have my pride too.
I'll never let him humiliate me
like this ever again.
I hope you weren't bluffing
when you said you could
get the artist on board.
You're not that pathetic, are you?
I shouldn't have overreacted.
Should I beg him just this once?
No.
He even threw salt at me.
Why were you so distracted?
Hey.
Be careful. It's a narrow alley.
It's been ages.
What brings you here?
I should ask you that question.
Why are you here?
Right. You live here too.
Don't tell me you're here to see Choi Ung.
Don't even get me started.
I came to see the great Ko-o,
-but he treated me like a doormat.
-What do you mean?
Will he never grow up?
He became even more immature.
Did he spray water and throw salt at you?
How did you know?
He practiced doing that
on Eun-ho more than 50 times.
What?
He's crazier than you think.
I had no idea
you'd actually come see him again.
I guess his practice paid off.
It's driving me nuts.
I can't believe I thought
I could talk with him.
-I must have been out of my mind.
-What's wrong?
I had to see him regarding work.
Forget it. What can I do
with that lost cause?
Bye.
Sorry. Look at me.
We haven't met in ages.
How have you been, Ji-ung?
Was I too harsh with the salt?
Grandma, let's eat.
Okay.
My goodness.
Is it already dinner time?
Yes. Eat up and go to bed.
What time is it?
I need to stay up for the drama.
It hasn't started yet. Eat first.
How could someone be so beautiful
and have glowing skin?
Oh, come on.
I just washed my face. That's all.
I've seen her on TV often lately.
How could all her facial features
fit in that tiny face of hers?
Grandma, who's prettier? She or me?
What are you on about?
What? You're really hurting my feelings.
I'm your granddaughter,
and she's a stranger.
She must have a grandma too.
What?
What kind of ridiculous answer is that?
It's the perfect answer
to your absurd question.
Eat up. The food will get cold.
You're unbelievable.
I have your exact personality.
That's why I'm so hot-tempered.
Being hot-tempered
is a must if you're poor.
Don't let others look down on you. Okay?
I've been too kind these days, haven't I?
Maybe that's why
I feel so down these days.
What? Did someone look down on you?
Who was it? Who made you feel that way?
What a scumbag.
Let me have at those jerks.
I'll teach those brats a lesson.
You're definitely my grandma.
Grab this black part
and push it in. It's very simple.
Bring it outside.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Sir.
-Yes?
-Two dark beers for table five.
-Okay.
Hold on. Once you're done with that,
just go home.
Why do you keep coming here
and helping us out? I feel bad.
You give me an allowance.
I should do something in return.
You don't have to.
Sir, two more beers, please.
Sure.
Excuse me.
One minute.
Here are your dark beers. Enjoy.
Yes, what would you like?
-One half-and-half spicy chicken.
-Okay.
One chicken salad.
One tteokbokki
and one chicken feet fried rice.
Okay. But why aren't you drinking?
I will.
-I'll get the food ready.
-Thank you.
Your food is here.
Tteokbokki and chicken feet friend rice.
Are you sure you can finish them?
Sorry? Why would you ask me that?
I can, so don't worry.
That's not why.
This is on the house.
These are crispy tenders.
It's our new dish,
and it's the most popular one.
Really? Are you sure this is for free?
Of course.
Seeing how much you've ordered,
the dishes must be scrumptious.
Do you own a mukbang channel?
I think I've seen you before.
-You're mistaken. Thanks anyway.
-Opened a business nearby?
Yes. What?
It's okay. It's not bad
to size your rivals up.
Many of our customers are like you.
I saw you jotting something.
What did you write?
Where's your shop? What's it called?
-A restaurant? A bar?
-Gosh. I said you're mistaken.
You're making me feel
so uncomfortable that I can't eat.
You see, I'm very close with the owner.
-Should I ask him for the recipes?
-Can you really…
Goodness. Not at all.
You're wrong. What time is it?
Oh, dear. I should get going.
-The bill please.
-What about all this food?
Should I pack them to-go?
Yes. You can do that.
I hope you savor the food slowly
and find out what the recipes are.
Good luck.
Damn it.
-Thank you.
"Super tasty, extremely tasty,
incredibly tasty."
Her business is going to go under.
Gosh.
Why are you sleeping so pitifully
when you look pitiful enough already.
-I couldn't sleep well this morning.
-I heard Yeon-su came by.
Get that away. It's blinding me.
-How did you know?
-I ran into her.
Before or after we met?
-After you threw salt at her.
-Gosh, did she tell you that?
She didn't have to.
I know you've been rehearsing that.
Have you gone insane?
I'm getting secondhand
embarrassment from what you did today.
I had no idea I'd see her again.
So how was it to see her again?
I don't know.
I don't even remember what I said.
You probably babbled on about nothing.
Come on. Are you here to pick a fight?
What? What is it that you want to know?
Let's see…
Your mental age, perhaps?
Stop that.
Hey. By the way,
what else did she say?
Not much.
I see.
Let's go inside. It's chilly.
I'm going home.
What? Then why did you come here?
Beats me.
Bye.
Grandma, I'm off now.
Remember what I told you.
If anyone looks down on you, you ought to…
Okay. Don't you worry.
She made everything simpler.
-I should be more straightforward…
-Good morning.
-…and fix the issue.
-You too.
Ms. Kook, you look like
you're in a good mood today.
Really?
I'll tell him that I couldn't cast Ko-o
and propose an outstanding alternative.
I'll show him what I'm made of
so he won't look down on me anymore.
Oh, and Mr. Bang is with--
Hey, Ms. Kook.
Mr. Jang Do-yul visited us
early in the morning.
I heard the project is going well.
I thought I could do it.
You must clock in late, Ms. Kook.
No, you're mistaken.
For a more free and creative
work environment,
our employees clock in whenever.
Creativity stems from
great work environment after all.
I didn't expect to see you here
so early on a Monday morning.
We have some matters to discuss,
and I'd like to attend
Soen Shop's soft launch together.
All right. Come with me, sir.
I'll go with Ms. Kook.
Isn't she in charge of this project?
Exactly. Going there with a hands-on staff
would be the most efficient.
What are you doing? Go with him.
Yes, sir.
This was unprecedented.
Mr. Jang.
Did you get home safe that night?
Do you…
not remember what happened?
Sorry?
Ms. Kook.
I think you're quite drunk.
I told you. I don't get drunk.
So why would you think that?
Then I'd appreciate it
if you walked in a straight line.
And why aren't you using your umbrella?
Umbrella?
Umbrella…
I…
I don't have an umbrella.
Unfortunately, I don't have…
I don't have an umbrella…
My umbrella…
What is this flashback that I'm having?
Aren't you getting out?
Yes. I am.
We should take my car.
Okay.
Mr. Jang.
Yes, Ms. Kook.
I think
someone is stealing your car right now.
He's not stealing it. He's driving it.
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'll keep a close eye on him.
Okay. Thank you.
Is she okay?
Sir!
Sir, please be careful.
Jang Do-yul has a nasty temper.
He won't show you any mercy.
You know I can hear you, right?
You're awfully quiet, Ms. Kook.
-Sorry?
-Do you remember now?
No. I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about.
You do.
I don't understand.
How much do you remember?
Do you remember calling me a sociopath?
What?
You think you're a sociopath.
Sorry?
You're a cold-hearted man
who won't hesitate
to walk all over someone
to achieve success.
Are you talking about me?
"I may not be able
to empathize with others,
but I'm a cold-hearted man
who's intelligent and good at his job."
Ms. Kook--
Unbelievable.
TVs really give off the wrong image.
My grandma and I watch this drama,
and there's also this character
who's just like you.
People think those bastards are amazing.
but they're just losers.
Ms. Kook.
Don't do something you'll regret--
Stop cutting me off. Will you?
Why do you keep cutting me off?
How would you like it
if I cut your neck off?
Mr. Jang, I'm truly sorry
for what I've done.
I'm really sorry.
So you remember that.
I'm extremely sorry.
I have no excuses.
I was drunk and made a huge--
I thought you never got drunk.
You were incredible.
What can I do for you to forgive me?
It's fine. Please just make sure
this upcoming project goes smoothly.
-Well, you see…
-We're here.
Ung. Hey!
-Ung.
-You startled me.
-I just fell asleep.
-What is this?
What about that?
What is this? Who gave this to you?
Oh, this? Yeon-su did.
Yeon-su? No way. This is what she does?
No. More importantly,
she wanted you to do this?
Unbelievable.
I see. So that's why she came to see you.
Right. She wouldn't have stooped so low
to just come and see you.
What are you talking about?
-You said you'd do it, right?
-I told her no.
Are you nuts? Why would you do that?
Did you even read it?
No. She talked about doing some live show,
so I refused right away.
You know I don't do those.
-You'll be drawing Soen Shop.
-What is that?
It's a new boutique that has launched
in Paris, London, and now, here.
Is this news to you?
You should've said yes immediately.
-You of all people should have done so.
-Why?
Because Jean Ferrat designed it.
How do you not know this
about your favorite architect?
Go to Yeon-su this instant
and tell her you'll do it.
Why did you have to act all tough
and throw salt at her?
What a fool.
Go beg.
WORLD-FAMOUS ARCHITECT, JEAN FERRAT
Damn it. I won't do it.
You must be crazy.
You're opting out of this?
Wait right there. Let me show you.
SOEN SHOP
What? Today is their soft launch.
Today?
Go see for yourself
and decide whether you'll do it or not.
NJ. It's one hour before your rehearsal.
Please get ready.
-Okay.
-Let's get ready.
-He's not calling me.
Who?
That artist.
Did he say he'd call?
Yes. I asked him for a favor.
He said he'd think about it and call me.
How long has it been?
A day and three hours?
Come on. That's not a big deal.
To me, it is.
He's an artist.
A pretty famous one at that.
He must think you're a snob,
so he's taking his time.
That can't be.
Is he handsome?
No. He looks a bit…
like a fool.
Oh, dear. He's just your type.
Exactly.
But why would he not call me
when he's just my type?
Chi-seong. Is my schedule--
No, it's full. It's completely packed.
-Can I skip any of them?
-No, you can't.
You're making up for what you skipped
in the past two weeks,
so that's definitely not an option.
NJ. I can see
that you're racking your brain.
Can you please not do that? Please?
-For my sake.
-Should I call him first?
No.
I've reached out to him too often
when he's not even a celebrity.
No. Since he's an artist,
I guess he's kind of a celebrity.
Then I guess it's no big deal.
Are you going to do it?
-No, I'm not.
-Then why keep watching it?
-Just because.
-It looked fun to me.
Why do you say that?
They're so lively
as if they've been freshly caught.
Are they fish or something?
I liked their chemistry
and their characters.
It's perfect for the early summertime.
They're awkward and young.
It's a documentary
that's more exciting than most dramas.
It's childish, but it also deals with
the worries people their age have.
I could understand
why people love it so much
and want to see them again.
All they did was argue and fight.
Did you see the original?
Watch it, and you'll think otherwise.
The original? When did you watch that?
You're in it a lot too.
-You were rather cute when you were 19.
-Whatever.
Anyway, take a look at it.
No, thanks. I have no time for that.
I'm off to a shoot.
Bye.
EDITING ROOM
Gosh. Why am I doing this?
SBC SPECIAL
The barricades might take up
too much space on the opening day.
-We should remove them.
-Okay.
Hello. This way.
We should make it so
that the guests can tour…
I'll send you an email.
Should I put these items
where they're more visible?
Mr. Jang?
Okay.
That's good.
So? Do you still not want to do it?
Take a look inside.
You'll change your mind.
-Sir.
-Yes?
They're taking turns inspecting
the elevators.
It'll take about 15 minutes.
That's fine. We'll take the escalator.
Let's go.
Our key features
are furniture and lighting,
so put them at the top
of the product placement list.
Also, please utilize
all the areas
within the shop for publicity.
And please make a list of products
that can be showcased in dramas,
variety shows, or documentaries.
Yes, sir.
-Also, about that collaboration--
-Yeon-su.
Yeon-su!
We'll go up. Stay there. Hold on.
I'm sorry.
That's fine.
Should I give you some privacy?
No, you can continue.
Over here.
Hey, Yeon-su.
Here you are.
I brought him here. Aren't you glad?
Hey, drag him out of here.
I didn't want to come here.
I heard you wanted to work with him.
You might as well tell everyone.
Eun-ho, I'm working right now.
Ms. Kook, I can give you
some privacy if you need it.
No, that's okay.
Excuse me, but are you working with her?
Yes. He's the marketing team leader
of Soen Shop.
Really? No way.
We're very interested in this shop.
Ung, did you hear that?
He's the team leader.
Stop embarrassing me. Let's go.
This is only our soft launch,
so it's still a bit hectic.
But I hope you enjoy it.
And if there's any inconvenience
or if you have any suggestions,
please tell our employees on your way out.
Sure, we will.
You're very friendly.
Yeon-su, call me when you're done.
My number is…
Never mind. You can just call Ung.
Make sure you call--
Don't forget to call.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's okay. They're interesting people.
What's the matter?
I'm just surprised
that you weren't offended by--
Is it because
I didn't act like a sociopath?
No. That's not what I meant.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Why is that team leader so good-looking?
They look like a couple and
not work partners that they're together.
You bastard.
How could you tell everyone
about my identity when you're my manager?
Come on. Are you Batman or what?
Why do you keep trying so hard
to hide your identity?
-Shut up.
-Hold up. Are you leaving already?
You're not going to talk with Yeon-su?
I'm going upstairs.
Look at you.
You're totally into this place.
NJ, take a deep breath
at the count of two.
Here we go. One, two.
Done. Okay. Good.
-Unzip me.
-What? Why?
-Hurry up.
-Why?
I did it. What's wrong?
MR. CHOI UNG
READ
Is he crazy?
How could he ignore my text
when he's read it?
That artist?
You've met your match.
He must be writing his reply.
He's just being prudent, right?
How long has it been?
Thirteen minutes?
I really don't get
young people these days.
It's only been 13 minutes.
How childish.
He didn't strike me as the prudent type.
Why is he ignoring me?
Take this off.
-Chi-seong.
-Yes?
She's at it again.
What is it this time?
I can skip the rehearsal.
I need to go out for a bit.
Mr. Jang.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
It's about the collaboration
-with that artist.
-Okay.
I don't think it'll pan out.
Why not?
I wasn't able to contact him.
And through my research,
I found out that he doesn't like
to be seen in public.
-Ms. Kook--
-I know you're disappointed.
I'm truly sorry.
However, I promise that I'll come up
with a better alternative.
You must not remember
what happened at the end.
-Sorry?
-You remember calling me a sociopath
but not what happened
in front of your house that night.
What do you mean?
I found Ko-o.
I didn't want you to look down on me.
That's great news.
I really hoped it wasn't him.
I really didn't expect it to be him.
Sorry?
But how…
How could I possibly see him again?
What do you mean?
How could I…
see that bastard, Choi Ung, again?
Do you personally know Ko-o?
It's been five years since we broke up.
Hey.
Ms. Kook?
Of all the people…
how could I face Ung again?
What in the world did I tell him?
-That man earlier was Ko-o, wasn't he?
-Well--
He seems to know about this project.
If you're uncomfortable
about working with him,
we're willing to replace you
with someone else and proceed with it.
-Mr. Jang--
-Since you were in charge from the start,
it'd be great if you did it.
But we have no choice if you keep letting
your personal matters get in the way.
-Mr. Jang.
-One minute.
You can leave first.
Let me know if anything
new comes up. Goodbye.
Yes?
What is it?
It looks good.
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Aren't you getting in?
Where is Eun-ho?
He's already downstairs.
What's going on?
Right. They said they were inspecting
the elevators.
EMERGENCY CALL
We're in elevator number nine.
Please check.
-It won't take long.
-Why aren't you surprised?
Why should I be?
You said you weren't interested.
Why are you here?
I read the proposal today.
I knew it.
You didn't even read it that day.
How are you still so immature?
I heard you rehearsed
spraying water and salt.
-Did Ji-ung tell you that?
-Grow up, will you?
Was that all you could think up?
What about you?
Was work the only excuse
for you to come see me?
Then what excuse did you expect
to hear when you saw me?
I didn't plan on
acting immature like you did.
It's been five years after all.
What if I was serious
and didn't act childish?
Would you have managed?
If you were sincere,
what would you have done?
I'm sorry. They must have made a mistake.
No, it's okay.
I am childish.
I just ran away.
Hi.
What?
NJ, what brings you here?
-Where's your phone?
-My phone? It's right here.
I see. You didn't lose it.
Then why did you ignore me?
Oh, that. I put it off
because I wanted to think
-before replying.
-You put off my text?
-Then what were you doing in the meantime?
-I went out.
What are you doing here?
Why did you come here?
No particular reason.
I was wondering why you ignored me.
But aren't you busy?
Don't you have a packed schedule?
I was going to leave in five minutes.
I have a live stage scheduled.
I just had some free time.
-All the way here?
-I'm usually too busy to be bored,
but things have changed these days.
I wanted to see what you were doing
instead of replying to my text.
What?
You're very…
Well…
Unique.
-I'm running late. Goodbye.
-Is that really why you came here?
If you want to find out,
ignore my text again.
Let's go.
SBC SPECIAL
HWIYEONG HIGH SCHOOL
Hey.
I'll do it. I'm up for it.
SBC SPECIAL
What? What do you want me to do?
-What?
-You need to do it.
Gosh, don't annoy me.
I need to do it, so you have to do it too.
-Does Dad want to film me too?
-No, not that.
You and Yeon-su.
Let's film that documentary again.
Are you insane? Why would I?
Do you think I'm a doormat?
Hello, my name is Choi Ung.
EPILOGUE
My name is…
Gosh, do we really have to do this?
1792 DAYS OF SUMMER
Why do you think people decide
to star in a documentary?
My skin used to be so elastic.
Oh, things I hate?
It's still Kook Yeon-su.
To put Ung and Yeon-su together…
Wouldn't that be disastrous?
Wait. My crutch!
Why would I? You mean nothing to me.
She's so selfish
and always so full of herself.
Let's see who wins.
How precious it is to be able to
capture and store a moment in your life.
Be honest with me.
Does that really mean nothing to you?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim