National Radio. And Telvison Administration
Wait.
What's wrong?
Sir, what’s your name?
Yanyan.
Yan Yunyun.
Yunyun, don’t worry.
Don’t be nervous.
These two doctors
are the best doctors in our center.
We have to trust them.
We have to believe in fire.
Stop it. Stop it.
Hurry up. Stop talking.
Let's talk when it's done
Qi Tuo, put your hands on it.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Hang in there, far.
I got it.
It's okay.
Chi, calm down.
Hold on.
Hang in there.
All right.
It's okay. Come on.
Alright
Slow down.
Slowly.
Stretcher. Come on.
Okay, right away.
Come on.
Is Zheng Bo not here yet?
Coming.
Bo, hurry up.
Hurry up, Zheng Bo.
Hurry up.
Slowly.
He can only sit because he has difficulty breathing.
Sit down.
Zheng Bo, be careful.
It should be stuck in the soil.
Okay.
You have to dig out the soil first.
Come on.
Slow down.
Low blood sugar.
He can only sit when he can't breathe.
Slow down.
After the examination,
send him to the hospital for an X-ray.
Let's go there first.
Come on.
One two three
Be careful.
Hold it. Hold it.
Hang in there.
Slow down. It's okay.
It's slightly slippery.
It's okay.
Hang in there. It's okay.
Slowly
Take your time.
One, two, three.
Come on, Wang City.
Move back a little. It didn't match.
Okay, the front is matched.
Slow down.
Come, hold him.
I'll hold him.
Behind you.
Come on.
Lock it up
Yuan Yuan, get in the car. Hurry up.
OFFRI
Hurry, get in.
Close the door. Get in.
Close the door.
Slow down. Go.
Slowly.
Let's go.
Gauze.
Here.
Lift it.
Three, two, one.
Stretcher.
Take your time.
Side. Side. Side.
Raise your legs here.
One, two, three. Okay, slow down.
Slowly.
Come on.
Let's go. Slow down.
Be careful.
Don't look.
The data is normal.
Jiangdong EMSS Emergency.
Only you are a doctor.
I can understand.
This is too close to the heart.
It's probably pricked.
Once you enter the operating room,
you might not be able to come out.
Stop it.
I won't die.
Why are you in a hurry?
Master.
Zhang Chi.
I'm really happy
I'm really happy.
Stop talking, Xu Chengyuan.
Let me finish.
If I go into the operating room,
I won't be able to get out.
I won't have a chance to say it.
Look.
Who would have thought
I would end up in this mess?
So,
I don't know
I don't know which one will go first.
Zhang Chi.
Master.
Take care of yourselves.
and be happy.
If you keep talking, I'll...
I'll scold you for real.
Fine, I won’t.
Jiangdong LMSS emergency.
I'm hanging up.
Master! Master!
What?
Come here.
Don't cry for me in front of Zhang Chi.
Give it to me.
Get me a needle and come quickly.
Okay.
I'll give you a needle.
Stop talking.
You don't listen to me.
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Jiangdong Emergency
Don't worry.
Stop it.
I'll be fine.
I'm lucky.
Don't worry.
Jiangdong LMSS Emergency.
Gangdong LMSS Emergency!
The surgery is over.
Dr. Oh.
How was the surgery?
He's only two centimeters away from the heart.
It's only this close to the major blood vessel.
Where is he?
He's fine.
He's lucky.
But
he needs to be hospitalized for a few days.
Don't stay here. Go back and rest.
Thank you.
Let me tell you again.
no matter what happens,
be careful.
We must evacuate as soon as possible
we must evacuate as soon as possible.
This time,
is inevitable.
Fortunately, he was saved.
During his absence,
we need to
should be adjusted.
Zhang Chi.
You've been in the center for a while.
From now on,
you'll lead Xu Chengyuan's team
until he comes back.
Okay.
If anything happens, 008401.
If anything happens, 84001.
If anything happens,
if anything happens.
Got it.
What are you doing?
Are you making trouble for me?
The doctor doesn't allow you to be discharged.
You can't be discharged.
Why didn't you listen?
What doctor said?
I'm a doctor.
Who wants to be discharged?
Let's see who's going to be discharged.
You're leaving?
You scared me.
Sister Qi, Dr. Zhang, you're here.
Sit down.
No, sit down.
Sit here.
The doctor said
I've recovered.
I can't live here anymore.
I'll go crazy if I go on like this.
I'm going crazy.
Being crazy is better than being dead.
Are you... Do you have any superpower?
Are you Wolverine?
Why don't you stay in the hospital?
Do you want to die?
What's wrong with our center?
what's going on in our center.
We're short of hands.
I'm short of hands. Are you?
You're a loser now.
Do you know what you're doing?
I...
Sister Qi, stop talking about him.
It's still bleeding
Let me tell you.
If you don't stay here for 50 days,
I'll beat you until you stay for another 50 days.
Do you hear me?
Lie down. Hurry up.
Jia Qi is looking for you.
So gossipy.
Isn't that normal?
Well...
My app The investor
to talk to me.
You haven't confessed to her yet?
What are you waiting for?
I just want to make some achievements
and tell her something else.
She doesn't care about that.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Well...
I'm going to talk with the boss.
I'm leaving.
Bye. Take care of yourself.
Hurry up. Okay.
I'll listen to Sister Qi.
Got it.
Move.
Lie down.
What are you thinking?
Get out.
I said,
After I was discharged,
after I was discharged.
You don't need to go for the examination.
The doctor said
this is a critical time.
Don't take it lightly.
You should be more careful.
Don't worry.
Everything is under my control.
Stop working.
Take a rest.
Okay.
I'm going up
Qi
Let me see what's going on
Coming
Qi hurry up
It'll be ready soon
What's wrong?
What news?
Why are you laughing like that?
Why are you laughing?
I just want...
Let me see.
There's someone funny.
You didn't let me see it but you sneaked into it.
Watch some serious news.
Zhang Chi.
Dong Liang from the gas station is sentenced today.
He will be sentenced to life.
He deserved it.
When I think about it, I was really scared that day.
There was a mistake in the middle.
There are school kindergarten nearby.
Of course.
We're really lucky.
Yes, not two lives.
If it explodes,
no one can escape.
If we have kids in the future,
If something like this happens,
I can only go alone.
Someone has to take care of the child.
You're thinking too far.
You even have kids.
How can this happen so often?
No.
What do you mean? Haven't you thought about it?
No, that's not necessary.
You need someone to help you.
Listen.
Dating without marriage
is to play hooligans.
Haven't you heard of that?
Who's a bully?
Who said that?
If you do this, I won't be polite.
What are you doing, Zhang Chi?
Help me, Zhang Chi.
You have to take me to the hospital.
You're going to crush me.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Let's go.
Okay.
What do you want for dinner?
Have a drumstick, Chi.
Make one
Chicken leg again?
I'm going to...
Wait, my mom.
What's wrong with Mom?
What?
Mom.
What's going on?
What happened?
Qi Tuo
Your dad.
Your dad was drunk driving.
The car went out of control and hit three people.
He quit drinking.
Why did he drink and drive? Why?
He has Alcohol dependence.
When did that happen?
Why didn't I know?
You told him to quit drinking.
he had been controlling it.
He just drank a little.
I think his business is hard.
I just turned a blind eye
I thought he could control it.
But unexpectedly,
I don't know what's going on.
I'm addicted to alcohol.
He's even better than before.
It's okay.
Is it serious?
I didn't see him either.
I heard they are all in the hospital.
Where is Qi Xuejun?
Get out!
Qi Xuejun, come out!
Are you Qi Xuejun's family?
My son went to school this morning.
I was hit by him.
Drinking and driving?
My dad went to buy groceries.
Why did I meet this crazy man?
Your husband is a troublemaker.
Let him out.
We are Qi Xuejun's family.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
What's the use of apologizing?
Please calm down.
No one wants to see
what happened today.
But the most important thing now is to save the injured.
to minimize the damage to them.
Don't worry.
We will try our best
We'll try our best to satisfy you.
My name is Zhang Chi.
I'm Qi Xuejun's son-in-law.
This is my WeChat.
You can call me anytime if you need anything.
We will try our best to satisfy you.
We will never escape responsibility.
Have some water.
The doctor said
the treatment went well.
I guess Uncle Qi will wake up soon.
Who would have thought this would happen?
I was fooled.
It's fine as long as he's fine.
That's the most important thing, right?
Okay.
How is it?
Qu.
Did the surgery go well?
He said there was no fatal injury.
It's nothing serious.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have kept it from you for Uncle.
If I told you earlier,
this wouldn't have happened.
You knew he had Alcohol dependence?
I went to a bar with him.
He was drunk.
When I sent him home,
Aunt told me.
I've been controlling it well.
It just relapsed recently.
Uncle didn't let me tell you
because he didn't want you to worry.
No, it was under control.
Why does it relapse?
What's the reason?
Maybe it's because
the car accident 20 years ago.
has hurt him a lot.
What do you mean?
20 years ago,
the car accident I was with my dad.
Yes, after the accident,
after the car accident.
The reason he was like this
because of the doctor who died in a car accident.
caused his stress disorder.
He can only paralyze himself with alcohol.
I heard that doctor is a cardiac surgeon.
He saved a lot of people.
and a child.
So over the years,
all these years.
My mom was the youngest cardiac surgeon
in the city hospital.
I'll go buy something.
Qi Tuo, I'm relieved that Uncle is fine.
Take good care of him.
I'll come back next time.
Qiqi.
Dad.
How do you feel?
I feel...
Where is this?
In the hospital.
Did you drink and drive?
A car accident.
You're fine after the surgery.
Drive. There was an accident.
Did you hit anyone?
I don't want to see
20 years ago.
I made another mistake 20 years ago.
Dad.
Hey, hey. Hey.
20 years ago,
the car accident we had together.
in the car accident
What's his name?
How did you know?
Your mom told you.
Yes.
After that accident,
every time I think about this,
I feel scared.
All these years,
this has always been my problem.
Dad, do you remember
Do you remember her name?
Of course I do.
I've never forgotten.
Never.
Her name is
Qin Shuhua.
Zhang Chi.
Qi.
Was that Zhang Chi?
Why did he leave?
Qin Shuhua.
Zhang Chi's mom.
Dad.
Dad, I need to go out.
I can't leave him alone.
I'll be right back.
Qi Qi
Come on.
Dad.
Doctor!
Blood oxygen.
Dad, I'm here.
The patient's cardiopulmonary function is not good.
He can't breathe on his own.
We have to intubate him immediately.
Does his family agree?
Yes, yes.
Dad, dad is fine.
It's okay.
What's wrong, Chi?
Are you not in a good mood without Sister Qi?
There's an old saying.
life and death
other than life and death.
Everything will be fine.
0108 Bulk Team, Emergency Mission.
An old man passed out at home in Sunshine Community.
Copy that.
Get out! Get out!
Qiqi.
You're awake, dad.
How do you feel?
Not bad.
Let me ask you.
Did I hit anyone
Did I hit anyone?
How are they?
Dad, just take care of yourself.
I'll take care of the rest.
It's better to get yourself ready first.
Okay.
No matter how much it costs,
you have to compensate him.
Ask the best doctor to use the best medicine.
Okay.
No.
Get our tea room out.
Okay, I'll deal with it when I'm free.
Don’t delay your work.
Let Qu help me alone.
Don’t bother her.
She's not related to us.
Listen to me, Qi Qi.
Everyone has their own strengths.
I know more about Qu than you do.
Ask him to sell the tea room.
Just give him the commission.
This time,
I've caused you a lot of trouble.
You still need to handle a lot of things.
Stop talking and get some sleep.
I'll call him.
Qi Qi.
Zhang Chi.
to Zhang Chi.
Hello, Qu.
Can you do me a favor?
to see if
buy my dad's tea room.
It doesn't matter if the price is lower.
It's better to pay in full.
Okay.
Come and get the key whenever you have time.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Mom.
Mom, where are you?
Mom!
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect
would happen between us.
I'm sorry, Zhang Chi.
Don't be sorry.
It's not up to us
can't be decided by us.
My dad wants to see you.
and apologize to you in person.
OK?
Zhang Chi.
After that, I found out
the female doctor I bumped into
is the Head of Cardio Surgery at the North Hospital.
She worked hard all her life
and saved many lives.
I...
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to those who got hurt
in the accident.
I know.
The most helpless thing in the world is an apology.
But the only thing I can do now
is to apologize.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Take care of yourself.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't been distracted,
when she hit me,
I could have avoided it.
But I still...
What did you say?
When she hit me,
I turned my head
and talked to Qiqi.
Qiqi, are you happy?
Yes.
I wish I could come out every day.
Then you have to get 100 points every day.
No problem, Dad.
What's that? A new friend?
What's your name?
Ma Hua.
Ma Hua is so cute.
When I turn around,
she already hit me.
I still couldn't avoid it.
No.
You mean she hit you?
You didn't hit her.
Then she...
She committed suicide.
I didn't shirk my responsibility.
She did bump into me.
There's an accident report.
That's what the court police think.
Although I took the main responsibility,
but your mother...
It's true that she died.
I shouldn't have come.
Zhang Chi.
He came to me today to apologize.
I can't accept it emotionally,
Reason tells me
it was an accident.
I'm here.
What did he just say?
My mom committed suicide.
What is he doing?
Isn't he shirking the responsibility?
Because of him,
because he shielded the responsibility.
I didn't mean to defend him.
He hit someone.
There's no excuse to escape.
But in that situation,
he had no reason to lie.
What's the point of lying?
I don't know what it means.
My mom is 28 years old.
when she was 28.
The first heart transplant surgery in the province
was done by my mom.
She's the best in the provincial city. She did so much.
She has such a successful career.
Her husband loves her and her son listens to her.
Why did she commit suicide?
I don't know why she committed suicide.
I want to know too.
I only know that my dad
he wouldn't lie.
I trust him.
He can't lie now.
Leave me alone.
Zhang Chi.
I really admire you.
You're the only one
I just
to make a bed for you as soon as possible.
Cut the crap.
Go back and rest for a month.
Don't rush to work.
Come to me for a check-up one month later.
Okay, I got it.
I'm a doctor too.
I know what to do.
My phone.
I'm leaving.
Okay, thank you.
Hello, master.
Do you have sharp eyes
or pleasant ears?
You caught me
I was caught by you.
You're discharged?
You confessed.
I've stayed here for 50 days
for 50 days.
I'm going back to the center tomorrow
and fight with you.
Well...
Something happened to my family.
I can't go back for a while.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I need your help.
Okay, I got it.
She did bump into me.
That's what the court police think.
I only know that my dad
he wouldn't lie.
I trust him.
He can't lie right now.
Mom, I'm done.
Okay, let me see.
Good.
Looks like you know a lot of words.
What book are you reading?
I borrowed math books from my neighbor.
This is the math for the third grade.
Can you understand it?
Most of them.
Let me give you a quiz.
What is a seduction theory?
Hook theory is a triangle.
The square on two angles
equals to the square on the diagonal side.
So A plus B equals C.
Sure.
Let me test you something harder.
What is intersection string theory?
The two strings intertwine in the circle.
Two lines separate at the intersection.
They have the same accumulation.
If string AB and string CD intersection is P point,
it means PA multiplying PB equals PC multiplying PD.
If the strings and diameters are intertwined,
it's half of the strings.
It's multiplied in a diameter.
between two lines.
Chi, you're amazing.
You got everything right.
Tell me.
What reward do you want?
I want to eat your cooking.
Read the book.
Mom, I'll make you fried rice with egg.
Hello?
Is Dr. Qin home?
Actor table.
Qi, Chen, Ren Suxi.
Bo Liu Yi.
Sun Jiaqi Zhang Yu Xi
Zhang Beihai Jiang Yiyi
Qin Shuhua
Xu Chengyuan, Wei Tianhao.
Sun Yimo, Liu Xinglin.
Qu Yufan, Wu Chengxuan
Old Zhang Beihai Sun Youning
Qi Xuejun, Zhao Chengshun
Xiao Yue, Liu Yi Zhen.
Chen Xue, Xu Shendong.
Huang Hao, Liu Shuyuan.
Gao Guangze.
Dong Xiao Qiu, Cao Lu.
Chen Guizhi
Li Xiaohong.
Xin Haojiang.
Dong Liang Qian Youchen.
Peach, Ding Yi.
Director Dai, Wang Zhengjun.
Liang, Tong Xiaohu.
Sun Yimo, Yu Xiaochun.
Wu Xiaoyue, Lu Qian.
Li, Jun, Lu Mei Fang.
Zheng Bo's father, Zheng Da,
Fang Qiqi, Gao Xianghai,
Cheng Xiaoyan Pang Danjing
Wang Tao, Wang Tao.
Zhang Chi, seven years old, Chen Tianyou.
Zhang Chi, Yu Bi Cheng.
Wang Jianguo, Qin, Hai.
Kui Lifang Ren Zijie
Lijun's mother, Ge Zhaumi.
Mr. Jiang, Luo Lei.
Yang Jing, Gao Ruoxin.
Ren Jie, Liao Juan.
Mu Shengying.
Weibo Wang City.
Yuan Yuan, Yuan, Ge Linfei.
Xu promise, Zhen.
Wedding girl, Zhu Su Jie.
Liying Feng Xingqi.
Tian Limei, Shang, Youning.
Chao Chao's mom, Dai Qihua.
Chao Chao's dad, Chi Rui Lin.
Chao Chao, Chen Long'an.
Dandan's mother, Wang, Zhang.
Yang Yang's dad, Ni Min Hao.
Yang Yang Xie Haoting
Lu Ang, Wang Jingyu.
Huazi's wife, Ma Yuan Li.
[Mother of the dump, Wang Yuan.]
Chief Zhu, the door, three.
Ma Bai Qi Guangfei.
Meng Xiang Fang Guangnan.
Xiaoyu Wan Shuya.
Xiaodie Zhang Ying
Eagle Clothed Man Wang Kun
Pregnant woman Shao Yifan
Mrs. Cui.
Liao Xiaomei, Yan Wenjun.
Liao, father, Zhang Xiaoming.
Liao's mother, Wu Fei.
Mr. Yan, Xiao Wei.
Youth Qi Xuejun Chen Wenwen
The girls are together, Ye Xuantong.
Sun Jiayi, Huang Jingwen.
Hu Xiaodie, Xiang Zeren.
Jia Jia, Wang Yi.
Qianqian, Zhang Yanqi.
Liang's wife Yan Jingli
Lin Guangwen's son, Sun Dake.
Captain Wang, Geng Dayong.
Zhao, Jie, Su Wenwen.
Dr. Sun, Zhang, Yi
The man with the duck tongue cap, Cheng, Zhen.
Aunt Jia Jia, Wang Li Shun.
Yun Yun's mother, Liao Song Mei.
Director Sun of the Health Commission, Zhang Yiming.
Game Boy Xu Yiyi.
negotiator, Li Yan.
Middle-aged traffic police, Huang Xufei.
Mr. Guo, Chen Xiaodong.
Professor Wang, Hu Kai.
Nana Liu
and actors.
Feng Fan, Zhou Renliang, Xing Lei, Zhang Lanxing, Wang Yijun.
Performers.
Hao, Zhejiang, Zhang Yaoxing, Zhang Zekun, Cai Wenbin, Zhuo Shaohua, Meng, Yu, Ning Qixuan.
Huang Zhenghui, Huang Fengrong, Long Xinyue, Tian Chengwei. Du Shuhan, Lin, Mo, Cheng Xiaogang.
Lin Zhixian Lei Liuqin Hu Bohao Yan Shanshan Peng, Yang, Li Jiayu, Hao Yunshuang.
Tang Jinyu, Cai Hunwei, He, Nan, Meng Sijing. Shi Zi'an, Xu, Yan, Xu, Xu, Fei.
Wang Tieyan Huang Wenqi Du Xinjie Huang Xuanye Ge Qingwei Wang Jingru Guo Shaojie
Luo Zu Su, Cai Yufei, Cai Yulin, Wu Nuo Xi Li Zhaixiang
Staff Form.
You're here. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
The production team.
Executive Producer, Wang Pin Ken, Liu Xinyue
Producer director Instructor Fu
Assistant Producer: Li Jiaqi, Huang Yiyi
Outer Producer Huang Wenxin Gao Hao
Life producer, Mjurrong Qiang.
Late production, Liu Xinyue.
to purchase Chen Weimin.
He's in charge of Zhu Yayun.
Drama Pictures Zhang Xingxing Chang Yujie
Zhang Qunbo, Du Yiwei.
behind the scenes, Chen Junjie.
PR Plan Song Won Min Wang Pil Seung
The director team (Team A).
Director Liming, XIN Liu.
Executive director Fu Bin
Cai Xiaoyan.
Director assistant, Ma Qing Qing.
Director team (Team B)
Executive director Wang Zhaotao.
Vice director Ren Peng.
The scene record is the couple.
The audition team.
ZD Auditing Studio.
Auditing director, Zheng Haoyu.
Actors Organize Zhuang Yin Ming
Vice director Nie Zhen Le Liu Haohao
Photographer group (Team A).
Camera A, Li Weicheng.
The second assistant of Camera A, Zhong Yuu.
The third assistant of Camera A, go, go.
Photographer Zhu Jiajia.
Second assistant of Phone B, Cheng Linhao.
Yuan Zhili, the third assistant of the B phone.
Camera C, focus, Liu, Yong.
The second assistant of Camera C, kiki Pan.
Mobile team leader Ma Mingse Wang Lili
The first assistant, Ma Mingzhi.
Moving the third assistant, Li, Ha Honghao.
Photographer, Zhao Minyang, Zhang Li Cheng. Xu Ting Xiao.
Moving and robot, Hwang Chou-seung.
Photographer team (Team B)
Camera A photographer Cheng Guojie
Camera A focus, Chen Chuang.
The second assistant of Camera A, Zhang Weiwei.
Photographer B, Zhu Jiajia.
Focus on B, Shi Fengfeng.
Yuan Zhili, the third assistant of the B phone.
Mobile team leader, An Chang Liang.
Lee Ahn, the first assistant.
Move the second assistant, An Jiahe.
Moving the third assistant Bruce Lee
Moving the fourth assistant Lü Linlin
Moving and player Yue Haijun.
Lighting team.
Shi Yuan.
Lighting Master Yang Chengwu.
He Pin Bo, lanterner.
Lighter Kwok Ki-liang.
The lighter, Jo Min-sung.
Team A.
Film team. Okay.
Medical consultant.
Lin Jiankong, Hong Jianfang, Hu Yuanyang, Teng Ling Fang, Li Jizhong, Chen Zhi.
The post-production team.
DIT Li Haoming.
DIT Chen Ke.
Art team.
Sub-art Liu Baibat Wang Hongyang
Chen Xiao Ting, Li Shu Ling
The atmosphere map, Dong Mengyao.
Scene-survey art, Wu Yanling.
Props set team.
The set team leader, Fang Xingwang.
Vice-leader of props, He Jinlu.
The prop for the play, Lü Kang.
Focus on Team A, Fang Kaixin.
Vice-monitor (Team A) Fu Weibiao.
Vice-monitor (Team B) Cui Kang Jing.
Costume team.
Costume design, Liu Peng.
Yu Xinyi.
Costume main focus, Luo Jie.
Costume assistant Rex Zhang.
Costume tailor, Li Ke Jun.
Costume assistant, Chu Dalin.
Costume assistant, Luo Yan Zhang called his brother.
The dressing team (Team A)
The makeup team leader, Kwok Jinjin.
Makeup artist Zhang Haolin.
Makeup Daisuke, Pan Jiadong.
The makeup site focuses on Nie Dongxin.
He Xingliang, the makeup team leader.
Makeup artist Cheng Xianyu.
The main focus on the makeup scene is Xie Zhaoyu.
Makeup assistant Li Yafei.
The dressing team.
Action team.
Action director, Lim Hyun-chul.
Action guidance, Cai Wenbin.
Team A.
Producer Zhang Bin
Director Zhang Yongqiang.
Manager Han Bo-sung.
Late production.
Late video production.
Beijing Fishinson Culture Co., Ltd.
Video Director Chen Yifriend
Video technology, Hu Weiwei.
Cooperate Hu Weiwei.
Digital color.
Visual Director Zhang Na.
3D production Wang Chun
Digital picture, Hou Jiacheng.
Audio production.
Beijing Orange Yisheng Culture Co., Ltd.
Voice director, Huang Bin.
Voice Effect Liu Jian Li Teng Fan
Foley master, Shi, Shi, Shi Yifu.
ADR recording Huang Bin Li Yan Mei
Sonic Huang Bin.
Mr. Zhang, voice mixing assistant.
Music design, Huang Bin.
Music editor Jiang Zeyu Liu Yanzi
Dubbing director.
Dubber.
Guo Hao, Li Jin, Sun Jin, Liang, Yang Rui Xin, Li Yang, Tang Zichu.
Music Producer.
Jia Tao Music Studio.
Music Planner, Wang Jie.
Song production.
The first song, Wind.
composed by Jia Tao.
Arranger Liu Wen.
The ending song, Warm Light.
Singer Zhang Yu Xi.
Lyrics He Lihua
Arranger Zheng Kun.
Producer Jia Qitao
Studio, Beijing Jintian Studio
Arrange "Warm You".
Singing Liu Yiwan
Lyrics, Yu, Jia, Tao.
Arrangement: Rao Yongheng.
Producer Jia Qitao
Arrange "The Replay of Love".
Singer Wei Tianhao, Cao Lu.
Arranger Zheng Kun.
Producer Jia Qitao
The Last Light of Night.
Lyrics: Luan Fuhai
Lyrics by Luan Fuhai
Singing Wei Tianhao
Production company, Beijing's first visual
"The Sea of Time" (Promotion Song)
composed by Liu Jiaxian.
Singing Wang Yushu
Production company, Beijing's first visual
The preview of the film.
Hu Siyuan, Yang Zhenwu.
Beijing Bochuan Haina Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
edited by Liu Lei.
On the surface, Wang Le, Zhang Lina.
Guangzhou Seven Diagram Visual Design Co., Ltd.
Project Manager Zheng Wei.
Project Planning, Zheng Pei Xin.
Late-production.
Beijing Central TV and Northern Film Production Co., Ltd.
Director Li Yue.
Gu Yu and Xie Bing are in charge.
Marketing company.
Beijing Sleeping Sky, Yiyu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Marketing Zhang Jinyang
[Marketing Director Tian Yuan]
Project Manager Ren Ruoshi Chen Jie
Project Planning, senior three, Bai, Tao.
Project Manager Zhang.
Exclusive CTV8
premiere platform, TV series,
iQIYI
Quan Zhou City People's Government
Chunzhou City Cultural Guangdong and Tourism Bureau
Quan Zhou City Health Commission.
The PR Department of Luojiang District Committee of Zhonghong Chungzhou
[Chunju City Pungtaek District Cultural Sports and Tourism Bureau]
[Chunju City Table Investment Committee]
Chunju Emergency Command Center.
Emergency Command Center of Jinjiang City.
Health Department of Anxi County.
Quanzhou Binhai Hospital.
Anxi County Hospital.
Quanzhou Luojiang District Hospital.
Shenzhen Meili Biology and Electronic Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Fengze Cultural Foundation Park.
Quanzhou Travel Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Fujian Province Mindong geology Brigade
Fujian Quanzhou Pink Group.
Fujian Province Quanlong Health Development Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Wanke Company Co., Ltd.
Chunju Jinjiang International Airport Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Binjiang crown holiday hotel.
Quan Zhou Hao'an Trading Co., Ltd.
Chunzhou City Yinghong Fuling Park Co., Ltd.
Jinwei holiday Hotel, Quanzhou, Fujian Province.
National ceramic industrial design institute.
The capital of pottery in the world, Dehua.
Li Ning (China) Sports supplies Co., Ltd.
Selis Motors.
Fujian Boergege supply chain Co., Ltd.
Beijing Taotao Technology Co., Ltd.
Phoenix Network Phoenix Network Entertainment
Production unit.
Zhejiang Kunse Film Co., Ltd.
Qunzhou Kunse Film Co., Ltd.