National Radio And Telvison Administration
Beihai, here's a toast to you
Come on
Come on, come on, come on
Look at this. Look at this. Look at this.
He only drank one kilo of liquor.
Shu Hua is getting married today.
As her family, I must do it.
When did you
become Miss Qin's family?
You have no idea.
Shu Hua and I grew up together
Zhang Beihai I tell you
If you treat Shu Hua badly
and bully her,
I won't forgive you.
I'll keep my eyes on you.
I'll supervise you for the rest of your life.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Have more wine.
I've been staring at you.
Happy wedding.
Happy wedding!
Cheers.
Let's eat.
Honey.
Brother Zhang.
Brother Zhang
I'm Guizhi.
Are you home?
My son is sick.
Brother Zhang, are you home?
Why is it her again?
Brother Zhang, I'm Gui Zhi.
Brother Zhang, open the door!
Brother Zhang!
Brother Zhang.
Coming
Poppet, Poppet has a fever.
He was shivering just now.
He fainted.
Go take a look.
Go back and take care of the kid.
I'll be right there.
Okay, hurry up.
Okay.
How is it?
I got a fever reducer.
His temperature has dropped.
But I suggest
take her to the hospital.
It's all my fault.
I didn't take good care of him.
Don't cry.
The baby is fine now.
Be strong.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
Brother Zhang.
Thanks to you today.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't know what to do.
Now
Thank you.
Look at my house.
It's a big day.
What is he doing?
Brother Zhang.
Thank you so much.
You...
I brought you glutinous rice balls.
Sister Gui Zhi, you brought us delicious food again.
Did you make these glutinous rice balls yourself?
Yes.
I grinded the glutinous rice flour last night.
Dr. Sun, let's eat together.
I've eaten.
I like this one
Sister, is it also food in this box?
This is for Zhang.
He's in the garden outside.
Okay, enjoy your meal.
There's a lot here.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Yimo, have one too.
You're so greedy.
I'm not eating.
Yimo, come here.
OK. Coming.
Hurry up. It's urgent.
I'm always an outsider.
For your mother,
for your mother.
But
Chen Gui Zhi went to the hospital
to provoke your mother.
Get some rest.
Don't worry. You'll get better.
Thank you, Dr. Qin.
Thank you.
Okay, next one.
It's you.
What's wrong with your heart?
Dr. Qin
I'm here to see you
I have something to tell you face to face.
If you keep hiding it,
I don't think it's fair to you.
Don't register if you're not here to see a doctor.
Don't occupy medical resources.
Zhang and I
are already together.
Can you quit?
Zhi Gang.
You may leave.
Okay.
We've been together for half a year.
I'm telling you now because
because I'm afraid you can't take it.
But people say doctors are kind.
Dr. Qin,
You either let Zhang go
and help us.
You don't care about him at all, do you?
No wonder he said
he couldn't stay in that house anymore.
He's like an ice cellar every day.
Dr. Qin
It's not good for a woman to be too strong.
You spend every day in the hospital.
You don't have time to take care of your husband.
Take care of the child.
He has been busy all day.
He doesn't even have a warm meal at home.
How can he live with you?
Are you done?
Brother Zhang.
for taking care of our family for so many years.
I know
his feelings for me.
The reason why I didn’t make it clear
because I am a widow.
I was afraid of dragging him down.
But he said he didn't mind.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have taken care of our family.
That long?
And my child likes him a lot.
He always calls him dad.
Dr. Qin, I really feel sorry for him.
I don't want him to suffer here with you anymore
Today,
I mustered up a lot of courage
to tell you this.
Please let him go and help us.
Next.
Have you heard?
That woman came to the hospital and asked Qin Shuhua to quit.
It's also spread in your department.
Yes, I just heard about it.
Dong Zi.
Pack up the car.
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay.
She is no match for Qin Shuhua.
Bei Hai is really blind.
Exactly. Why do you like her?
There's a big gap between a couple.
Think about it.
Men feel inferior after a long time.
He went out to find balance.
He has been secretly with that woman for a long time.
He even helped her raise a child.
Dr. Qin has been kept in the dark.
Poor thing.
Dr. Qin is an excellent woman.
How can her pride stand it?
That's right.
If I were you, I would've died.
Excuse me.
Is Dr. Qin Shuhua here?
Dr. Qin is on leave.
A leave?
She never asked for leave.
She said she's not feeling well.
She needs to rest for a day.
What's wrong with her?
Exactly.
How can you ruin her family?
Your mom's condition is getting worse.
When I heard about this,
It's too late.
I know you're home, Shu Hua.
Open the door, Shu Hua.
Shu Hua!
Shu Hua, open the door.
Yimo.
Come in.
Shu Hua, what happened to you?
Are you sick?
I just came back from the north of the city.
I heard about it.
Did Chen Gui Zhi go to the hospital?
Shu Hua, hang in there.
If Zhang Beihai really cheated on you
he doesn't deserve
to torture yourself like this.
Shu Hua, no matter what happens,
I will seek justice for you.
Stop it.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm tired.
Go home.
Go back
Zhang Beihai doesn’t deserve her
and let her down
I was afraid it would provoke her more.
So I've been waiting.
I wanted to wait for her to get better.
I didn't expect
was her death
Zhang Beihai, you bastard
You're a jerk
You're a jerk.
It's all your fault.
You should die
Zhang Beihai didn't say anything
I can see
I saw it.
From the moment Chen Gui Zhi met him,
to the two of them
Then Chen Gui Zhi went to the hospital to make a scene.
Until your mother was so dispirited.
I know.
Your mom is desperate
Zhang Beihai
with Zhang Beihai
Should I
listen to Uncle Sun alone?
Didn't you say
there's another Dong Zi in Jiangdong?
Where are you?
Otherwise,
I want to see you.
Zhang Chi, it's working time.
Zhang Chi.
Help me apply for leave.
Xue Xue.
Don't go home yet.
I have something urgent. Keep an eye on it for me.
Thanks.
I just got off work. I have a blind date.
Then buy me dinner.
No wonder I'm not in love today.
Go to work.
Coming.
Coming
I'm back.
Come in The noodles are ready
Come in
Let's talk inside.
Hello, Uncle Zhang.
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
You are...
I'm Qi Qi.
You're Chi's teaching teacher.
Dr. Qi, right?
Yes.
Welcome.
Perfect.
Let's eat jjajangmyeon today
The noodles are ready.
Come in, please.
Stop working.
We're not here to eat.
I have something to ask you.
You're asking about your mom, right?
Yes.
How did my mom die?
Suicide?
Why did she commit suicide?
You can't tell, right?
Let me answer it for you.
It's because you're with the patient's family.
She went to the hospital.
After that, the whole hospital
you stepped on my mom's dignity.
She felt ashamed.
That's why she committed suicide, right?
It's never like that.
Why don't you believe me?
Tell me what happened.
I trust you. Go ahead.
OK, Zhang Chi.
Let me tell you again.
Please trust me.
I've never done anything
to your mom.
Then why does my mom take pills every day 04577?
Then why does my mom take medicine every day?
I checked.
She took sleeping pills and painkillers.
She still can't sleep.
She has three surgeries a day.
She needs to focus.
Why would she waste her body?
Tell me.
It's been so many years.
I just want to know the truth.
I want to know how my mom died.
Is it that hard?
You won't tell me?
Okay.
Then don't ever say it.
Chi.
Uncle, I'll go.
I'll visit you next time.
Qi Tuo.
I want to be alone.
008401.
Your mom went to a dead end
Zhang Beihai
There's a big problem
It's been so many years.
I just want to know the truth.
I want to know how my mom died so hard.
Qi Qi.
Here is the authorization letter written by my dad.
I'll leave it to you.
I remember
your father taught you
to bear the consequences.
This time,
don't get me a lawyer.
You and your mom did a great job.
By the way,
Xianbing is a good man.
He's reliable.
Don't act like a boy.
like a boy.
Take care of her.
Don't work hard.
Protect yourself.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Take care of your mom.
Okay.
Give it to me.
Sit there and take a rest.
Who is it again?
Coming.
Your takeout.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Bye.
Mom.
Come and eat.
When you're done,
I'll be on night shift tonight.
Lock the door yourself at home.
Get back to work. I'm fine.
Don't do this. Mom.
Here.
Eat, mom.
Hurry up and eat.
After dinner,
I'll go to work later.
I'll stay with you for a while.
It's okay.
Just do your work.
Eat.
Mom,
What kind of food do you like?
I'm fine with anything.
Eat
I have to go to work after eating.
Eat.
I wonder if your dad has eaten now.
Can you eat first?
Let's eat first, okay?
Zeng Li, don't do this.
Don't do this.
Eat up.
Eat.
Zhang Chi.
Director.
Have a seat.
You didn't go home after work.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
You've been here for a long time.
This morning,
our leaders had a meeting.
The permanent position has been decided.
Thank you.
You and Qi Tuo are divided into cars.
What's the schedule of the car team?
We'll be informed in the group chat.
Okay.
Go home early after work.
I'm leaving.
Aren't you on duty?
I'm going to...
I have something to do.
I'm back to pack my stuff.
and stay with my mom for a while.
Yes, you should spend more time with her.
Go on with your work.
Qi Tuo
I...
looking for you.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
What?
Now I can prove that
committed suicide.
When I talked to Uncle Qi
and talking to you like that.
I was too impulsive.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were going to break up with me.
What are you talking about?
Don't be sorry.
It's okay. It's all over.
I understand.
I understand you very much, Zhang Chi.
Thank you.
I don't want this to affect us.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Go.
Bye.
Yes.
That card
This card is my savings all these years.
and what my grandpa left me before he died.
Take it away. I don't want it.
Uncle Qi's matter will cost a lot of money.
It may not be enough.
Just take it.
I don't want this, Zhang Chi.
Don't be like this, JOJO.
I'm leaving. It's too late.
Sister Qi is here.
Why are you here?
Look at you.
I brought you some food.
Let's go buy supper.
Let's go together.
Do you want to eat supper?
Yes, you guys eat.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Listen to the phone.
Okay, I brought it.
You made it?
I bought it.
It reminds me of Dr. Zhang.
I'm penniless.
I'm afraid you can't afford supper.
Eat.
What are you thinking?
No matter how poor I am, I still have a house.
and I don't have a loan.
Have some water.
Yes, stop drinking.
This is tea. I can't sleep after drinking it.
Eat it when you're hungry.
Are you hungry? Have some.
I've eaten.
My mom, do you like
you sent her today?
No.
Why?
You took the aluminum box
she put it in the microwave.
She almost blew up the kitchen.
It's my fault
I should have taken that plastic box
that can be heated in the microwave.
Why are you blaming me?
You're not young anymore.
She can't even handle her own meals
Uncle Qi has been taking care of her all these years
I guess she's not used to it
See? I'm leaving after seeing you off.
Take a rest if you're sleepy.
Okay, go to bed early.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Wait.
Thank you, Xianbing.
Thank you, Qi.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Hello.
Hello, is this Mr. Zhang Chi?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm from Falia Heart Research Center.
We're very interested in
the cardiac surgery project you're working on.
After our internal consideration,
we sincerely invite you
I hope you can work here.
Thank you.
But I replied to your email before.
I can't go.
We heard about your hand.
I feel sorry for you.
But your assignment
is very meaningful
to our Heart Research Center.
We still want to fight for a chance to work with you.
If you stay in the emergency center with your skills,
It's a waste of talent.
You don't have to give us an answer now.
Please think about it.
We'll contact you in a few days.
Okay, thank you.
AIGO
0104577.
Water.
Life.
If it doesn't work, you can stay in the emergency center.
I can make you shine.
I still have a distance
a mature ER doctor.
I'll keep trying.
Thank you.
What brings you here today?
Is it about work
or Chi's?
Today,
to bother you today.
Actually, I want to
to verify something with you.
About Aunt Qin's suicide,
Are you hiding something from me?
You...
Why do you think so?
Last time when Zhang Chi came,
when Zhang Chi came.
He may take your silence
your silence.
But in my opinion,
you couldn't tell me
that you can't say?
No.
I'm not hiding anything.
You think too much.
Have some tea.
Uncle Zhang.
I was the little girl in the car
I was the little girl in the car.
You carried me out of the car.
So this is not only related to Zhang Chi,
but also me.
Qi.
what happened back then
is the matter of our previous generation.
It has nothing to do with you.
And
And I never blamed your dad.
Thank you, Uncle Zhang.
I know Zhang Chi has always treated you as his target.
I think your father-son relationship
has something to do with this.
Now everyone tells him
Aunt Qin committed suicide.
It's hard for him to accept this.
Qi,
I have nothing to say
about Aunt Qin.
Uncle Zhang.
I'm actually selfish.
I love Zhang Chi very much.
I think he is a broad-minded person.
After he found out my dad was a hit-and-run,
he didn't want to leave me,
but also helped me a lot.
So I was thinking
it's time for you and your son
to forgive each other?
If you miss so much time
because of a misunderstanding,
What a pity.
I feel sorry for you.
Me too.
If this matter
is like a stone,
in his heart,
he will be very sad in his life.
Since young,
Mrs. Qin as his role model.
I want to be an excellent cardiac surgeon.
Although he was assigned to our emergency center,
I won't hinder him from becoming
an excellent emergency doctor.
But I really hope
no matter
or in our emergency center,
out of love.
not shackles.
But Chi
is not suitable for cardiothoracic surgery.
The ER suits him better.
You can't say that.
I think he should choose for himself.
We have to respect him.
If he continues to stay in Cardio Surgery,
I'm really worried that one day
he will be like his mother.
What do you mean?
Zhang Chi, these are great.
It's marked clearly.
I can understand it.
That's good.
I was afraid you wouldn't understand.
You're the food I brought.
Just heat it in the microwave.
I'm sorry.
I'm so useless.
Sorry for the trouble.
No, aunt.
If Qiqi and I weren't working in a special way,
Otherwise,
I don't think you should enter the kitchen for the rest of your life.
I have another favor to ask you.
Go ahead.
Teach me how to cook.
No need.
Aunt, I've done it every day.
Just heat it up.
That's too troublesome.
It's a long way.
Teach me how to do it.
Let's start today.
The dish you sent
is called
Sweet and sour ribs.
This...
Let's make this. Qiqi likes it.
Qiqi likes chicken drumsticks
and braised pork?
That's because it's cooked outside
It's not as delicious as the ones cooked at home.
Okay.
Do we have ribs at home?
Yes.
Come on.
The first column.
Auntie
The ribs are a little cold.
Let me tell you.
Auntie, the frozen meat
The first step
you have to put it in this warm water.
and thaw it.
It might take 40 minutes.
to an hour.
Sorry to bother you today, Uncle Zhang.
I'll go back first.
Qi.
Wait.
Give this to Chi.
He will understand after reading it.
Okay.
Actor table.
Qi, Chen, Ren Suxi.
Bo Liu Yi.
Sun Jiaqi Zhang Yu Xi
Zhang Beihai Jiang Yiyi
Qin Shuhua
Xu Chengyuan, Wei Tianhao.
Sun Yimo, Liu Xinglin.
Qu Yufan, Wu Chengxuan
Old Zhang Beihai Sun Youning
Qi Xuejun Zhao Chengshun
Xiao Yue, Liu Yi Zhen.
Chen Xue, Xu Shendong.
Huang Hao, Liu Shuyuan.
Gao Guangze.
Dong Xiaoqiu Cao Lu
Chen Guizhi
Li Xiaohong.
Xin Haojiang.
Dong Liang Qian Youchen.
Peach, Ding Yi.
Mr. Dai, Wang Zhengjun.
Liang, Tong Xiaohu.
Sun Yimo, Yu Xiaochun.
Wu Xiaoyue, Lu Qian.
Li, Jun, Lu Mei Fang.
Zheng Bo's father.
Fang Qiqi, Gao Xianghai
Cheng Xiaoyan Pang Danjing
Wang Tao, Wang Tao.
Zhang Chi, seven years old, Chen Tianyou.
Zhang Chi, Yu Bi Cheng.
Wang Jianguo Qin Hai
Kui Lifang Ren Zijie
Lijun's mother, Ge Zhaumi.
Mr. Jiang, Luo Lei.
Yang Jing, Gao Ruoxin.
Ren Jie Liao Juan
Mu Shengying.
Wang Cheng Weibo
Yuan Yuan, Yuan, Ge Linfei.
Xu promise, Zhen.
Wedding girl, Zhu Su Jie.
Liying Feng Xingqi.
Tian Limei, Shang, Youning.
Chao Chao's mom, Dai Qihua.
Chao Chao's dad, Chi Rui Lin.
Chao Chao, Chen Long'an.
Dandan's mother, Wang, Zhang.
Yang Yang's dad, Ni Min Hao.
Yang Yang Xie Haoting
Lu Ang, Wang Jingyu.
Huazi's wife, Ma Yuan Li.
[Mother of the dump, Wang Yuan.]
Chief Zhu, the door, three.
Ma Bai Qi Guangfei.
Meng Xiang Fang Guangnan.
Xiaoyu Wan Shuya.
Xiaodie Zhang Ying
Eagle Clothed Man Wang Kun
Pregnant woman Shao Yifan
Mrs. Cui.
Liao Xiaomei, Yan Wenjun.
Liao, father, Zhang Xiaoming.
Nana's mom.
Liao's mother, Wu Fei.
Mr. Yan, Xiao Wei.
Youth Qi Xuejun Chen Wenwen
The girls are together, Ye Xuantong.
Sun Jiayi, Huang Jingwen.
Hu Xiaodie, Xiang Zeren.
Jia Jia, Wang Yi.
Qianqian, Zhang Yanqi.
Liang's wife Yan Jingli
Lin Guangwen's son, Sun Dake.
Captain Wang, Geng Dayong.
Zhao, Jie, Su Wenwen.
Dr. Sun, Zhang, Yi
The man with the duck tongue cap, Cheng, Zhen.
Aunt Jia Jia, Wang Li Shun.
Yun Yun's mother, Liao Song Mei.
Director Sun of the Health Commission, Zhang Yi Ming.
Game Boy Xu Yiyi.
negotiator, Li Yan.
Middle-aged traffic police, Huang Xufei.
Mr. Guo, Chen Xiaodong.
Professor Wang, Hu Kai.
Nana Liu
and actors.
Feng Fan, Zhou Renliang, Xing Lei, Zhang Lanxing, Wang Yijun.
Performers.
Hao, Zhejiang, Zhang Yaoxing, Zhang Zekun, Cai Wenbin, Zhuo Shaohua, Meng, Yu, Ning Qixuan.
Huang Zhenghui, Huang Fengrong, Long Xinyue, Tian Chengwei. Du Shuhan, Lin, Mo, Cheng Xiaogang.
Ye Qingfeng, Li Jiaxuan, Xu Mengjia, Deng Huiwen. Zhang Huizi, Li, Yue, Gao Yuanyuan.
Xu Chengmin, Zou, Nan, Huang Botong, Wu Qihua. Li Li, Wu Tianbo, Zhang, Zhang.
Lin Zhixian Lei Liuqin Hu Bohao Yan Shanshan Peng, Yang, Li Jiayu, Hao Yunshuang.
Tang Jinyu, Cai Hunwei, He, Nan, Meng Sijing. Shi Zi'an Xu Yan Xu Fei
Wang Tieyan Huang Wenqi Du Xinjie Huang Xuanye Ge Qingwei Wang Jingru Guo Shaojie
Luo Zu Su, Cai Yufei, Cai Yulin, Wu Nuo Xi Li Zhaixiang
Staff Form.
Go...
The production team.
Executive Producer, Wang Pin Ken, Liu Xinyue
Producer director Instructor Fu
Assistant Producer: Li Jiaqi, Huang Yiyi
Outer Producer Huang Wenxin Gao Hao
Life producer, Mjurrong Qiang.
Late-production producer, Liu Xinyue.
to purchase Chen Weimin.
to lead Zhu Yayun.
Drama Pictures Zhang Xingxing Chang Yujie
Zhang Qunbo, Du Yiwei.
behind the scenes, Chen Junjie.
PR Plan Song Won Min Wang Pil Seung
The director team (Team A).
Director Liming, XIN Liu.
Executive director Fu Bin
Cai Xiaoyan.
Director assistant, Ma Qing Qing.
Director team (Team B)
Executive director Wang Zhaotao.
Vice director Ren Peng.
The scene record is the couple.
The audition team.
ZD Auditing Studio.
Auditing director, Zheng Haoyu.
Actors Organize Zhuang Yin Ming
Vice director Nie Zhen Le Liu Haohao
Photographer group (Team A).
Camera A, Li Weicheng.
The second assistant of Camera A, Zhong Yuu.
The third assistant of Camera A, go, go.
Photographer Zhu Jiajia.
Second assistant of Phone B, Cheng Linhao.
Yuan Zhili, the third assistant of the B phone.
Camera C, focus, Liu, Yong.
The second assistant of Camera C, kiki Pan.
Mobile team leader Ma Mingse Wang Lili
Mobile First Assistant Ma Mingzhi.
Moving the third assistant, Li, Ha Honghao.
Photographer, Zhao Minyang, Zhang Li Cheng. Xu Ting Xiao.
Moving and robot, Hwang Chou-seung.
Photographer team (Team B)
Camera A photographer Cheng Guojie.
Camera A focus, Chen Chuang.
The second assistant of Camera A, Zhang Weiwei.
Photographer B, Zhu Jiajia.
Focus on B, Shi Fengfeng.
Yuan Zhili, the third assistant of the B phone.
Mobile team leader, An Chang Liang.
Lee Ahn, the first assistant.
Move the second assistant, An Jiahe.
Moving the third assistant Bruce Lee
Moving the fourth assistant Lü Linlin
Moving and player Yue Haijun.
Lighting team.
Shi Yuan.
Lighting Master Yang Chengwu.
He Pin Bo, lanterner.
Lighter Kwok Ki-liang.
The lighter, Jo Min-sung.
Team A.
Aviation filming team.
Medical consultant.
Lin Jiankong, Hong Jianfang, Hu Yuanyang, Teng Ling Fang, Li Jizhong, Chen Zhi.
The post-production team.
DIT Li Haoming.
DIT. K.
Art team.
Sub-art Liu Baibat Wang Hongyang
Chen Xiao Ting, Li Shu Ling
The atmosphere map, Dong Mengyao.
Scene art, Wu Yanling.
Props set team.
The set team leader, Fang Xingwang.
Vice-leader of props, He Jinlu.
The prop for the play, Lü Kang.
Focus on Team A, Fang Kaixin.
Vice-monitor (Team A) Fu Weibiao.
Vice-monitor (Team B) Cui Kang Jing.
Costume design, Liu, Peng.
Yu Xinyi.
Costume main focus, Luo Jie.
Costume assistant Rex Zhang.
Costume tailor, Li Ke Jun.
Costume assistant, Chu Dalin.
Costume assistant, Luo Yan Zhang called his brother.
The dressing team (Team A)
The makeup team leader, Jinjin Guo.
Makeup artist Zhang Haolin.
Makeup Daisuke, Pan Jiadong.
The makeup site focuses on Nie Dongxin.
He Xingliang, the makeup team leader.
Makeup artist Cheng Xianyu.
The main focus on the makeup scene is Xie Zhaoyu.
Makeup assistant Li Yafei.
The dressing team (Team B)
Action team.
Action director, Lim Hyun-chul.
Action guidance, Cai Wenbin.
Team A.
Producer Zhang Bin
Director Zhang Yongqiang.
Manager Han Bo-sung.
Late production.
Late video production.
Beijing Fishinson Culture Co., Ltd.
Video Director Chen Yifriend
Video technology, Hu Weiwei.
Video Director Zhang Na.
3D production Wang Chun
Digital picture, Hou Jiacheng.
Audio production.
Beijing Orange Yisheng Media Co., Ltd.
Voice director, Huang Bin.
Voice Effect Liu Jian Li Teng Fan
Foley master, Shi, Shi, Shi Yifu.
ADR recording Huang Bin Li Yanmei
Sonic Huang Bin.
Mr. Zhang, voice mixing assistant.
Music design, Huang Bin.
Music editor Jiang Zeyu Liu Yanzi
Dubbing director.
Dubber.
Guo Hao, Li Jin, Sun Jin, Liang, Yang Rui Xin, Li Yang, Tang Zichu.
Music Producer.
Jia Tao Music Studio.
Music Planner, Wang Jie.
Song production.
The first song, Wind.
composed by Jia Tao.
Arranger Liu Wen.
The ending song, Warm Light.
Singer Zhang Yu Xi.
Lyrics He Lihua
Arranger Zheng Kun.
Producer Jia Qitao
Studio, Beijing Jintian Studio
Arrange "Warm You".
Singing Liu Yiwan
Lyrics, Yu, Jia, Tao.
Arrangement. Rao Yongheng.
Producer Jia Tao
Arrange "The Replay of Love".
Singer Wei Tianhao, Cao Lu.
Arranger Zheng Kun.
Producer Jia Qitao
The Last Light of Night.
Lyrics: Luan Fuhai
Lyrics by Luan Fuhai
Singing Wei Tianhao
Production company, Beijing's first visual
"The Sea of Time" (Promotion Song)
composed by Liu Jiaxian.
Singing Wang Yushu
Production company, Beijing's first visual
The preview of the film.
Hu Siyuan, Yang Zhenwu.
Beijing Bochuan Haina Culture and Communication Co., Ltd.
edited by Liu Lei.
On the surface, Wang Le, Zhang Lina.
Guangzhou Seven Diagram Visual Design Co., Ltd.
Project Manager Zheng Wei.
Project Planning, Zheng Pei Xin.
Late-production.
Beijing Central TV and Northern Film Production Co., Ltd.
Director Li Yue.
She's planning for Gu Yu and Xie Bing.
Marketing company.
Beijing Sleeping Sky, Yiyu Culture Media Co., Ltd.
General Marketing, Zhang Jinyue.
Marketing Director, Tian, Yuan.
Project Manager Ren Ruoshi Chen Jie
Project Planning, senior three, Bai, Tao.
Project Manager Zhang.
Exclusive TV CTV8
premiere platform, TV series,
iQIYI
[Quan Zhou City People's Government]
Chunzhou City Cultural Guangdong and Tourism Bureau
Quan Zhou City Health Commission.
The PR Department of Luojiang District Committee of Zhonghong Chungzhou
[Chunju City Pungtaek District Cultural Sports and Tourism Bureau]
[Chunju City Table Investment Committee]
Chunju Emergency Command Center.
Emergency Command Center of Jinjiang City.
Health Department of Anxi County.
Quanzhou Binhai Hospital.
Anxi County Hospital.
Quanzhou Luojiang District Hospital.
Shenzhen Meili Biology and Electronic Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Fengze Cultural Foundation Park.
Quanzhou Travel Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Fujian Province Mindong geology Brigade
Fujian Quanzhou Pink Group.
Fujian Province Quanlong Health Development Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Wanke Company Co., Ltd.
Chunju Jinjiang International Airport Co., Ltd.
Quanzhou Binjiang crown holiday hotel.
Quan Zhou Hao'an Trading Co., Ltd.
Chunzhou City Yinghong Fuling Park Co., Ltd.
Jinwei holiday Hotel, Quanzhou, Fujian Province.
National ceramic industrial design institute.
The capital of pottery in the world, Dehua.
Li Ning (China) Sports supplies Co., Ltd.
Selis Motors.
Fujian Boerge supply chain, Limited.
Beijing Taotao Technology Co., Ltd.
Phoenix Network Phoenix Network Entertainment
Production unit.
Zhejiang Kunse Film Co., Ltd.
Qunzhou Kunse Film Co., Ltd.