‪SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM XI XING’S NOVEL
QUEEN CHU ON QIDIAN.COM
WANGCHENG
Hooray!
- Your Highness!
- The Grand Princess!
Your Highness, we've prepared wine.
Do me the honor.
Have some victory wine before you go.
I appreciate it, General,
but we must hurry to Yunzhong. No delays.
Your Highness.
She longs to go home.
Don't stand in her way.
Everybody, thank you for all this.
Your Highness, take this for the journey.
- Your Highness.
- Folks, the army will move out.
Don't stand in their way or delay them.
We appreciate your good intentions.
My Lord, Mr. Deng is here.
- Show him in.
- Yes.
Mr. Xie, you're working at this late hour.
You truly are a pillar of the court.
You didn't visit me so late
just to praise me, did you?
I'm here to congratulate you.
Mr. Xie,
the battle of Wangcheng was a good one.
What makes you say that?
Her Highness commanded the victory.
And of course,
my brother fought valiantly.
I dare not take any credit.
Xie Yanlai escorted Her Highness
and helped secure
the victory of Wangcheng.
So, he's likely to take over
the frontier troops in Yunzhong.
Mr. Xie,
that was a clever plan.
Have you lost your senses?
His Majesty made Yanlai
the Imperial Guard Commander.
How could he leave the imperial city?
Besides,
it won't be easy
to take over frontier troops.
It might be hard for someone else.
But for you,
it's a piece of cake.
After all, your brother
deployed the bandits
from Cangmu Stronghold to fight for him.
I just wonder if he knows
his connections with those bandits
in the Wei Village.
Mr. Deng, what's said
can't be unsaid.
Mr. Xie, don't be nervous.
I'm just curious.
Who actually set the fire
in the Wei Village?
And why does a man
who cares for his younger brother
refuse to see the truth?
If you had proof,
you could report it to His Majesty.
Instead, you came to probe me so late.
Let me give you some advice.
You can't bring down my clan
by using Xie Yanlai.
There's a reason
that my clan has endured for a century.
I'm just talking about the facts.
As for your century-old authority…
Handled properly,
even a big tree can be uprooted.
How interesting.
Mr. Deng, how about
we make a bet?
On what?
Tomorrow,
we'll both plead illness to avoid court.
- See what His Majesty will do?
- No.
I want you to see
who the ministers will support
and how much
my clan matters.
All right.
I'll take that bet.
The Northern Desert envoy is here.
You promised
that you would send troops
to help us invade Wangcheng.
But instead of sending any troops,
you watched our defeat and heavy losses.
My remaining troops all died in Yunzhong!
I wonder how you'll explain that.
Battle conditions change rapidly.
I did my best to let you pass through
at great personal risk.
How could I have foreseen everything?
Besides,
if your remaining troops
died in my prefecture,
the court would suspect and blame me.
It wouldn't benefit me at all.
If it makes you
suspect my sincerity in allying with you,
I'll be really disappointed.
Do you think this excuse
will justify my troops dying in vain?
Has your king ever trusted me?
After all, he still hasn't told me
why he asked me to help your men
set the fire in the Wei Village
five years ago.
If I hadn't sent men to clear it up,
it wouldn't have been kept
so perfectly secret.
But now, you doubt me.
Go back and tell your king.
A plan succeeds through mutual trust.
If he demands an answer on this matter,
our alliance will end here.
Jiu, had a nightmare?
Just now, you looked in pain.
Nothing.
Just a dream.
I'm going to see my father soon.
Aren't you supposed to be happy?
It's not that I'm not happy.
I'm just scared.
Of what?
My father's illness.
People get sick.
Don't worry. Maybe
by the time we arrive,
your father will have recovered.
I hope so.
THE GREAT BORDER GATE
The General once said,
when you came back someday,
he would be waiting at the city gate.
Yeah. You're the undefeated God of War.
You're the esteemed Guard General.
But have you ever asked
if I wish to be a general's daughter?
Since childhood,
other girls have had parents around.
What about me?
I've always been neglected.
Have I ever cried or complained to you?
I've never dared
to ask you for a little concern
because you've always been busy.
You're busy protecting frontier people.
You're busy forging your fame.
You're too busy
to ask your daughter
what she really wants!
Father, Xun and I love each other.
What's wrong with his origin?
If I can't marry him,
why did you marry my mother,
a noble young lady from far away?
She stayed with you
and wasted her life here.
Your mother… You have no right to judge.
Then don't interfere with mine!
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Father.
Father.
I'm sorry!
Father,
I'm finally back.
Good.
Good you're back.
When did this happen?
How did your eyes…?
What did the Army Physician say?
We can send for an Imperial Physician.
You'll be cured.
Don't bother.
With or without my eyesight,
I can see everything in the camp.
It's all in my heart.
Actually,
after I lost my sight,
I finally managed
to find inner peace.
I feel I am getting old.
I often thought of the past.
The more I thought,
the more I felt sorry for you.
You've grown up,
and I've never flown kites with you.
I even missed
your coming-of-age ceremony.
I still remember those words you said
when you left here.
In the dead of night,
it has haunted me all this time.
You were right.
I've never been a good father.
I've never asked
what you really want.
I have no right
to beg for your forgiveness.
Don't say that, Father.
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
Father, I shouldn't have said
those harsh words.
Five years ago, I shouldn't
have left willfully
without even leaving you a message.
Father,
will you forgive me?
I've never blamed you.
There's nothing to forgive.
When you're no longer so stubborn,
it feels strange to me.
The biggest pride
of my life
isn't defeating enemies,
but having a daughter
even more stubborn than I am.
On the day of Wangcheng victory,
joy overwhelmed me.
I asked Changrong to write
a congratulatory poem on my behalf.
My precious daughter was too confined
To let her talents shine
How could I not think of her?
Yet she chose to temper herself
She left home and achieved great deeds
And her talents finally shone brightly
Glorious and bright
Her light reaches the whole land
Your Majesty, an urgent military report
about rewards
came from Wangcheng.
Without His Majesty's approval,
Her Highness distributed rewards
on her own.
Wasn't she overstepping her authority?
Mr. Xie is on sick leave.
Mr. Deng has a day off, too.
To whom shall we send
this military report?
Mr. Deng, of course.
The late Emperor made him the regent.
We can't bypass him in military affairs.
Military affairs are urgent.
Mr. Deng knows nothing
about warfare tactics.
Before Mr. Xie asked for sick leave,
he ordered that all military reports
to be sent to him.
Mr. Deng also gave an order.
Frontier affairs must be reviewed by him.
The Xie Clan of Gaoyang
has stood for a century.
Oh. My memory fails me.
How many prime ministers
have come from their clan?
Since the founding of our dynasty,
there have been six.
Then send it to Mr. Xie.
- But…
- This is ridiculous.
Anything else?
Then the court is dismissed.
- We bid farewell to Your Majesty.
XIE RESIDENCE
Mr. Xie, have you heard?
In today's court, we won decisively.
I heard that old censor
nearly fainted from anger.
How many times have I warned you?
You must not be so arrogant.
Arrogance leads to misfortune.
When people praise you
and our Xie household,
it's hard for me to stay humble.
I can't help feeling proud.
Forget it.
Mr. Xie, won't you review the report?
Send this report to Mr. Deng.
To him?
Won't you review it?
No one but Mr. Deng
can review this report.
What if he doesn't…?
He will.
Mr. Deng,
you lost.
Don't be angry.
You need patience when dealing
with Xie Yanfang.
He got the military report,
but didn't even bother to review it.
He's obviously humiliating me.
This man…
It's him.
- Who?
- Liang Qiang.
The Third Prince's case
involves his family.
Xie Yanfang had him exiled.
Very good.
APPROVED
Approving it already?
Since he's Xie Yanfang's enemy,
I'll give him some support.
SEAL OF THE GRAND MENTOR
IMPERIAL SEAL OF THE CHU EMPEROR
Father. Father, are you asleep? I'm back.
I got it. I'm still awake.
I was waiting for you.
Father, guess what I brought back.
Did my patrol lady
bring back a spy?
I brought back a rabbit.
Well done, Zhao.
Jiu didn't catch it for you, did he?
No.
Father. Look.
This little rabbit looks like a snowball.
Rabbits can bite.
Don't forget.
You got bitten when you were little
and cried for three days.
I did?
I don't remember at all.
You remember almost nothing
about your childhood.
In your childhood,
you were extraordinary.
When you were born,
the room was bathed in red light.
A fortune teller passed by
and was utterly shocked.
He pointed at you and said,
"She's blessed by heaven."
Really? Did you
go out again and hear
a story at the tea house?
What happened next in the story?
Later,
at this girl's first birthday,
she grabbed the Frontier Tally.
When she was five,
she led the servants and maids
to use brooms as spears
and pot lids as shields,
and she has piled up an enemy city
with bamboo steamers.
She even learned
to deploy troops.
In the end, she captured
the steward's three hens
that would still lay eggs.
I don't remember that.
Was I that remarkable?
Yes, you were.
And the old steward
cried for two nights.
Father, I love the congratulatory poem
you wrote for me.
Let me recite it again.
My precious daughter was too confined
To let her talents shine
How could I not think of her?
Yet she chose to temper herself
She left home and achieved great deeds
And her talents finally shone brightly
Glorious and bright
Her light reaches the whole land
Father. Father!
Father! Army Physician!
Father.
When I left five years ago,
Father could still draw bows and shoot.
When did he fall ill?
Let me be honest.
Over the past two years,
the General has been growing weaker.
Actually, whether he did or didn't disarm,
he'd end up the same.
He's been poisoned for three years.
You sent him those cakes yourself.
From the Capital to Yunzhong,
they were delivered monthly.
CHU MANSION
Chu Ling would be killed anyway.
Not only by my blade,
but also by his daughter's love.
This is impossible.
In my past life, poisoned jujube cakes
were sent to my father after my wedding.
But in this life, no cakes were sent.
Why is Father still ill?
Do you know what happened to my father?
I'm not sure about the reason.
I'll make him some medicine
for refreshment and replenishment.
You served him for five years.
Do you know why he's fading so quickly?
Sorry.
I have no idea.
In this new life,
nothing has changed.
For you, something has.
Yet some regrets are inevitable.
Everything has its destiny.
So does a human.
He's defended the frontier all his life,
and people revere him.
In the final days of his life,
his daughter and brothers-in-arms
keep him company.
Perhaps,
he isn't in that much pain.
Even if he passes away,
his love for you
won't fade away.
But he shouldn't be like this.
He just shouldn't.
He kills enemies at the frontier
and protects people here.
He has done everything
a general should do.
He protects 200,000 soldiers
and secures the peace of the state.
What else do you want?
I want him to live.
I want him to live!
I want him to call me "silly girl",
make jujube cakes with me,
and teach me riding and archery!
I want to make it up
and do what a daughter should do.
I want him to wait for me
to come home even if he scolds me.
I don't want a cold memorial tablet
of the Guard General.
GATEWAY OF CANGMU STRONGHOLD
What's wrong, Aunt?
Chu Ling.
CHU LING'S LIFE BURNS LOW.
BEYOND ALL HEALING. PLEASE REPLY SOON
He's dying.
Aunt, you…
Are you going to see him?
Jiu.
Tell me.
What will a man think
before he dies?
Words left unsaid,
promises left unfulfilled…
Or…
wishes that went unmet.
What could be
my father's wish?
If you really want to know,
you can ask him when he wakes up.
Just stop torturing yourself.
Zhao,
you look like you did something wrong.
Your father wouldn't like it.
I just want to figure it out.
What exactly went wrong
that made me end up like this again?
I have tried so hard.
I have tried everything.
Why will my father still leave me?
Zhao, calm down.
What else can I do?
Tell me. What else can I do
to save my father?
MIGHT AND RIGHT
It still tastes a bit bland.
He can't take Zhuyu Powder.
He's too weak to take it now.
Madam Ge? You…
Why are you here?
I'm your father's…
old friend.
I'm here for his final farewell.
Who on earth are you?
Old friend?
What kind of friend
would even remember his food taboos?
She didn't fight like ordinary bandits.
In the Wangcheng battle,
the way she wielded twin blades
was peculiar.
Mu Mianhong, head of Cangmu Stronghold,
mastered twin scimitars.
In the first year of Tianshu
when Father suppressed them,
she jumped off a cliff and died.
Could she be…?
Mu Mianhong.
General, this is our new maidservant.
She can't speak,
but she's good at decoction and soup.
Thanks for your work.
Thank you.
WE SWEAR THIS LOVE AND MATRIMONY
BEFORE HEAVEN, EARTH AND OUR ANCESTORS
BREAK THIS OATH AND WE BE CURSED
BY CHU LING, MU MIANHONG
Do you like this kind of father?
No?
Why?
Because he's a hero to others.
He's a hero to people in Yunzhong.
But I want him to be an ordinary father.
He would carve wooden dolls for me,
watch fireworks with me,
give me pretty braids,
and be there with me
for every important moment.
But actually…
none of this happened.
What about…
your mother?
Could Father have been lying all along?
My mother is…
It can't be.
JOY AND HEALTH FOREVER
Zhao.