Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Bu Bu Jing Xin Team at Viki.com
♫  In the blink of an eye, a thought of stubborn persistence  ♫
♫  We were destined to seek our doom like moths flying towards the flame  ♫
♫  Knowing that it’d be a disaster, why am I still at a loss about what to do  ♫
♫  The best is not to see, the best is not to miss you  ♫
♫  Only like this can I not be in love with you  ♫
♫  Just another brushing of the shoulder, and from then...♫
♫  I’ll keep falling deeper and deeper in love with you  ♫
♫  It’s the mistake of time, ♫
♫ forcing us to pass each other by  ♫
♫  How I miss you, how far you are  ♫
♫  Even though I’d known it’d only result in pain,  ♫
♫ at this moment, I still don’t want to escape   ♫
♫  Pity these words are too glaring, they hurt the eyes  ♫
♫  Two worlds later ♫
♫  Don’t want to escape  ♫
♫  It’s the mistake of time,  ♫
♫  we can only pass each other by  ♫
♫  The magnitude of me missing you is as much as how far you are   ♫
♫  Even though I know the ending is a mistake that I cannot oppose  ♫
♫  Staying in this moment  ♫
♫  We can only accept that the feelings run deep, but fate is shallow  ♫
Scarlet Heart
Final Episode 35
14th Prince's concubine,
Maertai Ruoxi,
died yesterday.
Maertai Ruoxi...
Without my permission,
you cannot die.
YOU CANNOT DIE!
Letter? Where's that letter?
Imperial Brother.
Where's the letter?
[ Fourth Prince,]
[ Life is like a dream, continuously changing.]
[ Rights and wrongs. Gratitude and resentment.]
[ But the days pass soundlessly.]
[ Waters pass without leaving a trace.]
[ It's hard to forget one's foolish longings.]
[ When someone told me very calmly that he wanted the throne, ]
[ he already held the key to my heart.]
[ When he threw away the umbrella ]
[ and endured and suffered the rain with me,]
[ I had already opened the door to my heart for him.]
[ When he protected me ]
[ by using his own body to block the arrow,]
[ I knew I would never forget him in this life...]
[ Everything that happened after that ]
[ only drew me in deeper.]
[ Having said that, ]
[ Do you still need to ask about 8th Prince?]
[ If there is love, there is anger. If there is love, there is hate.]
[ If there is love, there is obsession. If there is love, there is longing.]
[ Since we parted, ]
[ there has been nothing but anger, hate, obsession, and longing, ]
[ transforming into inches of memories. ]
[ I don't know if you still resent me, ]
[ hate me, loathe me, or detest me.]
[ Underneath the wisteria bower, underneath the moon in the bitter wind, ]
[ between my brush, inkstone, and paper, ]
[ in Ruoxi's heart, there is no Emperor, ]
[ there is only the Fourth Prince who has stolen my soul. ]
[ We love, we yearn, we don't meet. ]
[ Why then, bear the heavy hearts that only make both lonely.]
[ My weak inner being shatters.]
[ This letter is as blurry as my words.]
(Means the words are blurred from her teary eyes.)
[ As I gaze into the courtyard, I long to see you.]
[ Day by day, I will wait for your arrival.]
[ ~ Ruoxi ]
Take me to see her.
Bring me to see her.
Second Miss!
Only Wang'ye is attending the wake.
Wang'ye said CeFu'jin likes quiet, not--
Shut up! There is no Ce'Fu'jin here.
You may leave.
Ruoxi, he finally came.
(referring to Fourth Prince - Emperor Yongzheng)
Ruoxi.
After we parted ways last time,
(Rouxi's Memorial Tablet - belief deceased spirit resides there)
I thought we'd have another chance to meet again.
I thought I could always come here to see you.
Who would have thought...
Where's the coffin?
How is it, that there's no coffin?
Maybe Ruoxi didn't leave yet!
She is playing around with us!
Ruoxi!
Fourteenth! Fourteenth! Come out!
Fourteenth Brother,
why is there only a tablet but no coffin?
Ruoxi is here.
What does that mean?
I cremated Ruoxi.
Ruoxi...
- I'm going to kill you!!
-  Imperial Brother. Imperial Brother!
- Imperial Brother!
-  I'm going to kill you!
-  Imperial Brother, calm down a bit!
The fourteenth Brother would not treat Ruoxi like that.
(The body is a valued gift from the ancestors and buried whole)
Let's ask for an explanation first.
You hurried here now.
Where were you earlier?
Do you know that Ruoxi waited like a fool for you for days?
Why are you acting like this now for?
It was your fault and you dare to blame me!
I'm going to kill you!
Stop it! Stop it!
Because the envelope was written in your hand,
Imperial Brother thought you were writing to provoke him again so he threw it aside!
Even if he didn't receive her letter,
there are so many of your spies on this estate,
didn't they tell you about Ruoxi?!
You used so many tricks in the past,
it made Imperial Brother unwilling to hear any more reports about Ruoxi,
so do you still have to ask?!
Ah so, it was like that.
Ruoxi...
I didn't mean it.
That time under the plum trees,
when I had Ruoxi show intimate gestures to the spies,
it was only because my heart was hurt and suffocating,
and I wanted to anger you.
But I found out that I really did like speaking with Ruoxi
because it was like returning to the past.
Although, we were separated by a screen,
I knew that Ruoxi
was quietly laying there, I--
You shut up!
But why?
Why did you treat Ruoxi like this?
This is what Ruoxi begged for.
She begged me
to find a windy day
and spread her ashes on the wind.
This way, she'd be free.
She said she doesn't want any bad taste in her mouth.
She doesn't want to be buried in the dark earth. She was scared...
scared that she'd be bitten by worms.
Let us go home now.
Ruoxi is my Ce'Fu'jin!
You can't take her away!
I get to say if
she is your Ce'Fu'jin or not.
I never placed Ruoxi's name on the Imperial Family records
and you never had a marriage ceremony!
When Imperial Father passed away,
I couldn't see him one last time.
When Mother passed away, I also did not see her one last time!
Now you have come to take away my Ce'Fu'jin!
Don't bully me too far!
I will bully you!
Fourteenth Brother...
Please sympathize with Imperial Brother's feelings.
Moreover, I believe Ruoxi
is willing to leave with Imperial Brother.
What a joke! If she was willing
why would she leave the Forbidden City?
Fourteenth Prince...
It was Second Miss' own wish.
Let His Majesty take Second Miss away.
It's Second Miss' wish. Really.
Your Majesty,
please follow me.
Fourteenth Brother.
If you're really thinking for Ruoxi's own good,
stop making a commotion.
All of Ruoxi's sufferings,
her difficulties,
were for 8th brother, 10th brother,
and for you.
Now, she has already passed away,
don't make things difficult for her anymore.
Your Majesty, please.
Second Miss, every day she practiced her calligraphy.
She only stopped
when her hand had no more energy.
Your Majesty.
These were all written by Second Miss.
Also these,
belonged to Second Miss.
I was thinking to keep them for myself for remembrance,
but I think if I give these to Your Majesty
it will be much, much, better.
Before she left,
what did she say?
Second Miss thought that you hated her
and didn't want to see her.
So she didn't leave any words for Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Ruoxi...
Second Miss knew that Wang'ye would come back,
so she left a letter for you.
[ Thirteenth Prince,]
[ Rouxi knowing 13th Prince ]
[ was my good fortune. ]
[ I only have 13th Prince that I can ask for this favor. [
[ I know that doing this will give 13th Prince trouble. ]
[ But the Death Seeking 13th Prince of the past ]
[ would not be scared. ]
And this handkerchief,
Second Miss asked that it be given to 9th Prince.
Second Miss didn't leave behind very much money.
These things...
she told me to give half to Eunuch Wangxi,
but...
Not long after Ruoxi left,
Wangxi tripped and fell into the water and drowned.
He can't use these.
Second Miss also said
Wangxi was an intelligent person
and he wouldn't be able to use it.
So she told me to give this to his family in his stead.
Imperial Brother
already heavily rewarded his family.
What do you plan to do now?
Madam and Second Miss gave me their money.
Second Miss said
I should decide what I should do next.
I wish to serve Chenghuan Ge'ge. (Princess)
Second Miss also left this jade pendant for her.
That's good, I originally thought of that too,
but I didn't want to force you.
Since you're willing,
when I bring Chenghuan back to the estate
I won't have to worry that no one will take care of her.
Thank you, Wang'ye.
Nian Gengyao
has already received Imperial Brother's edict.
He has also already accepted the title
and returned his acceptance to the emissary.
Imperial Brother.
If Ruoxi sees you like this,
she won't rest in peace.
The Empress has waited outside for a long time.
She has never left your side.
Imperial Brother should appreciate her thoughts and actions now.
I want to see the Emperor!
Wang'ye...
- Let me in!
-  Wang'ye...
Let him come in.
Eighth Brother.
Ruoxi is no longer here,
why are you causing a commotion?
You should leave--
Ruoxi...
came from my manor.
Now that she's already gone,
why can't I
see her!
She is right here.
Now you've seen her.
Leave.
Why did you treat her like that?
Since you'd already let her leave the Forbidden City,
why couldn't you let her have a complete corpse and rest in peace?
8th Brother.
This was Ruoxi's own wish.
It's the truth.
She always had beyond ordinary thoughts.
Maybe this was the only way, she could
truly belong to her lover.
Back then, I gave up on Ruoxi because of power
and abandoned
the vows we made to never leave each other.
Now, Imperial Brother,
for the Qing empire
and your past grievances,
has also given up the chance to be together with her forever?
You're the same as me. The things you once had
are now all gone in the end.
With Ruoxi,
you're just the same as me,
a failure!
Leave.
I'm the Emperor of the Qing now.
LEAVE!
True,
you are the mighty Emperor,
but I
am still me after all.
Stripped of all titles and removed from the records.
Stripped of their yellow belts.
The wives of these two princes, if they have titles,
those titles are hereby revoked.
All of their children and grandchildren
are to be stricken from the Imperial Family records and are to be renamed.
8th Wang'ye's name is to be changed to A'qi'na,
meaning "to forever carry your crime".
Prince Hong Wang's name shall be Pu'sa'bao
(protected by Bodhisattva),
in the hope that the Yongzhen Emperor will be merciful like Bodhisattva and let Hong Wang live.
Since 9th Prince won't change his name himself,
Yongzhen Emperor has changed it to Sai'si'hei
meaning 'hateful devil.'
Ruoxi...
May your departure
take you to the free
and future world.
On 10th Brother's wedding night
I took Ruoxi to the countryside to drink.
When she was drunk,
she once told me
that she wasn't from this time period
but from a future world.
Back then, I thought she was being silly and funny.
As I think about it now,
I'm willing to believe
that she has returned to her own place.
I am not actually Ruoxi,
I am Zhang Xiao.
I don't belong to your world.
I am afraid that one day
I will leave here against my will.
Like how I originally didn't want to come here.
I hope that you really can return to your own time.
You're awake!
Doctor! Doctor!
- She's awake!
-  Awake?
Quick!
Here...
13th Brother, you have so much free time today,
that you won't admire the snow at home
so you came here to see me?
I am here to do someone a favor.
To give 9th Brother something.
Why is it not just hate?
Why?!
Ruoxi,
you deserve to be 4th's woman.
No, you're even more cruel than he is.
He can only torture our bodies,
so we can escape by dying.
But you
won't let me die in peace,
making me feel regret and sadness.
Don't block me!
You can't block me!
I have to go find that bastard Emperor!
Go! Go then!
Who would block you!
You said it!
You can't block me!
I have a score to settle with him!
Who is blocking you?
I... I...
I'll desecrate his ancestral tomb!
I... I'll yell at all of his ancestors so that they can't have peace!
Aren't his ancestors your ancestors?
Aren't you scared
that your ancestors will come to attack you?
That's right...
There's no use in continuing to act out this scene,
I can never out-talk you.
That's why it's meaningful.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be fun.
Alright. Come.
Come, sit and talk.
Come, sit down and talk.
Here, slowly.
I saw that you were play acting so happily,
so I didn't help you.
Look at you,
your stomach is already so big,
but you don't know any control.
Oh, so you're worried now?
I'm not worried.
Let's
try to have 2 kids in 3 years.
Who cares what 4th Brother is doing?
I don't have time to bother with him anyway.
That's right!
Your chess skills have improved.
You are so at ease now,
it's really like
the clean and pure De Fei of the past.
Of course,
I should thank Imperial Brother,
for putting me in house-arrest in Mother's palace,
and giving me such a peaceful place.
Now, every day, I can pray to Mother,
look at the books she often read.
It is like returning to the past.
There is nothing to worry about.
I only have to care about how to enjoy each day.
No matter what,
Mother is here to protect me.
Out of all of us brothers,
it looks like
your days are spent the best.
Yes.
There's 13th Brother
to play chess with and talk to often.
There's Fu'jin to speak comforting words.
There isn't a hint of loneliness.
Now that I think about it,
the throne that I spent half my life fighting for,
doesn't compare to these comfortable days.
Won't His Majesty punish you?
I will go tell His Majesty
that this is what Ruoxi wanted before she died.
Even if His Majesty gets angry,
he won't say much.
After I leave,
if I have a complete corpse
could you
bury me with Minghui's ashes?
If I am cremated,
then could you
mix her ashes with mine?
In life, I couldn't
be with her forever.
So in death
I hope to fulfill her wish.
Hongwang...
His Majesty will not punish Hongwang,
so don't worry, 8th Brother.
As long as I'm here
I will protect him.
In this lifetime, I cannot repay back
all that 13th Brother has done for me.
Thank you, Ruoxi.
Father.
Qiaohui...
I'm here.
Chenghuan...
continue... to take care... of her for me.
Don't worry, Wang'ye.
4th Brother,
your brother cannot
assist you any longer.
We brothers have walked this path together,
do we really need to say such things?
When Ruoxi left,
she didn't want us
to remember her,
but, actually, no one has forgotten her.
Let's
all meet again in our next life.
Father!
Wang'ye!
雍正
(Yongzheng)
They have all left.
There's now only me.
13th year of Yongzhen's reign, August 23rd of the lunar calendar, Yongzhen passed away. He is buried in the Western tombs.
After searching all over the place,
I still can't find a hint of Maertai Ruoxi's existence.
It's almost as if this person
never existed in history.
Unless,
those ten plus something years
and the relationship with 4th Prince
weren't real at all?
Was it all just a dream?
♫  Stopping here, afraid to go any further ♫
♫ so sorrow will be unable to make an appearance  ♫
♫  On the next page, the farewell penned by you,  ♫
♫ it was not up to me to refuse  ♫
♫  We’ve walked down this path too hastily  ♫
♫  Embracing desires that weren’t realistic  ♫
♫  Not in time, wasn’t able to ♫
I really did exist.
♫  wait long enough to look back and admire  ♫
♫  The fragrance of magnolia is unable to hide wounds  ♫
I really did exist.
♫  No longer looking for the sun’s rays peeking through the clouds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the paradise that we promised each other  ♫
♫  No longer sighing, you once said that life is unpredictable  ♫
♫  The three inches of sunlight that I was unable to borrow  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the Bu Bu Jing Xin Team @Viki.com
♫  No longer looking for the sun’s rays peeking through the clouds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the paradise that we promised each other  ♫
♫  No longer sighing, you once said that life is unpredictable  ♫
Do we know each other?
♫  The three inches of sunlight that I was unable to borrow  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the sunlight peeking through the clouds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the paradise that we promised each other  ♫
♫  No longer sighing, you once said that life is unpredictable  ♫
♫  The three inches of sunlight that I was unable to borrow  ♫
♫  That paradise is the place where I’d loved you  ♫
[ First, it's better not to meet you, so I won't fall in love with you.
Second, it's better not to know you, so I won't yearn for you.]
♫ Waiting for summer, waiting for autumn, ♫
♫  waiting for the next season. I have to wait  ♫
♫  for the moon to become full again ♫
♫ before you'll return to my side again. ♫
♫ Why do I still yearn for you, wanting to see your face. ♫
♫ That familiar feeling. ♫
♫ Unable to walk hand in hand hold as we stroll through wind and frost. ♫
♫ Not able to meet, we still yearn for each other day and night. ♫
♫ I just want to let you know ♫
♫ that I really am doing well. ♫
♫ Loving you my whole life, ♫
♫ I will wait for you till I'm old. ♫
♫ I just want to let you know ♫
♫ I can't let go, neither can I forget ♫
♫ Your smile and your goodness ♫
♫ are warm support for me ♫