Timing and Subtitles brought to you by the Bu Bu Jing Xin Team @Viki.com
♫  In the blink of an eye, a thought of stubborn persistence  ♫
♫  We were destined to seek our doom like moths flying towards the flame  ♫
♫  Knowing that it’d be a disaster, why am I still at a loss about what to do  ♫
♫  The best is not to see, the best is not to miss you  ♫
♫  Only like this can I not be in love with you  ♫
♫  Just another brushing of the shoulder, and from then...♫
♫  I’ll keep falling deeper and deeper in love with you  ♫
♫  It’s the mistake of time, forcing us to pass each other by  ♫
♫  How I miss you, how far you are  ♫
♫  Even though I’d known it’d only result in pain, at this moment, I still don’t want to escape  ♫
♫  Pity these words are too glaring they hurt the eyes  ♫
♫  Two worlds later ♫
♫  Don’t want to escape  ♫
♫  It’s the mistake of time, we can only pass each other by  ♫
♫  The magnitude of me missing you is as much as how far you are   ♫
♫  Even though I know the ending is a mistake that I cannot oppose  ♫
♫  Staying in this moment  ♫
♫  We can only accept that the feelings run deep, but fate is shallow  ♫
Episode 2
1. Return home.
2. Die.
3. Disabled
Worth it!
Are you okay, Miss?
Who asked you to stop the horse?!
Why is it you again?
Fourth Prince.
You weren't running around randomly at all.
You saw our horses and ran over on purpose.
You are seeking to die.
I....
Why would i seek death ?
You have misunderstood.
That was just an accident.
The first time was an accident,
but this time it wasn't.
If you still want to die the next time,
I won't pull the reins anymore.
I want to live that why i did that.
There are too many things I cannot let go of.
Why would I want to die?
What you're saying is really strange.
Medicine for your injuries
Fourth Prince,
thank you!
I saved your life.
In the future, without my permission
don't even think about killing yourself.
Slow down, Second Miss.
- Second Miss.
- Ruoxi.
Second miss
You leg has not fully recovered.
Why are you not resting it?
You're even walking around.
I'm fine.
I already applied ointment the last time,
it's already much better.
We really should thank the 4th and 13th princes.
We should go and visit them
and thank them.
I've already thanked them the last time.
Don't bother doing it again.
This is basic etiquette.
Just for such a small thing,
I guess the two princes
would not take it to heart.
But if Difujin were to find out,
I'm afraid she'd make a mountain out of a molehill.
You certainly know how to worm your way out of things.
Is that how you use your intelligence?
Jiejie, this letter is addressed to you.
Why aren't you reading it?
The eunuch in charge of reading letters is not here today.
Let's leave it first.
For a simple job like reading letters,
let me do it for you.
You know how to read letters?
What's so difficult about that?
It's a piece of cake.
Okay.
Since it's a letter from Father and Eldest Brother,
I will let you read it.
These words are for Ruolan to read.
"To the person reading this, it has been a long time since we've written to each other.
We have missed you a lot.
Reading your letters is almost as good as seeing you in person.
Greetings. What word is this?
Words after not having met for a long time.
Something win something... ?
Something, something.
Something, horse god*!"
(*Horse god is a homonym of something and is a modern slang for "what the heck is this!?")
There's even a horse god?
No.
Sister...
I have not seen you for a long time
I thought you will have become wiser
Able to read letter , read books
Turns out, your capability is nothing more than this.
Jiejie, I think this letter...
It is better for you to wait
for the eunuch to come and
read for you.
Have you given up?
No!
I think I had better
start studying from the beginning.
Then, I'll head back first.
"The falling leaves herald the leaving of winter.
The autumn winds over the lake stir up thoughts of homesickness in travellers.
There must be children catching grasshoppers,
seeing a brightly lit lamp near the fences late at night."
To think that I as a modern person,
studied hard persevered through 16 years of modern education,
and can be considered as an educated person.
But once here,
I'm considered half-illiterate.
Luckily. I came into this young lady's body.
I don't have to worry about starving or freezing.
Otherwise,
wouldn't I,
who can't do menial labour,
starve to death?
Little ants, don't run, don't run!
Come, let me play with you.
Greetings to Eighth Prince. Greetings to Tenth Prince.
Rise.
Looking at you crazy girl just now,
I thought there was something fun to play with.
It looks like I overestimated her.
To be esteemed by you isn't really an honor.
Reading Song poems?
Yes.
She was playing with ants!
It's just, she was putting on an act of being studious.
This rascal,
pretending to be some big shot in front of me?
Haven't you heard,
“To see a world in a grain of sand, and heaven in a wild flower”?
I'm looking at ants,
but I'm not looking at ants either.
Tenth Brother, you need to study hard.
A fool is a fool.
Just one sentence and you become mute.
Can't argue.
You read Buddhist scriptures?
I hear Jiejie chant them often, so I know a little.
It's true that she chants them often.
She only asks for her heart to be at peace.
There are overtones in Eighth Prince's words.
His true feelings are hidden.
If you were a boss,
you would be a boss among bosses.
You recognize all these words?
Yes,
I recognize them,
but they don't recognize me,
but we are getting to know each other.
Eight Brother, listen to what she's saying.
How will you let yourself know them better?
Through guessing.
That works too?
If that's the case, then none of us need to hire teachers,
we can just guess, can't we?
Let's leave.
We're going horseback riding. Do you want to come?
Horseback riding?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go.
Lucky!
Eh?
What did you just see?
I'm not telling you what I saw.
What did you just "Eh?" at?
If you want to know,
But you need to give me some benefits.
Aren't you a little too materialistic?
I was only asking you,
and you want benefits?
You can't it say it like that.
I was the one who saw something interesting.
Since you want to know,
of course you have to give me some benefits.
Unless, when you're listening to storytellers tell stories,
you don't pay money.
For you.
Now can you tell me?
What? You think it's too little?
I'm not as materialistic as you.
You're not materialistic?
If what you're doing isn't considered materialistic, what is it?
I can't think of what I want at the moment.
How about this?
In the future, you need to agree to one of my requests.
It definitely won't be something you can't do.
Besides, you, as a prince,
agreeing to a little favour of a little girl,
what's so hard about that?
Yes. Okay then.
I promise you then. Say it.
Then you'd better remember it well.
I have a witness.
I'll remember. You can say it.
There are so many people on the street,
but our carriage is able to travel ahead without any hinderances.
Everyone who sees it makes way from afar.
But we have no sign that declares that Eighth Prince is in the carriage.
I was wondering why that happened.
So I made an 'Eh'.
Then why did you shake your head?
After that I thought about it.
This type of carriage
is definitely not one an ordinary person can ride in.
And we're in the capital (at the feet of the emperor).
These peasants have experience.
Even though they don't know who's in the carriage,
they know that they won't go wrong by making way.
As to shaking my head,
I only felt
that I became a fox*.
(*Chinese idiom where a fox swaggers around in the borrowed authority of a tiger)
Fox?
What does this have to do with being a fox?
"Fox borrowing Tiger's fierceness"
(Chinese idiom)
I understand. Fox borrowing the tiger's fierceness.
Just this?
Just this and you swindled a favor
out of a prince of the great Qing empire?
I'll let you guess what I'm thinking about too.
Wait.
No. This one's too old.
Come.
This one is too young.
His personality isn't set yet.
How did you go about finding these horses? Where's the horse?
Take Linglong here.
Yes.
That horse is gentle.
You can ride safely.
Ruoxi, you're so lucky.
Eighth Brother actually let you ride Linglong.
Wait for me.
So handsome.
Ruoxi. Ruoxi!
Why are you daydreaming? Hurry and get on the horse.
Why are you dilly-dallying?
Are you riding or not?
Go ride your own horse.
Why are you bothering with me?
I'll go ride after you get on.
Horses are meant to be ridden,
not for staring at.
I don't know how to ride.
What did you say?
Looking at you strutting around,
but you don't even know how to ride a horse?
How did your father teach you?
So what if I can't ride?
If you can't ride...
If you can't ride, I'll help you hold the reins.
Yes, let him help you hold the reins.
Come.
Weren't you going to help me hold the reins?
Hold it.
Holding... I'm holding.
Come, be careful.
- Thanks.
- Sit steady.
Be careful.
What are you looking at? Daydreaming again.
Concentrate on walking!
You only know how to bully me.
If you keep bullying me, I'll let go.
Let go.
I'll let go.
- Let go.
- I let go.
Just joking.
This Eighth Prince...
if you want status, he has status;
if you want looks, he has looks.
A top-grade man.
You'll only anger yourself to death if you keep making comparisons (Chinese idiom)
Luckily, right now I'm a Lady.
The name Linglong is perfect.
Although the horse isn't small and delicate,
but it is agile and swift.
Riding it up the hill
feels like walking on flat land.
Even if I close my eyes, I'm not afraid I'll fall off.
Jiejie,
do I not know how to ride?
You don't remember again?
Then what should it be?
Since young, you didn't know how to ride.
No matter how Father tried to force you to learn,
you weren't willing to learn.
I really don't like horseback riding?
Then it's fine then.
Right now,
not only do I not hate riding,
I actually quite like it.
Next time, Jiejie
must come along and play with us.
First take a bath, and then let's eat.
Eighth Prince is pretty good at taking care of people.
With him there,
nothing will go wrong.
Next time, Jiejie
must go with us.
I'm not interested.
Even if you aren't interested in riding,
but you can go have fun with Eighth Prince
and find some interesting things to do.
Eighth Prince is both attentive and refined in manners.
Many things, even if you don't say them,
he seems to already understand
and is already well prepared.
Jiejie, I feel that
he treats you pretty well.
Since you're already married to him,
why don't you treat him a little better?
This type of man
is still worth fighting for.
- Madam.
- Jiejie!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Dongyun, go with me to the altar.
Qiaohui,
did I say something wrong?
No.
Second Miss don't ask me anymore.
Qiaohui,
you understand Jiejie best.
You must know.
Second Miss,
for two people to become a married couple,
they have the fate, but we cannot force their affinity (feelings).
Since they can still treat each other with respect,
is already a blessing.
What you mean to say is
Jiejie doesn't quite like Eighth Prince?
Second Miss,
I didn't say anything.
I dare not guess what Mistress is thinking about.
Qiaohui, when you see Tenth Prince later,
don't say I'm looking for him to play.
Say I'm there to pay my greetings.
So that he won't be so pleased with himself.
Don't worry, Miss.
Actually, he's quite amusing as a person.
Say, if he doesn't get insulted by you every few days,
he'll feel terribly suffocated.
Even though he can't argue as well as Second Miss,
but he smiles so happily every time.
He's definitely taking pleasure in it.
Actually, Tenth Prince is pretty fun to play with.
He is not scheming, and isn't very knowledgable.
He is also a bit rash.
But simple-minded people like him
are the most suitable to be friends with.
Second Miss,
the few of them are in the study discussing matters.
For us to just walk in on them like this,
isn't too good is it?
Don't worry.
As long as I don't see that ice block Fourth Prince's face, it'll be fine.
Qiaohui!
Madam... Madam is calling for you.
- Second Miss.
- Go then.
I'll take my leave.
Ice block face. Oh god.
Maertai Ruoxi!
Greetings to Fourth Prince.
Rise.
It seems like you really don't want to see me.
No. I wouldn't dare.
Then what do you mean by running once you see me?
I suddenly remembered I had something to do,
so I didn't notice Fourth Prince.
I think you're having a guilty conscience, and scared that I'll ask you why you were seeking death that day.
The more you don't want to say, the more I must ask.
Tell me.
No. I wasn't.
Seeking to die, but also hoping to live.
You don't want to say, do you? Forget it then.
How about this? Let me make an analogy.
You're walking around in a dream, and once you're in the dream,
you want to wake up from the dream, but you can't.
What should you do?
Six words.
Make the best out of it.
Understand?
Strong wood that don't bend will break.
Forget it. It's like playing zither to a cow.
(idiom meaning the person's too dumb to understand)
Make the best out of it?
I told you to do it like this.
I don't think so.
I think it's a pretty good idea to do it here.
What's wrong?
Good, Fourth Brother is here. Why don't
we ask for Fourth Brother's opinion?
Fourth Brother.
Weren't you just discussing Tenth Brother's birthday banquet?
How did you start arguing?
What were you arguing about?
Fourth Brother, Tenth Brother wants to hold his birthday banquet at my estate,
but the Crown Prince
wants to help Tenth Brother hold a birthday banquet
so that we brothers can have fun.
What does Fourth Brother think about this?
Since it's Tenth Brother's birthday,
Crown Prince has already said,
everything should follow Tenth Brother's wishes.
There's nothing wrong with Eighth Brother organizing this.
Exactly.
I think it's great to hold it at Eighth Brother's estate.
Crown Prince is making a superfluous move.
Tenth Brother, Crown Prince means well.
He just wants you to be happy on your birthday.
Tenth Brother, Crown Prince cares about his brothers
and regards you as important.
You should be happy.
I am already very happy now.
Eighth Brother,
are we holding it at Cefujin's place?
What's going on with you?
You want Ruoxi to plan it for you, right?
No.
I was just casually asking.
I was wondering why he argued with me for so long.
You really don't?
I was really just casually asking.
Six words.
Make the best out of it. Understand?
No wonder he's the future Qing emperor.
Make the best you can of things. Bingo!
Play shuttlecock, huh?
Second Miss knows how to play too?
Lil' bit. (slang)
Lil' bit?
I finally found
something fun to play with that transcends both time and age.
Second Miss is amazing.
Count.
- Second Miss.
- Quick, count.
Shuttlecocks can be kicked like this too?
Second Miss is really awesome.
Second Miss.
Second Miss is really amazing.
Second Miss can kick it so many times.
Greetings to Bei'le.
Greetings to Eighth Prince.
Rise.
We'll take our leave.
Looking at people kicking shuttlecock, and not saying anything.
You watched me nap,
but didn't say anything either.
In the carriage.
I'm going to find Ruolan and Difujin
to discuss the matter of Tenth Brother's birthday celebration.
Come along.
Bei'le,
I don't have experience with planning these sort of things.
Why don't we ask Difujin instead?
Minghui is already very busy handling household affairs.
What more,
this is what Tenth Brother himself wanted.
Since Bei'le asked you to do it,
you should do it.
Yes. Then I'll organize it then.
It's just a family banquet.
You don't need to be too nervous.
We just want a place to have some fun.
If you need anything, feel free to come find me.
Remember,
don't let Bei'le lose face.
Yes. I understand.
Thank you, Jiejie.
Bei'le,
if there isn't any other matters,
I'll return first.
What time will you be coming tonight?
I'll tell the servants to prepare.
No need.
I'm staying at the South Building tonight.
I didn't know Bei'le was staying over tonight.
Allow me to make the preparations first.
I'll go see if there's anything I can help with too.
This fish isn't fresh; get another one.
Yes.
How could you shred the carrot like that?
So thick. How do you expect people to eat it?
Yes.
Madam.
Qiaohui, it is just an everyday family dinner.
Don't be so nervous.
Madam, that's now how it is.
It's rare that Bei'le is staying over,
how can we be sloppy?
Bei'le likes to eat the dumplings you make.
The dumpling skin has already been prepared for you.
Qiaohui,
why are you even more nervous than Jiejie?
Second Miss, I don't want Madam to be bullied by these servants anymore.
Before, Bei'le rarely came over.
So they think that because Madam is not favored,
they don't have any respect for her.
Does Jiejie know?
Of course, she knows.
But Madam herself doesn't care.
I'm feeling indignant on Madam's behalf.
Second Miss, you don't know.
Within this household, if you don't have any status,
it's hard to get by.
It's only by letting them know
that Bei'le cares about Madam,
and regards her as important,
then they will respect her more.
Tenth Prince's birthday banquet is our chance to show them.
Jiejie, let me help you.
Tenth Prince's birthday celebration,
we must organize it well.
Don't worry.
Since you two are such good friends,
your feelings toward him,
I already know.
What are you talking about?
Actually, Tenth Prince
wants you to plan his birthday.
Do you understand?
I know.
It's because we have fun playing together.
Jiejie, I hope you're not overthinking it.
Am I really thinking too much?
Yes, you're overthinking.
So bored. So bored.
Rabbit!
Be good, little rabbit.
If you stay with me, you'll have meat to eat. (slang for have a good life)
You'll have carrots to eat.
Come. Come.
Follow the big rabbit home.
Running away?
Quick, quick, quick. Stop running! Stop running!
Tenth Brother, why did you think to have Ruolan plan your birthday?
Minghui won't plan it to your liking?
Eighth Brother, stop guessing anyhow.
Actually, I'm always very happy during my birthday every year.
It's only that
I feel that Ruoxi has a lot of eccentric ideas.
Maybe she'll have something fresh.
Stop running! Stop running!
Little rabbit.
Ruoxi?
This little girl really is a little eccentric.
Hearing isn't the same as seeing; she sure is lively.
- Ruoxi!
- Stop running, stop running.
Ruoxi, what are you doing?
What happened?
Ruoxi.
Eighth Prince, there are rabbits in your estate!
Rabbits? Where are the rabbits?
Where did the rabbit go?
Hurry and say. Where's the rabbit?
It got scared off by you!
My fault again?
It's okay, it's not like this place is very big.
If you want to find it, you'll definitely be able to.
Fourteenth Prince.
Greetings, Fourteenth Prince.
Are you still going to look for the rabbit?
Of course.
- Then, then hurry and look!
- Look!
Lively indeed.
Eighth Brother, let's go have a look. Come.
Sorry.
If not because I chased after you guys to play with you,
they wouldn't have captured you to give to me either.
They are princes.
Since they gave you to me,
I can't set you free.
But don't worry,
I will treat you guys very well.
Actually we're all the same,
stuck in a cage.
I heard that when you fell from the second store
you damaged your brain.
Seems like it's true.
Who are you?
You don't even know who I am now?
Your brain really got damaged.
Lady Mingyu was there.
She said you fell down by yourself.
Okay then.
Seeing as how you're so pitiful,
I'll tell you.
My elder sister is the Difujin,
Gorolo Minghui.
Now do you know who I am?
I don't know her.
Do you guys know?
How dare you not hold me in esteem?
So what if I don't show you any respect?
You!
Even your sister has to behave humbly in front of me.
Who do you think you are?
What right do you have to speak to me like this?
You!
Best not to cause problems for Jie Jie.
I remember now.
You're Difujin's younger sister,
Gorolo Mingyu.Correct?
I have to practice my writing. Goodbye.
Let's go.
Stop there!
Is there anything else?
Where did you get the rabbits?
None of your business. The princes gave them to me.
Give them to me.
Why should I?
I want them.
There are no whys.
There are always exceptions.
Are you giving or not?
I've already given, My Lady.
Glad that you know what's good for you.
My Lady is mistaken.
I've already given you face.
You!
Give it to me!
Stop!
Jiejie!
Mingyu.
Let go.
It's only an animal.
How could you
do things that would lower your status just for its sake?
That's right.
I wouldn't want to
lower my status just for this little beast.
I'm returning it to you! Little beast.
Very good.
Why did you insist on me bringing him out?
Use him to deal with,
deal with bad people.
Deal with what bad people?
Someone dares to bully you?
What a joke. Who would dare to bully me?
I just heard
that Tenth Prince's dog is extremely loyal,
so I wanted to see it for myself.
Tenth Prince, do you come to Eighth Prince's estate often?
Yes.
Then you must definitely know
how the Difujin bullies my sister. Hurry and tell me.
No.
They get along very well.
Why would she bully your sister?
And to think I thought of you as a real friend.
But you're giving me such an insincere answer.
So not dependable.
Who says I'm answering you insincerely?
As a friend, you must be dependable, and be willing to die for each other (literally be stabbed on both sides of the ribs).
You don't even dare to tell me the truth.
Of course you can't stab my ribs on both sides!
I'm not an undependable person.
What do you want to know?
How does the Difujin treat my sister?
Between women, of course it's inevitable that there will be rivalry for favor
and harsh words exchanged.
"Rivalry for favor?"
She wouldn't hit my sister, would she?
Of course not.
"Even if one does not respect the monk, he has to respect Buddha." (Chinese idiom)
With Eighth Brother there, no way.
Then my sister must definitely have been bullied.
Your sister is gentle-tempered.
Of course, she'll get bullied a little.
Let me tell you.
Minghui and her sister are infamous for being extremely unreasonable.
Even I'm a little scared of them.
But,
that Minghui's not that reckless.
As for that Mingyu...
What about her?
Sometimes she doesn't even respect me!
Hey! You say "Oh" like it's a natural thing for her not to respect me!
Don't be mistaken.
What I mean to say is,
someone as willful as her
might not even respect the Emperor.
She wouldn't dare! Even though her grandfather was one of the dynasty's founding figures,
but she wouldn't be that audacious*, would she.
(literally guts are so big, they cover the sky)
Her guts may be big, but cannot cover the sky.
But surely, dog's guts can cover the sky*, right?
(*also means audacious)
"Dog's guts can cover the sky"?
What does that mean?
Where is it?
Here it is.
Coming. Coming.
What?
Let's play over there.
Where?
Lady Mingyu is there.
So what if she's there?
This is Eighth Prince's estate.
Even though it's Eighth Prince's estate,
but we can't create trouble too.
It's better that we go somewhere else to play.
Who's creating trouble?
Who's bothering whom?
Here, it's here. There.
What are you doing?
What does he like to play?
Ball.
- Give me.
- It's there.
I still can't catch it.
Higher.
Okay, I'll try again.
- I'm so scared!
- Are you all right?
Go away! Go away!
Someone! Hurry and go away! Go away!
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
Something happened!
Go away!
Lady! Be careful, Lady!
Something happened!
- Lady! Lady!
- Lady Mingyu!
Are you all right, Lady Mingyu?
- It hurts!
Lady Mingyu, are you all right?
Lady!
It hurts!
Sorry.
Whose dog was it?
Mine.
You could've raised anything! Why did you have to raise a dog?
Lady, come.
It's gotten me into such a mess!
Beast!
You don't even look before biting!
You cannot bully people (literally dog threatening others based on it's master's authority)!
Little beast, no humanity.
Lady Mingyu, be the bigger person
and don't be angry at Tenth Prince anymore.
You-you-you...
you guys did it on purpose!
I didn't do it on purpose.
You!
Stop arguing!
- I'll hit you! I'll hit you!
- Don't hit anymore!
- You hit me?
- I'll hit you to death!
- Stop hitting!
- I'll hit you!
- Come and hit me!
- I'll teach you to ask the dog to bite me!
It's hurts!
You! You!
Here I go!
Pain!
- Tenth Prince.
- What kind of girl are you?
You hit so hard.
- It hurts like hell.
- Calm down.
Lower your voice.
Lower your voice, lower your voice.
- It hurts so much.
- Please.
- Lower your voice.
- It hurts.
If Jiejie hears you,
then there'll be big trouble.
You dare to do it, but don't dare to admit to it.
What kind of hero are you?
I wasn't a hero to start with.
I'm only a coward.
Miss, Miss, Miss. It's here.
How will this do?
No. No. No.
Xiao Anzi, summon the imperial physician.
- Yes.
- No. No. No.
You definitely cannot summon the imperial physician.
If Eighth Prince knows,
the matter will become serious.
This won't do, that won't do.
Then what do we do?
What if...
how am I to go out with my face like that?
There's no what if.
There's only a thing called foolproof.
Just rub for a while and it'll be fine.
Rub for a while.
My birthday is in a few days.
How do you expect me to face people?
It's fine, it's fine.
It'll be fine by tonight.
Believe me and you won't go wrong.
Really?
Really!
Tenth Prince, don't worry.
Using boiled eggs to rub your face
and the bruises will fade quickly.
It's all right.
Then you guys give it a try then.
Do it lightly.
Lightly, lightly.
I'll do it lightly.
Lightly.
Lightly, lightly.
Don't you think it feels less painful now?
Doesn't it feel quite comfortable as well?
Yes.
Then, don't tell others anymore.
Fine then, I won't tell anymore.
But even if you don't tell,
other people might still say it.
Who? Who would dare tell?
Both of you listen carefully.
Everything you saw and heard today,
don't spread a word.
If any of you dare spread the news,
you'll be in for it!
Yes.
This will do, right?
Then rub this side too.
Okay. Come. Sit here.
Okay.
But even if they don't talk about it,
there is still someone who might.
Who?
Lady Mingyu.
Don't worry about her.
What kind of person who'd gotten into trouble
spill on his own wrongdoings?
Regarding this, I can guarantee it for you.
Really?
Let me tell you.
In this, I have experience.
Yes.
Be good. It'll be all right.
I'll just rub it for a while longer, and it'll be all right.
Come. Sit.
Isn't it very comfortable?
Does it look good?
It looks good.
But I think it's a little too plain.
There's still this outfit.
Does this look good?
Looks good.
But I think
the color is a little too light.
Second Miss, what do you plan to wear?
I want my clothes to be pretty,
and my makeup to be pretty.
All of Second Miss's clothes are very beautiful.
For Tenth Prince's birthday, I must look festive.
Festive.
This color. How is it?
The color is good.
- Go.
- Jiejie!
Jiejie!
What's different about me today?
Your hair is different.
Eye makeup is also different.
Do I look good?
You look good.
Everyone says
that we sisters look similar.
So if I look good,
doesn't Jiejie also look good?
You sure do know how to sweet-talk.
I'm speaking the truth.
Jiejie,
and I thought that this Cefujin would have some surprise in mind,
turns out, it's nothing more than this.
Looks like we'll have to eat in this empty place tonight.
Greetings, Jiejie*.
(*Minor wives/concubines tend to address the primary wife as elder sister)
Greetings, Difujin.
Greetings, Lady Mingyu.
Rise.
Cefujin plans to celebrate Tenth Prince's birthday here?
Having the meal outside with just the blue sky overhead, and the ground below your feet.
Aren't you afraid you'll humiliate Bei'le
and become a laughingstock?
Bei'le said before
that he hopes to organize a festive family banquet.
I thought that
such a setting is sufficiently ceremonious,
while allowing the princes
enjoy themselves without restrictions.
Really?
I'm only afraid that without having had any experience to compare against,
you don't know what is appropriate.
Mingyu!
Cefujin has already put in a lot of thought.
You're right, Jiejie.
We are straightforward and honest.
We don't know how to be hypocritical.
If one doesn't put in effort,
how would one get Bei'le to side with her?
Mingyu, stop talking
or Bei'le will be unhappy.
She has already spoken her mind.
Only now do you act magnanimous.
Ruoxi!
What did you say?
Eighth Prince is fair.
Who is being scheming and manipulative?
Eighth Prince knows it in his heart.
Besides, Jiejie and Eighth Prince's hearts are linked as one.
Whatever Eighth Prince is thinking of,
Jiejie knows it all.
So there's no need to trouble Difujin
and Lady to worry about it.
Quickly, how's the planning going?
Eighth Sister-in-law.
Greetings to the Princes.
Rise.
Lady Mingyu,
really looks radiant today.
When did a fairy from the Heavens arrive here?
She must be the Ruoxi Tenth Brother speaks about so often.
Right, Twelfth Brother.
How did you know she's Ruoxi?
The other princes said that there's been a pretty girl who's come to Eighth Brother's estate.
Just take a look to see who's the prettiest here.
Is there still a need to say anything else?
Ruoxi!
How come you look different from how you look normally?
But you still look especially pretty.
Good taste.
Of course.
Ruoxi, is today's decoration all done by you?
Eighth Brother, look.
This place is decorated so beautifully.
So festive.
It was Ruolan's idea.
Thank you, Cefujin!
I especially like it.
Bei'le, I don't feel too well.
I shall return and rest.
It isn't something serious, is it?
It's just my head hurts a little.
But don't worry, Bei'le,
it's nothing much.
Go back then.
Princes, I'll take my leave then.
Crown Prince and Thirteenth Brother haven't arrived yet.
Fourth Brother, why don't we go to South Building and drink some tea?
Okay.
Good. Good.
Then we'll wait for him today.
We must make Thirteenth Brother thoroughly drunk.
Tenth Brother, you can't outdrink "Go-All-Out Thirteenth Brother" (gives his utmost in everything).
Even Yama (Chinese King of Hell) is afraid of ghosts who gives their utmost.
But, I like it!
Miss.
Miss, what's wrong?
Nothing. Just daydreaming.
Qiaohui, I'm hungry.
Go get me something to eat.
Then I'll go grab you something to eat.
Wait for me at North Building.
Second Miss, food's here.
What's wrong?
That Gorolo Mingyu.
I've seen her so many times,
today was the time she was the most arrogant.
Her mother
is the Emperor's cousin,
Princess Heshuo.
Her father is Mingshang Prince Consort.
Her sister is Bei'le's Difujin.
Naturally, her status isn't ordinary.
So what?
Who's afraid of whom? What can she do to me?
Second Miss is still so competitive.
It's called a reasonable self-defense.
Please don't get into another accident.
You were already taught a lesson here the last time. And you're doing it again.
Taught a lesson?
I fell down the stairs the last time.
Could it be her?
Second Miss, I didn't say anything.
I-I didn't say anything.
Didn't say anything.
Got it.
♫  Stopping here, afraid to go any further ♫
♫  So sorrow will be unable to make an appearance  ♫
♫  On the next page, the farewell penned by you, ♫
♫ it was not up to me to refuse  ♫
♫  We’ve walked down this path too hastily  ♫
♫  Embracing desires that weren’t realistic  ♫
♫  Not in time, wasn’t able to wait long enough to look back and admire  ♫
♫  The fragrance of magnolia is unable to hide wounds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the sunlight peeking through the clouds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the paradise that we promised each other  ♫
♫  No longer sighing, you once said that life is unpredictable  ♫
♫  The three inches of sunlight that I was unable to borrow  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the sunlight peeking through the clouds  ♫
♫  No longer looking for the paradise that we promised each other  ♫
♫  No longer sighing, you once said that life is unpredictable  ♫
♫  The three inches of sunlight that I was unable to borrow  ♫
♫  That paradise is the place where I’d loved you  ♫