Lee Joon Gi
Lee Kyung Young
Kim Ji Eun
Again My Life
Episode 5
We oppose the restructuring of Mirae Automobiles.
- We oppose!
The company's compulsory liquidation should not be allowed.
- Do not allow it!
We oppose the sell-off.
We oppose! We oppose!
We oppose the restructuring of Mirae Automobiles.
Mirae Automobiles was dissolved after it was sold to a foreign company
as the result of a labor-management conflict.
I know what’s going to happen with Mirae,
but I can’t do anything right now.
- We oppose the sell-off.
-  We oppose it!
- We're oppose it!
- We oppose it!
We oppose the restructuring of Mirae Automobiles.
We oppose it! We oppose it!!
Where is Kang Man Cheol these days?
Are you referring to the Kang Man Cheol from the Progressive Labor Party, sir?
That's right.
He's at the protest camp at the factory in Byeongtaek.
- Let's go to Byeongtaek.
- Sorry? Right now?
Let him know I'm on my way. I want to have a cup of coffee with him.
Yes, sir.
Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop,
I heard if you go to the Blue House, even the President himself will scramble to greet you.
But here you are in this shabby tent to share instant coffee with me!
I don't expect you to scramble to meet me.
So at least get yourself some new shoes. It looks like you're putting on a show.
I live by the teachings of Lao Tzu. Isn't it about having fewer possessions?
Having a lot is chaotic.
Chaos can be fun too.
I heard your son got into Harvard?
I thought people of the Juche faction
generally sent their kids to places like Byongyang University.
(Juche supports North Korean political ideologies.
Do I get to decide which school they go to?
They figure it out themselves.
That's true.
Time flies when I talk to you.
Coming to the point. This strike... let's wrap it up..
- Neatly.
- What?
You are holding something big.
Then just enjoy it by yourself. Why are you trying to get us involved?
Is there a deal that would favor such a fringe party like ours?
This is all to save workers and businesses. What other deal do you need?
I’m curious.  I'm really curious.
Also, for how long are you going to be the party representative?
Parliamentary Negotiation Body. Floor leader. It's time you take those positions.
Last time you took three seats.
- If you consider the proportion, it's just one seat.
- That's why!
No more graceful concessions every election season. Sure, you can say it was for unification.
But in reality, you're just treated as window dressing for the Daehan Party.
Are you already preparing for the general elections?
Saving the economy. Bipartisan. Cooperation?
You are aiming for that, I see.
Even if your opponent's ranking rises, yours will as well,
and you can keep an eye on the main opposition party.
Just how many birds are you killing with one stone?
I don't like it, but it's good.
All I have to do is take a picture next to you.
How can I reject this?
What an offer!
Jo Tae Seop!
They made this decision for the good of the country.
A big round of applause!
From now on, we'll work
to make an environment where workers and companies can coexist...
Mirae Automobiles is going to Cheonha?
This is a different story from my previous life.
Until the dramatic conclusion of the Mirae Automobile strike,
Assemblyman Jo Tae Seop raised his voice at the party meeting
to focus on revitalizing the economy with a bipartisan mindset.
The Daehan Party preparing for the general elections ...
The goal is not the general election, but the presidential election.
Ridiculous stuff.
It once again hit an all-time high. The next news.
A horrific thing happened when a friend of 40 years went home
and killed his friend for not paying money back.
The police arrested the suspect, Mr. Park, and are investigating other details.
This case...
Mr. Park's fingerprints were found on a weapon at the crime scene.
The investigation is focused on the possibility of a crime of revenge.
An on-site inspection is expected to be conducted today.
Here, take the knife.
Victim
From here. Like this.
Like this. Do it, just like you did last time.
I didn't do it.
Are you going to change your position here? It will complicate things for us.
Don't you remember this knife?
That, that is ...
It's the one that I held,
but when I thought of my son, I did not stab him.
How can you do this here? There's proof also.
If you continue this, only your sentence will increase. Your sentence!
It's not me. Really!
I did not kill him.
He's coming out. There he is!
They should at least show his face.  Heaven will punish him.
You killed someone for some money.
Raise your head if you are confident, you bastard.
Where were you going, really?
Dad! Father! My Dad did nothing wrong.
It's not him! Catch the real culprit! Why is it my dad?
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Park Sang Man?
- You are Park Sang Man, right?
- Yes. What is it?
- Who are you?
- I'm the one who will prove your dad's innocence.
In exchange, return to school tomorrow.
You, come over here.
Why did you take off your backpack? Stand here.
The real culprit of this case is revealed after 10 years.
Believe me and continue your studies, Park Sang Man.
How can he study?
Do you think he will be first in the school?
Hey, be careful.
That punk might stab you for rolling your eyes, just like his dad.
It won't take too long. Bear it and get through it.
I know it's hard to believe unless I show you the results.
But believe me.
There's nothing you can do to help your dad now anyway.
Again My Life
Drinking when you feel like it's not enough... will it fill what's not there?
Ohh, my kid brother!
- Sunbaenim!
- Yeah.
What's the matter? Sit down.
Please take a look at this case.
Daesin News: "Man who killed his friend of forty years, arrested due to his fingerprints found on the weapon."
What about this?
It's the father of a friend I know.
I feel like the police have missed something.
Hey, Kim Hui Wu. Why are you meddling?
Murder case arrest rate in Korea?
It's almost 100%.
Here!
- They found the murder weapon, right?
-  Yes.
- They got fingerprints there.
- Yes.
- There is a grudge.
- That's right.
- Gosh! He was drunk?
- Yes.
That's it. There's no need to dig deeper.
That's the problem.
- Murder weapon, motive, and fingerprints. Everything came out very perfectly and quickly.
- What?
There was so much evidence
that they didn't even feel the need to prove his innocence.
Take a look at this.
Now, look here.
- What's this?
- It's the clothes my friend's father wore on the day of the murder.
If you check the CCTV in the vicinity, you can confirm it.
What's the probability of not having blood stains on your clothes when stabbing someone?
Zero! As you see, the clothes are clean.
And there is no evidence that it was washed or erased.
Other than this also, there are many ways to confirm it.
Wow!
Sunbaenim, wasn't the law actually made for the suspect?
I learned that avoiding unfair punishment comes first.
If this is true, then there's a gaping hole in the police force.
And the prosecution is filling it?
Then, the story becomes splendid!
Do you know anything else in detail?
Of course!
Okay, Ms. Lee Seon Yeong.
- You are Hong In Pyo's wife, right?
- Yes.
I heard that you often said you wanted to kill your husband.
- Is that right?
- Please call my lawyer.
Right. Of course.
But before that...
Here.
What is this?
You must be glad to meet him.
The affair itself began with a breach of trust.
How can you have faith in that? Let's hear what happened on the day of the murder.
That day... I received a phone call late at night.
Why are you calling a person who was on his way out?
What this? Have you lost your mind?!
You said... you needed money, right?
This man's property is ours now.
We are going to be rich now.
This...
Quickly take this far away and burn it.
This knife too. Hurry.
Did you kill your husband Hong In Pyo?
Yes. I did it.
Why?
It was a good opportunity.
Pay me back at once. My 100 million won! The money I worked so hard for.
Hey... friend. How can I pay back what I don't even remember borrowing?
Do you have proof that you loaned me money?
You... How could you do this to me?
Stab me.
Go ahead and stab me!
Stab me!
If you want to ruin your son, Sang Man's future, try and stab me!
That bastard deserved worse than death.
He only thinks about himself.
He would often disregard the weak and beat them.
You're right. That's why I have always wanted to kill him.
And I was afraid that I would be caught in my infidelity too.
Prosecutor, I'll be pardoned right?
If you're not careful, you'll take the fall for everything. So think wisely.
1 day ago
- That will never happen.
- All right.
- Where did you hide it?
- Sorry? Hide what?
You're giving it away by acting surprised like that.
The evidence from the scene of Hong In Pyo's murder. You're the one who hid it!
Prosecutor, you shouldn't count your chickens before they hatch.
There's a trend in those who hide those types of things.
Nowadays, kimchi refrigerators?
They tend to hide them there.
If I find it, and recover it. You'll be charged with concealing evidence,
and negligent homicide, and conspiracy, no—
Never mind. I'm just going straight for homicide.
If you confess now and ease the load of work on my subordinates,
t would help reduce your sentence, yes? Here ...
Prosecutor, I will tell you everything.
Hey, wrap it up.
- Yes, sir.
- Prosecutor.
Prosecutor!
Everything was exactly as Hui Wu had said.
Pressure the wife's lover first.
It's something he can use to hold leverage over her. So he clearly must've hidden it somewhere.
I'm half-joking, but
they say there's a trend in where those things are hidden.
First-time offenders tend to follow what's depicted in videos or movies.
For example... I mean, I'd hide it in my kimchi refrigerator.
- Gosh.
- Joking.
But you never know.
Kim Hui Wu, who the heck is he?
what the hell is he?
- Oh, Prosecutor Jang.
- Oh, yes.
- Well done! I just heard it.
- Ah yes.
It'll be a big thing when the media hears about it!
There are great expectations of you.
Thank you, sir!
Hey, Kim Hui Wu, thank you.
I feel really awkward being in the position of owing you.
But it's actually not bad.
Seonbae, you just need to keep marching on the smooth, obstacle free road.
I'm just your lumberjack.
Hey!  I have to say you're really growing on me.
You need to keep your wits sharp. Hui Wu is quite extraordinary.
If he becomes a prosecutor, surely he'll be soaring here and there.
I know. You'll help me out later on, right?
Oh! I'm embarrassed. I'm still lacking.
Hey, don't be so modest.
You can be aptly arrogant, and as long as your work can back it up,
that's way cooler.
Hey, Kim Hui Wu, how did you know?
Sorry?
How would I know?
No, I mean you said it was a favor,
said it was half a joke, and everything you told me was exactly correct.
And what's more, you sounded professional.
I was merely earnest and was lucky.
You listened to me, Sunbae-nim, and even resolved it.
I am just so very thankful.
Here. With this atmosphere, let's all have a shot, guys!
We'll be saying cheers.
And we'll continue zooming straight down.  (Onomatopoeia for drinking was used as a pun)
It was the first case I worked on as a prosecutor. Of course, I know everything about it.
- Go all out.
- And you need to work a bit harder.
- Over here!
- Honey!
Father!
Honey!
Don't worry! I'm fine. You must have been worried sick.
Honey, it must've been so hard.
- Oh you're so gaunt.
- No it's okay.
You must've suffered so much.
You look so skinny.
I feel so bad for you, Honey.
- Are you okay? How's your health?
- I'm fine.
You were the one who saved your father.
It took ten years.
Please prove my father's innocence.
Please help me, Prosecutor.
So at least your face doesn't look as bad.
It must have been hard because of me.
The ten years that it took to reach the truth,
use them solely on yourself this time, Park Sang Man.
It's so nice since you're finally out.
Wishing you perfect scores on the CSAT
- Fighting!
CSAT, even if you guess may it be correct. Let's go! Let's go to college!
With the wisdom you have acquired, we hope you get a high score.
CSAT, 18th Testing Site
Fighting! You can do it!
Kim Han Mi!
What? Have you come to wish me luck?
This early morning? In this weather?
You deserve it.
- As a woman?
- As my student.
- Your defense is unbeatable.
- Just do as you've prepared, don't get nervous.
- Were you this nervous too?
-  Don't worry,
you studied hard, so expect good results.
What? Are you scared?
I expected as much, so I prepared something for you.
- For me?
- Yes.
- What is this?
- Let's call them good luck charms.
I used these pens last year.
They're filled with the energy of a student who got into Hankuk School of Law.
♫  Waking up in darkness  ♫
- Your arrogance is overflowing.
- Of course it is.
♫   frozen time  ♫
The CSAT pens filled with the energy of arrogant Hui Wu. It's a nice feeling.
♫  I'm lost somewhere it is pitch black in front of me  ♫
♫  And if I get another chance  ♫
Don't worry too much.
You're my student who's smarter than anyone else.
Do well on your test. Then I'll be off.
♫  In the suffocating smoke  ♫
♫  I wanna rise higher  ♫
♫  Under the blackened sky   ♫
♫  I'll let it burn   ♫
Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
Exam Ticket: Park Sang Man
♫  I'll protect my life  ♫
♫  Even if it's both painful and hard, I will run  ♫
♫  until I reach you, I'll follow  ♫
♫  I really want a better way  ♫
♫  I'm lost somewhere it is pitch black in front of me  ♫
♫  And if i get another chance  ♫
♫  I'll follow you to the end of hell  ♫
♫  I'll let it burn, fire  ♫
♫  In the suffocating smoke  ♫
♫  I wanna rise higher  ♫
♫  Under the blackened sky  ♫
Wait, does this even make sense?
♫  I'll let it burn   ♫
What?
♫  I'll let it burn, fire  ♫
♫  In the suffocating smoke  ♫
Well done. Great job.
What are you going to do?
- Congratulations, Han Mi.
- Oh my god!
♫  I'll let it burn  ♫
♫  With nothing to protect and nothing to lose   ♫
2009 CSAT Science Correct Answers
Geography Subject
Three and one.
♫  A new opportunity again to light it up  ♫
♫  makes me burn  ♫
Exam Ticket
♫  I'll let it burn, fire  ♫
♫  In the suffocating smoke  ♫
Hangang University
Acceptance Inquiry
Accepted
Kim Han Mi
Dept of News and Broadcast Media
I need to call to Hui Wu.
Deputy Prosecutor
- Yes?
- You got accepted into all the colleges you applied for.
- Yes.
- You can go to Songwha Women's University Dept of English.
Aren't congratulations in order for things like this?
- I thought you weren't interested  and out of the blue—
- Kim Han Mi.
- Are you afraid of me turning out well?
- What?
I put in my own effort to get accepted, can't I decide for myself on the school and major?
Did you forget? Live quietly.
Don't select a job where your name will become known.
You cannot go into media or public service, even more so.
Do as you're told
if you'd like to continue to live in a country where you at least speak the same language.
News and Broadcast Media
Journalism and Media Studies at Hangang University?
Yes.
You chose well. You'll become a good reporter.
Huh? What?
How did you know?
I haven't told anyone yet.
Well, just...
Don't kids who go to the Department of Mass Communication usually dream of being a journalist?
Oh... Good point.
Proud of you, Kim Han Mi!
I am proud of you too! For not giving up on me.
Thanks to your determination, I was able to come this far.
Thank you!
No, this is just the starting point.
- You haven't reached anywhere yet.
- Ugh.
Gosh!
Just when I start to like you, you have to ruin the mood.`
I like that.
Anyway, be thankful later.
- Pay me back when you become a journalist.
- Okay!
I am sure there will be a day when I'll pay you back big time.
- Cheers!
- Okay!
Waiting for that day! Congratulations, Han Mi!
It doesn't suit me to be this happy.
If it doesn't suit you, who would it suit?
Do you want me to cover you thickly with happiness?
- How?
- Order another side dish.
- Wow... it's so easy.
- Yes it is.
If I order a side dish here and it tastes good, I feel so happy!
I feel really good!
Why is your expression like this then?
Don't you know?
Why I'm unable to fully enjoy this?
Did I want to be acknowledged?
Mom, Dad! Today was hard wasn't it?
How can I help you?
What's with the mood?
Business wasn't good today, right?
My baby boy!
Son!! So... that is...
What's the matter?
You got a draft notice.
Gosh! Why would I receive the draft again...
Draft Notice To Mr. Kim Hui Wu
Oh my God, my son has grown so much. Now he is going to serve in the military.
Yes.
Th-The military is a thing.
Of course, it's is a thing. All countries have one.
Our country has a draft system.
That... if you pass the exam, you can become a military judicial officer.
- Oh right, the military judicial officer.
- I think it would be good for you to take it on like a man, without any delay.
Yes. I will do so.
By the way, I was from the Special Forces.
When I was parachuting, I was able to shoot at a peanut and hit it.
When I was a diver, once I got into the water, I came out the next day.
What are you saying? You were the military cook, weren't you?
- In every letter, you whined about not wanting to peel onions.
- I was the Special Forces cook.
There was also a time when I had to peel 1000 onions in one sitting. When your mother came to visit at that time,
she was touched that I was crying and did not go home that day.
That's cool!
That's when you were made.
Stop it!
What? Military?
You subtly keep doing whatever you want.
Subtly? This is on the face. Who gives only a two-day notice?
Like someone here. I am upset.
- Like you'd be more upset than the guy going to the army a second time.
- What?
Yes. What? Why?
But, why are you getting angry?
- We are just flustered!
Aren't you nervous? How come you are always in a far-sighted mood?
- Why would I be nervous when it's my second time?
- Then again...
It's not like you're going twice. Finish it short and sweet.
Meanwhile, we will become old-fashioned seniors.
Okay!
If you come in as my junior, you are dead!
I will make it hard for you, so be prepared.
Anytime.
I am speechless.
By the way, what did you say earlier? Like someone?
- Don't you know yet? Hui Ah...
- What?
She is going abroad to study. The day after tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
Yes, esteemed elder.
What, elder?
He has so many secrets. What's with the elder?
- Do you notice anything?
- Not sure...
He doesn't open up about his private life.
Wow, he is so charming, Hui Wu. He is the first guy to make me this curious.
Okay, everyone! I have a dinner appointment, I will take my leave now.
- His cool nature. Wow.
- Where are you going?
Aren't you having a farewell drink? You should have a farewell party.
Why is going to the military a farewell? Time will fly.
Anyway, I'll be back safely. I'll see you on the other side, Sunbae.
I'll be back!
Does he think of the military as a 4-day retreat?
Not even a retreat, but a Templestay, maybe?
Real Estate
I am going to the military.
So? No need to tell me about it.
About the money you gave me. Because it's such a large amount
leaving it quietly for two years doesn't feel right.
I couldn't think of a way to manage it safely.
That's why...
Here you go.
Please watch over it.
Do you think I'll readily accept money that I've already given away?
Also! How do you when what will happen to me?
But no matter how I think about it,
you're the only one who can handle this money.
Is that so?
There are some real estate properties I have my eyes on.
Where are they?
Mapo.
As expected!
Seeing how you're not questioning me, I take it you have a gut feeling about this.
I already felt that you were not a normal guy.
Please take care of it.
Alright. I'll at least ease your concerns before you go to the military.
Master! Thank you!
Loyalty!
A life is given to me again.
Mom, Dad.
- Kim Gyu Ri!
- Don't try to repay in the wrong way.
You are my friend, right. We are all your friends!
I am a freshman. Computer Engineering Major. Kim Hui Ah. And you?
Do you know what real estate is? You see only money if you started with that as a goal.
Thank you.
I am changing the lives of precious people around me and the future.
♫  Give up, I warn you so  ♫
♫  Who would ever find out who you really are? Hm  ♫
I, Jo Tae Seop, will help you.
- I am Jo Tae Seop.
- Jo Tae Seop! Jo Tae Seop!
I need to let my son, Hyeon Seok, go.
Even Jo Tae Seop's life is changing a little bit.
♫  I don't care what they say  ♫
♫  At the end, They'll know there's no where to hide  ♫
And...
Han Ji Hyeon...
♫  Oh I'll wait for now   ♫
♫  Let them get what they want  ♫
♫  At the end, I'll get that chance to beat them  ♫
Will you be alright alone?
Why am I tearing up?
If both of you accompany me, I don't think I can leave.
Let me just say goodbye here.
Be healthy. Don't hurt yourself.
Okay.
Please sit down. Let me bow to you.
Okay, let's see it.
Mother and Father, I'll be back safe and sound.
Why didn't you tell me?
It's upsetting.
And you?
Same reason, then?
Aren't you leaving?
Yes, I should.
- Hey?
- Keep quiet.
You're supposed to play dumb at times like these.
Besides my dad, you're the first man whose arm I've held.
This is the end.
Goodbye, Kim Hui Wu. Let's meet again.
Alright. Let's meet again.
Go safely.
You too.
- I'll get going.
- Yeah.
Seven Years Later
Gangwon District Prosecutors' Office, Gimsan Branch Office
Hello. I am Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu.
Branch Chief Jeon Seok Gyu
- Kim Hui Wu?
- Yes.
- Top at the training center?
So why have you come here?
I came here to take you to Seoul.
- Me?
- Yes.
Is it not to keep an eye on me?
You're mistaken.
- About what?
- You're not even worth keeping an eye on.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Now I'm curious. I'm a throwaway prosecutor, and you're here to take me to Seoul for no good reason?
Good reason? I can make you one.
Got it. You can find your office, right?
Detective Oh Min Guk will assist you with any questions. Let's have a drink once Prosecutor Ji Seong Ho's back.
- You can go.
- Sure.
- Top at the training center?
- Yeah.
I've never seen a top-rated prosecutor in my 15-year career as an investigator.
And the funny thing is that he applied to come here.
Really? The head of the training center class chose our branch?
That's what I'm saying!
But why? Isn't it a given to apply to Seoul with such a resume?
Yeah! It's strange, isn't it?
For sure! Why would someone apply to a rural area unless they've lost their mind?
I hope he's not an over-achiever. Those are the ones who always get into trouble.
Don't worry. There's nothing to over achieve about here.
The Branch Chief is living proof of that.
- True.
- I love it.
Hello. I am Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu.
Hello Prosecutor, I am Investigator Oh Min Guk.
Oh right, it's nice to meet you.
Oh, I work for Mr. Ji, so.
- Is that my desk?
- Yes.
Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu
I organized your desk with the basics. If you need anything, just tell me.
It's my first day. Can I still take your offer?
Of course, you can. Would you like some coffee?
No. I can get coffee myself.
Gather all the cases from the last six months, whether they're criminal or civil, and report them to me.
- Pardon?
- You told me I could ask for anything.
Ah, ah, right, yes.
What is this unnerving sensation?
We have a newbie, right?
Oh, yes. I am Kim Hui Wu.
There's no need for that. Follow me.
Wow! The Regional Prosecutor is here!
Have a seat first.
So that's where all of you were.
Your face has become better, Hyeong-nim. I guess you're living comfortably now.
- Yes
- The mayor.
We're busy handling all of the cases
so you must have a lot of free time.
Police precinct head officer.
You're right.
Since it's been a long time since we last met, you should have a drink, yeah?
Assemblyman.
And that gaudy-looking guy is the community leader, but he's a gang leader.
Everyone was born and raised here.
Here.
Thank you.
I love it a lot. I love that the regional prosecutor is able to drink so well!
You're doing so well.
I'm putting in a good word to the superiors for you, so there's going to be good news soon.
Shouldn't you go to a better place when you leave here?
Thank you.
You saw right? That's the country for you.
In the country, your connections come before the law.
They're all so tied up together, so they're mean to outsiders.
These sons of bitches.
What's up with you today? Throwing out these grievances.
I just wanted to say it.
I didn't want the rookie to take me lightly.
That's what makes you look easy.
You could just follow my concept.
It's because your politics are neither here nor there
that you're like this.
What's so cool about being a lone wolf?
There are no ropes to rescue us.
This guy's drunk again. Come to your senses, kid.
Yes.
Team Leader,
don't you want to go to Seoul?
Why do you keep nagging at my side about Seoul?
The way I see it,  although you've been exiled here because you upset your superiors,
I don't think the fire from your youth is gone.
Are you drunk too? The arrogant talk from earlier is all I need.
But you want to go, don't you?
Seoul. Seoul. Seoul.
Pretending you don't.
I'll send you. To Seoul.
- Stop.
- Regional Prosecutor—
Be quiet while you're here.
Then why would I have bothered to come here?
What, is there something you want here?
- Yes.
- What is it?
As for that, I'll report to you once I've sorted it out.
Your motivation might be overflowing, but there won't be much for you to do.
- Can I act freely?
- As freely as you want.
If you give me permission, starting from when I start and end work?
Do as you please! Even if you come to work, there's nothing for you to do at this regional prosecutor's office.
- Want a drink?
- Yes.
It's been a few days, so what do you think about Prosecutor Kim? You were worried that he'd be hard to work with.
I thought so too, at first. So I was really nervous.
And?
Don't be surprised. He really, truly does absolutely nothing.
- He aggressively does nothing.
- Nothing?
Right. On some days he doesn't even come to work.
In some ways, he does even less work than the regional prosecutor.
Even the first place in the training institute is helpless in Gimsan.
No, he could be really smart on the flipside.
As a reward to himself for studying all these years, he came on vacation. Paid vacation.
Or he could be a weirdo.
Weirdo.
What is all this, Prosecutor Kim?
Please reorganize all of these files.
- All of this?
- Yes.
When I looked over all the files you gave me last time, I thought this was a quiet neighborhood,
but there were a lot more cases than I thought.
When am I supposed to—
When do you think? Before you clock out today, of course.
Before the end of the workday? How can I—
Oh by the way have you heard of the Yuchae faction?
Yes, they run a few of the entertainment joints. They're the neighborhood gangsters.
Neighborhood gangsters...
So when I looked at the investigations, all the cases relating to the Yuchae faction weren't closed.
So will you reinvestigate them all?
Yes. I will.
I will be working offsite for a couple of days.
Ah, and send all of the information you organized to me by mail.
I'm supposed to reorganize all of this?
He was a weirdo.
Yes, Elder. Have you been well? It's Hui Wu.
Yes. I was going to see you. Right now.
Hello!
Oh my! What brings this old man here?
I came to meet you, old man.
Well, I'm naturally an old man.
Sure.
What about Sang Man?
Yeah. Well, I did take him in because you earnestly asked for it, but...
What about it? He should be a good kid.
He's good and all, but he doesn't respect the elderly. Talks back.
Wow, you sure have a lot of energy. And you pour all of that energy to insult me?
Look at the way he talks. So rude.
- It's time for your medicine.
- I won't take it, you brat.
Please take it. Straight down.
Hyeong-nim. Did you have a safe trip?
Indeed. Could you be any slower to greet me?
Elder needs a lot of help.
I don't know where he sold off his manners.
Please teach him well until I finish at the institute.
Hello. I am Park Sang Man.
Got it.
So are you here to take him back?
Yes, I am.
- You're ready, right?
- Yes. Let's go.
Oh, are you sad to see me go?
Leave quietly or I'll tie you down.
Wow, I'm so scared. I'll be back!
While I'm gone, be sure to take your medicine well.
Yes, be well.
Yes.
Then, we'll get going.
This is great. Now that I'm in the field. It's so refreshing.
I brought the money like you asked, but where will you spend it?
Are you going to buy that building?
Don't get too ahead of yourself. Elder was concerned about you.
I sought you out because I wanted to repay you and maybe stake my life on you...
Mr. Kim Hui Wu?
Park Sang Man, how did you...?
Did you think that I wouldn't be able to find you?
Well, you did spend ten years finding the criminal. I must've been easy...
I wanted to meet you Sunbae-nim. Let me greet you formally.
I am Park Sang Man!
I'm also a student at Hankuk University and I'm studying computer science,
and I was a scholarship student until last semester.
But I still haven't had a campus romance. But
after receiving the enthusiastic support of my professors and male classmates, I stand before you...
He's much brighter than I expected.
Why are you laughing?
No reason. It's nice to meet you.
I came to pay you back for saving my father.
From now on, these hands and feet
"are yours," was what I wanted to say...
Helping the elder is the same as helping me,
so learn everything thoroughly.
Nagging here and nagging over there.
I thought something interesting might happen when I went in the field.
Something interesting will happen soon. Take the bag.
What?
I heard there's a house nearby.
What? There's nothing like that here, so go on your way.
Now then...
I really shouldn't do this.
Let's have a little taste.
By the way mister, you shouldn't make an estimate just based on the size of the building.
It's really big.
I'll escort you, Hyungnim!
This way, please.
Good shot.
The bag with the money...
Welcome, Boss.
The next time you visit, just ask for Ms. Kim.
Okay. I'll do that.
Let's go.
Let's go in.
♫   Hold on to your mental state and   ♫
♫  I will make you look agile   ♫
The boss is coming through.
♫   I'll take a step or two   ♫
Win a lot of money.
♫    closer   ♫
♫   There's nothing to be afraid of in my dictionary  ♫
♫  Even if you weakly look down on me  ♫
♫  I won't back down   ♫
♫   again  ♫
♫  Don't be afraid  ♫
♫   I'll be easy on you  ♫
♫  Bring it on just bring it on.
I will fight back   ♫
♫   much as I can  ♫
♫   i will keep on fighting  I won't back down again.  ♫
♫   Bring it on it is all worth fighting for  ♫
♫   It's on Don't look back cause i never lose  ♫
You can buy chips over there.
♫   Just bring it on   ♫
♫   I will keep up the fight. You make me   ♫
♫   stronger. Bring it on it is all worth fighting for   ♫
You know what to do next, right?
♫  It's on Don't look back cause I never lose  ♫
How much would you like?
♫   I won't   ♫
Let's start with 10 million won  (10,000 USD).
♫   back down again   ♫
♫  I'm not afraid of the deep darkness  ♫
♫   That high wall can't block me.   ♫
The fee is 10%.
♫  'Cause I'm going one step further  ♫
What the... Ten million won instantly turned into nine million.
Don't be so boorish.
♫  No matter what confronts me,   ♫
♫   I don't care   ♫
♫  I won't back down again.   ♫
This is the most popular game.
The rules are simple. All you have to do is match the number on the dice.
But as you can see, the odds are different for each number.
If you hit 7, the number with the highest odds, you get six times the bet.
If you hit 2 or 12, the numbers with the lowest odds, you get 36 times the bet.
Easy, right?
Yes, well. There's nothing too hard about it.
You're not playing any tricks, are you?
Of course not. We're a local business.
Have fun.
We will.
Here, here, come on ten!
Nine! Nine!
It's an 8.
What the matter?
Ugh, really?
- Seven! Seven!
- A hundred thousand won  (100 USD).
Ten! Ten! Four! Ten!
Come out, come out.
Seven.
It's a six.
Eight!
It's a seven.
- Five.
- It's a seven.
- Eight. Five.
- It's a seven. It's a nine.
Will you keep going?
Of course.
- Sang Man!
- Yes?
Go exchange the rest of the money for more chips.
- Okay.
- Also ...
Oh! And...
Let's keep going.
I have a good feeling.
Seven. All in.
- What?
- All in?
How much would that be if he's right?
It would be 42 million won  (42,000 USD).
Hold on.
I'll change it to six.
Six?
Are you sure you would like to change your choice to six?
The corners of her mouth curved up.
I'm not sure. It also feels like it could be an eight.
It's an eight.
Or maybe a six?
She's relaxed. Then maybe...
Seven!
Please make a final decision.
Oh. Sorry. I guess I'm just being overly cautious since I bet everything.
Hold on.
Six.
No,
let's go with seven.
Hold on.
I'm sorry.
I'll change it for the last time.
Let's go with six.
It's a seven.
- Why did you change it!?
- Wow, just a single round and you're already bust.
Would you like to stop?
Yes. I've spent all the money I brought with me.
Good game.
You lost on purpose, right?
You kept changing your choice on purpose.
Being indecisive doesn't suit you.
So I watched the dealer.
As I kept looking, I found a pattern.
When you changed your number at the end,
It was subtle, but I saw her moving from hell to heaven.
How astute.
After spending so long with Elder, it feels like I've only gotten better at gambling.
At least you got better at something. Great job.
You're not the kind of person to spend money recklessly.
You're also not the kind of person to do it to impress a pretty dealer.
Don't you think I could win her heart without doing anything?
You don't miss a chance to show off. I respect that.
What is it? You even called me to go along with you.
It's boring if you know everything.
You'll see as we go along.
Either way, I'm on my way to Seoul.
- Turn off the lights.
- Okay.
Could we share the bed?
- Don't cross the line.
- Okay.
Oh? You're here early.
Yes. I read all of the materials you e-mailed me.
What about them?
Reorganize everything focusing on these events, one more time.
I've picked out the ones that had slight weaknesses in the police investigation.
Ah... I see.
When do you need it?
Before you leave work, of course.
You can send it via email.
Oh, right! I'll be working outside of the office for a few days.
That crazy...
He's driving me insane.
What's good here?
No need to deliberate too much. The flounder is the best this time of year.
- I'll take that.
- Okay.
I'm Do Ah Jin.
- Why did you do that?
- Do what?
You lost on purpose yesterday.
As if.
If I won, I would have gotten 40 million won.
What do you want to say?
Good game.
I have something to say.
If you're looking for a partner to cheat with, I'll leave now.
It's similar, but I have my own angle.
A personal interest?
I went through a lot of trouble to pick you out, but you keep disappointing me.
Do I look that simple to you?
Let's keep your point short and sweet.
Information on the Yuchae gang who run the gambling house.
What are you?
I'm Kim Hui Wu, the prosecutor at the Gimsan Branch Office.
Prosecutor Kim Hui Wu
Why are you calling me at this hour?
The Yuchae gang.  I'll wipe them out.
What?
Hey, what did you just say?
I said I will wipe out the Yuchae gang.
Do you have evidence?
I can make it now.
What's the matter with you?
They are running an illegal gambling house.
That alone is reason enough. I'd like to call for police assistance.
Hey, punk, listen up.
I don't know what you're up to, but it's dangerous.  Don't do it.
My job is prosecutor.
If I stop because it's dangerous, then I should quit.
Does he have to be so direct?
Hey, you saw them when we were drinking, right?
They're gangsters, right?  But those bastards think they're civil servants.
They're in cahoots with the cops. They're so chummy I bet they even prepare kimchi together.
Police assistance is what they would ask for. Don't do it.
You don't know this place well. That's not how it works.
I'll try to do as you did in Seoul.
What?
Hey, Kim Hui Wu!
I'll report to you again.
Hey. Hey, Kim Hui Wu!
Hey!!
That rock-headed punk.
Billiards
Hyung, will this really be okay?
It's not okay, but if I go, it will be okay.
Why?  Because it's me.
You're sexy.
Want to get married to me?
Oh, that's bad luck.   Want me to slug you?
You're handsome.
Stop talking bull and be sure to be on time.
Yes!
Billiards
I am going.
You're so cool.
Billiards
Designated Smoking Area
Gimsan Billiards
Aigoo, nice to see you.
You came again.
What'll it be this time? Craps again?
- No.
- Then?
Attention everyone here!
Attention!
I'm from the Gimsan Branch Prosecutor's Office.
Everyone here is under arrest for violation of Articles 246 and 247
in flagrante delicto.
Quiet! Quiet!
I see you were a prosecutor all along.
But what's wrong with you? How can such an educated person be so senseless?
- Do you have a warrant?
- Nope.
For in flagrante delicto, I learned a warrant is unnecessary.
Oh is that so?
You seem to be a little uneducated about being in the field.
However, I'm very good at understanding such things.
Okay, I understand that you, the young prosecutor, are upset because of what happened yesterday.
You can just tell us you're upset in a more positive tone.
What is all this? You're giving everyone a hard time with losses.
Here, here.
It's okay, it's okay.
Good.
Good, good.
Let's add bribery charges.
I guess you're serious.
Hey, prosecutor, you're really going to be in trouble.
This is Gimsan.
Do you know why Gimsan's shrimp are so plump and delicious?
It's because they grow up eating human corpses.
Would you like to be dipped in the shrimp habitat out front in the ocean?
Now you're threatening a prosecutor?
I'm adding obstruction of government duties.
You're going to get a lot of jail time. Huh? Huh?
Why you...!
I tried talking to you nicely,
but you won't accept my sincerity.
Hyeon Jong, give me the tool.
Oh no, oh my.
You should kick the can instead.
Don't you know if you come at me with a knife, it'll add to your sentence?
I never learned it, you fucking prosecutor.
Crazy bastard.
One moment.
Looks like you have more than enough manpower.
Hey, it's me.
Now.
What? Turn on the light! Who did this!?
What? Which punk did it? Hey!
N-Not yet...
Hey, Sang Man!
Everybody freeze!
What's going on?
Ajusshi, stay still!
Who are you, Ajusshi? Show me your ID!
Who are you?
Sang Man...
Hyung!
Investigator Oh, what happened?
I came as the backup from the District Prosecutor's Office
and this guy was suspiciously hanging around in front of the breaker.
That's understandable. It's not exactly something I should be doing with confidence.
You two are on the same team.
He said we are on the same team!
Same team?
Anyway, I still have some things to take care of, so make sure you're both safe,
and I'll see you later. Okay?
Yes.
You didn't need to come out just to greet me.
Let's go in.
Why are there so many workers in such a tiny business?
Hey. Do you guys get a dedicated break room working here? Huh!?
I'm a Korean prosecutor. I guess that won't work on you guys.
Hey. I don't have time.
Let's get things started.
Come here!!
♫  Hey, you're so cold.  That evil leer  ♫
♫  You clearly intend something nasty  ♫
♫  Lie lie lie gradually it will come out  ♫
♫  Standing up better watch  ♫
♫  Gonna let you know  ♫
♫  You make me bad with cowardly words  ♫
♫  I’m a piece of threat bet you can’t break it  ♫
♫  Try, Try, Try,  ♫
♫  Even if you look like you're struggling  ♫
♫  Standing up, standing up,   ♫
♫  standing up  ♫
♫  What kind of gang came at me?  ♫
- Bastards... I'm exhausted.
♫  Stopped in your tracks. Stay there and wait just for me  ♫
♫  Even if you fool everyone else with that innocent face  ♫
What do you think? Seems like we took enough care of it, right?
♫  You can't get away from me.  ♫
Yes, of course.
Okay then. Let's go.
Okay.
♫  Oh, bring it on, bring it on, bring it on  ♫
♫  Oh Yeah  ♫
♫  Bring it on Bring it on  ♫
There's an office next to the gambling parlor's chip exchange.
It's the base of the Yuchae faction.
It's an office, but even we can't go in there.
I bet you'll find what you're looking for there.
Oh. Here they were.
- Investigator.
- Yes?
Begin seizing every document that's in this office.
Okay, I understand. I'll bring some boxes.
Sang Man, hack the computer password and compare it to the books.
Okay.
Do you think hacking the computer password will be...
possible.
What was I worried about? He broke through the prosecutor's office server in order to clear his father's name.
Who are you?
Staff Only
Are you okay, Investigator?
I'm o-o-okay.
- Sang Man.
- Yes!
Hey, it's good to see you, Lee Yeon Seok.
- Do you know me?
- You're the reason I'm here.
Of course, I know you.
Then you must know who my master is.
I do. Very well.
But, you should work for me from now on.
I know that you want to use your fists to fight for something meaningful.
Seems like that mouth of yours will be torn soon by the sound of it.
How come you speak in such a scary manner? I'm scared.
Fine.
I'll win for your sake.
If I do, you have to listen to me. Okay?
Sure, Hyeong.
Then even if your trap is ripped open, we're even.
Deal.
Lee Yeon Seok.
If he's left like this, he'll become the best fist in the whole country.
This time,
I won't leave him to live life like that.
You bastard, seriously.
- Sang Man!
- Yes!
- This guy.
- Should I kill him?
- What?
That's what they do in movies.
I almost lost! What are you talking about?
We should get him a job.
- Where?
- Working under you.
Excuse me?
We need a new employee anyway. He can be your bodyguard too.
I'd need a guard to protect me from him first.
He doesn't bite. Don't worry. He'll listen to you.
Educate him well.
But...
Okay, Hyungnim!
H-H-Hey,
get up.
Kim Hui Wu!
♫  Dear, All your things you've done  ♫
♫  We are here to wreck it up  ♫
♫  Who knows, how will it go?  ♫
♫  Hiding in black and white  ♫
♫  We are here to find the truth  ♫
♫  Give up, I warn you so  ♫
♫  Who would ever find  ♫
Again My Life
♫   out who you really are? Hm  ♫
Why did you come so far down here?
Because I just wanted to see the ocean.
I will be sure to personally quarter and skin you.
You... bastard!
It's best if you cut off rotten parts.
Go ahead, apologize.
- It's you.
- We'd like to investigate following your directions.
Isn't it?
Kim Hui Wu? I'll present it directly to the chief prosecutor.
Because you need power to bring justice.
♫  I'll wait for now  ♫
Again My Life