Found her!
This way!
I guess it was just a drill again,
not a real escape.
You're wondering what that is, aren't you?
Going up and down.
You see,
when you look from the outside,
it looks so much fun.
But when you're actually on the ride,
it feels terrible.
I guess that's how life works.
There are consequences for your actions.
Karma, if you will.
FAMILY MATTERS
How dare you take pictures?
What you did to Ji-woo was unforgivable.
So it's only fair
that you experience a nightmare.
Something that you'll remember
for the rest of your life.
SIN
Oh dear, it seems I'm 300g short.
I must have lost my touch.
What, does it hurt?
You think it's unfair?
Something you want to say?
Fuck, it wasn't me!
I didn't make those pictures,
blackmail them, and share them online!
It was Jae-gon!
He did all those things!
The student president!
Holy shit.
Shit.
These are killer shots.
This is bad.
I may be good at slicing things
but I'm not good at patching things up.
Let go, come on.
Here.
Okay.
So you're saying my boy Kyu-tae...
Goddamnit.
He was beat up by this new girl?
Yes, sir.
Oh, they're twins. One of them is a boy.
I knew it.
He didn't get beat up by a girl!
No, it was the girl who beat him up.
Where does she live?
How should I know? It was their first day.
Don't open your mouth like a pig
when you don't have anything to tell me!
Go.
Now?
Go, you bastard!
But there's so much left.
The number you dialed is unavailable--
Where the hell is he,
doing god knows what?
SIN
It wasn't supposed to go down like this.
You froze up, right?
The first time is tough for anyone.
That's normal.
Who the hell is she?
Why, she's your mom.
Grandpa!
I know.
You must be upset and frustrated.
It will all be okay tomorrow.
I'll drop him off by his house
in the morning,
so don't worry so much.
I don't.
- I'll go with you tomorrow.
- No.
Things can get ugly
when there's a man around.
I am worried, though.
I know.
Ji-woo must be in shock.
Ji-woo is one thing
and there's Ji-hoon.
What about Ji-hoon?
It wasn't his first time.
I know.
But today...
he was smiling the whole time.
He was smiling?
KUMSU CITY INFORMATION CENTER
CONTROL ROOM
Hold it there.
What? What is it?
Look.
When this SUV passed,
there were no other cars around.
And stop here.
On the next screen here,
this vehicle pops out of nowhere, see?
Come on. What about it?
There must have been a backroad
in between the roads.
No, there isn't any road
a vehicle can enter.
What?
But there is an entrance
leading to the Kumsuak Mountain trails
between these shots.
PAWFECT HAVEN ANIMAL HOSPITAL
So, have you looked around?
The arcade, internet cafe,
bowling alley...
We've searched every hangout
but couldn't find him.
Where is this jackass,
doing god knows what?
Excuse me, coming through.
Hey!
Kyu-tae, you dumbass,
what happened to you?
- Dad!
- What is it?
Are you hurt?
Why are you in a wheelchair?
Well, someone...
What are you doing?
SIN
They butchered my leg!
Your leg?
What about your leg?
Can't you see?
Look here.
It was sliced out
and then patched back up.
Where, here?
Where? You mean here?
Jeez, what have you been doing,
you bastard?
Okay, put those pants back up.
Why would you pull them down?
Dad! This fucking hurts like hell!
What the hell happened? Damn it.
What is this?
It's okay, it's like supplements.
You seemed restless.
It will help you sleep tight.
It wasn't me!
I didn't make those pictures,
blackmail them, and share them online!
Jae-gon did all those things!
The student president!
So you're saying,
my son got beat up by your kids, no,
they got into a fight.
And you called him over
so that the kids made up
and he slept over at your place?
Yes.
Then what the hell's wrong with him?
I'm sorry.
Seeing him like this, it made me lose it.
It's okay.
I would've reacted the same way.
But are you really their mom?
You look young for your age.
No, I am actually young.
I see.
After meeting Kyu-tae,
I figured
Kyu-tae must cause you lots of trouble.
Well, boys will be boys
and get into a fight every now and then.
No, actually Kyu-tae is...
quite a...
lame.
"Lame"?
He's the school bully.
He acts all tough
but you never know what he's feeling.
He must be having nightmares.
In his sleep...
he even wet the bed.
Tenth graders are
usually too old for that.
He wet the bed?
I felt so bad for him,
so I gave him supplements
and let him sleep.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have.
But he was so restless.
Are you a doctor?
- A vet.
- A vet?
Well, I only deal with animals and beasts.
Anyway, after a good night's sleep,
he suddenly claims
he has this scar on his leg.
There is this thing called
"attachment disorder."
When you're neglected and unloved
by your mother as an infant...
Are you saying that my boy has a disorder?
I'm not saying that.
I'm not a doctor,
and Kyu-tae is not an animal.
So you mean,
what Mom's doing is...
some sort of hypnotizing?
"Hypnotizing"? More like torturing.
You're both right, and both wrong.
They may seem similar,
yet completely different.
It's called "a brain hacking."
It's a highly-advanced
interrogation technique, you know?
You completely dominate
a person's brain, spirit, and mind.
And even take over
the person's memory completely.
It's hard-core stuff!
So that bastard doesn't remember anything
that happened yesterday?
Depends on what Mom wants.
Fabrication, distortion, even erasing.
Anything's possible.
She can erase his memory completely
or make it last forever.
Wow.
Seriously?
How is that even possible?
Come on.
You remember vividly
what you saw yesterday, don't you?
If not for this video,
you would have lived with that memory!
Well...
What a relief, right?
Yeah.
What?
What do you mean, "a relief"?
It doesn't matter how you do it!
How did she do it?
We'll unravel this one at a time.
If we tell you everything at once,
you won't believe it or understand it.
Come on, Grandpa!
You're home. How did it go?
- Fine.
- Okay.
It went well.
Did you show the kids the video?
Yes.
You'll be late.
You should go to school.
We'll talk about it later.
See you.
Good job.
Off you go.
What are you going to do?
Isn't it obvious?
We get this guy Jae-gon and deal with him.
No, I mean that woman.
Come on, she's our mom, not "that woman."
She's not even our real fucking mom.
Hey, she raised us.
That makes her our mom.
Giving birth isn't everything.
Damn it.
Seriously though,
did you already know about it?
Yeah.
I remember seeing it when I was little.
Help!
Help me, please!
- Help me!
- You bitch!
Where do you think you're going?
You bitch!
- Help!
- You want to die?
Come here!
Honey...
I didn't know it wasn't real,
and that it was some sort of hacking.
Whatever it is, I can't be like you
and act like it's nothing.
Dude, what is your problem?
Why are you always so mean to mom?
She pisses me off, that's why!
What kind of a messed up family
keeps us from having a yearbook,
let alone a family photo?
Photographs are overrated.
The way I see it,
you're just looking for reasons
to hate Mom.
"Reasons"?
You saw her face was blank
like a corpse, doing all that crazy shit.
Whenever I see that face...
This is why I'm always angry.
Anyway, you're on your own
with your problems.
And I'll...
deal with my own problems.
JENITH HOTEL
CONVENIENCE STORE, MOTEL
Hello, everyone.
It's our grand opening
and you're all invited!
Shinara Night Club.
GRAND RE-OPENING SALE
Come on inside!
We're giving out flyers over there.
Get your gifts and come on in!
"Hard liquor"?
SHINARA NIGHT CLUB
Excuse me, Pastor.
Listen...
You don't think Sister Lee's disappearance
is related to those cases
making the city consider canceling
development plans.
Pardon? What do you mean?
You know, the Doom-veloper.
That psycho serial killer.
I wonder if she...
You know, I was just scared for her.
Oh, I'm...
I'm sorry, Pastor.
- Deacon Joe.
- Yes.
You must be busy
with your worldly business affairs.
Well, something came up
with my son yesterday--
What about Kyu-tae?
I mean, did something happen to your son?
He's not feeling so well.
So he's resting at home.
Both your son and Sister Lee Yu-jin
are children of Christ and our family.
- Amen.
- I know you feel the same way
so pray for her a lot.
Amen. Yes, I should pray.
I'll pray, Pastor.
Where are you going?
The Pastor's dog is sick
and it's in the animal hospital.
"Animal hospital"?
- The new one in town?
- Yeah.
GRAND OPENING
FREE CHECK-UP
Hey, come on in, Pastor.
You're also here, Chief Oh.
It's the first time I see the missus.
You look too young to be a mother!
Nice to meet you. I'm Oh Gil-ja,
the Deaconess of Aspirations Church.
Okay.
My hands are filthy.
My hands are not so clean themselves.
I understand, I've had lots of dogs.
You're a shy one, aren't you?
Just like a cat.
I can fix you right away.
Well, how is Simbok?
He's a lot better now,
but feeling a bit low today--
- Hey, he must be here!
- Chief Oh, not that way!
- Here!
- You can't go in there!
Come on, here.
Looks much better than before.
I'm talking about Simbok.
Still, he should stay here a few more days
until he fully recovers.
His wounds run pretty deep.
"His wounds"?
You mean he's wounded, not sick?
He has many wounds.
You didn't know?
So this must be the cage.
Yes.
God, this is all rusty!
It's so unsanitary!
- Why would you cover it?
- Don't.
- No, it's not like that.
- Then what is it?
No, that's...
Yes, I mean...
Yeah.
Last night, Kyu-tae went to that house
and came out all messed up.
Hold on.
Are you mistreating them or something?
What did you say?
I've raised them myself, I'd know!
Did you lock up the innocent ones
- Come on.
- and abuse them?
It's a hospital for the animals.
We'd never do that!
Then let me see! Let me see in there!
- No, no, please.
- Let me see!
What is this?
It's empty.
It is.
It is empty.
But why?
Oh.
Pastor, my gosh.
Oh, dear.
Anyway, I'm relieved
to see Simbok feeling better.
I trust he's in good hands,
until he is healed.
PAWFECT HAVEN ANIMAL HOSPITAL
"Pawfect Haven"?
Pawfect, Haven...
It's more like hazard.
Oh, right.
Didn't you say you have twins?
What are the kids like?
"The kids"? Oh, you mean our kids?
I guess they're just typical kids.
Right.
They must be trouble.
Send them to our church study club.
I'll turn them into model students.
No kid is born compliant!
- They need discipline--
- Excuse me?
My kids,
they were born good.
Okay, sure.
Well then.
But being good is not enough.
They should contribute to the household.
Whoa, my heart almost dropped.
So did you take care of him
and let him out last night?
No, I didn't.
You didn't?
Then what? Did he run away?
Yeong-su, should we pack up?
He'll call the police.
If he wanted to, he would have already.
And the police would be here.
He didn't run away, he was let out.
"Let out"? By whom?
Who else?
It's either Ji-hoon or Ji-woo.
I can't get a hold of Kyu-tae.
What happened to Fuc Kyu-tae?
Is he okay?
After everything he's done to you,
you worry about that jerk, not me?
Do you like him?
Sorry!
Sorry, that was a reflex.
Fine.
Let's be a couple.
- Starting today.
- What?
Start what?
Since you like me,
I'll try to like you too.
You're nuts.
I thought you were a loser
but you're a psycho.
Look.
It's impossible to delete all the pictures
but I hid them.
I planted a malware in there.
If anyone finds it...
- It will blow up their accounts.
- Really?
You're not a psycho, you're a genius!
As for Kyu-tae, my mom took care of him.
No, she treated him, so don't worry.
"Treated"?
My mom's a vet. We run an animal hospital.
You said he was an animal.
Wow, I see now why you liked this school.
What is this? New love blossoming?
Hey, Ji-woo. I'm Min-jung, Kwon Min-jung.
Hope we can be friends.
Whatever.
What?
- You want your legs broken this time?
- No, not that.
The president wants to see you.
Baek Ji-woo!
- I heard you topped Kyu-tae.
- "Topped"?
That's lame.
Are you a gangster wannabe?
I was getting annoyed with him.
He was stepping over the line.
So thank you for taking care of him.
Take this.
It's a reward for your hard work.
I opened up an account under your name
in the cryptocurrency exchange.
Run a tight ship around here,
you'll get a fixed income
every month, like clockwork.
So you're saying,
you're the real boss who owns the school.
And I'm just a paid worker?
Nah.
You'd be the official top dog
of the school.
I'm just someone
who handles the operations here.
A manager, if you will.
Whatever.
Your family must be well-connected.
Not well-connected.
Just on another level.
What?
- You don't want this?
- Come on!
Who would say "no" to money?
Just do it.
It'll be nice to make some cash.
Don't mess up.
I thought he was just a jackass
but he's a class-A jackass.
It's for the better.
I was worried
he might be some small-time punk.
Now what?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll get rid of him.
And take complete control
over this school.
Dude.
Drop the psychopath act.
That's so fucking lame.
What do you mean, "act"?
KUMSUAK MOUNTAIN TRAILS
I'm at Kumsu-ro.
What about the vehicle search?
No need. We picked up the suspect
from the security cameras.
Lee Dong-min.
KUMSU-RO TRAIL SECURITY CAMERA
It's you, right?
Hey!
Dong-min, your shoelaces are loose.
Let's tie them up first.
So tell me, buddy.
Do you know how to drive?
You own a vehicle?
"A vehicle"?
No.
I failed. The driving test.
Ah, I see.
Then tell me, did you follow this girl
up in the mountain?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Phone.
You... your phone.
Your phone!
I tried to pick up her phone for her.
I've been waiting for you, Yu-jin.
Huh?
Let's go. I'll walk you to your house.
Wait.
What did you say her boyfriend called her?
SERIAL KILLER IN DEVELOPMENT ZONES
KILLS A FIFTH VICTIM
KUMSU CITY
JULY 15TH, DEAD, ON HER BED AT HOME
HAN SU-JIN, AUG 11TH, 2021
GACHEON CITY, APARTMENT STAIRS
I've been waiting for you, Yu-jin.
Thank you.
But how did you guess my name correctly?
What a coincidence.
There's no such thing as coincidence.
Excuse me?
Those fucking bastards.
PAWFECT HAVEN ANIMAL HOSPITAL
It was you, right?
What are you talking about?
Whatever it was, it's not me.
Then was it you, Ji-hoon?
Did you let him out?
Let who out?
Then it must be you, Ji-woo.
Who else can it be?
Don't accuse me out of the blue!
Enough!
Look at you guys.
The lack of communication is serious.
And we call ourselves a family?
Okay, starting now...
You each get to ask only one question.
First, Ji-woo.
What are you?
Where did you learn such horrible skills?
And why would you do this?
Grandpa said
you each get to ask one question.
So choose between "Where" and "Why."
Huh?
"Why"?
To keep you safe.
What? Give me a break.
- I never asked you to do that!
- Okay.
Next up, Ji-hoon.
Can I learn how to do that?
No, only your mom can do it.
Next, Chul-hee.
Ji-woo, you really didn't let that man go?
Let who go? What are you talking about?
Wait, he got away?
So it's not Ji-woo!
Next, Yeong-su.
Huh? Well...
- Um...
- Was that a question?
No, I'll just let Ji-woo have my question.
Really?
Okay, Ji-woo. Ask another one.
What exactly are you?
ONE MIND
I was maybe five or six?
I'm not exactly sure, but...
ever since I was little,
I was taken away to Special Trainings
where I had special trainings.
"Trainings"?
You mean you were soldiers?
At the beginning,
we started off as soldiers.
But as time passed...
we were passed around
intelligence agencies, from KCIA to ANSP.
And even that stopped
when Kim Il-sung and Kim Jong-il died...
Spies, Fixers, Technicians,
we were called many things,
but never had an official name.
"A Fixer"? What did you fix?
We got answers
from people we need answers.
And we caused pain...
to those who deserve it.
But your mom,
she was determined
not to let you kids have the life she had.
So when she was just about your age,
she carried you on her back and escaped.
Risking her own life.
Us?
For whatever reason,
unlike us,
you were put in that place as infants.
Young-hee!
Young-hee, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's get you up.
Young-hee.
I think something went wrong
with my father.
You go ahead.
Chul-su!
Don't go.
I promised you.
I'll keep you safe from harm's way,
until the end.
I will...
No, Mommy will go get Daddy.
Wait here just for a moment.
Don't worry.
I'll keep you safe from harm's way,
until the end.
I promise you.
Because I'm your mom.
So you're saying
we all escaped from that place
and now we're on the run?
We couldn't use smartphones, social media,
and couldn't even take pictures,
because we were on the lam?
Because they might catch us?
- But that's--
- Yes, you're right.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
You're "sorry"?
They should be thanking you.
Okay, now it's my turn.
What is important for this family now
is the present, not the past.
That guy.
Whether he escaped, or was let out,
every member of this family
should band together
and put our heads together.
We should be of one mind and fix this.
Hello?
- It's me.
- Who is this?
Damn it, it's me.
"Me," who?
The one who you beat up,
dragged and caged like a dog.
Don't tell me,
you forgot my voice already?
How can I?
Tell me though, how did you get out?
Do you really think that matters?
What really matters is,
that I saw everything your wife did.
What are you talking about?
And you think I just saw it?
I put everything on video, as evidence.
You put it on video?
Then you'll see.
What is this?
What? It can't be.
- What?
- What else?
- You call it as you see it.
- Shut up!
I filmed how you locked me up in there!
Anyway, wait until I pay you back
for what you did.
First, check out my gift for you.
And call me at this number.
What is this?
You were right about your feeling.
Thank god he was more than a jerk
who's all talk.
"Thank god"?
Yeong-su, how can you say that
in a situation like this?
Now do you know who I am?
SEVENTH, SHIN JI-EUN
DEC 7TH, 2021
Shaking in your boots?
No.
- So who are you again?
- What?
You still don't get it?
Do you know how many fan clubs
and followers I have?
SERIAL KILLER KILLS NINE VICTIMS SO FAR
"The serial killer
who killed nine victims so far."
No, make it ten now.
A.k.a. the Doom-veloper.
That's me.
You're saying you're the Doom-veloper?
No way, you can't be him.
Hello?
"No way"?
What's with that random reaction?
I mean, this is his style alright.
But neither the body
nor that bastard
had a marker on them.
Whatever he is,
he won't be able to call the police.
So that's a relief.
I guess you're right.
But, what do we do with her?
We can't just hide things from the kids
from now on.
Like Father said,
we should band as a family
and put our heads together.
What are we even waiting for?
We should call the cops right now!
And then what? Tell them we locked him up?
So why did you lock up an innocent...
Wait, he was fucking guilty.
Baek Ji-woo! Language!
What should we do?
We can't just leave
a dead person out there.
Grandpa.
We're cleaning
traces of the murderer as well.
What can I say?
Forget about that guy.
Focus on the poor victim and us.
Go now.
Oh, no.
- The car won't start?
- No.
Darn it.
Should we call the tow truck, then?
What, and let the whole neighborhood know?
Forget it, we should all push this car.
Push this car?
All of us?
No, not the kids.
Why not? We're part of this family.
We should all come together.
That's right.
We're not doing anything wrong.
Don't worry, I got every location
of the security cameras covered.
I hid an ace in the hole
for an emergency like this.
Get to your positions!
Yes, sir!
Come on, why does it have to rain now?
I'm soaking wet in a dog costume.
All thanks to you, Father!
I told you,
we should have called the police!
You know what they say,
no good deed goes unpunished.
This costume isn't waterproof.
Wait!
What now?
Open the trunk.
The trunk? Why?
Jeez.
Her life was tragically cut short.
She should feel a little more comfortable
before she leaves this world.
KUMSU PRECINCT
What is this?
SHE IS A POOR VICTIM OF MURDER
PLEASE RETURN HER TO HER FAMILY
Twenty-six-year-old Ms. Lee
has gone missing
from Kumsuak Mountain Trails
since the 15th,
and her body was found today.
People saw
the poor victim's family in sorrow,
and found consolation in the fact
at least her body is found.
But at the same time felt outraged
at the perpetrators' deviant behavior,
taking the body to the police station
in funny costumes, putting on a show.
Those people are idiots.
Not the sharpest tool in the shed!
What kind of a crazy person
would kill someone
and take her body to the police station?
If you finished breakfast, get going.
See you later.
You see?
See how nice it is
when the family comes together.
Alright.
Nothing's going to happen.
Why?
I thought you wanted something to happen.
Huh?
What do you mean?
Ji-hoon didn't let the guy go, you did.
You half-witted fool.
Why would you be so clumsy?
Leave before sunrise.
Subtitle translation by Jody Park