Characters, actions, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Uncle Jim.
I’ve cleaned all my mess.
Do you still not trust me?
And you're about to graduate from high school.
Maybe we can be together again.
I never said I wanted to go back there with you.
So what exactly is your relationship to him?
What is your relationship to Wen? That’s what we are as well.
Li Ming.
- Mrs. Hong!
- Mom. Mom!
She’s gone.
If it hadn’t been for you, we would not have broken up like this.
But I wasn’t there back then.
[It's okay, Sis. I'm going to try it my way.]
Here you go.
Wow! Looks yummy.
You’re lucky that you get to eat
before the diner is closed down.
Have you thought it through about the diner?
Why did you return the title deed?
Li Ming should be able to decide what to do with his life.
If he doesn’t want to go back, let him.
Jam,
we shouldn’t become the kind of adults we hate.
About the diner, I can manage to survive.
So can Li Ming.
Honestly,
I can’t help worrying about him.
About what?
Well.
Him being gay.
Jam,
you accept your brother but can’t do the same with your son?
What is this? I don’t get it.
Hey, I’m okay with that.
I’m just worried about him as a mother.
He’s young.
Will people disdain him when he becomes an adult?
Who will take care of him when he’s old?
There’s no guarantee either that straight couples can always make it.
Look at you.
Yeah.
You’re right.
Li Ming might even have a better love than we do.
Whatever mistake he’s making,
he has me to give advice.
Don’t you worry.
I guess he was right to choose to live with you over with me.
No, Jam.
We’re just learning together.
Keep eating.
Right.
I’ll finish it all.
Chapter 8: The Self-made House and Home
I said I’d come.
I’m not that mad at Mom.
Come on.
Let’s make it her day today.
I’ll pick you up later.
Wait. Why?
So you can spend time with your mom.
We live together every day.
I’m sick of seeing your face.
Oh, yeah?
Let’s go.
Hi.
Are you guys hungry?
Not at all, Jam.
You guys go ahead.
I got something to do around here.
What?
I’ll call you later.
Let’s go then.
Are you hungry?
Come on.
What do you want to eat?
You’re standing here looking so handsome.
Have you got yourself a lover?
I haven’t.
It’s this room.
Please take a look inside.
Sure.
Please take your time.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
How’s it, Uncle Jim?
Nice location.
I thought it’d be further.
10 minutes from the mall.
When I’m tired, I’ll crash here.
When I miss you,
I’ll sleep at your place.
Why would you want to hurt your back?
Sleeping here seems a lot more comfortable.
Comfortable but not with you.
I’d rather choose the back pain.
Uncle Jim,
I think I’ll keep this loose furniture.
If I get bored with them, I can easily replace them.
What color do you think I should paint the walls?
Black or blue?
Green.
Green?
Interesting.
If green walls, then I think I should change the couch.
Good idea?
I think a leather couch will fit better. What do you think?
That’s your call.
This is your home.
Uncle Jim,
it’s my first home.
I want you to be part of it.
I changed my mind.
I’m gonna call it
our home.
You want this pair?
No.
Who would wear these?
Why? I think they’re pretty.
You can wear them to school or when you’re on trips.
You can play football in these too.
No, I can’t.
Football boots and leisure shoes can’t be the same pair.
Two different purposes.
I can’t wear the same pair for both.
Here.
Since I get to buy you stuff once in a blue moon.
They’re expensive. Why did you buy them?
We could’ve got them for a cheaper price online.
And these are the socks.
I think they’re cute.
You like them?
I do.
That’s all it takes.
Did you use your credit card to buy these?
Yeah.
Tong got me the card.
Uncle Tong,
do you really love him?
Of course.
Otherwise, why would I marry him?
And…
You get married many times. Aren’t you afraid people will talk?
If they want to gossip, they still do whether I get married or not.
You’re the only one I care about.
Whatever makes you happy,
do it, Mom.
Come on. Why are you crying?
Keep it.
I just want you to have it.
Here.
For you.
Pour water of dedication and get blessed.
Your mom isn’t around anymore.
Do you want to continue the chicken stall, Gaipa?
When I was young, I hated working at the chicken stall.
I thought I wouldn’t sell chicken meat when I grew up.
I would do something else.
Do you want to close it down?
Right now,
you have your own life.
I will continue the stall.
Do you think it’s wrong?
I have a bachelor’s degree.
But in the end, I’m still a chicken meat vendor.
Hey.
I don’t think it’s wrong.
Don’t be dramatic.
I myself want to run a Chicken Rice diner.
I’m serious.
You’re right.
Uncle Jim, let’s go.
I’ll bring the car here so that you don’t have to walk a long way.
I’ll catch up with you.
I’m sorry about Mrs. Hong.
Yes.
Thank you so much for helping out at the funeral every day.
Damn it.
There’re many spots available. Why here?
Stop complaining.
I’m gonna find out whose car it is.
Do you know whose car it is?
No, I don’t.
The Moonlight Chicken diner will open for the last time tonight.
Do you want to join the farewell party?
I think I’m good.
Have fun at the party.
Come down here. It’s hot.
Let’s go.
Okay.
Anyone want my special recipe Chicken Rice?
You mean your haphazard recipe?
Haphazard, my ass.
Let me help.
Here.
My recipe is to mix the sauce with the rice.
Keep mixing it. The more sauce we add, the more mouthwatering it gets.
That looks just like monk’s food.
Why don’t you pour the soup on it too?
Damn you, Li.
So?
Good, isn’t it?
I told you, Leng.
You always brag about this recipe.
But no one likes it.
Do you want
to try
chopping the chicken?
Why don’t you try my recipe first?
I told you it’s haphazard.
Yes, right there.
Now let’s count it down.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey.
These pictures,
which box should I put them in?
Leave them here, Jeab.
We don’t need to take them.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I don’t know where to keep them anyway.
Up to you then.
So what time are you going to the doctor to take the cast off?
During this initial phase, please do not take heavy steps.
But you’ll get used to it in no time.
Sure.
Thank you.
Of course.
I’ll take it from here.
Would you please excuse me then?
Sure.
Thank you.
Here. Let me help.
Wen.
Hm?
You don’t have to help me anymore.
I can walk myself now.
Hey, but I think…
I can really walk on my own.
Trust me.
Bye now.
This is it, ma’am.
It’s a university like what we have in our country.
But particularly for deaf people.
That’s great.
There’s the Faculty of Engineering that Heart wants to join too.
Oh, yeah?
If we don’t try, we’ll never know.
I’ll talk to my husband later.
If you need more information on this, I’ll be happy to help.
Stay for dinner.
You can help me explain this to him.
Ah, sure.
Don’t be home so late.
[Li Ming’s and Heart’s offerings.]
Hey.
I used to work as a lion dancer.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
Long time no see.
Can I borrow this for a second?
Of course.
You haven’t been around that much lately.
My uncle’s making me work my ass off.
Come visit sometimes.
Of course.
All right. Should we do this?
Let’s try it. See if you can still do it.
Okay.
[Have you had a boyfriend before?]
[Never. You?]
[No.]
[What do you think having a boyfriend is like?]
[Like this, perhaps.]
Hey.
Read my lips.
Boyfriend.
Here.
This cup is surely yours.
I bought it for you.
Are you tired, Uncle Jim?
I am.
But I’m used to it.
It used to be more tiring back in old days and I got through it.
When I have a job, I’ll pay you back every baht I spent.
What, Uncle Jim?
When did you know yourself?
What kind of question?
I don't know.
But I didn’t copy you for sure.
I’m glad you realize what you like.
And please know that you do nothing wrong.
From now on, your life might not be easy.
Don’t worry about me.
Love isn’t that big of a deal.
Earning money for a living is much more important.
But if you’d chosen to stay with some other relatives,
your life might have been better.
No.
Staying with you
is the best.
Thank you, Uncle Jim,
for everything.
Thank you too.
For what?
For teaching me to be more mature even though you’re still a kid.
I’m out of here.
I love you, Uncle.
These are the hands that have made Chicken Rice for almost 10 years.
I sometimes feel envious of Li Ming
for knowing what his dream is.
Don't you want to sell Chicken Rice anymore?
Li Ming asked me if it was really my dream.
Come to think of it.
I don’t even know the answer.
I have no idea if I do what I do because I love it
or I just don’t know how to do anything else.
You can think now.
What do you want to do?
Without knowing it,
life tells you there’s too late to dream.
We’re free to dream anytime, Uncle Jim.
Without money,
dreams can be tough.
I have an amount of money.
Whatever you want to do, just let me know.
If it’s interesting, I can be your investor.
I actually
have a fund.
Are you serious?
It’s been with you forever, hasn’t it?
It’s been with me for so long.
That’s why I want to sell it.
Can you help take a picture of me and the truck?
Sit down, please.
Smile handsomely.
One, two, three.
Come on, Uncle Jim.
Let’s take some pictures.
With me or the car?
Both–duh!
One, two.
The Marina Food Court project is 80% complete.
Next week, you can inform the tenants to decorate their shops.
[ TWO MONTHS LATER ]
I’ll give you two thumbs up.
You never disappoint me.
It was two weeks behind the schedule yet you managed to put it back on track.
Thanks to the foremen.
Give them a big bonus, please.
I felt so bad for pushing them so much.
All right. You got it.
And what about the Marina project in Rayong province?
If we don’t postpone it, the timeline will be really tight.
Well, Boss says we can so we can.
I have no idea how he did it.
He got the license so quickly.
Hey, Wen.
For this project, you're coming with me.
You’ll get at least 30% of your salary for extra.
Me?
In Rayong?
Yes.
No one is in charge of this project.
You can do it. Trust me.
Hey, Wen just got a loan to buy his new condo.
Are you moving him now?
Right.
I have a solution.
What?
I go instead.
I have a solution too.
You stay at Wen’s condo.
Come on.
Here.
Read your promotion letter.
Let me know later what you think.
Is there another one?
You, shut it.
There’s just one.
[Job Promotion Letter]
[You have been promoted from Art Director to Project Manager.]
It’s okay.
We still got time.
It’s all right.
Don’t worry.
I will be
the subtitle
for you.
You have to sign here as well.
All right.
This.
You can use it.
Okay.
Right here?
Yes, sir.
Right here, too.
Okay.
Okay, then.
All right.
I think we’re all set here, Mr. Gaipa.
Sure
I’m sorry the headquarter asked for more documents.
That’s totally fine.
Please take it from here, Mr. Alan.
Of course.
How refreshing.
Right.
May you please excuse me now?
Mr. Gaipa.
Yes.
I just changed my phone number.
Can I please have your chat ID?
Yes?
In case the headquarter asks for more documents.
You can just take a photo and send it to me.
Ah, of course.
QR code.
Yes.
Let me scan it.
We got it.
Okay then.
If we’re done here, I’ll be on my way.
Sure. Have a great day.
Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
- No problem. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Sorry.
I have your pen.
Right.
What’s your order number?
A115.
Here you go. Thank you so much.
Uncle Jim.
Hey.
Tired?
I’m okay.
Sir, what’s your order number?
A116.
A116?
It’s right there.
Here you go. Thank you.
Lots of customers today?
Quite a lot.
Yeah?
Your order is ready.
Chicken breast, no skin.
May I get one Chicken Rice with extra bazooka skin, please?
- Leng.
- Wow.
Customer, why don’t you go buy Fried Chicken Skin instead of Chicken Rice?
Oh, please.
Why wasn’t your diner looking this cool back then?
None of your biz.
Very nice mouth.
Want some water?
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Wen.
Wow.
You seem like a pro now.
Uncle Jim,
do you still get any customers who pass out drunk here?
Yeah?
And then you guys hook up.
- Damn you!
- Do you?
You look more masculine.
Of course.
I’m a waterpark staff.
I carry swim rings and chase after kids all day.
It’d be weird if I didn’t gain any muscles.
Here. Can you see it?
Be careful it might hurt your eyes.
Here.
I got the Best Employee award last month so I got the star.
Are you sure you didn’t get it yourself?
Call me workplace and ask.
They gave me this from the customers’ votes.
Leng, I was joking.
How’s your son Jason?
I asked Praew to quit her job to take care of him.
We will take him to a nursery when he’s a little older.
Uncle Jim, can I have that apron?
Why?
I want free food.
Oh, come on, Leng.
Take it off, Uncle Jim.
Are you serious?
I am.
All right then.
Here.
Sit down.
Are you giving me an order?
Yes.
I’m the one with the biggest apron.
Wow! It fits perfectly.
Hey, what is this, Uncle Jim?
What, Leng?
How’s this?
Do you like it?
Give me your hand.
Hand, please.
I saved up to buy you back this gold necklace.
Here.
Next month, I’m taking Praew back to her hometown to get the marriage blessings.
Thank you for trusting me.
Wow, Leng.
I didn’t see you for a while and you’ve become a lot more mature.
It’s not much. They just made it look big. Don’t praise me.
One Fried Chicken with Rice for takeaway, please?
Oh, come on.
Don’t you see me here?
You two stay.
One moment, please.
You guys stay here. I’ll take care of that.
I love this truck, Uncle Jim.
I’ve worked here for so long but haven’t got a gold necklace yet.
Yes, sir.
You want gold.
Yeah.
I have one for you.
For real?
Here.
One baht.
Can I get one more baht? I want some candies.
You’re such a greedy man.
Just take it back.
Jam.
Jim!
You came so late. Why didn’t you call so I could go pick you up?
Jam, there’s no problem at all.
Don’t act like I’ve never been here.
Tong.
Yes?
Hello.
Good evening.
You guys must be tired.
Come on in and have some food.
Come on.
Please.
Jam.
Tong.
This is Wen,
my boyfriend.
Hello.
I finally get to meet my brother-in-law in person.
Oh. I’m just his boyfriend.
Thank you.
Mom, this is Heart.
Heart,
she is my Mom.
And he’s her boyfriend.
Hi.
Heart.
His name is Heart.
Gam, have you greeted your guests?
What did I teach you to do?
Good evening.
Good girl.
You don’t seem vibrant as when you make your TikTok videos.
She isn’t used to you guys yet.
She’s shy.
Let’s eat.
Everyone, please get started.
Eat before the food gets cold.
You want sticky rice? Here.
Looks yummy.
Wen, can you eat this?
I can.
Get that for your boyfriend, Jim.
Your friend,
is he in school?
He finished non-formal education.
High school equivalent.
He’s joining a university for deaf students in America.
Hey. He’s great.
I think
I'm going with him.
To America?
Yes.
To study and work.
And to…
keep him company.
And how much money do you need for that?
About a hundred thousand baht.
I’ve saved up some already.
Uncle Jim sold his car and lent me thirty thousand.
I’m also planning to work in the water park with Saleng.
It pays really well, Mom.
Oh. In America, people tip generously for your service.
It’s around 1-2 thousand baht per time.
If I work and save up, I can get a hundred thousand back in no time.
Heart and I are going together.
I won’t be lonely, Mom.
It’s great.
Heart.
Is he your boyfriend?
Why?
Is it troubling you?
Him being deaf?
Yes.
Honestly, Mom.
I have no problem at all with him being deaf.
He understands everything just like everyone else.
Did you learn sign language?
You seem good at it.
I just started.
I still make mistakes when I use it.
We mostly talk through written messages.
Nothing is too difficult, Mom.
I love it when I’m with him.
Mommy.
Yes, dear.
What is it?
Heart peeled an orange for me.
How nice of him.
Thank you.
Wait.
In sign language,
how do you say thank you?
When you want to say ‘thank you,’ you do this.
This and this.
Right.
Mom said thank you.
He thanks you too.
Ah!
It’s late. You should go to bed.
Let’s go to bed, honey.
Yeah?
Not as cute as you.
You can
say your name
so clearly now.
Your voice
is very
nice.
I want to
hear it
more often.
What’s that?
Li Ming.
Did you just say my name?
My name?
Yes?
Can you say it again?
One more time.
Li Ming.
That’s cute.
Cute.
You finally have a permanent home.
Um.
I hope I don’t have to move again.
Thanks a lot.
I couldn’t have raised Li Ming all alone.
I learned maturity from him too, Jam.
Here.
Take care of his tuition.
Jam.
Use it as collateral. I’ll pay the installments.
No, Jam.
Tong can get you wrong.
I already talked to him.
Let me perform a mom’s duty for once.
To pay him back for all those times he’d been neglected.
All right then.
I’ll take care of it for you.
Uncle Jim.
Uncle Tong asked if you wanted to join us for a beer.
Wanna come?
Don’t complain if all the beer was out.
Come on, Wen!
I think he’s drunk.
Wen finishes two cans already.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Yes, I’m joining you. Quickly.
If I get…
graduate certificate,
I will send you.
Okay.
When approximately will it be?
Next month.
Okay. Perfect.
If the application gets any progress,
I’ll inform you as soon as possible. Right?
And please feel free to ask me about anything anytime.
Okay?
Can you please, too, sign the application?
Sign the paper.
My signature, right?
Okay. Let me go make a copy.
Thank you, Uncle Jim.
Thank your mom.
Thank you both.
Li Ming, I think you should call her.
Okay.
Sign?
Yes, you need to sign it too.
I will pay you back every baht you paid.
Don’t worry about it.
Here’s your change.
Thank you.
Alan.
What’s up?
Are you here to eat?
I’m here to meet a client for his documents.
I’m sorry.
I don’t have time to drop by the bank.
It’s fine.
I was just running errands in this area.
Ah, cool.
Do you guys know each other?
This is Wen,
my friend.
Uncle Jim.
Would you like to join us for dinner?
Please join us.
We can go over the documents.
Well, then.
Can I have Chicken Rice with no blood cube, please?
Of course.
Thank you.
Please.
Sure.
Have you got all the documents needed?
I think so.
Can you please…
Sure. May I?
Recheck for me.
May I?
A banker, I see.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Will you get a free credit card if you date him?
Date, my ass, Leng!!
Don’t. You’re blushing.
He’s here for my documents.
You’re always furious when you blush.
Leng, come back here.
Don’t poke your nose in their business. Come here.
Goodbye, sir.
Sorry about him.
That’s okay.
Leng, hello.
Wen, hello.
Uncle Jim.
Two Chicken Rices, no offal.
Okay.
You got it, Li Ming.
Hello, sir.
Hello
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ No matter where you are ♪
♪ Feeling blissful ♪
Right here and here.
♪ Or in tears and sorrow ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ No matter if love will come ♪
♪ Within your reach ♪
Thank you.
♪ Or at a far distance ♪
♪ There will be tomorrow for you to find ♪
Thank you, Wen.
♪ And dry your teary eyes ♪
♪ There’s tomorrow ♪
(Eat up. it’s so good.)
♪ For you to seize and treasure ♪
♪ There will be tomorrow for you to love ♪
I chose to sell Chicken Rice because it’s a simple dish
consisted of four components;
rice, chicken, broth, and sauce.
It might have only four units
yet everyone's definition of 'delicious' differs.
Some love to eat chicken skin.
Some love chicken thighs.
Some don’t eat it with the sauce at all.
Some love the hot broth.
That’s what makes this simple dish stand out.
♪ There’s tomorrow ♪
♪ For you to seize and treasure ♪
I see people eat Chicken Rice every day.
And they enjoy their Chicken Rice in their own way.
♪ There’s tomorrow for us to start over ♪
♪ If you ♪
♪ Just wait ♪
Directed by Noppharnach Chaiyahwimhon
See?
I told you it’s the player.
The DVDs work fine.
I believe now that you don’t give up easily.
Isn’t it good?
If I give up easily, will we have us today?
Come on.
Let’s watch your favorite movie.
Uncle Jim.
You said the male lead got together with his fiancée.
I did.
I said he got married to his fiancée.
I didn’t say he didn’t end up with the female lead.
If I told you the ending, it wouldn’t be fun.
You’re being a smartass, huh?
Do you get it now why I love this movie?
The right love consists of the right person…
and the right time.
At midnight.
At a Chicken Rice diner.
Uncle Jim,
can I sleep on your lap?
Uncle Jim.
You’ve become more romantic.
Isn’t it good?
Hm?
Aren’t you tired of eating chicken every day?
No.
Are you?
What are you referring to?
The chicken or the uncle?
If you mean the chicken, I must admit I’m tired of it sometimes.
The uncle, however,
I’m never tired of him.
You might get tired of him in the future.
Don’t think so.
I’ll never get tired of the uncle.
I’m tired of going out to theme parks.
Maybe I’m already old.
I just want to stay home.
Wen - Moonlight Chicken - Temp staff.
When will I get to be a permanent staff?
You just want to be my employee?
What else can I be?
Boyfriend.
The seller’s boyfriend.
What did you say?
It wasn’t very clear.
Clear enough now?
[Job Promotion Declined]
[Reason: I just built a home. I don’t want to move anywhere.]