Characters, actions, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Stop pushing the burden towards me.
Do you know this guy?
Does he show any sign at all though?
No. Mom, why is it so hard to hit on an old man?
Don’t you like me?
Is running a Chicken Rice diner really your dream?
Are you truly happy?
Look at me. I'm soaking wet here.
What are you playing?
I’m sorry, Uncle Jim.
I want to take you somewhere.
Did you sleep with my boyfriend?
You stop!
Wen.
I broke up with him, Uncle Jim.
Please believe me.
And this is the man who posted
“An early bird gets things done first.”
Put that away. It's my day off. Can’t I sleep for a little longer?
No, you can’t.
Who promised me yesterday that he would go jogging with me today?
I’ll do it tomorrow. I’ll go with you tomorrow.
“Tomorrow is too late.”
Who posted this?
Are you bullying me?
No.
Are you bullying me? Huh?
Ouch.
It tickles.
Wen.
Wen, it tickles.
What day is today?
I don’t know.
You don’t, really?
I don’t.
I’ll be mad.
I don’t know.
Fine.
Come here. Let’s snap a picture.
For what?
For our anniversary.
Here we go.
One two…
Look at our first anniversary picture.
How many 'N's are there in anniversary?
A-N-N, two Ns.
I always forget it.
You rarely use it.
I want to use it a lot more often with the same person for a long time.
Did I make you blush?
Write it.
One year anniversary.
You will now remember how to spell.
Sure.
Come here.
To where.
Just come.
Hold on.
Come on.
What?
Here. Our board of memory.
Let me put it.
How about we celebrate our first year anniversary?
Wen.
Seriously,
can you tell me what I did wrong?
I’m done talking about that.
Then tell me how you want it to be.
I’ll do better.
You don’t have to do anything.
You don’t have to do anything for me anymore.
You don't give me any choices?
All you want is to break up with me?
I don’t want to torture you any longer.
For me, really?
How could you say that?
Because you are like this.
I wanted to call it quit, but you said we could try to be friends.
Look how we are now.
Can’t you see it doesn’t work?
Do you think it's easy to go from being a boyfriend to a friend?
Exactly!
That’s why I didn’t want us to stay even as friends.
You never treat me as friends.
You can say "friends" as if you don't give a shit about us.
I don’t?
I wouldn't be staying here if I didn't care.
That’s why I believe there’s still a chance in our relationship.
It won’t get any better.
What else do you want me to do then?
You broke up with me out of the blue and said you didn’t love me anymore.
That’s one shitty excuse.
I don’t get it.
Do you want to hear it again?
The shitty excuse you said.
I don’t love you anymore.
I don’t want to get up early to go jogging with you.
I don’t want to have a Shabu with you.
I don’t want to go anywhere with you anymore. Do you get it?
And I don’t want you to stay up waiting for me when I come home late.
Don’t be upset about that anymore.
But I can’t do that because I still care about you. Can’t you see?
However you want to live your life, do it.
Just let me be a part of your life too. Can I?
You don’t want just that. Deep down you know you want more.
You always initiate it.
You still want to get it on even though we already broke up.
That’s bold of you to say.
We slept together, but I'm the only one who gets blamed..
I did it because I felt sorry for you.
Are you happy now?
I slept with you because I felt sorry for you.
See?
I’m the jerk here whenever we talk about this.
Deep down you don’t want us to be like this.
But I did my best.
I did my best, really.
Look where it got us.
We ended up fighting as always.
Aren’t you tired?
You are tired, so am I.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry too.
I try to stay as a friend to you.
Chapter 5: Wrong You in the Right Time
I broke up with him, Uncle Jim.
Please believe me.
Hello.
Where are you, Gong?
At my condo.
You called me this late. Did you get stopped at the police checkpoint?
No.
Another fight?
Can I stay at your place tonight?
Wen.
I think you should stop doing this.
You can’t run away every time you have a fight with him.
That place is also yours.
You're a grown man. You should set things right.
It’s suffocating.
Then move out.
Be decisive.
If you continue to stay with him, you will only give him hope.
It’s never going to be over.
I got it.
Wen.
Come here.
I’ll dress your wound.
Does it still hurt?
Um.
I…am sorry.
For?
For hurting you
and for being a jerk to you.
We are not what we used to be anymore, Alan.
Can you tell me?
What does he have that I don't?
I don’t have an answer for that.
I never compare you with anyone.
When I was with you,
I focused only on you.
My love was just for you.
But it's no longer that.
You don’t leave me any options?
Wen.
It’s late.
I’m tired.
I’m going to bed now.
[Gong.]
[Help me find a pre-owned condo.]
[Sorry.]
[Do you have time?]
[Can we talk?]
[Let’s talk later face to face.]
[Wen - Incoming call]
If I were them, I would do every possible way to make it work.
Even if it means hurting someone's feelings?
That can’t help.
There is no one in this world who has not been hurt by love.
If it doesn’t hurt, it’s not love.
Being hurt when you're in your twenties is totally different from being hurt when you're nearly 40.
Really?
Hey, Jim. The other day, I heard that Mr. Song would like his building back.
Did he say that?
I haven’t heard about it yet.
Bill please.
Coming.
Is there anything I can do to help you?
Just finish your breakfast.
Hey, Gaipa.
Eat with us.
Sis, one porridge, no offal.
Have a seat.
Allright.
I was about to see you at your place.
About Mr. Song, I already talked to my mother.
If you want him to sell out the diner, you can borrow some money from my mother.
No way. I won’t do that.
I knew you would say that.
So I brought you this.
My mother owns a plot of land.
You can use this to get a bank loan.
[Title Deed]
Gaipa. I can’t take this.
Return it to my mother yourself.
She asked me to tell you that.
You can sleep on it.
If you feel uncomfortable about it, we may get you a contract to sign.
Wen.
I’ll be with you in a minute.
Have you been busy recently? I haven't seen you at the diner.
Um.
Do you want to sit with us?
Maybe next time. I’m with my colleagues.
See you.
You guys, let’s grab something to eat.
Help yourself. They have just arrived and are fresh.
They are all the same.
If they are all the same, I won’t bother picking.
We need old Winter Melons for our soup.
If we boil it for too long, it won't become mushy.
Is Wen no longer working with us?
I don’t know. You should have asked him earlier.
Did you two fight?
No.
140 baht.
Here you are.
To me, Wen is an okay guy.
What are you getting at?
What is it?
Nothing. I’m just saying.
Thank you.
He's a pro at doing the dishes too.
Wait a sec.
Can I have one Bubble Tea?
Okay.
Make it two. Don’t put the straws in yet.
Okay. A moment.
Li Ming, I don’t want it.
It’s not for you.
Two Bubble Tea, 50 baht.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I’m taking off first.
What?
Hey.
You want to study in which faculty?
[Engineering or Computer Science.]
Get out.
[Were you in the Math-Science program?]
Really?
Wow. You are smart.
I know.
Your mother is worried about you.
Do you get it?
Hm?
(I know.)
[I know, but I can't live off her forever.]
[One day I have to stand on my own feet and work like everybody else.]
Hey.
Let me tell you something.
Work is really not fun.
It’s exhausting.
Exhausting.
You do want to work for real, right?
It’s gonna be exhausting. Are you up for it?
Are you?
And we have so many special activities for you today.
There are also discounts and giveaways.
Look at our cute mascots here.
Mr. Bunny and Mr. Teddy.
They love to be photographed with you.
Aren’t they lovely?
Our two mascots are taking a break now.
Let’s wave goodbye to them.
Bye-bye.
Have you brought along your IDs?
Yes.
So freaking hot.
Hey.
You OK?
Good.
Thank you so much.
Hey.
Li Ming.
What are you doing here?
Work.
Thank you.
Here.
Is it good?
Wen.
Huh?
This is Heart.
Heart is deaf.
Heart.
This big bro, his name is…
Nice to meet you too.
So, how did you come to work here?
A senior at my school told me about this job.
So I asked Heart to join me.
It's a change of scenery that also pays.
Self-made teens, huh?
I want to save money for the Work & Travel program.
So I don't have to ask Uncle Jim for it.
Is he okay with that though?
He is.
What about you? I haven’t seen you come to work at the diner.
It's been a while.
Well…
Your uncle said that the diner hasn't been very busy lately.
I don’t have to be there.
That's not true. It’s so busy.
Anyway, Gaipa is helping us at the diner now.
That’s nice.
Could you take a picture of us?
Of course.
One two three.
One two…
Here you are.
Handsome.
[Mr. Anantachai Lertwongsa - Credit Manager]
Good afternoon.
May I see the document?
[Title Deed]
What is your relationship with…
this title deed’s owner?
She’s my relative.
May I know how you are related to her?
Your signature is missing in one section of the form.
Please sign it.
I’ll send your request to the headquarter to consider.
If it goes through, I'll have to call the owner of the title deed over.
Okay.
That's not a problem for you, right?
Not at all.
I can use the contact number that's written here, right?
Yes.
Hold on.
That’s my pen.
Sorry.
I'm not aware that I'm taking it.
That’s all right.
Now that you are aware,
just return what you took to me.
[No Answer]
Hey.
How come you are home early?
Stop picking on me.
I’m just asking.
Why?
I'm that much of a jerk to you?
Are you sure you are not picking a fight?
Okay. Let’s be civil.
Alan.
Yes?
Can I ask something?
To get a bank loan, can we use someone else’s title deed?
Of course, as long as the owner lets you.
Why?
That man told you to ask me?
He came to my bank today to request a loan.
There are so many banks to choose from, but he chose mine.
Do you think he'll be able to get a loan?
Do you think I’ll approve it?
Is this what you call being civil?
What's wrong with my words?
I’m professional enough to separate work from private matters.
Even if his loan gets declined, I still like him.
Look, guys. We are told to inspect the site today.
Is anyone free to go with me?
I can go with you.
Hold up. Did we get a green light to go ahead with Phase 3?
The contractors are not able to get to the site by the original timelines.
That’s right. Some homeowners are hesitant to sell their properties.
The negotiations are not yet finished.
What a waste of time.
If Marina really wants those properties, they should be able to work it out.
That’s true.
But some of the houses near the Chicken Rice place have yet to accept the deals.
What if we fail to acquire those places?
Shouldn’t we delay the project for the time being?
You can go ahead with the project. Don’t wait.
I’m sure the board can sort this out one way or another.
This is Thailand.
Big fish always eat small fish.
Go for it.
Get yourself ready. We are going to the site.
I forgot to tell you this.
Alan asked me about that picture in your Story.
He asked me who he is.
What did you say to him?
I said I didn’t know and told him to ask you himself.
Whatever you choose, make it clear.
I have been so clear. We already broke up.
I have nothing else to say to him.
I still don’t understand.
You broke up, but you're still living together.
Isn’t it strange?
Well, he said we could stay as friends.
I understand that part where you can still be friends.
It’s actually nice.
But think about this.
A friend who once was your lover and had intimate relationship with you
stays under the same roof, in the same room and on the same bed as you.
And for a drinker like you,
I’m sure you can get it on easily.
Get it on, my ass.
I’m trying to find a new place to live.
I don’t want to imagine this.
If I’m your new boyfriend and know about this.
I don’t think I can sleep.
Anyway, see you.
See you.
Thank you.
What’s wrong?
Nothing. I just don’t want to talk to you.
Didn’t you say we should talk face to face?
Here I am.
What do you want to talk about? Go ahead.
What do you want me to do?
You can let me know.
I don’t want anything from you, Wen.
I think I made it clear from Day 1.
And now, it couldn’t be any clearer.
Be logical, please.
Alan and I did break up.
We are now friends.
We just live together.
You can have any kind of relationship with anyone. It’s totally up to you.
Don’t involve me.
I’m not a part of it.
You are.
You do know that I like you.
And I’m sure you like me too.
Wen.
Do you remember my question?
I asked you if it’s going to be complicated.
Then what is this?
I’m a grown up man.
I don't like things that are complicated like this.
You got what I meant?
Jim, one Chicken Rice, please.
Sure. Your usual, right?
Yes.
Okay, ma’am.
My love was just for you.
But it's no longer that.
It’s suffocating.
Then move out.
Be decisive.
If you continue to stay with him, you will only give him hope.
It’s never going to be over.
I asked you if it’s going to be complicated.
You dumped me
for this Chicken Rice seller?
Hey!
Stay the f**k out!
Calm down.
Then what is this?
I’m a grown up man.
I don't like things that are complicated like this.
You broke up, but you're still living together.
Whatever you choose, make it clear.
Hello, Alan.
Are you free this evening?
Want to go out to eat?
You know what?
I only started to eat beef when I went out with you.
Yes, I know.
When you had that first bite of beef,
I could tell by the look on your face.
You'd clearly never had beef before.
It was our first date.
You even ordered imported beef.
So I ate that to please you.
Now we have just simple cheap beef together.
You know what?
I don’t really like beef.
Then you don’t have to eat it.
But you like it.
I can eat it too.
But now you like chicken better than beef, right?
You were not this sarcastic back then.
I have always been like this.
You just start to not like it.
I told Gong that we broke up.
You brought me here to tell me this?
What about those past 4 or 5 months?
Why did you make me hope?
I was wrong.
Deep down, I also hope we could make it work again.
Everything you did for me,
I saw it.
I'm sorry…
for being the one who fell out of love with you.
But I can't keep lying to myself any longer.
Can I ask?
If there’s no one else,
will we reach this point in the relationship?
I asked myself that too.
Even if there was no one else,
it wouldn't be any better.
I'm thinking...
I should make this clear once and for all.
For what?
So that you would feel less like a jackass?
No, Alan.
So that I could finally let you go.
Why would you stay with someone who no longer loves you?
Excuse me. I’ll rekindle the fire for you.
No need to.
We’re done. Thanks.
Let’s stop hurting each other.
Now we are truly friends.
You can go first.
Leng.
Please lend me your motorcycle.
Go ahead. The key is over there.
Don’t you have to go to Officer Supoch's house?
I'm finished with that. I'm going to Noch's house to work on an assignment.
I’m leaving.
Hold up, Li.
Fill up the tank for me too, my Li bro.
Okay, bro.
Here.
What is it for?
For your gas.
Li Ming has been using your bike.
I would be an ass if I take that.
Wait. But I’ll keep it to buy my baby’s diapers.
You told me not to turn down money, no matter how small.
Have you taken Praew for an ultrasound?
We won’t need that. It’s a waste of money.
A baby girl or baby boy, we raise them the same.
We let them choose their gender identity when they grow up.
Don’t eat your own words later.
Who cares if people are straight or gay these days?
The ones who could make more money are the winners .
Or simply the ones who are happier.
What about you?
When will you find your own happiness?
Huh?
[I've lived in Pattaya since I was born, but I have never been up here before.]
I will bring you back here more often.
[I will bring you back here more often.]
[I haven’t felt this way in a long time.]
What way?
[What way?]
[Like a normal person.]
To me, you’re normal.
Very good.
Oh shit!
[Saleng]
Hello, Leng.
(Where are you now? Uncle Jim is looking for you.)
At the hospital.
(What?)
The bike skidded.
(Holy shit. Are you okay?)
I’m okay.
But Heart.
(What?)
(You went with Heart?)
(Have you told his mom?)
(Hello, Li Ming. Are you still there?)
(Hello.)
Good evening.
Tell us what happened.
I’m sorry. It was my fault.
I taught Heart to ride a motorcycle and it skidded.
We went to the hospital already. It was not serious.
You taught him to ride a motorcycle?
He’s deaf.
Ma’am.
Deaf people can ride motorcycles.
He asked me to teach him how to ride.
But I never gave permission.
Your previous offense has yet to be cleared, and you have now added to it.
Please accept my apologies on behalf of my nephew.
You Li Ming, why did you do it?
Heart asked me to.
Stop saying that.
He was bored staying at home.
I said stop!
There you go again.
You know that he’s mute, so you can say whatever you want?
Mute?
Aren't you aware that deaf people dislike being called mute?
He’s just deaf.
Li Ming.
I said stop.
It’s the truth.
He said you know nothing.
He wants to live his life like everyone else,
not cooped up in here like this.
I…
I don’t know how to…
What did he say?
He's been deaf for 3 years now.
You’ve never tried to learn sign language.
What did he say?
He said that you are ashamed of him being deaf.
I…
Heart, I’m sorry.
I don't know what to say, dear.
Please help tell this to him.
Heart.
Heart!
He’ll be fine, honey.
Just let him for now.
Why do you keep causing trouble after trouble?
It’s not like I want it to happen.
It’s an accident.
It would not have happened if you hadn’t taken him out.
He asked me to.
I’m the only friend he has.
You shouldn’t have taken him out like that.
Be considerate to his parents
What if something more serious occurs to him?
I never think it will occur.
I didn’t say you couldn’t be friends.
But there must be some boundaries.
If I’d become like Heart, you would do the same as Mrs. Jintana does, right?
It’s not the same.
If you have a friend who hasn't left his house in 3 years,
and you are the only person who can take him out,
will you do the same as what I do?
I’m grown enough.
If something happens, I can take responsibility for it.
If I get into trouble again, you don't have to help me.
I'll sort out my own problem.
[Wen]
I don't have a place to stay anymore.
♪ There’s tomorrow for you to seize and treasure ♪
♪ There will be tomorrow for you to love and to move forward ♪
♪ There’s tomorrow for us to start over ♪
♪ If you ♪
♪ Just wait ♪
Directed by Noppharnach Chaiyahwimhon
Are you guys boyfriends now?
I’d like to know too.
Uncle Jim, what should I call this relationship?
Friends.
Why is your wall so high?
Is it possible for me to be the right one for you?