God
my life
is very boring
What are you
alive for?
-Daruma-san-
-Fell-
Do not move.
Do not move
Move or you'll die
-Daruma-san-
-fell-
God.
Please send me
back to my boring life
-Daruma-san fell-
-Daruma-san-
My legs are starting to go numb
So what do you want us to do?
Why?
Why is everyone dying?
Is this a terrorist attack?
Why does that Daruma Doll can move
and speak?
Hey Class President?!
How should I know?!
-fell-
-Ah? tsk-
Must get out of here.
Asshole! You are the one who is suppose to tell us what to do.
Why can't we open this?!
Get out of my way.
-Daruma-san fell-
-Ah? Ah?-
-Laughs-
No. I don't want to die.
Calm down!
Calm down?
Do you even understand what is happening right now?
-fell-
-Ah? Ah?-
-Tsk. Boring.-
This
represents the Daruma-san's death doll.
As to why could this be a problem?
Escape is not considered as an option
in this horrible situation.
That game is very boring.
If you want to steal something, go to the other side of the shelf.
It's the dead spot for the spy cameras.
You can find interesting games there.
Now, get out of here straight and calmly.
But how do we get out of here?
Look, behind that bastard Daruma
-Daruma-san fell-
-boring-
According to the words on the back
-up ~-
We don't know the exact rules.
but most likely pressing that button will end this.
-Mount up ~ ~-
Live it up to me.
Wait-
-Fell-
-laughs-
-up-
What now?
Don't panic.
Do not worry. We should do it slowly step by step.
That won't work!
What do you mean it won't work?
I agree with him.
Quickly look at that.
- of ~ Mount tumbler-
A timer.
What would happen if it reaches zero?
Although I'm not entirely sure,
I'm afraid everyone will die
-fell-
Only one minute left.
-down-
-laughs-
-chants-
Damn
-Daruma-san fell-
Please!!! Someone !!! Stop this!!!
-down-
It's no use already.
-Chants-
Stand
I will instantly
send you over there
Huh?
Step on me to fly over
this pile of corpses.
What?
Remember when we practiced gymnastics in P.E
It's that one.
I know.. I know.. BUt?
-not fall ~~.-
Now come here!
Arghhhh
-fell ~ down -
-ah ah ah.-
End End End
We did it!
It worked.
The switch button is pressed by Takahata Shun
Survived. Survived.
What the heck is this?
Shun, have you already unpacked
I'll do it tomorrow.
You've been saying that for a month
and I haven't seen you do it.
Tomorrow I'll finish it
The car parked next to a bulding
suddenly exploded resulting to
16 nearby pedestrian deaths.
52 people who suffered light injuries
was rushed to the city hospital
It is not yet confirmed whether there is a Japanese killed.
Local government considered it to be
an act of an anti-government groups
Right now they are doing an investigation regarding this.
Good Morning Shun.
Hey you
Why don't you ask her to be your girlfriend?
Her family lives next door
so since childhood we've know each other.
So I can't harbor any special feeling
I think it's like that for her too.
Oh, she is very popular.
Many wants to be in your position.
I know. I know.
Another boring day.
Those guys are really interesting
During the reign of Louis XIV
French monarchy autocratic was in its prime time.
He said "I am the State"
Therefore "I'm the Sun King."
Takahata
Yes?
Just continue to sleep.
Now here is the coverage of the test.
God.
Please give back to me
my boring life.
You're are a rat
Something is coming.
A cat is coming.
Mouse?
A cat is coming!
A cat is coming?
Ichika
Shun
Thank goodness. You're alive.
Where is everyone?
I want to save everyone.
When finally I'm lose enough
I pressed the button
I killed everybody
It's all my fault
I did the same thing
I pushed it too.
Why is this happening?
I don't have any idea.
Ah.. Let's try calling the police.
Eh.. why?
You are the mouse
A cat is coming soon.
It is coming.
Let's get out of here quickly and let the police know.
Not here also.
Ichika get out of the way.
Oh, It's bulging
Everyone
It's useless.
Once you get in you can't get out.
Ah.
What the heck is this?
Make the cat wear the bell
and it will end.
What does this mean?
Well, quickly change your clothes.
If we don't follow the rules, we don't know what will happen.
Come, get dressed
Quickly, put it.
This is an order of the Student Council President!
The cat is here!
-feed-
That will eat all of us!
Ichika, stand up quickly
Shun, what is that?
Make the cat wear the bell, and it would end.
Then that's...
There.
We have shoot that bell into that basketball hoop
9 minutes and 30 seconds left
That's totally impossible.
Everyone if we put that bell in that cat's collar.
This game will be over.
Good. That would do.
Akimoto Pass.
Please,
I've never been lazy
365 days a year
500 times a day, I practice shooting.
During that, my nails splitted 30 times.
Why should I sacrifice my life
to practice basketball
Now finally I understand
Everything is for this moment.
It will go in.
Great
It's hand is moving.
Everyone take that dress off.
The ones who were attacked are only those who are wearing that dress.
Get it off.
Hurry up or you'll be eaten
So we'll not be eaten like this right
Are you kidding us!!!
You said to wear this dress right
How should I know
that it's a trap all along.
You bastard!You told us it would be different...
I see..
A mouse are not,
it would only eat people
Only three minutes left?
There is no time left.
I will...
die.
Look here.
Look here
Shun!
Someone...
While I attract its attention...
Shoot the bell!
Stop dreaming
I can not die like Yoshikawa.
If this continues, then we'll all die.
It hurts...
My back is itchy
It's itchy
Who is that?
My back is itchy
I can't sleep ..meow.
Who will help me scratch it meow.
What is this guy saying?
It's itching.. Itching.. ahhh..
back tickling tickling ah ah
Only I can hear it.
Why is that?
meow.
Meow meow
meow
My back is itchy
My back is itchy, I can't sleep meow
So that is really it.
Who will help me meow?
What is happening shun?
The ones wearing this dress will be eaten by this guy
But at the same time
Only those who wear this will be able to understand this guy.
Good.
How's that? It feels good right.
More.. More...
Meow want to be scratched again
More.. More...Scratch me again meow
Must scratch
Must scratch.
Everyone
Help me!
It itches... It itches...
Who will help me scratch it meow
More.. More...
It feels good to be scratched meow
More... More...
Scratch me more Meow.
It feels so good meow
Great
Let's do it now.
Wait a moment
Maybe
will be like that time, with the Daruma doll.
Everyone aside from the one who shoots it will die?
This time everyone gave the cat a scratch.
Everyone have done their duty.
So I think, we will all survive.
Are you sure?
This...
Then I'll shoot
Who agreed with you here
I'll shoot
This time it should be ladies first
Get out you a sow
Me.
Let go
Let go...
Now is not the time to fight!
You're the one to say that
You're also thinking that you want to survive this
Don't lie.
Calm down everyone.
If you don't be quiet, then that guy...
You
Everyone take your hand off of it.
This is the student council president's order
You're just using your advantage to bully everyone
To give it to you.
If we manage to make it fell asleep, then
It's no use.
We do not have that time
Then what do we do?
What to do?
What to do right now?
Ichika, get that bell.
Follow me.
We cannot just let them escape
Which one is the bell? and Which one is the basketball?
Eyes?
It's eyes distinguishes whether or not someone is wearing a mouse clothes
Throwing it like a basketball
It will catch the bell.
That guy will first confirm it before moving.
So in this case we will be able to create a delay of time
before he confirms it and make a move.
Success rate is...
50%
Guess which side is the bell
That idiot
It's the critical moment right now
Then the one who has the bell is...
The genuine one is here!
How could this be..
Then letting it see the ball is...
intentional.
To make it think I am holding a bell
Get in..
How could...
God.
You...
-End-
We did it.
It's not finished
It's to early to be happy right now.
The ones who survived are.
Amaya Takeru
Takahata Shun.
Akimoto Ichikata
Great.
See, we can actually survive...
The top three survived
Survive
What about the others...
God revolutionized this world
where power is everything.
Survivors are the good ones
while the ones who died are evil
I've always dreamed of such a world.
Thank you God
I appreciate it.
This guy...
is dangerous.
All the normal humans have already died
And only we have survived. We are the chosen ones
You're also thinking of it that way.
Takahata Shun
I'm not thinking that way
No.
You and I are the same
Similar?
When do you feel alive?
In my case. It's when I'm destroying something. That's when I feel I'm alive.
So in order to survive this
I'll do everything.
Don't joke around. What are you saying?
Look at this intent look.
You
Are also looking forward to this world
Just like me
No.
The two of you are not the same at all
Shun is very gentle and very strong.
And you are completely different
Right.
Stop.
All High Schools WorldWide.
All national high schools in
Washington, Moscow, New York, Sydney and London
Madrid are in the middle of terrorist attacks.
Now information is still not clear
It is said to have more than 10 million young people died
A new intelligence report just came in.
Just now, Prime Minister Abe
of the Prime Minister's official residence established
an Emergency Countermeasures Headquarters.
They announced the it is a National Level Disaster.
Look at that
Right now
Cube like this one appearing suddenly around the world
Rumors said
That the terrorist attack occuring
simultaneously in various High Schools
Was said to be held in the cube
that contains the surviving students.
Police and self-defense forces are now being deployed
together to implement the rescue operations.
But the entrance to the cube could not be found
Next in the news, a cube that appeared in Hokkaido
is now being tracked by Reporter Sato...
Now switching to live...
Oh what now.. Now that the news actually matters.
...SDF also thinks that there is no way
That the main road in the city...
Thank you, ah uncle.
Now here in the studio is.
Our guest, Professor of Department
of Human Environment Studies from Touto University
Okuhira Tadakatsu.
This series of terrorist attacks and the mysterious cube
Is there a link between the two of them?
This is not a terrorist attack
Alien invasion is what we are seriously
should consider right now.
The situation is beyond the scope of human cognition.
Hey.. Hey.. What is he saying?
But you see...
Right now
Across the internet, surviving students are being called as "Children of God"
We are starting to see an emergence
of a human deification.
Children of God...
Takumi
I'll put food out here, oh
Takumi.
You should occasionally come out to see your mother...
Shut up.
Go away, old woman.
Children of God.
Children of God
It hurts...
Are you okay, Takahata-kun?
I had a dream of being licked by a cat
I'm feeling the cat's tongue...
Thank goodness. Long time no see
Takase-san, why are you here?
Anyway, where is this place?
Just like you Takahata- kun
When I woke up, I'm already at this place.
I see.
How many years we have not seen each other anyway?
I transferred back when we are in first year, if we are to count it...
We've not seen each other for three years.
Well, you're looking good.
But now, in this situation, I cannot say that.
Takahata-kun.
Is this the end of it?
Why do we encounter this kind of thing?
I do not really know
But we are lucky though.
Yeah, also we managed to meet again
Can you be a little quieter?
I am now doing physics vector analysis of that thing.
Using the Helmholtz Theorem to attempt to
disassemble its current status.
Huhh
This is Taira-kun from a
private high school.
While there is Taoka-san from an all-girls High School.
They both played the "Daruma Doll"
and also the "Lucky Cat" and survived.
Taira.
Taoka Takase.
Takahata.
Is the distribution of students
per room is according to the syllabry order of names?
That's about right.
The both of us occupying the same room
proves that it is not distributed
according to one's IQ level.
How come everytime you start talking
you always tend to find a fault?
Now I see.
So perhaps Akimoto and Amaya are in the same room
We were brought in together. I must go and see.
Damn! It's locked
Someone - Someone - Someone out there
Nothing will happen, so just stop it.
...suddenly appeared all over the world...
...Worldwide high schools...
Meanwhile a spate of terrorist attacks.
...This is not a terrorist attack...
...occurring simultaneously throughout various high schools...
...Okuhira Tdakatsu in just the Prime Minister
Prime Minister's official residence...
...alien invasion...
...released national level emergency...
...this is what we should now be...
Nobody will save us.
SDF are not able to enter the cube to rescue us
Then what should we do?
You should just wait.
Wait for the next game to start.
You still think there will be another game
Not really "think", it's more of a "hope"
I can not wait to catch you idiot guys out.
...The surviving students throughout the internet
are called "Children of God"
We are beginning to see a deified wave...
"Children of God"
Not a bad name...
A key to open the door
will appear if it ended
It's here.
-Let's play together.-
-Taira-kun let's play-.
Okay
What will we play?
-The game we will -
-be playing is "Caged Bird"-
-At the end of the song you should
guess who is behind you in 10 seconds.-
-And your eyes would be-
-Blindfolded-
This is very interesting.
-So...-
-Let's start-
-Ready...-
-Kagome kagome -
-The bird in the cage-
-When, oh when will it come out-
-In the night of dawn-
-The crane and turtle slipped-
-Who is behind you now?-
It's Akemi
-Wrong.-
-Unfortunately I was Hanako-
-bye, bye-
Wait...
-Bow down-
-Up-
-Next then it would be...-
-Let's see.. Let's see...-
-Who will be the one playing it.-
-Who will.-
-Taoka-san play with us.-
No. I don't want to play.
-What... that's really boring-
-Then should we just kill her?-
-Let's do that-
I understand. I'll play. I'll play.
-It doesn't matter. If you hate it, you should not do it.-
I don't hate it.
I'm looking forward to it.
-Then you really want to play it-
-Then there is nothing we could do-
-Let's play it-
-Kagome kagome -
-The bird in the cage-
-When, oh when will it come out-
-In the night of dawn-
-The crane and turtle slipped-
-Who is behind you now?-
It is...It is...
-Time is up.-
Don't!!!
Stop it!
-Let's see-
-Who is next.-
-Takase-san-
-Let's play it-
I will be the one who would play with you.
Let's just start this now.
-OK, ok.. You understand-
-This guy is totally funny-
-Idiot are friends with idiots.-
-Takahata-san-
-So... Let us get started quickly.
-One, Two-
-Kagome kagome -
-The bird in the cage-
-When, oh when will it come out-
I'll survive this
-In the night of dawn-
-The crane and turtle slipped-
-Who is behind you now?-
-Time is up-
-You'll gonna die-
-Kenichi-
-The one behind me is Kenichi-
-But you are already out of time-
No, I made it just in time
-That's right.-
-What are you saying-
-Why are you saying it's not time yet?.-
It is because of this.
-Time is up-
-I recorded it when Taoka-san is playing.-
The moment you say time is up
You are just spouting lies.
That is why I lure you into speaking
because the way you re-arrange yourselves
are always the same.
That way, I'll know who is the one behind me.
-You'll gonna die.-
I may seem like an idiot to you.
Takahata-kun
Thank goodness. Thank you very much for saving me.
Hey, let's hold hands
-I'm so lonely-
-I don't have any friends to play with-
Hey, let's hold hands
-You are friends right-
-nice nice ah ah-
-tskk-
We are saved
If you don't hold hand with somebody
That guy will attack you
Takahata-san
My hand.
Please do not let go of my hand
I will certainly not let go
Break it
You'll feel the enjoyment of it
Do not
Let's go.
Ichika.
Shun
-Tsk-
-So lonely again-
Thank goodness
I made it in time
Thank you.
Amaya?
I do not know
Although we started in the same room
He struck down after the puppets.
And goes with the person holding a key.
Shoko
It's been a long time.
Kotaro.
Ahh, What is this?
Could it be that
to seven people while inserting Seven Keys
-Seven people holding seven keys-
-will insert it and rotate it simultaneously-
How many are you people?
Only four of us
We are one person short
What does this mean?
It seems like seven people is required to gather.
And seven keys is needed to unlock it
For us to move to move forward.
How many keys do you have?
We have two.
We also have two.
Then we still need three keys and one other person.
Otherwise there is no way to open the door
Perhaps if we wait
Someone will finally..
You manage to play this far and you still
don't understand it yet.
Two minutes left
Anyway. Let's just go and look for..
That would be impossible.
We'll be speaking for two minutes
and no time to collect the three keys...
Amaya
So cool
Now we can finally clear this
but now one person has to...
No problem
The only reason I was with him is because
I don't want to be turned into a kokeshi doll
He is now out of use.
Hey
Is he your friend?
A problem might bloom
if we go along with this madman.
We're friends, right Takahata Shun?
Come on time is running out
I know
Let's go Amaya
One
Two
-Finished.-
-Takahata Shun.-
-Akimoto Ichika.-
-Amaya Takeru.-
-Roku Eiji.-
-Maeda Kotaro.-
-Sanada Yukio.-
-Takase Shoko-
-This seven -
-survived-
Put on your clothes
-You survived-
Why are my clothes in here
-Come-
-Come over here-
-Come here.-
-Do not stop.-
Please get out of the way
Please make way
Those people standing there
Please make way.
That's why I'm asking
Where the heck is that video coming from
They failed to make it inside the cube right?
There is no way aliens contacted the media.
Children of God.
Where is this place?
Snow Palace
What the heck is it this time?
-Hello-
-I like the white color.-
-I really love pure white-
What?
-I hate dark hearted people.-
-That's is why you absolutely must tell the truth-
-Tell the truth and it would end.-
What do you mean?
-It's very simple-
-Everyone must please-
-Answer honestly to my question-
-If everyone says the truth-
-Then the game ends.-
-But if someone lied,-
-Then pick one person out every time as a sacrifice.-
-Please take note-
Sacrifice?
-So the first question is...-
-You.-
-What is your favorite food?-
Oh that is the question?
If it is those kind of question
Then we'll win it easily.
My favorite is
sushi
I like.
Ramen
Meat
Parsley
Curry
Omelette rice
Cream crepes.
-Do not lie.-
-Who is lying?-
-Within two minutes, the liar has to surrender-
-Otherwise, I would eat all the people-
-Two minutes left-
Who lied?
Honestly answer the question.
So you're saying it's not you.
Of course it's not me
I did not lie
Where is the evidence?
Are you kidding me?
Evidence?
Where do you think you'll find an evidence here?
What is with your look?
Then Sanada-san, do you have an evidence with you?
I'd want to see
Guys please calm down.
I'm calm.
Pretending to be a good student when
you're the most dubious one here.
I know Shun likes to eat curry
As for me
It doesn't matter if I eat
egg three meals a day.
You sure are lying.
What?
-One minute left-
We'll die
we have no time.
What now?
Ah you say like to eat parsley right
So?
Right
Someone who eats that kind of thing has definitely a problem.
Everyone is different from each other.
Wait guys..
Right
It's definitely a problem
I agree.
What?
-The time is almost up-
-Who is the one who lied-
What?
It's you
It's you right
No
Not me
I really
like eating parsley
-Liars will have the same fate-
-So everyone pay attention, okay?-
-Let's move on to the next question.-
-Do you -
-like Takahata Shun-kun?-
-Yes or NO?-
No
This is kind of irritating huh...
Yes
-So how do the girls think?-
Well I've known him since we were a child
and if we consider that fact
I'd have to say
Yes
How come do I feel like you are just forced to say that?
My answer is, yes
-Very popular thing-
-This kid-
- Now how about yourself?-
I
No
I never liked myself
-You guys-
-Someone among you lied-
-Who is the one who lied?-
-Two minutes left-
-Two minutes.-
Who is it?
Please stop this right now!
Is it...
You
You tried to kill us before
But then you said you like Shun.
That would be odd.
The one I want to kill and love are at the same bar.
Takahata-kun.
Do not lie to yourself
You're saying you don't like yourself
but you still exist now.
Say something.
It's really very suspicious
Originally
If everyone honestly answered the questions, everyone can be saved
Obviously, we don't need to lie.
But in the end, someone still lies
-You finally noticed the key in it.-
-That is because-
-One of us is among you-
- And puts a human like facade-
-In order to kill all of you-
-By lying-
-You have to find this guy-
-Otherwise all you will truly die-
-I really hate it-
-Liars are dark-hearted people -
-I like the white-
Among us
Someone is their accomplices.
There one minute left
We have no time.
Wait.
I think this maybe very simple.
What
because I know students that are in great Gakuen Heaven
for a while.
Takahata-kun
Ichika-san.
Amaya-kun
We met each other that time during the
High School meet, right?
Then
the enemy accomplice is
not her...
It's you, right?
The only one we don't know is only you.
No
I did not lie
Both of us are friends in junior high
She could not be the enemy associates
That is even more suspicious
Those kind of people are actually the suspects most of the case.
What?
Are you sure it's not a trap?
I believe Takase.
Do not be fooled by her beauty
-You should hurry-
-or all of you would die-
-Do you really know -
-Who is the traitor?-
It's her
Stop that.. you
I said stop that.
Stop
I did not lie.
I
really like Takahata.
Please do not let go of my hand.
-Awww.. It's sad..
-She is really a human being-
-Okay next question-
Wait a moment
-Why are you interupting me-
I know
In the end who is lying
You finally noticed.
Who is it?
The true liar is....
It's you!
I realized it from the start
How did that happened?
This game from the start is a lie.
He said that one of us is their associate.
It's actually a lie.
It's Takase
It's Takase's blood
which told me the truth.
You don't like white things
-You saw it-
Takahata.
Oh.
Hot
It's so hot!
I will burn to death.
The way to clear it is not to tell you the truth but
to realized you're not what pure white bear
but a terrible black bear
A devil bear
-The game has ended.-
-Takahata Shun.-
-Takeshi Akimoto-
-Takeru Amaya-
-Roku Eiji-
-Maeda Kotaro-
-These five people.-
-Survived Survived.-
Please do not run.
What will appear next?
Probably.
A game with "ma" at the beginning of it
Ma.
What, did you not notice it?
The oppenents before have names
that are connected like shirotori
Shirotori?
Right Shiritori.
The first is Daruma.
Then Maneki Neko
Kokeshi
Followed by Shiro Kuma
That's right.
Yes.
So what is the game with "ma" in the beggining of it.
Such as...
Matryoshka Matryoshka
-You guys actually made it here.-
-This is the last hurdle.-
-So let's us happily play it to end everyone.-
This is the last
What is it you want to play?
-It will be-
Kicked the jar
Then it would end.
Kick jar?
-The rules are very simple-
-The monster will take the can from above-
-and put it in the designated place-
-The players will hide while he is at it-
-After the countdown, the monster will-
-search around for the players.-
-If the players face is seen by the monster and the monster-
-Stepped at the can while shouting their name -
-That person will be caught.-
-Anyone who is caught -
-will be held in a prison cell-
-If a person who isn't caught yet, kicked the jar-
-Before the monster sees them, then-
-Everyone will be released from being caught.-
-But the can will explode by the time it's kicked-
-So in order to save everyone-
-One would sacrifice himself-
-It's very interesting right?-
-The game will end if-
-The last man claims victory-
-or the other way around where the it-
-caughts three or more people to victory Hey.-
The game is kicked jar where people would die
Death-defying Kick Jar game
-Stop it please... This game would be fun to play-
-So who will become it-
-Draw lots to decide it-
-One, Two-
I am the it
What the hell?
Why is it the most troublesome guy?
-The time limit is until the sun sets-
-Go ahead-
-Game Start-
Let's go
The start here is the most important.
Until that guys gets the can
We should escape as far as we can..
Good
-Amazing-
We've run this far. We'll be alright here.
There is about one hour before the sunset.
If we don't move until then, we will not be found.
Too easy
No, it's impossible.
What were your names again?
Damn
What was it?
Ah I remembered..
Roku-kun
Kotaro-kun
Found them.
Sure enough, the guy is not normal.
It feels like he is looking right here...
Go ahead.
Go ahead do it quickly.
You go
No Ickika .. Ichika....
Akimoto Ickika, found you.
It's all over.
Takahata will not sacrifice himself to save our lives
It's alright. I don't think he would sacrifice Ichika.
Damn!
The moment the sun goes down
We are also finished
What should I do?
What will I do?
Takahata, do you hear me?
I caught already three people
so I will be able to survive this.
That is why I'm not going to arrest you.
Do not worry about it.
So when the time limit ends
Two people will survive this
Survive
We are chosen by Gods
We can survive in the new world.
New World
You are also looking forward to this world
Like me.
I
I...
Shun, can you hear me?
Honestly, I really hate you.
You always stay away from other people.
Always making promises and breaks it
Always able to read my mind
I do not want to see your face.
So...
So never get out
You should not believe
What this guy is saying
Just quickly escape from here
Understand me
Ichika.
Shun and you are simply not the same
Shun is gentler and stronger than you
and you are completely different.
Takahata.
We're friends, right?
The game will be over
Believe me, go out of your hiding place
I understand
I will come out right now.
Shun, please not be fooled
I kept you waiting
Ichika.
The rule states that in order the to catch someone,
you should first see their face then shout their name
before arresting them.
So you can't see my face behind this mask
That fool
What the heck is he doing?
It's true that in that way he would be
able to hide his face and
guard himself from the explosion when he kicks the can
but that way
he could easily be caught and have his mask removed.
Takahata-kun, why are you doing all this ruckus?
Come, Amaya
I will be your opponent.
What now?
I thought you want to be my opponent.
Shun, Run away!
In my opinion, that armor is very unwise of you.
Takahata-kun, found you
You're actually right, Amaya
I still think that
all the boring nonsense in this world
should all be destroyed.
I also joked with the Gods about it.
But absolutely not like this.
Now I know how is it to lost something I treasure
I was a fool
I only felt the sense of being alive when
I'm at the brink of death.
I'm really a fool
We have the right to be alive.
Important things seem trivial
Those boring days are the best.
Sorry, Amaya
I'm not like you.
Don't worry
I don't intend to help you from the start.
Even if you are struggling that much
As soon as I step on the can and say your name
You lose
That's not it...
Wearing this armor is not to hide my face
Nor to protect myself from the explosion
This is for this
Shun.
Enough.
Please stop this.
Shun.
Satoke and Shoko-chan
Surely, I still wants to do a lot of things.
but
Saying that we are chosen by God.
If this world is created by God.
What the hell is wrong with God?
Shun!!! No!!!
Takahata
It's going to explode.
Huh?
-The Game ended-
-Because Takahata Shun rescued the people who were arrested-
-Amaya Takeru's catch totalled into zero-
-Therefore he is out-
-Akimoto Ichika-
-Roku Eiji.-
-Maeda Kotaro-
-and lastly Takahata Shun-
-You Won-
Thank goodness
Although it's a little bit unclear why
We actually survived?
We won?
But why didn't it explode?
-Ah that-
-That is a lie-
Huh?
-Because it is more interesting that way right?-
You guys, don't mess with me.
I'm chosen by Gods
How can I die here?
-Huh? Die here? What are you saying?-
-From the start everyone is-
-Happily playing the game-
-No one said that those who lost will die ah ha ha ha-
Is that really true?
That.
-Everyone-
-All of you worked hard to reach it here-
We really...
We really are still alive the ah
Thank goodness.
-This is a reward for everyone-
When you finished, we will send you back home.
It's really beautiful.
Hey, Ichika.
After we get out of here
Let go out and eat something delicious.
After that...
Let's see some movies.
Okay.
Also after that...
Let's do a lot of things together, Ichika.
Also my mother wants me to clean up the storage room.
You haven't still done that.
Mom and Dad would probably
wants me train.
But now i think
It's not bad at all
It's delicious
Hmm.. I got a lucky.
What is it ?
Sorry, Shun.
I
won't be able to go to the movies with you
-Everyone-
-In order to live this far-
-"Intelligence"-
-"Physical Strenght"-
-'Imagination"-
-You've been able to display all of that-
-And we know you lot worked very hard-
-But there is..-
-One last necessary thing-
-And that is-
"luck"?
Shun
it seems like
I like you a little bit.
Bye-bye
-Luck-
Ichika
What the hell is this?
What the hell?
-Takahata Shun.-
-Amaya Takeru-
-Survived Survived-
The cube is finally here.
The surviving teenager finally appeared.
Takumi-chan
I;ll put the rice outside here okay
I will go out
Where are you going to?
To save the world.
Do not come back too late ah
Children of God, Children of God
Children of God
God doesn't exist.
-Well, you are wrong-
-Daruma-
-Manekineko-
-Kokeshi-
-Shiro Kuma-
-Matryoshka-
-God-