[English subtitles are available]
[Pretty Guardian of the City]
[Episode 8]
Here.
Great.
I'm free now.
Let me help you.
Qing,
do it yourself.
Young Master, let's go.
Yunxi.
What is your relationship
with Guard Tang?
You two acted so intimately in my mansion,
which was very insolent.
Young Master,
Don't get us wrong.
Tang Qing and I
grew up together.
He's like my brother.
You take Tang Qing as your brother?
Yes.
There are two suitable locations
in Cangyue City for the market.
One is the manor land to the north.
The other
is Winding Alleys to the south.
Roads there
lead everywhere,
with complete infrastructure.
The shortcoming is its dense population.
Relocation and demolition costs
will be very high.
You know that place well.
Of course.
The Jianjia Alley I once lived in
is there.
Besides, it's my job
to walk around and remember
every detail of the city
in my mind.
This is
the manor land I mentioned before.
Its advantages are the beautiful scenery,
vast space, and sparse population.
It's a better site for the market.
What's more,
we can make use of
both water and road transport
to make goods exchange fast and efficient.
This place
is far from downtown.
But in terms of other aspects,
it's a better location for the market
than Winding Alleys.
Young Master,
why are you staring at me?
Nothing.
What you said
reminds me of Luo Daoan.
Father.
My father once said that
20 years ago, Lord Luo proposed
to redesign Cangyue City
and exploit the northern lands.
It was a turbulent time,
so his plan wasn't carried out.
Some of your ideas
are exactly the same as his.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm just excited
that you mentioned Lord Luo.
He's my favorite surveyor.
I admire him very much.
Rumor has it
that after Luo Daoan
embezzled the construction funds,
he and his family committed suicide for fear of punishment.
But I've seen
his works.
I don't think he was someone
who would debase himself for money.
The dead doesn't
tell stories.
So we can hardly know
what really happened.
You have a point.
You wouldn't ride with me the other day.
Let's see how you can refuse me
this time.
My horse!
-I'll go get it back. -Wuyan, wait!
Young Master.
Why are you always the unlucky one?
I don't think
they will come back anytime soon.
I'll do you a favor
and let you ride with me.
I'm not going to ride with you.
Fine.
I prefer riding alone anyway.
You said no but hurried to mount my horse.
Good for you, Yunxi.
Why are you turning back?
How dare you abandon me?
Not that way!
Young Master,
I just had
a test ride.
Wait.
It's improper for us to be too close.
You should not get on the horse.
If you don't want to ride with me,
that's okay.
I believe you can
run back to my mansion
before dawn tomorrow.
Come down.
Take a look.
Don't move.
You may fall.
Candied haws!
Take a look!
It smells so good.
Take a look.
Wait.
I need to buy something.
I'll go back by myself later.
What are you going to buy?
Let me go with you.
I haven't visited the market
in a long time.
No need.
I'm going to buy
girls' stuff.
I'd feel uncomfortable if you came along.
Sir,
can this incense
make a man who doesn't have feelings for me
fall in love with me?
Sure.
It can do more than that.
Look at this.
As long as you use my incense,
you can get any man you want.
This incense will make
Jiang Chaoxi and Xiao Fengyi
have an unforgettable night.
Sir,
I'll buy it.
Okay. Thank you.
Here.
Thank you.
Take care.
No man can resist.
Hot Night Incense.
What a surprise!
Young Master.
How is it?
I can only have him
drink some soup.
There's no clue about Fengchi.
I'm afraid Luo Hexuan
won't last long.
Young Master,
this is the blueprint
just sent by the Planning Department.
Wait.
In my mansion,
men and women
are forbidden from getting too close.
Be careful.
Don't be a bad influence
on other people here.
Young Master,
are you talking about me and my sister?
Sister?
That's an intimate way of addressing her.
Of course.
Yunxi and I
grew up together.
We've never separated.
We're indeed
closer to each other than to others.
I don't care about the past you shared.
In my mansion,
men and women
should keep a distance.
Anyone violating that rule
will be kicked out!
Yes, Young Master.
What are you looking at?
You got anything to say?
I don't have the nerve.
I'm going on patrol.
Yunxi,
how could you plan to make advances to me
and in the meanwhile
be another man's sweetheart?
That's not what a lady should do.
You've found the secret room?
Take me there.
No hurry.
We need the key to get in.
It's Young Master's jade badge.
Good.
I spend lots of time with him during the day.
I'll find a chance to get it.
Let me do it.
I'm more skilled.
It's my call.
Don't rush into anything.
Yun'er,
I'm afraid
I can't protect you anymore.
No, Brother.
I'll do as you say in the future.
I won't go down the mountain again.
It's not your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
The Swing Painting at home
is a map that leads to Fengchi.
You must go back to get it.
Also,
keep this white jade comb
with you.
Brother,
after I get the jade badge,
I'll go save you.
Is there a problem with this one?
No.
How about this one?
No problem.
This one?
She's staring at me
so boldly.
She's not shy at all.
How can I get
his jade badge?
Since you're so obsessed with me,
I'll give you a chance.
The incense today
doesn't smell so good.
It's a bit pungent.
I think it's good.
Expensive incense like this
smells of money.
You fool.
Use that Hot Night Incense you bought!
Seize the opportunity!
The ink has gone dry.
Let me grind the ink for you.
Are you alright?
It's all my fault.
Let me fix it.
Stop!
You wanna feel me up?
You're a girl.
Restrain yourself.
Zhu Wen.
Steward Zhu is not here.
Why don't you
get changed first?
She followed me all the way here.
So persistent.
I'll go wash the clothes.
Where is the jade badge?
Stupid woman.
Even if Cupid shot a bullet
into your heart,
you wouldn't feel a thing.
I'll give you
one last chance.
If you can't seize it either,
you can only blame yourself
for not being blessed.
What are you doing?
I was cutting the loose threads
on your clothes.
Loose threads?
My clothes
are of high quality.
There are no loose threads.
That's crap.
No matter how expensive your clothes are,
they are sewn by threads.
Of course there are loose threads.
I just saw one.
Where is it?
This is improper.
Maybe I was mistaken.
I'll leave you to rest.
I'll go.
Come back!
You can't fool me again!
He gave the order yesterday
♫I like to be behind you♫
that men and women in this mansion
shouldn't get too close.
But now he's holding her in his arms?
It turns out that the rule maker
♫Even the night breeze becomes gentle♫
doesn't have to abide by his own rule.
♫I feel so happy♫
Yunxi.
♫Time seems to have stopped♫
I was holding her in my arms,
but she just got up and ran away?
Is that some new trick?
♫I wish to hold your hand♫
♫Till the end of the day♫
Yunxi,
Young Master just hugged you.
Then you don't care about me
anymore.
♫But I can't escape from fate♫
I was holding my pastry,
and I saw Yunxi
lunge at our Young Master.
In broad daylight,
Yunxi was too bold.
She was.
Pepper.
Don't spread rumors.
There's no way Yunxi has a feeling
for Young Master.
Tang Qing,
there's no impossible for feelings
between men and women.
Besides,
Young Master is an outstanding one.
It's normal if Yunxi can't hold
her feelings.
Tang Qing!
My waist!
My cousin didn't even mention paying a visit.
Miss.
Bad news!
Quiet!
Is it the end of the world?
It's worse.
Yunxi hugged Young Master.
They have fallen in love with each other.
What did you say?
Miss.
Take it easy.
No.
I can't  believe it.
Really?
This has spread around
in the mansion.
Everyone knows it.
Damn Yunxi. Let's go.
Find her.
Yunxi.
The whole mansion is talking about
you hugging Young Master.
I'm afraid if this continues,
it will disgrace your name.
I accidentally bumped into him
just because I was trying to steal the jade badge.
Yunxi!
Trouble is coming.
Miss Fengyi,
have you recovered?
How dare you hug my cousin
during my recuperation?
Looks like you don't want
your arms anymore.
Don't think I won't hurt you,
just because you're good-looking.
Miss,
you can't accuse me
without confirming reason.
I hugged Young Master
for you.
For me?
This is Hot Night Incense I bought for you.
It can definitely let Young Master
fall in love with you.
So magical?
No.
But you still can't
hug my cousin.
I did that to protect the incense.
To keep it from Young Master.
But someone misunderstood and spread the rumor.
If you
don't believe me,
what's the point
for me to do this?
Miss,
this will be helpful.
Have a try.
Do you think Yunxi
has been flirting with me lately?
No.
I think you've been
amorous lately.
Me?
It's no use asking you.
After all, no woman
has ever liked you.
What is this?
Three quarter past 7 p.m.
Feiyu Pavilion.
I will be waiting for you.
I won't go.
Why are you so narcissistic?
Who wants to take you there?
Look.
She is still flirting with me.
Now she wants to meet me in private.
Why is she
so bold?
Does she really believe I am what she thinks?
You are a real gentleman.
Your character is worth learning.
Can you idiot learn this？
Get me some night snacks.
Yes.
Where are you going?
The washroom.
But why have you changed clothes?
Young Master.
You're going the wrong way.
The washroom is over there.
As long as we succeed tonight,
I will give you rich rewards.
Thank you, Miss.
With the help of Hot Night Incense,
we definitely can make it.
I'll wait outside
later.
As soon as he comes in,
I'll close the door.
So he won't be able to leave.
Then,
you can lift the gauze curtain,
and call his name.
With the effect of Hot Night Incense,
as long as he approaches you,
his lust
will be awakened.
Is he really gonna like me
because of this Hot Night Incense?
Be confident.
Don't doubt it.
Doubt?
Under the candlelight,
your charming appearance
is more attractive
than a fairy's.
Even without the incense,
Young Master will still have a crush on you.
He has arrived.
Let's go.
Arrive?
Go. How does he come so fast?
This way.
Hurry.
I'll go out first.
OK. Go ahead.
Yunxi, I'm coming.
Oh, no.
The incense is pleasant.
The atmosphere is good too.
You're really good at planning.
Good.
Since you like it,
please have fun.
I won't bother you then.
At this moment,
you really want to leave?
Or
you want to get something?
I'll wait for you.
Tell me.
How do you want to play the act?
Act?
Young Master.
So you've already known.
He has found out?
You're making it
so obvious, so straightforward.
Even a fool knows it.
How could I not understand?
Since you know,
it's easy now.
The effect is amazing.
Looks like the money is worth it.
Young Master,
please.
Let's begin.
What are you going to do?
To do what you want to do the most.
Oh, no.
The effect of Hot Night Incense
is beyond magical.
Young Master even has a feeling for me.
Young Master.
Look carefully.
It's me. Yunxi.
I know.
I know you are Yunxi.
You're a special person.
You helped me a lot
in the city construction.
I appreciate that.
But in love,
you are a miss.
You should be more missish.
Young Master.
I know.
These days,
you've been trying to flirt with me.
All this implies
that you like me.
Young Master, you misunderstood.
How could I like...
Don't explain.
Alright.
Let me tell you the truth.
I'm here today
not to give you hope.
I just don't want
to waste your time.
I have to tell you something.
You have to follow the rules in my mansion.
You should be patient sometimes.
In the future,
you are expected to be gentler,
and more reserved.
I'll give you another chance.
Young Master, stop it.
You two have gone too far!
Oh my god.
You...
Why are you here?
Miss, listen to me.
Shut up!
You liar!
You lied to me
that you would set me up with my cousin.
And you are flirting with him at the same time.
All my trust is in vain.
You have played with my feelings.
Today,
you embarrassed me even more.
You...
What?
Don't be rude.
Just you wait.
Miss.
My shoes.
Fine.
It is not you who want to express obsession.
Young Master, you misunderstood.
I was helping Miss...
Forget it.
Miss Fengyi
can't forgive me now.
Young Master,
please help me.
You deserve it.
Why am I so unlucky?
I have offended two great lords.
It's all Jiang Chaoxi's fault today.
He was out of his mind and speaking nonsense.
In the future,
you are expected to be gentler,
and more reserved.
I'll give you another chance.
Yunxi!
I thought about it all night.
Finally, I figured it out.
You've been treating me like an idiot.
You can't stay here anymore.
Jiaobai, go!
Yes.
Miss!
Miss, let me go!
Lie down. None of your business.
I'm not going to get up.
Let go of me!
Come here.
I'm not leaving.
Leave!
Let go of me!
I'm not leaving.
I was invited by Young Master.
So only he can force me to leave.
You're here for my cousin indeed.
Since you don't want to leave.
Jiaobai,
come.
Since you don't want to leave,
you have to kneel
until I'm not angry.
Yunxi.
What happened?
Get up.
Qing, I'm fine.
Leave now.
I'll kneel for her.
Since you care about her so much,
you can kneel with her.
-You... -Qing.
Calm down.
I have to find my brother.
Young Master.
Why are you so angry?
It's raining.
You...
Young Master.
Bad news!
Miss Fengyi is punishing Yunxi.
That means Yunxi deserves it.
What has she done to Young Master?
Yunxi,
you are frail. Get up.
It's raining heavily.
You can't take it.
I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
I've told Commander Xiao and the Chairman
to demolish Jianjia Alley
and build a commercial market.
They showed no objection.
Since there is no objection,
it's settled.
Young Master.
Anything else?
What should we do
about the people in Jianjia Alley?
Young Master,
Commander Xiao has already chosen a place
outside the city
for those people.
At the same time, the Planning Department
will pay compensation
to them.
When will the compensation be paid?
Young Master.
Tang Qing wants to see you.
What's the matter?
He
wants you to save Yunxi.
I don't want to meet him.
And I don't want to save Yunxi.
Yes.
How is it?
He said he didn't care about Yunxi.
Go back.
I'll talk to him myself.
Stop!
Don't put me in a dilemma.
Fine.
I will not.
Get out of my way!