What is Sun Cheol up to?
He's studying, of course.
Yes, yes.
It's the midterms.
He studies hard to prove himself to you.
Yes.
So, why are you punks loafing around here?
Why don't you study together?
We were going to go now, anyway.
Let's go.
G-Grandpa,
if Sun Cheol is too busy to come,
we'll keep coming.
Huh?
Let's go.
You little bastards.
Have you...
been at least eating going around?
Hey, I can't do this.
Why? What do you mean?
They said they'd call us when they got the knife,
but we haven't heard from them.
It's Yun Ga Min. He'll figure it out.
We let some juniors
we don't know take care of a friend of 10 years.
Aren't you embarrassed we're just waiting?
I feel like shit, for one.
Don't act like you're the only loyal one.
Didn't you ask them, knowing this would happen?
Don't go if you don't want to.
I'll go alone.
You can't just say that, you bastard!
You heard from the doctor, too!
Grandpa can pass away anytime now.
At least, his last image of Sun Cheol
might not be someone f***ing great,
but he shouldn't be a scum. Right?
You f***er know how to talk.
Let's go and reclaim...
Grandpa's hospital fee.
Yes, that's right.
And Chae Seon Ho, that f***er.
Let's get back the money from the car sale, too.
Idiot.
Bastard.
Son of a b****.
[Study - Join if you want to study!]
[Hwang Min Hyun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Woo Min]
[Lee Jong Hyun]
[Shin Su Hyun]
[Yoon Sang Jung / Gong Do Yu]
[Study Group]
Let go! Let go!
Shit.
Let go, Strawberry Head!
Go ahead and say it again.
Was it "Go, go. New person"?
I'm different than Jang Bi Hwan, and
Guk Gwan Wu, those idiots, okay?
They got scared because
a detective threatened them a bit.
The juvenile jail?
So what if you get a criminal record?
It gets you a badge.
So, tell me now, okay?
Tell me why you guys came in here.
Shit...
Shit.
Hey.
Your school uniform looks like Heukchang High.
But I've never seen you before.
I haven't played tag with a girl in a while.
What you're holding
isn't something a girl should want.
I think she knows something.
Let go, you pervert!
Shit. How embarrassing.
Wow, you have a pretty face,
but you can't stand losing, can you?
F***. Let go of me, I said.
Keep doing that.
Seeing that look of hatred
turning into a look of fear
is the most thrilling.
You piece of trash.
You'd pass out, too.
They must've locked it securely inside.
How about Jun and Ji Wu?
You can't reach them yet?
No. We lost them almost at the same time.
Everything should be fine, right?
I can't hear his reply.
Hey, Yun Ga Min. Yun Ga Min?
He's answering.
Ga Min?
Se Hyeon, what's wrong with this?
Hello? Ga Min.
Huh?
Hello?
Ga Min?
[Ms. Lee Han Gyeong]
- Ms. Lee?
- Yes.
Is the exam preparation going well?
The thing is,
there's an error in the practice sheet
I gave you earlier today.
Can you have a look right now?
Well, right now?
Why? Are you out?
No. Of course, I'm home.
Just one second.
[1-4, Yun Ga Min]
Hello? Hello?
What's wrong with the phone?
Where did they go?
Huh? What did you say?
Ga Min.
Ji Wu?
What about her?
No, Ms. Lee.
I'll call you back in a bit.
Okay.
Yun Ga Min, are you there yet?
Geez. Hee Won, go to the rooftop.
Okay.
What? What?
What? Did it hit something?
What? This isn't right.
"Hee Won's"?
What do we do?
We'll get caught, won't we?
What do we do? What about them?
We can't even reach them right now.
What do we do?
Hee Won, we should go there.
- Where?
- To save them.
Pack your things, Hee Won.
Hey.
Send the backup fighters back home.
Okay.
Why are you here now?
Tell me. Why did you kill him?
We got into a fight. So, I did it on impulse.
You really killed him, then?
You don't have to worry.
Just say, "I'm the culprit." That's it.
The company will get you an attorney.
We'll take care of the rest.
You serve three years like that
and join our family.
Everyone would be happy, right?
[Deputy Kim Sun Cheol]
Put this away...
and take out what's in there.
In your inner pocket.
We're not forcing you at all.
The decision is up to you.
Yes, I killed him.
On impulse during a fight?
Yes.
You stabbed him three times on impulse, correct?
You've got to be kidding me.
Where's the knife, then?
I threw it away.
Where?
My attorney will talk to you.
So, you're saying you got into a fight and
you stabbed him three times to kill him on impulse
and your attorney will tell me about the knife?
Yes. I'm sorry.
No need to apologize to me.
By the way, can it be this easy?
Pardon?
Can you give up on your life this easily?
I'm sorry,
but there was only one stab wound.
H-Hold on.
I think I was mistaken.
- At that moment-
- Okay. I hear you.
I'll ask you one last time.
You'll make the decision.
Think carefully and answer.
Did you really kill someone?
I'll die in peace if I saw my grandson
become a great man.
Won't you study?
Hey.
You can't be here right now, can you?
Let the girl go.
Was that an order?
For me?
Shit...
If you decided to act up,
you should've at least brought your underlings.
You thought you could fight me one on one?
His underlings are here, you son of a bitch!
Don't laugh, you bastard.
You're dead after this, too.
The knife.
The knife!
Stupid bastards.
They don't know what matters.
You're totally f***ed now.
It would've been nice if you went to jail
as you were told to.
Hey, why did you try to be clever...
and give up on the easy fortune?
Shut up, you son of a bitch!
Why is everyone from the Yeonbaek Gang the same?
Shit!
I didn't want to lose my cool over some kids.
You f***ing bitch and bastards.
Why don't you do as you're told?
Why won't you? Huh?
That crazy bastard.
Who are you?
You're that four-eyed loser.
Four-eyed Psycho!
He's holding the evidence.
Give me a break. What are you, Bruce Lee?
What age do you live in?
Don't insult Bruce Lee in front of me.
Four-eyed Psycho, look at you go.
Yun Ga Min!
You don't use a nunchaku in an actual fight.
And it's so heavy, too.
What's this?
That?
It's an aluminum nunchaku that costs 5,000 won.
It wasn't a lie that you destroyed the scouter.
Brace yourself.
You're next.
Okay.
Let's go.
Shit. Four-eyed Psycho.
Hey! Bruce Lee, are you shocked?
You wanted to show up like a savior
and destroy everyone.
But it didn't go as planned, right?
Sun Cheol.
So...
did you think you just needed the evidence?
You should've turned yourself in
and gratefully taken the reduced sentence.
No way.
I even brought my nunchaku
because I heard you're very strong.
But you're too weak.
What?
You tried to ruin
someone's life with that strength?
You asshole.
Fajin, a fist stabbing method
comes in three kinds.
One is Cheokgyeok,
where you attack from a 10-inch distance.
And there's Chonggyeon,
which is often called a "1-inch punch."
And...
a punch within a less than 1-inch distance.
[Uncle's Forbidden Technique No. 4]
The ultimate fajin.
[0-inch punch]
[Bungyeong]
Hyung.
Are you okay?
Hyung, let's go back to school
and study together.
- Study?
- I know you want to study, too.
Can I do that?
Can I pretend...
to be an ordinary student now?
That bastard.
I knew it, you son of a bitch!
I wish I could kill him, but I can't.
Live a long, painful life, idiot.
Hey, ear piercing.
It's just studying.
Why make such a big deal about it?
No one's that interested in you, okay?
You hesitate when you're doing something bad.
Got it?
Right.
Shit!
Who the hell is the crazy bastard?
Look who's here.
Mr. Na Tae Man?
You f***er.
It's not Mr. Na Tae Man. Detective Na to you.
I get scared by a cop for no reason.
Are you alone?
- What is it?
- Your confession. What else?
Mr. Chu Seong Wung,
the culprit of the Ancheon Port murder.
What the hell are you saying?
Kim Sun Cheol is the killer
for the Ancheon Port murder.
Didn't he turn himself in yet?
Don't blame the wrong person and-
You don't let me speak nicely to you.
Fess up while I'm being nasty to you.
Shit. You son of a bitch.
I came to get my notebook back,
but I detected a chance.
[Study Plans]
The fate-deciding midterm is finally here.
Stop looking at the answer sheet, idiot.
Don't pass them over yet.
Yuseong Tech High's midterm.
The questions are ridiculously easy.
Are they not discerning, then?
I can hear your eyeballs moving.
They are.
Hey, No. 1 for Question 9?
Question 9?
Give me a break! No. 3 for Question 9!
- No. 3.
- She's my type.
I chose No. 5.
- No. 5 for Question 9-
- No. 3.
I chose No. 3.
- I told you, you crazy bastard!
No, it's No. 1.
Is it? Is it No. 3?
No. 3 for Question 9.
[5]
- Whoa.
- Geez.
- Give me that.
- Why No. 1?
Not all of my answers are right-
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I got one, at least.
[Yun Ga Min]
We got the same thing!
We can all check later.
- But why?
- I chose No. 3.
"Here we go"?
Was it, "Come on now"?
It's "Go, go."
"Go, go! New Person!"
Stop the young bloods from joining Yeonbaek Gang.
A rehabilitation project for the youth.
Give me a break.
Were you influenced by Na Tae Man?
Gwang Hyeon, get your act together.
You know what I mean, right?
- Pardon?
- Has anyone volunteered to join?
It's still at an early stage.
See?
I'm telling you.
I guarantee no one would participate.
Hello.
I'm here to change.
Sunbaenim.
Ms. Jeon, I heard you were discharged today.
How are you feeling?
I feel even better because I finally got to rest.
You must be tired from caring for the kids, too.
It's very difficult, but it's fun.
By the way, don't the exams end today?
Yes, they ended today.
Is everything okay?
By chance, has Ga Min...
told you that he's going somewhere?
He's not home, and he won't pick up.
He was going out
with his friends because the exams had ended.
He's going out?
It'd be better if he didn't go anywhere today.
Right now! Right now!
I'm bored. Should we play a round, too?
The lowest scorer buys ice cream.
The three of us?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Hurry.
Whoa. Not bad at all.
He's pretty good.
He's good.
Is it my turn, then?
Here comes Lee Jun!
- What the heck?
- I did...
100 pushups daily for a year.
We can't just let him do this...
No! That's our study group's money!
Pardon?
It'd be better if he doesn't go anywhere today?
Why?
Every year,
there are four days I don't bother Ga Min.
It's when the midterms
and finals end in each semester.
He acts strangely after checking the scores.
He can't focus on anything, and he's a bit...
Yun Ga Min, score lower than 300
and pretend the machine is broken.
So, he'd believe it. Okay?
Let go!
My hard work won't betray me!
I guess he can't control his strength.
Shit.
We'd be having endless meat
at a buffet if we went with the plan.
- Sorry.
- It's okay. It's okay.
The owner said he planned to get a new machine.
Gochujang, you're actually the one to blame.
Why did you have to be so stubborn?
I'll open this for you. Don't be angry, okay?
Eat, eat. It's my treat.
We already paid. What do you mean?
Are you worried it'd be lower than you thought?
- Huh?
- Aren't you worried
about the exam results?
Yes, I thought it'd be different this time.
By the way, I don't understand it.
You get at least 20 points from
guessing the multiple choices.
How's your average score 10 points?
He doesn't guess when he doesn't know the answer.
- Are you joking?
- Why not?
He doesn't think he deserves the score by guessing.
Geez.
Ga Min is the best.
Guys, I have a quiz for you.
Okay.
What happens when you boil water?
Yes, Yun Ga Min. You answer.
Me?
You can eat ramen.
- Wrong.
- Really?
The answer is, "Nothing happens."
Huh?
Water starts bubbling and creates opportunities
when it reaches the boiling point.
But nothing appears to be happening until then.
So what?
- Huh?
- What?
So, what I'm saying is...
Until you reach the boiling point,
you might think nothing is changing at all.
But...
if you put energy into something steadily,
a big change has to happen eventually.
Whether that's water or studying.
It's from a text I read yesterday.
[010-0021-9621]
Is it tasty?
Hello?
Dae Cheol?
Sun Cheol isn't with me right now.
Why don't you answer, you bastard?
Hurry up.
Grandpa is in a critical condition.
I need to take the exam!
It's about to start soon.
Please wait a moment, sir.
We'll take you there once Sun Cheol comes.
Grandpa.
I said I can go on my own.
Kim Sun Cheol, you f***er.
Where are you going after taking our jobs away?
Shit.
You agreed to cover for Chu Seong Wung.
You should've said you killed, no matter what.
I was about to join the family. What will you do?
I have no time.
Shut up and come at me.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, you're ready, right?
You...
Hurry up and get up. It's time.
Kim Sun Cheol, that bastard.
Hey, what took you so long?
Don't open the door.
Move.
Grandpa...
is taking an exam right now.
Ms. Lee got him
the TOEIC exam sheet from last month.
Thank you.
That's how
our first exams in high school ended.
And...
Grandpa's last exam ended, too.
♫ Filled with my dried-up dreams ♫
♫ If I look at you silently ♫
Hey.
If you meet Sun Cheol,
teach him how fun it is to study.
I think you could do it.
♫ I sit blanking out and shed tears ♫
Grandpa, Sun Cheol already knows...
that studying is fun.
♫ All by myself ♫
♫ As long as someone could hear it ♫
♫ Is there anyone by my side? ♫
♫ Maybe I already knew ♫
The moment a person stops learning,
their life stop, too.
♫ Even the warmth is gone ♫
♫ I stayed up alone that night ♫
♫ Some days pass by ♫
♫ As if they're mocking me ♫
Thank you,
Ga Min.
♫ I close my eyes while being paused ♫
♫ In a painful memory ♫
♫ I fall asleep after wandering a while ♫
♫ All by myself ♫
♫ As long as someone could hear it ♫
♫ Is there anyone by my side? ♫
One, two...
three!
Gosh, this is amazing!
Mine is, too!
Gochujang Head, why are you better than me?
I'm smarter than you.
Shit.
Wow.
That's what a top scorer's report card looks like.
I'm a joint No. 1 with Ho Min.
Wow.
Stop acting modest.
You're so annoying.
Daebak! Yun Ga Min is No. 209 out of 220.
His ranking went up by 10!
- Wow, really?
- Wow!
Ga Min!
Congrats!
Wow, he did it!
Good job!
[Yuseong Tech High's Study Group Improvement]
If I improved all of their rankings by 10,
you promised to help me hold
a disciplinary committee for Pi Han Ul, right?
[Notice for a disciplinary committee meeting]
[Subject: Pi Han Ul]
What's this?
- Pi Han Ul?
- What's this?
Pi Han Ul?
Who is it?
Look. Whoa...
Students' vehicle stops at the gate.
Get off and walk.
I'll study the whole time.
- What?
- What's this?
- It's Pi Han Ul. Pi Han Ul.
He's walking?
Is he crazy?
Hey, Pi Han Ul!
What will you do now?
The disciplinary committee is on you now.
Keep your neck clean until then.
[Study Group]
♫ My name on top ♫
♫ Parking lot, backyard, rooftop ♫
♫ I turn them into my stages by standing there I'm yawning ♫
♫ I'll let you sleep soundly as if you're on vacation ♫
♫ I go after my goal with a pure look ♫
♫ I don't want to see a loser in the mirror ♫
♫ Make more plans ♫
♫ I have no doubts ♫
♫ It's pretty funny that you ask why ♫
♫ You throw an egg on a rock ♫
♫ Looks like you don't get it ♫
♫ Look at my grades, I bet everything ♫
♫ My growth rate is high ♫
♫ I throw a fast breaking ball, slider ♫
♫ Yeah, I'm a rider ♫
♫ When I go low, look down ♫
♫ Or keep your mouths shut ♫
♫ I'll sink a goal like in football ♫
♫ I enjoy pain, I'm addicted now ♫
♫ I'll embrace it and go further like a bulldog ♫
♫ Cut it off, please ♫
♫ Set me oh, free ♫
♫ Just bring me closer and closer ♫
♫ Run it off, I got my hoodie on me ♫
♫ Let me go, let me go, let me go ♫
♫ Cut it off, please ♫
♫ Set me oh, free ♫
♫ Just bring me closer and closer ♫
♫ Run it off, I got my hoodie on me ♫
♫ And imma make it up from this hood ♫
♫ From this hood ♫
♫ Go on and poke me, it's your loss ♫
♫ Take it, pass out instead of breathing in and out ♫
♫ I'm not interested in a childish fight at all ♫
♫ If you want to touch me, you'd better think twice ♫
♫ Because my life is a mountain of my assets ♫