[Lee Jun / Yuseong Tech High, 10th grade]
You might not believe this, but I'm bad at fighting.
Why am I so bad at fighting?
Is it because I'm weak?
Or is it because I'm not trying hard enough?
When I was devastated that my fighting ability wasn't improving,
I discovered a new method.
I want to become f***ing strong.
If you want to become so strong,
go to Yuseong Technical High
and fight against the best fighters of Ancheon.
What are you saying?
[Welcome to Yuseong Technical High School]
[No. 180]
[No. 173]
[No. 139]
[No. 17]
No matter how much I tried, I couldn't go above No. 17.
But it's too early to give up.
[Study Group Application - Conquer Yuseong Tech High]
I still have the last method I haven't tried yet.
Wow.
[Study - Join if you want to study!]
[Hwang Min Hyun]
[Han Ji Eun]
[Cha Woo Min]
[Lee Jong Hyun]
[Shin Su Hyun]
[Yoon Sang Jung / Gong Do Yu]
[Study Group]
- Hey, Yun Ga Min!
- "Conquer Yuseong Tech High"?
Conquer by fighting, did he mean?
- Hey! Hey!
- Wouldn't it be weird to think he meant studying?
I know.
He must be really good at studying. I'm jealous.
Yun Ga Min, hear me out for a second.
I'm sorry, but I started the study group to study.
Not to help you go up in ranking in fighting.
This is studying, too.
Fighting study.
Fight with me just once, then.
If you don't want to, teach me how you normally train.
Otherwise, I'll study, too-
Will you really?
- Huh?
- Will you really study?
Yes. I will.
I have to.
We'll visit Ms. Lee at the hospital.
Solve all the problems while we're gone.
Is it a test?
Yes.
Hold on. I'm almost done.
[Basic Math]
Are you Yun Ga Min?
Pardon?
Follow me. It's for a test.
T-Test?
Aren't you Yun Ga Min, the No. 1 in the 10th grade?
Yes.
I am Yun Ga Min.
Long time no see, Detective.
I know.
I haven't seen you since that case last year.
By the way, why are you at Yuseong Tech High, of all places?
Hey, stop.
Stop it, I said.
Are you okay?
Anti,
why am I so weak?
What are you talking about?
You aren't weak. You haven't become strong yet.
I believe you'll become powerful and protect me someday.
I'll be in your care then, Lee Jun.
I passed the test.
I'm in Yeonbaek Gang now.
So, don't look for me anymore.
Get off.
I'm Oh Jang Ho, the scouter of the YB Family.
This is a test to scout a reserve soldier,
a backup fighter for the Yeonbaek Gang.
The Top 3 students of each school can take a test, and they only get one chance.
Shit, I'm so good at saying these lines because I say them all the time.
Listen carefully. The goal is simple.
You see that car over there, right?
If you grab the car key on the hood,
not only will you become a reserve soldier of the Yeonbaek Gang,
but you'll own that car, too.
What do you say?
The goal is simple,
but it won't be as easy as it sounds.
This isn't a f***ing kid's play or something, right?
Some people will stop you from doing that.
They're your sunbaenims who passed the reserve soldier test recently.
[Jang Bi Hwan, 17 / Yeonbaek Gang's reserve soldier / Criminal record: Theft]
[Seo Yu Bi, 18 / Yeonbaek Gang's reserve soldier / Criminal record: Attempted murder]
[Guk Gwan Wu, 17 / Yeonbaek Gang's reserve soldier / Criminal record: Aggravated assault]
There are no rules.
Get the car key, no matter what it takes.
If so, you'll take the first step into a successful life.
Are you ready?
Did you get tricked by that bullshit?
Start.
Come at me, sons of b****es!
I bet he ran away.
- Where did he go?
- What?
See? I said he won't be here.
His eyes said otherwise.
Give me a break.
He dyed his hair red like gochujang.
He's obviously a thug.
What do we do?
We told Ms. Lee that we got all five members.
I'm hungry. Let's just go get food.
I even got him a brain supplement, too.
Yuseong High kids are high quality.
They don't just call them a thug academy for no reason.
But this strawberry-head bastard...
No. 1, Yun Ga Min,
I thought you were the monster of Yuseong Tech High.
Was that just a hoax?
By the way,
are you really Yun Ga Min?
I don't know how you had the audacity to do this,
but regardless of who you are,
as the result of the Yeonbaek Gang reserve soldier test,
you didn't pass.
But it's not over yet.
You should pay for wasting our time.
That's how the world is.
[W College Prep Academy - Math 1 Mock Test]
Lee Jun,
as the result of the study group test,
you passed.
They're Yuseong Tech High kids.
They're idiots but loyal.
You're an idiot for being a thug.
Aren't you embarrassed for doing that at your age?
These babies are fearless.
Are you acting cheeky because you think
you can tell a police officer?
Jun, come here.
You're Yun Ga Min.
You don't know yet because you're just kids.
The law isn't in your face,
but the pain is.
- Stop it.
- Yeonbaek Gang's reserve soldier test.
Should we restart it?
You'll pass the test if you come and get this.
By the way, Pi Han Ul left as soon as he came to the station that day.
He even knew my name even though I was newly appointed.
Isn't that kind of strange?
I don't know. Is it really strange?
Are you sure the job is getting done?
This police station, I mean.
Don't overreact.
He's just a high schooler.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Don't try too hard. Just go home.
Yes, that's how normal kids behave at a police station.
By the way, what do we say inside?
Not sure.
Let's go inside first. It'll work out somehow.
Aren't you scared, Se Hyeon?
Of course I am.
I came here because I was too scared to go with those guys.
But the police station isn't as scary as the thugs' hideout.
- Let's go in.
- Okay.
[Munjeon Police Station]
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Four-eyed Psycho, guard your glasses well.
Your mom will be worried.
I don't know what makes you so cocky,
but in the end,
the one with a knife is stronger.
You f***er.
Knowledge is stronger than a knife.
You f***ing bitch.
I've never seen anyone block the Four-eyed Psycho's punch.
No. 1, Yun Ga Min.
The rumor was true.
Because I'm doing this with high schoolers here,
you must've underestimated me.
What?
Did you get punched on purpose?
He must be in pain from being beaten.
- Don't step on him.
- Was it to make me move my foot?
Give me a f***ing break.
Wow, what a cool club.
It's not a club.
It's a study group, okay?
F***, I need to stop smoking.
Hey, High Schooler.
By the way,
he pretended to be you to take the test.
He can't even fight.
He'll obviously get in your way.
Why are you defending him so much?
Ouch.
You can't use that technique any more.
That's not fair.
Anyway, your kicks are more powerful than usual. Is something wrong?
[Sewun Middle School Level Test - 8 points]
Eight points?
Why won't my grades go up, no matter how hard I study?
[Hanrim Gym]
I wish you had one of those.
- A reference book?
- No, it's better than a reference book.
What is that?
It makes you work harder,
it makes you do your best passionately,
and it makes you change.
I'm asking you what that is.
[W College Prep Academy - Math 1 Mock Test - 24 points]
Twenty-four points?
Not bad, right?
He's a serious contender.
What's important is that...
he actually solved them without guessing.
I finally found one.
Jun isn't in my way.
He's more of a rival.
Jun, don't get the wrong idea.
I've never thought of you as a rival.
It's okay to use that on you, right?
- What?
- My uncle told me to never...
use this technique because it's too dangerous.
Kid, don't do anything dangerous.
No. You'd be in danger, not me.
[Uncle's Forbidden Technique]
[One-sided attack]
Hey, the scouter of the Yeonbaek Gang.
Can we talk for a second?
Hey!
That's crazy!
I thought the car was empty.
He almost got hit.
No, they were actually trying to hit him.
Bingo.
Hey, Yun Ga Min,
are you interested in joining us?
You'd make a perfect reserve army manager.
Reserve army manager?
How would the losers of Yuseong Tech High make a living?
- Don't you agree?
- No.
Wow, how loyal.
We'll go to college.
What? College?
Hey, are you out of your mind?
Geez, he's so my type.
Hey, do you go to their school, too?
Do you go there to pay condolences?
Or was it in the will?
Open it!
Park Geon Yeop?
Huh? What was that?
Shit, sons of bitches.
F***.
Get in. Get in.
Okay.
Okay. Get their testimonies.
Okay, okay.
That kid is safe, too.
Gosh, what a relief.
Wow. That evil bastard.
A high schooler caught a member of the Yeonbaek Gang?
Hey, what's wrong?
We didn't do anything wrong.
The police should give us a medal or something.
Right, right.
We did nothing wrong.
We reported them, too.
That's enough. Stop.
What? You never know.
That could help our college admission.
- Really?
- Medal, my foot.
"The law regarding assaults and their punishments."
- Be grateful you aren't being arrested right now.
- Pardon?
You should've reported immediately if something was happening.
Don't you see that ambulance over there?
He was getting beaten to death. How would we report?
You mean violence can't be justified in any way, right?
Y-Yes, he's smart. He gets it.
What a ridiculous man.
But that only applies when the authority is operating properly.
The system is very diseased right now.
Well...
I can't praise you as a detective,
but it's not like I can't punish you, either.
Anyway, I'm sorry...
that a thug came to your school.
Call me immediately if anything happens.
I'll even stop pooping and run to you.
He's not a piece of trash, at least.
Right, Four-eyed Psycho?
Where did he go now?
What?
I'm on my way right now.
I'm on a bus.
Did you forget to come back by 10?
The thing is, a friend was in danger.
So?
I'm sorry, Mom. I'll never be late again.
You remember you went to Yuseong after promising me, right?
Of course, I remember.
Oh, really?
This really will be the last time. I promise. I mean it.
Thankfully, it ended well.
We gained an advantage thanks to the study group kids.
Using the Yeonbaek Gang members' testimonies,
we could find out more about Pi Han Ul.
Okay.
Anyway, it looks like you and the kids
are bringing a new change to Yuseong Technical High.
We're in your care.
No, I'm in your care.
Be safe.
You'll be in danger from now on.
Yun Ga Min even beat up the scouter.
[Lee Han Gyeong]
He's definitely above average.
Shit! Shit, I died.
Whoa, four stars?
It's been a while since you gave four stars, right?
Things will get interesting.
[Yuseong Tech High Study Group]
Yun Ga Min, shouldn't you be doing this?
- Wow.
- Why isn't Gochujang joining, by the way?
Did he run away?
That can't be.
Someone just read.
[Jun 2]
Are you feeling okay?
Don't you worry about me.
Thank you for today, everyone.
Idiot.
[LOL]
Is the study group finally complete with us, five members?
What are we supposed to do now?
Yun Ga Min, say something.
Study 14 hours a day?
Do you want to die?
[How to be good at studying]
Let's watch this one.
- This?
- Yes.
Guys, guys. Look.
I think it's highlighted.
[Math 3, Korean 2, English 3]
[Math 6, English 6 / Korean 1, Math 1, Korean 1]
- Gochujang, you've been fined.
- You're right.
Four-eyed Psycho, how much will it be?
The five of you.
Come here. Come here.
What's this now?
Who said you don't have to wear a jacket?
It's still winter dressing season, you brats.
I'm wearing a jacket.
Go back home.
Are you kidding me right now?
What? You don't want to? Do you want penalties, then?
Penalties?
I thought the jacket wasn't mandatory anymore.
- Ms. Lee!
- Ms. Lee.
It's the winter dressing season until May,
but the mixed dressing period starts on April 20.
The school rule must say it's okay to wear the spring uniform.
The disciplinary committee should know the rules, at least.
Go in.
Idiot.
Thank you, Ms. Lee.
By the way, are you already discharged?
Yes, I'm fully recovered.
- What a relief.
- That's such a relief.
Thank you, guys.
Hey, is she the legendary Ms. Lee, who got stabbed to protect a student?
Yes, she's in charge of the study group.
Wow! The study group is the best!
Our teacher got stabbed, even.
You punk.
Don't talk about Ms. Lee like that.
I don't know what's wrong with Jun.
You must be Jun.
Yes, I'm Lee Jun, ma'am. I respect you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
Guys, I'll go see the Vice Principal.
You go ahead.
- Okay.
See you.
[Yun Ga Min / Kim Se Hyeon / Lee Ji Wu / Choi Hee Won/ Lee Jun]
[Application for a School Club]
You somehow got the members.
Thank you, Vice Principal.
What happened to the Lee Hyeon Wu case?
He was sent to the juvenile hall last week.
- How about what I said?
- I rejected all the reporting requests.
Good job.
Everything was resolved.
And regarding that, there's a second page.
What kind of nonsense is this?
[Students: Pi Han Ul, Lee Hyeon Wu]
Sir, will you just ignore Pi Han Ul like this?
Please schedule a disciplinary committee meeting.
Our study group was officially approved as a club.
We'll get our own room, too, soon.
- A study group room?
- Yes.
We'll start our activities now.
The first one will be-
- Choosing the main member?
- Shut up.
A Study Group exchange meeting.
Exchange meeting?
You'll meet with students like you who are studying in study groups,
hear their experiences, and learn.
- Wow.
- Are we going to Seoul, then?
Hi.
Are you going on a trip somewhere?
- How about yourself?
- Shut up?
Hold on.
Is he out of his mind?
White rice and gochujang?
What?
Are you country bumpkins visiting Seoul?
Geez, what the f***?
Shit, what the f***?
Hey! High schoolers!
Why don't you respond when I'm talking to you?
Hey, cuties. Where are you from?
Do you want us to show you around Seoul-
Shit...
We're from Gwangyeok-si.
Kneel.
We'll never look down on country bumpkins...
Oh, I mean, the residents of Gwangyeok-si.
We'll never look down on the residents of Gwangyeok-si.
Say it together.
We'll never look down on the residents of Gwangyeok-si!
One more time.
We'll never look down on the residents of...
- Guys.
- Gwangyeok-shi!
Hey, Ms. Lee is coming.
Disappear on the count to three. One, two...
Thank you!
What? Were they Jun's friends?
No.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
By the way, where's Ga Min?
Don't even get me started.
He must've been nervous to meet smart students.
He stayed up all night and woke up late.
Isn't Four-eyed Psycho so extra?
I know. We aren't going anywhere that impressive.
Ms. Lee, isn't this a university?
Can lowly people like us go in?
Guys, why are you intimidated already?
Ms. Lee Han Gyeong.
Hey, Sunbae.
- Who's that?
- Don't know.
Guys, say hello.
This is my college senior and...
a teacher at Manil High, Mr. Park Wu Yeol.
You must be Ms. Lee's students.
Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Sunbae, what's the plan today?
Wow, she sure is the legendary Ms. Lee.
Sunbae? He's clean-cut.
By chance, are they flirting?
T-They must've been that thing. A campus couple.
Guys, it's not like that.
Let's go now.
And text Ga Min to come straight to Manil High.
- Okay.
- Hey, come quickly.
- Okay, okay.
At Manil High, most students are in at least one study group.
The school supports them so they can study on their own.
And Manil High is an elite high school that's on the same level as
Hwamun High, Chaehwa Girls' High, and Kangwon National University High.
Do they send a handful of students to elite universities?
We send about 200 students a year.
- Wow.
- 200?
Not bad.
They sure are impressive.
These are our study group members.
And this is the group leader, Hong Jae Hee.
These are the Yuseong Tech High students I mentioned.
Hey, you can hear it, right?
I think I did.
I'm not the only one who heard, "Who are these idiots," right?
Hey, what are you saying? No one said that.
Right. They didn't say, "idiots."
Guys.
Everyone is here, right?
Yu Jun Min isn't here yet.
Really? Jun Min is often late these days.
It's okay. We're waiting for a student, too.
Really? How about you guys chat
to get to know each other?
What a nice study group room. I'm so jealous.
Right?
But we'll get a room soon, too.
They must take notes using tablets.
Look. The pencil case has a passcode, too.
They use unusual pens, too.
That has ink that vaporizes.
If you write down the answer with that, they disappear the next day.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yun Ga Min would lose his mind if he saw that.
Hey, you can hear it, right?
Of course.
They're disgusted by us.
Because they're smart.
Why isn't Ga Min here yet?
Are you sure you texted him?
I texted him in the group chat.
[Come to Manik High in Yeonggeungpo]
Hey. It'd be hilarious if he went to "Manik High."
There's no way that school exists.
[Manik High School]
[Manil High School]
If it's a school with a long history,
it must be this one, right?
[Manik High School]
[Study Group]
Dramaday.me