You meant to–
I just love you.
You’re my best friend.
And that will never change.
What I did was disgusting.
If it’s disgusting, then both of us are disgusting.
Yes?
I’ve checked the CCTV as you asked
and got the bike that ran you over in it.
(Already forwarded to you.)
(You can check it out.)
Okay.
(You’ve seen it, right?)
(Yeah.)
You’re with Botpleng now, right?
(If yes, )
(don’t say anything.)
(Don’t let him know)
(that you know that guy is Tanu)
(who used to work for Khitakarn, his mom.)
Thanks for the ride.
Are you not going in with me?
Inspector Dao pretended not to know
about me pretending to be Thunphob
out of my request.
The one who should feel most guilty
should be me, who tricked you.
That’s not what it is, Tankhun.
It’s not that I don’t want to meet
Inspector Dao because of you.
I’m just afraid.
I’m afraid that the more the truth is unveiled,
there would be more things
that make me regret what I’m doing now.
You should get going.
I should head to the office now.
SUSPECT.
VICTIM.
The first victim of the murder was found
where Botpleng asked you to meet.
As for the second case,
there’s a relation in the means of murder
and the weapon used.
The latest one.
Your assault case.
I’ve looked into it and found that
the attacker was Tanu
who used to work for Khitakan,
Botpleng’s mom.
You’re saying that the link between the cases
is that they’re related to Botpleng?
I wouldn’t think so
if I hadn’t found additional information
that the second victim was a clerk
when Botpleng’s dad was a sheriff.
Not to mention Thunphob, Botpleng’s lover.
That’s enough.
SUSPECT.
If you were to suspect.
VICTIM.
You should be suspecting that
Botpleng’s a victim.
I saw Tanu attacking Pleng.
Are there any other reasons
for you to protect him?
Botpleng is your brother’s lover
not yours, isn’t that right?
Where did you get your scholarship from?
When we studied criminal behavior analysis
in the UK,
where we met.
The scholarship grantee would be so upset
if you’ve forgotten something so basic.
Tell me,
why would Tanu,
who could kill so cold-bloodedly
and so organized in his murder
would do something so reckless
like attacking Botpleng and me
and got caught by the camera?
Well.
It’s DID.
You still fail to pass the second test.
Wanting to win so much
that you leave the citizen in danger.
Even if Tanu really had DID,
it doesn’t provide the answer that.
Botpleng’s family is behind this
and that Botpleng wouldn’t be in danger.
You didn’t let me tell Botpleng about Tanu.
Can you still remember what you said?
If Botpleng is in danger,
will you be able to handle the responsibility?
But I won’t let Botpleng be in danger.
If this is what you need to know.
(If Botpleng is in danger, )
(will you be able to handle the responsibility?)
(But I won’t let Botpleng be in danger.)
I have both you and Tankhun
who care about me.
Are you really okay?
I don’t know.
I’ve been looking for my first love for so long
just to find out that.
I’ve fallen for this brother.
While the first love I’ve been looking for
died while he was looking for me.
I just want to be happy.
I want to be as happy
as my current memory allows.
Because I don’t know
what the memory that’s about to return
will bring to me.
Why are you following me?
Are you okay?
Hey!
Pleng!
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
The cut didn’t hurt.
The tetanus shot hurts more.
Don’t wander around alone next time.
It’s so…
dangerous out there these days, isn’t it?
You can send it to me.
Okay.
(If Botpleng is in danger, )
(will you be able to handle the responsibility?)
(But I won’t let Botpleng be in danger.)
I can put charges on you.
Go ahead.
You knew I wouldn’t dare do it.
That’s not it, Tankhun.
I did it because of Muenmile.
If I didn’t trust you,
we wouldn’t have come this far.
One more thing,
you’re even the brother of my lover.
But Muen is also someone important to me.
Ever since my mother fell into a coma,
there was only he who stayed beside me.
Being my only friend.
I just…
I just have enough confidence in you
to prove to my friend that.
I’ve trusted the right person.
You really knew I wouldn’t dare do it.
When you met Tanu last time
you had a panic attack, too, right?
Yes.
Any other symptoms?
I was afraid.
But it was controllable
unlike the first time.
Afraid?
But…
I wasn’t afraid that he would attack me.
It was fear that came from my gut.
It was like…
It wasn’t the first time I’ve seen him.
You’ve met Tanu before?
I can’t remember.
I don’t know or believe I’ve ever met
both the person in the picture and you.
The police said he used to work for Mom
so I thought you could know him.
That means you’re investigating something
that involves my family?
There’s nothing much.
He’s just a suspect in a normal crime case.
We just want some additional information.
But you’re not a police officer, aren’t you?
Though my husband passed away,
our family still has disciples
and those who work closely with us.
I don’t like people doing things
that are not their jobs
and use the name of the police
just to ruin their reputation.
My apologies.
I just happened to be investigating
how Thunphob,
Botpleng’s lover and my brother, had died.
So I asked him to bring me to you.
My real question is
do you know Thunphob?
I have no obligations
to answer this question.
Send your lover’s brother on his way.
Don’t forget your doctor’s appointment.
Don’t make me remind you.
You really knew my lover.
Why didn’t you or Mom mention him before?
Even you can’t remember
who would fancy helping you remember?
Grandma was really hiding Thunphob from me.
But your grandma wasn’t lying.
Both about not knowing Tanu
and about Thunphob.
So that means
my family is really not involved in this.
Or your grandma was lying flawlessly.
I thought you would take my side.
The way you did when talking to Inspector Dao.
A human’s heart is beyond fathom.
Just one behavior can’t tell everything.
I’m just trying to read into all the conflicts
and all the possibilities.
If you say so,
then you must think my family’s involved.
Aren’t you afraid I’d kill you in the woods?
I’m saying this
because I care about you.
Your grandma looks so unkind to you
that it worries me.
If you’re wondering
whether Grandma could hurt me,
I would say she could, without Mom.
Grandma loves Mom dearly
that it extended to me.
Though we never talk nicely,
she always cares about my treatment.
The doctor you mean is…
A psychiatrist.
Grandma wants me to get my memory back quickly.
I need your help.
Are you back already, Mom?
Mom!
If you’re feeling alright,
slowly tell me what you saw in your dream.
It seemed so real this time.
It was…
It was like it’s my memory.
It didn’t seem like a dream.
I was in a small, old house.
I was lighting up a charcoal stove.
And…
Mom.
Didn’t seem like her, but she was walking in.
It could be a lucid dream.
A dream when you’re conscious,
but it feels so real.
You had a memory loss
so you might get confused.
Theoretically speaking,
this kind of dream will lower your sleeping quality
and could be dangerous in the long run.
Then, I’ll give you some prescriptions.
Yes.
It seems like Mr. Pleng’s memory
is coming back.
Is that so?
Botpleng’s memory should be returning after all.
Boss!
What is it?
Someone asked to see you.
Who is it?
Hello.
I’m here to interview you.
I brought you some centella juice.
It’s pretty hard to find.
Is there any subtext in giving me this?
Just testing out the water.
See how you’re healing after a heartbreak.
Just say what you have to say.
Tan couldn’t contact Botpleng.
He wanted to come himself
but he sent me because he knew
that you won’t do anything.
I’m not the type to attack anyone.
Also, Pleng and I are done.
We - are - friends.
Then you can tell us where Botpleng is.
No.
Nothing to it, though.
The reason I look confused
is because I thought Pleng
was with your brother.
I couldn’t contact him for 2 days now.
Are you really going to do this, Tan?
Yeah.
There’s no other way.
Pleng.
Who?
(Then you took him out of the house so easily?)
(There was barely anyone there.)
(Isn’t that strange?)
(I only know that Pleng’s Grandma
doesn’t want anyone in her house.)
(I didn’t know she would go this far.)
(There’s no one on guard.)
(The other day, when I was on a lookout, )
(I saw some housekeepers)
(and a nurse who came and left on the same day.)
(I was surprised too.)
Pleng.
Are you awake now?
How are you feeling?
You keep making that dumbfounded face.
Can you remember me?
What the hell are you doing here?
And…
What happened to me last night?
Why do I feel so confused?
Um… let me do some initial testing.
Everything’s normal now.
Pleng said he’s just going to call his grandma
just to prevent any trouble.
Normal?
Really?
Why does he seem like he can’t remember
his conversation with me?
The human brain has a complex structure.
Pleng lost his memory in an accident
many years ago.
That could leave a chronic illness
or other factors that prevent the memory from returning.
Normally, a human brain might work 100%
but Pleng’s brain might only work at 80%.
Then, when he lacks sleep
or when other things are affecting him,
it could cause a temporary symptom too.
The forgetting things part might be normal
but going unavailable doesn’t seem normal.
Grandma wanted me to go live abroad
but I refused, so we fought.
Then…
I took some pills to help me sleep
then I was slipping in and out of sleep
and dreamt about things when I was young.
Slipping in and out of sleep?
Can you remember when you were awake?
I can’t.
I knew I was awake, but it was always blurry.
What kind of pill did you take?
I don’t know.
I only know it made me very sleepy.
Did you see the doctor?
I didn’t.
Are you suspecting something, Jen?
It seems like part of a hypnotizing process.
Some use it to bring back memories.
To help you bring back your memory.
If she really wanted me to remember things,
why did she not tell me anything
about the house in Korat?
She never took me there
and didn’t even let me go there.
You’re right.
It really seems conflicting.
If she really wants you to remember things,
why was she trying to stop you
from thinking about the past?
So what were you seeing the doctor for?
What if it wasn’t for you to remember things
but for you to forget certain events?
Jen, is this possible?
It is.
Even making you forget the triggering factor,
that missing memory,
how important could it have been?
What are you thinking about?
About the missing memories.
I’m curious.
What kind of memories was it?
Why does no one want me to remember it?
Can you believe it?
Before Mom fell into a coma,
I was so happy.
Mom used to say
it’s okay for me not to remember anything.
I only realized it now
that she never wanted me to remember.
If Thunphob were here.
I think he would want you to remember.
What about you?
Do you want me to remember?
The me now
is probably the same as your mom.
If it hurts so much that you need to forget,
then I
don’t want you to remember it.
Yes, Inspector?
(I found the link between the serial murders
and Thunphob’s case.)
I’m fine with you protecting your brother’s lover
but bringing him along to listen to all this information,
I think it’s too far.
It’s wrong, Tankhun.
I promise I won’t tell anyone.
Also, I’m not here today as a journalist.
I’m here today as someone who’s involved in this case.
I know
that all the cases involve me as the link between them.
I want nothing but the truth.
Even if it has to be squeezed out from
the truth everyone wanted me to forget,
I will do it.
Then if there’s anything wrong with this case,
you can go and bear the shame
along with your being the best of the class
all this time.
The mechanic found this attached to the wheel hub when they detached it.
After examining it,
it’s the same as the weapon of murder in
the first and second cases.
So can we now conclude
that the murderer has DID
and the prime suspect is Tanu?
Or the behavior might not have been conflicting.
Leave.
Unless you want to die.
Are you okay?
Because Tanu never hurt me.
Even when he got a chance, he didn’t do it.
Tanu is the suspect in Thunphob’s case
and the other two cases.
All of them are part of Botpleng’s family.
Tanu doesn’t harm Botpleng
but also doesn’t want him involved.
This resonates with what Madame Ked is trying to do.
Why do they all do that?
Maybe it’s to protect
something that’s in your memory.
Maybe there’s something they didn’t want anyone to know.
If we could access that secret
maybe we don’t have to force Pleng to remember.
Then you’re lucky, Tankhun.
FILE
WIND POWER CONCESSION.
15 years ago,
Sheriff Petchkla, Botpleng’s dad
was reported for fraud in a wind power concession.
The two victims of the murder cases
were part of the fraud.
I might be making too complicated a hypothesis here.
But isn’t it possible?
That Thunphob could have found that out
so he was murdered to silence out.
Surely, the memory of your own family
killing your lover
is probably not something
anyone would want you to remember.
I’ve never thought that one day.
I’d think I’m lucky to have lost my memory.
It was just a hypothesis.
That’s what I’m afraid of.
I’m afraid it’d be even worse.
Pleng.
I agree with your Grandma.
You should live abroad for a while.
MADAME KEDSARA.
Hello, Inspector Darakorn speaking.
(I’m Kedsara.)
Do anything to stop the police
(from digging up the wind power concession case.)
Yes, Madame.
Wait up.
Here. Help me out.
Do you want me to file it away?
FILE
WIND POWER CONCESSION.
File what away?
I’m going to dig up this case
and you have to help me gather the information
so that I can bring it to the superintendent
then set up a special investigation team.
Here.
What’s wrong?
You’re my idol.
What?
I’m right on it!
Your hair is so soft.
I always have my hair washed at the salon.
Whatever they used there,
That was probably it.
Then you’d better have it washed at the salon.
It’s not like your place makes it easy for me
to wash it for you.
It does.
Because I have you with me now.
One more thing,
I don’t want you to be alone.
I know now
why Thunphob wanted to be you so badly.
Because your heart is so big and warm.
Are you going to pretend to be me, too?
I can’t have it anymore.
No.
I just want to be in it.
You’ve always been in there.
Hey, Tankhun.
Let’s eat.
You know how to cook?
I never knew it either.
But after I could light up the charcoal stove,
I wanted to try.
Turns out I knew how to do it all.
Thun told me you don’t like vegetables,
just like him.
He didn’t like it because he hated chewing it.
While you don’t like it because it’s bitter.
I don’t know about that.
I now like both chewing it
and the taste of it.
Is there anything?
I’m memorizing this Botpleng.
The one who likes vegetables.
Knows how to light a fire.
Likes green tea.
Who couldn’t understand how leaves
can sound like a melody.
I’m scared you will forget.
It’s not bitter at all.
I definitely won’t forget.
Why are you writing on it
when it’s about to be removed?
Because you’re removing it soon.
If I wrote it from the start
and the ink seeps into the cast and ruins it,
your arm could be infected.
Alright, I got it.
Mr. Tankhun.
Please come right this way.
I’ll be right back.
Good luck.
Um, excuse me.
Could you take a picture of the cast for me?
Before you remove it,
I want to see what he has written.
Sure.
Here you go.
Thank you.
(Good luck.)
(Love you.)
(Goodbye.)
(I don’t want to be everyone’s Botpleng anymore.)
Put that down.
That’s twice now.
That you snuck into my house.
For you.
Both times.
I’ve decided to never see you again.
Don’t bother me.
Why?
Because I’m not him.
I’m not Botpleng, who likes vegetables.
Who can light up a fire.
Who can forget Thunphob
and love you.
It’s not just about how we can fall in love.
But how can I live?
If I have to hide my true self?
I can’t even remember
what happened in the past.
I told you.
I will make you remember.
No matter what your memory holds,
I will be with you.
What if it were me who killed Thunphob?
What if it were me who killed your brother?
What would you do?
I will hold you like this.
Whatever you ask.
I will do it for you.
If you want to remember,
I will help you remember.
Even if you can remember things
and forget about me,
I will remember you.
No matter
what your memory holds,
I will love you.
In the past.
In the present.
Or in the future.
Who are you?
Where are you?
Which identity is my true self?
Pleng!
I know him.
I think I love you enough
for my other identity to realize.
I will always be the second violin in your Canon in D.
So I became Botpleng.