The
the
現在我們 bought your run
Jesse
vity
Yes, I don't care.
I take care of those little cats and dogs every day.
I'm so busy.
Brother who has no poison,
you'd better come back and take care of them.
Only a little bit.
Everyone risked their lives
to steal these ashes.
Not for the money.
For the love of the Mermaid Guard,
the World Guards, and Zhang Mu.
Thank you.
My Lord,
we'd better go to do something early.
And make our way safe.
He knew it so soon.
Princess Li Cheng said
that the friendship between Yin Ni and Master Ren
would make a good leader
even if he couldn't find the bones.
She also said
if you have a little conscience,
you must help her
to make a good name
and worship Master Ren.
She knew that I was a good person.
Let them stop.
I'll find a way to see Master Ren.
You can get him out
when you get out of the palace.
Wait for a few hundred bowls.
Then seal the entrance.
Do we really have to seal it all?
Whether I'm a good person or not,
I don't allow anyone
to disturb her peace
before I come.
Even if I'd rather see her
in the middle of the night,
it's impossible.
Let's go.
When will Zhen Yi come back?
Your Majesty,
His Majesty called back His Highness's edict
and it was only passed out a few days ago.
I believe His Highness will receive it
in a few days.
You will see His Highness soon.
Very good.
Come.
I was strict with you before.
But that was for your own good.
I hope you can help me in the future.
Help Second Brother
to build up the country of Great An.
The reason why I gave you the edict
is because you also mean that.
Your Majesty,
I'll send you here.
Take it.
I know you've been in trouble recently
and need money.
Thank you, Your Highness.
By the way,
His Majesty has decided
to let Princess Li Cheng be the Crown Princess.
You don't have to tell me that.
I'm treating you well
not to get information from you.
But I can't just leave without knowing.
I'll go.
What do you want?
Can't I find you when I'm free?
I'm an orphan now.
It's easier to act now.
If you become the Prime Minister,
you'll have more reasons to see me.
It's inconvenient in the palace.
I've been in the palace for so long.
Can't you see me?
You have time to go horse riding with Chu Yue.
Don't you have time to visit me in the temple?
If I remember correctly,
you arranged this marriage
for me personally.
Didn't you?
You said these things
on purpose, didn't you?
I told you that
our cooperation is the cooperation between me and Sha Xi.
But now,
this person has become Chu Yue from you.
Do you love Yue?
You asked me to come here
just to ask these boring questions?
These questions
may be boring to you,
but they're important to me.
Answer me.
Or I won't help you anymore.
No.
She doesn't love me either.
Are you satisfied?
Do you love me?
You don't know?
I don't know.
Once you ask me some questions,
you're destined to get the answer you want.
So you've been using my feelings for you
to catch me
and let me help you,
right?
At the beginning,
didn't you want to know about the late queen
and approach me on purpose?
Why do you have to say such a bad thing?
Don't go.
I don't want to force you to do anything.
If you hate me,
we'll never see each other again.
Tong Guang.
For so long,
have you ever
loved me
even a little bit?
Very good.
Since you're unkind,
don't blame me for being unkind.
Get out of the palace now
and listen to that woman's words.
Who?
Who else?
The princess Li Cheng
you saved from the fire
without any effort.
What did you do?
A woman who wanted to take my place
and take yours.
What do you think I would do to her?
If anything happens to her,
I'll definitely
make you pay for it.
Protect the princess!
Hold on!
We must protect the princess!
See if there are any who pretend to be dead.
Don't let any of them go!
Search!
Find the princess!
Yes!
Search!
Watch out!
Yuan Zhou
Lin Mian
You're alive.
Is it you?
Is it really you?
Lu Yi Qian, you're really alive.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you come to me so soon?
I was worried about you every day
and almost cried my eyes out.
Where's my brother?
Where's my brother? Is he safe?
Don't worry.
Your brother is fine now.
Liu Daotang received the news
that he has passed Gui De Garden
and is heading to He County.
And a while ago
I had already sent An Li and the others
to rebuild the An Gui Pavilion.
With their help,
it will definitely go smoothly.
That's great.
Lu Yi,
what exactly have you been through?
Gui De Garden
Do you really have the heart
to let Li Tenguang know
that you're still alive?
My heart is already
in your hands.
What's in front of you now
is Ren Ruyi.
You're so ruthless
and heartless.
We're both heartless.
Your stabbing me
doesn't count as money.
According to the book,
the left is the heart of the people,
and the heart is different from the ordinary people.
The right hand is in the chest,
and not the left.
So when Cheng Tian was attacked
in the fifth year of spring,
he was able to see through the chest,
but he didn't die.
You let me stab your left chest.
You did it on purpose.
But I won the bet.
The bet is that you still have
a sense of righteousness and dignity.
You helped me.
You didn't let Andy
know about my death.
And I'm lucky.
Zi He survived.
I don't know
why I helped you.
Maybe it's because
of what you've done all this time.
You're like a hero.
Let's meet by ourselves.
Take the medicine.
So that's how it is.
This Deng Hui is a gentleman.
I was badly hurt this morning.
I was thinking
I'd come to you when I was free.
But I didn't expect to hear
the signal of the Sha Xi tribe
calling the people to attack at night.
I thought it was a horse farm nearby.
So I couldn't help but come to see.
My people have been watching Li Gong.
I heard that Li Tenguang's men
brought you out.
So I rushed the guest over.
But it was too late.
Yang, Yuan Zhou didn't protect you.
What are you talking about?
You escaped from death.
You rushed back to Andu
for me day and night.
I was so touched.
How could I blame you?
And I know
you never leave me alone.
Let's go.
Okay.
My people are waiting outside.
Ruyi, you have to work harder.
We'll rush to the guesthouse
and drive three hours.
Then we can get rid of
An Jun's pursuit.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
I want to go back to Li Gong.
Back to Li Gong?
Why?
You've probably already known
the order from Andi.
Whether to marry the second prince
or to marry him,
I'll be the future
of this country.
Ruyi, Yuan Zhou,
I don't want to go back.
You've turned the little sparrow
in the jade cage
into a eagle.
I can't go back.
Ying, you can't be impulsive.
It's not a child's play.
The political situation in the country is complicated.
Andi is ruthless.
You'll be dead if you stay.
And the one who just came to kill you
is probably the one sent by the Noble Consort Chu.
The deep palace is full of doors.
We're not by your side.
What if Her Highness's tragic story
is repeated?
I have the value of using.
Andi won't kill me.
I grew up in the cold palace
of the Wu Kingdom.
The bitter and sweet in the palace
and the evil plan,
how could I not know?
Don't worry.
I'll be more careful
and safe.
I want to go back to Wudu with you.
But what can I do
after I go back?
In the future,
I'm still just a gold sparrow
in the palace of the Wu Kingdom.
That's not the life I want.
You'd rather die than do it.
I have it, too.
And I've killed people.
Wouldn't I be the first to kill?
I've been the king for so long.
In the past few months,
I've been following you
through so many people and things
from Wudu to here.
Seeing you,
Brother Qian, Du Zhangshi,
and them,
to save my brother,
to put in all kinds of efforts,
even risk my life.
I've figured it out.
If I stay here,
and can fight for the peace
of our two countries,
even if it takes three years,
or five years,
it's worth it.
You've grown up.
I'll listen to you.
Okay.
Take this.
If you encounter an emergency,
go to Jinshan Road or Jinbaozhan
to find Meiniang.
Okay.
My people are outside.
The only place where Andu branch is located
is called Ye Guang.
You can trust him.
If you need anything, go find him.
Okay.
By the way,
we've already taken Mr. Du in.
He heard that you insisted
to come here.
If he can accompany you
to the Li Palace,
we can be more assured.
And,
take this puzzle.
If you encounter any danger,
your brother will receive the news
and come to save you immediately.
I'll let Ye Guang
arrange the rest.
Don't worry.
I'm Ning Yanzhou's sister.
I'm Ren Ruyi's disciple.
I won't embarrass you.
I believe
our little Ying
has always been the best.
Ruyi,
if you have a little niece,
call her Ying, okay?
I'll give her
all my best jewelry.
Okay.
What?
You won't give it to a boy?
I like girls.
I'll listen to you.
In my previous life,
the luckiest thing was to meet
a gentle and kind empress.
In the future,
little Ying will also have the same luck.
Let's go.
Take care, Ying.
You too.
Don't worry too much.
With Ye Guang and others,
it must be safer
than sending Ying back
to our two court prisoners.
That's right.
Where are we going now?
Sheng Sha and others are heading to Hexian.
We'll go there as soon as possible
and meet them.
Great.
I miss them too.
Let's see if Yuan Xiaolu
will listen to us.
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing
that I don't have to
go to you
with my whole body.
I can come back to life
in time.
It's the happiest thing
in the world.
If time is like a wave
It's like a wind
Who and I are going to travel far away
The sky is full of clouds
You are mine.
Love is the yellow rain between the two of us
Life and death are ordinary
We are only at the last step.
When he sends Sheng Sha back to Wu Guo safely,
we will leave everything behind.
From then on,
we will be ordinary people.
The world is big.
We can go wherever we want.
Okay?
Okay.
But
according to
what did you forget?
I didn't forget.
The sound of heartbeats
Yang,
Did he mention me?
Yes.
He heard Sha Xi's voice.
He came here because you were worried about something.
So he rushed here without thinking about the injury.
But he didn't expect it was me.
I knew it.
Go!
When we arrive outside the gate,
are you sure they can open the gate?
Don't worry.
When we arrive outside the gate,
we will call the guards to open the gate.
You just need to hide in the mountain.
Don't let the guards see you.
Okay.
I believe you.
Your Highness.
Do we really need to open the gate and let the guards in?
When the gate is opened,
there will be a fight between the two sides.
This place is cold and poor.
I am dying here.
It's none of my business if I fight or not.
Father would rather let me go.
You don't believe that I didn't kill the boss.
If so,
don't blame me for learning from father
and working with the traitors.
Please open the gate and let the traitors in three times.
This is a big crime.
Nonsense.
The North has a hard time.
I talked with the King of Youxian.
This time,
as long as they get enough gold and food,
I will ascend the throne.
I will kill thousands of people every year.
But...
Shut up.
You forgot that you and I
were trapped in the stock market
for three days and three nights
to find the food to repair the gate.
We were so hungry that we could only eat grass.
If it weren't for these traitors,
we would have died in this cold place.
I also know
those traitors
who think I am a fool
and don't care about my life
or my father.
Since they are heartless,
don't blame me.
Sun Lang.
Where are we?
Your Majesty,
the
Your Majesty.
Ren Luo.
Wake up.
Stop.
Your Majesty.
As I said,
can we see the
next city?
Brother Qian.
Forget it.
I have been driving all night.
I am a little bored.
Why don't we go with Qian Qing?
Yes.
Where is my wine?
Here.
Your Majesty, please wash the glasses.
I will go with you.
Brother Lang.
Brother Qian is too kind to His Majesty.
He even went to the police with him.
He even made you carry good wine.
His Majesty has been locked up for so long.
It's good to be the queen.
It's good to be a commoner.
Who doesn't have a noble hobby?
You can say you are lazy.
No matter where I go,
no matter how tired I am,
as long as I touch
the soft, fragrant, fluffy
little cat, little dog, little rabbit,
I will hug it in my arms.
I will...
Humph.
This is not a place
for showbiz.
Please take a closer look.
Qian Qing,
I can't see anything.
Have you ever thought
what the scenery
would be like
if the soldiers
who died in Tianmen Pass
were here?
This is...
That's right.
A few months ago,
His Majesty's army was defeated.
Brothers!
Today,
the blood of the dog emperor
will be on the line!
The blood of the dog emperor
When I open the gate
and make all the arrangements,
I will hang a red cloak
on my horse back.
Then you can lead the army
to the gate.
Your Highness,
you're finally back!
I've been looking for you
for days!
I didn't find anything.
I was injured.
Open the gate!
Yes!
Right.
Cover the wound
on the horse back.
What's going on?
Your Highness,
I couldn't find you
and I was worried sick.
The imperial edict
that summoned you back
arrived yesterday.
Your Highness,
hurry up and change your clothes.
What imperial edict?
Your Highness,
the eunuch who sent the edict
told me in private
that His Majesty
was going to marry the witch.
He said that
the witch is a woman.
His Majesty
is going to marry the witch
and will not leave the country.
Princess Li Cheng
will be the crown princess.
When His Highness
arrives in the capital,
he will be the crown prince
in the next nine years.
Congratulations, Your Highness!
Open the gate!
The ghost is coming!
Hurry!
Close the gate!
What should we do?
Are we running away?
Look carefully!
This is His Highness!
Your Highness,
what should we do?
Don't be afraid.
We will sneak out
of the North Sea to get your clothes.
Anyway,
the North Sea is going to the river.
We will sneak out of the river to get your clothes.
Anyway,
the North Sea is going to the river.
It was not our Da'an before.
It doesn't matter how many people died.
As long as my father doesn't know,
as long as the North Sea people don't let me out,
I can still be the crown prince.
I still don't have a way to get through the enemy.
Your Highness, let's go.
Let's go.
This way.
Iron Wolf!
Release the enemy!
Brother Lang.
What are you looking at?
You haven't come back yet.
Did something happen?
He hasn't arrived yet.
He can't die here.
Even if he dies,
he has to end the world.
Let's go and have a look.
Brother Qian.
Qian.
Don't come over.
Brother Qian,
what are you doing?
For the Chai Ming,
for the brothers of the Sixth Taoist Church,
for the countless soldiers of the Great Wu,
I'm going to make an explanation.
Qian,
calm down first.
That is His Majesty.
His Majesty?
If you dare to ask His Majesty,
I will tell him to stop.
Then I dare to ask His Majesty,
does he still remember those
souls who died for him?
The safe buttons of the Sixth Taoist Church.
Qian,
why are all the brothers' safe buttons
with you?
A move to get rid of the chaos.
If I don't keep their last thing,
who else will remember them?
Shi Xiaoyu.
She entered the Sixth Taoist Church at the age of nine.
She was once the fastest runner
in the Heavenly Path.
But she died in the battle
of Tianmen Pass.
She was killed by a blow.
She is only sixteen years old now.
Dong Dashan.
Twenty-one years old.
She was afraid of heat.
But she was burned to death
by the information of the Lord An.
Guan Qing.
Twenty-four years old.
She just got married before the battle.
But she never experienced the joy of playing with the child.
She was killed by Lord An.
She died of a heart attack.
Yan Jun.
To protect the Emperor of Gou.
On the 29th birthday,
Yan Jun was released from the battlefield
with his six long guns.
Gou Ping.
He was a drunkard for 33 years before he died.
But he was stabbed by his 18th gun.
He never drank the poison-free Dong Dashan again.
Qin Bin.
He was 48 years old.
He had no wife and no children.
He had experienced the battlefield of Rong City,
Tian City,
Pingying,
and Ju Langguan.
He died of 38 shots
in the battle of Tianmen Pass.
He was also the ruler of Da Wu.
I'm sorry.
What's the use of knowing you're wrong now?
Can you change their lives if you know you're wrong now?
Can you change my brother's life
if you know you're wrong now?
This Aimin...
This Aimin is your brother.
You don't know yet.
This Aimin
is my brother.
I hated him since I was a kid.
But he was so shameless.
He always tried to kill me.
He knew I was a part of the Yuling Army.
He tried so hard to get into Liudotang.
He said he could see me often in the palace.
No matter how I tried to find an excuse to punish him,
no matter how he looked at me,
he would call me
my brother
the next time we met.
I wanted to beat him up
a few more times.
When I was 20 years old,
I would stop beating him.
I would accept him as my brother.
But who would have thought
he was so good at the Heaven's Law
and was brought to the battlefield by you?
I'm sorry.
He would write me letters every day I went out of the city.
Brother,
I always try to persuade His Majesty
not to be too careful.
But His Majesty just wouldn't listen.
Brother,
His Majesty is too greedy.
We have to kill over 3,000 people every day.
I was the only brother in this world
who didn't have time to listen to me call him brother.
Just to protect you from the evil eye.
Your Majesty, be careful!
I stabbed you in the back.
I tried to kill him myself.
Right here.
I stabbed him in the back.
He was only 19 years old.
I'm sorry.
What is the life of the six realms?
The soul of the reincarnation?
What is the whole world?
The world is dead and the dead are alive.
From the day I set out,
I secretly planned to save you
and bring you here.
I used your life
to make the dead souls of the world see the truth.
Brother Chen,
the world is not a crime.
I understand.
You want to avenge your brothers and Brother Cai.
We want to do the same.
But have you forgotten
what Ning Tuo said when he handed you his body?
Do you deserve to be punished?
Brother!
Brother, calm down!
You dare to stop me
just for this bastard?
Who wants to separate in a lifetime?
The sky is dark and the road is slippery.
Looking back, the future is so beautiful.
The world is cold and the past is still cold.
Who will stay for the rest of their lives?
Who is drunk and worried?
The heart is tasteless.
Who wants to dream of the future?
Only for the wind to come back.
The world is cold and the past is still cold.
How many years have passed?
No one will be drunk forever.