♪In a world where
reality and illusion are uncertain♪
♪Piecing together fragments
of strange souls♪
♪Officially announced
as the lead players♪
♪The progress bar is only visible to me♪
♪Break the circle of fate♪
♪Ignore the system locking me out♪
♪Unveil♪
♪And sense who's more dangerous♪
♪I thought it was like other adventures♪
♪Yet I trust you with my back,
willingly leaping into this catastrophe♪
♪I just want the light of
the eternal night not to extinguish♪
♪Love gives me courage, crowns me♪
♪Before fate decides♪
♪Let the plot be rewritten for me♪
♪With you by my side on this journey♪
♪I'm not afraid of the unknown future♪
♪Before the eternal night falls♪
♪I seek the light of hope♪
♪The burning wish in my heart♪
♪Is enough to transcend the boundaries
of reality and illusion♪
=Love Game in Eastern Fantasy=
=Episode 32=
[Download Available now on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co]
How could this happen?
This…
(Qingyi Marquis Mansion)
The Prophecy…
The Prophecy has come true.
The Blood Moon in the sky reappears.
The catastrophe of heaven
is coming.
Hasn't the Resentful Woman
already perished?
Why is the catastrophe of heaven
still coming?
I don't know.
According to the ancient book,
the Blood Moon in the sky
is the source of the Resentful Woman.
But the Resentful Woman is already dead.
How can this still happen?
The Prophecy recorded
in the ancient book
should never be wrong.
Since it's coming,
let's save it one more time.
This time it's useless.
This is an ending
that was predetermined.
With our abilities,
we cannot change it.
What are you talking about, Miaomiao?
The ending,
we have already changed it
more than once.
Miaomiao,
did you know something?
The source of the catastrophe of heaven
is not the Resentful Woman,
but the person who created
this Demon Catching World,
the author of this novel,
Fu Zhou.
I am not Lin Yu either.
My name is Ling Miaomiao.
Actually,
I came from the world of Fu Zhou.
(Young Fu Zhou)
Fu Zhou is my favorite author.
I have read
all his journals and interviews.
He once wrote that, in his childhood,
he was not happy at all.
Your child has
Moyamoya Disease.
It is a relatively rare
progressive cerebrovascular disease.
From now on,
make sure the child
avoids strenuous exercise
and tries to minimize
emotional fluctuations,
or he may have
an intracranial hemorrhage,
(Ibuprofen Sustained Release Capsules)
which could be life-threatening.
At that time,
he did not believe
(Young Fu Zhou)
that people could stand together,
love each other
and understand each other.
It was during his most furious moments,
in his deepest despair,
that he wrote his first novel.
In that story,
(Catching Demons)
everyone was afraid of each other,
concealing their true feelings
from one another
until they fell apart.
He even personally wrote the ending,
(The catastrophe of heaven)
a doomsday that destroyed everything.
I finally understood.
The book "Catching Demons"
is not his new work,
but his debut work from childhood.
Fu Zhou said,
he always wanted to give his novel
the most perfect ending.
I know,
what I said
is difficult to understand for you,
but you must understand.
You must trust me.
Only this child
can stop the catastrophe of heaven,
- because…
- Because we are all characters in his book,
and he is the creator of this world.
Where can we find him?
In all the novels of Fu Zhou,
the ballads at the beginning
indicate the ultimate answer.
I think
this book should be no exception.
♪Red Moon♪
♪Round Moon♪
♪I carry a lantern under the moon,
stepping up the stairs♪
♪Those stairs lead to the heavens♪
♪Where a young immortal resides♪
♪The immortal sheds tears
without speaking♪
♪Tears fall on♪
♪The edge of the Milky Way♪
Little Shoot,
can you do us a favor?
What is it?
Let the whole world
hear our voices.
Cuicui is a bamboo forest now.
I did it!
Everyone,
we need all the power in this world
to build a ladder to the sky.
Everyone,
we need all the power in this world
to build a ladder to the sky.
All demon spirits,
all Demon Catchers,
please help us
save the world
that belongs to all of us together.
Come, move these things
to the Tianji Pavilion.
It is protected by the formation.
That is also the safest place.
Quick!
- Quick!
- Chief Wang.
Chief Wang,
what are you doing now?
- Chief Guo!
- What are you doing?
You come just in time.
I'm bringing these treasures
to Tianji Pavilion.
Come over and help move them.
Move…
The Guardian Master is building
a ladder to mend the sky,
fighting desperately for the world.
We need to use these to assist him.
What were you thinking
hiding them inside?
These are magical weapons
and national treasures.
No one can move them without approval.
I'm not wasting words with you,
give them to me.
No, no way.
- Chief Guo.
- Stop!
Supervisor Zhao, you come just in time.
He's abusing his power
for personal gain.
Stop speaking!
Let go. Give them to him. Just use.
If the world is gone,
what's the use of keeping
these treasures?
Demon Catchers
of the Astronomical Bureau, listen.
Yes!
Assist the Guardian Master!
Ziqi,
let's go to find him together.
Everyone, hold on.
Don't give up,
we can do it.
To save this world
requires everyone's strength.
Don't give up, we can do it!
To save this world
requires everyone's strength!
The ladder to the sky
is not long enough,
still a little short!
Ziqi!
Stand behind me.
Miaomiao...
Who doesn't care?
- Did you care?
- How could I…
- It's not...
- Have you taken care of him for a day?
Is he only my child?
Don't I have to work?
Where did these genes come from?
Without money,
how can I afford treatment?
Look at your family!
- What do you mean by "your"?
- Your family…
Now you're shifting responsibility,
aren't you?
You still want to leave now?
- I…
- You've never cared for him since his birth.
Since he got sick,
you haven't taken care of him
for a single day.
I have to earn money.
- Now you're blaming me.
- I have to earn money,
or how can we afford the treatment?
What's the point?
Let everything be destroyed,
isn't it better?
After all, the ending is the same.
(CT Medical Imaging Diagnostic Report
of Jingjiang Medical University Hospital)
Your child has
Moyamoya Disease.
It is a relatively rare
progressive cerebrovascular disease.
It is caused by an arterial blockage
in the basal part of the brain.
From now on,
make sure the child
avoids strenuous exercise
and tries to minimize
emotional fluctuations,
or he may have
an intracranial hemorrhage,
which could be life-threatening.
It seems like from the moment
of a person's birth,
his ending is already written.
Some people are destined
to play a supporting role in this world,
to struggle in the corner,
but they can't change anything.
The ending
can be changed.
What's the use of saying these things?
You are just a character in my writing.
You are also a supporting role
in this world.
Yes,
but when I believe
I can also love and be loved,
I am the protagonist of my own world.
I know,
for you right now,
the world seems like
an endless night without hope,
where not even a single star
can be seen.
(The catastrophe of heaven)
You will become a very good person,
bringing courage and hope
to more people.
Courage and hope,
I've never had them
and I won't have them
in the future either.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you have them before?
Show it to me.
Which color do you think looks best?
Try this one, it looks nice.
What are you doing?
This pen looks so nice, whose is it?
It got absorbed.
It comes in two colors.
It can really change colors gradually.
Really.
Right at the school gate.
- It's so beautiful.
- Miaomiao, is this your pen?
- Yes, it is.
- It's so pretty.
Isn't it?
Yiming, Qiqi is calling us.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I just went to ask the teacher.
The teacher explained,
but I didn't understand.
Why don't you ask the teacher
to explain it again tomorrow?
There are some parts
I didn't understand either.
Let's play soccer now.
Let's go.
(900 years ago, the catastrophe of heaven...
"Catching Demons")
At that time,
Miaomiao is like a sun,
illuminating your world.
She has saved you once
from the catastrophe of heaven,
hasn't she?
And her courage and hope
are also left by your side.
Was it you who reported to the teacher?
- I…
- Speak.
Speak up.
We have known it.
To be honest,
Pei Xiaocen,
what are you pretending for?
I tell you,
if you dare to report
to the teacher again,
you'll know the consequences.
Wu Nian!
You are bullying people again!
Do you think others don't exist?
Ling Miaomiao,
apologize.
I did nothing wrong.
Why should I apologize?
You all go out first.
- Goodbye, teacher.
Go to the infirmary
and apply some medicine.
Okay.
I can't teach you anymore, right?
Look at your exam paper.
It's all wrong!
You bully classmates
but refuse to apologize.
Do you know how bad this behavior is?
I'll call your dad.
Why are you covered in blood?
Are you alright?
Speak!
Miaomiao's dad!
I heard Miaomiao transferred schools.
Is it true?
I heard something happened
to her family.
It seems her dad was hit by a car.
Really?
Is it because of
Wu Nian's school bullying?
It's possible.
I… I'll help you.
She's leaving?
(With multiple students
telling the truth)
(and testifying,)
(after a serious investigation
by the school,)
(regarding the recent)
(school bullying incident,)
(Ling Miaomiao's right. I saw Wu Nian bully.)
(the Academic Affairs Office decides)
(all students involved in the bullying)
(publicly apologize to the victim.)
(The main bully Wu Nian)
(will be given a disciplinary record.)
(Other accomplices)
(in the bullying behavior)
(will be given a severe warning.)
Come out.
You don't need to hide inside anymore.
Who are you?
I am you,
but not entirely you.
You look so brave and powerful,
as if you're not afraid of anything.
How could you be me?
It's true.
The future you
will be brave
and powerful,
but not fearless.
But
no matter what you fear,
you can face it.
Really?
Yes.
Come on.
Come.
Save us.
I want to go to the future
you mentioned.
You will.
Ziqi.
Ziqi,
have you found him?
Can the catastrophe of heaven
be stopped?
This time,
I'm not sure either.
Fu Zhou is a gentle
and powerful person.
I have been his reader for ten years,
so I know him best,
- and he definitely...
- Miaomiao,
listen to me.
When I wrote this book,
I was not such a person.
You…
Are you saying
you are Fu Zhou?
Do you know
why someone like me,
sensitive, fragile
and desperate,
later wrote stories that were different?
Because I met you.
Every novel of mine
was written for you.
(Working Miao:)
(The only one who can surpass Fu Zhou
is himself.)
(Working Miao: The only one
who can surpass Fu Zhou is himself.)
(As a reader, I follow the protagonists
and their friends on adventures.)
(Their love, hatred and mutual redemption
move me to tears.)
(Fu Zhou's writing is so warm and healing,
thanks for creating such a magical world)
(that allows insignificant people like us
in reality to feel hope and courage.)
(Fu Zhou's writing is so warm and healing,
making people feel hope and courage.)
The surgery cannot be delayed
any longer.
Treatment must be expedited.
What a fool.
(Make exercise a habit,
make life more exciting.)
Hello, Zhang,
I'm planning to have an operation.
When you're facing life and death,
no matter how much preparation is done,
it's inevitable to have
lingering fears and wild thoughts,
wanting to escape,
wanting to end it,
wondering why it is me,
and thinking about
whether there is
a completely different life
in some world
unknown to me.
At that moment
I made three wishes.
First,
the original story
could be rewritten
into a beautiful ending.
Second,
the girl I like
could see my hidden true feelings.
Miaomiao,
I hope that you and I
can have a good ending.
I also hope
that you can see my true feelings.
I hope you can see
my hidden true feelings.
I hope you know
I've always liked you.
♪It's hard to explain the reason♪
♪Why I only care♪
♪About holding you close♪
System prompt:
The catastrophe of heaven
is approaching.
The Demon Catching World
is about to collapse.
You should leave.
No, Ziqi.
This is also my world.
I want to accompany you to save it.
♪Even want to change
my destined mission♪
♪Longing seeps into my bones♪
♪Yet there's nowhere
to grow old together♪
♪In this life, I've kissed your brows♪
♪I've been saved♪
♪Don't cry♪
♪I've held your hand,
tracing your palm lines♪
♪The wind and snow aren't cruel♪
♪In this chaotic world, you gaze at me♪
♪It's a scene of my rebirth♪
♪Loving you completes my life♪
♪It's hard to explain the reason♪
♪Why I only care♪
♪About holding you close♪
♪Countless threads of sorrow♪
♪Are banished when your tears glide♪
♪Countless people in the world♪
♪I just fall in love with you♪
♪Even want to change
my destined mission♪
♪Longing seeps into my bones♪
Ziqi!
♪In this life, I've kissed your brows♪
♪I've been saved♪
♪Don't cry♪
♪I've held your hand,
tracing your palm lines♪
♪The wind and snow aren't cruel♪
♪In this chaotic world, you gaze at me♪
♪It's a scene of my rebirth♪
The third wish is
to survive,
to run towards her
and tell her personally
that my courage was born because of her.
Miaomiao,
along this journey,
it was you who helped me
find myself again
and saved my world.
Now
I should depend on myself.
♪Don't cry♪
♪I've held your hand,
tracing your palm lines♪
♪The wind and snow aren't cruel♪
♪In this chaotic world, you gaze at me♪
♪It's a scene of my rebirth♪
♪Loving you completes my life♪
♪Loving you completes♪
♪My life♪
Dad,
last night
I seemed to dream about you.
Ling Miaomiao,
this is the PPT you made, right?
The client didn't sign the contract
all because of this PPT.
Look what you've done!
The first page is too short!
♪At this moment, everything fades away♪
(That night, I had a long dream.)
(Perhaps because I've read too many
supernatural novels.)
(In my dream, I became a Demon Catcher,)
(conquering demons, punishing evil
and promoting good.)
(Finally, I saved the world.)
(In the dream,
I seemed to fall in love with someone,)
(but I can no longer recall)
(his name and appearance.)
(Dreams are like snowflakes
in your hand.)
(The more you try to hold on,)
(the quicker they disappear.)
♪Dear, things are too shallow♪
♪Please take a look at me♪
♪See how I briefly descend with you♪
♪You are soaring bubbles♪
♪When the sunlight irons the outline♪
♪Does it resemble your eyes♪
♪When I look at you in my destiny♪
♪No need to set a time♪
(Fu Zhou's Signing Conference:
Love Game in Eastern Fantasy)
(Love Game in Eastern Fantasy Adapted from
the novel "Catching Demons" by Fu Zhou)
(Fu Zhou's book launch site)
(It's another Saturday.)
(Today is also a special day.)
(It's Fu Zhou's signing conference
for the reprinted debut work
("Catching Demons".)
(Although I think this book
isn't that great,)
(it's said that the whole book
has been revised.)
(The story is completely different now.)
(As a ten-year-old book fan of his,)
(of course I have to come
and support him.)
Did you see the ending?
The ending of this book
is incredibly exciting.
It's perfectly satisfying.
(Love Game in Eastern Fantasy)
Really?
Yes, I stayed up all night to finish it.
Every character, from the protagonists
to the supporting roles,
even a minor character,
has a particularly beautiful
and healing ending.
(Love Game in Eastern Fantasy)
♪You are my continuous fireworks♪
♪Illuminating my universe♪
(Love Game in Eastern Fantasy
Signing Conference)
Here, hold it.
Goodbye.
Ice cream!
- Ice cream!
- Delicious ice cream!
Delicious ice cream!
- Ice cream!
- Come and have a taste.
(Bamboo Tube Ice Cream)
Ice Cream!
So many people.
Come and have a taste.
This is Bamboo Tube Ice Cream.
Miaomiao!
♪You are my continuous fireworks♪
♪Illuminating my universe♪
♪Dear, things are too shallow♪
Mr. Fu Zhou.
- Coming!
- Mr. Fu Zhou!
Mr. Fu Zhou!
Fu Zhou is coming!
He's really coming!
♪You are soaring bubbles♪
♪When the sunlight irons the outline♪
♪Does it resemble your eyes♪
When do people
love the other one hundred percent?
(Love Game in Eastern Fantasy)
It is not when I love you
more than I love myself,
but only
when I truly like myself
and believe in myself,
can I love you
wholeheartedly and truly.
This book is dedicated to a girl.
She saved my world twice.
♪The sky in my eyes is
always dazzling blue♪
♪The departing ship raises its sails,
waiting for the wind♪
♪It says breaking through
layers of obstacles♪
♪Will lead to the stars and the sea♪
♪The fledgling bird at the cliff's edge
spreads its wings♪
♪How high must it fly
to meet the expectations♪
♪The waves say
the breeze will come naturally♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular
and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪
♪A flower breaking through the stone,
pure and soft♪
♪Open up an umbrella on a long journey♪
♪No matter where the wind comes from,
I'll look forward to it♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular
and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪
♪As the wind blows open the folded
crane-shaped letters♪
♪The yellowing paper
reflects forgotten wishes♪
♪I want to talk to the passionate persistence
I had back then♪
♪Thank you for not retreating♪
♪Thank you
for always guarding your beliefs♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular
and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪