=Love Game in Eastern Fantasy=
=Episode 17=
- Young Master Liu.
- There are still a lot here.
Your Highness.
Since you are unwilling to
get on the carriage,
I get off and walk with you.
(Why does she always follow us?)
Miss Mu, do you mind it?
- Sister Mu.
- No problem.
Young Master Liu, look,
Miss Mu has already said so.
You are guests at the Imperial Capital,
as the host,
can't I accompany you on a stroll?
Let's go.
Young Master Liu,
what are your usual interests?
What do you like to eat?
- She has so many questions.
- What do you like to do?
Can you tell me about it?
I…
Brother Liu doesn't have any interests.
He just likes to daydream alone.
Young Master Liu…
(When Sister Mu was subduing demons,)
(she could fight ten at a time.)
(Why is she so down today?)
(Never mind.)
(Today I will be)
(their love guard.)
If you like, I will dig it out tomorrow
and invite you to taste it,
how about that?
- I…
- Brother Liu doesn't drink alcohol.
He'll get drunk at one cup.
He can't drink.
Young Master Liu must like drinking tea.
You are so elegant,
you must enjoy drinking tea.
My Mother always said
that a woman knowing tea art
is truly graceful.
I never liked learning it.
If you like it,
I will definitely practice tea art well.
Do you need to learn?
I think your tea art is quite good.
Who are you?
You all take your time walking.
I won't be accompanying you.
- Sister Mu.
- Yao.
Young Master Liu.
- Your Highness,
- Yao.
I am a good friend of
Sister Mu and Brother Liu.
Since they have all left,
I will leave now.
Please walk at your own pace.
Stop right there!
I was speaking with Young Master Liu.
Why were you interrupting?
There should always be an order
to things, right?
Today, Sister Mu, Brother Liu and I
arranged first to go shopping here.
How dare you
offend Her Highness!
Do you know the rules?
Yes.
I realize my mistake.
- Please forgive me, Your Highness.
- You…
You have quite a sharp tongue.
You must be Lin Yu, the daughter of
the Taicang County Magistrate, right?
You know me?
Whoever it is besides Young Master Liu,
I must know.
You may rise.
Don't be afraid, I won't hurt you.
Miss Lin,
I don't blame you for today's events.
Then what do you want to say to me?
I want to say that,
in matters of mutual affection,
the order of arrival doesn't count.
And even if we consider
the order of arrival,
I met Young Master Liu first.
(Mount Zixia of Cainan)
Don't be afraid.
The demon has been captured
into the tower.
I'm fine.
Thank you for saving my life,
Young Master.
It was a mere trifle,
no need to mention it.
There are many demons roaming
on Mount Zixia.
You still have some distance
to go down the mountain.
Take this with you.
It will ensure your safety
along the way.
Please wait, Young Master.
Your Highness, don't.
You have a noble status,
how could you reveal yourself
before a commoner?
This is against the rules of propriety.
Later, I inquired along the way,
only to find out that
the Young Master's surname is Liu.
I always wanted to find him.
Blame me
for not stepping out of the palanquin
that day.
But now we have met again,
it is another chance
that fate has given me.
So I will never
let my pride and demeanor
keep me from the one I love.
But,
this…
Brother Liu's heart is
already filled with Sister Mu.
Before Young Master Liu makes a choice,
I want to let him know openly
that I like him.
I want him to know
that I am also an excellent woman
and worthy of his affection.
(Classic Artworks)
(Marquis Mansion of Imperial Capital)
My Lord,
please stop sighing.
You have sighed
for the eighth time today.
Going out from the main gate,
there are many women.
Though there are many,
none is whom I'm missing.
Jiu,
do you know what it means?
East.
What do you mean by "East"?
My Lord,
it is "Going out from the east gate,
there are many women".
Why are you a damper now?
Don't you see I'm missing my beloved?
All my beautiful mood
was ruined by you.
So I will still persist.
Close the window.
Wh…what's wrong, My Lord?
Bad luck.
Why isn't the Princess staying
in the palace
but wandering around aimlessly?
What are you waiting for?
Close the window!
Don't let her see me!
Bad luck.
My Lord,
Miss Lin is downstairs.
Look.
Miss Lin?
Is this shrew bullying her?
Take it slow.
Even if you hate me,
even if the whole world laughs at me,
I don't care.
Li Songmin!
What are you doing?
Don't bully Miss Lin.
Zhao Ruoshi?
Why are you everywhere?
Marquis, why are you here?
Li Songmin, you're getting bold.
You dare to sneak out of the palace
to stroll around.
I'll go back and tell your Mother.
Let's see if she scolds you.
Alright.
You're bold now.
You dare to report me now?
Stop looking.
Turn your head away.
Turn away.
Li Songmin,
I'm telling you,
if you behave,
just go back to the palace.
Be gentle!
You hurry back to the palace.
I won't tell your Mother.
I'll beat you to death.
You, let go of me, don't hit me.
You dare to threaten me?
You have quite the nerve, don't you?
Li Songmin, I don't mind you bullying me.
You are not allowed to bully Miss Lin.
What if I bully you?
She… she didn't bully me.
Miss Lin, you don't need to be afraid.
It's alright.
I… I'm not afraid.
Take care of yourself first.
She didn't bully you?
No.
Move aside.
Your Highness,
it's getting late.
The Dowager Consort should have
woken up from her nap.
Perhaps she's going to visit you.
Return to the palace.
Miss Lin, are you alright?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You know why I said
I didn't want to marry Her Highness?
She is just a shrew.
But I think
Princess Duanyang is quite nice.
Don't speak of her like that.
Even if you don't like her,
I believe in the future,
she will find someone who likes her.
As long as it's not Brother Liu,
that's fine.
Marquis, you are safe now.
I will go find my friends.
Oh my,
how can she see the good in
someone like Her Highness?
She is so kind.
No.
I will never fall in love with anyone
in this lifetime.
If you had not
fallen in love with father,
you wouldn't have ended up
in this situation.
You wouldn't cry
from night till dawn every day.
What good is there in loving someone?
I don't want it.
I don't want to be like you.
What exactly is going on?
Is a confession really that difficult?
There's clearly only a thin layer
of window paper left for their love.
Great!
(I understand.)
(The romantic scene where they fell in love
in the original work)
(was messed up by me.)
(So I must create)
(another new romantic scene for them.)
Respected Cuicui, please sit down.
Cuicui, you are knowledgeable
and experienced.
Do you know any place
in the Imperial Capital
that is romantic
and has a good atmosphere?
It's the kind of place
where once you enter,
you feel as if you're truly there,
your heart flutters
and you can't help
but confess to your crush.
What are you going to do?
The Astronomical Bureau
just released an oracle
stating that from tonight until tomorrow,
it's not advisable to travel
or move around.
Why?
They say
before Phospherus appears tomorrow,
there will be fire rain in the sky.
It is an ominous sign.
Fire rain in the sky?
It means many stars in the sky
will turn into fire rain and fall.
It's very frightening.
Isn't that a meteor…
a meteor shower?
Cuicui, you are so clever!
Cut off delusions,
abandon foolish thoughts.
Abandon distractions,
forget both self and objects.
- Mind and spirit…
- Ziqi!
I have thought of a solution.
I come to you for help.
Forget both self and objects,
mind and spirit unify.
Ziqi, open the door.
Don't bother me, I'm sleeping.
Why is he so fierce?
He's been very irritable these days.
Maybe we shouldn't provoke him for now.
Why is he so irritable?
I don't know.
Forget both self and objects,
mind and spirit unify.
I'll count down three, two, one.
You pretend to cry with me.
Find a way to lure him out.
Come over here.
Three, two, one.
Cuicui, what to do?
It's too late, Cuicui.
It's too late, what to do?
He's not helping.
I have no way either.
Ziqi doesn't help us.
We two can't do anything.
It's too late.
Miaomiao!
Wait for me.
Here.
This is the place.
It's quiet and has a great view.
It's the best spot to
watch the meteor shower.
Meteor shower?
You'll know in a moment.
Meteor showers represent
dreams and hope.
Legend has it that if you make a wish
upon a meteor shower,
your wish is more likely to come true.
However,
I still feel there's a bit of
atmosphere missing.
Cuicui,
can you conjure up some flowers?
Flowers?
The kind that is colorful
and vibrant
and covers the entire landscape here.
The more, the better.
I am bamboo.
We bamboos will die once we bloom.
That's not feasible.
Don't you have any other
plant friends who can help?
You can't confess without flowers.
It's hard to see clearly at night.
Make do with it.
Alright, I won't insist.
But there's one more thing.
That is absolutely necessary.
What is it?
Swing chair.
It's a kind of
chair.
It looks like this on top.
Then the chair will swing.
I got it.
What is this?
Not like this.
It's roughly like this,
and there's a stand.
There are vines and leaves.
I know.
Isn't it great?
This looks a bit like it.
- Doesn't it?
- But it needs to seat two people.
I don't know how to describe it.
It's just like this.
Ziqi.
How do you know?
I don't know either.
When I was little,
I used to play on a swing chair.
Back then, there were many couples
who would confess their love on it.
But I was too young,
so I always sat on it alone.
I didn't expect
to play on a swing chair here.
I can't bear it anymore.
I grow too much bamboos.
I'm sleepy.
How is it?
Isn't it particularly atmospheric?
Miaomiao.
They're coming.
Sister Mu and Brother Liu are coming.
Quick, hide yourselves.
Go.
No.
Quick, here.
Squat down.
She sat down.
Yao.
Why are you here too?
Where is Miaomiao?
I don't know.
Sheng had a cold face
and gave me this note,
asking me to meet here before dawn.
Yao,
I think
Sheng wants to challenge me to a duel.
You'd better avoid it.
Miaomiao also wrote me a note,
saying there's something important
to discuss here before dawn.
It seems I was overthinking.
Could it be that we arrived too early?
Let's wait for them.
They are sitting together now.
They're just sitting together.
Is it necessary to be so happy?
Now everything is ready.
We just need to wait for
the meteor shower now.
When the meteor shower comes,
with the romantic atmosphere,
they can express their feelings
to each other more quickly.
Do you really want them
to be together that much?
Of course!
I can tell
that they genuinely like each other.
But,
does liking someone
necessarily mean you have to express it
and be together?
Yes.
In this world,
how many people
who have given their heart
to another person
have a good ending?
Why are you like this?
You talk about the ending
before it even starts.
If there is no good ending,
it just adds another sadness
and another misfortune.
Why start then?
Although the ending is important,
it's not the most important thing.
There are so many people in this world.
How difficult it is to bring two people
who like each other together?
It's like someone
has already led you
to the gates of paradise,
and you just need to open the door
to find happiness,
but if you shrink back out of fear,
what a pity that would be!
However, I believe that
Sister Mu and Brother Liu
are not such timid people.
It's coming.
Quick, make a wish.
♪It's hard to explain the reason♪
♪Why I only care♪
♪About holding you close♪
♪Countless threads of sorrow♪
♪Are banished when your tears glide♪
♪Countless people in the world♪
♪I just fall in love with you♪
♪Even want to change my destined mission♪
♪Longing seeps into my bones♪
♪Yet there's nowhere to grow old together♪
♪In this life, I've kissed your brows♪
♪I've been saved♪
♪Don't cry♪
♪I've held your hand,
tracing your palm lines♪
♪The wind and snow aren't cruel♪
♪In this chaotic world, you gaze at me♪
♪It's a scene of my rebirth♪
♪Loving you completes my life♪
Did you make a wish?
Well,
if Miaomiao doesn't come,
I'll leave first.
Yao,
I like you.
♪Even want to change my destined mission♪
What did you say?
♪In this life, I've kissed your brows♪
♪I've been saved♪
♪Don't cry♪
♪I've held your hand,
tracing your palm lines♪
♪The wind and snow aren't cruel♪
♪In this chaotic world, you gaze at me♪
♪It's a scene of my rebirth♪
♪Loving you completes my life♪
They're kissing.
I can't bear to look.
♪Loving you completes♪
♪My life♪
♪Red Moon♪
♪Round Moon♪
♪I carry a lantern under the moon,
stepping up the stairs♪
Who?
Someone is singing.
- It's her.
- Sister!
- Singing?
- Sister Mu, are you alright?
Didn't you hear it?
Sister.
It's nothing now.
It seems I was too nervous.
(Xunxia Qiyue Pavilion)
My Lord,
everything is ready.
The best musicians in the capital,
ten thousand butterflies,
ten thousand flowers,
and countless treasures are all in place.
Got it.
Tomorrow, I will arrange it personally.
Jiu.
Do you think she will…
My Lord, don't worry.
No woman can resist such a grand setup.
I believe she will not refuse you.
I am thinking
will she be so overwhelmed
that she wants to marry me on the spot?
This won't do.
The wedding garments
hasn't been made yet.
What can I do now?
By the way,
I recently found something.
I want to give it to her
when I confess.
It couldn't be more appropriate.
This is…
the late Marquis's relic.
Yes.
I remembered it a few days ago
when I heard Peiyun mention it.
Otherwise, I almost forgot about it.
My father played with it every day
when he was alive
and held it tightly in his final moments.
It must be his cherished possession.
I even asked about
the origin of this bracelet.
Father,
whose wooden bracelet is this?
I don't know.
(Childhood Zhao Ruoshi)
Where did it come from?
(Zhao Qinghuan, Late Qingyi Marquis)
I don't know either.
One day
it felt like I had a long dream.
When I woke up, it was there.
What did you dream about?
I forgot.
I only vaguely remember
this bracelet
should belong to the one I love.
But in this life,
I have never loved a woman.
Why?
The heart is as empty as the yard
by moonlight.
My father never met the one he loved,
so he didn't give this bracelet to anyone.
Today let me
give this bracelet
to Miss Lin.
Master,
you called me?
It's an urgent matter.
Why do you keep delaying?
I…
If you can't find a way
to make Princess Duanyang wear
the wooden bracelet
of the Qingyi Marquis Mansion soon,
our plans will come to nothing.
Master,
what exactly is that wooden bracelet?
It…
Could it hurt the Princess?
Well,
there's no harm in telling you.
The wooden bracelet was transformed
from the hair of Goddess Mei.
No one can resist the allure
of the Goddess Mei.
Anyone who wears this wooden bracelet
will inevitably
fall in love with the person
who gave her this.
This allure is invisible and intangible,
penetrating the heart and soul.
No spell or talisman
can detect or break it.
I see.
Why?
Have you developed compassion
for Princess Duanyang?
Don't you want revenge anymore?
Don't forget, she grew up perfectly fine,
while your only sister
became her scapegoat
more than a decade ago.
I must avenge Peiyu.
But now, in my heart,
the only person who
deserves to die is Zhao Qinru.
So what will you do?
Our plan
only needs a wedding,
no matter who the bride is,
am I right?
(Tuanyuan Inn)
Guest,
take it slow.
Yao,
the sunshine outside is lovely.
Do you want to go out for a walk?
No, Fuyi.
I'm feeling a bit tired.
Did you not sleep well?
Shall I make some jujube soup for you?
No need.
Thank you.
You rest early.
I won't disturb you.
If you need me,
just let me know.
Cultivator Mu,
the matter you asked me to investigate
has some leads now.
Cultivator Mu,
here.
the task you gave me is done.
The great fire at Xingshan Hall
ten years ago
was announced as an accidental fire.
However, after my painstaking efforts
and tireless work day and night,
I have found out.
Just as you suspected,
the great fire is
closely related to the Dowager Consort.
The Princess's possession was feigned.
But Empress Dowager Zhao
insisted it was caused by a demon.
There must be a hidden truth behind this.
Since you have discovered some clues,
why are you hiding it from Fuyi
and telling me privately?
Because this matter concerns
your ancestor,
I think it's better to
talk to you alone first.
My ancestor?
Your father, Mu Huaijiang.
Does liking someone
necessarily mean you have to express it
and be together?
Yes.
How difficult it is to bring two people
who like each other together?
It's like someone
has already led you
to the gates of paradise,
and you just need to open the door
to find happiness,
but if you shrink back out of fear,
what a pity that would be!
(Bustling and Crowded)
Local specialties?
Yes.
I want to buy some local specialties
for my grandfather
to show my respect to him.
But
you haven't found your grandfather
and have no clues either.
So,
I need to buy it now.
When I meet him,
where would I buy it?
That's right.
Alright.
Let's go.
Go.
You have bought so many.
Aren't they enough?
It's far from enough.
We need to go shopping
for at least another hour.
Another hour?
I miss my grandfather so much.
I should buy more to show my respect.
Let's look at this store as well.
Green Bamboo Leaf?
Are you sure?
Who said bamboos
can't like Green Bamboo Leaf?
Let's go.
Miss Lin isn't here, right?
No, I've confirmed it.
Miss Lin left an hour ago.
(Tuanyuan Inn)
It seems even the heavens are helping me.
Miss Lin and I
are truly destined to meet.
Come on, move everything inside
and set it up.
Hurry up.
Take it slow.
(Tuanyuan Inn)
Slow down.
Jiu.
Today, don't let anyone in.
I want Miss Lin
to have an unforgettable
and overjoyed day.
It must be unforgettable,
but joy is not so certain.
♪The sky in my eyes
is always a dazzling blue♪
♪The departing ship raises its sails,
waiting for the wind♪
♪It says breaking
through layers of obstacles♪
♪Will lead to the stars and the sea♪
♪The fledgling bird at the cliff's edge
spreads its wings♪
♪How high must it fly
to meet the expectations♪
♪The waves say
the breeze will come naturally♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪
♪A flower breaking through the stone,
pure and soft♪
♪Open up an umbrella on a long journey♪
♪No matter where the wind comes from,
I'll look forward to it♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪
♪As the wind blows open the folded
crane-shaped letters♪
♪The yellowing paper
reflects forgotten wishes♪
♪I want to talk to the passionate persistence
I had back then♪
♪Thank you for not retreating♪
♪Thank you for always guarding your beliefs♪
♪So fly♪
♪Even if I encounter storms
and crash into flames♪
♪Even if the thorns cover me♪
♪I was meant to♪
♪Embrace every surging wave♪
♪This world♪
♪Has both spectacular and ordinary moments♪
♪Giving it my all is brave enough♪
♪The next stop♪
♪Is calling me from ahead♪