Qiao Jing, what's wrong? I'll take you to the hospital.
I'm fine. I'll just rest for a bit.
I will be fine as soon as I take some medicine.
Then I'll take you somewhere to rest.
Take some medicine.
- Thank you.
- Rest well.
You're awake. Do you feel better now?
I'm already fine now.
Thank you for helping me last night.
Why are you so polite? I just happened to be passing by.
I noticed your car was on the side so I went over to check.
Luckily, you noticed me.
Your lady's special time is indeed a bit scary.
I almost called 120 (Emergency).
Everyone's condition is different.
I'm in the minority.
If you need anything in the future, come find me at any time.
Thank you.
Hurry, we're running out of time.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
Secretary Qiao.
- Director Gu.
What is this?
Secretary Qiao, could this be you?
You went to a hotel with a man and got photographed?
Be more careful next time.
It's not like that.
Xiang Se Se, get rid of all the photos.
Not a single one is to be leaked!
Okay.
Do none of you need to work?
Stop looking, stop looking!
- Tang Ping, turn it off.
- Okay.
Tell me.
Yesterday, I got my period and felt extremely uncomfortable.
If you were uncomfortable, why did you go out?
Tell me, who is that man?
Why were you together?
Calm down.
I called you many times yesterday, but you did not answer.
I didn't answer so you called another guy, right?
I did not!
How can you prove it?
Tell me!
I can't prove it.
But no other man has touched me.
From the beginning, I have only had you.
- Did you get it settled?
- It's settled.
All of the photos have been deleted.
And all of the people have shut up already.
If anyone dares to leak this out again,
- there will be no mercy!
-  Yes.
This isn't going to get leaked,
but due to this fuss, Secretary Qiao's reputation might be ruined.
Listen to your typical male rhetoric!
Did Secretary Qiao kill someone or commit arson?
Wasn't she just photographed going to a hotel?
How has her reputation gone to ruin?
- Well—
- That's right. The person whose privacy was violated is Secretary Qiao.
She's the victim.
All right, all right, I'm wrong.
On that day, I left the Gu residence after Qiao Jing did.
Since we went the same way, I got the chance to take these interesting photos.
You did a great job carrying this out.
I just used a little trickery.
Cheers.
I've already dealt with all the photos.
Nobody in the company will dare to spread rumors about you.
I've already fired the employee who released the photos.
And I will also pursue legal action against him.
Rest assured.
As for Bai Yun, I'll make her apologize to you.
Tomorrow is your birthday.
I'll make time to be with you.
I have something to tell you.
- Mom?
- Get in the car.
Tonight, come with me to have dinner with your Auntie Bai
and discuss your marriage with Xiao Yun.
All of a sudden?
Why? Do you have urgent matters?
Yes.
No matter how important it is, it can't be as important as your marriage.
If you want to sit steadily as Anxia's successor, you still need the Bai family's support.
Don't wear a look of unwillingness and dissatisfaction.
If others see, they will be unhappy.
Listen to me. Get in the car.
You said you would never be absent for any of my birthdays.
But this time, you broke your promise.
Wishing you
a happy birthday.
I had a last-minute event yesterday evening. Here's your birthday present.
Open it and have a look. If you don't like it, I'll buy you another.
Gu Yi, I'm here to resign today.
Is it just because you're angry I didn't attend your birthday last night?
Thank you for your care over the last three years, Director Gu.
It's just a birthday.
Can't I just make it up to you?
We can't get back time that is lost.
When did you become so melodramatic?
Fine, I'll take today off then.
My whole day's time is yours.
It isn't about my birthday.
Then what is it about?
I'm tired.
I'm tired and exhausted.
I don't want to continue this anymore.
"Tired"?
Are you tired, or do you have your eye on another man?
Gu Yi,
let's break up.
Let us release each other.
Qiao Jing!
I will turn over the work matters properly.
Secretary Qiao, why are you resigning?
Is it because of the photos?
Don't mind the rumors so much. People will forget them in a few days.
Right! And many people don't care about that at all.
Everyone is on your side.
It's not due to that.
I've been working for too long, and I also wish I could "lie flat" (ease off) like you.
That's true.
If I had to work 365 days a year without any rest like you do,
I would have quit long ago.
Well, if you're gone, what will become of us?
Haven't you always wanted to replace me?
Now that I'm leaving, hasn't your chance arrived?
I just said that for fun...
for fun, for fun.
All of you have top-notch work abilities.
Even without me, you won't be affected much.
Yang Yang, you worked with me since joining the company.
You've grown the fastest of everyone.
Do not do everything by yourself in the future.
Be mindful of taking rests. Don't overwork yourself.
Tang Ping, if you want to nap, go to the break room.
The couch in there is more comfortable than your office chair.
And you, don't always sleep so late.
Don't frantically get to work exactly on time daily.
If you missed an elevator, wouldn't you be late?
No, I can't bear to see you go.
Exactly. How about you reconsider?
Yes, Secretary Qiao. Give it more thought, all right?
That's enough. Stop trying to persuade me.
Come on. Let's celebrate my regained freedom.
Come on.
All right.
To regained freedom.
Now that both families have met and decided the matter,
you're about to get engaged to Bai Yun.
I am finally relieved.
What are your plans for the engagement?
Have you any ideas for the venue decoration?
Mom, just do whatever you think is best.
This is a big life event.
Can't you put in a little more effort?
Hello? Hello?
Son? I'm talking to you. Can you hear me?
Hello?
He and I completely ended our relationship.
Have you really considered it this time?
Maybe I should have done this sooner.
I have a very important conference call on Wednesday afternoon.
The itinerary says the flight is at 1:30 p.m.
No, no, the version I gave to Special Assistant Bai wasn't like that.
Then why is this document missing a page?
It might have been Tang Ping's oversight.
Mr. Gu, the electronic version I sent is complete.
You can check it anytime.
So who made this flawed, error-ridden work plan?
I just thought your work was progressing too slowly,
and I wanted to help.
Who gave you permission to interfere with our work?
Now Secretary Qiao has left, I wanted to assist you.
I don't need it!
Redo it!
Let's go. Let's go.
Starting tomorrow, you don't need to come to work.
Go home and prepare for the engagement.
Why?
Do you think I'm not as good as her?
You're still missing her, aren't you?
How could that be possible?
She was only a secretary. Why would it be hard to let her go?
Get out.
- I—
- Get out!
If I don't see you downstairs in three minutes,
I'll come knock on your door.
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
How did you know I was here?
Would I not know all details about you?
As long as I want you, no matter where you go,
I will find you.
Why did you come find me so late?
If there is nothing, I'll return upstairs.
How long will you make a fuss?
I'm not making a fuss.
I was serious about all that I said.
What exactly are you unsatisfied with?
Is it just because I didn't spend your birthday with you?
- I'm going upstairs now.
- What do you want?
I can give you whatever you want as long as you ask.
I don't want any of those things. I want you to get away from me.
Impossible.
Gu Yi, your mom has already talked to me.
You're about to get engaged to Bai Yun. What's the point of doing this now?
We are done, and I don't wish to see you ever again.
What are you doing so early in the morning?
I found a new place; I'm moving out later.
When did this happen? Why is it so sudden?
I contacted them last night.
Tell me the truth. Why are you leaving?
Did Gu Yi threaten you so you want to leave?
Of course not.
You live-stream daily, turning day into night. Our routines differ.
I will disturb you by living here.
I'll be busy only a little while.
It'll be fine in a few days.
Even so, I can't loiter at your place forever.
All right, I'll take good care of myself. Don't worry.
Right. Here's your key. I'm returning it to you.
I can't change your mind no matter what I do!
But keep the key and come back anytime.
Okay.
Miss Qiao, sorry to bother you.
Our hotel system made a mistake.
This room was already reserved online by another.
However, we'll compensate you for your loss
and upgrade your room to a presidential suite for free. What do you think?
No need, just give me a comparable room.
Right now, all other rooms in the hotel are full.
Only the presidential suite is still vacant.
All right then. Sorry for the trouble.
No problem, it's our duty.
Miss Qiao, your room is ahead.
Okay.
- Wish you a pleasant stay.
- Thank you.
Qiao Jing.
Why didn't you tell me you wanted to stay in a hotel?
I could have stayed with you.
Are you bored or something?
No, I'm not bored.
How could I get bored?
Isn't it nice to occasionally play a game of cat and mouse with you?
I've said it. No matter where you go,
I'll find you.
Gu Yi, can you stop being so willful?
Did you consider what I said last night?
My engagement to Bai Yun is just for business interests.
It's because our Gu family and Anxia need the Bai family.
But don't worry.
I used to think you had emotional blocks
so you lacked empathy and respect for others.
I could understand all of that.
But now, how could you say such shameless words?
Is it I who is shameless?
I inconvenienced you tonight. Thank you.
Don't be formal. I'm just happy you called me.
It means you trust me as a friend.
Where are we going now?
We'll be there soon.
This was a guesthouse I designed before.
I haven't operated it since I went abroad.
But an auntie has cared for the plants here all this time.
Although this guesthouse is quaint, it is still fairly clean.
You can stay here for now.
There's a staircase leading to the second floor here.
There are several bedrooms. You can pick any of them.
That's the living room.
Mr. Bai, I don't even know how to thank you.
No need to say all of this to me.
I know some of your situation.
Gu Yi will be engaged to my cousin by the end of the month.
Before then, you should get some proper rest here.
Then how will the rent be calculated?
For a place so big and nice, there must be costs.
Between us, we don't need to discuss this.
Mr. Bai, the rent must be paid.
You've helped me so much already.
If you don't take rent, I'll have to find another place.
All right, then I'll charge for the most expensive double room.
And help me take care of the plants too.
By the way, you have to agree to one more request.
What's the request?
Don't call me Mr. Bai in the future.
Call me... Bai Yan.
Bai Yan.
Did you find her?
I've been searching all day, and I'm exhausted.
She didn't go to her friend's place.
No trace of her was in hotels, rentals, airports, or train stations.
Keep searching.
I don't believe she can hide forever.
Why don't you just forget it?
You already broke up with her.
Besides, you're getting engaged to Xiao Yun.
At this moment, it will affect you negatively to act so blatantly toward another woman.
I will let her go, but not now.
Anyway, you should decide who is more important, Xiao Yun or Qiao Jing.
All right, I'm going to eat something good.
You cover the expenses.
Qiao Jing, Qiao Jing, where are you?
I bet not many people in South City can enjoy a meal cooked by you, Great Secretary Qiao.
It's not that dramatic. Taste it.
Okay.
These foods appear to be served directly from a five-star restaurant.
I guessed your cooking skills were good, but I didn't expect this delight.
I didn't know how to cook before.
It was because Gu Yi was picky that I—
Leaving him is good for you.
He's not worth your trust, let alone your sorrow.
He'll be your cousin-in-law soon.
Why don't you defend him?
Although Bai Yun and I are cousins, we don't normally interact much.
Although everyone says Mr. Gu has good taste, I don't think so.
Why?
If his taste was really good,
he wouldn't treat a beautiful jade like mudrock (shale).
Gu Yi doesn't see your worth,
but someone can cherish it.
Don't mention him.
The food is getting cold. Let's eat.
Okay.
Who is that guy?
It's Bai Yan.
Where is she?
- Who are you referring to?
- Qiao Jing!
No comment.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you meddle in our affairs? Hand her over.
Qiao Jing has broken up with you already.
You and her are no longer "our affairs."
Gu Yi, calm down.
How childish. You are unworthy of Qiao Jing.
Get out of here.
Let go!
"The Honored Guest" by Zhang Yuan
♫  The bell rings imperceptibly  ♫
♫  You stay where you are, waiting for him to come closer  ♫
♫  He gently kneels on one knee  ♫
♫  Slipping the diamond ring onto your ring finger  ♫
♫  When everyone is happy for you, I become solemn  ♫
♫  It turns out no relationship is between us anymore  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness your love  ♫
♫  I remind myself constantly not to run away  ♫
♫  You are especially lovely today  ♫
♫  This beauty once was in my arms  ♫
♫  A pity this wedding is for you and him; I am just a guest  ♫
♫  I set down all my memories to fulfill your love  ♫
♫  But I never wanted to believe this is fate  ♫
♫  The promised forever has become the past  ♫
♫  I tried to give you my best wishes sincerely  ♫
♫  Please forgive me for being improper  ♫
♫  Choosing to excuse myself and leave  ♫
♫  It's not a drama  ♫
♫  Why am I so into it?  ♫
♫  This unbearable plot  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness the love you desire  ♫
♫  Being a guest may be my other destiny  ♫
♫  As the one who left, what gives me the right to care?  ♫
&lt;♫  After all, you're the one who finally got married, and I'm just a guest  ♫
♫  I drained all the memories to celebrate your wedding  ♫
♫  But I never had the courage to bless you  ♫
♫  Thank you for making me finally aware and returning me back to myself  ♫
♫  At least I can still be a guest to witness your love  ♫
♫  He's so lucky to have met you  ♫
♫  I hope he loves you more than I do  ♫