Miss Qiao.
The person I asked you to investigate, have you any news?
This person is very strange.
We've been searching for months, but we still can't find him.
Maybe you can gather more clues.
Things are not simple.
Back then, we only found out that it might be Mr. Gu who got Mr. Su's heart.
But when we tried to dig deeper, there were no more clues.
All right, I got it.
Sister, where did Brother Gu Yi go? I want to buy him my favorite ice cream.
He left.
What? He left?
Why didn't he tell me?
He had an emergency.
Qiao Zhi, have you finished your homework?
No.
Stop dawdling and do it quickly.
Look at the fine son you've raised.
After causing such a scene, he has completely tarnished the reputation of our Gu family.
What's the point of yelling at me?
If you're so capable, you should come back and take care of your son yourself!
Do you still dare to return?
Do you know how much trouble you've caused?
Now the whole of South City is laughing at us.
How am I supposed to explain this to the Bai family?
I'm talking to you.
I sent people to find you, but you didn't even care.
Now you're back. Do you not want your family and company anymore?
I'm talking to you! Are you mute now?
Mom, I'll handle the situation.
"Handle"? How will you handle it?
- By continuing to have an ambiguous relationship with Qiao Jing?
- Don't mention her name in front of me!
Mom, I'm sorry.
The other party in the accident was Su Juan.
The heart you received was his.
What you see as a coincidence
is actually someone's careful planning.
Every year, the birthday I asked you to celebrate with me
was actually his.
Qiao Jing.
My madam, you...
What's wrong with you this early in the morning?
I pondered it all night, and I couldn't figure it out.
What's there to figure out?
- Xiao Bai is just a friend.
- Yes.
- Xiao Gu is… just a colleague.
- That's right.
- Isn't there anyone more than that?
- All right, all right.
Fine, fine.
I think you're just crazy about finding a son-in-law.
- I'm crazy! I'm crazy! I'm just crazy!
- Lower your voice.
People are sleeping.
How old is Jing Jing now? How old is she?
If we wait a few more years, she will be…
She will be… be an elderly primipara (first pregnancy).
She won't be a w-woman of childbearing age anymore.
It has been so many years since Su Juan passed away.
Imagine how miserable it must have been for her.
I just want her to meet a man
and have a happy relationship.
Then she will be able to move on.
Right, right.
What we want is useless.
She has to figure it out on her own.
We shouldn't interfere too much.
We have to trust our daughter.
- I understand.
- You
don't worry so much all the time.
Look…
Mom, what are we having for breakfast?
Your mom is chopping some ground meat to make minced meat for noodles.
I love that. Add more chili, please.
All right, all right. Add more chili.
Easy, easy.
Are you trying to shorten your life by drinking like this?
If I didn't know better, I would think you were the one who got dumped.
What you did this time was really not cool.
If you didn't want to get engaged, you should have said so earlier.
Running away at the last minute? What's that about?
How should Xiao Yun deal with this?
- I'll make it up to her.
- "Make it up"? How?
She's still waiting for you with hope!
You left everything behind to find Qiao Jing.
But what happened? You still couldn't keep her.
If I can't keep her, then so be it.
She really thinks too highly of herself. Who does she think she is?
Look.
Since everyone is here, let's drink together.
Director Gu, don't drink so fast. You'll get drunk easily.
D-Director Gu.
Everyone can leave except her.
Leave!
Don't go too far.
Come, let's go, let's go.
Director Gu, can you please let go of me first?
I want to ask you a question.
Do you like me?
- Speak up!
- Y-Yes, I like you.
How much do you like me?
I've liked you since the first time I saw you.
Because I like you, I came to your side.
You're lying. You approached me only because of Su Juan!
Why is it you?
Shouldn't it be me?
You still owe me an explanation.
You don't plan to come to me so I must come for it myself.
Sorry, I've been busy lately.
Busy doing what? Busy looking for Qiao Jing?
You made me a laughingstock because of her.
Gu Yi, what did I do wrong to you?
It's me who wronged you.
Whatever compensation you want, if it can be done,
I can give it to you.
I want you to marry me.
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
This Gu Yi is really unpredictable.
He's so stubborn, even with the engagement.
Did he come to find you?
But he's already gone back.
He really came. What did he mean by this?
He wanted to reconcile with you?
"Reconcile"? We weren't meant to be together from the start.
He couldn't have really fallen for you, could he?
How is that possible?
He just feels he has lost his sense of control over me because I suddenly left.
You approached Gu Yi in the first place to investigate what happened to Su Juan.
I never expected both of you to end up like this.
Are you planning to stay at home and not go back to South City?
My assistant is on leave to visit her family a few days, and I'm too busy to handle things by myself.
Why don't you come and help me?
Give yourself something to do so you won't overthink.
I don't feel like going back.
Fine, fine. You can rest at home then.
Cheers.
Xiao Yun.
Auntie…
She's been crying in there all this time.
Can you help me persuade her?
If you keep crying like this, Auntie will worry.
Why do you all care about me,
but he doesn't?
What do I have to do for him to like me?
You're already doing great.
Don't cry, okay?
In terms of family background, appearance, and my love for him,
how am I inferior to Qiao Jing?
Why does he only have eyes for her?
Why?
Don't cry anymore, don't cry.
♫  The bell rings imperceptibly  ♫
♫  Waiting for him to come closer  ♫
♫  He gently kneels on one knee  ♫
♫  Slipping the diamond ring onto your ring finger  ♫
♫  When everyone is happy for you  ♫
He couldn't have really fallen for you, could he?
- Hello?
- Hello? Something happened to Gu Yi.
You need to come back now!
What do you mean?
Don't ask! Just come here quickly!
Gu Yi.
Gu Yi!
Gu Yi! Gu Yi!
Gu Yi! Gu Yi! Gu Yi!
Is it another dream?
What are you doing? Get up.
Get up.
Don't go.
You drank so much alcohol, and you soaked yourself in such cold water.
Are you trying to end your life?
Are you worried about me,
or are you worried about my heart?
Gu Yi, why bother?
If his heart wasn't inside my body,
even if I die, you wouldn't spare me a glance, would you?
You seem fine. I will just go now.
His heart is inside my body, isn't it?
Are you willing to leave me?
Are you willing to leave the heart inside me?
The two of you...
have always been different.
We have always been different,
but can you differentiate us?
Have you ever had me in your heart?
You are indeed not him
so you should cherish your life even more
and cherish the heart he gave you.
The number you dialed is currently unavailable.
Don't bother calling a number that won't go through.
Mom, give me the phone!
I haven't made things clear with her yet.
There are so many things I haven't said.
You're not going to work and not taking care of household matters.
You've made yourself neither a human nor a ghost.
I think you've gone crazy!
Since you can't forget her yourself,
Mom will help you!
We finally got it done. If it wasn't for you,
I don't know when I would finish these data.
Before your assistant comes back, I'll be your helper.
You didn't want to come back a few days ago.
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
Let me guess. Gu Yi?
Zhou Rui told me he was in trouble and tricked me into coming back.
You were easily fooled with a few words.
I think you're confused because you care.
But when it comes to whom this concern is directed at, it's hard to say.
He knows about Su Juan.
He must be furious.
It's good that he knows because I couldn't keep it from him forever.
For the past three years, I've been reminiscing about every little detail with Su Juan
while also being painfully aware that he's no longer here.
The man who holds my hand, hugs me, and kisses me is Gu Yi,
but I can't bring myself to leave him.
Gu Yi didn't come to celebrate Su Juan's birthday this year,
and I felt relieved instead.
I should thank him.
I used him as medication to numb my longing for Su Juan.
Without him, I really couldn't make it.
Such a karmic relationship.
Madam, Director Gu still won't eat.
Is it because the food doesn't suit your taste?
What do you want to eat? Mom will arrange it for you.
I can't eat.
You're not eating. Don't you care about your body anymore?
I don't care.
Anyway, it's not mine.
How could you say such a thing?
Are you being fair to me?
I didn't bring you into this world
for you to degrade yourself like this over a woman.
My son, what's wrong with you?
Mom,
I don't want to be like this, either.
But my heart is in love with her,
and I can't control it.
Ask the doctor to administer intravenous nutrition to him.
Yes, Madam.
I saw your light on.
Come in.
Why did you suddenly return?
Because of Gu Yi again?
There won't be a next time.
- Qiao Jing, do you really want to leave him?
- Yes.
My company plans to open a branch in France.
If you want, you can go with me.
This is too sudden.
It is a bit abrupt, but it's the best solution.
If you go abroad with me, he won't bother you anymore.
Take your time to consider.
You don't have to answer me right away.
I hope to hear the answer I want.
Rest for a while. You're not in a good state now.
I don't need to.
Do you really want to give up on Gu Yi?
Or what?
Everyone is laughing at me.
Do I still have to put on a fake smile and stick by his side?
Doctor, it's been several days since Director Gu ate or drank anything.
- Could you please give him a thorough checkup later?
- Okay.
Director Gu? Director Gu?
Chase him.
How do you feel, my son?
Mom.
Don't talk now.
Drink some water first.
Are you trying to scare me to death?
Do you know how dangerous that was?
It's all because you haven't been eating lately.
Your immune system is weak, and you are in very poor condition.
The doctor said your affective (mood) disorder has improved,
and it's basically under control now.
Why did you still act so impulsively?
Don't think about anything now.
You must stay in the hospital for a few days for observation
so I can be at ease.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Great, I will go and prepare something for you.
You be a good boy and rest in bed, all right?
Qiao Jing is in the courtyard.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
♫  You stay where you are, waiting for him to come closer  ♫
♫  He gently kneels on one knee  ♫
♫  Slipping the diamond ring onto your ring finger  ♫
♫  When everyone is happy for you, I become solemn  ♫
♫  It turns out no relationship is between us anymore  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness your love  ♫
♫  I remind myself constantly not to run away  ♫
♫  You are especially lovely today  ♫
♫  This beauty once was in my arms  ♫
♫  A pity this wedding is for you and him; I am just a guest  ♫
♫  I set down all my memories to fulfill your love  ♫
♫  But I never wanted to believe this is fate  ♫
♫  The promised forever has become the past  ♫
♫  I tried to give you my best wishes sincerely  ♫
♫  Please forgive me for being improper  ♫
♫  Choosing to excuse myself and leave  ♫
Qiao Jing!
♫  Why am I so into it?  ♫
♫  This unbearable plot  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness the love you desire  ♫
♫  Being a guest may be my other destiny  ♫
♫  As the one who left  ♫
Q-Qiao Jing, I surrender.
I don't know if it's me who can't leave you,
or if it's my heart that can't leave you.
All I know is I can't bear life without you.
Gu Yi, you're having a delusion.
You know about my past with Su Juan,
and you mistakenly believe you currently have feelings for me.
When you wake up, you'll find out
all of this is simply your self-suggestion!
How much longer until I wake up?
One year,
give me one more year.
Give me another 365 days.
We shouldn't repeat the same mistakes.
In this year, if you don't want to do something,
I won't force you.
I'll respect you.
Haven't you always wanted to investigate the truth behind Su Juan's accident?
I can help you.
You're still running a fever. I'll take you to the hospital first.
Promise me!
Go to the hospital.
Promise me.
Gu Yi! Gu Yi!
What did you promise me previously?
You said you wouldn't appear in South City ever again.
You didn't keep your part of the promise, either.
He still managed to find me.
If anything happens to my son,
I'll come after you.
He's out of danger for now.
But he had a heart transplant before, and his body can't tolerate much stress.
Your family must be more attentive and cautious.
Yes, I will.
This person is very strange.
We've been searching for months, but we still can't find him.
Maybe you can gather more clues.
We're really out of options here.
Give me one more year.
Give me another 365 days.
Are you feeling better?
You're here.
Have you made up your mind?
Or if you have other requests, feel free to tell me.
What is this?
These clues I've found over the years.
So you agreed?
I hope you keep your promise.
"The Honored Guest" by Zhang Yuan
♫  The bell rings imperceptibly  ♫
♫  You stay where you are, waiting for him to come closer  ♫
♫  He gently kneels on one knee  ♫
♫  Slipping the diamond ring onto your ring finger  ♫
♫  When everyone is happy for you, I become solemn  ♫
♫  It turns out no relationship is between us anymore  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness your love  ♫
♫  I remind myself constantly not to run away  ♫
♫  You are especially lovely today  ♫
♫  This beauty once was in my arms  ♫
♫  A pity this wedding is for you and him; I am just a guest  ♫
♫  I set down all my memories to fulfill your love  ♫
♫  But I never wanted to believe this is fate  ♫
♫  The promised forever has become the past  ♫
♫  I tried to give you my best wishes sincerely  ♫
♫  Please forgive me for being improper  ♫
♫  Choosing to excuse myself and leave  ♫
♫  It's not a drama  ♫
♫  Why am I so into it?  ♫
♫  This unbearable plot  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness the love you desire  ♫
♫  Being a guest may be my other destiny  ♫
♫  As the one who left, what gives me the right to care?  ♫
♫  After all, you're the one who finally got married, and I'm just a guest  ♫
♫  I drained all the memories to celebrate your wedding  ♫
♫  But I never had the courage to bless you  ♫
♫  Thank you for making me finally aware and returning me back to myself  ♫
♫  At least I can still be a guest to witness your love  ♫
♫ He's so lucky to have met you ♫
♫  I hope he loves you more than I do  ♫