Now, please welcome the new CEO, Su Juan.
To everyone at Anxia, a lot happens in the group during this time.
However, we can't let them stop us.
We can't fail Senior Gu.
We must keep up the good work.
As a precaution, I record a video as evidence.
My property and savings
are owned jointly by me and my spouse, Fang Pei.
As for my part, it will be divided equally among the rest of my family.
As for the 80% of the shares in Anxia,
Gu Yi inherits 50%,
Su Juan 10%,
Gu Yu 10%, and Gu Ying 10%.
Gu Yi, the company is now in your hands.
As a CEO,
I hope you'll run the company well.
As your father,
I may not have been a good father.
Over the years,
I've always been proud of you.
Watching you make the company better and better,
I am proud but also scared.
You've had a smooth journey;
I fear you haven't learned to deal with failure.
I also don't have time to teach you
so I transferred you to the construction site
to give you a trial.
Fortunately, you didn't fail me.
During that time, you didn't fuss or complain.
Instead, you found future inspiration.
I believe, soon you'll build your own company.
You're a lot like me, but also very unique.
You're a responsible man.
In my life, I've failed two people:
one is your mother,
and the other is Su Nian.
Su Juan, I know you've always blamed me.
I'm sorry to you and your mother.
I would do anything to make amends.
The company is the effort of many people.
I hope you'll assist Gu Yi to manage the company.
Su Juan!
I've cleaned everything up.
Where did you find the video?
You thought to control everything, but got cheated by yourself.
You overacted.
Is it that painting?
Miss Qiao, what are you doing?
I know this is wrong, and it's crossing the line,
but we need the truth.
Yang Yang, do you trust Director Gu?
Do you trust me?
This chip was hidden in the scroll of the painting,
which held the video left by Senior Gu.
At this point, what do you want to explain?
A'Juan, what's going on?
Su Juan, you failed me!
How dare you tamper with the will?
Why wouldn't I?
-  Director Su.
- Lawyer Zhao.
Thanks (for the water.)
My dad suddenly wanted to change his will today
and asked you to bring the original copy,
but he's been in a coma since he took the medicine,
and I don't know when he'll wake up.
It's okay. Call me anytime when he needs me.
Thank you, Lawyer Zhao.
Director Su, you are welcome.
Lawyer Zhao, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I must have eaten something bad at noon.
How could you suddenly throw up like this?
What has Gu family ever done to you?
How dared you do such a thing?
Dad felt guilty toward you
and tried to make it up to you,
but he couldn't stop your crazy ambition.
You schemed against him every second you were around him.
Who is scheming exactly?
You don't deserve to be here.
Get out of Anxia!
I didn't expect we still overlooked it.
Gu Nan was really cunning.
A'Juan, I really like the painting you bought.
We're all family. This is what I should do.
Good things like this should be well-preserved.
Keep it safe.
What use was tampering with the will in advance?
What's the use of turning the safe upside down?
I didn't expect
he would tamper with the painting I gave him.
Su Juan.
What a father-and-son love.
Fang Pei,
all these years,
I've been regretting.
For the company, for work,
I've neglected you
and failed Su Nian.
You were with me so many years,
and I've rarely seen you smile.
Although we always quarrel,
I know, in your heart,
there's only me.
Thank you.
You are returning to Anxia tomorrow.
What do you plan to do with the new company?
I'll keep developing the new company.
It's now part of Anxia's industrial chain.
My dad was right.
Over the years, under the Gu family's protection,
I haven't suffered or failed.
Now, everyone advocates for environmental protection.
I believe the new company will grow together with Anxia.
All right, I'll be with you.
He was a sharp knife
but now he's blunt.
I can't hand over the company to him.
Gu Yi is a blunt knife,
and I'm his whetstone (grinder).
CEO Gu.
CEO Gu, you need to go over the new project.
CEO Gu, hello.
- Send it to my office later.
- All right.
Su Juan's tampering with the will has been filed for investigation.
Jiang Sheng, as accomplice, will also be legally responsible.
The results will be out soon.
Su Juan will fully lose his inheritance.
I just returned. I'll change some company personnel.
CEO Gu, what is it?
I'll start an environmental company,
and I need a director in the PR department and a manager in the project department.
I wonder if any of you would like to apply.
The salary may not be as much as Anxia's,
but there are stock options and bonuses.
CEO Gu, do you think I look like a PR director?
Exactly like you.
CEO Gu, I want to ask
how many hours a day the project manager works?
What time does he get off work? And are statutory holidays and weekends guaranteed?
Here is the most important one:
how are bonuses calculated?
The project department is the company's core.
During the company's initial stage, it might be a bit tough.
All right. From now on, I change my name to "Tang Work Hard."
CEO Gu, what about me?
Are there any new positions over there?
No.
He did mention only two.
But Anxia still needs a
serious, responsible general secretary to assist the new CEO.
New CEO?
The new company will use a lot of my energy.
I need someone to help me lead Anxia.
So I asked my second uncle, Gu Yu, to be the new CEO of Anxia.
He will run Anxia with me.
Congratulations, Brother Yang, you're promoted.
- You have to treat us a meal.
- Yes.
Okay!
CEO Gu, thank you.
Su Juan, we should go.
Su Juan.
CEO Gu, aren't you leaving yet?
I'm waiting for someone.
Must be Miss Qiao.
Well, then we won't be the third wheel.
There are still two minutes; we are leaving.
You guys go for dinner;
- I'll pay the bill.
-  Wow!
CEO Gu, thank you!
- Let's go.
- Thank you, CEO Gu.
Hello.
Su Juan.
Gu Yi, you won.
At this point, no one wins.
You have everything.
Of course, you can say nice words.
Even if Dad gave you the company,
my attitude would still be the same.
You are his favorite son,
and I'm just your stepping stone!
How could he possibly give me the company?
Dad never played favorites with anyone.
He had been caring for you.
But you did too much wrong so he was disappointed in you!
Gu Yi.
Where is he?
Didn't we agree to have dinner tonight?
Mom, Su Juan asked me to meet him on the rooftop.
Just wait for me in the office.
If he had cared about me,
where was he when my mom was sick?
At family reunions, did he ever think of me and my mom?
You won the company and Qiao Jing!
You won everything!
Why?
Why should I be the one to lose?
You brought this all on yourself!
You failed Dad by lying.
You didn't fulfill Qiao Jing's hopes and love.
You used Zhou Rui, Bai Yun, and many innocent people.
How dare you still ask why?
Then how dared you kill my mom?
After you pay with your blood, come reason with me then!
Son!
Don't come here!
Su Juan, calm down!
I was calm for so many years,
and endured so long just to avenge my mom!
Now it's my time.
Why should I calm down?
Su Juan,
if you want revenge, come at me.
Don't hurt Gu Yi.
It was my fault.
I was the one who did wrong!
I feared that your arrival would threaten Gu Yi
so I asked Yao Shun De to stop you from meeting Gu Nan.
I never meant to hurt you.
I didn't know Yao Shun De would tamper with your car,
nor did I know that your mom was so seriously ill.
Do you think I'm stupid?
No!
You don't have to believe me,
but Gu Yi is innocent.
He saved you when your car failed.
If he didn't block your car,
you would already be dead.
If the hospital didn't find a good match for his heart,
he would long have died, too.
You are still making up stories.
It's true.
Gu Yi did have a heart transplant.
Back then I approached him
because I thought his heart... was donated from you.
I've been trying to hide it from Gu Yi,
but…
So I kept it a secret.
But I swear,
every word I said today is true.
You can check or verify.
I can get you all the information you need.
I've lost half my life just like you have.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You didn't, either.
What about me?
Whom should I take revenge on for my mom's death?
Who's responsible for my mom's death? You tell me!
I'll take responsibility. Su Juan.
If you want a life for a life, then take mine.
Don't hurt my son.
I beg you. Don't hurt my son.
Mom!
Too late. The truth comes too late.
Su Juan, are you crazy?
Yes, I'm insane.
Because I don't understand,
why does the world turn against me?
Why did the person I love leave me?
What were these years of revenge for?
You give me a reason to live.
Let go. Let go of the knife.
It's easy to just die.
You're so selfish.
You said you care about your mom!
Is this what you can do?
To the people who were hurt and used by you,
won't you take any responsibility?
I don't want to lose any more family members.
Brother!
Mr. Sun and Mr. Wu are back in the country.
They're witnesses to your father's will.
Before, Su Juan forged a fake will and deliberately sent them abroad.
Now they got the message and returned.
They want to know what you will do about it.
Maybe we should drop the charges.
What Su Juan did is in the past, and we know why.
Besides, your dad always wanted us to be a family.
Let's not hurt our feelings over the will.
I've already dropped the charges.
But he chose to confess his crime.
I respect his decision.
When he comes back, we'll start over as a family.
I often go to visit Xiao Yun.
She went from being scared then sad, to remorse then resolved.
She seems to have grown up.
It's good that she can change.
She's moved on from the past, while I'm still stuck in the same place.
I thought you kidnapped Qiao Jing and forced her to sign the letter of understanding, right?
Yes.
I'm going to confess my crime.
You're right. There's always a price to pay for what we do.
Believe it or not, in my heart,
you've always been my best friend.
ðŸ’–  Thank you to our lovely Channel Manager: oriannanixy_957
Take care and look after yourself.
ðŸ’˜  Thanks to our awesome Chief Segmenter: bjohnsonwong
ðŸ’“  Segmenters: porkypine, lyam_88, nmelova, hana_860, manganese, midnighthunter6
ðŸ’Ÿ  Chief Editor: worthyromance
ðŸ«¶  General Editors: oriannanixy_957, my_happy_place, mywishingflower, wanstwy_197, modestloving_147
ðŸ’  Translation Editors: mzchele_747, grum_ben_444, myblueskiesss_392, zahavahwin, lotus012
ðŸ’ž  Thank you to Other Language Moderators and subtitlers.
Our company's self-automated construction waste sorting
production line has been put into some pilot projects.
According to user feedback, this processing system
can separate and screen various types of materials at the initial stage of waste generation.
Of course, this can avoid the waste of resources and greatly save effort and labor costs.
Qiang, your construction site was the first to use it. What do you think?
- We have only one comment: awesome!
- Right.
We have implemented industry-leading transportation and processing services.
We dismantle and transport concrete blocks, brick tiles, and other construction waste for primary classification,
then send them to the factory in sealed containers.
Building aggregate is produced after crushing and processing.
These aggregates can replace the exploitation of natural stone and use of natural sand.
For the problem of weak compressive resistance and poor durability of recycled aggregates,
our company, Yi Jing, has developed
a key patented technology for the recycling of concrete.
This technology makes the rigidity of the concrete
and various quality indicators no different from original concrete,
and even reduces the cost.
Since this system was used, we not only save time, effort, and workers,
- but it's also much easier than before, right?
- Yes.
The workers from the construction site next door keep saying they want to use it, too.
Right, right.
Resource recycling has become the future of waste disposal.
And our independently-developed project has achieved results.
Yi Jing is creating miracles.
In recent years, the country encourages people to start a business and innovate.
As long as we try, there must be a miracle.
Good.
Mom, I'm in a meeting.
What? Something big is happening! Come out now!
What?
Mom.
CEO Gu, Miss Qiao, are you getting married today?
Mom, is this the something big you meant?
Isn't it epic?
You two work every day, no time for anything.
Do you know how many times Li Jing called to urge me?
Gu Gong. So you two aren't married yet. I thought you are already.
Bro, you need to hurry.
Miss Qiao is such a good girl; you couldn't get another if you let her go.
Correct.
I reckon today is the best day to get a marriage certificate.
I brought you everything you need to get one.
- Auntie.
- Stop with the "Auntie."
Starting today, you must call me "Mom."
But we have work to do today.
Everyone, take the day off!
Today is perfect to get married!
ðŸ’ Thank you to all our viewers. May you find your happily ever after!
"The Honored Guest" by Zhang Yuan
♫  The bell rings imperceptibly  ♫
♫  You stay where you are, waiting for him to come closer  ♫
♫  He gently kneels on one knee  ♫
♫  Slipping the diamond ring onto your ring finger  ♫
♫  When everyone is happy for you, I become solemn  ♫
♫  It turns out no relationship is between us anymore  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness your love  ♫
♫  I remind myself constantly not to run away  ♫
♫  You are especially lovely today  ♫
♫  This beauty once was in my arms  ♫
♫  A pity this wedding is for you and him; I am just a guest  ♫
♫  I set down all my memories to fulfill your love  ♫
♫  But I never wanted to believe this is fate  ♫
♫  The promised forever has become the past  ♫
♫  I tried to give you my best wishes sincerely  ♫
♫  Please forgive me for being improper  ♫
♫  Choosing to excuse myself and leave  ♫
♫  It's not a drama  ♫
♫  Why am I so into it?  ♫
♫  This unbearable plot  ♫
♫  Thank you for the special invitation to witness the love you desire  ♫
♫  Being a guest may be my other destiny  ♫
♫  As the one who left, what gives me the right to care?  ♫
♫  After all, you're the one who finally got married, and I'm just a guest  ♫
♫  I drained all the memories to celebrate your wedding  ♫
♫  But I never had the courage to bless you  ♫
♫  Thank you for making me finally aware and returning me back to myself  ♫
♫  At least I can still be a guest to witness your love  ♫
♫  He's so lucky to have met you  ♫
♫  I hope he loves you more than I do  ♫