The Long Ballad
Episode 18
Sister, why did Duke Su ask you to come here today?
Maybe he's not happy that I used him to return to the Jiang family.
He was testing me today.
He must have some doubts about my identity.
Is it dangerous for you?
It's okay. I've made it clear to him.
We can just not bother him anymore.
There will be a big problem in the future.
Don't take this jade pendant as your last resort.
No one deserves to give up on this jade pendant.
The Long Ballad
Madam, Jiang Yu'e wants to see you.
She's already here.
Sister.
This is Jiang Yu'e, the only daughter of the third room.
She likes to bully others.
She's always been Jiang Ruoyao's follower.
This is the song book that Third Sister gave you.
She even invited you to go to the yard to read it.
Sister, you're so kind.
I'm so grateful.
Sister, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I just wanted to help you.
What?
How did you do that on purpose?
The Jiang family is getting more and more unruly.
Even a maid dares to lecture her master.
Yes.
How dare you!
You're so precious.
Please take away the dirt on your body.
It's a waste of money if you stay with me.
You're so kind.
I've already sent Third Sister's message.
You can do it yourself.
Why is she still the same as when she was a kid?
She's soft and tough.
She's a bad person.
I...
It seems that I should go to meet this third lady.
I'll go with you.
Second Sister.
I think it's Ruo Yang.
It's such a good song.
It stopped halfway.
It's a pity.
You've been in Zhen Nu Hall for many years.
You know music?
I've learned a little from Zhen Nu.
It's not a big deal.
This zither is not mine.
Last time I passed by the teahouse,
I heard a song playing.
I heard it for the first time.
This time I passed by the teahouse,
I heard a song playing.
The zither is a good zither,
but the song playing is not good.
It's ruined.
I just took it back to play.
It's broken now.
I should throw it away.
The zither is broken.
Not really.
There are some things that are mine,
they are mine.
Even if I don't want them,
it's not others' turn.
How do you know
what you don't want,
will be what others want?
It's best not to want them.
Otherwise, the result will be very unkind.
I don't want them.
Sister,
you should have passed the festival.
Tomorrow, I will be at the ceremony.
You must come.
Of course.
At this time,
I will definitely send you a gift.
Qing Hua.
My lady.
Take out my best clothes and jewelry.
Tomorrow at the ceremony,
I will show her
what is the real lady of the Jiang family.
Yes.
Is Ruo Yao asleep?
She hasn't slept yet.
I asked Jin Hua.
She said that the third lady
opened the cabinet
and turned the clothes and jewelry
over and tried them on.
She couldn't even sleep.
The daughters of the Jiang family
are all in good shape.
But no matter how good the clothes and jewelry are,
who can they be compared to in terms of discipline?
The third lady
is still young after all.
She is pure in mind.
Then we have to think about her more.
I will keep the third lady's discipline
intact.
My lady.
This is the salt-soup soup
that I cooked in the kitchen.
My lady asked me
to bring it to you to nourish your body.
This soup
will become beautiful after drinking it.
Is there anything else?
My lady.
This salt-soup soup
will become beautiful
after drinking it.
I will drink the salt-soup soup
when you go downstairs.
Okay.
Tong'er.
Sister.
Yinzhen.
Yinzhen?
This is too much.
I will go to find the old lady and Zhu Jun.
It must be the poisonous hand that Ji Shuran put on.
Although there is a false evidence,
who dares to be the witness
who will kill the person after he is admitted?
What should we do?
What if this is something that will cost your life?
If I die in the Jiang family,
Ji Shuran will have to
beg the government for mercy.
It's not necessary for me to die.
This poison
should just not let me
appear in the discipline.
Tong'er.
This salt-soup soup
is so delicious.
Oh my god, Sister Xiao Qiao.
Are you okay?
I...
I'm alright.
I just...
I was waiting for my wife.
I was waiting for her to hold the bowl.
My dear.
Why are you so tired?
I'm just tired from work.
I just feel...
I just feel tired from work.
I just feel tired.
My lady, you drank it all?
Yes.
This pork salt soup is really delicious.
My lady, you look beautiful all of a sudden.
I think so too.
You're so clean.
So beautiful.
Tong'er, come with me.
Find a way out.
My lady, as you expected,
Jiang Li Jia drank a few sips and then she spilled it.
She's very thoughtful.
She's been in Zhen Nv Tang for so long.
She should have the ability to deal with it.
This is to remove her guard.
I'll do the rest as I said.
The time has come.
If you don't let me go, don't blame me for not playing with you.
What's this?
These are not mine.
Burn it.
Wow.
Wow, it's so fun.
This...
This is all money.
It's not yours. Why are you making noise?
I just...
Who saw you burning it?
I don't believe in money.
I can't open a casino and I can't open a brothel.
Unlike you.
What's wrong, Mr. Qin?
You've been living with me for days.
You can't get money from your account.
The factory is going to collapse.
I didn't.
I can catch every private criminal under you.
You've been playing for a long time.
Of course, someone will be afraid of you.
To be honest.
But I don't want to waste my energy.
Mr. Qin.
If you're willing to save my energy, I promise you.
Money.
I'll pay you back.
I've let go of your man.
What do you think?
It seems that you don't want to help me.
Fine.
I don't want to ask you.
Just wait.
I'll send you the money.
Wenji.
Lock him up.
Don't bother him.
Wait.
The money of the criminal.
The money of Yan Dieci and me.
I don't have any.
The criminal.
You really let him go?
What if he's lying?
I dare not bite Yan Dieci.
According to the future.
Yang Song went to Yan Dieci's place to search.
Now he's on his way back.
Keep an eye on him.
When he comes back, go to catch him.
Yes.
I'll take a day off tomorrow.
To listen to Xiao Tao Hong's play.
Mr. Chu.
Xiao Tao Hong can't sing tomorrow.
Why?
This is the ceremony of the third wife of the Jiang family.
Xi Yanlin invited Xiao Tao Hong to sing.
You've been with Mr. Qin.
I didn't tell you.
Shen Yurong.
Is he also on the list of the guest singers?
That's more interesting than watching the play.
Husband.
Tell him.
Tell him to dress up quickly.
If he dares to do it, he dares to do it.
If he doesn't dare to do it, don't come out.
Yes.
Isn't this the famous Danjue Xiao Tao Hong in Beijing?
His play is very rare.
Today is a blessing.
Mr. Sun.
Mr. Liu.
Please.
Husband.
Today I come to congratulate the third wife.
It's a pleasure.
Thank you.
Husband.
Husband and wife.
We're late.
The young master personally gifts the gift.
The little girl will be happy.
I have a marriage agreement with Ruoyao.
Today she is in a hurry.
I must send it to Helin.
Please.
Madam.
Today is a blessing.
So lively.
Prime Minister.
Madam Jiang.
Wait.
Where is the second wife?
I also brought her a gift.
I will accept Madam Liu's heart for Li'er first.
No need.
I will personally give it to her.
This child is suffering.
She is still a little scared.
I am also worried that she will be scared here today.
So I let her rest.
Madam Jiang hasn't returned to the capital for a long time.
I'm afraid she has forgotten the rules she once learned.
She was difficult to discipline when she was young.
Madam Jiang has lost her mind.
Isn't it?
Someone taught her.
Later, she was abandoned in Zhennv Hall for more than ten years.
Let alone the etiquette.
Now it's not easy to come back alive.
Right?
She forgot the rules and should be punished.
But what about her people?
How to say?
As a person, who would be willing to see their own children suffer?
When my child was gone,
I also felt heartache.
So I let my husband take care of it.
When I came back to the capital,
I felt heartache.
Madam Liu, don't worry.
Since Li'er is back,
I will make up for it.
You are too kind.
Madam Liu,
Jiang Li was suffering in Zhennv Hall.
No one would think of her.
But don't forget,
why did Jiang Li enter Zhennv Hall?
If it wasn't because...
Today is Yao'er's wedding.
Don't mention the past.
Madam Liu.
Madam Liu, this way.
You are all here.
Madam Fang.
Madam Liu, we are waiting for you.
Tong.
Damn.
Oh no
Tong'er
Wake up
Sister, I dreamt someone pinching my face
Sister, why are you up so early?
I'm not up early
I've slept
You've slept?
The ceremony has begun
We can't have slept together
Someone did it
But sister
We've avoided it yesterday
I was careless
The salt-soup is their secret
Let's leave it here
Hurry up, put on makeup
Yes
Yuanbai, congratulations
Yuezhi
This is a gift from Consort Li
It's a gift from His Majesty
I don't care about it
I can only thank her
You know
Although she is a concubine now
She is the family's old friend
and very close to the family
In this rite of rites
Consort Li cares about it too
I'm very grateful to you
Your gift is too precious
I can't accept it
It's a family
Shuran
Take it
Yes, father
I'm going to die
A family is like a family
Have you seen Shuran's cousin?
Think about it
You should ask His Majesty to give you a suggestion
Yes
Father
Why do you mention it again?
It's good to know that you are a family
His Majesty follows the rules
How can my husband be a good husband?
I know it
Today is Ruoyao's wedding
We can't talk about it
We will discuss it another day
OK
I will listen to you
Yuanbai
I will go in now
Please
Prime Minister Jiang
Madam
You are welcome
I told you
You should come often
You should know Ruoyao
Thank you
You are the commander of the court
You are better than my family
They are all different
I heard that
They are all above the rank
Tell your brother if you need help
Mother
No one is young
Old people love people
Come with me
Go
It's too much
They sent people to guard it
I will go now
Go now
I am joking
Jiang family is shameless
You are shameless
Ji Shuran is so cruel
What should we do now?
I hope the gift bag I sent out yesterday
will be worth it
Even if Jiang Yuanbai marries you
he will be so rude to our family
You are useless
You have been married for so long
You don't know how to take care of your family
Did you want me to marry him?
Now it's good
He is so poor
He wants to kill us all
Don't say that
Remember
You are a member of the Ji family
You should think for the Ji family
What's wrong with Su Gonggong?
What's wrong with him?
Why is Su Gonggong here?
He is here to do good
He is here with a knife
Something big is going to happen
Is Su Gonggong here to kill us?
Mr. Jiang is joking
Today, there is no official business
Ji Gonggong is so shameless
The little red-head even gave me the play I made
I will follow him
and give him a show
Mr. Jiang will not be displeased
If so, then I will go
You are so cruel
I will go
If so, then please go
Where is Mrs. Jiang?
Mr. Su
Li is not feeling well today
He is resting in his room
Mr. Jiang
My half-sign is for Mrs. Jiang
She should come out
and thank me for her kindness
She is really rude
If so, I will go
and ask her
Mr. Su, please
Check it
Yes
Good, Ruoyao is in the prime of his life
He is so famous
and he is so talented
Mrs. Jiang and Mr. Zhou
are perfect
Today is the day of Ruoyao's ceremony
Thank you for your support
Thank you
Thank you for your visit
Where is he?
I have a stomachache
Where is my father?
We have a family in Jiang's house
We are independent
We are free from the world
We are natural
Yes
He is so handsome
We found him
There are two people watching at the door
I think they can't get out
I said he is not afraid of the crowd
He was locked up
Do you want me to go?
No
Jiang's family is in a mess
He even wants to come back
Now we can see
how much Mrs. Jiang wants to show up
It's time
The ceremony begins
Mrs. Jiang
Thank you
Reporters, please
You are so talented
Next, Mrs. Jiang
Please put on the crown for the reporters
The moon is bright
The family is blessed
The wife and son are childish
The son is good
The wife is good
The son is blessed
The ceremony is over
Thank you
Bravo!
Marquis Yingyuan is really blessed.
From now on,
there will be another bride in the show.
It's my blessing.
It's my blessing to marry Ruoyao.
Fire the fireworks!
Where are the fireworks?
No fireworks.
They've given away the fireworks.
Where are the fireworks?
Fireworks...
Master!
The fireworks...
They're on fire!
On fire?
Go and solve it!
What a beautiful flower!
Isn't it beautiful?
Who is she?
Why is she so beautiful?
Isn't she the second wife
who just came back from Zhennv Hall?
So she's the second wife
who killed the emperor's mother.
This...
This is the second wife.
Mother,
Huiran...
Mother.
It's Concubine Su.
It's her.
It's her, mother.
Mother, mother.
She's back to die, mother.
Shut up!
Third sister.
A little token of my gratitude
to congratulate you on your marriage.
Li'er,
you're finally here.
Why are you here so early?
I'm not familiar with the way to home.
I'm a little late.
Fortunately,
I caught up with third sister's momentum.
Let me introduce to you.
This is
my second daughter,
Jiang Li, who just came back.
Prime Minister Jiang has adopted a daughter.
Don't mention about
the mother-in-law killing Li'er.
She's the second wife.
Mother,
isn't she the second wife?
How can there be
such a perfect person
in the world?
She's really
the daughter of the Prime Minister's family.
She's been living alone for many years.
She's still so dignified
among the nobles.
Prime Minister Jiang is really lucky.
Mrs. Liu, you flatter me.
We're related by blood.
How can parents not care about their children?
I know
that you've been really worried about Li'er.
That's why I brought Li'er back.
Today, I met the second wife.
I can't bear to see her.
You've been away from home for so many years.
Why haven't I seen your wife?
Who told you that?
I've been away from home for so many years.
There are many plants in the mountains in Qingcheng.
Li'er has never been to the capital.
So,
when Li'er was in the capital,
Mrs. Jiang
never went to see her.
She hasn't been to see her for ten years.
Jiang Li is so pitiful.
She's like a princess.
She doesn't even have a capital.
She's too much.
Mrs. Jiang shouldn't...
Mother has been working hard at home.
If you're tired because of Li'er,
I can't rest easy.
It's not too late today.
You still have twenty to go.
Here, this chicken.
Chicken gizzards.
The ancients have their own luck.
Chicken can is a honor for the adults.
Today,
I'm giving it to you.
It's a compensation for your regret for not having the chicken.
Here, I'll give you a gizzard.
Thank you for your kindness, Mrs. Liu.
It's just that Li'er
and mother are still in the hall.
I don't dare to accept your gift.
Why am I confused?
Is Mrs. Jiang still here?
Come, come, come.
Mrs. Jiang,
this hairpin
is for you.
Li'er,
I'll give you a hairpin.
Thank you, mother.
I beg you to take her
to find my father.
Tell him
that I'm here
suffering a lot,
full of hatred,
but I'm not wrong.
I've never been wrong.
I hate him.
I hate every person in the Jiang family.
Even if I'm underground,
I have to curse them.
I can't stand it.
Jiang Li, Jiang Li, Jiang Li, Jiang Li.
Mrs. Jiang, you're so lucky.
The daughter of the head of the family
is really extraordinary.
Jiang Li, Jiang Li, Jiang Li.
Your daughter
is really extraordinary.
Mrs. Jiang,
I'm so lucky
to meet your eldest daughter today.
The daughter of the head of the family
is at least intelligent.
The blue mountain is like a honeycomb
and the white dragon is like a snowy chicken.
The blue mountain is like a snowy chicken.
Jiang Li, Jiang Li, Jiang Li.
Third Miss.
Ruo Yao.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, my lady?
Ruo Yao.
Third Miss.
My lady.
Ruo Yao.
Li Er, did you see that?
This is the gift I gave you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for carriage
for your late appearance.
But I didn't fuckin' give you a friend.
A friend?
I have a friend now.
You have one friend?
Okay.
Okay, you go ahead.
Thank you.
The sun is setting
I am still in a daze
I want to ask
If I could say a word
If I could tell you
What should I do?
I can't do this
Ruoyang
Young Master
Go, go
I can't do this
Go
Aunt Liu
Thank you for what happened today
You don't have to thank me
If you need anything, just call me
Okay
I am leaving
Why are you so forced by the Liu family?
Father asked me
I want to ask you
When can you stop your grudge with the Liu family?
My daughter is so smart
But she forced me to open a coffin for her
Okay, okay
It's not a big deal
But I saw Duke Su was in charge of the coffin
When did he come to the Mansion of Duke Su?
Do you know?
Father, have you forgotten Duke Su's memorial?
Zhenzhen can't stay in the river
Go
Mrs. Jiang
We meet again
I am afraid you have forgotten
Last time at the gate
You
I didn't expect you to be Jiang Li
You are better than when we made the engagement
Mr. Zhou
By the way
This is my small gift
I want to give it to you personally
I don't want to regret
Mr. Zhou
The engagement has been fixed
Now I can't accept your gift
I am sorry
I will give it to the one who should be given
Mr. Zhou, please
Jiang Li looks like Consort Xue
Brother
Is she pregnant?
Shut up
Today, Ji Lishang
Jiang's family has clearly adopted this daughter
So she is the daughter of the Prime Minister
It's just a coincidence
If you talk nonsense again
Be careful of the fire
Go
Shen Xue
Who is it, Madam?
Go
Madam
What are you looking at?
I thought I couldn't see this scene
I didn't expect that Jiang's wife has good taste
She knows how to force people to go south
As for Brother Lin
She knows how to do things in a hurry
Go
Oh, no
Hit me
Shen Xue, you are done
It's you
Don't go
Hit me
You can't run away
Come down
Hit me
Let go
Don't go
Why are you coming to Jiang's family?
I don't understand what you are asking
I thought Jiang's family was a good family
And people were kind
You are so kind to your family
You didn't expect me to be in the family
But you still came back
Now it seems that your situation in Jiang's family is just like that
Jiang's family is my home
I have to come back
It's a little too broad
If it's not broad
Can you come back?
Tell me
How can I repay you?
Thank you for sending me back to the capital
But I also helped you solve the Qingcheng Mountain case
I can also repay you
Now we are even
I won't blame you for wronging me
Please forgive me
Don't blame me
You reminded me
I am so old
It's the first time someone scolds me for being stupid
You are so stupid
Jiang Li
What should I do with this?
Then you scold me back
Since you don't scold me
It's over
I will go now
Xue Fangfei
Second lady
Something happened
I will go with you
I am sorry