I will never give up.
Then I will not give up.
Slowly, I will endure the pain of life.
After going through the cold winter, I still feel the same.
Waiting for the spring to return again.
I will not give up.
The Legend of Chusen
When a person is in a crisis,
he is like falling leaves.
His fate is drifting.
He can't have himself.
The Prime Minister's Manor can't tolerate this kind of falling leaves.
But A'Li, you...
will have a long life.
Master, the breakfast is ready in the hall.
Second Lady Jiang, please.
The Palace of the Sun
Where is Situ?
She left.
She didn't leave any living people in the yard.
Then...
You slept so much.
It doesn't count.
Hurry and eat.
Father, the fried food is ready.
Be careful.
It's so hot.
Are you okay?
Enough, enough.
Stop it. The porridge is almost cold.
Come and eat.
Hurry and eat.
Your porridge is getting cold.
What?
I treated you to a meal.
Are you moved and crying?
I'm not crying.
You can't eat or talk.
Father.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome.
Father, I'm sorry.
Father.
Thank you, thank you.
It smells so good.
Do you want to eat?
I'll eat this.
Try this bun.
This morning, the people in the mansion
went out to buy it.
It's specially...
Duke Su.
You don't eat or talk.
You don't talk or talk.
Second Madam Jiang.
You came so late.
I thought you wouldn't dare to come.
How could I?
I put the bet on my heart.
That's good.
Mr. Li.
Each of you put 20 disappearances of special south magical miss 묻
All our political news is going to start this year.
Which means,
for your own mixed feelings,
I've prepared it
As usual
The last pair will leave Mingyi Hall and the Imperial College
Good luck to you all
His Majesty will personally give the imperial college's student certificate
Shen Xue will be the host of this year's
Imperial College
Jiang Li, Jiang Li
What are you thinking?
It's started
Student Shen, can we start?
Let's start
The first test begins
Duke Su, the days you asked
The ones who are on the stage are all Little Taohong
What's behind?
Little Sun Tu from Boss Xiao
Pipa Ji from Boss Zhang
And Little Taohong's old case
I got it
Go down
Ok
Chu Jun, you can't bear to leave Little Taohong
Check this woman
Don't alert her
Although money has no legs
It's faster to keep it than anyone else
Check it
Tighten the belt
Yes
Stop
Why are you in a hurry?
She's going to the gambling house
Why are you talking about everything?
What are you talking about?
Today is the day of the broken city
The gambling factory in the city set up a bet for Jiang Li and her
Everyone is gambling
You bet
I bet earlier
Who doesn't bet if they have money?
Li Lian will definitely win
Chu Jun has such a big hand today
Today Little Taohong can't touch
Touch the second lady Jiang
The last one
The final match is
Yan Shijie
It's up to you
Li Jin
Please listen to the question
Three rivers are connected
The knot
In this test, the three rivers are connected
The knot is the bottom
The three rivers are the three rivers that flowed from Taihu
Song River, Lou River, Dong River
Correct
Yan Shijie, one point
Next question
This game is from the Han book
It's better to buy a gold and win a gold
From the Lv's Spring and Autumn
The winner will win
Yan Shijie, one point
If it goes on like this, the winner is one point
Mr. Tian is really a scholar
Next question
Bei Zhou is a generation
It's not uncommon
Yin is in the Yang family
It's not in the Yang family
Correct
Can't you answer all?
From the Nanqi book
Wang Jingze's book, No. 36, 11
When you are well-prepared, you are more prone to being careless
You are secretly hiding in the public
Correct
Li Jin, one point
My brother is like this
He likes to be punished later
Next question
From the history book, No. 65
The thin and thin air is the biggest feature of Tang's jade cup
It's often used to make carving patterns, flower patterns, and character patterns
Correct
From the history book, No. 16
Li Jin, one point
Last question
The flag is not fixed, the flag is not raised, the flag is not raised
Correct
From the history book, No. 25
If the next game is unambiguous, it is impossible to defeat the opponent
Yan Shijie, one point
Each one gets one point
The first part ends
Li Jin, one point
Yan Shijie, two points
Oh no, I didn't expect Li Jin to be so good
The next question is a serious question
Li Jin has been by Prime Minister Li's side since he was a child
He is like a wooden person
I don't know if he is more confident
The final serious question is judged by Shen Xue Shi
Shen Xue Shi, please
This question is a question that His Majesty and I have asked together
The new emperor ascended the throne, and the treasury was empty
There is a worry of corruption and
Li Jin, what do you think?
I think that solving the disaster needs to be very precise
The corrupt officials can't move first
In order to ensure the lower level of disaster relief
Although those who help the wall can't stay long
But at present they are the main forces to transport and deliver food
Otherwise, the disaster is not handled well and the people's hearts are lost
Then His Majesty's position is even more vulnerable
What Mr. Li said seems reasonable
But in fact it is a way of winning
Even if this method solves the problem of the disaster
It is also impossible to hold on
Since these corrupt officials have tasted the sweet
It is impossible to let go
Will definitely cause a disaster
Only because of human nature
In the end, the emperor's disaster is two-headed
Only the corrupt officials' power is the only one
Mr. Ye, the view is really good
But it's just a building in the air
I'm afraid it's not going to happen at all
If you want to pursue the clear water, Mr. Ye
Mr. Ye, the clear water is the best
Everyone can think of the big picture
But the real work is much more complicated than just talking about the soldiers
It's really a young man from the country
He is more intelligent when he sees the problem
Ye Shijie has no practical experience at all
I agree
Oh, no
Why do I feel like Ye Shijie is going to lose
No
Ye Shijie is going to win
Why?
Why did the emperor reward you with so many things?
The emperor asked me today
Under the disaster, the corrupt officials are not afraid of the clear water
Then what does this have to do with the reward?
I said that in childhood
I saw my father killed for the corrupt officials' power
Causing the family to be destroyed
The corrupt officials are in the country
The national treasury is empty
Then there is no food and drink
If there is no food and drink, then the people will be ruined
How can I go because of the clear water
I'd rather be an isolated official
Mr. Li
The country's financial disaster is not only the reputation of the people
It's also the dignity of the emperor
If the subject is not changed for a while
Let go of corruption
Then there are thousands of people dying under the sky
This official position is like a school's
The night is the victory
Ye Shijie is five points
Ye Shijie, Li Jin, ranked first
Mr. Ye's performance today is really wonderful
Mr. Li's performance is also unique
Then continue to look forward to the performance of the team
I invite everyone to dinner today
Let's have a good meal
Celebrate Ye Shijie's victory
I have never seen such a careful understanding
It seems that the Li brothers are Dongzhen Pavilion
I wanted to win the first prize to give everyone confidence
I didn't expect to play it to the end
I'm sorry
You two are fighting on the same level
I was still proud of you before
I should apologize to you
Mr. Ye
It's not easy to get the first prize
Next, it's up to you
Jiang Jingrui, can you wake up
Remove the bruise
My chess skill doesn't count as the first prize
But I won't touch anyone
You'll tell me when you win
I'm waiting for you
Give me your hand
What are you doing
I just want to get lucky.
Come on, Liu Xun.
Why are you holding my hand?
Can't I get lucky?
Fine.
Everyone, come on.
Mr. Ye.
Your hand.
What are you doing?
I just want to get lucky.
Although Mr. Ye doesn't believe me,
don't be so sad.
Fine.
He'll give you all the good luck.
Get up.
Together.
Then please don't meet Li Lian in the first round.
And please get a high score.
Come on.
Okay.
One, two, three.
We'll win.
What's Shen Yurong?
Isn't he just being
spoiled by His Majesty?
How dare he teach your brother a lesson?
I think in the capital,
I think he doesn't want to stay in the capital.
Shen Yurong,
you can't move.
Think about it.
He's from Hanwen.
He's not a good person.
He's not like the Li's.
Who can be the official?
He's the only one who's a good person.
But he's very stable.
He even got into His Majesty's eyes easily.
Why?
Don't you think it's strange?
No, brother.
Who's behind him?
Even if we have to move,
it's not our turn to move.
The most important thing for me
is to win the world.
You must be the first one
to take the chess.
Don't worry.
I've made the call.
No one dares to win me at this time.
Jiang Li
is not far from Zhenning Hall.
Brother.
I didn't understand the game of chess.
Can you help me again?
Go to your sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law?
Brother.
Are you okay?
I still have something to do.
We'll talk later.
How could I remember her?
How could I forget her?
The night of Mount Qingcheng,
the coldness of the bones,
coldness can make people see through everything.
Why did my beloved family
send me to Mount Qingcheng
for ten years
with such a heart?
The End
You lost.
I told you it's okay.
Such a good chess skill is not bad.
You lost to me on purpose.
You were playing a guided chess.
It seems that I won.
But in fact,
you are in charge of the game.
You are the one who should win.
You can see my intention.
It means your chess skill is good.
Of course.
My father's chess book
is not 180 times.
It's definitely a reading and a variation.
Your style of chess is similar to mine.
But your
unyielding thinking
gives me a new insight.
By the way,
who did you learn your chess skill from?
I was also watching chess
in Zhennv Hall.
So,
you are the same as me.
I heard that there are many good players in the Imperial College.
Have you played against them?
I don't need to play against them.
I know it.
The Imperial College plays chess
because of the human emotions.
Li Lian can get the first place.
It means that the one who plays against him
will not dare to beat him.
Then you will teach them a lesson
when you meet them next time.
Of course.
Ding Liangzhu.
I explained it.
He is very smart.
Since he has no idea
what's going on,
he is getting closer and closer to me.
If that man really wants
my place,
I should understand that he doesn't want it.
It's not a good time.
It vaccines my teeth.
You have already solved the case.
But now you just wake the truth.
Linanting,
I think that
you have learned a lot on chess this year.
And you will not have to be7 cheers or fingerprints on the ground.
I'm just a peasant
Please help me
Fairy Jin Hong
She's not an ordinary person
She's the top of the court of the Immortal Tower
And she's also one of the judges of this exam
Yesterday's competition was really wonderful
I wonder how the chess will be today
The one who participates in the competition will draw a lot of money
The one who loses will be eliminated
The winner will be promoted
Why is it not Shen Xue Shi today?
Isn't Shen Ruo Yun her sister?
I guess she won't participate in the competition
just to avoid the penalty
Tao Cheng versus Liu Lingzi
Give me a book
It hurts
Can you not say it in your heart?
If I don't say it, how can God hear it?
Li Lian versus
No, it's not me
Zeng Qi
I'm screwed
Jiang Jingrui versus
It's me
Shen Ruo Yun
Why do you always win?
I'm not going to play
Mom, I'm not going to learn chess anymore
Why are you making her angry again?
Yun'er is your little sister-in-law
Can't you just let her have a little bit of it?
Jiang Jingrui
Don't leave any love for her
You scared me
Kill her, you can't lie to me
Jiang Jingrui, you can lose if you don't want to play
You can't win anyway
I think you should think about it
You'll cry later
Ridiculous
Start
It's a pity to keep it
Let's go
What is going on in here?
It's not interesting
Skin's gone
The pawn'sla tease
It seems to be a serious injury.
He did it on purpose.
He's trying to lure the enemy into the trap.
Really?
The stronger you attack,
the more flaws you'll have.
Next, it's my turn.
Yun, you should play more carefully.
The stronger you attack, the more flaws you'll have.
Next, it's my turn.
I thought Zhang Jingrui was just a nobody.
I didn't expect that from the beginning,
he's been playing for this one trick.
He's always humiliated in front of the enemy.
He's always retreating.
Under the pretext of not getting angry at the enemy,
he's already bitten the dead flag in front of him.
He's become a chess piece.
Get off here.
You can walk here.
You should remember the formation of the game.
You must have been bitten by a dead flag.
Did I eat a dead flag?
If you keep playing here,
our game will be over.
That's boring.
Get off here.
Mr. Xiao, he keeps bothering me.
Stop making a scene.
The way Jiang Jingrui plays is not to win the opponent directly.
It's to let the opponent see hope and guide him.
In private, it's a kind of guide to teach the opponent how to play.
But in the game,
it's the most boring and cruel way.
Ru Yun, don't give up yet.
I hope you can attack me from the other side.
Why is it always you?
What's wrong?
Do you want to catch me first?
Do it.
Me?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Congratulations.
I'll treat you to a meal today.
You didn't even get the first place.
You're so arrogant after you died in the fifth place.
What do you mean?
I won so many games
and got such a high ranking.
I should be praised.
Don't be sad.
Don't be nervous.
I'll give you all my good luck.
I wish you a good luck tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Liu Xun.
How's your old injury?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'll get up from where I fell.
Thank you for taking care of my business.
I'll give you a gift today.
Thank you.
Here.
What's this?
TIP 너은 tempt
TIP 너은
Brother,
I was so scared.
Jiang Li is Xue Fang Fei.
Don't talk nonsense.
How can there be such a person in this world?
I've heard enough of this.
Don't mention it again.
When I played chess today,
I felt like I was playing chess with Xue Fang Fei.
Stop talking.
I felt so familiar.
Xue Fang Fei definitely didn't die.
Do you think Jiang Li was killed by Xue Fang Fei?
I told you to stop talking!
I used these hands to bury her.
Jiang Li is Jiang Li.
No matter how you frame her, it can't be Xue Fang Fei!
You know you're scared now.
When you and mom received the gift of Wan Ning
and framed her,
weren't you happy?
The situation has been decided.
You're afraid of seeing ghosts.
Mom forced me to do it.
I don't want to do this either.
If I don't obey mom,
mom will force me to die.
Don't make me see your guilty face again.
Listen.
I'm telling you.
Xue Fang Fei is dead.
Dead!
She died in the mountain of Qingcheng.
Do you remember?
I remember.
Louder!
Get lost!
Mom!
After the following day,
I won the money I paid.
Don't be so shy.
The one who sees it will get a share.
When I get the money,
I'll treat you to a big meal.
I don't think so.
Master, what do you think?
You're waiting for me to reward you with wine.
No, Master.
Don't blame me for being talkative.
Why are you betting on Jiang Li?
She can't win.
Ye Shijie and the Li family won the game.
Actually, Li Lian won the first place.
Jiang Jingrui only took the fifth place.
Liu Xu and Jiang Li
are both the top three
in Meng Hongjing's exam.
Even if Liu Xu won Meng Hongjing,
it's just a gap
between Jiang Jingrui and him.
In the last round of the piano competition,
Jiang Li must win the first place.
Wang Qingqing is in the Li family's team.
She's been a teacher for many years.
How can Jiang Li beat her?
Even if Jiang Li beat Wang Qingqing,
don't forget that
she's the best in the world.
That means she must win
the first place in the piano competition
for several years in a row.
The second lady of the Jiang family
is going back to Zhennv Hall.
Go and see how she's doing.
Yes.
I'll go.
Why is she in the water?
She's not in the water.
Huaiaun
Oh my,
we have our granddaughter's death.
Our career is ruined.
Where's she?
Perturbed by forever.
The
Down this clip,과의 tym 시 Lap 4
Part 1
In the shooting competition this time,
the shot created by the former emperor
will be examined.
What's the의着天功术?
They are the number of balls
The more shots the ball is hit, the higher the score.
They were always prepared by the shooting.
Why did they change the form?
The shooting game is always changed.
Shoot the ball, shoot the ball.
One is riding the shot,
the other is running the shot.
Now we consider that we are a team game.
So we are shooting with the ball.
We can't change the medicine.
The first group, Zhou Yan Bang, Zhu Ge Pei.
The players are ready.
Zhou Yan Bang will win.
The game starts.
Are your hands okay?
No problem.
Are you scared?
Are you nervous?
Shut up.
Chen Zhu, calm down.
Be confident.
I told you to shut up.
Liu Qu, you are the best.
Jiang Jingrui, you can die if you don't talk.
You guys are up next.
The first round of assessment begins.
Get ready.
Set off.
Go!
Zhou Yanzheng will win! Zhou Yanzheng will win!
It's time for the next round.
High-five up!
Okay.
b
will conspire to defeat Lin Hao.
Don't worry, young master Zou,
just let them...
Lord King!
Don't be nervous!
You've worked hard!
Much to our face.
Nothing to be nervous about.
Tell me about your aggrostness.
Which maybe
can be eliminated by me.
Here is our result.
Let's share it.
Wang Hongqing! Wang Hongqing! Wang Hongqing!
Liu Xu, I didn't expect you to come to the competition.
If you fall again,
your paw will be broken.
Is it worth it for the big talk of this country girl?
Mind your own business.
Contestants, get ready!
Ready!
Go!
Wang Hongqing! Wang Hongqing!
Liu Xu, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Liu Xu is usually fierce.
What's going on today?
He may have a hypothermia.
Hypothermia?
Yes.
As long as his feet are on the ground, he will feel dizzy.
Then let's pull it lower.
It's useless.
As long as he is hanging in the air, he will feel dizzy and dizzy.
How do you know?
In my childhood, I was good at both civil and martial arts.
But I found that I couldn't practice in the Qing palace.
Pull it higher!
Release!
Wang Hongqing! Wang Hongqing!
Liu Xu, you can't give up so early.
Don't be a disgrace here.
Release!
Xiaolv, I haven't lost yet.
It's not the time to say sorry.
Who said I was going to say sorry?
I mean, you pull it higher!
Aren't you afraid?
Of course I'm afraid.
But I want to win!
We believe you!
Come on!
I haven't seen Red Fairy since yesterday.
What if he's still inside?
I think the stone leaf top becomes disappearing.
Do you know that?
He went to the other room with
strange pig trotter as it was.
Liu Xie!
Wang Hongjie!
Ready!
Pop!
Yes.
You think
I dare anime her?
You do Anime.
But not a arms race.
Why do you have the courage,
because you're not willing to die,
Mr. Guo...
Be careful.
Let's go!
gibta
the fairy weiß
fairy
Liu Xun! Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
Let's go! Let's go!
I'm leaving, too.
Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
Liu Xun!
Mr. Shen! Mr. Xiao!
I'm hurt! I'm hurt!
Where are you hurt?
My butt is hurt!
Someone's secret weapon
shot my butt!
Why did it shoot your...
Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
...butt?
I don't want to!
It's my fault!
I'm the one who got shot!
Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
Where's the secret weapon?
Here!
Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
Blood!
My butt!
Liu Xun! Liu Xun!
What's going on?
Why is he so close?
The team that won the competition
is even worse than the team that lost.
They still lost one more place.
The daughter of Mr. Li's team's
chief assistant, Wang Qingqing,
was the second place in last year's chess competition.
The first place is Jiang Ruoyao.
That means
Jiang Ruoyao will win the first place.
That's right.
It seems that
a great show of the same age
is about to begin.
The bet between Jiang Li and He Heyangyang
has become a hot topic in the city.
I wonder if my niece Ruoyao
can achieve good results this time.
Consort Li, please rest assured.
Ruoyao is my favorite student.
Her music is always famous.
I think
this time, she will be able to
win the first place.
I think so.
There shouldn't be any problem
if she wins the first place this time.
I just don't know
if there will be a show of the same age in the school.
In terms of skills,
I don't think
she can compete with Ruoyao.
Little Head, have some tea.
Let's go.
Slowly.
Tomorrow's competition,
is Sister Ruoyao ready?
Jiang Li will win the competition tomorrow.
Our team will win the bet.
We are family
You should be more flexible
I don't want to do my best
It will make me look disrespectful
Jiang Li
Are you sure about tomorrow?
I'm sorry
Jiang Jinrui
You go back first
I want to take a walk and have a walk
Then you pass by the rice cake shop
Remember to bring me rice cake
Ok
Then I go back first
What do you want from me?
Burn it
You are the first person
who can't even cure Si Tu Jiu Yue
I have been practicing for a few days
You are in a hurry to make a contribution
Li
You still haven't grown up
after the last time
It seems that you don't want to win tomorrow
Today
I will have a good rest
Please let go of me
Let me go back
It's not shameful to owe me a favor
Please give me a signal
Send a message to Si Tu Jiu Yue
Her reputation is ruined by this girl
Let's go
Yes, Master
Xiao Heng
Why is my reputation ruined?
Why is it you again?
You owe her in your last life
Let's see
You can't even hold on to the light of two days
What are you doing?
After the treatment
I can't feel the pain
I thought I was fine
I couldn't hold it in yesterday
so I tried to lie to you
You want to win so badly
Please save me
Your hand
is damaged
If you want to recover
at least three days
Only one day
Then you should be more clever
There is also a disease
that the best doctor in the world can't cure
Look
You scared her away
It's the best gambler
Xiao Heng
If you insist on treating her
there is still a way
But if you can't hold it
she will die
Do you dare to hide?
I disobeyed the doctor
so I ended up like this
I'm willing to fight
for anything useful
I'm willing to fight for anything useful
Two cold, heartless people
Holding hands, can we get through the snow?
In the cold wind, in the long night
Embracing the remaining warmth
Holding on, not sure if I can bury the regret from yesterday
Loving is to cherish with life
To live on, even if it's a little hurtful
No matter sorrow or joy
I believe you
Would rather be trapped in the cold of the world
To live on, to use up all the courage
To love until you're out of breath
To cross over the loneliness of half life
Just to meet you
After the