I ignored the road
The moon knows all my efforts
But it's in your heart
That I write a letter
Then I laugh and cry
I'm in my heart
I accept all the sad gifts
I don't even dare to let go of my regret
And I don't want to lose
I'm slowly struggling to hide my pain
I've walked through the cold winter and I'm still lonely
Waiting for the spring to return to the earth
Episode 1
I came to find Qiong Zhi's wife
I have something to ask
What?
I know your lover?
Maybe
I know your lover
I don't even know if I have a lover
The son of the county magistrate
Xue Zhao
I didn't expect Duke Su to be so polite
What are you doing?
You've seen my body
I can't see you
I like you
What did you eat just now?
Nanzhang Valley
If I don't have a sister
I'll have blood in a month
Who are you?
I'm Zhao's friend
Jiang Li
I've pressed her down
Send her to the basement
Help
Be honest
Go
Help
Let go
You're a beautiful woman
Do you have any ideas?
Who are you?
Don't worry
I owe you money
I've said it
I'll pay you back every month
I won't take it
You owe me 50 taels
If you don't pay me back
I'll ask who you want
I'll pay you back
I've said it
Why do you have to force me?
It's none of your business
Go
Did you know?
Yes
I'll pay you back
I know
She owes you money
I'll pay you back in the future
If you harass her again
I'll be in trouble
I'll pay you back
Yes, I'll pay you back
Go
Are you okay?
Do you know how to live with your son?
Those people are not dead
I'll come to Lu Yang's house every day
If they dare to do it again
I'll help you to take care of them
I thought he was just saying
I didn't expect
he would come to visit me every day
At that time
he would always wear several clothes
before he came to Lu Yang's house
until he was satisfied
You seem to be very close to him
A Zhou's sister is my friend
A Zhou's sister told me
What are you doing?
You're so ugly
Forget it
I'll do it again
So many
Who are you giving this to?
You're so considerate
My sweetheart
They give you names
for your guests
Why are you still engraving your own?
I engraved my own name on it
So he can remember me when he sees it
When we first met
I was still a Liang's daughter
But now
he probably feels very disappointed with me
So he never looked at me
He never looked at me
He didn't want to see you
but he died
Xue Zhao was on the way to the capital
and was killed by the robbers
What was the point?
Not only that
Xue's family was separated
His father and his sister
were all dead
An Zhao
Within six months
Xue's family was separated
There must be something wrong
in this
I came here
to ask you
if you know anything
This
is the last time
Xue's family saw me
as a gift
There are ten silver coins
He said
if the debtor
works less
he would use this silver
to pay the price
But those people
never appeared in Xue's family
and never succeeded
How could they see
the letter?
How could they see the letter?
Have you seen this?
Let's see if they know each other
This is what Zhao put in the silver
I don't understand
what you said
But the letter
is the letter
of Zhao
I kept it
and never showed it to anyone
He left it to you
Keep it
My dear
Is there anything I can do for you?
This Xihua House
is the most important
in Lu Yang's family
You can ask me
about Lu Yang's case
I want to ask Qiong's wife
to help me
Huai Xiang County
Xue Huai Yuan
died half a year ago
Who is the heir of the family?
Where is he buried?
It's the love
between me and Xue's family
This is what I found
I can't help it
I'll call
your family name
My dear
Where is Zhao's
home?
The heir of Xue's family
will return to Gu Xiang
in the capital
when they
return to Gu Xiang
I'll let them go
I'll tell you two ways
First, go to Chu Lan
Second,
join me
Join me?
I'll help you
to get Chu Lan out
You're more interesting
If I help you
Will you come often?
I'll see your performance
I'll help you
Thank you
Duke Su
Why are you here?
The investigation
What a coincidence
I came to Lu Yang
You came to Lu Yang's investigation
You want to say
I'm following you again?
You left so soon
Your things are gone
Such a delicate jade pendant
was left to Wuland
It seems I misunderstood
You're here to do the case
I'm sorry
I'll go now
Li
It seems you don't want to work with me
It's normal for a young lady to be jealous
Just explain it
Just be jealous
Be jealous?
I'll spare you this time
If there's anything else
I don't mind working with someone else
Sister, I was wandering in front of the door
I saw Duke Su here
How is he?
I have nothing to do with him
My lady, this is the account book of this month
Forget it
It's all in my head
Li Zhengtang sold 921 pieces of it
It's 1353 pieces
The income is more than the month
It's a whole increase
But from the front
It's good
But when I first entered Hanqiu
It was the time of Tianxin Yi
The autumn clothes were more expensive than the summer clothes
If you look at the general account
It's a big loss
My lady, don't forget it
Madam is still waiting for you in the room
Let's go
Mother, I'm back
Mother
What's wrong with you?
Your mother
Mother
This time I'm back
I brought a little smoke fire
Mother
I'm back
Take care of my mother
I'll ask my father now
Don't worry
I'll do it
Father
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Little wild fox
What little wild fox
You brought it back
You asked me
I brought it back
Little wild fox
You said it was Li
Look, look
It's so close
It's not a little wild fox
You said this little wild fox
Is our relative
Jiang Jia Li
Oh, look at our Ye family's shop
Father
What's wrong with our family?
Why did you bring such a big trouble back?
How to talk
He is the future of the country
It's also your cousin
Little wild fox
You entered the big gate of the Ye family
You said it
Father
You solved the problem of the eyes first
You let me die
Little wild fox
You entered the big gate of the Ye family
Ye family is mine
Win
Madam, you can't go
Let me go
This family has a little wild fox
Not me
I don't have that little wild fox
I'm not for you
I owe the wild prince
What are you doing
I don't
Madam
Even if you die
We have to say it clearly
I don't want to live
Shut up
What you said
That's not a little wild fox
That's our foreign girl, Jiang Li
Help
Madam
You
Look at Brother Tang
Be a guardian wolf
What are you doing
Father, you are also
Why do you have to bring him back
You girl will be confused
Even if you brother Tang
Be a guardian wolf
Then they can't afford
Dad and our Ye family
Besides
Your cousin
He said he would follow
I can still stop him from following
I didn't recognize him
He is my cousin
No
Let's do it first
Let's watch here
There are many things at home
The shop is not peaceful
The old lady is doing business
It hurts
If she knows that Ah Li is coming
She can't help it
Let's talk about business first
Old madam
There is a lot to talk to her
So as not to make the old man's house quiet
But just let him go
It's not okay
Our house
We have to have a person at the top
Tomorrow
Take care of Jiang Li well
Otherwise, our house
It seems like there is no Li Shu
Let Jiang Jia see the joke
Who goes
Why do you look at me
I just finished with him
I can't go to anyone
Don't look at me
I'm going to the shop tomorrow
I didn't have that time
What are you looking at me for
Jiang Li has always been my substitute
You don't show up
It seems like our Ye family
Don't bring him
Or
Then follow our old rules
Catch the bar
Three groups
Only one friend
Who goes first
I don't say
Come first
The smallest family
I don't say first
Come one
You worked hard
Rest tomorrow
Prepare the horse carriage
Yes
Remember to put the kitchen back
Put the light on the car
Yes
And the hot water
OK
The clothes
The rouge
Tong
Sister, you are awake
Who is talking outside in the morning
Sister, it's Jia'er's wife
Jia'er's wife woke up early
Asked us to go out to play
Go out to play
So early
Sister
The thing about the water yesterday
You didn't rest well
How about I go to the drama now
Let's sleep more
They are well arranged
We can't go
It's fun anyway.
Let's go and teach her something.
You haven't started yet?
How long do you really need to teach her?
Are you waiting for this game over night?
Just a few players. Hurry up.
表姐.
I know some oozing
Today
go to今日は
Baiograf Mountain first
ThenMo
The special food of the latter
A visit by a group in the afternoon
Miaoyuan
Winter here
I...
Cousin,
I know you're being dragged by your family.
You're afraid of being bullied and want to play with me.
Actually,
I've been working hard on my journey.
I don't have any fun.
What do you mean?
It's not good enough to arrange it first.
You can change it if you like it.
How about this?
I'll tell Uncle and Aunt.
Lu Yang's mountain water is famous and delicious.
Cousin has shown me a change.
You don't have to work too hard.
We don't have to waste time.
But since Cousin is so rude,
I'll just tell you the truth.
You can't say that.
I can't make it.
I'll arrange it.
I'll make it.
You should have said that.
I've got a bunch of trouble to deal with.
The carriage is ready.
It's sunny.
I'll go out and have a look.
I'll come back when it's dark.
Cousin.
I want to go to the shop.
I don't have many clothes when I come out.
I want to be a new clothes.
You don't know the sky is still bright.
You don't know the shop is still open.
Let's go after an hour.
Let's go.
Okay.
Cousin.
I can't give you the money.
All the money in the cabinet are going to be in the account.
If you want to marry her,
you must have the rules of the owner's carriage.
It's the rules.
There's no rules until the last time.
There's a rule this time.
You're making rules for me.
Uncle San.
Cousin.
It's impossible.
What's wrong with her?
I guess she did some business again.
She got the money from Huohuo.
She borrowed money from her.
Wait for me here.
I'll handle it. Come back.
I'm so unlucky.
Uncle San.
You're back.
Why are you here?
Miss Xia, you're finally here.
Qi'er.
You're here just in time.
Give me some money.
Uncle San has more than the buyer.
He has less than the buyer.
He's the last one.
How much do you want?
Just a few thousand or two.
What buyer?
You don't know.
Just give me money.
I'll give you more when you get the money.
Uncle San.
I don't want to be a bunch of rascals.
You're so capable.
You little girl.
Just give me some money.
I don't know you.
Don't talk nonsense. Just give me money.
No.
Uncle San.
It's hard to have a loan.
You can borrow the money from me.
Otherwise, you can find my father.
You're so capable.
You can take your father's money.
Don't blame Uncle San.
He's not welcome today.
If you don't give me money,
I won't leave.
Right.
Mr. San.
What's wrong?
You want to hit me?
Hit me?
No.
Get out.
I'm your uncle.
Do you think I can't let you eat
your mother's knife?
Uncle San.
I'm in charge of the accounts of Li Zhengtang.
Don't blame him.
Uncle San.
Who are you calling uncle?
I'm Jiang Li.
My mother.
I'm Zhenzhen.
You never left home.
You must learn to protect yourself.
I'll always be your hero.
You'll protect me.
Zhenzhen.
You must be happy.
I'm happy.
Mother.
Please let me go to the Jiang family.
Bring Zhenzhen and Li back.
Sister is afraid of one person the most.
I can't let her leave alone.
Mother.
She married into the Jiang family.
She was born into the Jiang family.
Death is the ghost of the Jiang family.
Mother.
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Lv.
Yes.
When did you come to Lu Yang?
A few days ago, I came with Er Jiu.
I had time to come to the shop to see.
Did you have a good time these years?
It's a long story.
Third uncle, why don't we go home and have a talk?
Forget it.
Today,
I don't want this money
and this money.
Second uncle, let's go.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Little sister, don't you want to take some clothes?
Come and have a look.
Do you have a favorite?
Second madam, this is our shop.
The new material is very good.
The color is also the most fashionable.
Manager Qian.
Manager Qian, I demand a refund.
Uncle Zhao, what did you say? Reunite?
We can't continue this matter.
Since your father and their family are not here,
I'll talk to you first.
Little sister, I have something to discuss with uncle Zhao.
Which department do you think
should be wrapped up by the manager?
Cousin, you go first.
This way, please.
Okay.
Sister, do you have a new job?
I always feel that the Ye family has encountered a problem.
And this problem is not small.
Ye Mingyu, this bastard.
He has been out for several years.
What's his name?
He's a bandit.
Tell me, where have you been?
I don't know.
You...
Ye Third...
Li is back.
Second uncle.
Li,
Li, why are you back alone?
Didn't Jiaer accompany you?
Jiaer arranged it very well.
Li is very happy today.
She went to the shop to deal with some things.
I came back alone.
That's good.
Second uncle.
Did something wrong with the business in this house?
This...
Second uncle.
Madam.
Tong Fuyin sent someone here.
Tong Fuyin?
Yes.
Why did she send someone here?
I don't know either.
Zhu Xianwei, I don't know what happened this time.
Boss Ye,
please go with me.
Go?
Where are you going?
What did she do?
Why did you ask her to come?
Madam, you are so naughty.
I am a servant.
Please tell Boss Ye and Tong Fuyin about these problems.
You...
Our business is very quiet.
I am not afraid of the shadow.
I will go with them.
Zhu Xianwei, can you wait for a moment?
I will tell my family.
I was going to take you to see your grandmother.
I didn't think that something like this would happen.
You still have to wait for a while.
Second uncle, I will go to work on you.
Madam, I am not here for a few days.
I have worked hard to take care of the family.
If anything happens to Li Zhengtang,
I will leave it to our family.
This is a good opportunity.
I hope she can be more independent.
Don't tell her about it.
I will go to see Tong Fuyin.
Don't worry.
Zhu Xianwei, when can Second uncle come back?
I have to ask Tong Fuyin about this.
Boss Ye, you can leave after you finish your work.
After the seven days of the Chulan,
you will go to Luyang.
Get ready.
Feed me.
No.
Throw it away.
I am free now. I will come to the Xihuan House.
I will give you some time.
Zhu Xuan,
why do you still keep the grass?
It is not good to pay the money.
Shut up.
Master, Tong Zhiyang has already done it.
It's too early.
He sent someone to arrest him in front of Ye's house.
He is still not ready.
Now Ye's house is not enough to hide.
I think Luyang knows it.
As for Li's house,
he is not ready to laugh.
I heard that Second Madam Jiang was also there.
But Second Madam Jiang did not do anything.
I really have to be sent to the Li's house this time.
You are so jealous.
Why do you still dare to laugh at him?
I dare not to laugh at him.
But the matter of the old and broken,
once it is out, Li Zhenggang will not be kidnapped.
Ye Mingxuan is not there.
There are only a few women left in Ye's house.
Li's house is already out of control.
Zhu Xuan,
should we go to the bureau?
Don't treat people as fools.
This show is not over yet.
Don't make a fuss too early.
Keep watching Ye's house.
Yes.
Tong,
help me to get some tea.
Sister,
it's so late now.
You drank too much tea and got hurt.
You woke up so early this morning.
Cousin,
you should go back to the yard and rest.
Don't stay here with us.
If we can't get any news tonight,
I will die too.
I'm afraid that
waiting till the end
is the worst outcome.
Madam.
What do you say?
I didn't even see Tong Fuyin's face.
I didn't even see her face.
Who has the guts?
There are three more people to kill.
We are caught by Ye's family.
We don't even have any instructions.
I...
Madam, what are you doing?
I'll kill you at the entrance of the mansion.
Don't push me.
I don't dare to do this.
Don't worry.
Uncle is still safe now.
Today,
there was such a big battle.
He was in the mansion and took people.
After taking him away,
he didn't have a meeting with the court.
He didn't even have the official documents to report to the world.
I guess
Tong Zhiyang and the others
wanted to take the price.
Take the price?
But he didn't take our money.
It's the same business as this.
The two sides are on the same side.
There is a process of
fighting and fighting.
At this time,
they took the price with the people as goods.
But they didn't want to take the price.
They were waiting
to let Ye's family
take all the money.
How dare he!
Mother,
let's hear the general's story first.
What Erzhong said is not reasonable.
He, Tong Zhiyang,
is a good man.
But Ye's family is not a small family in Luyang.
First, he didn't take the money.
Second, he didn't have the official documents.
He took the money
of Ye's family like this.
Isn't Tong Zhiyang afraid
of being taken to the capital?
Sister,
what you mean is
I'm afraid
he is just a mute who walks in the middle.
There are other people behind him.
Luyang and Fu Yin have been made mute.
Oh, my god.
Our Ye's family is a white-and-white businessman.
We are like a huge figure.
In business,
we have never offended anyone else.
Other places
may not be the same.
What you mean is...
Shi Buxiangman is in the capital.
Ye's family has refused
to let others down.
Let them down?
Yes.
Li Zhongnan, a son of Li Lian,
and Ye's family
are the same-sexed twins.
He didn't want to
make Ye's family
do it for his own sake.
After Ye's family was broken,
he decided to do it.
That's not fair.
It's just a small matter.
You mean...
So you mean
they want to use Ye's family
to threaten my brother?
That's just my guess.
But
before the person behind
shows his true intention,
it won't happen.
Then...
Isn't it dangerous?
Ye's brother was just
made mute by His Majesty in the capital.
Plus the marriage between our family.
Other people can't move him easily.
But we
don't want to mess with the town.
Maybe they just want us
to be in the wrong.
I'm relieved
by hearing you say that.
Then we'll wait
for Tong Zhiyang to get out of the prison.
Uncle.
What happened to the ancient box?
I'm thinking about it.
I'm afraid it's just a matter
that makes people feel guilty.
The ancient box
was made by our Ye's family.
What you see
is all the samples
that the family has produced
for the past three months.
I've been checking it.
There's no problem.
I don't know where it's from.
It's said that the ancient box
is dead.
It's so dirty
that it's in the blood.
Lu Yang's cloth and clothes
and clothes are all worn out.
They're all coming to get them.
Now I'm thinking about it.
It's just a matter of
making a living.
Have you investigated it?
The thing that's worn out is
the real one.
It's a piece of cake
that's been torn apart.
After the rumor was spread,
my father sent a lot of people
to investigate it.
The dead didn't find it.
But
there's really a group of
ancient boxes that have problems.
The people who have been in contact with this group
have all been red-skinned.
Now
we don't know
if this rumor is true or not.
Then tomorrow morning
we'll go and see
if there's anything wrong with this batch.
Cousin.
If you didn't hold back today,
the Ye family would be in big trouble.
I've been busy with business
but I don't know how to observe these troubles.
It's all thanks to you
that you've supported my mother.
I'm the daughter of the Ye family.
I should do all these.
I'm so polite with you.
It's so refreshing.
But
I'm still very worried.
What are you worried about?
I'm afraid this is just the beginning.
If this time
no one can be like the one behind it,
the Ye family will not be
the one behind it.
Why should they be like this?
Didn't you say that they would be like this?
Is it because of the hard work
and the hard work
that you've done
to save the people
just to save the people
from being killed?
They won't be
killed because of your retreat.
They'll be punished
and be killed.
The Ye family is prepared to be in trouble
and the family will be in trouble.
If you're all out of the business
and not just the Ye family,
how many people will be killed?
You're right.
I almost died in Zhenyu Hall that year.
But I've survived.
Since I can still live,
the Ye family will be fine.
Cousin.
Why didn't you see Second Uncle?
My mother has gone to take care of her grandmothers.
Now everyone in the family
is hiding their grandmothers.
I don't know how long
they can keep them.
Don't worry.
Let's find out the truth
about the ancient incense stick.
Madam, it's bad.
Li Zhetang.
Li Zhetang was killed.
Killed?
Those people started to kill things
when they came in.
Even Li Zhetang's tricks
were killed.
My nose was broken.
How should I smell it?
Madam, please go and have a look.
How many people have come?
At least a few.
Li Zhetang was surrounded.
They said
the ancient incense stick
we sold out before
was still in the trouble.
Cousin, wait at home.
I'll go and have a look.
Let's go together
and think of a way.
Master, the holy thread.
The holy thread is inside.
He still likes to sit in the teahouse
and watch his own dirty tricks.
Then we...
Are you the Duke of Su?
There's a young master Li
in the box.
Let me invite you in.
He also said
you came to see him
and saw him with a great light.
Why did you send
a scoundrel to investigate?
Who's scoundrel?
I'm a scoundrel.
Lan Lu.
This way.
Master Li,
I didn't expect
I could meet you in Lu Yang.
I'm really lucky.
Okay.
I didn't expect
I could meet you in Lu Yang.
Good tea.
It's good for your mood.
Thank you, Master Li.
So you invited me
to see the witness.
You're overthinking.
We just drink tea.
Cheng Cheng.
I know him.
He's the one who's been talking about him.
Cheng Gui.
Lady, you're here.
Thank you.
Go inside and get dressed.
But so many people.
It's okay.
I'll take care of it.
Let's go, Cheng Gui.
Don't go.
I'm the master of Li Zheng Tang.
Ye Jia Er.
If you have anything to say,
we can sit down and talk.
Ye Jia will give you an answer.
You're so stupid.
You're a national servant.
Exactly.
You're so mean.
You even want to take the money
of our people in Lu Yang.
You're making money with black money.
You're taking the life of our people.
You're so stupid.
I don't know
where the saying of
the people who will die in the Gu Xiang Duan comes from.
But our Ye Jia
has been doing business
in Lu Yang City for so many years.
It's all because of the mutual gambling.
The most powerful one in the world.
We can't afford it.
Please leave a message.
Let us investigate it.
Liar.
Ye Jia is a liar.
He killed a long life.
He's saved the soldiers.
I'm afraid he won't make it.
The new army is coming.
Take him away.
Why are you arresting me?
You're not arresting the person who caused trouble.
What's the point of arresting me?
We received a report
saying that Li Zheng Tang
was killed by the army.
And he caused a human death.
Didn't you take care of the matter?
Follow us.
Yes.
Catch him.
They killed Li Zheng Tang.
We can't arrest him.
Catch him.
May I ask you.
Who told you
that Ye Jia's hometown is in trouble?
Look at you.
You have a problem
with Li Zheng Tang's hometown.
Who doesn't know about it?
Look at me.
Look.
I'm a real man.
Look at me.
Look.
What are you doing?
Catch him.
Ke'er.
Look.
The clothes I'm wearing
are Li Zheng Tang's clothes.
It's the new clothes
that Ye gave me yesterday.
It's also the cloth from the hometown.
But I've been wearing it all day.
There's no such thing as you.
You don't believe me?
Fine.
If you don't believe me,
these ladies
come and see.
Let me see.
Yes.
It's really the cloth from the hometown.
If the hometown
really has a problem,
isn't it possible
to wear it on yourself?
It's impossible.
You're Ye's son.
You're the one who took Ye's money
and made a film for Ye's family.
What's the point of your life?
You're wrong.
My life
is even more valuable
than Li Zheng Tang's.
You're so cruel.
Who are you?
I'm the prime minister of the court.
The daughter of the crown prince.
Jiang Li.
Jiang Li?
I didn't expect
to have a wife like Jiang Er
to help Ye's family.
She's not afraid
of being exposed.
She's not afraid of being exposed?
Mr. Li,
the film is still behind.
The film is still behind.
Two cold words,
a heartless silence.
Holding hands,
can you pass through the snow?
In the cold wind,
in the long night,
the warmth that is left behind
is embraceable.
The body is still alive,
not firm.
Can you bury the traces of yesterday?
Love is going,
with life to cherish.
Fire goes down,
even if there is a little injury.
No matter how much I am hurt,
I believe in you.
I'd rather be trapped in the cold of the world.
Fire goes down,
hold on to all the courage.
Love goes down,
even if there is a little injury.
The process of passing through life,
is not for you.
After the cup,
I won't be far away.