I ignored the road
The moon knows all my efforts
But it's in your heart
That I write a letter
Then I laugh and cry
I'm in my heart
I accept all the sad things
I don't even dare to let go of my regret
And I don't know
I slowly feel the pain in my life
I've been through the cold winter and I'm still lonely
When spring comes, I'll return to my path
The Story of the Phoenix
Episode 1
Jiang Li, don't blame Uncle San in the future
You're deeply in their hands
I... I... I had no choice but to do that
Don't blame me
Did you get mad?
I didn't touch him
He's the right-winged man who's seduced Xiao Heng
He can't be a good man now
I understand
But the war is over
You still have to be careful about Xiao Heng
Is he that dangerous?
Of course, a common man can't bear to bear it
He'll be angry
No matter what happens, he'll be the one to do it
Do you know Xiao Minghan is dead?
He'll have to settle the problem
He'll be in danger if something happens
Don't worry
If Xiao Heng comes, I'll make sure he can't leave the Palace
That's good
I'll go back and prepare for the night
Don't let me down
All the orders are in the palace
There's no place to stay except for a few
The rest are in the important place
Good, we must keep these three rooms
No one can let them in
Even if the imperial guards come, we can't let them in
We're the last room in the imperial court
Yes
Lord
I deserve to die
My wife was caught
What's going on?
I just finished my mission
The three of us were threatened by the chief
We followed her and were stopped by the guards
I don't know if she's gone
But she must be in the chief's hands
I'll go find a guard
We can't let them in
I'll go alone
No
Mingzhi is a scapegoat
The chief is in danger
Who's going to be the next one?
Don't worry
I won't miss such a wonderful performance
You just need to follow the plan
Protect your health
The war is over
How can the chief leave the capital?
I'll go save my wife
What?
Is Grandpa not like your grandson?
Be careful
Yes
Your Highness
This is the stew from the kitchen
He said you need to take care of yourself
He's finally drunk
Why didn't he come here?
The school teacher said he'd come later
The chief asked me to bring someone
Open the door
Yes
What's wrong?
I'm sorry
Open the door
Yes
You can leave now
What are you doing here?
You asked me if I wanted to kill you
Second time
Now I'm here to tell you the answer
You want to save me?
Yes
I want to take you away
Wanning is really miserable
She's wrong to give you
She killed me
What did she do to you?
You chose all of this
You're afraid of death
You're afraid of losing your future
You're afraid of losing your mother and sister
I can understand
As long as you tell me
I won't stay by your side
But I don't understand
Why did you kill me?
I was forced to do so
I was forced by Wanning
Li
Don't be like this
I'll go with you
Really?
Take me back to your home
I haven't been there for a long time
I want to go back and see
Okay
Go
Li
Go to sleep
Just sleep
Your Highness
What's wrong with you?
I'll go to the doctor
Why isn't Shen Yirong here?
I'll ask someone to find him
Go and get me the antidote
But I'm afraid I can't get rid of it
I want to find him personally
Go
Where are you going?
To save him
You want to kill me?
The soup you sent me
I've already had it
I want you to be honest
What do you want to hear from me?
I used to kill him
But you chose him in the end
Am I not good to you?
How can you bear to do this?
My brother won't spare you
Why not?
Prince of Cheng's death
is a fatal death
My sister was killed by the emperor
and her brother was killed
The day of the war
was a great success
I even thought about it
in the past
I'm afraid he has already
made up for you
This is your fate
I can only be
a pawn for the rest of my life
If I don't need it
I'll be abandoned by the people
Shen Yiruo
Have you ever loved me?
A battle for every word
you said
killing to my love
This is my gift
This is the hairpin you gave me.
I'll give it to you now.
I'll never forget the pain of life.
I once fell for you.
I can't even touch you.
Who can?
I just want to get a new illness.
I'll give it to you.
But Shen Yirong,
if the people in the world don't believe me,
I'll die in the hands of my brothers.
Then you think that the King of the City will protect you.
You'll be the one who killed my life.
If you want to kill me,
I'll kill you in the hell.
I'll never forget the pain of life.
But I'll die in the hands of my brothers.
Then you think that the King of the City will protect you.
The King of the City
Don't look at me like that.
I've already avenged you.
You killed me.
If you want to avenge me,
then you...
You're the one who killed me.
Then you're the one who killed me.
I can't die.
I'm dead.
Who's going to protect you?
I don't want you to protect me.
You still want to know the truth.
I'll tell you.
He'll die, too.
What are you talking about?
Look.
What is this?
You're the head of the palace.
Tell me what you want.
After the King of the City takes the soldiers to the city,
please hand over the fish suit to me.
I want to kill Xiao Heng personally.
You hate him, too?
I hate him for being stubborn.
Bastard.
You should scold him.
You should scold me.
When you come here,
don't scold him anymore.
I'll wipe myself clean.
Don't hate me.
I'll give you everything.
Say it.
I'll wipe myself clean.
Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Consort Li.
Master.
The Palace Bureau has not returned to the capital for this time.
They've added a new song to my song.
Please sing it to Your Highness.
I didn't expect you to add a new song to my song.
You've been working for me for years.
You're so bold.
You're really a great model.
I often tell the officials
to be like the King of Cheng.
Not only can they do a great job,
but they can also be loyal to the court and the design.
That way, the people can be blessed.
Your Majesty, you're too much.
You're loyal to the Emperor.
If you're loyal to the people,
you can serve the people.
I'll do my best for you.
I'll do my best.
Father.
You stay with me outside the palace.
Don't let them come in.
Yes.
Qu Zhai.
Ju Zhi?
The guards are the Qing army, Du Zhi, Huishu, Zhang Wei.
They secretly invade the north and betray the army.
They are plotting to rebel.
Take them down!
I wanted to keep you for a few more days.
But you are so anxious.
You came to find me. Take them down.
Ju Zhi,
I knew you were the spy I arranged.
The reason you were eliminated
was to make you think you were successful.
Zhang Wei, do you know that you are plotting to rebel?
You are not a 15th prince.
You can kill the throne of the King of Cheng.
You are the official of the new royal court.
Take them down!
You!
Zhang Wei!
Stop them!
Send out the signal to the King of Cheng.
Come to me immediately.
Take them all down!
Yes!
You are so serious about this play.
She is dead.
Are you crazy?
The princess found out she was poisoned
and misunderstood my intention.
I can't stop myself from doing this.
Then what are you doing?
I am not a spy.
I am a spy.
I can't stop and explain.
Then what are you going to do?
The plan is in the dark.
I can't forget the great plan of the King of Cheng.
After the time is up,
I will personally apologize to her.
Let's go to the palace.
Princess!
What do you want to say?
You can't go back.
Wait for me.
Take care of her.
Yes.
Go.
Who dares to touch her?
General Xiao Lang.
Go and save Xiao Heng.
I have taken the Yufo from the day before yesterday.
I will kill the people who are going to kill me.
Xiao Heng!
Then I will save you first.
Go back to the mountain and save your blood.
General Xiao Lang.
General Xiao Lang!
We meet again.
No.
Cousin, you are here.
Why are you here alone?
Where is Xiao?
Duke Su went to the imperial court.
I want to talk to you.
Duke Su said that the time has come.
You are here just in time.
General, you have to take care of her.
Leave the rest to us.
Take her away.
Okay.
I will leave it to you young men.
Go!
They have already started.
Let His Majesty come out.
I will go to the back to pick up the clothes.
I have drunk too much.
I have to go to the school camp.
Your Majesty, where are you going?
You are not coming back, are you?
It is the good time to go to the imperial court.
Why am I not coming back?
How about I go with you after listening to this song?
Prince Cheng, I am still here.
Why is His Majesty not coming back?
Come on, Prince Cheng.
I will toast to Prince Cheng.
Prince Cheng, I will toast to Prince Cheng.
Your Majesty.
No one in the palace has received the seal.
I will send you there.
Aren't you going with me?
Prince Cheng is still inside.
I will wait for him.
Tomorrow, I will see you alive.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Princess Zhanggong is killed.
Princess Zhanggong is killed?
What?
She is not alive.
What is going on?
The emperor killed her at night.
Princess Zhanggong was killed by the emperor.
How could His Majesty kill the princess Zhanggong?
His Majesty is the emperor.
His Majesty said that you should be a princess.
You can't let her leave the capital alive.
Just let your own comfort
catch the princess Zhang as a hostage.
Princess Zhanggong is angry and defrauding her son.
I will kill her.
Then I can bring the princess
to the capital.
No.
His Majesty killed the emperor
and killed the people.
I will die.
Prince Cheng.
Please be a witness.
I can't tolerate the Zhao's night.
I have led the soldiers to the battle.
I only want to avenge the emperor.
But the Zhao's night is a disaster.
I am a fool.
Today,
he killed my sister.
You are so ridiculous.
Princess Zhanggong is the emperor.
I am sorry for your nonsense.
Please come to the capital to find out the truth.
You knew that
you would kill the princess, right?
You are a public figure.
Guards.
Take this bitch down.
Zhao Sheng.
You want to break the law?
Let me go.
You are so ridiculous.
Today,
I will take the justice for the emperor.
I will bring the princess
and the dead soldiers to the capital.
If there is a meaning,
I will tell you now.
If there is no meaning,
I will kill the emperor
if there is no meaning.
What do you mean?
You are a wolf.
You want to be the emperor.
I will follow the king.
Princess Wei Zhang, avenge.
I will protect the emperor.
Listen to my command.
All of you, kill Zhao Yan.
Yes.
Everyone, listen to my command.
The emperor is not a man.
Kill the princess.
The king will follow me now.
I will attack you.
The capital is back.
Shi San, someone is looking for the signal.
Zhang Wei is back.
Take the flag.
Kill him.
Zhao Sheng, we meet again.
Shi Zhi.
You are too brave.
Just use it.
What a vicious poison.
After all, the poison of the king
is my father's.
My father taught me to use it.
I dare not.
I am so careless.
This is the sword your father used.
It is a good sword.
I fought with it in the battlefield.
He used this sword to teach me martial arts.
He used it to save me in the battlefield.
I am so suspicious.
If you are really suspicious,
how can you frame my father
eight years ago?
My father never framed you.
He is so cruel.
But you framed him.
I think he is a brother of the chief.
He is the master of the capital.
If he didn't block me back then,
I would be the one who killed him.
I will kill you tonight
and then kill you ten thousand times
to avenge my father.
The name of that year
is you.
I will kill you.
Kill.
Who let him in?
General Long Wu Jun.
Listen to my command.
Open the gate immediately.
Let the Beijing army enter the city.
What did you say?
Do you want to defy the military order?
I will kill you.
I will go back to the battlefield.
Kill.
If you listen to my command,
open the gate.
Let the Beijing army enter the city.
Your Majesty.
The road ahead is the west gate.
General Long Wu Jun.
Go.
General Long Wu Jun, you can't take care of me.
Why do you want to be a traitor?
Master!
Bastard!
You deserve to die.
Disperse through all of them!
If I recall correctly
Nuo I don't know for women
especially Fu Take even
Single48
It turns out that helping in early maken
Will useless
Who said it
Who said we'll useless
You can't organizations outside the town
What the hell is awkward
Lead上司他怎么 tooinen he
adore we
this
He свoud
god
the state of your blood player willさ
be yours for From partial release
I'll remeber to you
Li Zhongnan
You are now tightly closed
So I'm sorry
It's from my hands
If you cooperate
Go.
I'm here to protect you.
Jiang Yuanbao.
You are still kneeling.
Do you think you can escape
if you kill me?
I can tell you
that even if you kill me,
you can't escape.
The people of the city
have surrounded the whole capital.
Let's talk about it.
Today, I'll give you a chance.
As long as you are with me,
take the Zhao Yan.
I'll say a few words for you in the city.
Then, even if you are a great man,
the future of Ronghua will not be as precious as you.
Li Zhongnan.
I've been with you for a long time.
Take him down.
Don't move.
You can't escape.
Go.
Hurry up.
Your Majesty, I'm sorry.
Good job.
Go.
You have a chance.
I'll leave it to you.
The soldiers of the Zhao State will follow me
to the city.
Yes.
Come with me.
Search all the public places.
Yes.
Go.
You're not my son.
Where's the blood?
Why haven't you arrived yet?
Listen to my command.
Protect the people of this city.
Yes.
Don't kill them.
Your Majesty, leave now.
Hurry up.
Your Majesty.
How is it?
It's still possible.
Jiang Xianggu, please send His Majesty to the State Palace first.
Okay.
Lord.
Your Majesty,
the Luwu Army is here.
If we can't stop the Luwu Army,
they will soon catch up with the State Palace.
I can stop them.
Sun Zi.
I saved your wife.
So big.
Be careful.
Yu Fu is in the hands of Shen Yurong.
He's crazy. He wants to kill you.
Old man,
send your body to the Palace.
Master.
I'll go with you.
Everyone, listen to my order.
Protect His Majesty first.
Go.
Xiao Hong.
I'll go with you.
Where is he going?
He's going to take Long Wujun to the city.
What?
He's going to die.
My son
gave me a good grandson.
Do you have a bow?
Bow.
That man
only taught me how to shoot.
Xiao Hong.
I'm still looking for you.
How dare you come here
and shoot?
Go.
Long Wujun, listen to my order.
Kill Xiao Hong.
Go.
Leave.
Xiao Hong.
I didn't want to kill you.
But Alie fell in love with you.
Because of you,
she didn't want to see me.
Even I gave her my heart.
She didn't want to take it.
When you were buried in Qingcheng Mountain,
you didn't think about this day?
Shut up.
Shen Xueshi.
How dare you face the past?
Xiao Hong.
You're dead.
How dare you be so arrogant?
Alie said you're a spy.
You're right.
You're not qualified to call her Alie.
You're now a poor man.
You'll never see her again.
Xiao Hong.
No one can save you.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Death is death.
Refresh your life.
I'm not afraid of the cold.
In the long night,
I'm holding the warmth that is left.
I'm too deep.
I can't hold back.
Can I bury the traces of yesterday?
Love is a sentence.
Use life to cherish.
Fire continues.
Even if a little hurt.
No matter if it hurts or hurts.
I believe in you.
I'm not afraid of the cold.
The cold.
If we could be together,
I could be cold and free to free to be free.