Shen Zhengran committed treason,
was thrown into death row,
and his wife and children were enslaved.
My daughter is kind-hearted
and bought her former friend.
Who knew this woman, just like her father,
is completely vicious,
and stole my daughter's husband.
Your Majesty,
such a venomous woman will ruin General Weibei.
So that's how it is.
In that case...
You knew her identity,
yet you sent her to sleep with me for three days.
You deliberately made me obsessed with her and fall in love with her,
you scheming old dog!
Stop it.
Lu Jingxing,
who are you showing this barbaric behavior to?
To Your Majesty, of course.
So that Your Majesty knows
I have fallen deeply into Grand Tutor Wei's honey trap.
Now, no one can separate Shen Lvyi and me.
Not even me?
Your Majesty.
My father betrayed your grace.
As the daughter of a criminal,
I dare not cause any more trouble because of myself.
I beg Your Majesty to withdraw the order.
I am willing to return to the Grand Tutor's manor and work until death.
Truly the eldest daughter of the Shen family.
Appropriate in words and deeds,
retreating to advance.
Shen Zhengran was unyielding,
and the daughter he taught is also extraordinary.
Humph.
I am the Emperor.
My words are gold,
and cannot be taken back.
How can I go back on my word because of a lowly slave like you,
and hurt the bond between the Emperor and General Weibei?
Your Majesty is wise.
Stop flattering.
Your Majesty,
stop nagging.
Getting to the bottom of this,
since you knew Shen Lvyi's identity back then,
why did you send her to General Weibei for a trial marriage?
This...
It was my daughter's narrow-mindedness,
using this to humiliate Shen.
You just said your family bought the old and weak of the Shen family
out of kindness.
Enough.
I can't be bothered with the messy accounts between you.
Lu Jingxing, marry them both.
The Grand Tutor's daughter as your primary wife,
and Shen Lvyi as your concubine.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Shen Lvyi,
from now on I am the primary wife and you are the concubine.
You are destined to be beneath me for the rest of your life.
Your life and fortune
are all in my hands, the General's wife.
No matter how scheming Shen Lvyi is,
the one formally married by General Weibei
is still my daughter.
Men always have a moment of novelty.
It's all the same after sleeping with her for a while.
Only you, the primary wife,
she must respect you while alive,
and be buried with you after death.
You are right, Mother.
I will be in charge of the General's backyard from now on.
I have plenty of time to deal with Shen Lvyi.
By the way,
is the matter I ordered settled?
It's settled.
I guarantee that today the Shen family won't even have a single wedding dress,
let alone a piece of red cloth.
You are getting married today,
but this wedding dress is ruined like this...
Mother, I don't care about this.
You have endured humiliation
all for the Shen family,
but you also have Lu Jingxing in your heart.
I can see it.
God has eyes.
He came back to save you.
You finally have a happy ending,
but I couldn't even save a wedding dress for you.
The Shen family's grievance has not been cleared.
This marriage is just a part of my plan.
Don't take it seriously.
After all, it's a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
My lady, I'm here for you.
This fool.
He knows I hide many things from him,
yet he is still so happy.
Brother-in-law!
Take it.
Wedding money from your brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law is so generous.
I don't have a wedding dress to wear.
Can I just go with you like this?
Even if you wear a rag,
you are still stunning.
But on this big day,
you can be even more beautiful.
Bring them in!
General, there are over a hundred more that can't fit in. What should we do?
Leave them outside.
We will take them to the General's Manor later.
This...
This is the dowry I prepared for Luyi.
When our house was raided,
weren't all these confiscated?
Lu Jingxing, did you rob the Imperial Household Department?
I didn't rob them.
Didn't you say
I couldn't be arrogant?
I'm obedient.
I traded the treasures His Majesty gave me for them.
Here are all the account books of the General's Manor.
The keys to the storehouse are all yours.
Everything I earned is your betrothal gift.
I don't care about this.
To reunite with you in this life
and marry you,
even if we are only husband and wife for a few days,
I am satisfied.
The dowry you prepared for the eldest lady is so complete, Madam.
I'm starting to prepare now,
so I won't be in a rush when he tells me his feelings.
Our eldest lady has the character and looks of a fairy.
She is good enough to marry a royal noble.
Don't listen to them.
I don't care about this.
The person I want to marry is you.
Luyi.
No matter what you are looking for,
or what you are planning,
no matter if you were sincere to me before,
I don't care anymore.
I just want you.
This moment is enough for Lu Jingxing in this life.