Bitch,
did you drug us yesterday?
What kind of drug are you talking about, Madam?
I don't understand.
You still want to deny it?
The aphrodisiac was clearly in your tea cup.
How did it end up in Yingying's and my health soup?
It must be you.
Are you blaming me
for not suffering in silence?
Bitch!
If it weren't for the sake of our past friendship
that I bought your family out,
you would be in a brothel by now.
You don't repay my kindness
with your life.
Instead, you dared to drug me and my mother.
When you entered the palace at the age of ten,
you broke a glazed cup.
You said your father would beat you to death if he knew.
I was the one who took the blame for you.
At the spring banquet when you were fourteen,
you were jealous of my first place,
and put dirty things in my sachet.
I found out.
You knelt before me and begged me,
and I forgave you.
At my coming-of-age ceremony when I was sixteen,
at the Spring Festival when I was seventeen,
and at the Lantern Festival when I was eighteen...
Wei Yingying,
I have saved you,
helped you, and forgiven you so many times.
After you bought me,
you took me to nineteen banquets of all sizes.
Every time, you would
do your best to humiliate me in front of everyone.
Wei Yingying,
did you buy me for the sake of our past friendship,
or just to humiliate me
and trample me into the mud?
We both know the answer.
I just hate you,
Shen Lvyi.
I hate your always-so-arrogant look the most.
Madam, Second Miss, congratulations!
The people from the General Weibei's Mansion have come to present betrothal gifts.
The gifts are piled up at the gate.
There is no end in sight.
What?
I thought he had fallen out with our family.
It seems Lu Jingxing still dares not disobey the imperial order,
nor is he willing to give up the power of our Wei family.
Shen Lvyi, do you see?
The man you want to rely on has come to marry me.
I will be the wife of General Weibei.
Shen Lvyi,
you'll never catch up with me in this life.
The door of this storehouse is too solid.
If it weren't for the chance of presenting betrothal gifts,
it would be harder than climbing to heaven
for us to get in.
An ordinary storehouse
doesn't need such tight security
and solid doors.
The posthumous edict we are looking for must be inside.
Let's go.
Not here.
I didn't find it either.
The storehouse is full of calligraphy and paintings by famous masters of the Tang and Song Dynasties.
The author of this painting is unknown.
The brushwork is vulgar.
It doesn't deserve to be hung here at all.
Something is wrong.
Found it.
Oh no.
Who's there?
We can't alert the enemy.
Split up. You guys go out first.
Stop right there.
You can't escape.
Why are you here?
Weren't you presenting betrothal gifts up front?
What's the fun in that?
I'm here to keep my lady company, of course.
Stealing is much more interesting.
I am looking for something.
But the mechanism is too intricate.
I can't unlock it,
and they noticed me.
Help me.
Okay.
I'll kill them right now,
and smash the mechanism for you.
No.
They are innocent.
Besides, we can't cause trouble now
and alert the enemy.
Then there's only one way left.
What is it?
Who's there?
General Weibei.
What are you looking at?
Haven't you seen people having an affair?
Keep looking and I'll gouge your eyes out.
Master, bad news!
Is this the idea you came up with?
To make it convincing,
you need to kiss me hard
and leave hickeys.
Then they'll believe it.
General Weibei claims he's presenting gifts by imperial decree,
yet he's having an affair with a maid in my mansion.
He's clearly using this to humiliate me,
but actually humiliating Your Majesty.
You're the Grand Tutor.
You've read so many books.
When complaining,
why do you use my words?
Is this true?
Yes.
But I was also acting on your decree.
When did I issue a decree
letting you have an affair with the Grand Tutor's maid?
Your Majesty bestowed the trial-marriage maid upon me.
Naturally, I must present her with betrothal gifts today too.
I sent to the Grand Tutor's mansion
countless gold and jewelry as gifts.
The betrothal gift for my beloved
is my sincere love.
Shut up.
What kind of wild talk is this?
How can you say it in public?
I know you're vulgar, but this is too much.
Grand Tutor.
General Weibei was indeed out of line today.
But it's excusable.
I did give him the maid.
For my sake,
please forgive him.
Shut up.
Your Majesty's word is law.
It's only right that my family suffers some grievances.
Thank you for your compassion, Your Majesty.
However.
This maid's identity is special.
She is the daughter of the guilty minister Shen Zhengran.
Oh.
It turns out to be the eldest daughter of Minister Shen.
Your servant, Shen Lvyi, greets Your Majesty.
Thank Your Majesty for sparing my life.
Long live Your Majesty!
Long live!
Truly a noble lady.
Her etiquette is impeccable.
And she is indeed very beautiful.
No wonder she has enchanted my General of Weibei so much.
Lvyi just now
failed to find what she was looking for in the Grand Tutor's mansion.
Now she must be hoping to delay the situation.
But His Majesty despises Minister Shen.
I need to find a way to cause trouble
and distract His Majesty.