YEONG-OK AND JEONG-JUN
A CAPTAIN AND A HAENYEO TRY NOT TO BE
SERIOUS AMIDST LIES AND RUMORS
YEONG-OK, JEONG-JUN, AND YEONG-HUI 2
-Thank you.
-Why haven't you visited in so long?
Here.
It's on the house.
-You don't need to do that.
-No, just take it.
Just bring me two yellowtails next time.
-Just take it.
-Hey, come on.
Goodness, that boy.
Dong-seok, let's eat.
Say, "Hello." Hi.
SEON-A
She doesn't send me any texts,
but she sends me videos
of her daily life almost every day.
What do you think it means?
You know what it means.
How would I know? I'm dumb.
She knows you're worried about her,
and she likes you.
It's her way of saying,
"I'm doing well. How about you?"
But you didn't send her anything.
I don't send her stuff.
Why not?
Are you playing hard to get?
Cut the crap.
I'm off.
Hey, wait.
Hey. Help me out if you're free.
No, I need to go.
Yeong-ok's sister is here.
She wanted raw fish, so I bought some.
I just dropped by on my way back.
-How's it going with Yeong-ok?
-Good.
Dong-seok.
Yeong-ok's sister is a little unwell.
She has Down syndrome.
She's like a baby.
I know Down syndrome.
I've seen it in movies.
Their parents have passed.
I'm okay with all of that,
but I need advice on how to convince
my parents and Gi-jun.
I'm in no place to give you any advice.
Hey.
If your parents and Gi-jun
tell you to break up, will you?
No.
Then there's your answer.
Just do what you want
and be bullheaded about it like me.
I'm in love with a woman
whose father killed himself,
and whose mother got remarried.
She got divorced, and she even has a kid.
Plus, we barely meet each other.
But I still like her.
It's my life.
Who cares what other people think?
You don't even owe your parents anything.
You didn't go to college,
which saved them money,
and you bought that boat on your own.
In situations like this,
we're better off
since we don't owe our parents anything.
What can they do?
All they did for us was give birth,
so they have no say.
But they still brought me into this world.
If not for them,
I wouldn't have met Yeong-ok.
If you say that, what does that make me?
You punk.
You said you slept with her.
You slept with her. You like her.
She trusts you.
You can't walk away from that.
You two already built something together.
Tell your parents this.
"Mom, Dad, listen."
"I've made my decision." That's it.
If your dad beats you, then just let him.
As for Gi-jun, you can deal with him.
You're right.
I guess there's no way
to satisfy everyone.
I'll just put up with
whatever my parents have to say.
Thanks, Dong-seok.
My head's all clear now.
Go on, before the raw fish goes bad.
All right, bye.
SEON-A
The house looks great.
I just wanted to show you
how far along I was
and boast that I'm better
than most carpenters.
But I'm not pressuring you
to come or anything.
Is your kid doing well?
It's nice of you to ask about Yeol.
Are you doing well?
Of course.
I'm doing everything you told me to do.
I work out every day,
and I miss you at times.
Only as a friend?
Ms. Min.
I'm working right now. I'm at the office.
I'll call you later.
My colleague needs me.
All right, then. Bye.
Here.
BOIL OINTMENT
APPLY 3 TIMES A DAY
Don't hate him so much.
I know the captain seemed startled
when he first saw you,
but he's a decent guy.
Did you sleep with him?
It's rude to ask that.
Did you sleep with him naked?
How do you know that kind of stuff?
Okay, where else?
Are you going to marry him?
Are you going to have kids?
That's enough.
Do you think aging leads
to poor blood circulation?
Why are your boils getting worse?
-It's because you ate ice cream.
-No, it's not.
Sure, it is.
That stuff is bad for your digestion.
The ice cream caused you
to have diarrhea yesterday.
You have digestive problems
because of your weak stomach.
I can't believe you pooped your pants.
Hey, stop it.
-No, you can't stop me.
-Stop talking about poop.
No, I'm going to talk about it.
I'm going to say it. Poop!
You pooped your pants!
Stop it.
You're so strong! Come here!
Yeong-hui, are you
going to eat ice cream again?
What do you want?
Can we talk?
Why are you using sign language?
Sign language is for deaf people.
What?
Why are you using sign language
when you can't even understand it?
It's for deaf people.
Let's go out.
Will you go out with me? I like you.
If you like me,
does that mean I have to like you back?
Why? Because I'm disabled?
Let me make myself clear.
I don't like you.
I'll do this one, okay?
I think it'll work.
-Wait.
-Are you sure?
-Hey, give me a second.
-Careful.
I did it.
-We're going to win.
-She's scary.
-So scary.
Seong-jun, go ahead.
Captain.
-Seong-jun, it's your turn.
-"Seong-jun"?
Who's Seong-jun?
He's my ex-boyfriend.
I dated him the longest until recently.
Don't mind her, Jeong-jun.
She's just being mean.
She knows how to express herself.
It's okay. She'll end up
liking me a lot more than that punk.
Here I go.
No, it won't work.
-Nice!
-Yes!
Don't shout. It might collapse.
-It's my turn.
-Eun-hui.
-Careful.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-I'll go with this one.
Good job, Yeong-hui!
Oh, come on.
-Nice one, Yeong-hui!
-We did it!
Hey, that's cheating.
-Let's play again.
-No way. Yeong-hui won.
Isn't that right?
Now, let's have a beer.
Why do you all look surprised?
She's old enough to drink.
We're all here for her.
Let's drink.
-She's right.
-Yes.
She's allowed.
-Right.
-Yes, she's allowed to drink.
What's your go-to beer?
Go-to beer.
Oh, so you like Go-to Beer?
-"Go-to Beer."
That constellation over there
is called "The Big Dipper."
The…
The Big Dipper?
That constellation over there
is called "Cassiopeia."
Maybe that's too hard.
Cassiopeia?
-Good job!
-That was great.
Then let's move on to that one.
That one is called "Venus."
Venus?
-Great!
-Nice!
-Good job!
-You're good at this.
-Come inside, guys.
-Let's go.
-It's beer!
-Gosh.
Here.
We need to make a toast.
Here. Cheers to Yeong-hui.
-Cheers.
That's nice and cold.
Here.
-Is it delicious?
-Yes, it's the best.
The best?
Yeong-hui, do a wave.
How do you do it?
Gosh, I don't think I can do that!
You're amazing. How did you do it?
Look at her dance.
-She's a great dancer!
-Who taught you these moves?
-She's good.
-I don't know.
-You don't know? Well, teach me.
-How do you do it?
Yeong-ok, come dance with me.
I'd rather just watch.
-You're good. How do you do it?
-My back hurts.
-Your back.
-This is too hard.
You don't have to be too nice to her.
You remember things
from back when you were seven, right?
Maybe not everything, but I'm sure
you remember all the big events.
It's the same with her.
She may have an IQ of a seven-year-old,
and not know how to count.
She may not be fully aware of things,
but she knows enough.
She knows how it feels
to love someone or be loved.
The feeling of betrayal and hatred.
The sorrow of losing our parents,
and how sad it is to be disabled.
She knows all that.
Look at her dance.
So don't be too nice to her.
Don't look at her
with affection like that either.
What if she feels loved and refuses
to leave? What will you do then?
Just take it easy.
That's what I'm doing.
I do just enough so that
she'll be able to forget about me
once she returns to the care facility.
So that she won't miss me enough
to want to come back here.
So that she'll feel more attached
to Ms. Jang, her caregiver, than to me.
That's why I'm taking it easy.
It's not that
I don't want to treat her better.
It's so that so she won't get hurt.
Yeong-hui can spend time
with Byeol-i tomorrow.
So just do what you need to do.
I already took a week off
from the fixed-net fishing gig.
Fine. Do as you wish.
Let's see how long it lasts.
Yeong-hui, let's call it a day.
You took enough photos.
Will you all stay still?
The photos I took are all out of focus.
That's because you're drunk
and can't hold the phone still.
I told you to drink one can,
but you drank three,
and now they can't even
go home because of you.
What is this nonsense?
-That's enough.
-I need these photos
to draw.
Yeong-ok, we're fine.
Yeong-hui, go ahead and take our photos.
Yes, she's going to draw pictures of us,
so this is the least we can do.
She's right. Go ahead, Yeong-hui.
-Just stop. I'll take it for you.
-No, I…
I'll do it myself.
You can't draw. Let go.
Let go already. Enough is enough.
You brat!
You don't believe me!
You don't believe that
I draw like Mom and Dad!
You don't believe that I'm an artist!
You…
You abandoned me
on the subway, didn't you?
Stop talking nonsense.
When did I ever abandon you?
Mom and Dad
told you to be nice to me!
So why did you abandon me? Why?
Why did you leave me?
Damn it.
You…
You brat!
Watch your language.
Or you'll be sorry.
Her cell phone's pretty old.
I should get her a new one.
She keeps lying these days.
She can't draw.
Don't expect anything from her.
This is nothing. It can get a lot worse.
Just give up already.
-Let's clean up.
-Okay.
But I must say, Yeong-hui is
a lot brighter than I thought.
She gets along with people just fine.
Yes, she's cute too.
Why are you so angry?
Are you angry because I told you
to stop taking photos?
Or…
You abandoned me, didn't you?
Stop talking nonsense.
We lived together until we were 22.
We lived with Ms. Jang
and all the other friends.
First, at an orphanage,
then we went to a group home.
Stop being a baby
and just show me your drawings.
I want to see
if you actually know how to draw.
Is it in there?
Hey, you're curvy.
I'm sleepy.
Do you really know how to draw?
I'm good.
Did Ms. Jang tell you you're good?
No, not her. It's what I think.
Ms. Jang never saw any of my stuff.
You never saw Mom and Dad draw.
You only heard that they were artists.
Did you ever learn how to draw?
I bet you didn't.
So how do you know how to draw?
When we were babies,
Mom and Dad
taught me how.
What are you? A genius?
So you just remembered
what they taught you when you were a baby?
Do you even
remember Mom and Dad?
How dare you try to bite your sister!
If you do that again, I'll bite you.
Oh, how frightening.
Good night, Yeong-hui.
And…
I'm…
sorry about…
the subway incident.
Yeong-ok.
Go make a lot of money
so I can get surgery.
All right.
So I can be pretty
like Byeol-i, Dal-i,
and you.
You got it!
Goodness.
I guess she wants to be pretty.
You'll have to make a ton of money
to make her look like you.
I know. I work hard to make money,
but I still have a long way to go.
She looks just fine.
She doesn't need surgery.
She's fine just as she is.
Don't exhaust yourself.
That's Yeong-ok's business, not yours.
She wants surgery
because people look at her strangely.
If people complimented her looks
and told her she was pretty all the time,
she wouldn't want surgery.
I'm sure she knows
it hurts to get surgery.
-Exactly.
-Hye-ja's right.
-Here.
-Would I look pretty if I get surgery too?
It'll cost a lot of money.
-Goodness.
-You have strong teeth.
It's nice to be young.
It really is nice to be young.
Goodness, look at them.
You almost had me.
-It's too much for us.
-I like candy too.
-Give us some too.
-Come on.
-Don't be so stingy.
-Exactly.
-Hand them out.
-Here.
What are you staring at?
Break up with Yeong-ok.
Watch it.
The girl I like is deaf,
and the girl you like
has a disabled sister.
How would our parents react to that?
It's not Dal-i.
I like Byeol-i.
I've liked her for a while.
I won't give up on her.
It's all Mom and Dad's fault
for giving birth to two handsome,
decent sons.
You drive the boat this afternoon.
I'm spending time with Yeong-hui.
Gosh.
Hurry up!
Why are they so late?
This tastes much better than the last one.
-Hi, ladies.
-Yeong-ok has gotten better at harvesting.
Yeong-hui, how's this?
Do you like it?
You buy it.
I have money too.
I work
at the care facility cafe.
I sell mocha lattes and ice coffees
and make money.
But I need to get surgery
so I can become pretty.
So you buy this.
You work at a cafe?
That's amazing.
Okay, I'll buy this for you.
Sir.
-Yes?
-We'll buy this one.
And about this…
-The photos?
-Yes.
Can you move the photos in here
to the new phone?
Yes, it's possible.
Thank you.
Yeong-hui, drink slowly.
And not as much as yesterday.
Tell me.
You like Yeong-ok
because she's pretty, don't you?
No, that's not why.
How should I put it?
Yeong-ok is nice.
Stop being funny.
Yeong-ok…
is sexy and pretty.
That's why you like her.
Guys who like girls based on their looks
and outer appearance
are all jerks.
Yeong-hui, I'm not that kind of guy.
I care more about what's inside.
Yeong-ok has a beautiful heart.
Then do you also…
like me?
Of course, I like you. You're adorable.
Then that means
I also have a beautiful heart.
But why don't I have a boyfriend?
I'm sure you'll meet a great guy like me.
I…
I won't be able to meet anyone.
Because…
guys only like girls who are pretty.
Do you want a boyfriend?
Of course.
Of course, I want a boyfriend.
I want to wear makeup,
and I want to look attractive.
I also want to know
what it's like to kiss someone.
But…
I don't have a boyfriend.
Guys are fools not to notice
how pretty you are.
You too.
You're right.
I fell for Yeong-ok because of her looks.
Gosh, I'm a jerk.
I need more alcohol.
I'm going to drink yours.
Yeong-ok is pretty.
I'm proud of her.
She's not like me.
She's attractive.
She's sexy.
I'm scared of the sea,
but she swims in it easily.
Yeong-ok is perfect.
She's pretty.
High-five.
You…
You're a really nice guy
for spending time with me.
Can I have that once you're done?
No.
I'm making it for Yeong-ok.
Hey, can you take this to that table?
Enjoy.
Excuse me.
-Can I have a cup of coffee?
-Oh, sure.
Just a second.
Turn off the stove.
Don't eat what's burnt.
Is everything okay?
I'm not spying on you.
Let me know if you need anything.
-Sir.
-Yes?
Can I ask you something?
What's the most popular brand?
The ones in that white box
are the most popular.
Then what's the most expensive one?
The ones in the red box.
-This one?
-Yes.
Try this. It's delicious.
Stop it.
Everyone in Seogwipo
knows that we're going out.
Just take it easy.
If we break up,
you'll be the one getting badmouthed.
People won't care how hard it was for you
to bear with everything.
They'll just condemn you
for breaking up with a girl
with a disabled sister.
People don't like you when you're
a woman with a disabled sister.
But people also hate guys
who break up with women like that.
That's cold.
Hey.
That's for talking nonsense.
Just make sure you don't dump me.
Wipe your face.
What was that for?
Come here.
Wipe your face.
-Right here.
-I can get you from here.
Hey, that's cold!
-That was nice.
-Nice pose.
-Great.
-Go on.
I'm smiling.
-Goodness.
-I hope I look nice.
Smile.
-One, two, three.
-One, two, three, go.
Pose.
Get ready.
Give me a nice pose.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Ms. Hyeon.
Yeong-hui can't draw.
She's just lying.
She only says that
because she likes getting attention.
Dong-i and Dong-seok.
It doesn't matter if she isn't that good.
Just let her give it a try.
Let her give it a try.
I sent the photos to Yeong-hui,
but don't get your hopes up.
Just don't get disappointed
even if she ends up giving you
a ridiculous drawing.
Yeong-hui, let's go.
Why would we get our hopes up?
When did we ever expect anything in life?
We always just go with the flow.
Yeong-ok, smile a little.
Did you guys fight?
Come on. Smile.
Stop it.
Can we stop now?
Kiss!
-Kiss!
Unbelievable.
My gosh.
Nice.
One, two, three.
-Yeong-hui.
-Yes?
The wind is blowing in your face.
There you go.
Stand right here.
-Here?
-Look here.
Try standing right here.
I don't like you.
I'm Park Gi-jun.
I've liked you since elementary school.
Why do you like me?
I can't even talk properly.
In order to talk to you,
I need to look at your eyes,
and they're beautiful.
I also like how you stare at me
when you talk to me.
See you tomorrow.
I…
I don't like guys who work at the sea.
If you don't like it,
I'll quit right away.
Just go out with me.
Why aren't you having fun?
I like being alone.
Do you enjoy solitude?
Who taught you the word "solitude"?
I…
I don't enjoy it.
I like being with you.
Do you like being in the sea?
Yes.
When I'm out in the sea,
there's no one else but me.
Do you like it there
because I'm not around?
Stop being ridiculous.
Let's go eat steak, your favorite.
Captain, let's go.
Here's what you ordered.
-Keep it down.
-Enjoy.
Thank you.
Eat up.
Yeong-hui, have this.
Stop…
Stop looking at me.
"Stop…"
"Stop looking at me."
Stupid.
Stop it.
Do you want to switch seats?
Stop…
Stop it.
Just eat your food.
I said, stop.
Your kid is making fun of my sister.
Please tell him to stop.
Tell him he shouldn't
stare at disabled people
or make fun of them.
Please.
Make sure you chew.
Stop! Why are you
making fun of a disabled person?
I hate you, Mom. I'm not going to eat.
That little…
Gosh.
This is so annoying.
I was looking forward to today.
The bathroom.
It's over there. Should I go with you?
Let's just go.
I lost my appetite.
What are you looking at?
We're going to leave
because we lost our appetite.
Your kid made fun of a disabled person,
so I asked you to make him stop.
Was that so appalling for you?
I already scolded my kid for doing that.
I told him not to mock a disabled person.
Do you have no manners?
Do you have to keep calling her disabled?
-What's the matter with you?
-What?
That's enough.
It's enough.
Sir, please stop.
You too, sir.
I'm sorry.
Do you like it
if I stare at you like this?
Give me your hand.
It's rude to make fun of adults.
It's rude to make fun of disabled people.
It's rude to stare too.
Do you like it when I stare?
You'll get punished for that, you know.
It's a red light.
You need to cross
when the light turns green.
Instead of leaving tomorrow,
maybe I should just live here, Captain.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're getting on a plane
and going back to the facility tomorrow,
like we promised.
Yeong-hui.
You can draw in my house. It's cold.
Come inside if it gets cold.
Okay.
Why don't you let Yeong-hui stay
for a couple more days?
The three of us can go on a trip.
Why?
Now that you've spent
about a week with her,
do you think
you can take care of her forever?
Don't kid yourself.
This is why I told you
not to be nice to her.
Why do you think I tried to break up
with a great guy like you?
Today's incident was nothing.
What you saw today was very minor.
I've experienced a lot worse.
I got into physical fights outside
and in restaurants
and got kicked out for making a scene.
I get it.
They're not familiar
with people like Yeong-hui.
They think she's weird.
So they just can't help but stare at her.
Do you know why
people aren't familiar
with disabled people like Yeong-hui?
Because most families send disabled people
to care facilities just like me.
I once thought of living with her.
But it was impossible
to find a place to live together,
and I couldn't even work.
If Yeong-hui
had gone to a normal school,
her condition could've gotten better.
But they refused to take her in,
and the special school was too far
because people didn't
want them in the city.
If I send her to a facility,
people call me cold and heartless.
If I don't, today's incident
becomes a daily routine.
So what am I supposed to do?
She knows everything!
Even dogs and cats have emotions.
Yeong-hui knows that
people think she's weird.
She knows that
I even tried
to abandon her on the subway
more than 20 years ago.
She remembers everything!
She knows how I feel right now.
She knows how much
I don't want to be with her.
That's why she's outside despite the cold.
She thinks disappearing from my sight
will help me cool my anger.
Even now, she's listening
to everything I'm saying.
But I'm going to act
like I don't know that.
I'm going to think that Yeong-hui doesn't
understand a word I'm saying
because she's too dumb
to think or feel anything.
I'm going to believe that
she's just dumb enough
to do what she's told.
That way, I won't have to feel so bad
about sending her back to the facility.
Because I live in a world
where I can't live with her.
Do you know what I think
when I meet those kinds of people?
"I hope they end up
with a kid like Yeong-hui."
"If not, then I hope
they get struck by lightning
or get into an accident
and become disabled."
Don't say that with your beautiful mouth.
Don't.
It's so unfair.
Why did I have to end up
with a sister like her?
Why did my parents leave me
to take care of her
when I'm not even a kind person?
It's so unfair.
You can't get any kinder than this.
I like you because you're kind.
I like the fact that
you couldn't abandon Yeong-hui.
But you see,
if I feel this way,
imagine how bad it must be for her.
No more than a can of beer each.
-Don't drink more than that.
-We'll just drink a can each.
No more.
Yeong-hui.
Your flight is tomorrow morning.
I'm not going.
Of course, you're going.
The sea looks scary.
Does it?
Then I'll just draw the curtains.
You're kind.
Of course, Yeong-hui.
Here.
When did you learn to drink?
After Yeong-ok became an adult
and broke up with Cheol-ung,
we went for drinks,
and that's when she taught me.
It was nice and refreshing.
What's this?
Take a look. They're my drawings.
Do you think Yeong-ok will like them?
Do you like them?
They're incredible.
When did you draw all these drawings?
I drew them whenever I got lonely.
Whenever I missed…
Whenever I missed Yeong-ok.
Everyone, I mean…
The ladies will love this.
I bet no one's ever seen
anything like this before.
I hope my adorable sister likes them.
You like her
even though she got angry at you?
That's just
how she's like.
But she's a nice girl.
She tried…
to abandon me,
but she didn't.
She even let me come to Jeju Island.
Yeong-ok will definitely love
these drawings.
She'll love them a lot.
But they're missing titles.
MS. HYEON
"Ms. Hyeon."
Nice handwriting.
Hang on.
Every artist should have their own seal.
MS. HYEON BY YEONG-HUI
It's a chick.
It's a bird.
A bird that's about to spread its wings
and fly into the sky.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
All right. Let's see.
Let's continue writing the titles.
Here. This one is "Dal-i."
"Dal…"
Yeong-hui, are you done packing?
It's almost time for your flight.
Hurry up and get ready.
You know how to pack your own stuff.
Yeong-hui.
What took you so long?
We need to get going.
It's 10 a.m.
I'll miss my flight.
Ms. Jang is waiting for me
at the care facility.
Go get your jacket.
I'll be back in a minute.
Yeong-hui.
Hey, Yeong-hui. It's me.
What are you doing?
You set it as your wallpaper.
-We look nice.
-Yes.
Please take good care of her.
Don't call me too often.
I'll be busy working.
Eat well and poop well.
Go to the hospital if you ever get sick.
Don't be scared of shots.
I'll see you in winter.
Make a lot of money
so I can get surgery.
Go on.
Bye.
Bye, Yeong-hui. I'll see you again.
Bye,
Captain and Yeong-ok.
You should go inside first.
I'll go get some coffee.
Okay.
MS. HYEON BY YEONG-HUI
MS. KANG BY YEONG-HUI
EUN-HUI BY YEONG-HUI
IN-GWON, HO-SIK, YEONG-JU, HYEON
BY YEONG-HUI
DAL-I BY YEONG-HUI
BYEOL-I BY YEONG-HUI
GI-JUN BY YEONG-HUI
HYE-JA BY YEONG-HUI
MS. HYEON'S GRANDDAUGHTER
EUN-GI'S FAMILY BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 12 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 14 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 18 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 19 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 24 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 23 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 25 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 26 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 28 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 27 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 31 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 33 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-OK, 38 YEARS OLD BY YEONG-HUI
MOM, DAD, YEONG-OK, YEONG-HUI
BY YEONG-HUI
YEONG-HUI AND YEONG-OK LOVE EACH OTHER
YEONG-OK AND JEONG-JUN IN LOVE
Later on, I asked Yeong-hui this.
"How did you learn to draw so well?"
Yeong-hui told me
that she drew me
whenever she missed me or got lonely,
which is how she became so good at it.
I didn't know what to say to that.
I couldn't imagine
how lonely she must've been
and how much she must've missed me
for a person like her
to become this great of an artist.
YEONG-OK ENJOYING SOLITUDE
WITHOUT YEONG-HUI
I was…
too scared to find out.
YEONG-HUI LOVES HER SISTER, YEONG-OK
PUREUNG
I'll come back in two weeks
to pick her up, Mother.
Mom…
Did you buy this for me?
I caught the chicken
out in that field over there.
You didn't even let me
ride on your shoulders.
She abandoned her kid
at her mother-in-law's.
-Watch what you say in front of the kid!
-Don't fight.
-Carry her on your shoulders.
-Me?
I'm starting to get suspicious
as time goes by.
Did your mom abandon you here?
Where has she gone
after abandoning her own child?