[A Forbidden Marriage]
[Episode 15]
[Yunmen]
[Yunxiao Hall]
I failed to capture Yuan Yingxing
and bring Junior Yao back.
Please punish me, Sect Leader.
Stand up and speak.
This isn't your fault.
Thanks to you,
Jin Buhuan's madness was stopped
and the Liansha Formation was broken,
preventing a great disaster.
Otherwise, not just Chief Lu,
but even I, the Alliance Leader,
would have no way to explain this
to the other sects.
Now that Yuan Yingxing is dead,
everyone can finally rest easy.
Yuan Yingxing is still alive.
What?
The reports said
he died in the flames.
That was wrong.
I feared it would cause more trouble,
so I kept quiet about it.
With the recent turmoil in Biluo Valley,
all sects have returned to their homes,
so it's unlikely to gather them again
for another  suppression.
Indeed, this matter should
remain confidential.
Wait.
Fu hasn't returned yet.
Could Yuan Yingxing have captured her?
Junior Yao will be fine.
Yuan Yingxing won't harm her.
How can you be so certain?
Yuan Yingxing still has feelings
for Junior Yao,
and she's not completely indifferent
to him either.
Impossible!
Fu would never fall for someone
from the Shengyue Sect.
It must've been Yuan Yingxing
who used some underhanded tricks.
We must rescue Fu as soon as possible.
I'll summon the other sect leaders now
and send people after Yuan Yingxing.
Most likely,
Yuan Yingxing is on his way to Mount Yin,
intending to
rebuild the Shengyue Sect there.
The terrain there is too complicated.
None of our fellow disciples
have been there before.
Going there recklessly
would be too dangerous.
You have a point.
With the recent upheaval in Biluo Valley,
all sects are already exhausted
from travel.
Even if we pursue him now,
we wouldn't have any advantage.
How about this:
if it really comes down to it,
I'll personally make the trip
to rescue Fu.
You are the leader of our sect
and the alliance leader of all the sects.
It's not appropriate for you
to risk yourself.
Besides,
with Junior Yao's martial skills,
although she can't defeat Yuan Yingxing,
she can certainly protect herself.
Moreover,
Yuan Yingxing really wouldn't harm her.
What do you think we should do?
We can't just let Fu
stay with the Shengyue Sect
for years again, can we?
Actually, it's not that difficult
to solve this.
You often say that peace is precious.
Could the Shengyue Sect and we
resolve this matter peacefully?
"Resolve this peacefully?"
For instance,
negotiation.
"Negotiation?"
Those shameless lowlifes
don't deserve to negotiate with us!
Sect Leader,
not everyone in the Shengyue Sect is
beyond redemption.
They just don't follow the proper rules.
The deep-seated grudge between
the Shengyue Sect
and the entire martial world
cannot be explained
in just a few words!
Qing, you're too young.
Alright, go back and rest now.
As for Fu,
I'll think of something.
Sect Leader,
I... have one more thing.
What is it?
I want to get married.
You want to get married?
To whom?
That Miss Yang you brought back?
It is she.
I truly wish to marry her.
I remember her.
She acts inappropriately with men
in public,
showing no sense of decorum.
You and she are
from completely different worlds.
Among our major sects,
there are plenty of young women
who admire you.
And it wouldn't be difficult
to select a few well-mannered young women
of suitable status
for you.
Moreover,
you've been betrothed to Fu
since childhood.
Is Fu not good enough compared to her?
Why throw away
all these suitable matches
for some village girl?
I suppose it's because she's prettier.
Be serious!
Sect Leader,
I don't care
how amazing they are
or how perfect they might seem for me.
I love Wangyue.
I only want to marry her,
and I will marry only her.
Please give us your blessing.
You...
We haven't dealt with
the Shengyue Sect yet.
How can you still have the heart
to fuss over your love affairs?
At a critical time like this,
forget about getting married.
I must marry her.
I've already promised her.
You!
This trip down the mountain
has made you forget all your cultivation.
Do you still care about this sect?
Do you still respect me
as the Sect Leader?
I should never have let you
leave the sect.
Say no more.
Go to your room and reflect
while confined.
You're not coming out
until you've thought it through!
I won't change my mind.
[Yunmen]
Mr. Yang,
it's been three days already.
You haven't eaten
or had anything to drink.
Even a man of iron couldn't endure this.
Please eat something, at least.
I'm fine.
You may leave.
Sect Leader.
It's been three days,
and he still refuses to eat anything?
Not even a single bite.
What do you know about Miss Yang,
who returned with you?
Miss Yang is an orphan from Yangliu Town.
She has an uncle
who serves in the Shengyue Sect
and is not very familiar with
proper etiquette.
Sect Leader,
why are you asking about her?
Just curious.
She has an uncle in the Shengyue Sect...
She isn't a member of
the Shengyue Sect herself, is she?
No, no.
How could Mr. Yang possibly
bring someone from the Shengyue Sect back
to our sect?
According to her,
she has already cut all ties
with her relative in the Shengyue Sect.
It's just that...
Just what? Speak clearly.
It's just that, in my view,
her principles and behavior
are quite similar to those of
the Shengyue Sect members.
On our way back,
she kept clinging to Mr. Yang.
While she did provide us with much help,
she also caused quite a bit of trouble.
How does she compare to Ms. Yao?
Naturally, they're worlds apart.
She's just a small-town girl.
How could she possibly compare to Ms. Yao?
Yang Qing is suffering himself like this
for a village girl.
I'd like to see how long he can hold out.
You may go now.
Yes.
Miss Yang?
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I've been here three days
and haven't seen so much as
a glimpse of Yang Qing.
If he won't come to me,
I'll just have to go to him.
Mr. Yang has been confined
by the Sect Leader.
No one is allowed to see him now.
Miss Yang, you should leave now.
Yang Qing has been confined?
Why?
Well, your sect
is being completely unreasonable.
Yang Qing worked so hard out there
for so long,
and he gets confined
as soon as he returns?
This won't do. I'm breaking him out.
Yang Qing!
Miss Yang, you can't do this!
Without the Sect Leader's permission,
Mr. Yang cannot come out.
That old fool.
You might as well just let him
starve to death!
Wangyue!
Yang Qing.
You're so skilled at martial arts,
so can't you come out yourself?
I could.
Then why don't you?
It's not that I cannot come out,
but that I shouldn't.
The Sect Leader has punished me
by making me reflect in my room.
How could I just brush off what he said?
How long are you going to
lock yourself up in here?
Can't you just apologize and come out?
Who said anything about apologizing?
I'm reflecting in solitude
until the Sect Leader softens up.
The more miserable I look,
the faster he'll give in.
If you don't come out soon,
I'll go find another lover.
I've got plenty of men I like,
and even more chasing after me.
You wouldn't even make the list.
Indeed,
you like tons of men.
I'm not even in the running.
Miss Yang,
this isn't a place for chatting.
You should leave now.
It'll be even more troublesome
if the Sect Leader comes.
He'll come...
So, what exactly did you do wrong
that made things so tense
between you and your Sect Leader?
He said that I was out of my mind.
He's the one who's out of his mind!
Because I told him...
I want to marry you.
What?
Yang Qing, you're not lying to me,
are you?
You're not teasing me, right?
Miss Yang, hurry up and go.
Yang Qing, I'll come see you again!
Go!
Wangyue,
if you see the Sect Leader,
you must control your temper
and don't argue with him!
Jiang Yan, Jiang Yan.
Why exactly has Yang Qing been confined?
Well,
he just said a few words
to the Sect Leader and then got locked up?
Could it be...
I don't know the details,
but it seems Mr. Yang failed to
bring Ms. Yao back,
and the Sect Leader was displeased.
He was just teasing me again.
How dare you say it was because
you wanted to marry me?
Miss Yang? Miss Yang.
Well,
I have something to ask you.
It's about Miss Lin.
When the incident happened
at Biluo Valley,
I hadn't yet settled her somewhere safe
before the Sect Leader sent me away.
I wonder if Miss Lin is doing well now.
Miss Lin?
You mean Lin Yin, right?
Don't worry, she's doing very well.
Where is she now?
It's dangerous for a woman
to be alone out there.
Perhaps
I should go and bring her back here?
You're worrying for nothing.
Lin Yin is perfectly capable of
taking care of herself.
She's probably somewhere enjoying herself
right now.
Alright then.
I was overthinking.
Why is he acting so weird?
Young Chief!
How is my father?
Young Chief.
Is he feeling better?
The Chief is out of danger now.
He just asked you to go to Yunmen.
Yunmen?
Yuan Yingxing is already dead,
and their investigation into
the missing children has hit a dead end.
What is Father still worried about?
Here's the thing:
the Chief is very pleased
that Yuan Yingxing is dead,
but we still haven't found
the Shengyue Token,
which is the Moon Blade
that Jin Buhuan spoke of.
So, we don't know if Yunmen still holds
the full Alliance Leader's Token—
the Sun and Moon Blades.
Oh, right,
Jin Buhuan activated the Liansha Formation
without permission,
causing such a huge mess.
Where is he now?
That's also
what the Chief is worried about.
After the battle in Miyun Forest,
Jin Buhuan disappeared without a trace.
The Chief fears that he might have found
the Moon Blade
and wants to keep it for himself.
He's already sent more people
to search for him.
He's disappeared?
That's actually better.
Then he won't pester me anymore.
And my trip to Yunmen will be much easier.
Oh, right.
This is the Yunmen token.
Please keep it safe.
With this token,
except for the forbidden ground,
you can freely access any place in Yunmen.
They're currently recruiting
new disciples.
The Chief has arranged everything
for you to go there as an herbalist
and find out the truth
about the Alliance Leader's Token.
But ever since the missing children case,
they have been suspicious of us.
Previously, when we used Jin Buhuan,
his brutal methods
caused strong opposition from them.
I'm afraid that even if I go there,
it'll be hard to find any openings.
Young Chief, don't worry.
The Chief has already shifted
all the blame onto
Jin Buhuan, the Gold Hall Master,
so we're basically free from suspicion.
Besides,
our Biluo Valley claims the primary credit
for Yuan Yingxing's death.
That's what gave you
this great opportunity
to study at Yunmen.
Your visit this time is
under the pretense of
exchanging martial arts techniques
between our two sects.
But the exchange isn't important,
nor is the studying.
What's important is that you need to
make good use of these few months
to find out
if the Moon Blade has truly been lost,
as Jin Buhuan claimed.
I understand.
I'll do my best to investigate.
Once we confirm
that the Moon Blade is lost,
we can legitimately
strip Yunmen
of their Alliance Leader position.
Yes.
And one more thing:
after much deliberation, the Chief
has decided to give you the scripture
of the Six Harmonies Divine Art.
He hopes
you'll practice diligently
to prepare for any unforeseen danger.
Father should have given this to me
long ago.
With this, my martial skills
will greatly improve,
and Mr. Yang will surely see me
in a new light.
Sect Leader Feng,
I heard you wanted to see me.
When my disciples were training outside,
you helped them a great deal.
I thank you on their behalf.
Sect Leader Feng,
you're being too kind.
People of the martial world
should help those in need.
Besides,
Yang Qing and I have
a special relationship.
His business is my business.
What exactly is your relationship
with Yang Qing?
Whatever Yang Qing says
our relationship is,
that's what it is.
So it really is you
who's been clinging to Yang Qing,
making him forget
the rules and proper conduct.
I was just about to ask you about that.
Why have you confined Yang Qing?
What did he do wrong?
Do you know he hasn't had
any food or water for days?
This is an internal affair of our sect.
It's none of your concern.
You're a girl
and have been away from home for so long.
Your family must be worried.
You should hurry back to Yangliu Town.
I'll make all the necessary arrangements.
I no longer have any family
remaining in Yangliu Town.
Yang Qing is the closest person
I have now.
He promised to let me stay here.
I'll wait for him to come out.
Sect Leader,
please let me stay.
We have our own rules here.
Those who don't respect
propriety and rules
cannot stay.
You can go ask around in Yangliu Town.
I come from a proper family.
Then tell me, what do you like about Qing?
Who wouldn't like a talented young man
like Yang Qing?
It's that simple?
It's that simple.
No, no, let me rephrase that.
Yang Qing is unworldly,
noble, and upright in character.
I need to learn from him in the future.
Qing is indeed a rare and good young man.
However, Miss Yang,
you're still young.
Matters of the heart
are not that simple.
You haven't known Yang Qing very long.
You only see his surface.
You don't truly understand him.
Matters of the heart
aren't complicated at all.
If you're worried
that I don't know him well enough,
then please let him out quickly
so that I can spend more time with him
to know him better.
Nonsense!
Your pestering of Yang Qing like this
isn't good for either of you.
What harm could come from
a romantic relationship?
If you're really so worried,
why don't you...
let us get married?
Then everything would be proper.
You're a girl.
How can you speak so carelessly
about marriage?
Tell me,
what will it take for you
to leave Yang Qing alone?
He's not someone you're worthy of.
Sect Leader Feng, that's rather hurtful.
May I ask
who would be worthy of Yang Qing then?
Qing has a fiancée.
They've been childhood sweethearts.
Whether in personality, interests,
or virtue,
they are perfectly matched.
When Fu returns,
they will be married.
That shameless, vicious woman
could never be worthy of Yang Qing.
Yang Qing couldn't possibly like her.
They have no future together!
Please watch your words.
Fu is clever, beautiful, and virtuous.
She has never caused
any trouble for our sect.
She even risked her life,
leading all other sects
in eliminating the Shengyue Sect.
She is the pride of our sect,
more than worthy to be Qing's wife.
Seducing the Chief of the Shengyue Sect—
you call that virtuous and proper?
Ruthless and merciless are more like it.
When dealing with aberrations
like the Shengyue Sect,
we can't always play by the rules.
As they say, all's fair in war.
May I ask, Sect Leader Feng,
if someone were to use
the same dirty tricks
against your sect in the future,
would that also be considered
"all's fair in war"?
What utter drivel!
What would a village girl like you
understand?
Miss Yang,
you and Yang Qing will never be together.
You'd better leave quietly
before I have to force you out.
I'll leave if you want,
but shouldn't you offer me something
in return?
Fine. Name it.
1,000 taels.
What?
We will not be blackmailed!
Is your sect really this poor?
Such a small amount of money
can shock someone as mighty as you,
the Sect Leader?
How pathetic.
You...
[Yunmen]
Young Chief,
this is Yunmen's training ground.
After they've chosen their new disciples,
we won't be able to stay here anymore.
Later,
you'll need to familiarize yourself with
the terrain here
and memorize the guard positions...
Enough already.
You've been talking forever,
and my ears are numb.
Those are all the Chief's orders.
He's afraid that you'll be
thinking only of Elder Yang from Yunmen
and forget your mission.
This time, no matter what,
I will definitely succeed.
I didn't even catch a glimpse of
the Sun Blade,
and I was kicked out of Yunmen.
And Yang Qing has been confined.
What should I do?
Miss Yang!
How could you leave
without saying anything?
Your Sect Leader personally ordered me
to leave.
Should I have shamelessly stayed
and refused to leave?
The Sect Leader just...
He just thinks I'm a pretty village girl
with nothing to offer,
not worthy of your Elder Yang.
Miss Yang, don't think like that.
The Sect Leader just needs some time
to accept it.
Besides,
Mr. Yang and Ms. Yao have been engaged
for a long time.
Then tell me,
who's better, me or your Ms. Yao?
Well...
Jiang Yan,
I'm so disappointed in you.
I've been so good to you,
yet you can't even answer
such a simple question?
Don't you forget,
who was it
that found someone to cure your poison,
and who was it
that helped you deal with the villagers
from Yangliu Town?
I'm so disappointed.
Miss Yang.
Miss Yang, don't go.
Why are so many people gathered there?
Something happened?
Our sect recruits new disciples
at this time every year.
That's our sect's registration point.
All those who want to join our sect
need to register here
and then participate in the selection.
The new disciple selection?
Are there any special requirements?
Not really.
Anyone can participate.
There's no threshold.
It's just
that the selection isn't easy to pass.
The elders will personally oversee
the process.
So, the newly admitted disciples
can also stay at
your sect permanently like you?
Of course.
We disciples are not permitted
to leave the mountain
without special tasks.
Interesting.
I'll go take a look.
Miss Yang!
Sect Leader.
Miss Yang has already left.
I never thought
she was that kind of woman.
For money,
she betrayed Mr. Yang.
Mr. Yang hasn't eaten for five days
because of her.
This might be for the best.
Let Yang Qing see her true colors
and sever his feelings for her
once and for all.
Shang Huai,
ask him to come out.
He's been refusing food and water.
Even the strongest man can't endure that.
Yes, Sect Leader.
You truly care about Mr. Yang the most.
I hope he understands my good intentions.
Don't worry, Sect Leader.
Mr. Yang understands what's important.
He won't abandon our sect
for the sake of a woman.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Miss Yang!
Let me through, let me through.
Miss Yang.
Don't stop me.
I'm going to pass the trials
and join your sect,
fair and square.
Then we'll see who still dares to
look down on me as a village girl.
Miss Yang,
you need to think this through.
If you join our sect,
you'll have to formally address him as
"Mr. Yang."
In our sect,
there's absolutely no other possibility
between an elder and a disciple.
That serious?
It's just a title, isn't it?
If you become my junior,
the Sect Leader will be
even less accepting of
you and Mr. Yang getting together.
He doesn't accept me now anyway.
I don't care.
I'm determined to stay at your sect.
I'm not only going to pester Yang Qing,
but I'm also going to
have an epic romance with him
just to spite your Sect Leader.
Miss Yang.
Let go of me.
Mr. Yang!
What's wrong?
Miss Yang...
in order not to be driven away
by the Sect Leader,
so she's applying to join our sect.
She's already filled in her name
and is about to take part in
the selection.
Mr. Yang, what should we do?
Mr. Yang, where are you going?
I'm going down the mountain.
But the Sect Leader has confined you.
Tell the Sect Leader
that I'm probably out of my mind
to think of marrying her,
and I'll explain to him when I return.
[Name Card]
Miss, you're from Yangliu Town.
And your name is?
Yang Wangyue.
My name is Yang Wangyue.
That's the same name as
the Saintess of the Shengyue Sect.
Please wait a moment, miss.
Let me check the disciples
registered from Yangliu Town this year.
Sir,
your Elder Yang Qing
is also from our Yangliu Town.
I want to join your sect
because he said
I have an exceptional physique
and I'm a martial arts prodigy.
Don't believe me? Feel for yourself.
Miss, Miss Yang.
I believe you.
Since Mr. Yang praised you,
you must be exceptional.
No need to check. Please go right in.
[Yunmen]
It's fine, it's fine.
As a proud Jianchuan heir, I've practiced
martial arts since I was a child.
Although our sect has declined,
my father always says I'm talented.
Yunmen's requirements aren't that high.
I'm sure I can get in.
Miss,
I believe the one who tested you earlier
was Elder Wang Yuanhao from Yunmen.
He's known to be strict.
Did he give you a hard time?
Such elementary questions,
and he thought he could trip me up?
That's basic knowledge
to all martial artists.
I'm Jiang Yu. And you?
Yang Wangyue.
Look,
that's Mr. Yang Qing, an elder
from Yunmen.
If we're fortunate enough
to become new disciples of the sect,
we must respectfully address him as
"Mr. Yang."
Him?
That's right.
He's so young.
He doesn't even look as old as I am.
Exactly.
He seems a bit too young.
Elder Yang is exceptionally talented,
and his martial skills far surpass
his peers.
He's the youngest elder in the sect.
Many juniors are actually
older than him now.
You'll get used to it.
Sir, you seem to know a lot about Yunmen.
My name is Yang Wangyue.
May I ask your name?
Su Ming.
The elder is here.
The final round of testing is complete.
After our elders' deliberation,
you have all passed the test!
We've all passed!
-Greetings, Sect Leader!
These are the new disciples
who just joined this year?
They all appear to have good potential.
Sect Leader Feng.
We meet again.
What?
You...
How did you become a fellow disciple?
Who let you pass?
Sect Leader,
Miss Yang's aptitude, talent,
and character
are all excellent.
What's wrong with accepting her?
Her? Excellent?
Do you know how much it cost me
to get her to leave?
What?
She is the village girl
who has bewitched Junior Yang?
Well...
How about
I expel her right now?
Expelling a disciple who has just joined,
in front of them all—
wouldn't that damage our sect's prestige?
Sect Leader, don't worry.
She definitely won't pass
the entrance examination
in a month from now.
Then we'll have every reason to expel her.
Within this month,
if anything happens,
I'll hold you accountable.
Yang Qing,
when were you released?
I'm now a disciple here,
and I can enter and leave the sect openly.
Yang Wangyue,
do you realize what you've done?
You mean today?
You know what?
I just casually showed a few moves,
and the elders were impressed.
I got admitted to the sect so easily.
Aren't I amazing?
Do you know what it means
to be my junior disciple?
Is that what you're worried about?
Isn't it just a form of address?
Why take it so seriously?
Is it really that important?
I need to go now.
Not important?
Then what is important to you?
Yang Qing, what's wrong?
You... You're scaring me
when you act like this.
Wangyue.
I was wrong.
Why are you suddenly calling me
by my name?
Are... are you angry?
Why do you always
act like you don't know anything?
Since the day we returned
from Biluo Valley,
I've checked your horse myself every day,
only letting you ride
after making sure it was safe.
I didn't know that.
I remember your birthday.
Even though it's the wrong one,
I remember it clearly.
But what about you?
Have you ever asked me about my birthday?
I know exactly what foods you like.
But what about you?
During meals,
you always pick what you like for me,
assuming that I like the same things
you do.
But in reality,
you have no idea what I like
or what I dislike!
You need to give me some time. I'm trying.
When we returned here,
I told you that I wanted to marry you.
But what about you?
Did you think I was joking?
Have you ever seriously asked
how I planned to provide for you
or how I planned to
talk to the Sect Leader?
Because I trust you.
No.
You never tell me
what you're really thinking.
Whenever something happens,
you always beat around the bush.
Do you think I'm just someone
easy to manipulate?
What do you take me for?
It's not like that.
I just wanted to go along with
your wishes.
Go along with me?
So, you've become my junior disciple
in the sect?
What exactly were you thinking?
Your Sect Leader Feng doesn't want me
to hold you back
or pester you,
so he's tried every way to drive me out.
I couldn't bear to part with you.
That's why I came up with this solution.
Yang Qing,
I have to address you as "Mr. Yang" now.
Don't you think it's funny
when I address you like that?
Funny?
I have countless junior disciples.
I can't even remember any of their names!
I can't even remember their faces!
They're the ones who recognize me!
Do you think I care about
having one more junior disciple?
And are you really
an important junior disciple to me?
Yang Qing, what do you mean by that?
Just say what you want to say.
Don't beat around the bush.
Yang Wangyue,
do you realize
you've undone all my efforts?
I was in a tug of war
with the Sect Leader,
standing my ground against him.
I was begging him to let me marry you.
And he was about to give in.
You... you really told him
that you want to marry me?
What else did you think?
In just a few more days,
he would have softened.
I haven't eaten a single bite
in five days.
What do you think I was enduring it for?
For you to become my junior disciple?
Wait... you...
♪ Time flows like sand in an hourglass,
counting down to forever ♪
♪ Only at the moment we met did I learn
what pain and sorrow truly are ♪
Yang Wangyue.
You're heartless.
You know full well that I love you,
yet you still joined the sect,
♪ The cold wind softens little by little ♪
treating it like some kind of joke.
♪ Though carefree, I can't resist the gaze
written in my fate ♪
What do you take me for?
You never told me,
so how was I supposed to know?
I didn't tell you?
You didn't!
♪ I vow never to look back
for the rest of my life ♪
How... how can you blame me for this?
♪ Betting on forever ♪
I misunderstood,
but you weren't being clear.
♪ I dare to let go of right and wrong
and stay by your side ♪
You didn't speak directly,
so how was I supposed to know
what you needed me to do?
Y-You just expect me to
figure it out!
Yes,
♪ Unafraid of hardships
or raging torrents ♪
I just expect you to figure it out.
Wasn't I clear enough?
♪ I see longing with new clarity ♪
♪ Love can heal all pain ♪
Think about it carefully again.
Yang Qing!
Yang Qing,
if you don't cooperate with me
and talk to me properly,
I won't marry you.
You think you're some peerless beauty?
You think I'm so eager to marry you?
Qing,
since you've come out,
you must have realized your mistake.
I was reckless.
I shouldn't have defied you, Sect Leader.
Now that you've seen
Yang Wangyue's true colors,
you should come to your senses
and return to the right path.
Wangyue is just a bit willful,
not the "heretical sort" as you claim.
You're still defending her.
Earlier, I had to give her
a large sum of money
just to make her leave.
It's only been a few days,
and she's back again.
She even became a disciple
of our sect now.
But we cannot tolerate
such a money-grubbing,
smooth-talking person.
Since she's passed Senior Wang's trial,
it proves she has her strengths.
You've often said yourself that
we shouldn't judge the whole by a part.
Enough.
I won't waste time
debating over one woman with you,
nor do I care what virtues she has
or how she joined us.
If she doesn't pass
next month's entrance exam,
she must leave.
Also,
you are now Yang Wangyue's senior.
You should mind your boundaries
and keep your feelings in check.
I don't want to hear any gossip.
Otherwise,
I will severely punish both of you.
Yes, Sect Leader.
Regarding the case of missing children
in Yangliu Town,
you said it's related to Biluo Valley.
This matter is indeed related to
Biluo Valley,
but not entirely so.
What do you mean?
Take a look at this.
This is a wanted notice from Biluo Valley.
[Wanted]
Jin Buhuan?
According to their message,
they were also deceived by Jin Buhuan.
Jin Buhuan didn't truly repent.
He only pretended to side with us.
After joining the Biluo Valley,
he abducted children from Yangliu Town
for personal gain.
He also manipulated Biluo Valley disciples
to hunt down Yuan Yingxing
to seize the position
of Shengyue Sect Chief.
What do you think of this?
It must be Chief Lu's excuse.
All four major sects are ashamed
to associate with the Shengyue Sect.
Jin Buhuan was cunning.
Chief Lu's willingness to trust Jin Buhuan
is, in itself, very suspicious.
To atone for this matter,
Chief Lu even brought generous gifts
and personally apologized to
all the other major sects.
After the battle at Mount Yin,
Yuan Yingxing escaped
while being escorted to Biluo Valley.
To save face,
Chief Lu kept it under wraps.
Then Jin Buhuan approached him again,
offering to help capture Yuan Yingxing.
And he believed it.
Now that Jin Buhuan is dead,
there's no way to verify anything.
Are you sure he's dead?
In Miyun Forest,
the body thought to be Yuan Yingxing's
should actually be Jin Buhuan.
Then, we can only trust Biluo Valley.
Besides,
they have no motive to abduct children.
But I still think this case is
full of doubts.
If we investigate this matter,
it'll consume
a lot of manpower and resources.
Moreover,
all the abducted children
have returned home,
and the real culprit, Jin Buhuan,
is already dead.
So let this matter end here.
There are still many suspicious aspects
of this case.
Please let me continue the investigation.
Now that the new disciples have joined
and Yuan Yingxing has fled to Mount Yin,
we should focus on
more important matters.
Alright,
let's handle this matter as I said.
Yes, Sect Leader.
Mr. Yang!
Mr. Yang.
Thank you for helping me up, Mr. Yang.
Mr. Yang,
the room I'm staying in
has drafty windows and a leaking roof.
Could you please...
It hasn't rained these past few days.
It's raining right now.
Mr. Yang,
could you really bear to let me shiver
in the wind and get soaked in the rain?
Jiang Yan will handle
dormitory repair.
There's no need for me
to do it personally.
How could Jiang Yan enter my boudoir?
You should be the one to fix it, Mr. Yang.
Yang Wangyue,
since you're so eager to join the sect
as my junior disciple,
you should keep your distance from me.
I don't want others
to misunderstand anything between us.
Why...
why are you calling me by my full name?
Since you formally address me,
you should behave
like a proper junior disciple.
I...
From now on,
don't say inappropriate things
or do inappropriate actions.
Junior Yang, do you understand?
I...
Well, well, who do we have here?
Turns out it's just
a newly admitted outer disciple.
What? Still keeping your wicked ways?
Still acting like a witch,
even after joining our Yunmen Sect?
What's it to you?
To me? Naturally, it's no concern.
I just wanted to give you
a friendly reminder.
There will be a trial in a month,
and I'm afraid some people
will have to leave in disgrace by then.
Listen, Lu Xuanxuan,
you're from Biluo Valley,
so why are you here interfering in
our sect's affairs?
Miss Yang,
you mustn't be disrespectful to Senior Lu.
Senior?
Mr. Yang,
I've prepared all the herbs
that the Sect Leader requested.
You promised to teach me swordsmanship,
so don't go back on your word.
You mustn't teach her.
And you mustn't learn!
That's not for you to decide.
You woman...
Miss Yang, watch your words.
Miss Lu here is
the herbalist invited by the Sect Leader.
If you offend her,
the Sect Leader won't let you off.
Yang Qing...
Miss Lu, let's go to the training ground.
Whatever techniques you want to learn,
I'll teach you.
Okay.
Jiang Yan,
say that again.
Lu Xuanxuan is the herbalist
invited by the sect.
Would Biluo Valley really be so kind?
I say she surely has ulterior motives.
Mr. Yang,
every time Yang Wangyue is around,
you promise to teach me swordsmanship,
but as soon as she leaves,
you make excuses and hurry away.
You can't make any more excuses today.
Miss Lu...
Mr. Yang, if you brush me off again
this time,
I'll have no choice but to
speak to the Sect Leader about this.
After all,
I came here hoping to learn something.
Last time I saw you perform
a sword technique,
smooth and flowing,
like a startled dragon or a soaring swan.
Would you teach me that technique?
That's called the Suwen Sword Technique.
Alright.
This sword technique
focuses on spirit, not form.
Those moves are "Sunset"
and "Lone Wild Goose."
When practicing, Miss Lu,
you must pierce the sunset
and point at the lone wild goose.
If you can master these two moves,
I'll teach you the rest of the technique.
Please give me more guidance, Mr. Yang.
This sword technique
requires someone
with profound inner strength to execute.
Don't worry
if you can't master it right away,
Miss Lu.
I understand.
Lu Xuanxuan is young
and has always been pampered.
She absolutely cannot
develop such profound inner strength
in a short time.
Unless...
How was that, Mr. Yang?
Did I make any mistakes
in my swordplay just now?
Miss Lu, one of your moves seemed
a bit too forceful.
Why don't you try it again?
Alright.
Mr. Yang,
I might have exerted myself too much
just now,
and I'm feeling unwell.
Perhaps we could continue another day?