[A Forbidden Marriage]
[Episode 11]
Miss Yao has two extremely serious wounds,
one on her shoulder
and one on her abdomen.
They don't appear to have been inflicted
by the same person.
Both wounds are extremely deep
and weren't treated promptly.
So, they've begun to worsen.
If they continue to worsen,
her life will be in danger.
She will die?
If the wounds don't heal,
her days are numbered.
How can we heal her wounds?
The healing depends on her own strength.
All I can do is clean her wounds daily.
You can't cure her.
Is there anyone else who can?
If my lady can't heal her,
then no one under heaven can.
She's been unconscious for so long.
I fear the worst.
If she dies,
both of you will join her in death.
You...
Sir, if you
continue with this attitude,
I'll have to ask you to leave.
What are you doing?
Is there really no way to save her?
Sir, if you insist on behaving this way,
I won't help her
even if you kill me.
Let go of my lady now!
My lady kindly saved your lives.
If you can't show gratitude,
that's one thing,
but now you want to kill her?
Save her.
Apologize.
My lady,
don't be so confrontational with him.
Don't we still have another way
to save her?
Don't talk nonsense.
My lady!
I apologize for what I did just now.
Please save her.
She can only recover on her own.
You truly want to save her this badly?
At any cost?
I have unfinished business with her.
She cannot die.
Please, I'm begging you.
Here is a Nine-Eyed Ice Silkworm
that can devour rotting flesh
and heal wounds.
But it has remained dormant
for many years.
To use it, you must awaken it.
The process is extremely painful.
Are you willing to try?
What should I do?
The Nine-Eyed Ice Silkworm feeds on
human blood,
preferably from someone
with deep internal strength cultivation.
But because it has been dormant
for so long,
even with sufficient blood,
there's no guarantee it will awaken.
It all depends on fate.
Okay.
What?
There's nothing wrong
with the Alliance Leader's Token?
I secretly gathered information
the other night.
Feng Xingyun truly isn't worried about
the token
and has already entrusted it
to Yang Qing for safekeeping.
Buhuan.
Didn't you tell me
that the Yunmen only has the Sun Blade—
half of the Alliance Leader's Token—
making their leader's position
illegitimate?
What's going on here?
Impossible.
The Moon Blade is the Shengyue Token.
It should be with Yuan Yingxing,
definitely not with Yunmen.
Father,
the Alliance Leader's Token is
of great importance.
If Yunmen still has the Moon Blade,
and you encourage Feng Xingyun to display
both blades at your birthday banquet,
wouldn't you be giving them
a chance to shine at your expense?
I'm willing to
investigate this matter for you, Father.
You?
You've failed at every task
I've given you.
Father,
I promise there won't be
any problems this time.
Please trust me once more.
Don't disappoint me again this time.
You claimed you were going to
help the Chief look into the token.
I think you just want to see Yang Qing.
So what if I do?
It's none of your business.
You and Yang Qing can never be together.
I can't be with Yang Qing,
but I can be with you?
Just look at yourself.
Xuanxuan.
I really care about you.
I don't need it.
Get lost before I really get angry.
Don't interfere with my mission.
-Let's go.
I heard from people in Biluo Valley
that every night at 9 PM,
there are fewer guards,
so there shouldn't be as many now.
Who's there?
Wh-Which sect do they belong to?
Behaving so shamelessly in public!
Don't talk nonsense.
There have been many distinguished guests
in the valley lately.
Watch your mouth,
or you might offend someone.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Go.
That was close.
Let's get out of here now.
What are you doing?
Still savoring that moment?
You...
Wanna attract more guards?
Let's go. Hurry up.
Yang Wangyue?
It's not in Feng Xingyun's room.
Then it must be in Yang Qing's room.
That little tramp, Yang Wangyue,
sneaking into Mr. Yang's room
in the middle of the night.
Could she be
trying to seduce Mr. Yang again?
I just needed a reason to search for
the Alliance Leader's Token in his room.
Her sneaking in there
gives me the perfect opportunity.
Looks like
this cabinet is the only place
where the Sun Blade could be kept.
I just saw a thief
breaking into Mr. Yang's room!
Go in and search!
We can't let the thief get away with this!
-Yes!
Check the roof beams, under the bed,
and behind the screen—
search every corner thoroughly.
Go!
-Yes!
Wait.
Miss Lu, you're causing quite a commotion
by searching my room.
Has something happened?
Mr. Yang,
I just saw a thief
sneaking into your room.
Please wait a moment.
Once we find them,
we'll teach them a good lesson.
Someone broke into my room?
Yes.
This is intact,
and there's no one in the closet either.
That's weird.
Not on the ceiling beam,
not under the bed,
and not inside the closet either.
Where else could they possibly hide
as a living person?
Could it really be
some spirit-possessed rat?
But nothing's missing
from my room.
But I really wasn't mistaken.
Mr. Yang,
you need to check carefully.
Are you certain nothing's gone?
The most valuable thing
in my room is
this Alliance Leader's Token.
Now that it's safe and sound
in the room,
how could anything else be missing?
Perhaps I was mistaken.
We're sorry for disturbing you, Mr. Yang.
We haven't been good hosts.
Miss Lu, you were just eager to
catch the thief.
Don't blame yourself.
What are you standing around for?
We've completely embarrassed ourselves.
Let's go!
-Yes.
Mr. Yang, I'll take my leave now.
All right.
Come out.
Wangyue.
They're gone. Come out now.
You could still fall asleep?
What am I going to do with you?
Are they all gone?
Yes, they've left.
Thanks to you,
or else they would've called me a thief.
But aren't you a thief?
Of course not.
Then why are you hiding in my room?
Care to explain?
I...
I just missed you, that's all.
You missed me inside my closet?
Yang Qing,
you have to believe me.
The moment I came in,
I heard footsteps outside.
Lu Xuanxuan was calling about a thief.
She already hates me,
so if she could accuse me of stealing,
she'd have a legitimate reason
to kick me out of Biluo Valley.
I...
I was just desperate,
and that's why I hid in the closet.
Is that so?
I just heard you talking about
the Alliance Leader's Token.
Is this... the Alliance Leader's Token?
May I take a look?
Sure.
So, this is the Alliance Leader's Token?
Yes.
Is this the legendary Sun Blade
that can cut through iron like butter
and slice through anything?
Yes and no.
If Chief Lu wants to see
the Alliance Leader's Token,
do we, Yunmen,
really need to present the authentic one?
The Alliance Leader's Token is
of great significance.
If anything were to happen to it,
we couldn't bear the loss.
So naturally,
the real Alliance Leader's Token is
kept safe at Yunmen.
I see.
You Yunmen disciples really know
how to handle important matters.
So cautious.
Impressive.
You look very disappointed.
No, I'm not.
I'm actually happy.
You just casually told me
such an important secret
about the fake items,
which shows how much you truly trust me.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm going back now.
Do you really think I can't tell?
Are you getting close to me
just for the Sun Blade?
She kissed me...
Mingyang?
Mingyang!
What are you thinking about?
I'm talking to you.
Something bad has happened.
Yue just came to me and said
that Feng Xingyun, that old fox,
is incredibly cunning.
He claimed he'd come
with the Alliance Leader's Token,
but in fact,
he only brought a pair of
fake Sun and Moon Blades.
The real Sun Blade is still in Yunmen.
Not only did Yue make a wasted trip,
but now Yang Qing is suspicious of her.
We need to find a way
to dispel Yang Qing's doubts about her.
If we keep wasting time like this,
when will we ever rescue the Chief,
and when will we restore our sect?
I miss the Chief too.
Haven't you always been afraid of
Yuan Yingxing?
You'd actually miss him?
I didn't realize you were so loyal.
If the Chief were here,
he would've led us
to fight our way in already.
We wouldn't have needed to
make such a fuss.
Mingyang,
are you brainless or what?
That's all in the past.
Our Shengyue Sect used to
dominate one region,
so naturally, we had the strength
to confront them directly.
But now,
there are just a handful of us nobodies.
How can we possibly fight them?
Saying you have no brains
really isn't wrong.
It's been a whole night already.
He'll die if he continues like this.
At this rate, you'll be finished.
Quickly use your internal strength
to force out the Ice Silkworm.
Then you might still have a chance
to survive.
Do you want to die?
Chenxiang,
quickly seal his acupoints.
The Ice Silkworm won't let go
until it's drunk its fill of blood.
We can't take any more risks.
Stay back.
I'm not taking a life
on my conscience for this.
Chenxiang, do it!
Stay back.
The Ice Silkworm is now awakened.
Quickly, take it to her.
Let's go.
I've already placed the Ice Silkworm
on her wound.
But when it feeds on decaying flesh,
the pain is extreme.
Having someone close by
would make it more bearable.
Sir, would you be willing to
stay by her side?
No, I'm not someone close to her.
So they're a pair of lovers
bound by resentment.
Miss.
Bear with it, miss.
Please endure it a little longer.
You go rest first.
I'll take over.
Don't move.
I gave you the chance to live.
Don't you dare die on me.
Yingxing! Yingxing!
Don't move. It'll be over soon.
Stay still. I'm here.
Mr. Yang.
It's so late.
Did you need something from me?
I have something to ask you.
Sit down.
After the battle at Mount Yin,
when the Shengyue Sect was destroyed,
I returned to Yunmen
and went into seclusion for several days.
What happened during those days?
I've been wanting to
report these matters to you,
but you seemed uninterested,
so I didn't say much.
Why are you suddenly interested now?
The Sect Leader was
fully in charge of that matter,
so it wasn't my place to inquire too much.
But now,
I need to confirm some things.
At that time, Sect Leader Feng led us,
along with Biluo, Qingcheng, Cangtong,
and other major sects,
to capture
all the remaining Shengyue Sect members.
Except for the two hall masters
of Water and Fire,
whose whereabouts remain unknown,
all other Shengyue Sect members
who were at Mount Yin that day
are now imprisoned
in the dungeon of Biluo Valley.
I heard about that,
but there's one thing I'm curious about.
Given Yuan Yingxing's martial arts skills,
although he couldn't turn the tide
and save his sect,
he could have easily escaped capture.
Why was he caught too?
That was all thanks to Ms. Yao.
After Ms. Yao assassinated
the witch Wang Yue,
Yuan Yingxing was completely devastated
and even seemed mentally unstable.
When Chief Lu captured him,
he didn't even resist.
Wasn't Yuan Yingxing infatuated with
Junior Yao?
Why was he so devastated
by Wang Yue's death?
As far as I know,
the Shengyue Sect had a tradition
of the chief marrying the saintess.
Which means,
if not for Ms. Yao,
Yuan Yingxing and Wang Yue
would have been a couple.
With that,
their feelings for each other
must have been special.
So, Yuan Yingxing is now
in the dungeon here?
Yes.
Mr. Yang,
I know what you're worried about,
but you can rest assured.
Although the valley has been open
to guests these days,
and all sorts of people are here,
no one will be able to
rescue Yuan Yingxing.
He has no chance of escape.
Why are you so certain?
The dungeon
that holds the Shengyue Sect remnants
was built jointly by us
and other major sects.
There are guards watching outside
and all kinds of traps
set by Cangtong inside.
Even the only door to get there
can only be opened
with our sect's Sun Blade.
How come I never heard
that the Sun Blade was involved?
All of this is confidential.
If I hadn't been present
when they were designing
the restricted area,
I wouldn't have known either.
So, Mr. Yang, don't worry.
As long as we protect the Sun Blade,
they
will never escape in this lifetime.
I see.
No wonder she's so forward.
Mr. Yang, what did you say?
Is someone really trying to
rescue Yuan Yingxing?
Nothing.
I'm just worried
that, even though
the Shengyue Sect was destroyed,
there are still many people
who secretly follow them.
They won't give up
on the Shengyue Sect so easily.
Yuan Yingxing...
Yuan Yingxing. Yuan Yingxing.
♪ Time flows like sand in an hourglass,
counting down to forever ♪
I hope I'm just overthinking here.
♪ Only at the moment we met did I learn
what pain and sorrow truly are ♪
Yuan Yingxing. Yuan Yingxing.
Yue, if you can't sleep,
♪ The cold wind softens little by little ♪
recite the formula
I secretly taught you today.
♪ Though carefree, I can't resist the gaze
written in my fate ♪
Tomorrow, when they come after us,
stay behind me
and don't charge ahead.
I don't want to recite it.
Then...
♪ I remember the old days,
forgetting all past grudges ♪
count my eyelashes
to train your eyesight?
Why do those adults keep chasing us?
When can we escape from here?
♪ Through the rise and fall
of the world's cruel game ♪
They're testing us.
We will get out.
♪ I cherish your gentle touch ♪
In the future, I'll be the chief,
and you'll be the saintess.
We'll never be apart.
♪ The long, winding road
lingers in my heart ♪
♪ Like dark clouds surging ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
Yuan Yingxing!
♪ I vow my life, giving all I have ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
♪ Betting on a timeless promise ♪
♪ Holding you despite tremendous danger ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
♪ Unraveling the conspiracy of time ♪
♪ Holding your hand ♪
♪ I walk with you
through countless mountains and rivers ♪
♪ I vow my life, never turning back ♪
♪ Betting on forever ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
♪ I dare to let go of right and wrong
and stay by your side ♪
Don't be deceived by that woman, Yao Fu.
Yuan Yingxing.
♪ Unafraid of hardships
or raging torrents ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
Yue.
♪ I see longing with new clarity ♪
Yuan Yingxing.
♪ Love can heal all pain ♪
Yue.
I'm here.
Yuan Yingxing.
I'm here, Yue.
It's alright.
Yuan Yingxing.
It's alright. I'm here.
Yue.
Yuan Yingxing.
Yingxing.
Nothing good ever happens
whenever I see you.
Don't let me see you again.
What?
I called out Yuan Yingxing's name
in my dream yesterday,
and Yang Qing overheard me?
I don't want any.
You have no idea.
When he heard it outside,
his expression turned absolutely awful.
I'm doomed.
Yang Qing definitely misunderstood me.
He doesn't think I like Yuan Yingxing,
does he?
A man's pride...
Hearing something like that...
he's definitely really upset.
What should I do?
I need to explain this to him.
Yang Qing.
Here you are.
Did I say something last night
that made you sad or disappointed?
No.
I... I didn't say anything?
Nothing happened.
I'm not hurt, disappointed, or sad.
You don't need to explain.
How long are you going to
keep pacing back and forth?
You're making me dizzy.
You know,
if he would just get angry with me
or have an argument with me,
I'd feel better.
But he's not saying anything.
It just makes me so anxious!
Do you feel like
you've betrayed him somehow?
Well, calling out another man's name
in your sleep
is pretty much like betrayal.
The more he acts like he doesn't care,
the more heartless I seem.
Forget it. I don't want to
dwell on it anymore.
There's really nothing to dwell on.
If you ask me,
you should figure out
how to swallow your pride and fix this.
So, you think
that if I try to please him
and make him happy,
this whole thing will just blow over?
Yang Qing is such a good person.
Once this passes,
he won't hold it against me anymore.
Do you really think
he can be that forgiving?
Actually, all the slip-ups
I've made before
and the things I owe him explanations for—
even I feel guilty thinking about them.
But he never showed
any intention of settling scores later.
Since he could do that before,
he can certainly do it now.
Yang Qing,
you've been reading for so long.
You must be tired.
Let me give you a massage.
No need.
Then...
let me get you some water.
No need to be polite with me.
I'm not being polite.
That's great.
Why don't I accompany you
to your room for a rest?
You've been reading for so long.
You must be tired.
I'm not tired.
Then...
I'll go out for a walk with you?
I don't want to go.
Alright, then.
I'll just keep you company here.
Eat up.
Stop doing this.
Normally, I'd find it amusing
when you do things like this,
but right now,
I'm not moved at all.
I'm not just putting on a show.
I'm very serious about you.
But from my perspective,
I don't see any sincerity.
Then, what counts as sincerity?
I'm clearly doing my best
to be good to you.
Have you ever considered
that perhaps I don't need
this kind of flattery?
When you act this way,
it only makes me more uncomfortable.
What's wrong with being passionate?
I have a heart full of passion,
and I haven't given it to anyone else.
I've given it all to you.
Why would you think
that I'm not serious enough?
I can't tell which of your words are true
and which are false.
Maybe I should really think about
what I actually mean
to you.
Why is love so hard?
Yingxing.
Yingxing?
I know what you're planning to do.
I'll go with you.
Yingxing.
You want to rescue the disciples
of the Shengyue Sect, don't you?
On your own,
you won't even make it through
the gates of Biluo Valley.
I can help you.
Biluo Valley is
hosting a birthday banquet soon,
and our sect has been invited.
I can disguise you as a fellow disciple
and bring you in.
Yao.
First, you saved me,
and now you offer to
take me to Biluo Valley.
Are you sincere this time?
Sir?
What a coincidence. We meet again.
Oh, it's you.
Why are you here?
I'm just here to
freeload at Biluo Valley's banquet.
I see that your brow is tightly furrowed.
Have you encountered some trouble?
Tell me about it,
and I'll give you a fortune reading.
Even if I get it wrong,
at least I can listen to your troubles
and help ease your mind.
It's nothing serious.
I just suddenly realized
that a certain young lady
cares deeply about someone.
That certain young lady
is the one
who was with you last time, right?
And the person she cares about
is a man, right?
Mr. Yang, could it be that you're jealous?
I...
I'm just worried
that she'll cause trouble again.
Why don't you just go straight to her
and talk it out?
Even if you end up in an argument,
it's fine.
I don't want to force her
to admit anything,
and I don't want her to lie to me either.
But my heart feels heavy.
Thinking that she might be secretly
plotting something for someone else
makes me feel upset.
You're clearly suffering inside,
yet you don't even dare to ask her?
Yes, indeed.
Harboring secret doubts
will only push her further away.
I advise you, sir,
to talk it out with her
sooner rather than later.
I don't want to push her away.
Just give me some more time.
I'll definitely find a solution.
Since you already have your answer,
I won't intrude any further.
Same as last time,
10 coins.
See you.
Fire Hall Master, you've trespassed into
Biluo Valley.
Are you trying to
get Wangyue into trouble?
Do you know how many disciples
from righteous sects are here right now,
grinding their teeth in hatred
against your sect?
I need to protect them.
You're putting them in danger.
Or are you secretly
plotting something shady again?
If you have something to say,
go say it to the people
who need to hear it.
Mingyang?
Saint...
Miss Yang.
Why have you also come to Biluo Valley?
Miss Yang, you're speaking so loudly.
Are you trying to attract everyone
in the valley over here?
I'm not interested in your business.
I just want to know exactly
what you're really plotting.
What could we possibly be plotting?
Then why did you sneak into Biluo Valley?
Still refusing to talk?
About... about what?
I don't even know what you want me to say.
What kind of place is this valley?
Who is imprisoned here?
What is your identity?
What's your relationship with him?
Do you need me to spell it all out?
What are you trying to say?
You can't rescue some people
just because you want to.
Rescue... rescue who?
What are you talking about?
You're making me more and more confused.
Mingyang, didn't you come here
because you're pursuing me?
That's right.
I don't care why he came here.
He must leave immediately.
Why should I listen to you?
Because you're the Fire Hall Master
of the Shengyue Sect.
Everyone in this valley
will be targeting this place
because of you.
The longer you stay here,
the more trouble you'll cause.
I think Yang Qing is right.
Mingyang,
you really shouldn't pursue a girl
like this.
You still need to follow
the proper approach when courting a girl.
You just showed up
out of nowhere in this valley.
You'd better leave now.
I'm coming on too strong here.
I'll leave right away.
The main road has heavy guards. Follow me.
You can leave from here
without encountering
the Biluo Valley disciples.
If you don't want to cause trouble
for Wangyue,
don't ever come back after you leave.
Yang Qing.
He's already gone.
Why are you still angry?
You're trying to rescue
the Shengyue Sect members imprisoned here,
aren't you?
How could you,
an orphan girl from Yangliu Town,
know Yuan Yingxing,
the Chief of the Shengyue Sect?
And how do you know
the Shengyue Sect's mental techniques?
Is it really because of your uncle?
I've told you before.
I don't like it when you keep lying to me.
You're awake.
I asked people from the valley,
and they said there's a shop nearby
with really good jujube cakes.
I wanted you to try some,
so I bought you some.
The nearest market is
over 10 miles away from here.
When did you go buy it?
Last night, at midnight.
I walked a long way in the dark.
The whole way I was thinking—
back in Yangliu Town,
when you stayed up
to buy me lotus cake,
were your feelings
the same as mine?
But then I thought,
your feelings should be different
from mine.
You always think more deeply,
while I think less.
For the same thing,
you can ponder deeply enough
to write a fascinating novel,
while I only see the surface.
So I've decided,
whatever you've experienced,
I want to experience it too.
With enough experience,
I'll naturally come to understand
the tangled, mixed feelings in your heart.
Wangyue.
That's just who I am.
I never get hung up
or weigh myself down with worry.
♪ At that moment, I fell for you again ♪
I don't care about the past,
nor do I care about the future.
What I care about is the present.
♪ Love can't be confessed,
afraid heaven might bear witness ♪
You heard me call out Yuan Yingxing's name
in my dream,
and you must be wondering about
♪ Memories return,
afraid it's a fated misstep ♪
my relationship with him
and who I truly care about now.
♪ Why does fate always keep us apart? ♪
I want to tell you
that right now,
the one I care about is you,
♪ A restless heart, an iceberg melting ♪
and the one I like is you.
♪ Rewrite the stories in this world ♪
Got it.
I know you'd read into it.
♪ Gaze is brighter than the moonlight ♪
You'd wonder
if I came with ulterior motives
and how serious I really am about you.
♪ I can't hide my lovesickness ♪
Please believe me.
I'm really serious about you.
I've never treated you like a plaything,
♪ Let me love you more ♪
acting out just because I can't have you.
That's not who I am.
Maybe sometimes
I don't handle things well,
♪ Make up for the years to make us even ♪
but
people change and grow.
Can't you grow with me?
♪ I hear flowers bloom,
I see clouds drift ♪
Okay.
Besides,
♪ I'm attached to this world ♪
even if we separate in the future,
I'm sincere with you now.
"Even if we separate in the future?"
♪ Now it's my turn to fall for you ♪
Are you saying
that you came with the intention of
eventually leaving me?
Of course not.
I came with the intention of marrying you.
♪ Using the chapters of my remaining life,
I trace your face ♪
But the future is ever-changing.
We never know what might happen.
That's up to fate.
♪ I meet the future, I dream of the past ♪
It makes me unhappy
when you call out another man's name
in your dream.
Very unhappy.
♪ I'm attached to all of this ♪
However,
dreams are different from reality
after all.
Since you're willing to
tell me all of this today,
♪ I find warmth, I dream of forever ♪
I won't dwell on it anymore.
Right? Right?
I've dreamed of you many times,
and in those dreams,
I've called out your name plenty of times.
♪ Your eyes, my whole world ♪
You just weren't lucky enough
to heart it.
Yes, it was my bad luck.
You walked all night.
You should go back and rest now.
Then I'll go back.
Wangyue.
Today is May 15th.
Your birthday.
Oh, right, today is my birthday.
I almost forgot.
You still remember?
Of course, I remember.
Go back and rest first.
I'll come see you tonight.
Okay.