[A Forbidden Marriage]
[Episode 21]
I couldn't stand by and watch heroes
across the land be deceived by Yunmen,
so, risking the world's condemnation,
I want to invite
Yunmen disciple Yang Wangyue
to the main hall.
I have a major announcement to make.
Junior Yang,
come with me.
The Sect Leader wants to see you.
Me?
I knew that one day
you'd land yourself in big trouble.
Let's go now.
Sect Leader, Junior Yang is here.
Sect Leader Feng, you wanted to see me?
It's Miss Lu who wants to see you.
Wangyue,
will you say it yourself,
or shall I say it for you?
Say what?
Lu Xuanxuan,
this is Yunmen Sect,
not your Biluo Valley.
Still pretending?
The Saintess of Shengyue Sect,
Wang Yue.
She's from Shengyue Sect?
What are you talking about?
What?
Just because my name is Wangyue,
I must be the Saintess?
Since you won't admit it,
I'll ask you a few questions.
First,
when we first met in Yangliu Town,
in front of everyone,
why did you speak up for Shengyue Sect?
I...
Second,
the widely discussed case
of the missing children
has now been confirmed to have been committed
by Jin Buhuan of Shengyue Sect.
The investigation was going smoothly,
but after you appeared,
there were poisonings and explosions.
Were you colluding with Jin Buhuan?
Don't slander me.
I was helping Yunmen investigate.
Everyone in Yunmen can vouch for me.
Third,
everyone keeps their distance
from Shengyue Sect,
while you are on close terms
with their Fire Hall Master Mingyang
and Water Hall Master Lingyin.
You even claimed Lingyin is your cousin.
How do you explain that?
Everyone!
This person is the Saintess
of Shengyue Sect,
Wang Yue.
She really is
the Saintess of Shengyue Sect.
She's a member of an evil sect!
The Saintess of Shengyue Sect
is now a disciple in Yunmen.
Sect Leader Feng,
don't you need to explain this?
That's right, Sect Leader Feng.
You should explain this.
Has Yunmen had dealings
with Shengyue Sect all along?
Then the peace talk you just mentioned,
is it truly out of fairness,
or does it hide selfish motives?
Exactly.
Does Yunmen have hidden agendas?
About this…
Miss Lu,
every disciple who joins Yunmen
undergoes strict scrutiny.
We would never allow someone
with an unclear background to join.
You're just making accusations.
Do you have any evidence?
I would not make false accusations.
I once found
rove beetles under Mount Yin,
where Shengyue Sect is stationed.
As everyone knows,
rove beetles are vicious.
They bite everyone,
except people
who live on Mount Yin for years.
Whether she is the Saintess
can be tested by rove beetles.
Rove beetles?
Servant.
Miss Yang, please.
Look,
this is the evidence.
She really is the witch.
She is Wang Yue,
the Saintess of Shengyue Sect.
Sect Leader Feng,
do you still have any doubts?
Guards!
Capture the witch
and lock her in the Seclusion Valley.
Now!
Yunmen
definitely has ties with Shengyue Sect.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Do you have anything else to say?
I have nothing to say.
You knew all along
that she was
the Saintess of Shengyue Sect?
She once confessed her admiration
for you under our mountain.
I thought you were unmoved.
It's all my fault.
I will take responsibility
for all the consequences.
Sect Leader, please don't blame Wangyue.
You've been pushing for reconciliation
between Shengyue Sect
and the four major sects
all for her?
Making peace with Shengyue Sect
benefits the Central Plains martial world
in every way.
Even without Wangyue,
I would still find ways to make it happen.
Besides,
I truly can't let her go.
How foolish you are, Qing.
She's a witch from Shengyue Sect.
You're bewitched.
Your mind is clouded by a witch.
No matter what,
in three days,
you must marry your Junior Yao.
Wangyue is the only woman I will marry.
I will not take Junior Yao.
In three days,
you must marry Yao.
Or I'll kill that witch.
Choose one.
Sect Leader!
Make your choice!
Please punish me.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Where is Feng Xingyun?
Tell him to come out!
About today's incident,
he must give the martial world
an explanation!
Is it enough to just capture her?
What about Yuan Yingxing
and the evil sect?
If Yunmen wants to clarify this matter,
it's actually very simple—
just kill Wang Yue.
That's right!
[Yunxiao Hall]
Kill the witch! Kill the witch!
Wang Yue can die,
but she must not be killed
during the Yunmen Grand Ceremony.
Miss Yao,
are you speaking for Shengyue Sect?
I'm speaking for all of you.
Yuan Yingxing is already intending
to step back,
retreat to Mount Yin,
and coexist peacefully with us.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Why do we have to stir up conflict
and come to blows with him?
My past is well known.
I once killed Wang Yue,
which led Yuan Yingxing to send
a large force after me.
You can try if you dare,
and see how merciless Yuan Yingxing
can be when enraged.
Here's a broadsword.
Go ahead.
Who says we're afraid of him?
Who does he think he is?
We are being generous
by calling him the Chief of Shengyue Sect.
Fine.
Since none of you are going,
I will go.
Miss Lu, wait.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Since this happened in Yunmen,
we promise
that we'll investigate it thoroughly.
Please rest assured.
How will you investigate?
Sect Leader Feng,
if you don't provide a solution,
I can't rest easy.
I will soon negotiate with Yuan Yingxing.
Negotiate?
What is there to negotiate with a madman?
Sect Leader Feng,
are you trying to protect that witch?
It's well known that
Mr. Yang of Yunmen
has feelings for that witch.
This negotiation
might be his roundabout plan
to save her.
Nonsense!
Qing has nothing to do with that witch.
In three days,
he will marry Yao Fu.
At that time,
Yunmen will present
the Alliance Leader's Token
to witness their wedding.
I sincerely invite you all
to attend and bear witness.
As for Shengyue Sect,
please trust Yunmen
and me.
I would never gamble
with the safety of the martial world.
Congratulations on the union
of Yunmen's two finest disciples.
What a perfect match.
We were being too suspicious earlier.
Well, thinking about it,
it seems Mr. Yang has no connection
with the witch.
I must attend
Mr. Yang's wedding.
Even though Mr. Yang and Yao Fu
are getting married,
the witch still must be dealt with.
If we don't make a decision today,
we'll need to settle this matter
eventually
to eliminate future troubles!
I've said all I need to say.
Let's go!
[Yunxiao Hall]
They think a wedding will let them
get away with hiding the Saintess
of Shengyue Sect?
Dream on!
If I don't bring Feng Xingyun down
from his position
as the alliance leader this time,
I'll renounce my name!
Xuanxuan!
You're still hung up
on those trivial love matters.
You were blinded by love
that you failed
to complete the task I gave you!
You...
How could I, Lu Jin,
have such a useless daughter?
[Seclusion Valley]
Mr. Yang,
the Sect Leader ordered
that you are forbidden
to enter the Seclusion Valley.
You should know
you can't stop me.
My martial skills
are certainly no match for yours,
but I must follow the Sect Leader's order.
I don't want to hurt you.
Mr. Yang.
Senior.
Just say it here.
You're so desperate to see her?
Outside the Seclusion Valley
are just a few guardian disciples.
What good would
making it difficult for them do?
Wangyue has been captured.
I can't just stand by and do nothing.
But the Sect Leader imprisoned Wangyue
specifically to prevent you
from seeing her.
I promised the Sect Leader
I would marry you.
Didn't we agree to oppose this together?
You have no feelings for me.
Why did you agree to this marriage?
With Yunmen facing a crisis,
I naturally have a duty
to assist the Sect Leader.
Junior Yao, you're not the type
to sacrifice everything for Yunmen.
Whether you believe it or not,
I've already promised the Sect Leader.
Actually,
you could look at this differently.
On the wedding day,
with Yunmen bustling
and disciples scattered,
that will be the best time
to rescue Wangyue.
Going now
will only alert them
and achieve nothing.
You hold a grudge against Wangyue
and have feelings for Yuan Yingxing.
Why are you giving me advice?
I just
want everything to return
to the right track,
including my own life.
Sometimes I really don't understand you.
Your thinking is different from ours,
as if
you're scheming something no one knows.
But I still
won't agree to this marriage.
[How I Got My Husband]
[Upon our first meeting,
my heart felt the old warm greeting.]
♪ At that moment, I fell for you again ♪
♪ Love can't be confessed,
afraid heaven might bear witness ♪
[Like a message carved deep into the bone,
my love grows.]
[This ache of longing within me,
only my heart knows.]
[I pray your heart proves true like mine,
so that we'll never let each other down.]
♪ Memories return,
afraid it's a fated misstep ♪
♪ Your eyes, my whole world ♪
[Deyue Hotel]
Come, drink.
Come.
Aren't they from Biluo Valley?
Has the Martial Arts Conference
already ended?
Haven't you heard?
The Saintess of Shengyue Sect
has come back to life.
Come back to life?
She was captured alive by Yunmen.
Don't move!
What did you just say?
Say it again.
The Saintess of Shengyue Sect
was captured alive by Yunmen?
What happened?
Wait...
Sir, Sir!
I really don't know.
I just heard...
I just heard it!
I'm just a bystander.
I only know
the Saintess of Shengyue Sect...
was captured by them.
[Yunxiao Hall]
What are you doing?
Are you trying to make Yunmen
a laughingstock for the world?
Please, Sect Leader, withdraw your order.
I once promised Wangyue
that I would marry no one but her.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Miss Yao is smart and sensible.
She's a perfect match for you.
Qing, tell me,
what are you so stubborn about?
There are countless
smart and sensible women in the world.
I can't
like them all.
But you and Yao grew up together.
If childhood companions
were to be married off,
most of Yunmen's disciples
grew up with me.
Am I supposed to marry every one?
You...
Are you really going to ruin Yunmen's
century-old reputation
for the sake of a witch?
Wangyue is not a witch,
and Shengyue Sect
is not beyond redemption.
Aren't you afraid I'll kill that witch?
You may not say it aloud,
but I know
you've always been willing to reconcile
and achieve a merit
that will benefit future generations.
I trust you won't kill the innocent.
Fine.
It's fine not to kill her,
but this wedding will happen,
whether you like it or not.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Sect Leader!
You know the Sect Leader
has a strong temper.
Why provoke him?
I also want to know,
since you clearly like Yuan Yingxing,
why are you willing to marry me?
Are you
marrying me for some other reason?
You're overthinking.
[Yunmen]
I've already asked around.
Yue is locked in the Seclusion Valley.
We'll change into Yunmen clothes
and go straight to their forbidden ground.
-Let's go!
[Yunxiao Hall]
Mr. Yang,
the alarm's ringing—someone's intruding.
Take some people to inform Shang Huai.
Guard Langhuan Pavilion together.
I'll handle this.
Don't alert the Sect Leader.
Yes.
[Seclusion Valley]
Seniors.
Senior,
we're here to deliver food.
Hasn't food been delivered once today
already?
You two have eaten,
but the witch locked inside
hasn't.
How do you know about that?
What are you talking about?
We...
We ate with the witch.
Right.
The Sect Leader said
Yang Wangyue is, after all,
the Saintess of Shengyue Sect.
If she starves to death in our Yunmen,
it would be hard for us to explain.
I just didn't want you to make a mistake
and offend the Sect Leader,
so... Right?
Well...
you may...
Juniors.
[Seclusion Valley]
Don't let them in.
Well, who do we have here?
So it's Senior Jiang.
Miss Lingyin, stop pretending.
You're here to rescue Yang Wangyue,
aren't you?
You're the Demonic Healer, Lingyin?
[Seclusion Valley]
Mingyang!
Don't kill him! We're friends.
Be careful.
He may be your friend,
but not mine.
If you dare lay a finger on him,
don't blame me for turning against you!
You...
Jiang Yan.
[Seclusion Valley]
Mr. Yang.
Let them in.
Mr. Yang,
are you really letting them in?
Step aside.
[Seclusion Valley]
Mr. Yang!
Mr. Yang.
Get in.
Let's go.
[Seclusion Valley]
Mr. Yang,
isn't Sect Leader Feng's token
the only thing that can open it?
I stole the Sect Leader's token.
Mr. Yang.
Are you really going to let Miss Yang go
just like that?
This time, whether she leaves or stays,
it's her choice.
I won't blame her
either way.
She's over there.
Yue! Yue!
Saintess.
Why are you here?
Don't worry.
I've got good food, drink, and fun here.
You should go back now.
Listen to yourself.
You're literally locked up here.
Are you still not going to leave with us?
I'm not leaving.
You...
If Mingyang and I hadn't brought you food,
I think Yunmen would have starved you
on purpose.
Yang Qing just brought me tasty food.
Look, dried fruits and meat jerky.
Would you like some?
You...
Yue,
aren't you afraid Yunmen will kill you?
With Yang Qing here,
who would dare?
Saintess,
I truly don't understand.
You used to hate being controlled.
Why don't you want to leave with us now?
We could get in
only because Yang Qing allowed it.
That shows
he wants you to go with us.
If I go with you,
Yang Qing will bear the blame.
I'm already known as a witch,
but I can't let him be accused
because of me.
Is Yang Qing's stupid reputation
really more important than your life?
There are only a few days left
until our agreed date.
I believe he can convince Sect Leader Feng
and reconcile the two sects.
Then
I can walk out with my head held high.
What if he fails?
In the past, I always hurt him
and didn't trust him.
This time I won't hurt him again.
If he fails…
I've already given you the method
to steal the Sun Blade.
Once you get it,
go rescue them immediately.
I've always said,
once someone falls in love,
they lose their mind.
Forget it, Mingyang. Let's go.
Let's go.
[Seclusion Valley]
Wangyue didn't come out with you?
Your Wangyue
plans to stay in there forever.
She even said she believes
you will persuade the whole world
and promote reconciliation
between the two sects.
I really don't know what she's thinking.
Jiang Yan,
are you alright?
Were you hurt just now?
[Seclusion Valley]
Fire Hall Master,
why are you holding my hand like this?
What exactly is our relationship?
You are my girl.
Dream on.
You never even asked if I agreed.
Besides,
you always shout at me
and aren't gentle at all.
I don't like that.
Then I promise
I'll be gentle with you from now on, okay?
I've told you my true feelings.
So, tell me,
what would it take for you to be my girl?
That depends on how you perform.
[Yunxiao Hall]
Senior.
Junior Yao?
Senior, you must know
why the Sect Leader called us here, right?
I won't agree to this marriage.
Really?
Senior,
you should just go along
with the Sect Leader's wishes.
It's better for both of us.
Don't you agree?
What's that sound?
No!
Alright.
I'll do
whatever you say.
Let's go tell
the Sect Leader about this now.
Alright.
Report!
Chief,
I have something important to report.
I'm listening.
The Saintess's identity has been exposed.
Yunmen has sent a message:
If you want to take the Saintess,
you must go there in person
to discuss an alliance
between the two sects.
What?
They've captured Yue?
Yes.
What is Yang Qing doing?
He couldn't even protect Yue.
Yunmen has sent out invitations.
On the 15th of August,
Elder Yang Qing of Yunmen
will marry Yao Fu.
[Invitation]
[Wedding Invitation]
Yunmen?
Yao Fu?
Yang Qing and Yao Fu's wedding?
[Yang Qing and Yao Fu's Wedding]
Outrageous!
Saintess sacrificed everything
for Yang Qing,
and now he's marrying Yao Fu.
This is too much.
I'll kill him right now!
Wait.
Why are you always so impulsive?
If Yang Qing were truly heartless,
he could never have fooled Yue
into being so devoted to him.
Something doesn't feel right about this.
Yunmen has sent out invitations
far and wide.
Everyone in the city
can attend the wedding.
And you're telling me
something's not right?
What is Yunmen trying to do?
They don't want to give Yang Qing
a chance to back out?
A chance to back out?
Yang Qing betrayed Saintess!
Even if he did betray Yue,
that's her business.
What right do you have
to kill him for her?
Since that's the case,
I'll go to Yunmen again
and see if Yue
will leave with us this time.
[Yunmen]
You think Qing is deceiving us
and actually has another plan?
Yesterday at the training ground,
Junior Yang was clearly acting strange.
It was very weird.
He actually agreed
to try on wedding clothes with Yao.
That's...
That's not like him at all.
Elder Shen, what do you mean?
Are you saying Fu
isn't good enough for Qing?
No, no.
I just find it strange.
Sect Leader, think about it.
Just days ago,
Junior Yang was kneeling outside
Yunxiao Hall, refusing to get up,
completely determined to marry Wangyue.
But now he's completely silent.
I just feel something's not right.
That means Qing has come to his senses.
Sect Leader, could it be that
Junior Yang is trying to make us
let our guard down, so he can
secretly go rescue the witch?
Has Qing shown any unusual behavior?
Yesterday, Junior Yang behaved properly.
In the morning, he accompanied Junior Yao
to guide the disciples in their training.
In the evening,
he read in Langhuan Pavilion.
He didn't go see the witch
or insist on calling off the marriage.
See?
Qing isn't the type to act recklessly.
But Sect Leader,
it's precisely because he's not
making trouble that I'm worried.
We've watched him grow up
and know him too well.
Beneath his calm exterior
lies a volcano.
The calmer he seems,
the more concerned I get.
So, what do you think...
we should do?
Sect Leader,
either you or I
should talk to him.
He keeps everything bottled up.
I have a feeling he's going to do
something earth-shattering.
The wedding day is approaching.
We need to be extra vigilant.
Senior,
you look so handsome
in your wedding clothes.
Junior, why haven't you changed yet?
The Sect Leader asked us
to try the wedding clothes
to see if they fit.
There's no rush.
Senior,
I have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
In the future, we'll be husband and wife.
You don't need to be so polite.
Then I'll be direct.
I heard the Sect Leader passed
the Alliance Leader's Token to you.
May I see it?
I'm really curious what it looks like.
Such a sacred object
as the Alliance Leader's Token
cannot be casually revealed.
You'd better not look at it.
Senior,
the Sect Leader's purpose in matching us
is to make us support each other
and thus strengthen Yunmen.
We're about to get married.
Don't you even have this much trust in me?
How can we work together
to lead Yunmen in the future?
I've been overly cautious.
Since you want to see it, then see it.
After our wedding,
I'll find time to take you to see it.
Can't we go now?
Why are you in such a hurry?
You haven't changed into
your wedding clothes yet.
The Sect Leader specifically instructed us
to put them on before going to him.
He wants to see us in our wedding clothes.
Conveniently,
Langhuan Pavilion is in the same direction
as the Sect Leader's residence.
Senior,
let's go see
the Alliance Leader's Token first
then go see the Sect Leader together.
It's settled then.
Hurry and get changed.
Okay, I'll go now and be out shortly.
[Seclusion Valley]
What?
Yang Qing is marrying Yao Fu?
You're talking nonsense!
The Sect Leader
will personally officiate the wedding.
Yunmen has been fully decorated.
How could this be false?
How could this happen?
He told me to trust him.
[Seclusion Valley]
Yue!
-Saintess!
-Yue!
Why are you two here?
Yue,
come with me now!
Yang Qing is going to marry
that wicked woman.
Are you still not willing to leave?
So it's true?
Of course it's true.
It's been announced to the world,
and you still don't believe it?
Where is Yang Qing?
I just saw
him going to Langhuan Pavilion
with Ms. Yao.
See?
[Langhuan Pavilion]
Senior,
is this the Sun Blade?
The Alliance Leader's Token
you want to see
is in this box.
Senior,
can you open it so I can see?
Isn't that inappropriate?
Didn't you just agree to let me see it?
Or...
do you still not trust me?
Since you want to see it,
then see it.
Yang Qing, how dare you hurt him?
Hurting Junior Yao is like hurting me!
What about me?
If I hurt Yao Fu,
will you kill me too?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Fine, tell me,
dressed like this,
are you going to marry this woman?
Yes.
Tomorrow I'm marrying Junior Yao.
Yang Qing,
do you even know what you're saying?
Was everything you told me before
just a lie?
Stop talking!
-Senior, take back the Sun Blade.
-Shut up!
Yang Qing.
Yang Qing, I'm Wangyue.
Have you forgotten me?
Yang Qing, wake up!
Senior!
Yang Qing!
Say another word and I'll kill you!
-Yang Qing!
-Wangyue?
Yang Qing!
Wangyue.
-What's wrong with you, Yang Qing?
-Hurry up and do it!
Wangyue, go!
I'm not leaving.
-Yang Qing.
-What's wrong?
What's really going on?
Wangyue!
Go now!
I'm not leaving! We're going together!
Get the Sun Blade back quickly!
You two, take Wangyue and go now!
What's wrong with you? Tell me!
Sen... Senior...
Go!
Saintess, let's go!
Let's go!
-Let's go!
[Yunxiao Hall]
[Kindness and Virtue]
Sect Leader!
The Sun Blade is missing?
You two
have truly disappointed me.
How many times have I told you
that the Sun Blade is Yunmen's last token?
I entrusted it to you for safekeeping.
And what did you do?
Did you forget the oath you swore to me?
Junior Yao
insisted on seeing the Sun Blade.
But ultimately,
it was my negligence.
Sect Leader, please rest assured.
I will take the Sun Blade back.
Sect Leader,
that witch's martial art skills are weak.
Even with the two hall masters
of Shengyue Sect
assisting,
she's no match for Senior.
He must still have feelings for her.
Sect Leader,
I'll personally go down the mountain
to get the Sun Blade back.
Neither of you gives me peace of mind.
If you hadn't insisted
on seeing the Sun Blade,
Qing wouldn't have opened the iron box.
Junior Wang, Elder Shen,
quickly send people to retrieve
the witch and the Sun Blade.
Yes.
-Sect Leader.
The wedding is canceled.
You, come with me to apologize.
Sect Leader, but...
Now is not the time to assign blame.
The Sun Blade is lost.
Yunmen cannot hold the wedding.
We cannot let anyone else know
our Sun Blade is missing.
Stay in your room
and don't see anyone.
[Yunxiao Hall]
This could be considered
turning a bad situation into a good one.
That's right.
They're coming!
Why isn't Elder Yang
in his wedding clothes?
Why is he dressed like that?
He came dressed like this.
It's his wedding day.
This isn't appropriate.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
Fu is sick,
so today's wedding is canceled.
What?
-It's canceled?
-Why is it canceled?
-Why is it cancelled?
-The wedding is cancelled?
We've traveled so far to get here,
and you just cancel it like that?
Feng Xingyun!
I think you're
deliberately hiding something big!
Yunmen has lost
the Alliance Leader's Token.
-What?
They lost the Alliance Leader's Token?
Nonsense!
I just received news
that the witch
actually went to Biluo Valley with people
and rescued the imprisoned
Shengyue Sect disciples.
That witch!
The witch has escaped?
As everyone knows,
the dungeon in Biluo Valley
can only be opened with the Sun Blade.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
Not only did the witch escape,
she also stole the Sun Blade!
Sect Leader Feng,
did you really lose
the Alliance Leader's Token?
While all the heroes
of the world are here,
give us an explanation!
Yes, give us an explanation!
This was all done
by the witch of Shengyue Sect.
But rest assured, everyone.
I've ordered Tianyou to pursue her.
We will definitely retrieve
the Alliance Leader's Token.
Yunmen was harboring Wang Yue.
In less than three days,
the Sun Blade has already been lost.
You're about to negotiate
with Yuan Yingxing soon.
What a load of crap!
From today on,
Biluo Valley will no longer trust Yunmen!
The witch and the Alliance Leader's Token—
Biluo Valley are determined to get them!
It's all my fault.
I will retrieve
the Alliance Leader's Token,
no matter what it takes.
I'm starting to get a headache.
Could it be that the Fusheng Spell
is beginning to backfire?