Is my baby…
all right?
It's dead.
You killed…
my baby.
You…
Did you kill my baby?
What?
Why did you lie to me all this time? Why?
You of all people
don't get to say anything about lying.
Aren't you the biggest liar?
Let's end this.
A quiet divorce would be best
for the sake of you, me, and the company.
What do you want?
I already told you the other day.
I'm taking Ha-joon with me.
I'm divorcing you so that he won't turn
into a monster like you.
Even if you neglect him,
he'll pick up on your behavior.
Just the thought of that drives me insane.
Don't use him as leverage.
Do you know why I told Ms. Lee
to request a transfer of custody?
You may be Ha-joon's biological father,
but I wanted the court to recognize
I'm the one who's actually raising him.
To make my next step easier.
The court values precedents very much.
Why are you making
such a foolish decision?
Seeing people like you gain such power
makes me feel hopeless.
But you see…
It strangely gives me a thrill.
Having a powerful opponent
makes me fight harder.
I'm looking forward to this fight
and you should too.
It doesn't look like you'll consent.
So I'll file for divorce.
Why…
Why is this happening to me? Why?
Why?
Why…
What happened?
What?
Are you telling me you had a miscarriage?
Yes.
Then why did you pretend
that you were fine?
Because I had a plan of my own.
And I'm divorcing Ji-yong.
Did he agree to it?
Of course not.
So we'll end up going to court.
I've been your daughter-in-law
for six years.
I'm informing you out of loyalty and duty.
I figured you were sick of hearing
this kind of news through the newspapers.
I don't understand why you're doing this.
I know that you didn't give birth to him,
but you should've raised him right.
You! How dare you talk to me like that?
How impudent!
I raised Ji-yong into a fine man!
How could I do a better job than this?
It was Ji-yong who stabbed me in the back!
Exactly.
He betrayed you.
That means you didn't raise him well.
I don't want Ha-joon to turn out like him,
so I'll raise him by myself.
If he stays here,
he'll be just like his father.
And I learned what not to do from you.
So…
you're telling me
you're going to raise Ha-joon?
You seem shocked to hear it
when it's the obvious thing to do.
Having you as my mother-in-law…
has been very difficult.
You…
Chef Jung!
-Hello.
-Hi.
I heard you'll be in the new drama.
-Hello.
-I loved the script.
-I see.
I'm happy to hear that.
Congratulations
on your husband's appointment.
That has nothing to do with me.
Because I'm divorcing him.
That's why I'm coming back.
It's a boring turn of events,
but it happened that way.
What? Then why is
Hyowon Group against this?
What do you mean?
Hyowon Group has been pressuring
every TV station to prevent you
from coming back to the industry.
There's nothing I can do.
CHAIRMAN HAN JI-YONG
Your brother picked men…
and made them fight each other here.
And he watched.
CHAIRMAN HAN JI-YONG
We had to fight like dogs,
so it was called a dogfight.
He told us to become dogs.
If we broke something,
we would get paid more.
So we had to destroy
a part of our opponent.
The more we bled, the more we got paid.
And I ended up fighting my brother.
Kill him!
At that moment, I lost it.
I beat up my bleeding brother
until he passed out.
So…
all the men on his secret phone
fought in this ring?
If my brother dies,
I'll kill your brother right here.
EPISODE 12
CRIME AND SIN
Being able to do whatever you want in life
is a privilege.
I'm embarrassed to call you my son!
Try to be half as capable as Ji-yong!
This is why you will never succeed.
That's the reputation you've built.
No one finds you trustworthy.
Do you have something to tell me?
You're not Father's real son, are you?
I knew something was off.
A different mother wouldn't make
such a difference.
How did you find out?
I put up with you
because you were my half-brother.
If I knew that we didn't share
a single drop of blood,
I would've kicked you out long ago. No.
I would have killed you.
Because I always wanted to.
You shameless bastard!
How dare you take over the company?
Do you think you deserve
to be the chairman?
A bastard without any pedigree like you
covets the crown of Hyowon Group?
You piece of trash!
Look.
Should I tell the world about your hobby?
Then the company my stupid father built
will fall apart.
But I'll do it anyway.
I'll destroy it
if it means catching a bastard like you.
That's all I amount to anyway, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's why you lost the company
to a bastard who's not even related.
What?
Do you think
you can take my seat with that?
I don't care about that.
Soo-hyuk deserves the position.
You'd better give it up.
But Soo-hyuk doesn't want it!
You can't even control your own son.
Don't make me the bad guy.
Do you think
you can blackmail me with that?
Why? Will you go to the press with it?
Go ahead. Do whatever you want.
Before you know it,
reporters will be publishing stories about
how your ex ran away from an alcoholic.
Come to your senses
and think carefully about what you can do.
-You son of a bitch.
-Han Jin-ho.
Listen to me carefully.
You're just a loser.
You'll be a lunatic making up stories
because of an inferiority complex.
So you escaped
from an alcohol treatment center?
Who would believe a man like you?
Maybe you shouldn't have lived like that.
You bastard.
I won't let you get away with this. Never.
Do you remember what I said before?
What do you have to do
to get what you want?
I said you'd have to kill me.
There's nothing you can do.
So just keep your mouth shut.
My inauguration is in nine days.
But I didn't invite you since I feel bad.
Get out.
Take care.
My brother escaped
from an alcohol treatment center.
So he's a bit unstable.
He's fragile right now,
so be gentle with him.
Take care of yourself.
You bastard.
I'll…
kill you.
Let go of me. I'll leave on my own!
Damn it.
-Hello?
-It's me.
Did you know?
That Ji-yong isn't Father's real son?
Yes.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Well, you know now.
Do you think knowing this sooner
would have made any difference?
Of course!
If I knew he wasn't even my half-brother,
I would've tried my best
to make Father approve of me.
Whose side are you on?
You're not on his side, right?
No.
What should I do now?
Seo-hyun.
Help me.
Help me bring down Ji-yong.
You should…
take over the company instead.
It's humiliating for me either way.
But I'd rather have you lead the company.
I don't want to take the position
just to stop him from taking over.
However, I will
take responsibility for my actions.
I let Ji-yong take the position
instead of persuading Soo-hyuk.
I'm responsible for that.
Is something wrong?
Han Ji-yong…
Forget it.
-You're pregnant right now.
-Say what you were about to say.
It's fine.
Have someone tail Jin-ho.
Should I assign one of our own
or contact an agency?
-One of ours would be better.
-Yes, sir.
Oh, right.
I have to visit my father at the hospital.
Get the car ready.
I'm going to disclose this to the public.
I don't have any reason
to protect him anymore.
He's not my real brother.
He's like a complete stranger.
The same goes for you, too.
Do you know where this place is?
This dogfighting ring.
It's me.
Can you come somewhere with me?
I'll pick you up at your place.
Hurry up!
When will you finish?
The chairman is getting discharged today!
Damn it.
Move all this stuff to the other house.
If he likes Mi-ja's son that much,
he can go live with him.
Ji-yong and Hi-soo are
getting a divorce anyway,
so he can use Hi-soo's study.
-A divorce?
-Forget it.
Call all the maids and move it all.
Everything!
Yes, ma'am.
But ma'am,
Mr. Han needs medical treatment.
-If you stress him out--
-What about my stress?
What about the 50 years of stress
I've received while living with him?
Do you know how I feel right now?
I'm about to go insane right now.
Are you telling me
I should put up with him
being cooped up in the bunker
to be with Mi-ja even when she's dead?
Why is everyone taking his side?
What about me?
Who will understand my feelings?
I've led a miserable life.
I wanted to join my brother
when he passed away.
What's the point of living
when all I feel is misery after misery?
The son that I raised all my life
as my own betrayed me.
And Hi-soo stabbed me in the back today.
What's wrong?
All right.
Pack up all of the chairman's belongings!
What?
Why do you think I doted on No-deok?
Because I was so sick of people!
I thought birds would be different.
But that bird is no different!
It's a male, after all.
The day my husband woke up,
No-deok came back home.
That awful bird.
Even if I died tomorrow,
I would have no regrets.
I just want to die!
Chef Jung!
-Chef Jung!
-Yes, ma'am.
Make some Buddha's Temptation for me.
I need to regain my strength.
Add in a seal penis.
I'm going to have a double portion.
Yes, ma'am.
Double portion?
The chairman is home, ma'am.
Take him to your house.
Since…
you love your son, Ji-yong, so much,
you can go stay with him.
Why would I?
You'd better go as I say!
Before I destroy that bunker with a bomb!
How did you--
Leave!
Let's do as she says, Father.
He'll stay with me.
I think that will make me
feel more comfortable, too.
Ms. Joo.
-Yes?
-You should come with us too.
What do you think you're doing?
The house Father lives in
is the main house.
And it's only right
that Ms. Joo works there.
Who said you could take Ms. Joo
as you please?
Ms. Joo, let's go.
Mr. Kim, escort my father
with the buggy car.
Yes, sir.
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Wait.
Be careful.
-Grandpa!
-Hey.
Good to see you.
His back still hurts, Ha-joon.
Have you been well?
-Yes.
-Good.
What about your mother?
Let's go inside.
We'll set up a new room on the first floor
to make it easier for you.
We'll start tomorrow.
No, it's all right. Going up and down
the stairs will be good exercise.
But you should still be careful.
I'm fine. All right.
Let's go upstairs together.
Let's go.
We should hire a caretaker for my father.
Yes, sir. I'll look into it right away.
I'm also looking for a tutor for Ha-joon.
I'll interview them myself.
-Yes, sir.
-Fire Soo-young tomorrow.
Pardon?
But Ms. Seo hired her herself.
She was Ms. Seo's manager from before.
I said to fire her.
What more is there to talk about?
-Nothing, sir.
-Fire her right away.
Yes, sir.
Tell Mr. Yoon to bring the car around.
I have to get back to work.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Han Ji-yong fired
Ms. Oh Soo-young yesterday.
Okay. You can go.
I would like to tell you
about Mr. Han Ji-yong's
unforgivable actions
toward Ms. Seo Hi-soo and me.
All the directors who are on your side
have received Ms. Lee's video.
What should I do?
Don't do anything. Just leave it.
DIRECTOR CHA GYEONG-TAEK
Yes, Mr. Cha.
You must be shocked
after watching the video.
I'm embarrassed to say this.
But she's insane.
No need to pay her any attention.
No-deok.
You know how I feel, right?
Of course, you don't.
You're a male, after all.
My life is…
so bleak.
I was miserable enough when I had to
raise someone else's son. And now this?
What's that?
That's an egg!
It's an egg!
Oh, my. Some bird laid an egg here.
Whose egg is that?
No-deok must've come back
to raise the baby in a rich family.
-But No-deok is a male bird.
-What?
Did his lover lay the egg and leave?
What are you talking about?
As if having to raise someone else's son
wasn't enough,
even birds are dropping their babies
at my house.
My gosh.
Hey, you go inside and get rid of it.
Get rid of it now!
Gosh, this is such a curse!
Does bad energy flow on this land or what?
Even so, every life must be cherished.
Get rid of it now. Do it now!
If we throw it out
when we don't know who the mother is,
it might cause a problem later.
A problem?
Are you telling me the mother bird
will come back and complain?
I mean, what if the bird comes back
like Ms. Kang?
The bird might ask you to give back…
What? What did you say?
How dare you say such a thing?
A reporter will come here tomorrow.
What?
Don't worry.
Your identity won't be disclosed.
Just tell the reporter
what Han Ji-yong did.
-I can't do that.
-Why not?
Because I'll have to go to prison again.
I'll make sure you don't have to go back.
Don't you want to destroy my brother
like he destroyed yours?
Just do as I say.
Let's destroy him together.
Mr. Han Jin-ho met with Kwak Su-chang
at the hospital just now.
Ji-yong.
This is the address I got from Jin-ho.
BUSINESS PLANS FOR PERFORMANCE START-UPS
CEO JUNG SEO-HYUN
Hello.
I'm Jung Un-yeong,
the chairman's secretary.
He hasn't been inaugurated yet.
You already call him chairman?
Why are you here?
The chairman instructed us to move
Hyowon E&M's office to the headquarters.
He made such an important decision
without talking to me first?
It's the chairman's decision.
Tell him I don't plan to move.
That I'll stay here.
To make things easier for you,
should I make a scene?
Han Ji-yong.
Know your place.
Tell him exactly that.
Were you eyeing Jin-ho's position?
You know very well
that you're unqualified.
You are a sexual minority.
In that sense, you and I have committed
sins of the same degree.
So we shouldn't try to
bring each other down, should we?
Mr. Choi.
We have to bring down Han Ji-yong
as soon as possible.
Schedule a luncheon with the presidents
of our main subsidiaries except for
Hyowon Hotel, Electronics, and Bakery.
Don't invite Han Ji-yong.
Is she moving her office now?
Well, Ms. Jung said a few things to you
that I'd rather not say
and refused to move.
What did she say?
She told me to tell you
exactly what she said, but…
It's all right. Just say it.
"Han Ji-yong.
Know your place."
She asked me to relay that message to you.
I'm sorry, sir.
Okay. You can go now.
Everyone's losing it.
They haven't learned their lesson.
I'm so tired.
If Ms. Joo stays at Rubato,
what's going to happen to us?
Then who's the most powerful person here?
I don't know who I should listen to.
Exactly.
They're all on bad terms,
so we're suffering in the middle.
We should listen to Ms. Jung.
No.
We should listen to Mr. Han Ji-yong now.
The director…
I mean, Mr. Han Jin-ho said he would
take care of everything that goes on here.
-Attention, everyone.
-What is it?
I'm back.
Have you been well?
-Gosh, it's so good to see you!
-Gosh.
What are you staring at?
What's with him?
Yes?
Everything is going as planned.
Be careful tonight and stay low.
Don't underestimate Ji-yong.
Okay.
Han Ji-yong.
It's over, you asshole.
TAEWON DAILY
RESTRICTED NUMBER
I WANT TO MAKE A TIP-OFF
Go to the States with Ha-joon.
Get him out of this house
as soon as possible.
I can't have Ha-joon
under the care of such a man…
even for a day.
What do you plan to do?
I will reveal the true face
of Han Ji-yong to the world
and make him face judgment.
Take care of Ha-joon for me.
I'll stay and do what I can here.
Leave.
I'll take care of the rest.
-Stop.
-Hurry.
Go over there. Why are you following me?
Over there.
-Where?
-There.
Here?
Soo-hyuk.
-Yes?
-What do you want to do in five years?
In five years?
I'm not sure. I haven't thought about it.
Your father told me that you won't be able
to make any money on your own.
The same goes for him.
Don't worry.
I'll go out and face the world.
You made me want to do that.
What about you?
What do you want to do in five years?
-You have a dream, don't you?
-Of course.
No one wants to work as a maid forever.
First of all, I'm going to pay off
my dad's debt and move to a new house.
In five years, I'm going to study more
about social welfare.
And…
my dream is to set up a shelter for kids.
That's cool.
Hold on.
What? Hey.
Are you sure
about your feelings for Yu-yeon?
Yes, I'm sure.
I feel at ease when I'm with her.
Then…
introduce her to the family
and make it official that you're dating.
I'll help you.
Really?
Yes.
It's a miracle for two people
to meet and fall in love.
Falling in love should be pure.
On your last day,
that's the memory you'll hold onto.
Although…
I failed to do so…
you should live the life you want.
Soo-hyuk.
Han Ji-yong hasn't…
officially been appointed chairman yet.
Help me oust him.
Leave with Ms. Kang first.
I'll join you in ten days.
What about Dad?
When will he come?
You know he's busy.
I think I'm going to miss him.
I heard Dad became the most powerful
man at Grandpa's company.
Isn't he really cool?
I look up to him the most in the world.
You look up to him?
Why?
-Because he's your dad?
-No.
He reads five newspapers every day
and works hard at everything.
And everyone likes him.
That's why Soo-hyuk listens to him
more than he listens to Uncle.
Dad is so cool.
I'm so proud to have him as my dad.
I want to be just like him when I grow up.
Mr. Park, drive me to the airport.
Yes, ma'am.
Seo-hyun.
I never…
had a chance…
to tell you this.
Thank you…
for being in my life.
Be happy.
You have to be happy…
for me.
Why didn't you say anything about us
in your interview?
Because I don't care about other people.
It doesn't matter as long as…
you and I…
remember how much we loved each other.
What I wanted…
wasn't approval from the world.
I just wanted you…
to muster up your courage.
So I'm happy now.
Wherever I am,
I'll remember…
your face today.
You couldn't help…
but run over to me.
That look on your face.
How you look today.
That's all I need.
No.
Give me…
just a bit more time.
Where's my father?
He's in the study.
Mr. Han.
Don't you have…
anything to tell me?
Like what?
I did everything you told me to do.
But Ms. Jung found out about it.
Of course. I'm the one who told her.
That's no way to treat a human being.
If you toss me out like a piece of gum
that you're done chewing,
what am I supposed to do? Tell me!
That gum will want to cling to
the bottom of your shoe…
and pester the heck out of you.
Ms. Joo.
You just called me. What is it?
Right.
Do I have to stay here, Mr. Han?
I mean… Sir?
Stay here until I say otherwise.
Yes, sir.
Did you have dinner?
Yes.
It's been a while
since I thoroughly enjoyed a meal.
Chef Hwang is pretty good.
The room on the first floor
is ready for you.
Please try to understand your mother.
She…
eventually found the place…
where I used to secretly
meet your real mother.
And I'm sure she was livid
beyond my imagination.
Since I know how angry she must be,
I'm not upset
that your mother kicked me out.
I did put her through a lot.
The woman who gave birth to Ha-joon.
And Hi-soo who raised him.
Be grateful to them.
Don't hurt anyone.
Because you are at fault.
Good night.
HI-SOO
Hello?
-What are these photos?
-Han Ji-yong's double life.
Were you waiting for me?
I need to tell you something.
It's about Ji-yong.
I know about it.
-You do?
-I saw what you found out.
I guess I can benefit
from your rage sometimes.
Good job.
Ms. Joo.
Yes, sir.
You know where the secret place
at Cadenza is, right?
Hello, Ms. Jung.
I need to talk to Father.
Should I take you there right now?
Yes.
Ji-yong.
I'm…
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Why…
Why did you do that to me?
Even when the whole world
turns its back on you,
if you have just one person
who believes in you,
you can go on living.
But…
he never had that one person.
Yes, Mr. Yoon.
I received a tip-off
regarding Mr. Han Ji-yong.
No.
Did you know about the dogfighting ring?
It's shocking to find out
what kind of person he is.
Please stop it.
Please.
I must protect my son.
You really…
only think about your son.
I'll do my best.
You need to make up your mind
and decide as soon as possible.
Get some rest, Father.
You should get some sleep.
I have to drive Mr. Han Ji-yong
back to Rubato.
No. Don't!
Just leave him there.
What do you mean? Leave him where?
He's in the bunker right now.
The chairman's bunker.
And the door is closed.
What? No way.
But it can't be opened from the inside.
That's not my problem.
When people cross me, I get upset too.
Do you know
what it's like to be humiliated?
It's impossible not to feel humiliated
when you work here.
Put yourself in my shoes.
And do as I say.
-Answer me!
-Okay.
Drive.
I told Father everything.
I have to protect Hyowon Group,
so I can't reveal Ji-yong to the public.
And I have to protect Ha-joon.
That's all I can think about now.
I'm sending him abroad.
Ms. Lee will take him.
Okay.
I think that's wise.
I'm about to lose it.
When I think about Ha-joon, I'm terrified.
I can't do anything.
I have to end this marriage
and escape from this family
as soon as possible.
I have to separate Ha-joon
from such a monster.
But I can't bring myself to destroy
the perfect image he has of his father.
If he finds out
what his father is really like,
he'll be traumatized
for the rest of his life.
I change my mind every second
because of this terrible dilemma.
I think I'm going insane.
Don't beat yourself up.
You're in a dilemma no one should be in.
No one can make a better decision
than you.
I can't advise you on what to do either.
It's only natural…
that you're suffering.
I've been in a similar place before.
Do you know whom I went to for help?
Mother Emma.
But…
there is one person in this family
who has never gotten counseling from her.
Han Ji-yong.
That's understandable.
-He's given up to be human--
-No.
Mother Emma knew Han Ji-yong
before she knew anyone else here.
She has known him…
for a very long time.
How?
She and Han Ji-yong's birth mother
were very close.
They were close for decades.
But…
why have they…
pretended not to know each other?
Hey, open up.
Is anyone out there?
Ms. Joo!
That bastard.
Damn it.
Poor thing.
I heard you fired Soo-young…
in a rude and disrespectful way.
I'm going to get rid of people
who aren't on my side one by one.
I'll be in a drama soon.
Don't get in my way.
Nothing will go your way.
Should I give you
a taste of your own medicine?
I know you like making people fight.
How far does your inhumanity extend?
I'm not going to protect you now because
you're not carrying my child anymore.
Why don't you get in the ring
instead of watching like a coward?
Speaking of which,
we can't…
let Ha-joon watch this fight.
And to prevent that,
I'm sending him abroad to study.
What?
It's only a matter of time
before the world finds out about you.
Ha-joon can never find out
what kind of person you are.
He's my son.
You can't do as you want.
A father paid men to fight
and enjoyed watching them.
How do you think his child would feel
when they find out?
Why must that child be Ha-joon? Why?
You'd better stop here.
If you don't, I'll kill you.
You cannot entrust him with Hyowon Group.
Your emotions cannot sway your decision.
He is…
a destroyer.
Kill him.
Hello?
Hello.
This is Inspector Hwang Hyeong-su
from Gwangun Police Station.
Hello.
Last night,
Kwak Su-chang was found dead.
But the last person
he talked to on the phone
was you, Mr. Han.
I need you to come down to the station.
THE REASON HAN JIN-HO GOT PASSED OVER
"TURNS OUT TO BE AN ALCOHOLIC"
Did you want to see me?
I want you…
to kill Ji-yong.
Ha-joon.
Don't go on the internet
with your phone today.
Why not?
Yes, Mr. Yoon.
Yes.
He's dead?
Mom, the light.
My gosh.
Han Ha-joon.
You're the only person
who can protect yourself.
So you have to be strong. Okay?
Whatever happens,
I'll be right behind you.
So don't be afraid of anything.
Wait.
You should meet the tutor who will
take Ha-joon abroad before you leave.
Hello.
I'm Ha-joon's tutor,
Lee Hye-jin.
Hello, Ms. Joo.
It's been a while.
This way.
Who do you think should take the position?
I'll do it.
I will protect Hyowon Group…
at all costs.
10 DAYS BEFORE THE MURDER
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM JUNG-HWA
Do you think you can go on living
like nothing happened?
Just stay quiet.
You should know to be afraid
if you know what kind of person I am.
What are you planning behind my back?
Just stay still and don't do anything.
There were a total of three people
at the scene.
Ms. Seo Hi-soo, the late Mr. Han Ji-yong,
and one more person. Who could it be?
I don't remember anything.
All the memories I had
after meeting Han Ji-yong are gone.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son