аго
remedy
Colombia
Sha Stop
He is a man of the martial arts world.
He is actually a king.
He is good friends with the court.
He is a man of the martial arts world.
I heard that he is going to give up martial arts.
He is going to play chess and painting.
His martial arts are very good.
He is a man of the world.
He is immersed in peace and is very mischievous.
Officer Cai, my porridge should be here.
If I keep talking, the porridge will get cold.
It's rude to bring it in and eat it.
You are holding hands with me.
Are you afraid of being rude?
I came to visit the bedroom.
I can't even see you.
I am disabled.
I am blocking the screen.
First, for the sake of the party.
Second, people with disabilities are ashamed to see people.
Officer Cai is the leader of the royal family.
Don't be like me.
Then just say it.
My family and the dead gold hall are in a fight.
Which side do you stand on?
I am the leader of the royal family.
The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Officer Cai,
I am not a martial arts master.
I don't know martial arts.
It's useless to stand on any side.
The Yan Gang is a rich country.
Don't say that.
You are going to kill me.
Then why do you earn so much money?
The Yan Gang
is a lawless country.
The business is illegal.
There are many enemies.
The court is also an enemy.
The court is an enemy.
What's wrong with us?
It's different.
You treat the court as an enemy.
The court treats me as an enemy.
The Yan Gang
is going to find a way
in the gap.
Please
forgive me.
I will say a few things.
Chief Hu, please think about it.
Last October,
the Taifu Temple
was destroyed.
Seven people died in one night.
They were all poisoned.
In July of the previous year,
the Ming Zhou was betrayed and killed.
The officials
were shocked
by the news.
Five days ago,
the new leader of the Ba Zhou,
Feng Youlan,
was not killed.
He must have died.
Chief Hu,
if you don't help,
the enmity between the Chai family
and the Yan Gang will be over.
Chief Chai.
Chief Chai,
Chief Hu asked you to come.
Please close the door.
Don't hide.
Face to face, say it.
Chief Chai, say it.
The Chai family and the Zijing Hall
all have your people,
right?
Before the Zheng came,
some of the money
was spent in the court.
The other part
was spent
on the Chai family
and the Zijing Hall.
Otherwise,
how could the Yan Gang
survive
between the court and the Jianghu?
Qi Qing,
Tie Ling,
Tie Mu,
who is your man in the court?
Come and see me.
The six masters of the Chai family
are called three.
All three are.
How can the six masters
be bought with money?
Chief Chai,
you are too suspicious.
I have made it clear.
I will not leave
for nothing.
Chief Chai,
the soul-suppressing
Qi Gong is already
the seventh one.
How about this?
The Chai family
is fighting with the Zijing Hall.
I stand
It's not good for them
They just want to make some money
Well
My people
will listen to you
Okay?
On the eighth day, I will meet with Dantian
Before the eighth day
half of the people of Wuhang Bazaar will die
You are too high-minded
Two of them died in Baxian
Now five are in Jiangling
You are not high-minded
Why do I come here and visit you personally?
Then today
I will kill one more person
to reassure you
I will stand by your side
It's a deal
You should leave
Hu Jianshou is disabled
I can't see him off
Goodbye
I went to Lin'an to see Dantian
I heard that Chayu came here
Chayu came here
Chayu wants to fight against Zijintang
I will stand by Zijintang's side
Chief, have you decided
to fight against both sides?
Not directly
I trained the masters of both families
and waited for this time
After the eighth day
there will be no Chayu and Zijintang
Only Yan Gang and Zijintang
I see
It's cold
It's from Kuizhou
I will ask Yanshi
What should she do?
escort Xie Huizhen into the military
We deal with two tactical encounters
We'll all kill you
As long as they deal with girls
the sizes of your body are enough
I'm still worried about you
I mean the fire
Chief, your son, Hu Baili, is dead.
What else did you say?
The 17th is about to arrive.
Take Young Master to the city.
Next time you leave, you will die.
Okay.
Let's go.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I've never seen you like this.
You dressed so well, but you didn't let anyone see you.
Why?
I don't know if you can see me.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
You're so...
Brother.
It's our young lady. I didn't see it wrong.
Young lady, two people are in Cuihua House.
One more student is with them.
I've never seen him in Kuizhou.
Did Elder Wu Ha call you?
The deputy chief of the official business is in Pengzi.
He should be here.
It's the same. Don't follow me.
Young lady, there are only two people left in the West Wing.
Even if Ouyang Feng's martial arts are good,
if we go together, we can do it.
Why do you...
Why what?
Why do you invite Elder Wu Ha?
It's complicated.
It's complicated. You can talk about it.
Let's go.
Am I not good in this?
You're good in everything.
Young lady, I think
it's better for us to stay by your side.
After all, the rest of the people died in my hands.
If the chief of the unit is blamed,
I can't afford to take the responsibility.
Young lady, how complicated is it?
To put it simply,
I just want to play with Ouyang Feng.
Good.
Come on.
Beat him.
Hold the chopsticks.
Good.
Come on.
This is too much fun.
Good.
What do you want to play?
Brother Ouyang,
why don't we find a quiet place
to rest?
Come on.
Look around.
There is only such a place in the South.
Go.
Brother Yao.
There is a woman
in the car.
Young Master,
the body of the immortal brought back from Mount Ba,
before he died,
he gave him a letter of filial piety.
Open it.
My son died in Kuizhou.
Why are you back?
Master,
let you know the reason.
We'll leave after we finish talking.
Say it.
Young Master,
under the order of the master,
went to Mount Ba
to kill the new Ba Zhou
leader, Feng Youlan.
Feng Youlan was killed.
His daughter jumped off the cliff.
Young Master looked at the bottom of the cliff.
Unexpectedly,
Feng Youlan was killed.
He looked at the bottom of the cliff.
Unexpectedly,
Feng Youlan was killed.
He was covered in blood.
He was so close to the East.
He jumped up and ran away.
Go on.
Young Master was filial.
He knew the body of the master,
so he brought this woman back to Mount Ba.
He wanted to send a general to help the master.
I followed Young Master's
imperial edict
to kill the three Westerners.
The people were killed.
The people of the government were arrested.
I took the luggage of the three people
back to Fenduo.
It was dark.
A demon came back to take the luggage.
I killed Young Master.
Demon?
Master,
I've never seen a person's
martial arts skills
so high.
I've never heard of it.
A person's martial arts skills
can't be so high.
Was he with the Westerners?
Yes.
He met him at the first station.
The three Westerners' leader is Ouyang Feng.
His martial arts skills are also very high.
Do you have anything else to say?
Master,
I have two more words.
That demon
must have a private relationship with this woman.
When he was at the first station,
the demon took the pill for him.
This woman can't die.
She must have something to do with the demon.
Si Qi Guang!
Master!
Master is our brother
who is fighting with Kuizhou.
It's me!
I told him to keep an eye on
the whereabouts of the demon and Ouyang Feng.
Master!
Call him in.
Si Qi Guang!
Master!
Speak.
A foreign man came
and he went to see the Westerners.
He was at the first station.
He's dead.
He's at Cuihua Pavilion.
Go to Cuihua Pavilion
and tell that demon
to come here.
Chief Lei?
Didn't you say
that woman and I have a private relationship?
Don't disturb the business.
Just tell him to come alone.
I know.
The drum is played by the hands.
It's played slowly.
It's the fun of playing the drum.
Yes.
It's boring if you turn it around.
Really?
No way.
Am I the winner?
The little friend is a pair of red heads.
The third one is the last one.
But it doesn't matter.
Do you want to add ten coins?
Yes.
Add some.
Add some coins.
I'm still a kid.
Yes.
I may be younger than you.
What are you looking at?
Okay.
Add ten more coins.
So rich.
Add some coins.
Five.
Go.
Four.
Ding.
One.
Two.
One pair of coins.
The second one is the right number.
You lied to me.
I lose if I bet.
How is it?
Is it fun?
You can have me if you can.
Yes.
Again.
Do you miss someone?
Yes.
Kuizhou is dying.
We three came out of the Western Regions.
We have only two left after Brother Lie died.
You joined and there are three left.
What are you?
But Young Master likes you.
He is happy to see you.
He is in the Southern Dynasty and he is in a good mood.
It may be better to kill you.
He is afraid that you are unhappy.
It's too complicated.
Too complicated.
From Kuizhou to Jiangning,
there is no difference between
my body and yours.
This is your reason.
I will untie you.
Can you move?
Can you talk?
When I was young,
I went to Bashan.
There are mountains,
roads and cliffs.
How can I not die
when I fall?
There is no one in this world.
What is the name of the person
who gave you the pill?
How did he save you?
Head, put me down.
Put me down.
Do you understand?
Let's move.
How?
I know a little about monogamy.
There are two ways to get a good monogamy.
First, it requires a lot of money.
Second, it requires a lot of time.
Third, it requires a lot of effort.
Fourth, it requires a lot of patience.
Fifth, it requires a lot of effort.
Sixth, it requires a lot of patience.
Seventh, it requires a lot of time.
Don't move.
I beg you to do me a favor.
Say it.
Kill me.
Everything has a cause and effect.
Your father died in my son's hands.
My son died in the hands of the one who gave you the pill.
He will be here soon.
You will see him.
I want him to keep his promise to my son.
Do you want to add more?
Did you see the sign?
I didn't see it.
It doesn't matter even if you see it.
I believe you.
Add more.
Give me a gold.
Young Master.
Give it to me.
Kid, you can't gamble for money.
I don't gamble.
Then why?
I don't believe it.
You should be good at family life.
You can't stand the frustration and anger.
You will hurt your body and money.
You will be drunk and strong.
I won't play with you.
You are not happy.
Just gamble.
Don't talk about the North.
I bet gold.
Dare or not?
It's too big.
I'm worried.
I don't want gold.
Add ten more.
Okay?
I'm afraid.
I've never been afraid in my life.
Start.
Go.
Is it big?
Wen Zi.
Double sky.
It's the same as my previous card.
It's the second card.
You are so arrogant.
Who is arrogant?
Open your card.
I'm so unlucky.
Blow.
Ding.
Kid.
Sorry.
I'm so unlucky.
I can't meet you twice a year.
You.
Come.
You just took my secret three-day soul umbrella.
I'm so unlucky.
I turretults took the soul umbrella.
It's rocket of the
Do you want to come in?
What about you?
Imperial Physician Huang.
Physician Huang?
Is he willing to let her live?
He is.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have saved her in the Eight Hills.
How did you save her?
The bones around her
were broken into 70 pieces.
They were all fixed.
For her two pieces,
nine times the Yin Wheel Pill.
Nine times the Yin Wheel Pill?
It was practiced many years ago.
There are only seven in the world.
Now there are only five left.
In order to save her,
are you willing to die?
Why did you choose to do so?
Because I have no grudge against her.
You killed my son.
Since she is dead,
don't care too much.
It's no use caring.
If you don't care,
you will feel better.
I don't care.
It makes sense.
Take me away.
I'm sorry.
In the Yizhan Valley,
I can't take you.
Forget it.
Then why did you come back?
My brother,
Ouyang Feng, said
we should meet.
What you said just now
makes sense.
I'm sorry.
Since my son is dead,
don't care too much.
It's no use caring.
It's great
that you think so.
I have long vowed
not to kill.
I had no choice
at that time.
You and him
have no personal feelings.
My subordinate said
we just met by chance.
We don't know each other.
Now,
we only meet for the third time.
I take back what I said just now.
Let's change our way of saying it.
Let him live.
You can kill your brother,
Ouyang Feng.
Why do you have to choose?
Because no one can stop you.
You don't want to take him away.
I just
gave him
my secret
three-day soul-losing pill.
He won't remember
the person he knew
when he was young.
He won't know
who he is tomorrow.
At this time in the day after tomorrow,
he will
be scattered.
Before the day after tomorrow,
bring your brother Ouyang Feng
to see me.
To detoxify him.
Let him go.
The past is a mess.
I will protect him.
I will keep my words.
Go.
Oh my god.
I'm leaving.
Go.
I won't come back.
Don't come back.
The one who doesn't remember the past
is a good person.
It's better to be scattered.
In this world,
what else
do you want me to do for you?
This one thing,
don't listen to him
and kill your brother.
Live well in this world.
The longer, the better.
This painting,
someone told me
it's exactly the same.
Go.
Let's part ways.
I will be with you.
What's your name?
Feng Heng.
Get out!
Go!
Calm down.
Let's buy a new one.
You can buy a new one.
Today's first day is going so smoothly.
Everyone is happy.
Thank you.
Look at him.
Give it to him.
Prime Minister, these people
are shameless.
I admit defeat.
I'm just being honest.
My friend is very good.
I like you.
Why don't you burn this place down?
Kill these shameless people.
Give me the gold.
Let's go.
Don't be angry.
What is he doing?
Just let it go.
Then I'll be shameless.
Yes.
Happy today?
Very satisfied.
Take two pieces of gold.
What are you playing?
Let's go.
You want to leave?
What did you say?
Give me the gold.
Again.
Two pieces.
I don't believe it.
You're a bad mouth.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
I'll see where you're going.
What's your name?
Ouyang Feng.
I'm Chai Qiong.
I'll let you be honest today.
I'll teach you how to be a person.
Show your cards.
I'm nervous.
You two are so handsome.
That's right.
You're a bad mouth.
Don't laugh.
I'm not bad.
Sir, you're a good mouth.
Only Lingling is less good than him.
You don't have to be happy.
No need to worry.
Don't be angry.
Go, go, go.
No more water.
Master's treasure
kill the four of them.
I'm so happy.
I'll kill you guys.
Sit and eat.
Water usage.
Then you're willing to accept me to be your governing body,
sent me to Chuhua Tower.
If you want a horse,
say yes or no.
H..H..
Wow!
Oops!
Stupid f.. tu..
Good horse!
Well,
should I
No.
I'll sell it at the market tomorrow morning
Yes, Master Chen
That's how Ma became his?
Come on, let's go
Ouyang Feng, my friend
It's good news that you lost
Go back to find Brother Yao
You're leaving just like that?
No, you can't leave
I was not clean-mouthed just now
I want to apologize
Young Master, you heard it
Jin Zi and Ma gave him
and you want to apologize to him?
How?
You're good
He can apologize
He's my man
He should apologize to me
You should apologize to him too
Give me the gold
Zhao, don't hurt anyone
Apologize is not enough
Kneel down and kowtow
I'll let you go
It's not too late to kneel down
I'll let you kneel down
Two more
You know martial arts?
Not much
Do you want to learn?
I'm willing to admit defeat
He scolded you
You just hit him
Let's go our separate ways, OK?
No
Don't hit me
I don't want to hurt you
Come on
I won, you can have the gold
Give me one
Yes, only one hand
You want to find the rose yourself
He's good at martial arts
but he's good at fighting
Now you see
I'll fight with you
My hi
I'm Xin Ji
Really?
Come on
Your fight cant have this
negócio
Good
Go
You...
You've been so angry since the first move.
You can't stand any grievance.
Your moves are bad.
Your martial arts are also bad.
Well,
I'll give you a leg
to teach you a lesson.
What martial arts?
Nothing special.
I haven't fought with people for years.
I'm happy today.
I'm also good at fighting.
Come on.
I'll let you learn the Western Baituo Mountain's martial arts.
It's a little difficult.
Composer,
o Official,
is a good move.
An eunuch like me
only has to need powerful moves and martial arts.
He's good, isn't he?
Your...
Your attack pasayed to my hand.
I won't let you be fought by anyone.
What's your identity, Wu Lin of the Southern Dynasty?
Don't talk about Wu Lin
I'm just a gambler
Don't talk about the Southern Dynasty
People from the north and the west should know
This is the Song Dynasty
Wu Lin of the Southern Dynasty, are you the best?
Why do you still talk about the Southern Dynasty?
Song Dynasty!
Are you the best?
You're happy if you lose to the best?
At least you're the second or third?
Little friend
Everything is as usual
The king is like gambling
The next game, you lose
Don't talk about the rules with me
You're really a bad guy
I'm Cuihua Tower
The best in martial arts
Jiangling is also the best
The Song Dynasty
Song Dynasty?
Who dares to say the first?
Excuse me, where is Cuihua Tower's horse house?
Where is it?
Turn left
Thanks
You and Ouyang Feng are a team, right?
It's okay
Relax his heart
Life is a little more open
I'm going back to quit gambling
Today's handover is too smooth
The Song Dynasty