(Refresh Over Flowers)
Nice to see you.
It's been a while, Joy.
- It's been a while.
- Hello.
How have you been?
I've been getting
a lot of attention these days.
(She spent...)
(three hours
just on at-home treatment routines.)
You'd see these devices
at a skincare clinic.
(A flood of useful devices
for her silky-smooth skin)
("After I saw her use the device,
I couldn't help but buy it.")
("How cute. She's so busy
taking care of herself at home.")
("It's so cute that she's in pajamas
and a total homebody.")
After her episode aired,
the devices she used...
- Right.
- were sold out.
You know the fascia massage tool?
- Yes.
- I wanted to buy it too.
- Was it sold out?
- It was sold out.
- Really?
Hyun Moo, did you buy anything?
I bet you bought something.
I already had a few of them.
- I knew it.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He's the Trend Sensitive Man.
So I didn't buy more stuff.
(I knew it.)
- Okay. So spring is in full bloom.
- Yes.
So we prepared
a new makeover episode.
It's called
the Rainbow Refresh Special.
Yes.
This will be a series.
- What's the hotkey for refresh? F5.
- Yes.
F5.
(What did I just witness?)
- He had to press it twice?
- Twice?
Na Rae is the first member
for the Refresh Special.
- Yes. It's me.
- I see.
I got a complete makeover.
- Again?
I was aware of this problem
for a while now.
But I wanted to turn away from it.
I tried to fix it gradually,
but I fixed it in one go this time.
- Okay.
- All right.
Part One
of the Rainbow Refresh Special.
Let's check out
Na Rae's day-to-day life.
- It's Part One. This must go well.
- How cute.
That's so cute.
(Rainbow Refresh Special for Spring)
(Let's Start Afresh)
(The spring sun
beams down brightly.)
Gosh, sir.
- Hold on.
- What?
- I'll do it fast.
(Why is Na Rae
on the operating table?)
(The lights in the OR
turn on all of a sudden.)
- Something to wipe it with.
- Yes.
- Hand me a piece of dry gauze.
- Dry gauze?
Just the dry one.
(Surgery equipment is seen
all over the room.)
My gosh. Hold on.
I came to remove
fibroepithelial polyps.
- That's why I'm here.
- What's that?
Fibroepithelial polyps?
(The name of the disease is
fibroepithelial polyp?)
Yes. I'm here
to remove rat's nipples.
I see. My gosh.
- So cute.
- Rat's nipples.
But the correct name is
fibroepithelial polyp.
I'm embarrassed to say it,
so that's what I tell people.
But why do people call it
a rat's nipple?
Because it really looks like
a rat's nipple.
- It must be so tiny.
- A real rat's nipple?
- Yes. Right.
- Yes.
I heard there were so many of them
people weren't even aware of.
- Right. I bet everyone has some.
- Yes.
- Right. Everyone has it.
- Everyone has them.
When you scratch your neck,
you'll feel these bumps.
- Those bumps.
- But people aren't aware.
Will they keep getting bigger?
- Yes, if you let them be.
- If you let them be.
Those two hit a growth spurt.
Yes, they did.
(Given the size,
they must've hit a growth spurt.)
(I must get them removed
before they grow any bigger.)
- Why is your neck so long?
- Gosh, look how thin her neck is.
- I was so tense when he did that.
- My gosh.
- Hey, working out paid off.
- Yes.
During my 1st appointment,
I removed about 120 of them.
During my 2nd appointment,
I removed 80.
Today, I only removed 20.
It's the result of aging.
That's so draining.
You have to cauterize them all
while you're at it.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
(Her skin is fully refreshed.)
Your skin looks clear.
The weather is good, at least.
(Yawning)
(She yawns
after removing rat's nipples.)
My gosh.
There are so many people
since it's lunchtime.
I must hurry up.
(Is she trying
to protect her makeup-free face?)
- Hello.
- My gosh. I'm a fan!
Enjoy your lunch. Yes.
Enjoy your lunch.
You should've said,
"I got rid of rat's nipples."
How could I?
They were on their way to lunch.
It's not easy to walk around
after the procedure.
(She hurriedly heads
into a building.)
(Plastic Surgery Clinic)
Another one?
You visited
two plastic surgery clinics?
- It's the Refresh Day.
- Hello.
I made an appointment.
- What's your name?
- It's Park Na Rae.
That's right.
I believe...
I've reached the peak of my looks
in my lifetime.
The thing is,
your hard effort does pay off.
Hold on. My gosh.
The year 2019 was the worst for you.
My gosh, that was...
Your beauty had
a decade-long dormant period,
and it's finally out now?
But isn't that great?
If you look the best now?
(- "Na Rae looks so beautiful now."
- "When did she get so beautiful?")
A lot of people commented on
how beautiful you looked now.
- She looks so beautiful now.
- Right.
Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- Please sit down.
- It's my first time here.
- Okay.
- Yes.
What brings you here, though?
- Well, when you look at me,
- Yes?
- you wouldn't think I have it.
- Right.
- But...
- Okay.
- this part...
- Yes.
(This part...)
At one point,
my makeup artist started...
- to fill in these gaps...
- Yes.
- with something.
- I see.
- She also does the same here.
Gosh, I'm at a clinic that
specializes in treating hair loss.
- Oh, no.
- My gosh.
(Na Rae. This can't be.)
(Is your hair thinning too?)
(This is a plastic surgery clinic
for hair.)
There's been an increase
in female patients now.
- There are a lot of us now.
- Right.
A lot of people go there
to prevent hair loss, right?
Indeed.
As for the rat's nipple,
I accepted them, so I went there.
But it took a long time to accept
that my hair was thinning.
But from time to time,
I looked at pictures
and watched videos of me.
(Dense, voluminous hair)
Look at my hairline. It's dense.
- Look. Her roots were still strong.
- Right.
Her hair was voluminous too.
It must be because...
- you dyed your hair a lot.
- Yes.
By the way, back then,
your hairstyles were great.
I bet I dyed my hair
in every color possible.
I probably dyed it
as many times as an idol star.
(But 2 years ago,)
(it was the day
when the heart of a beast awakened.)
- Your hair started thinning then.
- It was this day.
(Hair loss was discovered
by this cool girl.)
When your testosterone level is high,
your hair thins out.
(The patients of hair loss
had warned her about it.)
Back then,
I thought you were joking.
One, two. Great.
(Was it because of
her intense workouts?)
My testosterone level did go up.
The bigger your lats grew,
the smaller your head got.
(Looking bulky)
I'm starting to see some empty spots.
Oh, no.
By the looks of it,
you'll lose hair in a circular patch.
Only that part will be bald.
But I can't give up on
working out my lats.
- Right.
- After developing lats,
the testosterone level did go up.
- That usually happens to men.
- Right.
- So she became a strong man now.
- Yes.
- You bet.
- Gosh.
You are both experiencing hair loss.
How can you tease her like that?
We're in the same boat.
- He's too blunt.
- Yes.
- This show isn't easy.
- Right.
If you stay here longer,
you'll develop lats.
You'll be Ms. Jo Lats soon.
(You'll be Ms. Jo Lats soon.)
"Jo Lats?"
Gosh, that's a pretty name.
- You were a Jo?
- Yes.
No, my last name is Park.
- Jo Lats.
(Jo Lats: Real name, Park Soo Young)
- Let me take a look.
- Okay.
(Let me take a look.)
Is it gone?
(Trailing off)
Na Rae.
(Doctor, please say something.)
I was in despair back then.
(He continues to check her scalp
without saying anything.)
Am I in big trouble?
Let me explain everything to you
after I check it with a microscope.
- I'll explain everything.
- Okay.
He didn't answer her right away.
- Let's take some scans.
- Okay.
- Why don't we discuss this again...
- Yes.
- after we look at your scans?
- Okay.
You can sit under it.
- I bet you've never seen it before.
- I know what it is.
- You do?
- Yes. When it comes to hair loss,
I'm as knowledgeable as a resident.
There's a website called
Baldies, Let's Get Together.
- There's a website like that?
- Are you talking about Daedamo?
Baldies, Let's Get Together...
- is a community website.
- Okay.
In Korean,
it's shortened as Daedamo.
- Daedamo.
- I've been a member for 20 years.
So I'm well-versed in this field.
I stopped hair loss that continued
for three generations in my family.
I stopped it.
I stopped hair loss in my family.
(I am a hero of hair loss.)
- The captured data...
- What is this?
The captured data can be used...
It looks like 3D printing.
She looks scary.
(Glaring)
- That's scary.
- This is a horror film.
It's because
I could hear the camera moving.
My eyes kept following it.
- It might come with your job.
- I think so.
Hair loss is related to stress.
- So, you will have a stress test.
- Okay.
- What is a stress test?
- Is this correct?
- Yes.
- Could you give me your wrists?
I'm so stressed lately.
- It's an ECG.
- Yes.
- Oh, my gosh.
- An ECG and that one.
- It's an EEG. It's interesting.
- Yes, an EEG.
- The test starts.
- I see.
- That's right.
- Close your eyes.
(Is stress causing my hair loss?)
- The test is done.
- Thank you.
You will see the doctor right away.
Please come this way.
Why did my photos
turn out like this?
Was I supposed to close my eyes?
(Glinting)
She looks like Kim Byeong Ok.
(Actor Kim Byeong Ok?)
What's that?
Let's see your hair condition.
If you look here...
(The test result)
You have no idea how nervous I was.
Let's see.
(Is my hair all right?)
If you see here...
Your hair gap is pretty wide.
It is empty, actually.
(Her hair now and then)
- Oh, my gosh!
- Na Rae.
- Oh, my.
- You're lowering your head.
You had thick hair back then.
- What should I do?
- Few people have hair like that.
- That's true.
- Not many people are like that.
- I used to have really thick hair.
- So did I.
I looked like the Simpsons.
My hair was like this.
You couldn't even see
his hair's texture.
I told you that I had curly hair,
so mosquitoes
used to get stuck in my hair.
- They got stuck like this.
- Like room escape?
(A mosquito nightmare)
I had so many mosquitoes.
But the hair all disappeared.
- I see.
- That's all the past.
- You can see that your hair gap...
- Yes.
is widening.
Also, you're not...
that young anymore.
- He was straightforward.
- Yes.
Hair loss is also part of aging.
(Hair loss is also part of aging.)
I see.
He said it's part of aging.
Unfortunately, as you age,
your hair gap is widening.
Your hair is getting thinner.
You need to
start taking care of this.
I was shocked at first.
Then, I felt humiliated.
I care less about my belly
and chubby back.
But it was embarrassing
to show my scalp.
I was really embarrassed.
I could see my scalp.
You're right.
We talk about two things.
What matters in your 40s and 50s
is your skin and hair.
- He’s right.
- If you have thin hair…
when you get older,
no matter how pretty...
or handsome you are,
- you don't look elegant.
- You're right.
You can often see bald men.
However, it's uncommon for women
to lose hair in their 20s and 30s.
- As women age,
- That's right.
testosterone levels rise
while estrogen levels decrease.
That could cause hair loss.
Many women over the age of 50
experience hair loss.
Does this mean I've started
producing testosterone?
Every woman has testosterone.
But women produce much more estrogen
so it protects the hair.
I also have estrogen,
although I'm a man.
- I also have estrogen.
- I see.
This is the result
of your stress test.
You can see how much your stress...
- causes your hair loss.
- I see.
I'm curious about the result.
Your stress level is high.
It's really high.
- Oh, my gosh.
- You have interpersonal conflicts,
work-related concerns,
and many things on your mind.
You don't have accumulated fatigue,
so it’s not considered chronic.
It's acute stress.
Something triggered stress lately.
Acute stress.
You're seriously lacking sleep.
Your alpha and theta waves
are too lacking.
High alpha and theta waves indicate
that you have rested sufficiently.
If a normal person's sleep quality
is 70,
yours is only 30.
- Yours is only 30.
- That's really low.
Are you having trouble sleeping?
- I sleep quite a lot.
- Okay.
- I sleep for eight hours.
- I see.
- But I keep waking up.
The result shows that
recent stress caused that.
This has been caused recently too.
- Have you read the news online?
- No.
- Of course not.
- Okay.
- I'm saying it based on the result.
- I'm sorry.
The result shows it.
Many things have happened.
The past eight days...
felt like eight years.
The news kept getting published.
Every day was a series of surprises.
(Every day was
a series of surprises.)
Listen, everyone. What matters is...
- that everything is fine now.
- That's good.
- Yes.
- It was a refresh, wasn't it?
It was a total refresh.
The case has already been sent
to the prosecutor's office.
- Really?
- Of course.
- Also, I got everything back.
- I see.
So I'm not stressed anymore.
- Do you sleep well?
- Yes, I do.
- That's a relief.
- I sleep really well.
The result shows
your heart is very healthy.
Do you work out?
- Yes, I do.
- When the level is...
above 9.2, it is considered normal.
So, you're healthy.
- Those who do weight training...
- Yes.
- tend to have a higher level.
- I did lat workouts yesterday.
- That's great.
- We should work out.
You have a good immune system
and vitality.
Your vitality is good.
Your autonomic nervous system
is similar to that of a 34-year-old.
- It's 5 years younger than you.
- It's 34 years old.
- Great.
- That's good.
If someone asks how old you are,
- say that you're 34.
- Gosh.
- I will.
- Who cares about hair loss?
- What are you talking about?
- Staying healthy is what matters.
Okay. So, I'll check your hair...
with a microscope now.
(My hair under a microscope)
I'm nervous.
- I'll look at it now.
- Yes.
I've done that.
- Look at the screen.
- What is this?
Don't panic. It's all good.
- Is it dirty? Why is it so red?
- You can see inflammation here.
- Look at that.
- Oh, my gosh.
Your scalp is red.
- Why does it look like that?
- There are many dead skin cells.
They are near the forehead hairline
because of stress.
It's okay. Anyone...
can have this much.
Your hair is thin.
This area...
I can see a lot of her scalp.
As you got older,
you probably lost your hair.
You have a lot of thin hair
in this area.
I can see these areas a lot.
It indeed became thin.
(Mixed feelings)
I can see my scalp through my hair.
Once it becomes thin, it falls out.
If you look at it...
Look at the screen.
You can see your hair condition
on the screen.
In the areas
where you have hair loss,
hair density is 50 instead of 120.
- Oh, no.
- No.
The hair thickness
should be 0.075mm,
- but it's only 0.023mm.
- I see.
The hair on the front side is thin.
I can see that.
In general, you have thin hair.
So, it says your hair
is thinner than normal.
You can treat it to make it better.
Don't feel too sad.
You actually came here
at the right time.
- It's great that you see a doctor.
- It is.
Would you like to get treatment
if you have time?
- What kind of treatment?
- I'll also prescribe medication.
Do I have to take medicine?
I would recommend it.
- It'd be good to start taking it.
- Is it finasteride?
No, that's medicine for men.
- How did you know the name?
- How did you know that?
Are you okay with getting
a shot on the scalp?
- Does it hurt?
- It stings.
- Like getting acupuncture.
- Okay. I'll get it.
(I'll get a shot on the scalp.)
- I have some questions.
- Okay.
I'm taking
brewer's yeast and biotin.
Are they effective
for treating hair loss?
I'm curious about that too.
They're not medications
for hair loss.
They're more like supplements.
If I use shampoo
that is good for the scalp,
will it be effective?
It won't treat hair loss,
but it will make the scalp healthy.
Like using good cosmetics.
- Is soybean juice effective?
- What?
I asked a lot of questions.
For it to be effective,
you must drink a ton.
I was so curious.
There are so many unverified ways...
of treating hair loss.
There are so many so-called experts.
(A resident specializing
in hair loss, Moomoo)
(A member of Daedamo
for 20 years, Kian84)
Some of the Rainbow Club members
are so-called experts.
So, I want to find out what is true.
(I want to know about hair loss.)
- Do women get hair transplants?
- Yes.
Why did they blur her?
Not many people get it
on the top of the head.
But this part is easy to transplant.
As you get older,
you lose downy hair.
That's why it looks empty here.
It looks darker
when you have downy hair.
- My scalp easily gets warm.
- I see.
I heard that wearing a hat
can be bad for the scalp.
Yes, it's bad.
- Sunlight is worse for the scalp.
- Gosh.
- That's right.
- Really?
- Wear a clean hat.
But don't wear one that's too tight.
People say it's bad
to pluck gray hairs.
- Is it true?
- Should I pluck it or not?
You're also curious, right?
If you keep plucking gray hairs,
your hair will degenerate.
- You should dye your gray hairs.
- What is this video?
I see.
I prepared for a body profile
photoshoot last year.
Did the testosterone I produced
cause this?
Those who prepare
for body profile photoshoots...
lose a lot of hair
because they are...
on an extremely restricted diet.
- This is the last question.
- Yes.
- It might sound ridiculous.
- Okay.
Is it possible to do a transplant
using hair from the chest?
- It's possible.
- Really?
- Of course.
(Maximum possibility)
If the chest hair
looks like maesaengi,
- will the hair look the same?
- Yes, it will.
(You reap what you sow.
Maesaengi transplant)
- I thought you might be curious.
- I knew about that.
- Did you know that?
- If you get a transplant using it,
your hair will look the same.
Can you get a transplant using it?
Of course, he can.
His chest hair is a resource.
It's like my insurance.
- Gosh.
- It's a garden.
- Right.
- It's an urban garden.
(Urban garden)
Why don't you move your eyes,
nose, and mouth to your chest?
- That's a good idea.
- Yes.
Put your eyes, nose,
and mouth on your chest.
(Move the face
to where the hair is.)
(Hyun Moo sure is funny.)
Give me a moment.
I'll wipe it with alcohol first.
Yes.
(Fidgeting with her two hands)
She's never gotten a shot
on the scalp, so it'd be scary.
- Do you have a stuffed animal?
- Stay still.
- What?
- Never mind.
- It'll feel cool.
- Yes.
I'll give you the shot now.
It'll sting.
- Yes.
- Oh, my gosh.
I hate that sound.
I'll start it now.
(The needle pierces the scalp.)
Does it hurt? You're doing well.
- Does it feel okay?
- It didn't hurt.
Didn't it hurt?
I'm trying not to hurt you.
Does it hurt?
(The needle is nothing to her.)
(Calm)
(Frowning)
It stings a little,
but it'll be done in 30 seconds.
- Just 30 seconds. It'll be quick.
- Hold on.
- No.
- Do you want me to stop? No more?
It feels fine
on the top of the head.
- But it hurts on the sides.
- That's right.
- The areas with many nerve endings.
- It hurts a lot on the temples.
Yes. I know what it's like.
Does it feel okay?
Does it still hurt?
There were spots that hurt.
I think it'll hurt the most there.
Distract yourself.
(Looking back on the days
with thick hair)
It's almost done.
(I should endure it.)
You're in a lot of pain.
- I think your scalp is sensitive.
- Hold on.
It's almost done.
I know the side parts hurt more.
You need to get a shot here too.
(Trembling)
You did well.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I finally completed the task
I've put aside.
Many women...
experience hair loss.
I heard that even students
and young adults...
- are worried about it too.
- That's true.
I did a big task.
I was told it'd grow with treatment,
even if just once a month.
To take care of myself,
I got treatment at the clinic.
It feels so great.
You should take care of yourselves.
Thank you. I'll call to
make another appointment.
Thank you.
I want to scratch it.
I want to scratch it so badly.
(Grow as much as it is itchy.)
(Leaving the clinic in frustration)
It's been a long time.
It's so windy suddenly.
(Even the weather is troubling.)
Is she getting plastic surgery?
Is she really getting it this time?
- Is it a plastic surgery clinic?
- Is she going to eat something?
- Is she getting coffee?
- Isn't it a bookstore?
- It's a bookstore.
- It is.
It's been so long.
I started buying books
because of my mom.
My mom often sends books...
about the things
she wants to tell me.
When I was having a hard time,
she sent me two copies
of "Courage to be Disliked."
She sent me the book, "How to Lead."
Three identical books, to be exact.
- She probably wanted me to be wise.
- That's so sweet of her.
Later, when I talked to my mom,
I learned why she sent me books.
Since then,
just having those books...
comforts me a lot.
- I know what it's like.
- I like having them.
I didn't understand
why she kept sending books.
I thought she sent me kimchi,
but there was always one
under the kimchi container.
- Did she place books?
- Yes.
It was always a book about
what she wanted to tell me.
(Visiting a bookstore
to feel better about hair loss)
(Gently folded hands)
(Looking around sophisticatedly)
In a bookstore,
I become solemn just like her.
I know.
We need intellectual nourishment.
We've been using
smartphones too much.
- Excuse me.
- How can I help you?
Where can I find books
about caring for the mind?
Books about reducing stress...
and calming the mind.
Where can I find them?
She's looking for books
about caring for the mind.
You can find them over there.
- Are those bestsellers?
- Yes.
Thank you.
(Growing interest in bestsellers)
(Grabbing)
(Skimming the cover)
(Turning around with two books)
(Let's see.)
(Grabbing)
(Holding three books already)
(Picking up books)
(Touching)
You don't open the books at all.
I never open them.
Gosh.
There are many books about the mind.
There is a saying.
"The food I'm craving is..."
"what my body needs at the moment."
I think it applies to books too.
By seeing the cover and the vibe,
some books move my heart.
Some books catch my eye.
I bought those books.
I understand. You can read it
when it attracts you.
Exactly.
(Even looking at the cover,)
(I know what to buy.)
(Even touching the cover...)
- You pick books very quickly.
- Yes.
I can feel it
just by looking at the cover.
How could you pick
only by looking at the cover?
It's like finding a restaurant
just by looking at the storefront.
You don't even open it.
I don't open it.
(I know what to buy,
although you don't speak.)
(I can read...)
(what's in the books.)
(Fiery love for books)
I picked so many books.
Who would buy books like that?
We usually see who wrote the book.
Even if you don't read it,
do you at least check the preface?
No, not at all.
- You don't even read the jacket.
- I don't.
It's like choosing fruits
at a store.
Exactly.
You look closely
even when choosing fruits.
Some might think
it's a new semester.
A new semester?
(A new student who bought
many books for her major)
It's like buying textbooks
for her major.
I'm reading that one now.
I'm on page 18.
- You're all set.
- Okay.
Thank you. Have a good day.
Weren't you feeling good
at that time?
I felt amazing.
- You're most excited at that time.
- Yes.
- He's right.
- Once you get home,
you don't even want to look at them.
(Looking around)
(No more worries about hair loss)
(Feeling good after buying books
about caring for the mind)
- Hello.
- Hi.
How long will it take, sir?
- It'll take about 15 minutes.
- It's close.
- It seems very close.
- It's 2:50 p.m.
Yes.
I'm starving.
- You haven't eaten anything.
- She hasn't.
I haven't eaten anything.
That's unusual.
- Thank you. Have a good day.
- Thank you.
(Am I almost there?)
- It's on the way to my home.
- I see.
Where is she going?
It looks interesting.
(Ringing)
- Whose house is this?
- Where is she?
The door looks old-fashioned.
The door is opening.
- Hey.
- Who's that?
It's me.
Is it your new office?
She came by my office
out of the blue.
- You should visit him quickly.
- Why is that?
He's moving again soon.
- Again?
- No. I'm just saying...
- because he moves very often.
- He loves moving to a new place.
I'm already tired of that place.
It's your first time here.
It's my first time.
I once stopped by...
when your office was in Gangnam.
It's a nice place.
It's not much.
Gosh.
There are so many rooms.
I liked his office.
What made you come, though?
I was in Gangnam for something...
-Yes.
- since I have a day off today.
- Let's go upstairs.
- How do I go upstairs?
- Let's go upstairs this way.
- Upstairs?
- Go upstairs.
- Gosh.
I went to a plastic surgery clinic
in the morning.
(Coughing)
She came by
when I was feeling terrible.
I went to a hair loss clinic.
Do you have hair loss?
You told me the other day
after watching a video of me.
"Na Rae, you've lost a lot of hair."
Since he's an expert on hair loss,
- I wanted to talk with him.
- Okay.
Also, I've been through a lot
during that week,
- but he wasn't here.
- You're right. I wasn't here.
So, I went to see him.
But he was in terrible shape.
Was it right after
you returned to Korea?
- Yes.
- He was sick for about two weeks.
Oh, my! It looks amazing!
This is nice.
It's like a gallery.
- It also has a high ceiling.
- Yes.
- It looks nice with a high ceiling.
- It's great.
It's very spacious.
I also bought some books.
And I thought of you.
I was at the bookstore.
- Did you go to the bookstore?
- It was pretty close to here.
- It's close.
- So...
I'm surprised by how sweet he is.
- He's such a sweet guy.
- I can tell.
- It's giving me butterflies.
- He's sweet.
- What?
- Did he give you butterflies?
- No, that's not what I meant.
You should be careful
about what you say.
Why are you being shy?
"Did you go to the bookstore?"
The way he said it was so sweet.
That was because he was sick.
- It was because I was sick,
- If he weren't sick,
he would've said,
"Why did you come?"
I don't believe
you'll read those books.
I see,
that's the way he usually speaks.
(He was sweet because he was sick.)
That is...
(Na Rae gave him something.)
- What is it?
- It's 23.9 dollars. What is it?
(Na Rae stopped by a general store
next to the bookstore earlier.)
(She picked a keychain
to give to Kian84.)
The yellow one is pretty.
They make pretty extension sockets
these days.
- Extension sockets?
- Yes.
- It's a cute color, isn't it?
- Yes, it's pretty.
- I like this one.
- Extension sockets are useful.
- This is...
- I always carry that in my bag.
This is apparently a talisman
that helps you love.
And this is a talisman
for a peaceful life.
Also, wasn't something delivered?
A love talisman?
I got a call from the delivery man.
- I see.
- I wasn't expecting anything,
- so it was sudden...
- When will it arrive?
- Did you send it?
- Yes, I sent it.
You keep sending me gifts.
- You don't have to do that.
- No.
- It's...
- Did you send me a potted plant?
- I sent you a potted plant.
- A potted plant?
- She's always caring.
- Where did you put it?
- She takes good care of her people.
- You really didn't have to do it.
I couldn't visit you empty-handed
since you moved here recently.
You really didn't have to
send me a plant.
- Na Rae wouldn't visit anyone...
- You haven't even brought it in.
without a housewarming gift.
- Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
Do you think you can carry it?
I'm not feeling very well,
but I can carry it.
Really? Can you carry it...
- I don't think you can.
- I felt bad.
You can't seem to lift it.
Are you okay, Kian84?
- Go back in. It's okay.
- Are you really okay?
- Will you take it upstairs?
- Let's go.
Okay. Go on.
Maybe I shouldn't have sent it.
- He's sweet, right?
- That's because he's unwell.
You're welcome. Oh, gosh.
- I don't think you should thank me.
- It's because he feels weak.
He's so cool.
He carried the pot
despite his condition.
- I'll always feel unwell, Na Rae.
- Gosh, it's heavy.
This plant is easy to grow.
(Groaning)
- Are you all right?
- I'm exhausted.
- I wrote a card too.
- I have a chronic health problem.
I wrote a message for you.
Gosh.
Gosh, thank you.
- I'll read it later.
- Are you really grateful?
- He looks like an old man.
- It's because I'm not feeling well.
(I'm sorry that
I'm not feeling well.)
I really don't feel...
(Coughing)
- Oh, dear.
- Are you all right?
Yes.
That is an eternity plant.
- One that attracts money?
- That's right.
I'll do my best to keep it healthy
until I die.
Of course.
We had something between us
a very long time ago.
Right. That's a good memory.
- That was a long time ago.
- We were young then.
You two shared special feelings
when you were most beautiful.
- Exactly. When I had a lot of hair.
- Yes.
He kissed your head
covered with so much hair.
- Look at my hair. Look.
- I'm embarrassed.
Look how much hair I had then.
I thought he had kissed her
on the crown of the head.
- Right.
- He kissed on her hairline.
- That's why her hairline receded.
- You lost hair in that part.
- What is this?
- I have an M-shaped hairline now.
- That's where you lost hair.
- So he kissed there.
- On her hairline, I mean.
- It's this part of her head.
Let's stop watching
this old footage.
Isn't that too steamy?
Let's move on. Come on.
- She had dense hair then.
- I used to have dense hair.
That's when her genes were modified.
A virus infiltrated her scalp.
That's when she was exposed
to the hair loss beam.
(Dazed)
Have you eaten anything?
Order some food if you're hungry.
- Okay.
- I...
I'm not hungry, though.
- He doesn't look well.
- Right.
He's not himself.
It'd be weird if I ate alone.
- Then...
- Yes?
- If you order some food for me,
I'll bring it home.
- He looks like he's terminally ill.
- There's nothing I can eat.
- He was too sick to even eat.
- Right.
- But... Goodness. I'm upset.
- But I wanted...
to console you...
as you had been going through
a hard time.
That's touching.
(That's because he was sick.)
I hope I won't get well.
No, that's not what I mean.
Okay.
- Goodness gracious.
- Oh, dear.
- Be careful not to catch my cold.
- Don't worry. I'll be fine.
He needs to get an IV right now.
What would you like to eat?
What do you want to bring home?
I recommend
spicy stir-fried tofu pork.
- Spicy stir-fried tofu pork?
- It's convenient to carry.
- For me?
- Spicy stir-fried tofu pork.
Spicy stir-fried tofu pork
sounds delicious.
- I think it'll be good for you.
- I'll have that.
- You can carry it easily.
- I need some protein too.
- Right.
- I'll order it.
So I went to a hair loss clinic.
Right. Let me see.
(Let me see.)
- Oh, please.
- I lost hair here...
- It's not so bad.
- Seriously.
This part...
- Stop getting heart flutters.
- Exactly.
We did all that a long time ago.
We passed that stage.
There are some
heart-fluttering moments,
- which is unexpected.
- If he were not unwell,
he would've teasingly said,
"You lost so much hair."
(He would've said,
"You lost so much hair.")
"Your life is over."
I wouldn't say those things.
- I lost a lot of hair...
- No, you...
No.
I lost a lot of hair in this part.
Usually, men lose hair in this part.
Why did you lose hair in this part?
(Usually,
men lose hair in this part.)
The hairline recedes on the sides
like this.
- Like samurai's hair.
- It looks bald on the sides.
- I mean... Show me.
- I guess I'm really becoming a man.
Take a look.
Look.
Usually, women lose hair...
- on the top of the head.
- No.
(Tousling her hair)
- But you lost hair here.
- That's right.
This is the male pattern
of hair loss.
I don't know.
I guess I've become a hermaphrodite.
But I don't know much...
(But I don't know much about
female hair loss.)
about female hair loss.
I know a lot about male hair loss.
I think it's male hair loss.
The doctor prescribed medications
for me.
You lost hair too.
I know you take medications.
I've been taking medications.
And I had a hair transplant
on my sides.
- You had a hair transplant?
- You had?
- Yes, in this part.
- I had a hair transplant.
- I did it quite a long time ago.
- Yes, in this part.
- Here.
- It's really dense.
What did you remove here?
What is this? What did you remove?
- A rat's nipple.
- A rat's nipple?
- Yes.
You got a rat's nipple on your face?
There was a wart here.
A nipple on the face?
Is that a real thing?
I didn't have a nipple on my face.
I got rat's nipples on my neck.
- You got rat's nipples?
- Yes.
Why did you get them on your neck?
How would I know?
Why would you get rat's nipples
on your neck?
I had 300 of them removed.
- I was a little surprised.
- It's caused by stress.
You lost hair...
and got rat's nipples.
What's going on with you?
It's because
I got stressed out so much.
Goodness.
(Goodness)
I'm sorry that
I haven't been of any help to you.
- That's not true.
- I haven't been reliable either.
- Give me a break.
- What?
(He's being sweet again.)
- Why...
- What...
- What's the matter with you, Joy?
- Is he sweet again?
- What's the matter?
- I see that he's a sweet guy.
- He's a sweet guy.
- Hold on.
His pink shirt makes him look sweet,
to begin with.
He's been wearing that shirt
for over ten years.
- I always...
- I'll wear it every day.
I always try to
see only good things.
I can feel my blood flowing well.
(The compliment therapy helps you
improve your health.)
I'm sorry that
I haven't been of any help to you.
- That's not true.
- I haven't been reliable either.
I know how busy you've been.
You went overseas and everything.
- I don't go out often lately.
- Why?
I don't know.
I feel too lazy to meet people.
I've changed.
I work out at the gym
and then go home.
Then what do you do at home?
I don't know. My personality
keeps changing. I stay home alone.
- You used to...
- He's becoming like me.
- It's coming soon.
- Right.
Gosh, this is killing me.
Did you take medicine?
I'll go to the hospital for an IV.
I wanted to chat with you for long
since it had been a while.
- Oh, dear.
- I know.
- What? I'll get it.
- Could it be our food?
Stay seated. I'll get it.
- Don't come out.
- No. I'll go.
I felt so bad
watching him like that.
You really should go see a doctor.
It seems very serious.
I've been sick for four days.
But the weather became
a little warmer, so I'll be fine.
Take one cold soybean soup.
You take it home.
- Thank you for this, Na Rae.
- No problem.
- I should've paid for the food.
- Don't worry about it.
You should've said that
before I paid.
He still says that
after someone else pays for food.
He says that every time.
That will never change.
(Embarrassed)
I was the one
who asked you to see me.
It looks delicious.
They make good food.
- That's a lot of food.
- It looks good.
The cold soybean soup
was really tasty.
- Cold soybean soup?
- Yes.
- It looks good.
- You haven't eaten until now?
- Food?
- Yes.
I know I should eat something,
but... Oh, it looks tasty.
- He hadn't eaten anything.
- You should eat to take medicine.
I'll put it here.
Take some more.
You will eat this too, right?
Can you give me some broth?
- No, you have this one.
- You want this? It's too little.
No, it's enough for me.
Hot soup is the best
when you're sick.
You see... You know what?
You have a weakened immune system
caused by aging.
- These days...
- That's caused by aging.
Right. I get sick often.
- They sound like an old couple.
- Gosh. I don't know.
(Sad)
- Eat the egg too.
- Okay.
- Eat even a little.
- He was too sick to get angry,
- which made me upset.
- Exactly.
(I should eat it all
since Na Rae bought it for me.)
(Relieved)
You don't take supplements, do you?
- Health supplements?
- Yes.
I heard taking too many of them
could harm the liver,
so I don't take many.
How about you take one
for liver health?
That's how it goes.
- Taking hair loss supplements...
- Yes?
- weakens sexual function.
- I see.
So you take a supplement
to improve it as well.
- Okay.
- And taking those supplements...
weakens your liver, so you start
taking a supplement for your liver.
- Right.
- That's how...
the number of supplements you take
increases.
After taking supplements
in the morning, I feel full.
- Oh, my.
- Taking many of them is not good.
- Right.
- It makes you nauseous.
- That's right.
- Oh, right.
- Eat this too.
- Okay. Will do.
I should take fewer supplements.
Yes.
(After looking after Kian84,
she finally has her 1st bite.)
- Eat some rice too.
- Okay.
- Was that your first meal?
- Yes.
My gosh. That's hard to believe.
I had my first meal at 5 p.m.
Gosh. Getting older is so annoying.
I even lack energy now.
I think it's really...
I mean, I think I should...
(I think I should...)
Gosh. Why am I so incompetent?
(Gosh. Why am I so incompetent?)
- Hey.
- I can't be of any help.
(I can't be of any help.)
- What are you talking about?
- I...
Hearing that made me so sad.
I rely so much on you.
I called you
whenever I had a hard time.
It's not that we go to see you,
expecting you to give us an answer.
Exactly.
Suddenly, I felt so sad.
I ask for his advice
when I have a hard time.
Whenever I consult with him,
he tries his best to
help me resolve the issue.
But listening to me alone helps me.
So when he said he wasn't reliable,
I felt apologetic toward him.
- Being there for her is helpful.
- Right.
Many things happened
while you were gone.
I found out that it was missing
on Monday.
- Right.
- And...
Guess how far the fake news took it.
Tell me.
- Well...
- Some said that Do Yeon stole it.
There was a rumor that
Jang Do Yeon didn't do it alone,
but with Han Hye Jin.
Those two tall ladies...
That article drives me crazy.
Fake news on the Internet
is so mean.
- Isn't it so mean?
- Yes.
Apparently, my mom stole my bag
because of her debt.
- It's absurd.
- I see.
- You must've been stressed a lot.
- They said your mom stole it?
Yes.
I felt guilty when I was the victim.
(I felt guilty
when I was the victim.)
You know how bad things happen
at the same time, right?
Is some part of the door
of your house made of glass?
Do you have a mirror near the door?
- No.
- No?
- You see, I...
- Maybe the location is the problem.
No, I was told that
the location was good for me.
I even have a moon jar
in front of the entrance.
I hear a moon jar brings good luck.
- That's a superstitious approach.
- And money too.
- Money and good luck.
- I did everything to bring them in.
- That's why the thief came in too.
- Something brought in a thief.
So that's what happened.
Stop doing such things.
Tell them not to bring in anything.
- Maybe, you put too many of them.
- Is that the case?
You put too much superstitious stuff,
which brought ghosts and all.
(Kian84's way of sympathizing:
Doing his best to find a reason)
- They shouldn't bring bad things.
- Right.
I'm sure no more thieves
will break into your house.
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
- On top of the walls...
- Yes.
It's an old-fashioned way
of decorating a house.
Buy 100 boxes of soju
and break all the bottles.
You've seen it, right?
Broken glass...
- on top of the walls.
- I've seen it.
It looks scary, you know.
- I should strengthen home security.
- It keeps anyone from coming in.
How about a trap?
You could set up a trap for people.
(He's happy that
he came up with a solution.)
Don't give up yet.
You haven't given up.
You're doing what you can
to improve your health.
You had treatment for hair loss...
and had nipples removed.
You had some nipples removed.
- They're rat's nipples.
- Right. Rat's nipples.
I mean, if you gave up
and did not take care of them,
letting all your hair fall out...
- I can't let that happen.
- If you have like 300 nipples...
on your body...
You have to take care of them.
- Right. I can't let that happen.
- Right.
(You're doing great.
It's too soon to give up.)
But you know, they say that
science has advanced greatly.
I think there will be a solution
for hair loss soon.
The person who achieves that
deserves a Nobel Prize.
- Oh, dear.
- Oh, gosh.
- It won't happen soon.
- You're wrong. It will happen soon.
- Go to the hospital now.
- I'll take this home.
Na Rae, don't do it. I'll clean up.
No, I'll do it.
I'll do it. Don't clean up.
- Put this... Okay.
- I'll put this in here.
- Here.
- Kian84. No, not there.
- Oh, gosh.
- I enjoyed the food.
(Home Alone)
It's time to meet the star
of Rainbow Live.
After the preview aired,
so many people got excited...
to see him on our show.
- I'm a huge fan, really.
- Right.
He's a really popular star.
"Nice!" Brother Woo Il.
Please welcome Im Woo Il!
- Welcome.
- Okay.
- "Nice!"
- Woo Il came on Home Alone!
Nice!
- Nice!
- Great.
- That was good.
- Hello.
Stand in the center.
I see that you pronounce
the "I" of "nice..."
for longer than you did before.
I wanted to enjoy the moment
for longer.
I wanted to get more screen time.
(It was all part of my plan.)
(With his sense of humor
he developed over time,)
(he makes great jokes
on every show he's on.)
(His realistic, funny acting...)
(cracks everyone up.)
(Now, even in front of his senior
of many years...)
(his jokes always bring laughter.)
(From YouTube videos to TV shows)
Look at the number of views
of his videos.
(- "Brother Woo Il is funny."
- "Brother Woo Il is hilarious.")
(Brother Woo Il is awesome.)
(At
the 2024 MBC Entertainment Awards,)
(he won the Popularity Award.)
(The natural-born comedian proved
his awesome sense of humor.)
(Comedian Im Woo Il)
- Say hello to the viewers.
- Okay.
Hello. I act as my alter ego,
Brother Woo Il, in my videos.
- I'm Comedian Im Woo Il.
- Yes!
How do you feel,
now that you're here?
I've been enjoying
watching this show.
So I find it hard to believe...
that I am on this show.
When I heard about his appearance
in this show,
since he was unknown
as a comedian for a long time...
- just as I was, I felt so...
- Right.
- I was so happy for him, and...
As for Na Rae who's my senior,
she passed her test...
in her early 20s,
which is considered very young.
- She took an elite path.
- What about you?
I made my debut at a very late age.
Didn't you get calls...
- from other comedians?
- About your appearance in the show?
As you must know, Na Rae,
most of them said,
"It's time for you to retire."
They basically cursed you.
Someone said this.
"Woo Il, climb up even higher..."
"so that it's more painful
when you fall."
I heard many things like that.
Saying such things
means that those comedians...
- acknowledged his success.
- That he's become popular.
- They approved his success.
- They must adore Woo Il.
- I'm excited to see his video.
- I'm so excited.
(One and Only Woo Il, the Pioneer)
(A room filled with sunlight)
The room is well-lit.
(There's someone
who likes pretty hair ties...)
Look at those hair ties.
- Why is his hair short? Oh, I see.
- He looks elegant from behind.
His hair is tied.
(He's sleeping
with his hair tied elegantly.)
(Wiggling)
(He tosses restlessly
and then turns around.)
It feels weird to watch myself.
Hello.
I've been living alone
for eight years.
I'm Comedian Im Woo Il.
I moved out of my parents' house
in my early 20s,
- so it's been over 20 years.
- Right.
But I shared a house
with other people at first.
- There's no choice.
- When I was an aspiring comedian,
I lived with some friends
who shared the same dream.
After I debuted, I kept living
with my fellow comedians.
It's been eight years
since I started living alone.
You know that, right?
Comedians have no choice...
but to share a house with others.
It's reasonable and practical...
- if you think about the rent...
- To save money.
and finding a place
to have a meeting...
- as we often pull an all-nighter.
- That's right.
After I moved out
of my parents' house,
I lived with someone else...
- for about four years.
- Whom did you live with?
At first,
I lived with Jang Hyo In...
- who was in the 22nd batch.
- Yes.
After that,
I lived with Jang Do Yeon.
Oh, you lived with Do Yeon
for a long time.
(Rubbing)
(Fumbling)
- Is that his phone?
- Oh, his phone.
- You should check your phone.
- Of course.
(He checks his phone
as soon as he wakes up.)
(Gazing)
He's looking at the phone, right?
It's as if there were gravity
that affected his face.
(He couldn't open his eyes fully
because of gravity?)
(I should stop looking at my phone
and get up now.)
He reminds me of the drama
"The Slave Hunters."
Look at his hair.
(He tied his hair in a topknot
like the traditional hairstyle.)
- A topknot is really comfortable.
- For those with long hair.
Yes, that's right.
- Right.
- I always do a topknot at home.
- What's that behind him?
- What's that? Gosh.
- What is that?
- My gosh.
(What is the photo behind Woo Il?)
- What is that?
- Who are they?
- That's...
- Tell us the truth.
- What is it?
- I mean...
- We'll blur the photo if you want.
- Are you a member of SHINHWA?
What is this?
- What...
- We'd been a team...
- since we were aspiring comedians.
- Yes.
We promised to take a nude photo
when we became comedians.
We became comedians
and took some nude photos.
I hung the mildest photo
among all our nude photos.
(He passes the photo
that made his fan laugh.)
(He came to the kitchen
to drink some water.)
(Gulping down)
(He drinks water from the bottle.)
(Woo Il woke up his mind
with morning water.)
(Spacious)
(Let me show you
around Woo Il's house.)
It's very spacious.
- His house is so nice.
- It has a nice view.
- You can see the Han River?
- That's right.
He's become successful.
I can see the buildings in Yeouido.
(There's another place
right behind the living room.)
(The walk-in closet and bathroom)
Oh, nice. That's impressive.
- It's tidy.
- Indeed.
Since I live alone,
it's easy to keep the house clean.
He has more hair ties
than most women do.
My goodness.
Woo Il worked so hard to save money,
- and he became so successful.
- That's right.
Comedienne Oh Na Mi rented
this house...
to use as her marital house...
- after getting married.
- Oh, really?
Her contract was finished
around the time mine was too.
So she talked to the landlord,
and I moved to this house.
Many comedians do that.
I rented the house
Kim Ji Min lived in...
- as she moved out.
- Right.
- Comedians often do this.
- I see.
But we only move into the houses
of successful ones.
- Not houses of unsuccessful ones.
- The opposite case...
- We don't...
- We don't even talk about them.
And those people don't recommend
their houses either?
- Absolutely not.
- Never. They know.
Na Mi became successful.
She got married
while living in this house.
The house has positive energy.
- It's the best energy for him.
- It's a house of love.
As Na Mi moved out,
she left behind her refrigerator,
Oh, I see.
the dining table,
and some other things.
She left behind good-quality
furniture and appliances.
And an acquaintance of mine
bought me the sofa and the bed,
- whom I'm grateful for.
- Oh, my.
A friend of mine who's a businessman
bought the television for me.
- A friend who's a businessman?
- As for the washing machine,
Yu Jae Seok bought it for me.
I received the air conditioner
from a comedian from SBS,
- My goodness.
- the induction from Cho Jin Se,
- Oh, Jin Se?
- and the food waste composter...
- from Kim Ki Ri.
- My gosh.
And I received the bidet
from Kim Won Hun.
I received the microwave oven
from Kim Hyun Ki.
- I received all of those.
- I received the vacuum cleaner...
from my junior, Lee Seung Hwan.
When I moved into this house,
everyone around me...
seemed to be proud of me.
- It means they're rooting for him.
- Yes.
Woo Il must've been good
to people around him.
Exactly.
We saw one another
going through hard times,
so I guess they felt
like a proud dad.
Many of my fellow comedians
offered...
a housewarming gift, asking me
what I needed in the new house.
- That proves you've been good.
- It's because you've been good.
The house I previously lived in...
I lived in Singil-dong before
moving into this neighborhood.
My old house was very close
to Na Rae's house.
- It was only 300m away from hers.
- That's right.
- Yes, it was.
- So I ran into her quite often.
Before she became popular...
when she was struggling
just like I was.
- You were really struggling.
- Right.
I worked hard to save up money.
I rented this house
with that money and a loan.
- You made the right decision.
- Yes.
(Woo Il is happy
in his dream house.)
(He lies down on the sofa.)
(Comfortable)
(He clicks a news article.)
He's reading a news article.
I read the news in the morning.
(This time,
he presses the remote control.)
(He turns on the news.)
You're very interested in the news.
I keep the news on.
I'm 100 percent certain
that you'll fall back asleep.
(Scratching)
(Sprawled out on the sofa,
he wriggles his feet.)
(Yawning)
(Scratching)
I didn't know that
I scratched my body a lot.
Your body becomes dry
when you grow old.
- Your body is dry.
- My body is dry.
(He scratches his back as well.)
My goodness.
(He sends his hand
as far back as possible.)
- I scratch myself.
- Why don't you take a shower?
It'll be nice if you had someone
to scratch your back.
That's why I hate living alone.
It must be refreshing.
(Farting)
Will that be revealed as well?
My goodness.
What kind of a question is that?
We can't hide it for you.
(His eyes become bigger.)
(Scratching)
- Oh, yes.
- I scratch myself a lot.
His armpit is soft.
- You have a lot of hair.
- Yes.
- I have a lot of hair.
Today's video will make me dizzy.
His armpit is soft.
- It's so relatable and nice.
- My goodness.
(Thank you.)
(The relatable man,
Woo Il, gets up.)
(He trudges over to the kitchen.)
I guess he'll eat something.
(He opens the fridge.)
What's there?
(The fridge is full of food.)
(There are burger...)
(and pickled radish
that comes with fried chicken.)
Unfinished iced Americano.
How are there cups of coffee?
(He takes out coffee
from the fridge.)
(He opens the lid.)
If there are snacks...
in the waiting room,
I ask this to the writers.
"May I take the snacks?"
They say, "Go right ahead."
- Then I bring them.
- The snacks.
- There they are.
- My goodness.
(He brings and stores
the leftover snacks.)
If there are gimbap...
and leftovers, I take them.
If I think I can eat them
1 or 2 days after,
I bring them home.
When I go to a filming set,
they give me coffee.
There's a variety of brands...
because they're
from different places.
I store them in the fridge...
and drink them when I want.
- I see.
- Each day, I pick one...
- depending on my mood.
- "I want this brand today."
"I want this brand today."
If I want bitter coffee,
I pick Starbucks.
- There are such rules.
- You're quite frugal.
One time, I was on a set,
and a box of packed lunch remained.
I brought the entire box home
and froze it.
(Moved)
- He's very frugal.
- I can see that.
Even among comedians, he's frugal.
- He has always been frugal.
- That was why...
everyone was happy for his success.
(He takes out ice from the freezer.)
Ice melts...
- no matter what I do.
- It can't be helped.
(He picks up the ice cubes
and adds it to the coffee.)
(Before drinking coffee,
he takes out his retainer.)
You're getting your teeth
straightened.
I'm getting my teeth straightened.
(He swirls the coffee
with his wrist.)
When you add ice, it becomes new.
- Of course. It becomes new.
- It's totally new.
(Bumping)
You didn't decide on
the interior design.
- No.
- That's right.
I've bumped into it so many times...
that I'm unfazed when it happens.
(He resurrected the iced Americano
with ice in a frugal manner.)
(Iced coffee is the best
in the morning.)
(He passes the kitchen light
that's still swinging.)
(He picks up a paper bag.)
- Recycling?
- No.
- It's a paper bag.
- What is he doing?
- It's a pen.
- Yes.
(He sits on the floor.)
What is it? He'll cut his nails.
I see.
- Newspapers are rare these days,
- Right.
so I use a paper bag.
There's something fascinating
about that paper bag.
I've used it for about five years.
- What did you say?
- That paper bag.
- What?
- Even in the previous house,
I only used that paper bag.
So I packed it on purpose
when I moved into the new house.
- Why do you like it so much?
- Seriously.
- Just because.
- Is it to your liking?
I grew fond of it.
- That's right.
- "I cut my toenails on this."
Yes. The soles of my feet...
- and the shopping bag...
- I see.
- made physical contact.
- You got used to the closeness.
There has been some physical contact
over the course of five years.
To you, that's Wilson.
- That's right.
- It's something like that.
(He uses his pet paper bag
as a rug.)
(He cuts his toenails carefully.)
Gosh, your toenails are strong.
I thought
they were a falcon's claws.
It sounds like a bone is breaking.
His toenails must be thick.
Why do I feel like I'm watching
a man from the Joseon Dynasty?
No matter the part of the world...
and the time period,
we'll be able to find
someone with his face.
- That's right.
- Yes.
So he can go to the Joseon Dynasty.
We can find that face
in South America as well.
- He can go to Machu Picchu.
- Yes.
He can go
to the Mausoleum of Qin Shi Huang.
We can find that face
in Mongolia as well.
- New Zealand too.
- New Zealand.
The Maori people.
I saw that face in Nepal too.
We can find that face in Nepal too.
I saw that face in the Himalayas.
- He can go to any country.
- That's right.
- He's a global character.
- Yes.
(He collects the cut toenails.)
(Then the universal man
resumes cutting his toenails.)
(Careful touches)
- His eyes are very clear.
- He has cow's eyes.
(Spotting the target)
(He found a big piece of dirt
under his toenail.)
Will he show that as well?
During my ten years on Home Alone,
it's my first time seeing someone
dig up toenail dirt.
(He cleaned his toenails
thoroughly.)
(This time, he takes out
a nail clipper for fingernails.)
You use different nail clippers
for fingernails and toenails.
- That's right.
- I see.
(He focuses on the task
for a while.)
(He cuts the fingernails cleanly.)
(Staring)
I need to collect the nails
that flew off.
- That's right.
- They run away.
(He picks them up cleanly.)
(He cleans up after himself.)
(Emptying)
He took good care of the paper bag.
I put it there...
and use it the next time.
He's frugal.
There are other shopping bags,
- but I use that only.
- I see.
(He puts the nail clipper back
in its place.)
- Still... Yes.
- He's clean.
- Yes.
- I wash my feet...
- after I cut my toenails.
- You need to clean the ends.
- He's very clean.
- You take good care...
of your hands and feet.
It's my first time staring at
someone's feet for so long.
My hair is long too.
People like me
make extra effort to be clean.
- I see.
- Yes.
(Bringing over)
Isn't that from a convenience store?
It's the only item I bought myself.
- I didn't know that they sold it.
- Yes.
It's very convenient
to fold and unfold.
I can see that.
(Rummaging the fridge)
(He stored food in the pot.)
It's a leftover.
That's right.
- Add more water.
- Yes.
It's soft tofu stew.
My junior brought it.
People call me
when there's leftover food.
Hold on.
Did your junior eat first
and give you the leftover?
They go, "I ordered something,
and there's a lot of leftover food."
Then I go, "Is that so? Okay."
And I go and pick it up.
"Send me a photo."
Then they send me a photo.
I need to check the food.
"Hey, that's Grade A."
(If it's Grade A,
he sets off right away.)
I once went...
to Kang Yu Mi's neighborhood,
Yongsan,
in order to receive free food.
- Hold on.
- Use the gas money to buy food.
- Listen.
There was so much frozen food.
Yu Mi took a photo
and posted it on the group chatroom.
What's this, a secondhand item?
Why do you guys take photos?
As soon as I saw that,
I hit the road.
Frozen food is nice.
- He needed to go.
- Yes.
I always think of
the opportunity cost.
(He's thorough
when it comes to gain and loss.)
(Woo Il prepares a frugal meal.)
If I offer some side dishes,
would you take them?
- Of course.
- Na Rae has many side dishes.
Of course.
(Breaking an egg)
(One more)
(He adds the eggs
to the boiling stew.)
Did you buy the eggs?
- Of course.
- Yes, I did.
I don't go to a chicken farm
for free eggs.
(He takes out a small portion
of the young radish kimchi.)
It's from my mom.
It's from your mom. Thank goodness.
(Rummaging)
(From the freezer,
he takes something out.)
What's that?
- Fried chicken.
- Potato?
- It was in the freezer.
- Fried chicken is nice.
I froze the leftovers
in the freezer.
He's the upgraded version of Kian84.
(While the frozen fried chicken
becomes warm again)
- What's that?
- Pickled radish.
- It comes with fried chicken.
(He discards the water
from the pickled radish.)
(He even retrieves
the chicken sauce he saved.)
(To the hot instant rice)
Dried laver.
It'll be tasty.
I see.
- You use the ingredients you have.
- That's right.
I have delicious meals.
It does look delicious.
- It's practically new.
- Yes.
(Scraping)
I added two eggs.
- My goodness.
- He's so frugal.
(He plates the fried chicken
that became warm again.)
My goodness.
- That table is nice.
- Yes.
- It was a good idea.
- It's like a tent bar.
He eats good meals.
Yes.
Today, I'll eat the leftover
meal-kit soft tofu stew...
I got from my junior yesterday.
I'll also eat fried chicken
that's less than a week old.
Fried chicken,
pizza, and tteokbokki.
As for those three dishes,
I find them a bit more delicious...
when they've been in the fridge.
- Does it age the food?
- Yes, I guess.
It takes on a specific taste.
It becomes chewy.
- It's like that.
- There's the fridge smell.
When protein comes into contact
with heat many times,
it coagulates...
and becomes very hard.
- It can smell too.
- Yes.
Do you study microorganisms?
- No.
- I see.
I'm 45 years old.
I'm still alive, right?
(Thank goodness.)
When I receive a medical checkup,
my health is fine.
I never said that
you were in poor health.
- I don't even have a single polyp.
- It's a lie...
- if you say that it's tastier.
- It can't be tastier.
He wants you to eat tastier food.
You freeze food and eat it later
because you don't want to waste it.
Seriously.
(Woo Il's frugal meal...)
(consists of food he froze earlier.)
I didn't know that I...
- So that's how I eat.
- That's right.
His mouth moves freely.
I look a bit like a camel.
I don't know which time period
this video is from.
I'm certain that he time-traveled.
(He transcends time, space,
and ecosystems...)
(and faces
the thawed fried chicken.)
The food is modern.
It's fried chicken.
(Eating)
(As he soaks up the warm sunlight,)
(he enjoys his feast
in a relaxed way.)
(He cleanses his palate
with pickled radish.)
(Chewing)
(I'm chewing like this.)
(The food at home tastes good.)
Still, it's a nutritious meal.
- There's protein.
- He can see the Han River.
- It's nice.
- Yes.
- You don't leave food behind.
- No.
I love mixing rice
with the soft tofu stew in the end.
- That's it.
- Yes.
I want to give him some side dishes.
(He eats with gusto.)
You really don't waste food.
All done.
(He emptied the bowls.)
That's right.
You shouldn't leave food behind.
- That's right.
- It's so nice.
I hate seeing leftover food.
It stresses me out,
so I end up bringing it home.
When I worked as a comedian
in the past,
- I wasn't well-off.
- That's right.
A meal costs 7 to 8 dollars.
When there are 2 people,
it costs 15 dollars...
to 20 dollars.
But if I bring leftover food...
and make two meals out of it,
- it saves me 30 dollars.
- That's right.
I saved a lot of money on food
that way.
(It was a nice meal.)
(He rinses the empty bowls.)
(He puts away the table right away.)
(Heave-ho)
(Cracking)
(What is he doing?)
You use dental floss.
I use it too.
You take good care of your health.
You keep your hands and feet
clean...
and use dental floss.
I heard that it was nice to floss
even if drew blood.
You have to floss.
(He flosses the nooks and crannies.)
(He keeps his mouth clean.)
He's fast.
Once you get used to it,
you can floss fast.
I know which spots...
- to floss.
- That's right.
(He cleans each crack
between the teeth with care.)
There won't be anything
under his toenails...
and between his teeth.
You're crazy about
cleaning the cracks.
(I feel refreshed.)
(He rinses his retainer...)
(and puts it back on.)
(He's done cleaning his mouth
after a meal.)
(Why is he entering the room?)
(Grabbing)
(Whirring)
(Now that my mouth is clean,
shall I vacuum the house?)
(Sticking in)
Brother Woo Il is neat.
That's right.
My hair falls out a lot.
- That's right.
It can't be helped
if you have long hair.
(He's a neat man who cares about
the cleanliness of the house.)
(As soon as he finishes vacuuming,)
(he cleans the filter.)
He doesn't think it's too much work.
It's his hair.
(Pulling)
- That's right. It's annoying...
- That's right.
- when your hair gets stuck.
Pulling out the hair
is a bigger chore...
than vacuuming the house.
(It's hard to pull out the hair.)
My hair is always on the floor.
When I vacuum the floor,
my hair gets coiled
on the sides of the vacuum cleaner.
When their hair falls on the floor,
women clean it...
with a lint roller.
I didn't understand why
they did it so diligently.
(He understands it now.)
You must relate to such problems.
There's this issue too.
When women with long hair
stand before an air conditioner,
they pull up their hair like this.
(They slap the back of their necks.)
I didn't get it.
"It's the forehead
that gets sweaty."
"Why do they pull up their hair
and slap the back of their necks?"
But I found myself doing this.
(He began slapping
the back of his neck.)
I do this.
- The back of the neck is blocked.
- It gets sweaty.
- In summer,
- That part gets hot.
I enjoyed the wind like this
back in the day.
- Now, I pull up my hair.
- The back of your neck gets hot.
This part gets sweaty.
It's suffocating when your hair
is pressed against the pillow.
- That's why...
- Up.
you sweep your hair up.
Otherwise, it'll feel bad...
- against your skin.
- Yes. It's inconvenient.
(People with long hair
have many difficulties.)
(He finishes getting rid
of the hair...)
(that was stuck
on the vacuum cleaner.)
(Grabbing)
What's that?
It's a spray mop.
(He opens the water container
of the spray mop.)
(He grabs soju from the fridge.)
Soju?
Do you add soju?
I mix leftover soju
and some water...
- to mop the floor.
- What?
- It works as a disinfectant.
- That's right.
We haven't seen a single new item.
(He's a frugal man.)
(Mopping)
(Spraying)
(He uses the leftover soju
to disinfect the floor.)
Doesn't it get sticky?
Since it's alcohol, it evaporates.
- So the floor becomes cleaner.
- Is that so?
- Doesn't it contain a lot of sugar?
- I know.
- Does soju contain sugar?
- That's why it's sweet.
Soju is sweet.
Did you think it was the alcohol?
- When you're old...
- It tastes sweet when you're happy.
- No.
- Really?
- It contains sugar.
- It contains a lot of sweeteners.
I should check it out
when I go home today.
Doesn't the floor become sticky?
- No, it doesn't.
- Really?
- It doesn't become sticky.
- In that case...
(Spraying)
(He sprays the leftover soju...)
(to mop the floor thoroughly.)
(I'm exhausted.)
(Despite being exhausted,
he puts away the tool right away.)
In the previous house,
I didn't clean so diligently.
But it's my first time living...
- in a house like this.
- It's your own place.
- Right. That is what happens.
- Right.
(He heads somewhere
after cleaning the house.)
- I look very busy.
- Right.
- You look busy.
- You keep doing something.
- Gosh, hold on!
- Gosh! That surprised me.
- I thought it was a girl.
- I thought it was a friend of mine.
(It's time to wash up
after cleaning the house.)
(Applying shampoo)
- So that is how you wash your hair.
- Right.
You do that when you have long hair.
There's a lot of work
when you have long hair.
(He even diligently applies
the hair treatment.)
He's applying the hair treatment.
I really didn't understand it
at first. Hair rinse?
Shampoo replaced soap.
But on top of that,
hair rinse and hair treatment
was created?
I believed it to be marketing.
They were divided up too much.
I was determined not to fall for it.
I just used shampoo,
but because so much of my hair
fell out,
I used hair treatment.
That was when I realized
that there was a reason...
the researchers came up
with all of these things.
The hair treatment
also made my hair smell nice.
My hair smells really nice.
(My hair smells really nice.)
(He made his hair feel and smell
nice with the hair treatment.)
(Woo Il comes out
after a refreshing shower.)
(Shaking)
Drying the hair
must be a lot of work.
Even drying short hair feels like...
- a lot of work.
- Right.
(Squeezing out the hair essence)
- Hair essence.
- Gosh.
Why are you doing that
over the toilet?
Because my hair falls out.
It's better to have it...
- on the floor over there.
- That's possible.
- I can just clean that spot.
- Right.
(He still can't lift up his head
because of his long hair.)
(I should dry it quickly.)
When will you finish
drying up your hair?
Gosh, that will take ages.
(My hair smells really nice.)
(Shaking)
(The scent of the shampoo
can be felt as he shakes his hair.)
(As he shakes his hair wildly...)
- He's good at drying his hair.
- That's how it has to be done.
(Shaking)
What is he doing?
(Hitting)
He must feel dizzy.
He looks like a rocker.
(Is that so?)
Look at how silky his hair is. Gosh.
(Come at me, wind!)
It's Park Wan Kyu.
(His hair flies freely
in the strong wind.)
Look at how much hair he has.
- You don't have hair loss, right?
- I don't have hair loss.
(I am a man
who doesn't have hair loss.)
I heard that long hair
represents a true man.
(There you go, my babies.)
(Patting intensely...)
(and heading to the climax)
He looks like
a professional wrestler.
(Shaking his head for the finish)
(Swaying)
(He uses all his might
to take care of his hair.)
(Grabbing)
(He pours out the skin toner.)
(Applying on his face
after rubbing it with both hands)
He likes doing things tough.
- It had to be absorbed by my skin.
- Right.
(Smacking for it to be absorbed)
(His face turns red
from his wild touches.)
(The intense toner session ends.)
(He smacks himself
with lotion this time.)
He has the hands of an expert.
I smack my face a lot.
(Skin management
by smacking himself)
His hands are so fast.
(Hitting myself is the best way
to get it absorbed.)
(He applies sunscreen this time.)
I've been appearing in
quite a lot of shows these days.
People might see me and think,
"How is he on TV like that?"
I have the thought of
wanting to avoid that.
That's great.
I might not become handsome,
but I might look likable
if I have good skin.
You're slapping yourself
around 500 times.
- He takes great care of himself.
- Right. He uses them separately.
I used three of them that day.
I normally don't buy skin products.
I place and use the products
that I get as gifts.
When I run out with 1 of them,
I just use 2 products.
- I just use 1 if I have 1 left.
- Then you get another gift.
Right.
I use it when I get another gift.
I might just use the moisture cream.
The gifts you get
might not suit your skin type.
I have to make my skin adjust to it.
- Men don't care about that.
- Right.
I can't throw away
the gifts that I get.
I use everything I can
after reading the instructions.
He has great skin.
My gosh.
He uses that too.
(The item
that will complete his beauty)
When I use that
right before I leave the house,
it adds volume to my hair.
It makes my hair last longer.
There are reasons
to everything you do.
(He washes his hands
that have worked hard cleanly.)
(After taking care of himself,)
(he heads to the dressing room.)
(Let's see.)
(Opening)
(He takes out a white T-shirt
as he seems to be leaving.)
(Taking off)
(Struggling)
- Gosh, that hair roller.
- The hair roller.
That gets in the way.
It stresses me out so much.
You should've used it
after getting dressed.
But it has to be used
before the hair dries up.
- Really?
Look at that. Look at the hair
sticking to his face.
Right.
(Hair sticking)
He became hot after taking a shower.
(Sweating after taking a shower
and using the dryer)
(He quickly changes into
a cool T-shirt.)
You must feel hot
because of your hair.
I do feel hot.
There are times when I sweat
even before I leave the house.
(He quickly gets changed
before he sweats even more.)
(He grabs the coffee
he was drinking earlier.)
He makes sure to keep it stored.
I can drink it again when I return.
(I'll drink it again
when I come back!)
We have to trust our fridges.
The researchers...
- did a great job making them.
- The experts.
- Right.
(He leaves the coffee
to the work of the experts.)
(Hair swaying)
(He walks while showing off
his neat hair.)
(Walking...)
(endlessly)
It's Hongdae.
You went that far?
I enjoy walking.
(A relaxed walk on his own)
Hello.
- Hello.
- He met his fans.
(Feeling grateful)
Hello.
(It's Brother Woo Il!)
You have a lot of male fans, right?
Around 99.9 percent of them
are male fans.
- The male fans that love comedy.
- Right.
- They're all men.
- All men would love him.
(The winner of men's hearts
keeps walking.)
Hello.
The women like him too.
Gosh!
Hello. Thank you.
(The charming man who even won
the hearts of the women)
(Feeling shy)
Hello.
(Bowing)
He has a lot of female fans too.
(Hot Woo Il is popular
with everyone.)
(Feeling grateful)
(With hot footsteps,)
(he heads somewhere busily.)
Where could he be going?
This is someone's house.
Does he have two houses?
The door is opening.
(He bought a second house
with his popularity?)
(Grabbing)
(He diligently picks up
the delivered packages.)
He's picking up the packages too.
It must be his family's house.
(He's opening the door
of his family's house?)
(Screaming)
(Come on in.)
Hello, Wooju!
How cute!
Gosh, how cute!
(Is this Woo Il's family's house
with cute cats that welcome him?)
I'm here!
This is Cho Jin Se's house.
He is my junior.
(Junior comedian Cho Jin Se's house)
I've known the passcode
to even his previous house.
He knows the passcode
to my house as well.
We all share our passcodes.
(He enters his junior's house
like it's his own home.)
I'm here! Come here!
Come here.
Here. Hold on.
Why are you catching
the back of this?
- How cute.
- Why the back of this?
It feels uncomfortable, doesn't it?
You have to keep it on
for a bit longer.
Where is Jin Se?
He was away for work.
You like this one.
You like this one, don't you?
(With skillful hands,)
They're so cute.
(he plays with the cats.)
The cats like him too.
(He even manages to get a kiss.)
I love animals.
I have a dog,
but the dog is at my family's house.
I can only see my dog
from time to time.
There are animals that I can see...
in my junior's house.
- Did you go to see the cats?
- Yes.
I went to see the cats.
Hold on. No.
Come here.
I brought this.
(What did Woo Il bring?)
(He visited a store
for pet clothes earlier.)
I'll get this color.
I'll get two white ones.
(He bought the hats instantly
while thinking about the cats.)
(Let's try them on.)
Done.
It's staying still.
It looks so cute.
How cute!
Wooju has to try it on too.
Wooju can't put it on
because of the cone.
Come here.
Let's send a picture to Jin Se.
(Grabbing gently)
All right. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
- It looks so cute.
(Getting on his back)
It's like you're in your own home.
- Woo Il!
- Hey, Jin Se.
I just sent you a picture.
- Right.
- I bought something. Take a look.
What did you buy?
How is it?
(Laughing)
It's so cute.
It does look cute.
I'll stay here for a while...
after playing with the cats.
I feel relieved
since you're playing with them well.
- He must feel really grateful.
- Okay.
All right then.
(Thank you, Woo Il)
(After playing for a while
with the cats...)
I'll get going now.
Bye!
(He gets ready to leave.)
I'm off.
Bye.
(He heads outside
while feeling sad to leave.)
(Humming)
(He heads somewhere
after getting on a bicycle.)
(Parking)
- You look handsome!
- He went to Ahyeon-dong.
- Gosh! They're going wild.
- Thank you!
(His popularity has spread
just like the scent of his shampoo.)
Hello.
Gosh, thank you.
(Smiling after seeing Woo Il)
Gosh, thank you so much.
- Could I get a handshake?
- Thank you.
Have a good day. Thank you.
He's loved by everyone.
(He enters an apartment complex
with light steps.)
Where is he now?
Please enter the passcode.
(He enters
the shared entrance naturally.)
(Beeping)
He knows the passcode
to this place as well.
(Opening)
Is it his family's house?
- Is it someone else's house again?
- Whose house is it?
Gosh, I'm here,
and you're not even coming out.
You're right here!
(He enters the house
with a strange voice.)
You're right here!
- What's going on?
- It's a cat.
- It's a cat?
Oh, no! It's so small!
It's a baby!
How cute!
Come here.
What did you do? Did you sleep?
- Whose house is this?
- Did you sleep?
What were you up to?
(He lifts up the cat
like the owner.)
Cats make you go crazy
when they are around that age.
Gosh.
This is the house of
a junior comedian named Bang Joo Ho.
- I know him.
- I went to his house.
He started raising a cat,
so I went to visit.
- The cat's name is Hiro.
- How cute.
It isn't fully a dog-like cat
or a cat-like cat.
It's in between.
It was a tough journey
to come and see you.
They make you go crazy at that age.
- That's crazy. It's so cute.
- Why are your legs so short?
(Before I forget about it...)
(Taking out)
I got you a gift.
He got one for this cat too.
You're going to become super cute.
All right.
There you go. Okay.
There you go. All right.
- My gosh.
- It looks just like a doll.
- Isn't that a cartoon character?
- It looks so pretty.
It's so cute.
(A successful selfie)
You like my hair.
- Gosh.
It's trying to catch the hair.
Cats go crazy
over things like strings.
It liked my hair.
It really likes your hair.
(Panting)
- My gosh!
- Gosh!
This is just like "Ring."
(A seaweed stem
crawling toward Hiro?)
(Falling)
(A frightening sight
of playing with the cat)
(Fully satisfied)
You love animals.
I love animals.
I'll get going.
I'm leaving now!
(I'll bring a gift that you'll like
just like my hair next time.)
Bye, Hiro!
This is a win-win situation
for everyone.
The cats will be taken care of,
and Woo Il can spend time with them.
Right.
(The sun starts to set
after playing with Hiro.)
(Opening)
(He finally returns
to his own house.)
(He takes off his socks first.)
(Putting down)
(What do I have that I can eat?)
There were a lot of things
in the freezer.
It's just like a warehouse.
(Did he bring out fresh food
out of the warehouse?)
(Opening)
- What is that?
(The unidentified food gets thawed.)
(Another dish gets put in
right after.)
(The unidentified food
gets put into a pot.)
It was some sort of braised chicken.
- I think it was jjimdak.
- What is that?
- Jjimdak?
- You can't tell what it is.
- What?
Someone is entering the passcode.
- Someone's entering.
- Is it his mother?
(Opening)
(Someone comes in
after pressing the passcode.)
- I'm here.
- He's a junior named Kim Hyun Ki.
- I see!
- Right.
So other people
know your passcode too.
I share my passcode with the juniors
that live around me.
(Moving with both hands full)
He lives five minutes away from me.
We have a lot in common.
(He sits naturally.)
(Beeping)
- There's someone else entering.
- Gosh.
(One more person comes in.)
(He enters naturally
as if it were his own home.)
(Taking out)
He's coming in
as if it's a restaurant.
- That is how men look.
- Right.
He's Park Won Jun.
It's Park Won Jun.
We see each other
almost every single day.
(His juniors visit his house
for dinner.)
(Bringing down)
(He naturally opens
three bowls of rice.)
(He puts the food into a bowl.)
(Opening)
(What is he opening next?)
Here's the ramyeon noodles.
- To add to the jjimdak?
- It's the ramyeon.
The ramyeon.
Frozen soup dishes...
must have ramyeon.
- You must end it with ramyeon.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- The main dish.
- The main dish is here.
- Right.
Usually, they would just leave...
- after eating.
- Right.
Hold on.
(He suddenly gets up.)
(He ties his hair neatly
before eating.)
(He places a bun on top
and returns to the table.)
(Now, I can eat comfortably.)
I'll start with the ramyeon.
(He slurps the ramyeon
before it gets soggy.)
That looks great.
- Gosh!
- That's the best.
(Slurping)
(The juniors start slurping
the ramyeon as well.)
(Gulping)
(Eating at the same time)
- It's not bad.
- Not bad.
That means it's good.
(The juniors enjoy the meal
he worked hard to prepare for.)
The sauce is good.
(It perfectly suits their tastes.)
- They're eating really well.
- Gosh, it looks good.
(Feeling proud)
Even with my age and experience,
I think I've been able to
be tight with my juniors.
- I can see that.
- Right.
As I've been tight with them,
they call me over
when something happens.
They ask to work with me...
on their shows.
I could be helping them out,
but it's a chance for me
to make myself known...
through their channels.
I went over
whenever they called me...
and did everything I could
for a couple of years.
(With an intense first impression,)
(he threw himself around
as a rookie.)
Im Woo Il.
(As he was unknown for a while,)
(he did everything he could
whenever he had the chance.)
(He won the Popularity Award
after a lot of hard work.)
(I've worked for 14 years,)
(but I think I've done a lot more
last year in 2024.)
(He has finally seen the light
after 15 years.)
This was really touching.
- I felt really proud of him.
- I remember this.
I drank and blamed myself often.
But if I look back,
I think I should be
considered lucky.
Whenever my juniors
told me their struggles,
I wasn't boasting about myself,
but I spoke to them with confidence.
"You guys are ten years
younger than me."
"That's enough time
to make anything happen."
"You can pass bar exams..."
"after studying hard
for three years."
"You can do anything."
That was the kind of message
I shared with them mostly.
You can say that
because you kept trying.
- Of course.
- Yes.
- It's good, right?
- This is good.
- It's tasty.
- It's good, right?
Watching you on TV...
must give them more strength
than 100 lectures...
- ever can.
- Of course.
- I mean it.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Hey, this is good.
(Woo Il is a reliable senior
who always takes care of them.)
(They gratefully eat up
their senior's love.)
Now that your career has taken off,
you can cook for your juniors...
- every day. You know?
- Is it good?
They're going to return
the kindness you showed them.
- Gosh, I'm full now.
- Right.
This is the kind of food
Woo Il likes.
You know the flavor, right?
(Woo Il's Era Has Come)
- It's tasty.
- Gosh, this is good.
(Next story)
(Rainbow Refresh Special for Spring)
(Jennie...)
(dips her body in a tub.)
(Hyun Moo in a tub)
(Shaking)
(It's freezing cold!)
(I'm doing a cold plunge.)
(It's a project to strengthen
Moomoo's immune system.)
(The second story
of the Refresh Special)
(I'll refresh my immune system
with the cold plunge.)
(My fitness must improve
for a stronger immune system.)
(Gasping)
(He will get in shape
with Martial Artist Ju Seung.)
(Slapping)
(It's not easy to strengthen
my immune system.)
(Getting emotional)
(I can't give up now.)
(Let me walk over the river
instead of driving.)
(Improving my endurance
is the only way to go.)
(Panting)
(A good rest is as important
as a good workout.)
(Moomoo refreshes his fitness.)
(Moomoo refreshes
his friendship too.)
(A man is breathing heavily.)
(Is that Jae Hyeon?)
(He has arrived...)
(at his friend's parents' house.)
(Hello, ma'am.)
(He will spend some time with
his childhood friends of 27 years.)
(As it's been a long time
since he last visited.)
(He wants to help
take care of the garden.)
(Let's get to work now.)
I can do a good job.
(Great! I know what to do now.)
(This is doable.)
(It's not too hard on my body.)
(Staggering)
(Unable to control his body)
How do you chop firewood?
- Hold on.
- That's not how you do it.
(Why is this so hard?)
(Let's talk about the old days
while taking a breather.)
(We didn't see him for a while.)
(He didn't even answer our calls.)
(He didn't want to see
how happy we were.)
"I don't want to see how happy
you are with your family."
(Let's change the subject.
What will you do when you're 40?)
(Is there anything
you'd like to do?)
Me?
(I'll wait for your third child.)
(I'll wait for your first child.)
My child will be good-looking.
We have so many memories together.
(May Our Friendship Last Forever)
(Global Music by VIVA TUNES)