=Deep Love Love Again=
=Episode 22=
(Fall for Her)
Pei Jinqing!
Get lost!
She is my fiancee, Gu Qingqing.
What do you want to do?
If you are a man,
just come at me.
Take a good look.
She is not Manqing.
The real Manqing
has long since been killed by me.
When I slit her throat,
she crawled to her necklace
slowly.
Right.
Just like
you are now.
This time,
I will never let my beloved leave again.
Pei Jinqing!
Pei Jinqing, get up!
Get up!
Pei Jinqing! Pei Jinqing!
Pei Jinqing!
Get up! Pei Jinqing!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
The police came here this morning.
(One month later)
After investigation,
Qiyan tampered with my medication.
He kidnapped and killed people.
Today's outcome is deserved.
His mother indulged him too much.
I didn't fulfill my duties as a father.
I own you and your mother an apology.
You don't have to apologize to me.
If you're willing,
do you mind calling me
Dad?
Dad.
Boss. These are today's documents.
All right.
I got it.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said I can be up
and about tomorrow.
Then I'm relieved.
I will leave.
Qingqing.
What?
Want my forgiveness?
I know I've made a terrible mistake.
It's normal for you not to forgive me.
It's still possible
for me to forgive you.
Just a moment.
I have a gift for you.
If you want to stop,
say "hot milk" anytime.
I don't want to stop.
From now on,
my body and soul belong to you.
Okay.
I accept your confession.
From this day forward,
you can only follow my orders.