Episode 20
President Yan.
Send Mr. Tong away?
What did he say?
He...
My fault.
I've caused a great loss
to the company.
I'll take the responsibility.
You're not familiar with
the business line.
Only calculated profits
but failed to pay attention
to the raw material prices.
You did overstep your authority,
but you're not reckless.
For my stupidity and recklessness,
I need to say sorry.
I'll accept dismissing me.
I've checked your mail to President Yan.
The opponent was too cunning.
Of course,
in the management,
we still have flaws.
As for dismissal,
that was the heat of the moment.
Although you're a novice,
you're responsible
and considerate.
Hongtu and President Yan
are willing to give you a new chance.
Fang Wanzhi...
Again...
Auntie Wanzhi.
Your phone has been ringing.
I was about to send it to you.
Hello, Mr. Yan.
Now?
Okay.
I'll go out for a bit.
This late?
Don't tell me your president want you
to have a drink with him.
I don't know.
I'll head out.
Be careful.
Take it easy.
Mr. Yan.
What can I do for you?
I'll prepare it now.
Just sit.
I ordered coffee for you.
It's hot.
Thank you.
I've checked your email.
Your suggestion for
Hongtu's future business
and the high-tech fair
impressed me.
So I want to know
more details in person.
I'm so sorry
for sparing your private time.
No.
It's me who wants
to do that.
If I give you a chance
to persuade the management,
what will you say?
Don't be nervous.
Just treat me as one of them
and tell me your thoughts.
You can start it now.
Well, as I think,
Hongtu is technology-focused.
The high-tech fair
happens to magnify our advantages.
I'll talk about it from two sides.
First, in the short term, we can gain...
Okay, Fang Wanzhi,
you may leave now.
Ms. Fang has a brilliant plan.
I support it.
I fully support it!
As for the high-tech fair,
we must participate in it
if we want our company stronger.
Mr. Zhang,
last year, you were opposed to it.
Saying it wasted money
and time.
Did... Did I?
At that time,
there was no one like Ms. Fang
to explain this
in a thorough way.
Do you agree with me?
Indeed.
President Yan.
Shall we take a vote?
From their attitude,
do we need to do that?
Then it's approved?
Time for a night snack!
Check what I brought you!
Wow, delicious food!
Where were you entertaining?
So much good food.
I bought these specially for you two.
Auntie Wanzhi, sit.
What good news? Tell us.
I got promoted.
Treated as a vice president.
My salary went up two levels.
Auntie Wanzhi,
you're amazing!
Oh my gosh.
I need to pay for a meal
to celebrate it!
Don't forget Gao Xiang.
Wait a while.
My company is busy
preparing for the high-tech fair.
Yan Ziwei put me in charge of it.
Wait.
Who is Yan Ziwei?
Your president?
It's your first time to call him this.
You used to call him
President Yan,
or Mr. Yan?
He isn't here now.
President?
How old is he?
Fifty? Or sixty?
About my age.
He looks cold,
but when he's at work,
he's very decisive
and visionary.
Fang Wanzhi.
You're acting weird.
What?
Yan Ziwei.
Don't talk nonsense.
Auntie Juan.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
It's better that you don't.
Let's eat.
Ms. Fang,
come with us.
At this high-tech fair,
we signed
four strategic agreements,
and would earn
more than 100 million yuan.
Thank you.
You deserve the most credit.
It's my duty.
Later, someone in finance
will find you for signatures.
Congratulations.
You're getting a bonus!
Ms. Yao.
I don't want
this bonus.
I caused a huge loss
for our company before.
President Yan approved the bonus.
But...
Don't turn down his kindness.
Thank you.
Many executives in Hongtu
are from Hong Kong, China.
When they work in Shenzhen,
the company pays for their apartments.
Now you've reached the level.
The apartment for you.
No, thanks.
I have a place to live.
This is a company benefit.
I picked it specially.
It's quite good.
President Yan is also in this community.
If you move here, it'll be closer
and convenient to work.
No need.
Living where I am now
won't affect my work.
Alright.
I'll keep it first.
Find me if you need it.
Thank you, Ms. Yao.
You're all awake.
My treat tonight
to celebrate your promotion.
I've already invited Gao Xiang.
Nice!
I don't have class tonight.
Even so, you still can't join us.
Go home and sleep.
You work so long every day,
so you can't lack sleep.
Fine, follow Wanzhi's words.
I'll pack the food.
Alright.
I gotta go.
Take care.
Why do you always
invite Gao Xiang?
Mr. Gao has been
asking about you.
Right after the high-tech fair,
he asked me
if you have time
for dinner together.
Why didn't he
ask me himself?
I see him every night
at evening school.
How's he doing lately?
Great!
Let me tell you.
Mr. Gao
is really a good teacher.
Simple and vivid.
Always making us laugh.
Nobody dozes off in his class.
Sometimes no seats are available,
so people stand.
And the point is
most are girls.
Why are you looking
at me?
Nothing to do with me.
This beef is delicious.
Thanks.
Fang Wanzhi.
A gift for you.
What's this?
Take a look.
I took it by myself.
How is it?
You're at the scene?
Seeing you running around,
I didn't disturb you.
Congratulations!
Taking a group photo
at the signing ceremony
fully shows
you're indeed important at Hongtu.
I was just doing support.
No...
I noticed
you were in charge of
the entire booth
and business negotiations.
How did you know that?
I followed you.
I...
Just kidding.
I am
a special reporter
for the high-tech fair.
Providing news reports
for major newspapers.
Oh!
Another gift for you.
Another one?
What is it? Show me.
Afraid of disturbing you,
I, the on-site reporter,
just served you quietly
nearby.
Gao Xiang, you're amazing!
Wanzhi was nice
in this photo.
Right?
Did you ask for my permission?
Everybody. Cheers!
Cheers!
Thank you.
Enjoy!
Gao Xiang has always
been caring about you
for all these years.
Hurry up and marry him.
Marry him?
I don't feel that way about him.
And he never even chased me.
Not once.
He really likes you.
He treats you differently
from other girls.
Look.
Here.
Toast
to you.
Cheers!
Where is the difference?
You don't have a thing for Yan Ziwei,
do you?
Look at the cook there.
Zhu?
Why didn't you
tell us you came to Shenzhen?
I was afraid you'd tip her off.
You mean Qian?
She doesn't know you're here?
Never, ever tell her.
Didn't you make up
last time you left?
It didn't last half a year.
Her pager kept ringing all day.
Then she ran to call back
at the village committee.
She laughed flirtatiously.
The whole village laughed at me.
My dad told me to discipline her,
but instead,
she lost her temper first.
Scratched my face
and neck.
I slapped her.
Then she ran away.
Why not come for her sooner?
I tried.
I've been here five times.
And I have Dahu.
If we both left him,
how miserable he would be!
Now my kid's older,
so I made up my mind.
Either I take her back,
or I'll kill her.
That's nonsense!
Someone saw her at this food stall.
So I got a job here
to wait for her.
If I run into her...
Zhu.
Do you remember
what I told you back then?
Violence can't solve any problems.
Maybe I can find her.
But you have to promise me
when you meet her,
talk to her calmly.
Wanzhi.
If you can help me find Qian
and persuade her to come back,
you'll be the savior
of my whole family.
- Zhu!
- Please!
What are you doing?
I'll try my best.
Come in.
Ms. Yao.
I've thought it over these days.
The company was considerate.
Living closer to President Yan
does make my work easier.
That's the spirit.
Luckily, I didn't give that house
to others.
I've visited the house.
Two bedrooms. Very spacious.
The community is nice, too.
Move in with me.
We'll take the larger room.
Zhao Jun takes the other.
I'm not going with you.
It's too far from the warehouse.
Although the house is nicer,
what about the commute?
Taxi?
Costs too much.
Don't forget
I'm your employee.
You have to calculate profits.
Profits can be a little less.
But we're besties.
Come on.
We are still besties
even if
we don't live together.
I'm not going either.
Auntie Juan.
If she moves out,
I can pay
more rent here.
Wait. Zhao Jun.
Why are you
still so formal?
She insists on paying every month
even though I refuse.
Zhao Jun, just come with me.
It's closer to where you work.
You can sleep half an hour longer.
Auntie Wanzhi,
I'm used to living here.
It's far,
but only one transfer.
It's convenient.
If Auntie Juan's on a business trip,
I can help feed Little Friend.
Then bring it, too.
Absolutely not.
It needs to be with me.
So none of you
want to move?
It's fine to move there alone.
Convenient for dating.
What are you talking about?
No.
I just...
Keep drinking!
Depth charge!
Slow down! Be careful.
We're home...
You can
try our coffee.
Our coffee is good.
Enjoy yourself.
Hello, Ms. Fang.
Hello, manager.
Mr. Yan told me
you'd moved here.
Ask me if you need help.
Thanks.
Manager?
Do you remember the person
I asked about?
Who?
One night,
a man and a woman,
who were both drunk,
were walking inside.
I chased
and asked you...
Sorry, Ms. Fang.
I don't remember that at all.
Slow down.
Come on, keep drinking.
I'm fearless.
I want a depth charge.
I...
I am not drunk.
Manager.
Ms. Fang.
You're still here?
Want something to drink?
No need.
The club has rooms?
We have a few VIP rooms,
reserved yearly for VIP members.
If Mr. Yan needs them,
you can book in advance.
You're given the priority.
Anything else?
The surname of that sir just now?
Sorry, Ms. Fang.
I don't know
who you're talking about.
I'm busy. I gotta go.
Madam.
Hello.
Good morning.
How long have you worked here?
Four years.
So you know
all the residents here?
Of course not.
The community is too huge.
Villas,
townhouses,
and apartments.
I'm only in charge of this area.
As for the villas,
I'm not even allowed in.
You...
Nothing.
Just wondering.
Morning.
Jogging like this
won't help you exercise.
Hurry in. Keep up.
I can't run anymore.
Mr. Yan, you go ahead.
Don't let me disturb you.
There's no shortcut to exercise.
Only persistence works.
Alright.
This time,
didn't you run too fast?
That would hurt you.
Take it slow.
Juan.
What's up?
Tomorrow is the weekend.
No overtime, right?
Come back tonight.
I'll make dumplings for you.
I really want
your dumplings,
but I still have work to do.
I can't go back.
Wait a minute.
Zhu contacted me,
pressing for Qian's news.
I got it.
Steady him first.
Tell him
it'll be soon.
Mr. Li.
Long time no see.
Madam, you've got the wrong person.
My surname is Xu.
Mr. Xu.
Sorry, bad memory.
Could you tell me
how to contact Hao Qianqian?
I don't know her,
or you.
I'm Qian's friend.
It's urgent.
Please help me.
I said I don't know her.
I'm taking my wife out now.
Don't be unreasonable.
Mrs. Xu.
Good morning.
From your accent,
you're not a local.
Yes.
Every time I run past your house,
I can't help looking.
Your flowers are so beautiful.
Madam,
what's your name?
My surname is Fang.
Ms. Fang, you like flowers too?
Wait here.
I'll cut you some branches.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Mrs. Xu, you're so kind.
Can I chat with you
when I'm free?
Ms. Fang,
welcome for tea anytime.
If you continue this,
I'll call the security.
If you don't want me
to bother you every day,
tell Hao Qianqian to contact me.
Ms. Fang,
I arranged them casually.
Arrange them carefully at home.
Okay, thanks.
They're so lovely.
I won't bother you anymore.
Alright, let's go.
Remember to come for tea!
Bye bye.
Bye.
Hello?
Hold on.
Hao Qianqian.
3 p.m. this Sunday.
At your old house.
Wanzhi, why the rush?
I have to check
if I have appointments.
Cancel them.
If you don't come, you'll regret it.
Wanzhi.
Zhi.
I missed you so much.
Has it been three years?
Be serious.
Didn't we meet
on my birthday?
Hao Qianqian.
Your singing is
much worse than before.
In these years,
drinking has ruined your voice.
You're indeed my good friend.
Not saving my face
at all.
However,
I know you care about me the most.
Deal.
Sunday.
What do you and Juan want to eat?
Alaskan king crab?
Lobster?
Got it. We...
Fang Wanzhi.
Why are you here?
Just passing by.
I don't buy it, Gao Xiang.
What's up?
I...
I've been consulting
for my student's company.
At a meeting this afternoon,
I met a man, also from Yu County.
He is excellent,
very capable.
A senior executive at a global company.
Therefore,
I invited him
for tea
on Sunday.
3 p.m.
I'll pick you up.
Wait,
you arranged it without asking me?
You're from the same county!
I'm busy that day.
I've had an appointment.
Where? Maybe we can join you.
I'll bring him over.
This man is really nice.
No airs at all.
Gao Xiang.
I have something important on Sunday.
Cancel it for me.
And please don't
do that again.
I'm leaving.
Qian is here.
You promised me.
Talk calmly.
Finally missed me.
See what I bought.
Where are you going?
Liu Zhu!
Li Juan.
Fang Wanzhi.
I thought you were
my best friends.
This is how you betray me?
Right?
No one betrayed you.
We mean well.
Well?
I managed to escape.
And you're pushing me
back into the fire.
Meaning well?
Qian.
Go home with me.
Dahu misses you.
He wakes up crying in his dreams.
None of your business. Get out!
I'll talk with them first.
We have nothing to say.
Zhu,
we found your wife back.
Solve your family business.
Wanzhi, let's go.
Liu Zhu, get out.
Didn't you hear me?
What to drink?
I brought red wine and liquor.
I've quit beer.
Who are you putting on airs for?
We shared the same bed
and table.
I know who you are.
I know it's good wine,
but nobody cares.
Hao Qianqian,
one day,
when you get by,
and I,
almost as poor
as a church mouse,
have few foods,
I'll cook you porridge
if I have a handful of rice.
I love hearing you talk like this.
Indeed.
I know
a loyal person like you
would never
betray me like Fang Wanzhi.
What did Wanzhi do?
Is "betray" the right word
for her?
Zhu has come to Shenzhen five times.
Staying here another half a year,
he has asked everywhere about you.
Without Wanzhi,
you might have been attacked
in the dark one day
and never know who did this.
How couldn't I know?
He refuses to divorce me.
You know me well.
I keep my mouth shut,
but I'm terrified actually.
His family never
treated me like a person.
After my first child,
they wanted a second.
I called my friend
a little too long,
and his whole family
rolled their eyes.
And they egged Zhu on to hit me.
Is this a life for humans?
Why didn't you talk to him
to move to Shenzhen with Dahu?
Talking to someone
who beats me?
Besides, I did tell him.
He refused.
He said
they built five tile houses,
so I had to stay with him
in his hometown
and care for his parents
until they die.
Liu is perfectly healthy.
So,
waiting for 20 years,
30 years?
You're a little heartless.
I wish his family well.
Long life. Many descendants.
But I can't stay!
I've been starving and bullied.
It's uneasy for me to be alive.
Luckily,
God
is somewhat on my side.
I'm not ugly,
can sing a little,
and men like me.
Why should I be trapped
in that valley forever?
I didn't contact you when I came here
because I was afraid they would catch me
and get you involved.
When I ran away,
my wallet,
pager, and ID card
were all stolen.
To get to Shenzhen,
I suffered so much.
I can't say it.
But it's okay now.
I got my ID card back
and got a driver license.
I have a house and a car.
I can't go back.
Wanzhi.
Juan.
In this world,
I really only
have you as my family.
If you really stand with Zhu
and force me to back,
I'll kill myself in front of you.
Don't say that!
About Liu Zhu...
What's your plan?
Zhu is dead set on this.
I'll send him away.
I knew
you still cared about me.
I, Hao Qianqian,
haven't been living for nothing.
You called me in such a hurry.
I knew he was definitely here.
Don't worry.
I'll solve
my own problems.
How long have you been here?
This time...
Five and a half months.
Must be a hard time.
It's nothing if you come back with me.
Dahu misses you.
I also miss Dahu.
Liu Zhu.
We...
didn't register our marriage.
But my family held a wedding feast.
That meant the marriage.
At that time, your dad said
we'd register after the baby.
If it hadn't been a boy,
what would have happened?
I heard it all.
He never thought
I was qualified, right?
No.
Forget him. I like you anyway.
But I've left for three years.
I haven't been faithful to you.
What?
You're an adult.
Don't you figure it out?
With the five tile houses,
it's easy to get married.
You didn't register your marriage,
so you're still single officially.
It's great.
No!
You have to come back with me.
This isn't your home.
This is Shenzhen.
If you go street on me,
I'll call the police. Believe it or not.
You think I'm uneducated
and illiterate, right?
I've asked a lawyer.
We didn't register our marriage,
so I'd never be your wife.
Your family wants to bully me again?
Daydream.
Once a couple, always a bond.
Dahu is my son.
I have to raise him.
This money
is enough to
grow him up.
Please take good care of him.
Don't let his stepmom bully him.
Money is hard to earn for me.
So I can't give you more.
Say sorry to your dad
and tell him and your mom
to care for the kid.
Let's break up peacefully.
Liu Zhu.
I didn't owe you.
Qian!
Who are you?
Who are you!
I was like you once.
As a result, I spent 3 years in prison.
Do you want to go to jail too?
Zhu.
If you're in prison,
who will care for Dahu?
If you're tough, come at me!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Get off!
Zhu.
Put down the knife.
Or I'll call the police.
Do you hear me?
Wanzhi.
Don't let him call the police,
please.
Gao Xiang.
Zhu.
I won't call the police for now,
but you're doing a crime.
If the victim presses charges,
you'll go to jail at any time.
Sir,
I'm Fang Wanzhi's brother.
Let me talk to you.
I don't want that.
My wife is gone.
I lost my wife.
I lost my wife!
How's your hand?
It's fine.
Mr. Li,
let's see a doctor.
Sir,
you hurt me.
Need to pay the bill, right?
See the doctor with me.
Zhu,
why were you so impulsive?
What if you hurt him
badly?
No thought for the consequences?
My job has me
traveling all over the country.
That makes me
a stranger in my hometown.
I didn't expect
the person Gao Xiang mentioned
was you.
He didn't tell me your name,
but I had an intuition,
it must be you.
Doesn't it hurt you?
If I hadn't grabbed the knife,
I'd be hurting right now.
Gao Xiang... Really a good man.
Does he have a chance
to be your husband?
Seems he still has to work hard.
Wanzhi.
I have a girlfriend.
Really?
Congratulations!
My mom also likes her,
but she says
you need to approve us first.
Where is she?
She came to Shenzhen with me.
I'll treat you to dinner.