Books Shop
Diet
ICHE
This world is very cruel to ordinary people.
Maybe you did nothing wrong,
but you will never find the truth.
This is a small hotel.
Mother left it to me.
It's almost half a year.
The doctor said I was sick,
but I don't want to take medicine.
I'm sorry.
I'm not patient.
My name is Song Yili.
I choose to die.
On my birthday,
I chose this medicine.
I've never had this medicine.
I finally used it today.
I'm sorry.
Please, stop.
He used a mouse.
Dongyiong, I can't see it now.
Don't try it at home.
I said so.
Uncle.
Uncle!
You're so cool.
Yu Xiao Qu.
Where's Yu Xiao Qu?
I heard he's the biggest.
I'm sure he's the biggest.
Or he's your sister.
Have you seen a girl?
No.
Where is she?
Yu Xiao Qu!
Shu An, you're so stubborn.
Otherwise, I'll keep my snacks.
Zuo Yi Li.
Are you okay?
How do you know?
The police contacted me.
I'll go to the hospital now.
I know.
I know!
Chen Nan Hospital.
The emergency room.
21st bed.
You're so stubborn.
Help me.
No one can see.
How are you?
Is it serious?
I'm fine.
Don't make people worry.
I want to keep this as a souvenir.
I'll return it to you.
I know you need money.
Happy birthday.
Lin Yi.
I'm sorry.
Did you change the police contact?
Uncle, happy birthday.
This is a gift for you.
Let me sing you a song.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
The other party is in a bad shape.
Song Yilin, what's your problem?
Nothing.
The check-up is all wrong, right?
It's a bit serious.
I don't think it's a problem.
You can go now.
Or stay in the hospital.
You can do the CT and X-ray.
Don't look for me again.
Don't look for me.
I'll stay.
Sorry, wrongberg.
Hello, Mayor.
What
Enjoy with me.
Wish you a peaceful life.
If you were willing to92 takes care.
2nd guy.
Hey.
I'll let you guys take him.
Ok.
Uh-uh.
Ok, let's go.
Ask every child to run from AAA to NOI and Revolt should know that they would treat the child to Babas favor give
How's the sister of seven
Where did you say
For around three people in college
One 마음
The other د are you
And I
Are us three brothers
Brotherade
I'm not better than you.
I'm more sad than you.
But I can't tell you.
Because I told you, it's useless.
I can't solve any problem.
I just have one more person to be sad with me.
But I want to tell you...
I want to die.
Actually, I want to die too.
I was taken to the hospital by my sister.
But I didn't come back.
So I'm dead.
I have to be happy to be in the hospital.
I have another secret.
Why?
I want to die!
You give me a little demon!
I don't even know how to die.
Why?
Why did my sister give you the ring?
What ring?
She said I'm a married woman.
So she gave you the ring.
And she told you to sell some money.
You're brothers now, right?
You've got so many problems.
You go back first. I'll go in myself.
Okay. I have to go to bed.
I'm leaving.
I'm going to bed.
You don't want to live like this?
The world is a mess.
I don't want to live like this.
The people who love you are all there.
But if I die,
you'll really live well.
I hope you'll be better next life.
Why am I here?
You're in the forest.
I'm thinking about you.
Uncle, you're awake.
Let's go.
I'm not going to sleep.
I'm going to bed.
Dad.
Where are you going?
To find dad.
I don't even know your dad.
How can I take you to find your dad?
You said it yourself.
Brother,
if I die,
I won't forget what you want me to do.
I'll tell you first.
I'm going to bed.
Why are you in my car?
Uncle, I'm thinking we have a problem.
What problem?
Don't you follow me?
You're so beautiful.
I'm finally out.
Uncle, are you here for the recording?
Uncle, will you be brave?
What do you want?
Are you done?
Where's your dad?
Dad is in the rooftop.
What?
He's in the rooftop.
I'll go to the rooftop.
Dad,
where are you going?
I'm going to bed.
I'm not going to sleep.
Aunt, are we in the hospital?
I'm not going back to the hospital?
I know this road. You're lying to me.
I'm not going back to the hospital!
What are you doing?
I can't get out of here if I get out of here!
Why do you have to tell me what to do?
Uncle, I'm not in any trouble.
It's not good.
You'll open my head.
I'm going to find my dad.
I haven't seen my dad for a long time.
Chang Pia!
I'll call your mom.
I'll send you back if she agrees.
My mom is in a bad mood.
She's too busy.
Mom, I'm going to find my dad. I'm still here.
Don't worry about me.
I'll send you back when your mom's back.
Okay.
Remember to take your medicine.
I can't remember.
Uncle, let's go.
Let's go!
Don't you worry about me being a bad person?
Uncle, I'm not looking down on you.
You're not like me.
Be careful, mom!
How is it? Did you find it?
Not yet.
Her things are gone.
She only has one note left.
Where will she go?
I'll send you back.
Did you take the medicine?
How do you know?
This green one eats the food every day.
This red one eats the food afterwards.
This white one...
I'm Chen Mo.
Welcome to the world of your dog.
I don't know who's watching my show.
How do I look?
To be honest, I'm very angry.
I won't open up for anyone.
Nor will I be the only one.
Why are you taking my picture?
I'm still forcing you to take my picture.
Give it back to me!
Uncle, we're going to the third camp.
The third camp...
One time.
One person.
I really believe in you.
The third camp...
The fourth camp...
Boss, come here.
Come on, let's go.
It's gone.
See?
Young man, I'll treat you to something to drink.
Come on.
I'll treat you to something to drink.
Please, don't do anything.
You're going to complain about me.
I can't do anything.
I'll give you a fried rice.
Give me a face.
Who's going to give you a fried rice?
You're annoying.
It's gone.
Please, don't do anything.
Are you annoying?
What?
What's wrong with you?
You're going to kill me?
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
I'm so tired.
Why are you afraid of running over here?
Am I going to be hit by a car?
Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
You promised to help me.
I'll help you move back.
I'm sorry.
Uncle, the clouds are so beautiful today.
Uncle,
have you ever been on a live broadcast?
Uncle, what do you live?
I cook.
You can continue.
You can eat and eat when you have money.
I'm going to go.
Uncle,
say hello to your fans.
Are you okay?
Uncle,
where's the noodles?
Do we still have food today?
Hello?
Give me the money this day.
Don't be so thick-skinned.
You can't contact me for a year.
You can only borrow money when you call.
No.
I'm really in a hurry.
Then come over.
I'll give you the money when you come over.
No.
No money?
Uncle.
I'm done crying.
Why are you making a scene?
Uncle,
is this your supermarket?
Can I go in and take a look?
Why?
Take it.
Who is this?
My butt.
Come here.
Take it.
Look at my good food.
Good food, good scenery,
good air.
You've been here for days.
I'm sure you're not tired.
I took a bottle of vinegar and a bag of micro-crisp.
I'll take it.
Okay.
12.5 yuan.
Xiaojun,
don't eat that.
It's not good for you.
Eat more food.
Uncle,
this is called free food.
I'll take it.
What is this?
As a princess,
as a prince,
I can eat well.
These are all my wishes.
Song Yulian,
do you know
how many wishes he has?
It's none of my business.
No?
I have money.
What money do you have?
I have a small shop.
I can have a few in my pocket.
Eat quickly.
I'll be in a hurry later.
Try this.
Drink more.
What?
I made it myself.
Can't you drive?
I can't.
Uncle,
when you were in school,
what did Uncle look like?
He...
He looked like a fool.
When he was in college,
he said
he wanted to be a superman
and be a super hero.
He is indeed a fool.
Once he got drunk,
he came back to the room
in our dorm
and ran around in a mess.
Then he also said
he could fly up
from one day.
Uncle Fang,
can you promise me something?
it's so sad.
Let's make him happy,
okay?
Xiao Ju, you are so good.
But it's too hard to fly up.
Actually, it's not hard.
I'm not good at flying.
Uncle Fang,
Uncle,
how did you get out of the car?
Xiao Ju came here,
and the business suddenly got better.
The car was gone.
I bought you breakfast.
I don't have a night shift today.
After you finish eating,
I'll take you out for fun.
Uncle!
Stop it.
We are still on the road.
How about this one?
This one.
You want to help the princess, right?
Yes.
Why do you call this princess?
The princess has already grown up.
She can grow up.
Brother,
are you crazy?
Brother, you are doing well.
I'm sorry about that.
Brother,
are you crazy?
Brother, you are not a good wife.
You are not a good wife.
How much do you want?
I'll ask you how much you want.
Don't care about it.
Take it.
No.
Hurry up.
Get back.
Why are you so tired?
I'm just a little bit tired.
I'm going to sleep.
In the past,
they always called me a dog.
Only you can call me a dog.
And they called me a beggar.
They called me a beggar.
In your heart,
you never considered me a dog.
You have been living a bad life these years.
I know it.
You used to talk to me.
Now I do.
Su Yi Lin.
You want to live in the world.
You can't live for two years.
I've been waiting for you for eight years.
Xiao Ju.
Look.
You like it.
I'll keep it for you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Uncle.
I'll always remember you.
Let's go.
You must remember me, too.
Brother.
I'm a little bit tired.
I'll make sure I don't get tired.
Brother.
You're better than me.
You've been living a good life.
I've known you for a long time.
You're better than me.
You've been living a good life.
I think you're better than me.
Trust me.
You'll live a good life.
You'll do anything.
You've been looking after me.
Why are you like this now?
Promise me, Su Yi Lin.
Oh, no.
Why are you like this now, Su Yi Lin?
Promise me, Su Yi Lin.
Promise me.
Brother.
Run.
Please show me your ID.
Your ID.
Why did you come to the highway without your car?
You can't go to the highway without your car?
How did you fall?
Sorry.
Go.
How did you fall?
Chen Dao Mei.
What are you doing?
You're living in your own clothes.
Have you heard of Channy Yu?
She came from Hu fathers relation
We have never seen anyła
She became a master of Mrs. Bao
She has married me
Moreover she got to work in this restaurant
More work for Mr. Lu
conocen
She came from the dry family
I see
I'm afraid I'll hit you.
Mr. Guo, I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Don't worry. We'll talk on the street if you have any conditions.
Right?
Hello? Mr. Guo?
Mr. Guo?
Oh my god.
Can you hear me?
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
I won't chase you if you hit me.
Give me a ride.
What?
A ride? Look at me.
Guo Shuang, you're a kid.
You don't need to ride a car.
How can you be a father?
My father is a black donkey.
Who's your father?
Oh my god.
A man.
I'm a man.
Hello?
You want to play?
Jingjing, I have something to tell you.
Go back and talk to me. I'm busy.
Let's break up.
Don't make trouble.
I'm serious.
It's like we can't keep walking like this.
We've only met once in a half year.
Do you think this is normal?
I don't know what you feel.
Send me to Ancheng.
Why do people come to find her?
I'm a man.
Every step of my life is planned.
Even if we break up,
we have to be careful.
Why can't we go to Ancheng?
Okay.
Security bureau, hospital,
Ancheng.
Go to A.
Where's your mom?
I'm late.
I'm getting married.
Look at you.
You look like a real man.
You should learn something good.
You have to learn to be a father.
You have to learn to be a father every day.
Uncle Ji,
where are you going to get the water?
I'm going to get it.
Uncle Ji,
sister is still in the car.
Since you know,
I don't think there's anything to say.
Is she inside?
It's none of her business.
Okay.
How long have you been together?
You know me.
I won't do this unless I'm good.
Half a year?
Actually, I've been trying to tell you.
I'm so busy with you.
I'm afraid it'll affect your work.
Really.
What you mean is,
it's my fault.
Don't blame yourself.
We all have our own problems.
We can't blame you.
Jingjing,
I'm more painful than you.
Except for three people who hurt you.
You're better than one person who hurt you.
You're stronger than us.
What do you mean?
I'm stronger.
I have to be hurt.
To be honest,
I'm very tired.
I'm tired.
Why don't you say something?
I'm not willing to.
But the truth is...
No.
If I can make you suffer,
I'm willing to sacrifice for you.
Okay.
I wish you two a long and long life.
Uncle,
Jingjing looks so sad.
Who made you sad?
I'm Chen Mo.
Welcome to the world.
Why did someone suddenly come
and leave suddenly?
Actually, there's no sudden person.
He must have thought it through.
He must have understood it.
Jump, jump, jump.
What?
Jingjing jumped on me.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hurry.
Uncle, are you okay?
Uncle, please help me.
Why did you go down?
I just wanted to calm down.
But you wouldn't swim.
You saved someone.
I was impulsive.
You were impulsive?
I found that you guys are so hard-working.
You're sicker than you are.
You said you'd only tell me after half a year.
I'm not.
I was so mad that I just told you.
Last month, the kid was shopping with me.
He was so mad.
Your mom didn't want to help me.
I'm sorry.
We've been together for years.
It's too sudden for me.
I know it's not worth crying for such a person.
So I can only allow myself to cry for five minutes.
I can only allow myself to cry for five minutes.
No one is so sudden.
I just want to come back clearly.
I want to leave after thinking about it.
I found that you're interesting.
You're so weird.
What's the point of being so weird?
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm afraid you'll die in the name of the Emperor.
What should I do?
Who's going to die?
What's the problem with death?
Mr. Guo.
I'm so sorry.
I have something to do on the way.
I'll be there soon.
I'm on my way.
Don't worry.
Bye.
That's enough.
Enough.
I'm sorry.
Xu Jingjing.
Love is gone.
Then just do your job.
Then we won't see you off.
I'm sorry.
Although I don't know what you've been through,
you're not bad.
Don't be so sad.
You're not bad.
Why are you so sad?
I'm leaving.
Xiaoju.
Live a good life with your father.
I'm leaving.
Uncle, you were so weak just now.
Why are you peeking?
You said don't peek.
I didn't say don't peek.
Stay here.
You can't go anywhere.
You are?
The same-sex express.
I wish you a happy life.
How is it?
Uncle, I'm going to make something.
Thank you.
Thank you, uncle.
I'm sorry.
The world is so big.
Do you know?
Actually, the world has a lens.
Where are they?
Uncle, are these your classmates?
We are college friends.
This is Uncle Song Yili.
This is Uncle Fan Kuaqi.
Well...
I've never seen him before.
But he's the best student I've ever seen.
You're right.
He's called Uncle Li.
I'll have a brother like him in the future.
I'm Xiao Ju.
This is my wish.
I've never seen my father.
Mom said he went to another world.
I'm a kid without a father.
Where have you been?
To find my father.
I don't even know your father. How can I take you to find your father?
I've never seen my father.
Why did you ask me to find you a father?
I'm sorry.
Where's your mother?
I called your mother.
Hurry up and call her now!
I didn't answer your call.
What happened to your voice?
I'm sorry.
How can I believe you?
I'm not coming out like this.
Why are you lying to me?
You're lying to me all the time.
Call me!
I don't want you to take me back!
I'll call my mother.
Mom, I'm here.
Mom, don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
I'll go back to work.
I'm a little worried.
Remember to take the ticket.
I'll put it under your feet.
If you're hungry, you can eat anything.
After you go back,
I'll listen to your mom.
Send someone.
You can get off.
Master,
I have a little friend to take care of you.
Please take care of him.
When he's in Nanjing,
his mom will pick him up at the station.
Uncle, are we going back to the hospital?
I know this road.
You're lying to me.
I don't want to go back to the hospital.
I'm going to find my mom.
Uncle, I'm sorry.
I'm a little worried.
Please take me down.
You're going to kill me.
Stop!
Uncle,
I didn't lie to you.
I'm sorry.
That's the picture that my mom hid.
Actually, when I was little, my dad left.
He didn't even leave a picture of me.
I was a useless girl.
I didn't do anything.
My dad didn't take good care of me.
Uncle,
my mom is the one who loves us the most in this world.
She won't blame you.
I ran out of the hospital.
I wanted to see how big this world is.
But only a few days.
I miss my mom.
Uncle,
I'm not afraid to be a uncle.
But I want to live well.
Because I'm with you.
I won't be sad.
Xiao Juan,
let's go back.
I lost a good friend.
Before he died,
I thought I didn't find
he had such a serious depression.
Later, I realized that
when someone has a heart of crack,
it's all so coincidental.
No one noticed.
Only when he's in a bad mood,
will everyone listen.
I'm asking Feng.
Feng?
Feng.
Feng,
I'll hit you with a head.
You're too young to learn.
Go to sleep.
Uncle.
Don't touch me, okay?
That was the end.
Running again.
My mind.
Saving time.
I'll give myself to that.
That was the end.
Running again.
Your mother's age is very serious.
She has to be trained by someone.
You don't want to live such a life.
I don't want to either.
But if I leave,
you'll really live well.
I'll be there for you.
Mom.
Mom, wait for me.
Uncle.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Xiaojun?
I'm sick.
Xiaojun, don't be afraid.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Xiaojun.
Xiaojun, hang in there.
Doctor.
Where's the doctor?
What's wrong?
I'm sick.
Let me go.
What are you doing?
I'm sick.
I'm sorry.
We found a treasure in your mother's house.
You're the one who said it.
But it's your own.
I'm sorry.
You're the one who said it.
We found a treasure in your mother's house.
But it's your own.
I'm sorry.
Take care.
The child looks much better than before.
He's father.
He is at a stука care.
We found a little treasure in him.
He is at a st药 Si Fu already .
You had one at that time,
a little treasure in his father's house.
We found a little treasure in him.
I didn't know what I should be doing.
These days, I want to make a dream.
In my dream,
I want to have a baby
and call my uncle.
Uncle, I'm so dizzy.
I should be hungry.
Uncle, you can't drink.
I know.
Let's play a game.
You say, catch a duck, you say, catch a few.
Catch a duck.
Catch a few.
Catch.
Hello?
Fang Guai Qi, why are you crying?
We haven't seen each other for three years.
You've been sick for so long.
Why aren't you telling me?
I'm not sick.
Lao Wei often tells you about me.
He's afraid you'll be sad.
Mr. Li Shu left.
I'll be the one to discuss with Wen Ke.
But he left us a gift.
It's a letter.
Someone said
I gave up my city life.
It's not easy to get back here.
But I think
the suffering of life
is not worth living.
The children of the hometown
don't have to eat anymore.
They don't have to walk
the path they've taken.
The lost hope
doesn't have to be with me.
The world they see
must be beyond my imagination.
I live in the place I love the most.
I do things
for the people I love the most.
I don't need sympathy.
I hope
you don't live for the past
but for the future.
People
live
not necessarily winning.
But they can't lose.
The End
It's still here.
Hello.
Mr. Song.
I'm Xiao Ju's mother.
Xiao Ju said
she wanted to see you.
Mom.
Why did you eat the baby?
Xiao Ju.
Go to bed.
It won't hurt if you're asleep.
Mom.
Uncle.
I want to talk to you.
Can you?
Yes.
I've finished writing this book.
I'll give it to uncle.
When I was in the hospital,
my next-door sister
cried secretly every day.
She cried secretly every day.
Xiao Ju.
I'll leave this earphone to you.
Really?
I also like to listen to this song.
If you finish the operation,
you can come back.
I'll take you to the concert, okay?
She gave me the light she liked the most.
She left.
Uncle.
If I can't come back after the operation,
you can take me to the concert, okay?
I'll come back.
Xiao Ju.
I want to see your uncle.
Let's clean up, okay?
Let's clean up.
If you agree with this situation,
please sign it.
Your son.
I saw Xiao Ju's mother.
On her body,
I saw the shadow of my mother.
It turned out to be a real despair.
It wasn't my own fault.
I was so worried.
I was so worried about your assassin self.
My droplets of sights here...
can't stop them playing.
It is a despair.
It was my own dreams.
It was my love.
I can't stop living.
I'm Song Yili.
My failure may not be special.
I've been looking for you since my mother's death.
I'm not sure if I can find you.
I'm not sure.
I grew up looking for my mother.
I studied, graduated, got married.
And then divorced.
Maybe you can't look down on me.
I can't figure out what's going on in the world.
When I gave up on my dream,
I met a little angel.
Her name is Xiao Ju.
She's nine years old.
She's a child.
So we fell in love.
I never thought that
I wouldn't save her on this journey.
She saved me.
We met many people, many things.
We had each other.
We fell in love.
I wanted to die.
My life is not like that.
But she gave me the same thing.
The courage to live on.
I want to live on.
Xiao Ju, how is uncle?
Do you want to come with me?
I want to live with you.
Sister Chen Yan.
Yu Xiao Ju, this is a gift for you.
Uncle, you're dreaming, right?
This is a gift.
Yu Xiao Ju, I'm here to cheer you on.
I know that the people who listen to my story
are very good at singing.
I heard that many people in the Tiantang Routine Club
hope that everyone
can help me to get out of this little hope.
Xiao Ju said
she wants to go to see this world.
Let's do it again.
What?
She said she would go to see the show.
But she may not be able to wait.
So I hope that
everyone can
help me
to get out of this little hope.
She's nine years old.
Uncle, how did you do this?
Because everyone is asking you
to cheer me on.
Uncle.
Where do you want to go now?
My mom will pick you up.
Then?
We'll pick up the most favorite characters
and then we'll keep shooting them until the end of the world.
I've been taking medicine for two years.
I've been working hard.
I've been having a little bit of a hangover
and I'm not done with the story.
The game is over.
It's almost over.
Hello.
Hello, how are you?
I'm fine.
I'll get you some water.
Here you go.
I'll get you some salt water.
Salt water?
I want a small piece of noodles.
A small piece of noodles?
The End
What are you doing?
As long as I can eat this,
I can go to another world.
I'm done.
The End
You can't find me.
Uncle,
I'm going to make a book.
This diary
is for you.
Actually,
when I saw you wanted to commit suicide,
I was so angry with you.
I thought
you were so hard to deal with
when you wanted to commit suicide.
I thought
you were so hard to deal with
when you were born.
But I still want to save you.
Because
you're alive.
Uncle,
you look like you're easily deceived.
I wanted to go,
so I lied to you.
I'm going to find my father.
In this way,
you'll have things to do.
You won't commit suicide.
Uncle,
you're not a fool.
You're just a little silly.
But I'm happy
to be with you.
I lied to you.
Don't be angry.
Uncle,
you have to live well.
Live well.
I can't stop doing something for you.
Even you think it's all yours.
If you can't live on,
you can't find out
what life will return to you.
The life between men
and women,
that's why I'm here.
I'm here to help you.
The life between men is endless.
That's why I'm here.
It's endless.
Why should people live?
Because people
are not just for themselves.
Uncle,
I'm here to see if we can be together.
you're a grown-up.
Don't ever come back.
You're not a fast food.
You should open your own restaurant.
You're right.
I'll listen to you.
Thank you.
For telling me this story.
You are the desert plan.
Where the world
horses run.
I want you to know
you're the first thought.
the grace you're made of.
I want you to feel
that you're mine and dear.
And I want you to know.
By the way,
Uncle,
are you still listening?
Can you promise me one thing?
I promise.
Can I call you
my father?
I want you to know
you're the first thought.
the grace you're made of.
I want you to feel
that you're mine and dear.
What a story.
I want you to feel that you're mine, dear
Whoa-oh
And I want you to know
I want you to know
I wanted to say it
I don't want any more
I don't want to be mean anymore
I want to say
Like a child, no need to be sad
But it's hard to be sad
As time goes by, I'm like a child
If I'm already hurt
I'll say my love will be forgotten
Hello
This is for you
The name of the flower is Wanyou
She said time is fierce
Like water on the river
Don't go far, I'll go home
Ah
When we were in the old days
We would come back to the childhood
To love and love and love
You don't need to drink
The clothes that are worn out
Hold that hand
Hold the smile when you see the warmth
When we were in the water
Like a child, no need to be sad
In the dream, make a dream
I saw you, I was old
That swimming pool was not a lie
There was no umbrella
This love is just a fire in another world
If we meet again
Open a new space
Every dream is just a chariot of time and space
You and I will be together
Please help me to love the universe
Wanyou, open the flower
You are not talking in the moonlight
The regret is like a clouds falling
I am willing to float in the deep of the earth
Translated by Releska