ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
-My lord, it is not what you think.
-Come outside.
Let me explain.
Come outside right now!
That feels nice.
I feel refreshed
now that my hair is clean.
-I feel great.
-My gosh.
That was nice, was it not?
Yes, it was.
Lady Kim.
Yes.
I was just about to go to bed.
-Come out for a moment.
-Is he nuts?
We need to give you something.
My goodness, we are practically a family.
-I will kill him.
-We can just
go inside ourselves.
You are right. Let us go inside.
Lady Kim, we are going in.
No, I will be right out. Just a minute.
Did Dong-ju come home?
She was outside all day.
Yes, she came home. She is sleeping.
We brought you some calamus.
You and Dong-ju should
wash each other's hair tomorrow
-and make up with each other.
-Okay, we will.
Why fight over a man?
It is all useless, Lady Kim.
I apologize for what happened.
You must all be tired.
You should get some sleep.
What? No, we are not tired at all.
No, you should go.
Go to your rooms and sleep.
-We are fine.
-My goodness.
-Dong-ju is fast asleep.
-But...
My goodness.
So that is why you let him hide the fact
that he is a man?
Yes.
He will be gone soon,
so please do not tell anyone.
Do us a favor.
Then why...
-Why were you two--
-It was an accident.
-He slipped.
-You expect me to believe that?
-I trust you, but not him.
-It was not an accident.
Be quiet.
I know you think him
as a reckless and shameless fool.
-Hey.
-But
he does not mean any harm,
so do not worry.
Are you worried about him?
If people find out he is a man,
I will also get in trouble
for helping him.
I am worried about myself.
So please do not tell anyone
and just leave.
If you stay, it will put us in danger.
I resent you.
You know very well
I cannot say "no" to you.
-Follow me.
-What are you doing?
Then are you going to sleep with her
in the same room?
That is up to us to decide.
Stop it.
I will sleep at the kisaeng house tonight.
-Wait a second.
-Darn it.
Wear this.
Hurry.
He does not have a mistress whom he loves?
Gosh, whatever.
How can we sleep with the lights on?
My goodness, you startled me.
-About--
-I will kill you if you mention the kiss.
-Then who--
-And do not ask me whom I like.
-Then what--
-And stop asking about the cough.
You keep saying things
I do not understand.
Will you please let me talk?
Why are you not asking me anything?
I told you I do not have a mistress
whom I love.
I lied to you.
The woman I met in Hanyang--
Forget it. I am not curious.
Why not? Why are you not curious?
Because unlike what you think,
I do not have feelings for you.
-You are lying.
-No, I am not.
Hey.
Are you angry that I kissed you
without your consent?
No.
That is no big deal. It was just a kiss.
You are being so harsh.
I felt it. I bet you also felt--
You have never dated anyone
in your entire life, have you?
What?
Yes, I have. You are wrong.
I have dated tons of women
back in my hometown.
What are you talking about?
Yes, I am sure you have dated
a lot of women.
-In your dreams.
-You little...
It explains why you are
being delusional and absurd.
"Delusional and absurd"?
Yes. Now, if you got the message,
stop bothering me.
I came to tell you this.
She thinks I am a bother?
Please!
Let me see my mother!
Once I exit that gate, I will never
be able to see my mother again!
So please...
Mother!
Mother.
-Mother!
-Your Highness!
Your Highness!
No!
Did he not cry a lot?
He became calm after passing the gate.
I heard many people wailed
for my poor brother.
I wonder if they did the same
when I went through all those hardships.
I wailed for you, Your Majesty.
Yes, you were the only one.
Even my own father
did not acknowledge me as worthy.
And he even left behind a brutal will.
If you had not
gotten rid of it beforehand,
the throne would not have been mine.
Therefore,
you are the one person
I trust unconditionally.
Do you know that, Yun?
I am
extremely grateful, Your Majesty.
A secret letter written by the late king.
So the rumors were true.
They why did you not make a move earlier?
6 YEARS AGO
His Majesty took the throne
very unexpectedly,
and the Grand Prince was too young.
So we were waiting for the right moment.
However, you were one step ahead of us.
You will get punished for treason.
There will come a day
when you utterly regret
taking that letter from me.
You are...
He is His Majesty's firstborn son.
He is growing up to be
a smart and honest man.
Now that His Majesty has taken the throne,
it is time to take him back
to where he belongs.
-No, that cannot happen.
-Why?
He has become the King.
So there is no reason for His Majesty
to be nervous anymore.
DETHRONE THE CROWN PRINCE
AND MAKE GRAND PRINCE YEONGCHANG
THE NEW CROWN PRINCE
What is this?
Today, I punished the man
who hid this letter.
So what do you think?
Do you think His Majesty does not need
to be worried anymore?
I cannot believe this.
And we do not know why His Majesty
made such a decision that day.
His Majesty may have taken the throne,
but what if that does not solve anything?
Then you, me, and that kid
might end up dead.
So do not get your hopes up
and just go back to your hideout.
If you show up before me one more time,
I will not be able to show mercy.
My lord.
What do you mean Yun-jeo disappeared?
The Muwol Corps standing guard
are all dead.
Find him. Find him no matter what.
Did you bring the dead bodies
of the Muwol Corps that were there?
No.
The dead body inside
was found at the widow village.
There were signs of torture.
The man who hid near the widow village
probably killed her
and ran away to Hanyang.
What if he found something
by torturing her?
I want you to quietly find the boy
and gather the Muwol Corps.
Let us get rid of the local functionary
and bring back the Grand Prince.
Yes, my lord.
You found the boss?
Not exactly, but I think I can guess
who the boss is.
Then wait until the boss shows up
and beat the living soul out of him.
It is not that simple.
He talked about the island,
so it has to be him.
Yes?
But I think he is getting orders
from someone else.
Who is that darn fellow?
Let us teach that guy a lesson, too.
-The King.
-What?
"The King"?
The King of Joseon?
His Majesty?
-Yes.
-Watch what you say!
I know it is difficult to stay here
dressed like a woman.
But do not talk nonsense
with a straight face like that.
It hurts me to see you go crazy.
I know it does not make sense.
But
what if my father is
actually acquainted with His Majesty?
What if he is an aristocrat?
What if he was living on that island
because he did something bad?
And what if I am only stirring things up?
Something bad?
Treason?
"Treason"? My father?
No.
No, it cannot be.
My mother told me
that it was because of me.
No, you are probably mistaken.
Your father would never plot treason.
He is the most honest man alive.
He would never.
Anyway, I should not do anything rash.
So I will look into it more.
Yes, it is important to be sure.
By the way,
your eyes are swollen.
You look like a guy who got heartbroken
and cried all night.
-My gosh, that is nonsense.
-Let me see.
Master, where is Aeng-du?
I have not seen her since last night.
Aeng-du?
She keeps saying things I do not get
and will not stop crying.
I forgot to call him my sister.
I totally forgot.
I should have called him my sister.
He is my sister! He is my older sister!
-Yesterday, I was--
-That is enough.
Did you beat him?
Did you beat him already?
Is my brother dead?
Then beat me, too! Do the same to me!
Are you sure?
Okay, fine. Let us go now.
Oh, my goodness! Father!
Father, I am going to die! Father!
Father!
Where in the world is Aeng-du?
She is nowhere to be seen.
Where are you going?
-Off to work.
-To do laundry?
I guess not.
I will be working in the kitchen
at the kisaeng house starting today.
Father.
Are you not going to beat me?
If you are gone,
who will be here to taste my food?
Then what about my brother...
I mean, my sister?
There are two ladies
whom he is trying to protect.
So I decided not to beat him up for now.
Instead, will you do me a favor?
First, go ahead and fill your stomach.
I will ask you once you are full.
Gosh.
Do not go.
You know nothing
about working in the kitchen.
Do you not know why he wants you
to work in the kitchen? It is obvious.
You are so naive.
So he could separate the two of us.
I guess you know.
So do not go.
I need to pay you back my debt.
I will give you a discount. Do not go.
I told you to stop being so clingy!
No, I am going to be clingy.
-What?
-You said you do not like me.
And I am fine with that.
But you see,
I will make you like me.
So do not go to him.
How are you going to do that?
Hey!
What is the matter with you?
You are making me feel very uncomfortable,
so just go.
Go on.
I will do as you asked
and act like I do not know anything
for your sake.
But are you going to keep
sleeping in the same room?
What do you take me for?
The little kid is staying with us,
so stop asking me that.
You are worried for nothing.
Okay.
But I have a question.
You said you like someone.
I heard you loud and clear.
So tell me.
Is it him that you like?
Of course not. I have eyes, too.
Yes, of course.
He is not a likable fellow.
Then...
Is it...
Is it me?
No.
I just got drunk
and said something I did not mean.
You did not have to deny it so strongly.
Gosh.
I might as well just beat that weasel up.
Darn it.
Hey, sister. What are you doing?
Gosh, you startled me.
Were you badmouthing my sweet Lord Cha?
What?
"My sweet Lord Cha"?
I am sorry about how things turned out.
I really could not help myself.
Aeng-du.
What are you talking about?
I thought about it.
When you get married,
you have to eat with your spouse
three times a day until death do you part.
And if that is the case,
I figured he would be a better choice.
I apologize.
Hey, Aeng-du.
He is well-built, so kind.
He is always smiling at me.
He exactly is the kind of man
that Dong-ju told me I would find.
There is no doubt about it.
Gosh, that little...
My gosh, Lord Yeon.
My goodness.
No, wait.
-That is sweet.
-Let me pour you another glass.
So are you telling me
that you are like a father to Lady Kim?
Yes, of course.
I practically raised her myself.
Master. I mean, Father.
Will you please help me?
I am willing to do anything
to win Lady Kim's heart.
My goodness, really?
Let me go first.
I am a professional
when it comes to wooing women.
But of course,
that is only the case
when the other person is a woman.
Anyway,
the secret to winning a woman's heart...
-The secret?
-What is it?
What is the secret? Oh, gosh.
This is embarrassing.
You need to be indifferent
but kind at the same time.
That is the secret. Let me explain.
For example, when you help her
with something,
say, "You cannot even do this?
You might as well
just go and kill yourself!"
And then,
help her as if you have no other choice.
My goodness.
Just go kill yourself
if you cannot carry this yourself!
What?
Gosh, it is okay. What are you doing?
I will do it myself.
I am helping
because I have no other choice.
My goodness. Hey!
-Who taught you this nonsense?
-It is not nonsense.
It will make you think of me at night.
I am indifferent yet kind.
You will find me attractive.
-Goodness.
-My gosh.
What is with that look?
You said you do not like me.
What? How did I look at you?
Like this.
Where are you going?
It is none of your business.
Do not be late.
Come home for dinner, okay?
Do you hear me?
My goodness,
she never listens to her mother.
You think we should use
the magistrate of Ganghwa Island?
Will the people not oppose?
Many people still care
about the Grand Prince.
We will not give them a reason to rebel.
So do not worry, Your Majesty.
And
it will be better for us
if people cause a fuss.
It will be a chance for me to find out
who could possibly betray me.
Lee In-woo, the local functionary,
is the one who sent
the Grand Prince into exile.
Tomorrow, his father is having
his 60th birthday party.
I heard he only invited
family and close relatives.
He must have been worried
that there might be killers
among the guests.
But he will never expect them to be
the working ladies there.
A total of seven including me
and Jeong-suk will head to Hanyang.
And once we are done,
we will ask around about Deul-re.
Okay. Then should I follow the rest
to Ganghwa Island?
Please let the others know.
Okay.
My goodness, the entire Muwol Corps
will be out of the village.
He is a better choice?
I cannot believe...
Cha Yul-mu, that jerk.
She likes food better than me.
Are you going somewhere far away?
Someone is holding
a huge 60th birthday party in Hanyang.
And we are going to make a scene.
Hanyang? Let me help you ladies.
No, it is an important and dangerous task.
Hanyang is in a mess right now.
His Majesty apparently sent
to Ganghwa Island--
You brat. You talk too much.
What did His Majesty do?
You do not need to know.
Take care.
Have a safe trip.
Ganghwa Island and his Majesty?
I got a letter saying the Muwol Corps
are on their way.
Is everything ready?
Yes, my lord.
Lord Lee's family is busy
getting ready for the party,
so it will not be hard to blend in.
Okay.
You must be up to something again.
Long time no see.
You...
Your Majesty, what brings you here
all of a sudden?
I told you to call me "Lord"
outside the palace.
Is he inside?
Yes, he is taking a rest.
Is that so?
Then
let me surprise him.
Where are my sons?
That is what I want to ask you.
Where is your son?
I mean, where is His Majesty's son?
What is up with you all of a sudden?
We lived like we did not exist,
just as you asked.
Then you never should have
caught anyone's eye.
-My lord.
-Is he not alone?
Your Majesty.
How about a game of chess?
Sure, Your Majesty.
All the entrances are blocked.
Follow me.
Mother.
I finished making it.
I can finally leave now.
Yes, I should leave.
I was going to leave
as soon as I finished making this anyway.
Gosh, the rice is getting cold.
Why is she not coming home?
Do you really think she would
come home for this food?
What do you mean?
Lord Cha already fed her
all sorts of good food.
Today, he made rice cakes
and ginger cookies.
What did I tell you?
If a woman has to choose a husband,
he is a much better candidate
than you are.
Gosh, I might as well just...
Are you not going to eat?
I already ate.
It is your loss if you do not eat.
What goes through your mind
when you cook in the kitchen?
Normally, nothing is on my mind.
But I was very happy when I made this.
Why is that?
Because I was with the woman I love.
Is she a kisaeng?
Yes, she is, Your Majesty.
You have a lot of free time.
I envy your life, my cousin.
Do not try to covet it.
I also enjoy my life very much,
Your Majesty.
Did you see anyone suspicious?
We checked everyone,
but no one seemed suspicious.
Do not let your guard down.
Check every single man
who enters this house.
Yes, my lord.
I will get going first.
You go and borrow a horse
from the kisaeng house and follow me.
Yes, my lord.
Hello.
Is this the famous Yeonhwa House?
Yes, welcome.
-Is this your first time?
-Yes.
I am the magistrate of Ganghwa Island.
And I was on my way to Hanyang
for a party.
But I was told this place is famous,
-"Ganghwa Island"?
-so I dropped by.
Thank you for stopping by.
Please come this way.
-This way.
-By the way,
I heard there is a kisaeng
named Mae Hwa-su.
Yes.
His Majesty banished his little brother.
And he ended up in Ganghwa Island.
His Majesty is so cruel.
My goodness, do not say that.
Thanks to that,
I got the chance to be promoted.
What does His Majesty's brother
living in exile
have anything to do with your promotion?
You see, there is a party in Hanyang...
Never mind.
Just know that something great
is going to happen.
What does he mean?
This way?
My goodness, I am so tired.
Are you going to start a business?
There are already merchants
who have long been delivering items
to the court ladies.
So it will not be easy.
No.
I only asked
because someone wanted to know.
My goodness.
Gosh, that feels nice.
Who are you?
You need to talk
about that party in Hanyang.
I cannot tell you.
Never.
Even if your life is at risk?
Mother.
Mother?
My goodness!
He is a pervert! Gather some people!
Oh, okay.
My goodness. Oh, gosh!
My gosh.
Madam Chun! I am the magistrate
of Ganghwa Island.
And this widow is trying to kill me.
He put a knife to my throat.
I was just...
Well...
Tell me why you are going to Hanyang.
Spare no details.
I cannot believe he called
the magistrate of Ganghwa Island
to kill his little brother in exile.
So you are the boss?
The boss of Muwol Corps?
I will explain after you come back.
This is very urgent.
Once you find Ssuk,
have her withdraw everyone
and tell her to go to the temple
where Lord Lee is hiding.
Tell her we fell into a trap.
Okay, do not worry.
There needs to be some noise
to get the job done.
But why is it so quiet?
Something feels wrong.
-We should withdraw.
-What are you talking about?
No way.
The women are the killers! Arrest them!
Kill everyone who saw us.
It is hot!
-Lady Kim?
-Madam Chun sent me here.
She did? Why?
She wanted me to warn you
that this will happen.
Lord Lee is hiding at a temple
in Inwang Mountain.
What?
-Can you find the way?
-Me?
I cannot leave you here.
This place is too dangerous for you.
We will go as soon as we are done,
so try to keep him there.
Okay.
It will be no fun to just buy time.
My goodness.
You should go back.
This is a restricted area.
If that is the case,
then you should have been more careful.
What?
Did we kill everyone?
I did not see anyone escape.
Let us go. We do not know
how long Lady Kim can stall.
Why do you do this?
What?
Why do you do something so dangerous
when you are free to live a normal life?
Do you all need money like me?
Most of us live by ourselves in hiding,
so why would we need money?
Then what for?
Because we are the only ones
who can live such comfortable lives.
What?
My in-laws punished me
for not dying after my husband.
He died three days after we got married.
If I had not escape back then,
I would have died after a husband
whom I just married.
But this is nothing
compared to the others.
Are you okay?
We are able to live comfortable lives
thanks to Madam Chun.
But widows outside the village
still are treated very harshly.
You surely know that yourself.
-Yes.
-We started out
by secretly helping widows in need.
Because no one else would step up
to help a widow who lost her husband.
Then did you kill Lord Lee
because he harmed the widows?
No.
But we did it to make a better world
for people who have no power like us.
That is what I believe.
We made sure Lee In-woo was dead
and made it seem like he died from a fall.
You did great.
We would not have succeeded...
if it were not for Lady Kim.
I made you a promise,
so I guess we can no longer
delay your admittance.
Welcome to the Muwol Corps, Lady Kim.
Jeong-suk is waiting for you outside.
She will explain in detail.
Meanwhile, the two of us
need to talk in private.
Okay, I will leave then.
Is there a problem?
He is not just some homeless scamp.
He is the magistrate of Ganghwa Island.
He cannot be a pervert.
Besides, those two are
nowhere to be found.
He did not come home?
No.
So there is nothing to tell you
about Nok-du and Dong-ju.
But why are you so tired?
My goodness.
Dong-ju kept wandering around all night
instead of going to bed.
So I could not sleep properly either.
Dong-ju did?
Yes. She constantly sighed,
opened the door to check outside,
and walked around out in the yard.
Then she kept saying this.
"How dare he sleep outside?
How dare he not come home
without even telling me?"
That is right.
We make wine here
and sell it to the kisaeng house.
And the money we make from that
is used for the Muwol Corps
and the widows.
It is a very beautiful story.
You did great today. You can go.
Let her stand guard with us tonight.
No, not tonight.
It is too early to overwork yourself.
Get some rest.
Okay.
Oh my goodness.
Is it you?
Dong-ju.
My lord.
-You cannot come in here.
-Yes, I can.
I am allowed to.
Pardon?
We got rid of Lee In-woo,
but this is just the beginning.
His Majesty might be thinking
that there are people who are in support
of the Grand Prince.
Do you think His Highness will be safe?
I sent someone to bring His Highness here.
-Are you saying--
-Tomorrow.
We will carry out our mission tomorrow.
WIDOW VILLAGE, MEN FORBIDDEN
We are prepared for everything.
But His Majesty is very insecure
right now. Must we do it now?
What if we keep delaying it
and end up failing to accomplish
our mission?
You are right.
It might be the perfect timing
when there are plenty of distractions.
-There is no need to wait. Let us hurry--
-Do not bother.
There is no need to hurry.
-What in the world--
-Oh, right.
I also took care of what was urgent.
Once I exit that gate, I will never
be able to see my mother again!
So please...
-Is there no one outside?
-There are people outside.
But they are all my people.
What do you say?
Should I ask them to come inside?
What have you done to the Grand Prince?
I killed him.
Are you really
going to keep your promise?
Of course.
Your job...
begins now.
Mother.
How dare you!
-It is me.
-Hey.
Do you know how long I waited for you?
Let us go outside.
Hey.
Why are you not looking at me?
What are you talking about?
Go on. Stay somewhere bright.
Why are you not coming with me?
I will explain that next time.
The guest at the kisaeng house...
He was not a pervert, was he?
Where did you suddenly disappear to?
Why did you come...
to the widow village?
I will also explain that next time.
I really do not want to cause a fuss.
Prince Neungyang!
PRINCE NEUNGYANG,
LATER ON BECOMES KING INJO
There is no need to complicate things.
Instead of the young and foolish
Grand Prince Yeongchang,
you can use me instead.
Make me become the king.
That is the only thing that has changed.
Did you think I would feel threatened
by some cheap blackmail?
My goodness, that is not what this is.
If I wanted to threaten you,
I would have done a lot more.
Today,
I just came to say hello.
You say you want to become the king.
But do you think you have what it takes?
A kisaeng house
that financially supports a widow village?
Bring me the madam
and all the widows who are close to her.
If I were the King's son,
I at least would not have gotten upset
that I had to stay hidden
throughout my entire life.
I heard you joined the Muwol Corps.
And I heard you are planning treason.
THE WAR
Everyone in the Muwol Corps must
leave the village tomorrow night.
Then would it not matter if I kill him?
BEGINS
I will not ask you to like me.
Just do not disappear.
Please.