IN THE SOOP: FRIENDCATION
(theme music)
HYBE HEADQUARTERS
V: This is nice.
Hey, you're here.
CHOI WOOSHIK
PARK HYUNGSIK
(V exclaims)
V
-(V exclaims)
-(laughing)
HYUNGSIK: Yo, yo.
PEAKBOY
-PRODUCER: Hello.
-SEOJUN: I arrived the latest.
(plastic rustles)
-SEOJUN: What's all this?
-PEAKBOY: There's so much.
-HYUNGSIK: I know.
-(Wooshik laughs)
THEIR FRIENDSHIP STARTED
THROUGH SEOJUN IN 2018
(all singing)
(upbeat music playing)
ARE FUN WHEN THEY'RE TOGETHER
THESE FIVE FRIENDS
ARE MORE THAN JUST FAMILY
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THREE YEARS,
THEY GO ON A WINTER TRIP
SEOJUN: How did it end up like this?
-I haven't even shaved.
-(laughter)
This is insane.
To put it into more detail,
-it might have seemed a little annoying...
-STAFF: Yes.
...but I think it has been
delivered very clearly.
Back then, the car was--
You told us clearly
that we can just do it.
So I asked him what we're actually doing.
I already told you everything, but...
-We went over this last time.
-Yes.
Yes, but it wasn't like this.
Yes, but I didn't know much about it,
so I just said we should give it a try.
"LET'S GIVE IT A TRY"
That's how it ended up like this.
Anyway, I do strongly feel
like I have been tricked into this.
How can you eat right now?
I'm so hungry though.
-This is good.
-Eat first, then.
I hope it'll go well.
This has been organized
off the cuff, hasn't it?
THE STAFF RECEIVED A CALL FROM V ON MONDAY
AFTER AN EMERGENCY MEETING
THEY GOT A FILM CREW READY,
WENT SCOUTING ON TUESDAY,
AND ORGANIZED THIS MEETING FOR WEDNESDAY
-So this is going to be a proper thing.
-STAFF: Yes.
On this show, this guy is going to...
You'll look really pitiful. Is that okay?
Can we destroy him?
-Destroy him?
-You'll have to retire, then.
I'm okay with showing myself.
SEOJUN: You'll really regret it.
-He does seem rather startled.
-Even on typical days...
We're still shooting a show, aren't we?
(laughter)
I thought we were only
filming a montage up until today.
Let's only show people
how well we get along on this show.
(laughter)
Let's just be mindful of that
for the camera.
Let's get along.
You can count on me.
So this is for three nights and four days?
And first of all,
Hyungsik is only available for two days.
I arrive on the morning of the 10th.
After arriving on the 10th?
And I'll stay until the night of the 11th.
HE'LL JOIN ON THE SECOND DAY
Ah... Timeout. I can only go
after my plans on the ninth.
-You'll arrive at night too?
-Yeah.
-At night?
Then, shall we leave first?
-Let's get there first, then.
-Sure.
The three of us will go first.
Okay, I'll be there soon on the ninth.
-I'll head over as soon as I'm done too.
-Mm.
I didn't know it would go this far.
I know.
But...
I do think it'll be fun.
-SEOJUN: Of course.
-Yes, I think it'll be fun.
I just
really wanted to make memories.
Sure. Since it's already come to this,
let's do it.
So do we just act like we're hanging out?
Not acting. We are hanging out.
-Okay, then.
-(claps)
You know,
this is the first time we got together
after Wooshik's fanmeet.
How long has it been
-since I've seen you, Peakboy?
-SEOJUN: He has been so busy.
No, I'm not busy.
Oh.
Then that doesn't make sense.
You haven't been seeing us on purpose?
No, I was busy.
You're an opportunist.
(laughs)
Anyway, let's give it our best.
Let's do this.
We need to think about what we'll do.
Then, let's spend time staring at the fire
-every day.
-I can do that.
-I can do that every day too. I love that.
-I want to stare at the fire.
It'll be nice to keep it going
since it's cold.
-Staring at the fire.
-That's the best.
Fishing. Let's go fishing.
-Barbecue.
-What about ice skating?
-That sounds great.
I don't know how to inline skate,
but I can ice skate a bit.
Really? Is that why you recommended it?
-Congratulations.
-Since he wants to go ice skating...
-Yes. Show us how you ice skate.
-Do whatever you want, V.
-Yes. Let's try it there.
It's not that I want to show you.
It isn't that I'm greedy
for more screen time,
-but it'd be fun to go together.
-It would.
-Of course.
-Sure.
(sucks teeth)
Mmm...
-Do we have to cook all our meals?
-Let's do it.
-We can do it.
-Sure, we can make our own meals.
-That would be nice.
-Yes, let's give that a try then.
-We should prepare.
-Isn't it good?
-This one is really good.
-When is it again?
The day after tomorrow?
-The day after tomorrow?
-No.
-No?
-It's in three days.
If I had known it would be like this,
I would've had my hair and makeup done.
-Hey.
-Jeez.
(abrupt laughter)
Won't everyone be
wearing their own clothes?
Your stylists won't be
packing for you, right?
Of course not. That's too much.
Let's not go that far.
But I'll be the most dressed up.
Everyone will be...
-Gosh. What am I going to wear?
-You have a lot of clothes.
Dress like this.
-All I need is some sweatpants.
-Wooshik, want me to buy you a mannequin?
-A mannequin?
-Yes.
-You can style it up.
-And dress it up?
I have to dress up based on a lookbook.
-The top and bottom have to be one look?
-Right.
Should we all get matching pajamas?
-Let's do that.
-Let's get a uniform.
-For indoors?
-Yes.
We don't have enough time though.
-Let's order online.
-Yeah, order it,
and we'll get it by tomorrow.
-(laughter)
-Get one that has express delivery.
All right. Then I'm going to quickly plan
on how I'm going to act.
I'm going to write it down on paper today.
"What I should be careful of
and what I can do."
I should write stuff down too.
"What I need to stop."
-Protect...
-(laughs)
-"What has to be protected."
(laughter)
-This is going to be fun.
-I know.
-HYUNGSIK: It's okay.
-V: Okay, let's do this.
-Put them in.
-PEAKBOY: Want us to put them in? Sure.
-We'll grant your wish.
-(laughter)
SEOJUN:
You can't do things like this, okay?
Let's be cool about it.
(clears throat)
-PEAKBOY: Let's see the plans later.
-You did it for him in the end.
THE EMERGENCY MEETING ENDS
PEAKBOY: Good job.
V: We got this, guys.
-Okay.
-ALL: Okay.
-HYUNGSIK: Okay, bye.
WINTER OF 2022
GANGWON-DO, GOSEONG
FOR 3 NIGHTS AND 4 DAYS
IT'S A REAL FRIENDCATION
SEOJUN, THE EMOTIONAL ANCHOR "DAD"
WOOSHIK: He's the one
we depend on mentally.
PEAKBOY, THE WILD "YOUNGEST DAUGHTER"
He's always pumped up.
WOOSHIK, THE TRUSTWORTHY "ELDEST SON"
HYUNGSIK: He's a leader
to the younger guys.
HYUNGSIK, THE KIND "MOM"
WOOSHIK: He's a bit gentler than the dad.
V, THE CUTE "YOUNGEST SIBLING"
V's our mischievous youngest son.
THEY EAT TOGETHER
WASH TOGETHER
SLEEP TOGETHER
THEY RECORD EVERY MOMENT
THEY SPEND TOGETHER ON THE TRIP
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE GOING BACK
TO OUR CHILDHOOD
V: I didn't imagine I would be the worst,
but I guess I am.
ALL: Whoa!
EVEN DURING UNEXPECTED MOMENTS
-PEAKBOY: Can we go home?
-WOOSHIK: I'm sorry!
THEY'RE HAPPY BECAUSE THEY'RE TOGETHER
THEIR EVENTFUL 3 NIGHTS AND 4 DAYS
NEVER BEEN REVEALED BEFORE
Anyway, you introduced those two.
Why did you do that?
THE TRUE STORY OF OUR FRIENDSHIP
WE ARE HAPPIER TODAY THAN YESTERDAY
AND TOMORROW MORE THAN TODAY
(all laughing)
-WOOSHIK: V, are you crying?
-V: No.
WOOSHIK: Are you crying, V?
V SUDDENLY CRIES
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
IT STARTS NOW
EPISODE 1. A SUDDEN TRIP
FRIENDCATION
D-DAY
(soft upbeat music)
(grunts)
V: I told you not to wear shoe lifts.
-PEAKBOY: This?
-V: I told you not to wear those.
PEAKBOY: It came with it.
Everyone is dressed up.
I thought you'd wear sweatpants.
-SEOJUN: I did.
-V: I did.
SEOJUN: What is this then?
PEAKBOY:
I should've worn cool sweatpants too.
(grunts)
PEAKBOY: It's heavy.
(sighs)
V: You should pull out the car a little.
-V: I'll be the DJ for today.
-SEOJUN: Okay.
-SEOJUN: Here we go!
-PEAKBOY: Okay!
V: Okay!
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
-Okay.
SEOJUN: It isn't my car, guys.
V: Okay. Let's drive safely.
SEOJUN: Let's just go!
SEOJUN, PEAKBOY AND V
OFF TO GOSEONG
SEOJUN: Gosh, I can't believe we're going
to Gangwon-do together.
-It's our New Year's party.
-New Year's party?
A New Year's trip.
When did you guys pack?
-Early in the morning.
-This morning.
I packed this morning too.
But I forgot my Bluetooth speaker.
-Wouldn't they have a stereo there?
-I think so.
-We need to have music.
-V: Exactly.
-You wore shoes today, V.
-V: Yeah.
-What has gotten into you?
-You told me to wear shoes.
-I heard it's very cold.
-It'll be cold.
SEOJUN: Did you guys get some sleep?
-I think I slept about three hours.
-Me too.
I think I slept
about three, four hours too.
The micro-dust level is really bad today.
I bet the air in Gangwon-do will be nice.
I'm sure they'll use CG
to make the weather look nice.
(chuckles)
-Makguksu sounds great.
-V: Makguksu.
I want some with suyuk.
Seojun and I talked about
makguksu a lot yesterday.
-I'm only going to eat a little.
-V: What?
-PEAKBOY: I'm going to eat a little.
-Since you're working out?
Good one.
-(V laughing)
-I'm working out,
and I should take care of myself too.
(laughs)
-You should.
-Yes, you should.
V: It really does feel different.
I've always traveled with my members.
I was so worried about
whether we could really go or not.
When you went with your members,
did you go by car like this?
Yes, us too. We drove as well.
V: It has been so long
since we've been on a trip.
-SEOJUN: Right.
-V: Has it been three years or two?
-Has it been that long?
-V: As a group,
we went before Hyungsik went
to serve in the military.
-PEAKBOY: That's right.
-It was that one time.
It was only that one time.
Even at Wooshik's fanmeet,
Hyungsik couldn't join
due to his schedule.
Actually, the reason why we mentioned
going on a trip together
-was all because of Hyungsik.
-That's right.
Since he has been discharged
from the army, he should be having fun.
V, can we have some music
that's more upbeat?
Okay. Then should I play
some Korean pop ballads?
DJ V PICKS SOME NEW SONGS
(soft guitar music)
-PEAKBOY: Is it playing?
-No.
I'm picking some out.
(both exclaim)
"LIE" BY ENAN
"Don't go."
This song was so popular
when I was in high school.
Ah...
-I sang this a lot at karaoke.
-I'm reminiscing now.
"Baby."
-"Baby, let's go."
-Yes, we sang this song a lot.
-Did you watch this drama?
-V: Lovers of Paris?
-Yes.
-I did.
-Weren't you in elementary school?
-V: Maybe middle school?
Really?
-Our first year of high school?
-V: Didn't this come out around 2004?
-It was when I was in high school.
-V: Really?
Then I was in elementary school.
You know what's funny?
It would be weird for a grade schooler
to hang out with a high schooler.
-Right.
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
How dare you try to join us?
(chuckles)
Then do you know the drama
Sangdoo, Let's Go to School?
-SEOJUN: I do.
-Of course, I know that drama.
I personally loved I'm Sorry, I Love You.
(groans)
♪ I loved you ♪
Iris.
V: No!
(chuckles)
No!
(V groans)
(chuckling)
PEAKBOY: Guys, Peakboy
is starting to get hungry.
I'm sorry. I'm hungry.
SEOJUN: First of all,
-I do think we have to get some groceries.
-V: We should.
SEOJUN: What do you want for dinner?
-Dinner?
-Shall we buy some steak and grill them?
-V: Yes.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
STEAK FOR DINNER
V: This is the best last song.
♪ So I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million tiny things that ♪
♪ You have never known ♪
THEY LOOK OUT THE WINDOW FOR A LONG TIME
♪ It all gets tangled up inside ♪
♪ And I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million little reasons ♪
PEAKBOY: Wow, it's the ocean.
THE WINTER SEA APPEARS
SEOJUN: It's the ocean.
♪ I just want to be where you are ♪
PEAKBOY: We're here.
V: Yes, we are.
PEAKBOY: Makguksu.
ARRIVAL AT THE MAKGUKSU PLACE
-PEAKBOY: Thank you for driving.
-SEOJUN: No worries.
V: Wow, wow!
Get up.
-SEOJUN: Let's go.
-V: Let's go.
-PEAKBOY: Hello.
-WOMAN: Welcome.
SEOJUN: What should we order? Hang on.
V: Their most famous dishes
are potato pancakes and suyuk.
PEAKBOY: Suyuk.
-SEOJUN: Makguksu.
-V: We have to get suyuk.
-Should we order one makguksu?
-V: What?
SEOJUN: One makguksu.
One suyuk, one potato pancake.
V: The noodle portions
are smaller than you think.
SEOJUN: Let's get double portions.
We can just order more later.
-V: Then, let's get two makguksu.
-SEOJUN: Let's get two.
THEY ORDER 2 MAKGUKSU IN THE END
-Thank you.
-WOMAN: Thank you.
Should we get a raw fish makguksu
and one regular makguksu then?
V: Yes.
-WOMAN: If you need more, let us know.
-PEAKBOY: Thank you.
SEOJUN: Buckwheat dumplings.
-Enjoy.
THEIR FIRST MEAL AT GOSEONG
V: It's our first meal here.
(chomping)
-Mmm.
Mmm.
Oh.
I was so hungry.
(gasps)
-Thank you.
-WOMAN: We just boiled these.
It's good.
SEOJUN: Is this the spicy raw pollack?
-Let me try.
-(slurps)
-Mmm. Mm-hm.
-Mmm.
SEOJUN: This is good.
Hyungsik would love this.
-This is really good.
-SEOJUN: Mm.
V: Mm.
(crunches)
(indistinct chatter)
SEOJUN: It has been so long
since I last ate out.
Mm.
-Can I have this dumpling?
-V: Go ahead.
-WOMAN: It's the potato pancake.
-SEOJUN: Have it.
The potato pancake is good.
Mm.
Mmm.
SEOJUN: We're eating all of it.
I told you we would.
We're absolutely no joke.
WOMAN: Who ordered
the raw fish makguksu?
PEAKBOY:
Just put it in the middle, please.
This is makguksu
and that's raw fish makguksu, right?
"Put one ladle of dongchimi in it."
-One ladle?
-Yes.
Okay.
PEAKBOY: "Add one or two spoons of sugar."
V: One ladle.
-Here too?
-"One swirl of vinegar and perilla oil."
PEAKBOY: One spoonful of sugar.
-Is it the same for raw fish makguksu?
-I guess so.
PEAKBOY: One spoonful of sugar.
"Put as much mustard
and sauce as you'd like."
We can do that after we try it.
V: I'll mix it up.
Put a little bit of mustard in it.
-The mustard?
-I mean, the sauce.
V: Oh.
-PEAKBOY: This much?
-V: I think that's enough.
SEOJUN: Help yourselves.
-Okay.
-V: Okay.
SEOJUN: We'll put it in the middle.
(sucks teeth)
What should I eat first?
SEOJUN: I'll try this first.
(groans)
(slurping)
(slurps)
SEOJUN: It's really delicious.
V: Mm.
(slurping)
-Did you always like makguksu?
-Yes.
(slurps)
(Seojun sighs)
-Aren't you full?
-I'm full. Why am I full?
Me? I can eat a little more.
I did eat more than usual.
My stomach has shrunk.
Why?
I've been working out less, so it shrunk.
Lately, I'm trying to get into the habit
of chewing 100 times when I eat.
You only chewed three times right now.
I did, but I'm trying
to increase it to ten times.
I heard that it's important.
It isn't easy to be mindful of that.
But it helps with your digestion.
-You don't exercise these days, do you?
-No.
-I don't exercise these days.
-You did for a while.
(distant phone chimes)
You see...
A PHONE IS RINGING SOMEWHERE
You have a call.
(distant phone chiming)
I got it.
SEOJUN: I got it.
(humming)
(humming continues)
"Für Elise."
(chuckles)
PEAKBOY: Für V.
(humming)
I was told that I had to perform this
when I took violin lessons.
That's it!
(humming)
This is important, right?
If I don't get this, I can't do anything.
I need to find out.
-It's your ringtone, isn't it?
-What is your phone number?
-Is this your phone's ringtone?
-(laughter)
-V: Is it?
-WOMAN: Give it a call.
-Eh?
-You have to tell us your number.
-WOMAN: It's 010.
-Okay, one moment.
(laughter)
If you call her, I'll use
my voice recognition to find out.
We have to find out what it is, V.
-I'll call you.
-WOMAN: Okay.
(phone chiming)
Here it comes.
That's it.
What is it?
SEOJUN: Is that right?
(upbeat music playing)
That's not right.
(chuckles)
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT SONG
(upbeat music playing)
(Peakboy chuckles)
What's wrong with this?
I'm sure this song exists, though.
-"Humoresques!"
-(chair thuds)
-Oh.
-Calm down, my friend.
Play it. Let's see if you're right.
It's "Humoresques."
That's right.
V: Okay. Here you go.
This is what it originally sounds like.
"HUMORESQUE" BY ANTONIN DVORAK
He's into it.
For real.
-It goes well with the makguksu.
-It goes so well.
-Everyone.
-Yes.
This was wonderful.
-Shall we have some soda?
-Yes.
THEY RAISE THEIR GLASSES
TO SOME ROMANTIC MUSIC
(exhales)
Play this as our wake-up song tomorrow.
(V chuckles)
Oh, boy.
("Humoresque" by Antonin Dvorak playing)
-V: Thank you.
-SEOJUN, PEAKBOY: Thank you.
SEOJUN: Let's go.
Music. Let's go.
V: Music on.
("Humoresque" by Antonin Dvorak playing)
(humming)
(clicks tongue, mumbles)
-What?
-It's all frozen.
PEAKBOY: Look at how it's all frozen.
V: It's like a ski resort.
AS THEY ENJOY THE SNOW-COVERED VILLAGE
Wow!
-Is it here?
-(V cheers)
PEAKBOY: It's nice.
-I think it's here.
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
This is the parking lot.
SEOJUN: We can park here.
THEY ARRIVE AT THEIR ACCOMMODATION
SEOJUN: We're here.
-V: Thanks.
-PEAKBOY: Thanks.
(groans)
(grunts)
V: I think it's here.
(exclaims)
("Dynamite" by BTS playing)
LOCATED DEEP IN GOSEONG
THE FIVE FRIENDS WILL BE STAYING HERE
(V exclaims)
PEAKBOY: Hey, steamed buns!
SEOJUN: What?
What's up with the steamed buns?
-Whoa!
-(mumbles)
-SEOJUN: The steamed buns look so cute.
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
THE BUNS WELCOME THEM
V: Guys, look.
(exclaims)
-How nice.
-It's a great place to stare at the fire.
(all exclaiming)
THE RELAXING FIREPIT IS LOCATED
IN THE MIDDLE OF THEIR LODGE
SEOJUN: Who will chop the wood?
V: Wooshik can do it.
-SEOJUN: Is it connected?
-(Peakboy exclaims)
PEAKBOY: Whoa!
-Whoa!
-(V laughing)
PEAKBOY: This place is awesome.
Are we in the right place?
V: Are you sure this is right?
V: The room is warm.
ROOM 1
(V exclaims)
V: It's not bad.
-SEOJUN: This place is so nice.
-PEAKBOY: This place is really nice.
SEOJUN: It's so nice.
THEY GRAVITATE TOWARDS
THE VIEW OUT THE WINDOW
(Peakboy exclaims)
PEAKBOY: This place is so nice.
SEOJUN: This place is stylish too.
PEAKBOY: This place is nice.
SEOJUN: It's cozy.
V: Cozy. Cozy.
Cozy vibe.
Each person should take one of these.
SEOJUN: Amenities?
V: It has pajamas and things we need.
SEOJUN: What? It's so cute.
A MUST-HAVE FOR A FRIENDCATION,
THE WELCOME KIT
PEAKBOY: Check out the pool.
BOTH: Whoa!
-V: Seojun!
-SEOJUN: What the heck?
What is it?
PEAKBOY: It's deep.
SEOJUN: Whoa!
-(laughter)
-SEOJUN: Okay, okay, okay.
V: Okay, okay.
SEOJUN: This is that room.
-V: What?
-SEOJUN: A sauna.
V: A dry sauna?
-PEAKBOY: Is there a sauna?
-SEOJUN: Yes, a sauna.
(Peakboy exclaims)
V: Okay, there's only a bed here.
-Let's go over there.
-PEAKBOY: I think we'll all sleep here.
♪ La, lalala, lalala, lala ♪
SEOJUN: I think this is also a room.
PEAKBOY: Mom!
-Mom, I'm home!
-SEOJUN: Mom, I'm home!
V: Mom!
Mom, I brought my friends with me.
-(chuckling)
-SEOJUN: Look outside.
(chuckling continues)
-SEOJUN: Mr. Kim, how have you been?
-V: How have you been?
-SEOJUN: This place is stylish.
-PEAKBOY: It's so nice here.
COMFY LIKE YOUR OWN BEDROOM
SEOJUN: This place is really nice.
THE SECOND ROOM IS COZY
SEOJUN: Let's check out the biggest room.
V: Okay.
-(both exclaim)
-SEOJUN: Board games.
(rattles)
-SEOJUN: There's a lot to do.
-PEAKBOY: Yup.
V: We can consider this room the playroom.
PEAKBOY: There's a beam projector
and a polaroid camera.
SEOJUN: There's a karaoke machine too.
I think we can all sleep together
in the first room.
PEAKBOY: I think so too.
DINING ROOM
THE LAST PLACE TO VISIT
SEOJUN: Ah...
-SEOJUN: Are all the lights on?
-V: I think coziness is key to this place.
SEOJUN: There's a toaster.
These are coffee beans.
It's a coffee grinder.
HE CASUALLY CHECKS OUT
THE KITCHEN APPLIANCES
-PEAKBOY: Done.
-V: Done.
SEOJUN: Wait, let me check
what kind of seasonings there are.
-PEAKBOY: Let's have some steamed buns.
-V: We just ate.
We can't eat steamed buns.
(gasps)
(clatters)
WHILE SEOJUN CHECKS OUT
THE KITCHEN BY HIMSELF
Whoa...
-V: Come over here.
-PEAKBOY: Hot.
PEAKBOY HAS A STEAMED BUN
It's hot.
(blowing air)
(thudding)
WITH ONE BITE OF THE STEAMED BUN,
THE COLDNESS DISAPPEARS
IN THE MEANTIME,
V FINDS SOMETHING TO PLAY WITH
-Peakboy, grab a racket.
-PEAKBOY: Okay!
(thuds)
-Give it your best shot.
-V: All right.
(chuckles)
-I was--
-PEAKBOY: Let's try to volley three times.
Okay.
(sighs)
What are you doing?
Jeez. I don't want to play.
Why not?
HE IS HAVING FUN TEASING PEAKBOY
(groans)
PEAKBOY: I almost cursed just now.
(rattles)
SEOJUN: I'm going to unpack.
PEAKBOY: Me too.
(sighs)
THEIR BAGS GO TO THE SECOND ROOM
SEOJUN: Okay.
We can unpack here.
-You can unpack here too.
-PEAKBOY: Okay, I'll unpack here.
I don't have anything to unpack.
I just need to keep it open.
TOUGH
SEOJUN: Oh, yes. Where is it?
-SEOJUN: You didn't pack much, V.
-V: No.
SEOJUN: I packed quite a bit.
(laughter)
PACKED
V: So it's like that?
PEAKBOY: You packed so much.
V, SEOJUN
-SEOJUN: What?
-PEAKBOY: What did you pack?
-What's this?
-SEOJUN: Why did you pack a shopping bag?
V: My slippers.
You should have told me.
(Seojun chuckles)
I have to take my supplements.
SEOJUN CHECKS HIS SUPPLEMENTS
V: You brought a lot.
I'm sure someone would try
to take some of mine.
-PEAKBOY: This is so good.
-SEOJUN: I packed workout equipment too.
(clanks)
He brought a rod.
You can do everything with this.
(chuckles)
I know what it is.
-SEOJUN: I can do everything with this.
-V: We have to listen to him.
PEAKBOY: If we don't listen to him,
he'll beat us up.
(sighs)
-I'm tired just doing this.
-V: I'm really tired too.
Are you very tired?
V: Shall we go to the room?
PEAKBOY: Let's go, Seojun.
-Let's get some sleep.
-V: What?
-PEAKBOY: We should get some sleep.
-V: We should.
-PEAKBOY: We have to sleep to move.
-V: Yes, we have to sleep to move.
SEOJUN: You can sleep when you're dead.
PEAKBOY: Do you want to dream or sleep?
-(Seojun sighs)
-(V chuckles)
V: Here, I'll give you a pillow.
Thank you.
(Seojun grunts)
EVEN AT THE MOMENT WHEN YOU WERE LEAVING
WERE YOU WORRIED ABOUT ME
V: It's so warm here.
SEOJUN: Now that I'm lying down,
I'm getting sleepy.
(sighs)
(Peakboy groans)
(V sighs)
(soft guitar music)
ONE BY ONE,
THEY FALL INTO A SWEET SLUMBER
(soft guitar music)
V WAKES UP FIRST FROM DEEP SLEEP
SEOJUN WAKES UP AFTER HIM
V: Are you up?
PEAKBOY: Gosh, I slept so well.
SEOJUN: Will steak be enough? Or...
V: Are you going to have a drink?
Yes. I think we should have a little.
A little until six in the morning?
Yes, let's drink until six.
-And go watch the sunrise?
-Yes. Then lunch...
For lunch, back to the makguksu place.
We'll get some makguksu again
and act like it was our first time there.
-PEAKBOY: Shall we go?
-SEOJUN: Let's hurry up and go.
V: I'll drive.
SEOJUN: Okay. Input the supermarket
into the GPS.
SEOJUN WORKED HARD
SO V SITS IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT THIS TIME
PEAKBOY: ♪ Oh, yeah ♪
PEAKBOY: If the weather is nice,
it would be so nice to go for a walk here.
SEOJUN: It's all frozen.
You'd better be careful.
PEAKBOY: Be careful, V.
SEOJUN: Be careful, V.
-Stop that!
-SEOJUN: Be careful, V!
SEOJUN: ♪ I got your memory ♪
DOWN THE SNOW-COVERED ROAD
(Seojun singing)
THEY GO FOR THEIR FIRST GROCERY SHOPPING
♪ Red sunset ♪
PEAKBOY: We're already here.
V: It's close.
SEOJUN: Good, V.
(chuckles)
PEAKBOY: Slow down, V.
-PEAKBOY: Good job.
-SEOJUN: Let's go, V.
Shut off the car, V.
(car door closes)
SEOJUN: Good?
Yes.
SEOJUN: Let's take one of these.
SEOJUN AND PEAKBOY: Here's one.
-SEOJUN: Come on, V.
-V: Be careful.
(laughing)
SEOJUN: Let's take a look around first.
-Strawberries?
-PEAKBOY: I like strawberries.
SEOJUN: It's from Geochang.
-V: Geochang is known for apples.
-SEOJUN: Shine Muscat?
-V: Shine Muscat.
-PEAKBOY: Good.
Are you going to cook mushrooms too?
There's a mushroom set here.
V: Let's have king oyster mushrooms.
But we haven't decided what we'll eat,
so I don't know what we should buy.
SEOJUN: I can buy the ingredients
for the steak.
-PEAKBOY: What about breakfast?
-SEOJUN: Shall we just toast some bread?
V: With some cereal?
-With cereal?
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
SEOJUN: Sure. That's fine.
-Let's have American-style breakfast.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
SEOJUN: There are some peeled potatoes.
I'll make mashed potatoes for you.
PEAKBOY: Oh.
-SEOJUN: Let's get some kimchi too.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
V: I've tried all the kimchi from
that brand and cabbage kimchi is the best.
-SEOJUN: Green onion kimchi is good too.
-V: Right.
SEOJUN: But the green onion kimchi is...
Let's just get some.
CAREFULLY(?) CHOOSING SIDES
SEOJUN: What kind of meat do you want?
-V: Beef tenderloin.
-SEOJUN: Beef tenderloin?
-Beef tenderloin?
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
SEOJUN: Tteokguk is so easy too.
V: Shall we buy some chips?
-Let's get this much.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
SEOJUN: Get some cookies.
Right over there.
PEAKBOY: Seojun wants cookies.
SEOJUN: There's a small one up there.
-PEAKBOY: This one?
-SEOJUN: The small one.
-Shouldn't you eat this, V?
-PEAKBOY: What? Why?
-SEOJUN: Peakboy should eat this.
-PEAKBOY: I want barley hardtack.
I don't eat cereal with milk.
I eat barley hardtack with milk.
-Thank you.
-V: Okay.
V: Let's check out now.
THEY FILL THE CART WITH WHAT THEY WANT
-SEOJUN: Did you get everything?
-V: Yes.
WITH BOTH HANDS FULL, THEY HEAD BACK
V: Let's go.
SEOJUN: If we don't have enough,
we can come again tomorrow.
Let's put away the groceries first.
SEOJUN: After we put the groceries away,
let's change.
-V: Okay.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
V: Got it.
-Okay
-SEOJUN: Got it.
V: Let's change.
There aren't any bugs here.
-You're right.
-SEOJUN: That's because it's cold.
THE THREE GET CHANGED BEFORE THEY EAT
This is mine, isn't it?
SEOJUN: I'm going with this color.
-PEAKBOY: Okay.
-V: Okay.
PEAKBOY: What?
-Hang on.
-V: What is it?
PEAKBOY: Why are my pants so short?
(laughing)
THE PANTS AREN'T LONG ENOUGH FOR HIS LEGS
This isn't the fit I was going for.
(laughter)
That's because you're 193 cm.
(Seojun chuckles)
V: Peakboy, he says
it's because you're 193 cm.
-SEOJUN: All right.
-PEAKBOY: All right.
SEOJUN: All right.
THEY CHANGE INTO THEIR UNIFORM
SEOJUN: ♪ I'll give you my everything ♪
HE GOES TO THE KITCHEN FIRST
TO PREPARE DINNER
THE MAIN CHEF FOR TODAY'S DINNER, SEOJUN
Can I help you out with anything?
Are there knives here?
SEOJUN: Can you go to our room
and get the forks and knives?
That's it.
V: What about the forks?
-Are there five?
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
V: Let's go.
THE TWO FOUND FORKS AND KNIVES
(dishes clanking)
-V: Seojun.
-SEOJUN: Yes?
Do you want a taste of my daggers?
SEOJUN: You're Wolverine.
(utensils clatter)
It isn't close to done.
WHILE HE COOKS THE POTATOES
FOR THE MASHED POTATOES
SEOJUN: Let's write our names here.
Write "Clown" for me.
(V laughs)
Okay, let's write our nicknames.
THEY WRITE THEIR NICKNAMES ON THE UNIFORMS
SEOJUN: Write it properly, will you?
(laughter)
-PEAKBOY: What should I write?
-V: You?
Giant.
(laughter)
(chuckles)
Good.
-What about you?
-V: What about me?
-V?
-SEOJUN: No, you should be...
THE NICKNAME THEY HAVE FOR V
-World Star.
Okay.
(chuckles)
SEOJUN: Clown is funny.
PEAKBOY: But Giant...
(all laughing)
CLOWN, GIANT, AND WORLD STAR
Let me go check.
This is really funny, though.
-Should we get these custom-made?
-Let's write it bigger on the back.
Okay.
Write his birth year on the back too.
HE CAREFULLY WRITES ONE LETTER AT A TIME
Okay.
Hang on. Okay, good.
PEAKBOY: Making it bigger?
What did you write?
PEAKBOY: Clown.
(chuckles)
Write mine too.
PEAKBOY'S TURN IS NEXT
-Write it properly.
-SEOJUN: It's already ruined.
(laughs)
HE WRITES IT BIG AND CLEAR
-This is your slogan, isn't it?
-V: Yes.
SEOJUN WRITES ON V'S SHIRT HIMSELF
-It looks like beansprouts.
-The nine looks so small.
Okay.
THEIR ONE-OF-A-KIND UNIFORM IS COMPLETE
(burbling)
MEANTIME, THE POTATOES ARE DONE
SEOJUN: It looks done.
I have something for you to do.
Are we finally doing something?
-V: What is it?
-SEOJUN: I'll put the butter and milk in.
-V: Okay.
-PEAKBOY: It's no big deal.
After that...
-I see.
-You can go like that.
-I'll do it.
-SEOJUN: But this is hot.
It isn't that hot.
Really? Then take it and do it.
V: Let's do it.
SEOJUN: Let's put some parsley in it.
Done.
Put a little more in it.
-SEOJUN: Parsley?
-V: Yes.
-SEOJUN: You like parsley?
-I think parsley likes you too.
-V: Parsley loves me.
HE PUTS A LOT IN FOR V
-SEOJUN: More?
-V: That's enough.
SEOJUN: You have to mash all of that.
-PEAKBOY: We mashed all of it.
-SEOJUN: Okay.
TIME TO COOK THE STEAK
(frizzling)
(V clears throat)
A guy that cooks steak...
V: I like it.
THE DISH IS SLOWLY COMING TOGETHER
Wow.
(V sighs)
V: You're a good cook.
EVEN THE PLATING IS PERFECT
THE FIRST DINNER OF THEIR TRIP
PEAKBOY: Thanks.
-V: Thank you.
-SEOJUN: Enjoy.
Here's the sauce.
HOW DOES CHEF SEOJUN'S STEAK TASTE?
It's awesome.
I thought it would be chewy, but it isn't.
Mmm.
-It's so good.
-So good.
Mmm.
SEOJUN: Shall we have a glass?
It tastes good.
Which part is this?
SEOJUN: They're all beef tenderloins,
but they cut it up like that.
Mmm.
Did you soak the whole potato?
SEOJUN: You boil them.
V: Mm.
And then, you just add butter
and mix them up.
Do you want to try cooking?
Well, yes.
I heard that if you cook,
you become very confident.
It is one of the ways to become happy.
I'm not good at cooking either,
but I feel happier
when I see people enjoy my food.
-V: Oh, really?
-Yes.
V, have this.
-Me? I'll eat it.
-SEOJUN: You're killing it.
-I think you're about to grow taller.
-V: What?
-You're going to grow 2 cm.
-Maybe you're growing.
That was good.
AFTER THE HEARTY DINNER
SEOJUN: Do the dishes, please.
PEAKBOY: Okay, let's do the dishes.
I'll do it.
WORLD STAR
V: It feels like
we're closing the restaurant
and cleaning up now.
SEOJUN: Wear rubber gloves.
PEAKBOY: I don't wear rubber gloves
at home.
SEOJUN:
It means you don't do dishes often.
PEAKBOY: Hey, I'm very good
around the house.
SEOJUN: I'm not interested.
V: Move aside now. I'll do it.
-PEAKBOY: Can I ask you to do this, then?
-V: Okay, I'll do it.
PEAKBOY AND V SWAP OUT
(water trickling)
V: Peakboy, which one is the dish soap?
You didn't wash them with dish soap?
-V: Which one is it?
-This is dish soap. That's hand soap.
-V: This is the dish soap?
-Yes, it is.
V: Okay.
SEOJUN: It's only eight o'clock.
What do we do now?
V: Let's go over there and play games.
There's a game console there.
THEY HEAD TO THE PLAYROOM
V: ♪ Ice tea and a game of ping pong ♪
♪ This is getting heavy ♪
♪ 'Cause I-I-I'm in the stars tonight ♪
THE FIRST THING THEY GRAB
IS THE INSTANT CAMERA
-What?
-How do I use this?
V.
PEAKBOY: One, two, three.
-SEOJUN: That's it.
-PEAKBOY: Yes.
SEOJUN: Are we all in it?
THE FIRST RECORD OF THEIR TRIP
V: Come over here.
V BRINGS THE GO BOARD
(V clears throat)
All right.
Hello, hello.
Hello.
Park Seojun, eighth dan
and V, seventh dan.
-They play each other today.
-Let's flick the stones.
Flicking stones? Okay.
GAME: FLICKING STONES
V USES THE BLACK STONES
SEOJUN USES THE WHITE STONES
PEAKBOY: He is very strategic.
SEOJUN: You're going to place them
like that? Come on.
V: Decide who will go first.
SEOJUN: Rock, paper, scissors.
PEAKBOY: Park Seojun will go first.
SEOJUN FLICKS THE STONE FIRST
(playful music)
V: You can turn it like this.
-No.
-No, you can't do that.
-You can turn your body.
-Yes. Turn your body, not this.
Jeez.
(sighs)
PEAKBOY: Usually, you can't do that.
-He sacrificed his stone.
-SEOJUN: Who will win?
PEAKBOY: He sacrificed his own.
SEOJUN: This is tough. Should I do this?
Why do you keep coming this way?
(clears throat)
(rattles)
V'S BLACK STONE ATTACKS SUCCESSFULLY
(V groans)
-PEAKBOY: He's desperate.
-V: He's desperate.
LEFTOVER STONES
BLACK: 4, WHITE: 3
SEOJUN: Actually, I can't play that well.
(rattles)
BACK TO SQUARE ONE
This is tough. Where do I go from here?
Should I go this way or that way?
(rattles)
V FLICKS OFF A WHITE STONE
ALONG WITH HIS BLACK STONE
Let's go. One stone, two birds.
PEAKBOY, V: Oh!
(both exclaim)
(imitates buzzer buzzes)
PARK SEOJUN WINS
SEOJUN: Come here.
-Come here.
-Isn't it this?
-No, it isn't. No.
-PEAKBOY: Yes, it is.
Bring your head there.
No, let's start now.
-Starting now.
-No way.
-V: From now.
-I played so hard, though.
Let's start from now. I went easy on you.
-You went easy on what?
-I went easy on you in the game.
-What are you talking about?
-You self-destructed.
-No, I did.
-Okay, if you want to hit me, go ahead.
I can't believe
he's playing dirty like that.
All right. Let's play one more game.
One more game.
-SEOJUN: You play.
-V: Okay.
Peakboy, are you going to do this or this?
You can do this, this, or this.
(laughter)
-This, this, this.
-And this.
IT'S UP TO THE WINNER
BLACK STONE, V
WHITE STONE, PEAKBOY
SEOJUN: What?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Should I go first?
(Seojun sucks teeth)
Isn't it better to go first?
BLACK STONE GOES FIRST
SEOJUN: Oh.
WHITE STONE TAKES IT SLOW
(rattles)
V'S BLACK STONE ATTACKS SUCCESSFULLY
(sniffs)
SEOJUN: He's acting serious.
(soft chuckle)
WHITE STONE TIES IT UP
I can't commentate.
-V: Ah...
-(chuckles)
V MISSES
THE BLACK STONE FALLS OVER THE EDGE
I'll wipe it all out
with just three stones.
WHITE STONE'S CAUTIOUS ATTACK
MEANWHILE, BLACK STONE ATTACKS HARD
-SEOJUN: Three to three.
-I told you I went easy on him.
SEOJUN: He's a timid player.
(rattles)
Which punishment will he get?
PEAKBOY'S FATAL MISTAKE
LEFTOVER STONES
BLACK: 3, WHITE: 1
-(Peakboy groans)
-V: I'm going to finish it.
-SEOJUN: How far are you going?
-Wait.
BLACK STONE PLAYER, V WINS
PEAKBOY: Good job.
(clatters)
HE HUMBLY GETS READY TO BE FLICKED
No, I'm going to hit you with this.
While wearing a ring?
-Wait.
-Okay. I'll do this.
-Do what you want.
-No.
I don't like it when people go easy on me.
V: No, I'll go with this.
That way, I can hit you properly too.
No, I'll go with this.
What if you hit me with this
when I close my eyes?
(laughs)
(Peakboy groans painfully)
(stifled laugh)
(pained groan)
(tapping)
(laughter)
I can't use profanity, can I?
(V laughs)
(laughter)
(Peakboy groans)
Would you like to play another match?
Let's play with three stones.
-V: Three?
-Oh, boy. Here we go.
V VS PEAKBOY, REMATCH
SEOJUN: What is this?
You look like you have a strategy,
but you don't, do you?
May I go first this time?
PEAKBOY'S WHITE STONE
STARTS OFF WITH A POWERFUL MOVE
(exhales deeply)
SEOJUN: How far are you going?
PEAKBOY: Come on. This is a bit much.
Why?
(V chuckles)
-(rattles)
-Oh.
HIS ATTACK SUCCEEDS
WHILE AVOIDING THE BLACK STONES
HIS FINGERS SLIGHTLY LACKED STRENGTH
(rattles)
(chuckling)
V'S CONSECUTIVE SUCCESSFUL ATTACKS
-(rattles)
-(laughs)
Ah...
GAME OVER
(V laughing)
(laughing continues)
THE UNAVOIDABLE TIME FOR PUNISHMENT
It really did hurt. I got teary-eyed.
(laughs)
It's red, isn't it?
-My mom is going to watch this.
-(chuckles)
PEAKBOY: But don't go easy on me.
That isn't fun.
-Do you want me to go easy on you?
-No.
-Don't go easy on me.
-Okay.
HE GIVES HIM A SIGNAL
SIGNAL REGISTERED
-(slaps)
-(laughter)
(V and Seojun laughing)
(laughing continues)
(laughing heartily)
PEAKBOY: Hey, jeez. Wait.
How could you slap me?
Jeez. V, I can't see well.
V, I CAN'T SEE (IN FRONT OF ME) WELL...
FLICKING STONES ENDS
LEAVING BEHIND PEAKBOY'S SCARS
-SEOJUN: That was fun.
-PEAKBOY: That was fun.
SEOJUN: Aren't you hungry?
-V: A little?
-SEOJUN: I think it's time to get hungry.
THEY START TO GET HUNGRY AGAIN
SEOJUN: Let's eat whatever we have.
CHEF SEOJUN PREPARES A NIGHTTIME SNACK
(frizzling)
PEAKBOY: You can really smell the bacon.
-I'm going to stop frying.
-V: Okay.
MEANWHILE
A CAR APPROACHES THEIR LODGE
(Seojun whistling)
I think someone is here.
WHO IS THE FOURTH FRIEND TO
COME LATE AT NIGHT TO GOSEONG?
PEAKBOY: Wooshik's here.
HE JOINS THE TRIP
LATE AT NIGHT ON THE FIRST DAY
THE LIFE OF THE PARTY
CHOI WOOSHIK
HE NEVER LOSES HIS ROMANTIC SIDE AND HUMOR
"I THINK… I'VE ALWAYS BEEN CUTE!"
THE SELF-PROCLAIMED(?) CUTIE APPEARS
Seojun.
THE LAST FRIEND IS CUTE AND LOVING
THE LOVELIEST GUY IN THE AREA
SWEET GUY
PARK HYUNGSIK
ALL FIVE FRIENDS COME TOGETHER
ON THE SECOND DAY OF THEIR TRIP
AND THE FRIENDCATION TRULY BEGINS
I CAN JUST BE MYSELF AND LET MY GUARD DOWN
IT'S A TIME HE DOESN'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING
IF WE HADN'T MET BACK THEN…
I'M SURE WE WOULD'VE MET SOME OTHER WAY
WOOSHIK: I'm happier today than yesterday.
SEOJUN: Then tomorrow,
you'll be even happier than today.
THE TRIP OF THESE FIVE FRIENDS CONTINUE
(soft music)