May I be like the stars
and you like the moon.
As long as the world remains,
so shall we.
I only wish to stay with the one I love,
watching every sunrise and sunset.
I want to be with you forever.
Eternals and demons walk different paths.
You and she are ultimately different.
Have you ever
truly cared for me?
No.
Never.
In this life and the next, through all lifetimes…
May we live and die together,
and share life and death as one.
[Moonlight Mystique]
[Episode 22]
[Unbridled Pavilion]
Cang Shan!
Coming.
Who is it?
Cang Shan!
[Unbridled Pavilion]
Cang…
[Mrs. Cang, Demon Race, Stone Clan]
Mother?
I-It's really you.
What brings you here?
Cang Shan,
something's happened to our Stone Clan.
Mother, you came all the way here
and insisted on meeting with Master.
Has something serious happened in the Stone Clan?
Thank you for meeting me, Master Fan.
Recently, the Stone Clan has been in turmoil.
Every night,
members of the clan go missing and die.
The bodies of the deceased
will be discovered the next day
in the stone forest.
The details of their deaths differ,
but they share one thing in common:
they all died
with their eyes wide open.
[Cang Xuan, Demon Race, Chief of the Stone Clan]
No.
I need to go out and investigate.
No!
You can't go.
You're the chief.
If something happens to you,
the clan will lose its backbone.
Precisely because I'm the chief,
I must uncover the truth
and give the clan members an explanation.
Then I'll go with you.
No, you stay at home.
What if...
Cang Shan has been away from home for years.
If you leave
and something happens to you,
you won't get to see your son
ever again.
It's better if he doesn't come back.
The Stone Clan today
is no longer the same as it used to be.
Then did the chief...
He never came back.
I led the clan members
to search every corner
of the Stone Clan,
but there was no trace of him.
Mother.
I'll go back with you to search for him.
I've always been straightforward.
In terms of spiritual power,
only Master Fan is stronger than Cang Shan's father.
Unless you go in person,
if anyone else goes,
I'm afraid the outcome
will be the same.
Why have you suddenly come back?
Is something bothering you?
I don't know why,
but I have this inexplicable feeling of worry.
I told you,
as long as I'm here,
you don't need to worry about anything.
Members of the Stone Clan suddenly died.
Cang Shan's father went missing,
and his mother came straight to you for help.
I know you wouldn't stand by,
but I feel a sense of danger.
Cang Shan calls me Master.
It's natural that his mother
would come to me for help.
But now, you only have two stars left.
It's not so easy for me to lose a star.
I remember you once said
you didn't want to be cowardly
because of the fear of danger.
But when it comes to me...
Bai Shuo.
The Contemplation Stone showed me another vision.
I saw a village
full of jagged rocks.
If I'm not mistaken,
the village you saw should be
the village of the Stone Clan.
Soon after Mrs. Cang came,
the Contemplation Stone was activated.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
The kindness in Ning'an City,
the killing in the Outlanders' City,
and the love in Jingyou Mountain have all seen bloodshed.
What remains are greed and hate.
Both of them sound ominous.
I'll go
to the Stone Clan.
You stay at the Unbridled Pavilion.
I'm no longer the weak Bai Shuo I once was.
I can go with you.
You cannot afford to lose another star.
Though you have power now,
the Contemplation Stone won't protect you anymore.
If anything happens...
Since it's an "if,"
it's beyond our control.
I can't hide forever,
never seeing anyone or doing anything.
I'm not the type to run away.
Besides, the more Contemplations I collect,
the more power I will have.
As long as I'm powerful enough,
I'll be my own shield,
just like you.
As the Demon King of the Polar Region,
when did you ever need others' protection?
I can't out-argue you anymore.
Master.
Bai Shuo.
I've made up my mind.
I'll handle my clan's trouble myself.
Once it's resolved,
I'll reunite with you.
The next Contemplation
is in the Stone Clan.
[Stone Clan, Demon Race]
Bai Shuo,
take a closer look.
Is the scene you saw from here?
Yes.
So something big
is going to happen to the Stone Clan, right?
The vision only showed this place.
Nothing terrifying has appeared yet.
Don't panic.
What are you talking about?
What vision?
What is going to happen?
Mother, stop asking.
It's hard to explain.
Since I've come to the Stone Clan,
I'm going to find out
who's behind all these murders.
Here we are.
Master Fan, Ms. Bai.
This place is not as good as the Unbridled Pavilion,
so you'll have to make do.
I'll go clean your rooms now.
Thank you, Mrs. Cang.
Cang Shan?
Shi Lei?
You've been gone for years.
You're finally back.
Have you learned that
[Shi Lei, Demon Race, Stone Clan]
something's happened in the clan?
I came back too late.
It's not too late.
What matters is you're back.
Master.
This is my best friend, Shi Lei.
This is the Master of Bright Moon Palace.
This is Ms. Bai, a human.
Master...
Master of Bright Moon?
Your mother said
you work for Bright Moon Palace.
That's actually true.
Master and Ms. Bai are here to help us.
Thank you, Master.
Thank you, Ms. Bai.
You're our guests.
We should treat you with hospitality.
But right now,
the Stone Clan…
We understand.
Time is tight.
Please tell Mrs. Cang to take us
to see the bodies of the victims first.
No need to trouble Mrs. Cang.
I know where they are.
I'll take you there.
Master Fan.
Ms. Bai.
These are the bodies of the three murdered elders.
I'm fine.
Cang Shan,
examine the cause of death and the wounds on their bodies.
This one's bones are completely shattered.
This one too.
Master,
they weren't killed in one strike.
The murderer
shattered their bones first,
then tortured them to death.
It looks like the work of a vengeful enemy.
The Stone Clan has been living in the mountains for many years.
We don't have any enemies.
If it's not an enemy from another clan,
have you considered that the killer
might be from within the Stone Clan?
Impossible.
People here live in harmony.
There has never been any conflict.
No one would commit such a brutal act.
Not wanting to believe it doesn't mean it's impossible.
Before everything is clear,
everyone is a suspect.
In Ning'an City,
the Outlanders' City,  and Jingyou Mountain,
Young Lord saved and helped you again and again.
When the Fox Clan's mission failed,
she took the blame for you.
Without the demonic flower armor protecting her,
the punishment
made her suffer far worse than before.
It's not because you're so great
but because Young Lord has suffered too much since childhood
that she treasures the little warmth
you unknowingly gave her.
It's you.
How do you feel?
What did you make me eat?
Medicine for healing and pain relief.
It's a pill from Lanling?
I'll take you out first.
If Grand Master finds out,
do you know the consequences?
No matter what the consequences are,
I'll take you out first.
Have you thought this through?
If you save me,
you might be tortured by Grand Master until you're in pieces.
How can I hide behind you while you take the punishment
for the failed mission?
You've changed.
The world is full of uncertainties.
Whether things change or stay the same,
I'm just doing what I'm supposed to do.
But I don't understand one thing.
He treats you like this, making you suffer so much.
Why are you still so loyal to him,
still willing to risk your life for him?
Those who gave birth to you
despised you for being weak and sick
and abandoned you in the wilderness.
I pitied you,
brought you back to Cold Spring Palace, and raised you.
You were born useless,
unable to transform
or cultivate.
It was also me who put in so much effort
to make you who you are today.
♫Across thousands of miles♫
In Cold Spring Palace,
only the strongest
have the right to survive
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
and become my disciples.
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
Grand Master.
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
Living in pain
is better than facing death with no escape.
As long as I'm still useful to Grand Master,
a little suffering
is nothing.
It's because of this
that he tortures you again and again.
If he wants to punish me, I'll accept it.
I'd like to see
if he wants to kill everyone
who's ever risked their life for him.
I'll take you out first.
♫I remember that moonlit night♫
♫The flowers that bloomed once in a lifetime♫
♫I remember that word of concern♫
♫But unfortunately, I didn't get to answer♫
♫I remember that drop of tear♫
♫It dried in the wind♫
♫The one in the autumn wind♫
♫How many times have I seen you in my dreams?♫
♫That year, that year♫
♫The leaves fell unnoticed after the flowers bloomed♫
♫I'm afraid the autumn wind will stir up memories♫
You're still carrying Lanling's medicine with you,
♫They unfold, one page after another♫
which makes your loyalty doubtful.
♫That year, that year♫
Don't do that again in the future.
I just wanted to return your favors.
♫The flowers flew under the moon, filling the sky♫
From now on,
we are even.
♫Falling to the mud, burying the memories♫
Even?
♫Layer after layer♫
Since the moment you saved me today,
our fates
♫Another year passed♫
in Cold Spring Palace
are tied together.
You're you, and I'm me.
I won't stick my neck out for you again,
and you don't need to take any blame for me anymore.
♫I remember that moonlit night♫
♫The flowers that bloomed once in a lifetime♫
As Lady Fu Ling of Cold Spring Palace,
♫I remember that word of concern♫
you look powerful on the surface,
but you've always been tormented by Zhen Yu.
♫But unfortunately, I didn't get to answer♫
The cold, unfeeling persona you've maintained
is just your way of protecting yourself,
♫I remember that drop of tear♫
not your true nature.
Fu Ling,
♫It dried in the wind♫
this kind of mere survival isn't the only way to live.
You can
♫The one in the autumn wind♫
choose your own path.
♫How many times have I seen you in my dreams?♫
♫That year, that year♫
Once you start
♫The leaves fell unnoticed after the flowers bloomed♫
taking this medicine,
you can't stop.
If you stop halfway,
♫I'm afraid the autumn wind will stir up memories♫
you'll feel pain every day.
♫They unfold, one page after another♫
A month after stopping taking it,
the poison will take your life.
♫That year, that year♫
Remember,
♫The flowers flew under the moon, filling the sky♫
your life
is in my hands now.
I can
♫Falling to the mud, burying the memories♫
take it back at any time.
♫Layer after layer♫
Chong Zhao.
In this world,
♫Another year passed♫
not everyone has a choice.
Chong Zhao, thank you.
You have feelings for Young Lord,
don't you?
Feelings are something
you can't see or touch,
and they change easily.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You and Young Lord are both stubborn.
No matter what,
you saved her this time.
I'll remember your kindness.
No need.
I've violated the palace rules
and privately freed Fu Ling.
Please punish me, Master.
You've come
sooner than I expected.
I deserve punishment.
All responsibility
falls on me alone.
I thought,
in your heart, there was only Bai Shuo,
but now, you seem to care for
Fu Ling as well.
I just didn't want to be indebted
to Fu Ling anymore.
I wanted to return her favors.
As for whatever happens next,
I'll just accept it.
Are you gambling on
my mercy?
What makes you think
I won't kill you?
Because Fu Ling is already useless in your eyes.
I believe
you need someone stronger by your side.
Who?
You?
I believe you have the answer.
The fact that I'm still standing here,
talking to you,
proves that you've already
made your choice.
Fine.
I'll let it slide this time.
Go return those favors.
After you're done,
there are many things here
that require someone like you—
someone stronger—to handle.
I've brought you
the person you want.
When will you let go of
the person I want?
The Stone Clan
doesn't look like a demon clan at all.
Life here is peaceful.
How could such a creepy thing happen here?
If everything in this world
could be as peaceful as it appears,
there wouldn't be so many injustices and killings.
The two remaining Contemplations
are greed and hate.
In a place like the Stone Clan,
do you think we'll find greed
or hate?
Murders out of revenge.
I'd say it's hate.
If it's hate,
there must be a reason.
If we find the root of it,
perhaps we can find a solution.
Mother,
where did you go in the middle of the night?
Where could I go?
With all these family matters,
I'm always bustling around
and making preparations.
The deaths of those victims look like an act of revenge.
Mother, tell me honestly.
Are their deaths
related to the event back then?
Stop talking nonsense!
That matter happened so many years ago.
If they wanted revenge, they would've come long ago.
Why wait until now?
Mother, do you guys all think
since that matter is in the past
and no one brings it up anymore,
everything can be forgotten as if it never happened?
We don't know if your father is still alive.
I don't want to argue with you over the past.
You're not allowed to bring it up again!
Why not?
You harmed people back then.
Perhaps the consequences today are the retribution!
No matter what he did back then,
he is still your father.
Cang Shan,
your father isn't as bad as you think.
As the chief,
many things
were beyond his control.
You shouldn't speak of him like that.
Now,
the Stone Clan is in trouble,
and your father is missing.
Can't you let go of what happened back then?
I'll find the murderer,
and I'll find him.
But back then, you indeed
did something you shouldn't have.
No matter how hard you try to cover it up,
it won't change the fact that you did something horrible!
Young Lord, I'll go make you some medicinal soup.
The poison is from Grand Master.
No medicine can help.
At least it can ease the pain
and make you look a little less pale.
Do I look very pale?
Young Lord, I don't understand.
Why don't you tell Chong Zhao about the poisoning?
It's a poison with no cure.
What's the point of telling him?
Would it mean one more person worrying about me,
or one more person pitying me?
I don't need either.
It's me.
Young Lord, you two talk.
I'll leave.
Drink it while it's hot.
I'm quite curious.
How come Grand Master didn't punish you?
I'm already in Cold Spring Palace.
He can take my life at any time.
It seems Chen Ye isn't in the palace.
He's physically disabled.
I heard he's been making medicine and poison and studying weapons
in the palace all these years.
He's suddenly gone on a long trip.
It looks like he has something important to do.
I advise you not to inquire about it,
and don't pass information to Lanling again.
Every move in Cold Spring Palace
is under Grand Master's watch.
Just because he hasn't questioned you doesn't mean he doesn't know.
What a beautiful spiritual herb!
I'll take it back to help Young Lord recover.
How dare you!
That's a spiritual herb planted by Lord Chen Ye.
Put it down!
Lady Fu Ling is injured.
She needs this herb.
She's already fallen out of favor with Master.
She doesn't deserve this herb.
What are you doing?
Go away!
What's wrong with you?
Fu Ling!
Why is it so hot?
Fu Ling.
What's wrong with you?
[Follow the way of heaven as the way. Practice kindness, caution, and harmony.]
Follow the way of heaven as the way.
Practice kindness,
caution,
and harmony.
What did you say?
♫What kind of fruit never sees a flower?♫
How do you know that saying?
Who told you that?
♫Withstanding the stillness, you are a broken piece of me♫
How do you know my family motto?
♫I am the fruit to your flowers♫
Tell me!
Why do you know the Chong family's motto?
As an Eternal,
I should follow the way of heaven as the way;
practice kindness, caution,
and harmony.
Mother, Father,
am I right?
Good.
You recited it correctly.
This is the motto of the Chong family.
As you live and cultivate as an Eternal, it's the standard to follow.
Do you remember?
Yes.
♫Across thousands of miles♫
That motto is known only by my parents and me.
Do you know my parents?
♫The pain of parting lingers♫
What parents?
I don't have parents.
My parents abandoned me
ten years ago.
♫ I light a lamp with no wick to carry me through the rest of my days♫
It was Grand Master
who saved me and brought me to Cold Spring Palace.
Ten years ago...
You came to Cold Spring Palace ten years ago?
What about before that?
♫Flowers in the wind, sand in the water♫
I don't know.
What about before that?
I don't know!
I only have memories after coming to Cold Spring Palace.
My head hurts so much.
♫What kind of tree never takes root?♫
That dagger...
Why?
Why did I see Bai Shuo's dagger again?
♫What kind of roots never turn into trees?♫
Those two girls…
Who are they?
♫To break the roots of love, to look at the past and seal one's heart♫
The dagger...
Two girls...
♫I'm your wanderer♫
Fu Ling,
who on earth are you?
How was last night?
Any more victims?
No.
I've checked every household.
Nothing happened last night.
No one died.
Perhaps
the murderer was afraid of Master Fan
and didn't dare to act.
He's obviously a trouble.
He's been here
for a long time.
Look. No one helped him.
Who is he?
-I don't know.
-I don't recognize him.
I saw him down on the hillside
when I was out gathering firewood.
He must have fallen from the slope.
The clan is already in trouble.
We don't have the time
to help an outsider.
-Yeah.
-Just throw him out.
Then throw him out.
-Right.
-But he's still alive.
Let's save him first,
then kick him out.
If you want to save him, go ahead.
I don't want to get in trouble.
Master,
it's an outsider in a wheelchair
who fell from the mountain.
Let me check his injuries.
Don't interfere.
-Why save him?
-Exactly.
Why help him?
Mind your own business.
I agree with you.
We should just get rid of him, right?
Guess what this is?
A vessel flute?
You can even play a leaf so well.
I've always wanted to make you a wooden flute.
Give it a try.
It's definitely better than a leaf.
♫I'm walking on a never-ending long road♫
♫In the vast world, how can I get there?♫
♫In the chaotic night wind, the melody stopped♫
♫The moonlight is gentle♫
♫All the feelings turned into nothing but a dream♫
♫Reminiscing about the good old days♫
♫Singing until the voice fades, I'm feeling lost♫
♫Forget all about the past and leave it behind♫
♫Time after time♫
♫Oh, melancholy♫
Qi Feng?
His new injuries are all external.
But the spiritual veins
in his legs are completely severed.
It looks like a serious injury from many years ago.
He must have suffered a lot these years.
Don't worry too much.
To see Qi Feng again
is already a gift from heaven.
I'll protect him well from now on.
I'll go prepare a decoction for Qi Feng.
Thank you.
He's your brother,
so I'll treat him like my own brother.
Thank you.
Bai Shuo.
Let me do it.
No need.
Qi Feng is Fan Yue's brother.
I must prepare this decoction myself.
Then,
I'll assist you from the side.
Cang Shan,
have there been any outsiders
who fell from the mountain here before?
I've been away from home for many years,
so I'm not very sure.
Logically speaking, the chances are small.
Maybe heaven thought
Qi Feng and Master had been apart for too long
and made them meet here in the Stone Clan.
You're awake.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Qi Feng,
I'm Yue.
Yue?
You're Yue?
Yue!
Yue.
It's really you, Yue.
I forgot.
You're now the Demon King of the Polar Region,
Master of Bright Moon.
That's not appropriate.
You're Qi Feng.
I'm Yue.
That has never changed.
How did you escape from the Tiger Clan?
Where have you been all these years?
Back then,
after I was captured by the Tiger Clan,
I was locked in the dungeon.
One day, there was internal strife in the Tiger Clan,
and I escaped amidst the chaos.
After that,
I wandered from place to place.
Then your legs…
Who broke them?
That's not important anymore.
There have been too many demons who bullied me.
If I remembered every one of them,
there would be no hope left in living.
To be honest,
surviving in the demon world,
where the strong prey on the weak,
and only losing two legs
is already good enough.
Since you know I'm the Master of Bright Moon,
why haven't you come to me all these years?
With my weak demonic power,
if I stepped into the vast
Polar Region,
let alone meet the Master of Bright Moon,
I probably wouldn't even survive half a day.
Besides,
I'm a cripple now.
How could I dare approach you?
By the way,
on the day the Baize Clan was wiped out,
how did you survive?
It was Grandfather.
He gave me all his spiritual power.
Then a few years ago,
when the Tiger Clan was destroyed,
was that your doing?
You did that to avenge the Baize Clan,
didn't you?
No, it wasn't me.
Why?
You're the Master of Bright Moon, the strongest demon in the world.
Why didn't you avenge them?
I went to the Tiger Clan to seek revenge.
I also went there to look for you.
But by the time I arrived, the Tiger Clan had already been destroyed.
I searched the entire Tiger Clan,
but I couldn't find your body.
All these years, I've been searching for the one
who wiped out the Tiger Clan.
And I've never forgotten
the revenge of the Baize Clan.
Nor have I ever stopped looking for you.
Back then, the Tiger Clan specifically demanded you.
Why was that?
Some things
are better left unknown.
Qi Feng,
we're brothers.
You can tell me anything.
Knowing the truth won't do you any good.
It will only bring you more pain.
Please, don't ask.
Was what happened back then related to me?
Qi Feng,
tell me.
I want to know.
Actually,
the purple-eyed boy the Tiger Clan wanted back then
wasn't me.
It was you.
♫Don't linger, don't regret♫
♫The last moonlight♫
Yue.
♫The water from my hometown flows gently♫
Let's go out and play.
♫Sending me to the distant place♫
♫In this life, at this time♫
What's wrong?
You were born with purple eyes.
Even though you never said it,
♫I dare not look back♫
I knew it had always bothered you.
♫Is there the same moonlight♫
Later,
I secretly learned a technique to swap eyes
♫On your path?♫
and switched your purple eyes
with mine.
♫I'm walking on a never-ending long road♫
See?
Aren't I amazing?
♫In the vast world, how can I get there?♫
Not long after,
Grandfather discovered what I had done.
♫In the chaotic night wind, the melody stopped♫
♫The moonlight is gentle♫
Yue,
♫All the feelings turned into nothing but a dream♫
why didn't you ever tell me
that you didn't like your purple eyes?
♫Reminiscing about the good old days♫
Grandfather, I'm sorry.
♫Singing until the voice fades, I'm feeling lost♫
I...
Grandfather,
it was my idea to swap eyes with Yue.
♫Forget all about the past and leave it behind♫
It's not his fault.
♫Time after time♫
What's done is done.
♫Oh, melancholy♫
Perhaps it's fate.
Now that you've exchanged eyes,
they can't be restored.
Purple eyes are a natural gift
and never meant to be forcibly changed.
Since you two
have already made the exchange,
I will temporarily
conceal Qi Feng's
eye color.
I hope that in the future,
both of you
can be safe and sound.
♫I'm walking on a never-ending long road♫
Why don't I remember any of this?
It happened when you were 14.
♫In the vast world, how can I get there?♫
Have you forgotten?
At 15, you fell from a cliff
♫In the chaotic night wind, the melody stopped♫
♫The moonlight is gentle♫
and lost all your previous memories.
♫All the feelings turned into nothing but a dream♫
Then why didn't you tell the truth
when the Tiger Clan came
♫Reminiscing about the good old days♫
looking for the purple-eyed boy?
And why didn't Grandfather…
Because Grandfather and the rest of the clan
had already made their choice.
♫Singing until the voice fades, I'm feeling lost♫
What could I do?
♫Forget all about the past and leave it behind♫
♫Time after time♫
♫Oh, melancholy♫
Fan Yue!
You don't need to say anything.
Calm down first.
So, I'm the purple-eyed boy.
The one the Tiger Clan wanted to capture back then was me.
♫The person standing far away♫
How could that be?
♫Don't be afraid♫
Then Grandfather
and the Baize Clan…
♫The stars will guide you to me♫
Grandfather and the clan stayed silent
in order to protect me.
They all chose to sacrifice Qi Feng.
♫Walk towards me♫
Bai Shuo,
who am I really?
What does being the purple-eyed boy mean?
♫My heart feels so...♫
Why did everyone sacrifice themselves for me?
♫It's pounding as I wait for you♫
Everything I have now
was bought with Qi Feng's suffering
and pain.
♫The stars light up your eyes♫
Don't put all the blame on yourself.
No matter who you are,
♫You are my distant call♫
you were innocent back then.
Do you remember what Grandfather told you
♫You are my first and last♫
before he passed away?
He told you to live well.
♫My heart is trembling for you♫
One day,
you'll understand who you are.
You can't let Qi Feng's sudden return
♫In this moment where we embrace each other♫
erase all the pain you've endured
♫Let's never let go♫
and all the effort you've made.
What we need to do now
is uncover the truth behind everything,
protect those who need protecting,
and keep living.
That's what Grandfather
would want to see the most.
♫The stars light up your eyes♫
♫You are the light I yearn for♫
♫You are my determined way home♫
She came to Cold Spring Palace ten years ago.
She knows my parents
and the Chong family's motto.
More importantly,
she has memories of Bai Shuo's dagger.
Could it be…
she's Bai Xi, who went missing ten years ago?
Follow the way of heaven as the way.
Practice goodness,
caution,
and harmony.
If Fu Ling really is Bai Xi,
after she killed Uncle Bai
and has repeatedly tried to kill Shuo,
how could she possibly face the truth?
And for Shuo,
if she learns that the sister she's been missing every day
is actually the person she hates most,
how will she accept it?
But Bai Xi was a human,
while Fu Ling is a demon.
Why is that?
Fu Ling's identity isn't fully confirmed yet.
Telling Master now
might be too soon.
I hope I'm wrong.
A truth so cruel
might as well remain a mystery forever.
Sect Leader,
you want to see me?
I haven't received
any word from Chong Zhao in some time.
I wonder how things are going on his side.
The last time you saw that evil insect in Ning'an City,
it was almost fully grown.
By now, it's probably
already fully grown.
I've already notified other Eternal sects.
Their disciples have strengthened daily patrols and inspections.
No trace of the evil insect has been found.
I wonder what that old dragon from Cold Spring Palace
intends to do with the evil insect.
The evil insect was created by Chen Ye from Cold Spring Palace.
It's said that he's highly skilled in weaponry and poison-making.
I'm worried...
Sect Leader, are you worried
that once the evil insect is unleashed,
its harm
may rival the Nether Poison from back then?
I hope I'm overthinking it.
May what I fear
never come to pass.
Come in.
You are…
Bai Shuo.
You're injured.
I've brought some pills
specifically for you.
You're a physician?
I'm Fan Yue's friend,
and I know a little about medicine.
These pills
will help with your injuries.
That's very thoughtful of you. Thank you.
While you were unconscious, I examined your injuries.
Your recent wounds are all external
and will heal quickly.
As for your legs,
I don't have a way to treat them right now.
I know.
My spiritual veins are all severed.
No medicine can help.
That's what the previous physicians said too.
It's fine.
I'm used to it.
Thank you for your concern.
Since you're Yue's friend,
then you're also my friend.
I don't have much to give,
just a few small handmade things.
I made this bamboo dragonfly myself.
I'd like to give it to you as a thank-you gift.
It's not as precious as these pills,
but it's a token of my appreciation.
It looks delicate.
I'm glad you don't find it too simple.
Is Yue okay?