Open the light
The light that doesn't matter
Wait for you to come
Welcome to see Fushan Sea
The tea is from the fairyland and the Chinese tea
The sea is full of flowers
Six treasures, welcome to see Fushan Sea
The eight big patterns
The
Shandong Ji Xi
Let's go to Zhenmei Pavilion
Let's go
What's wrong with this?
I don't know
Stop
Why did he suddenly commit suicide?
What are you doing here?
I was looking for Miss Tao
Get back my jade pendant
But how did this happen?
I saw her sneakily go here
I followed
I didn't expect her to see me
Just kill me
Old brother
Should be stunned by the mist
Uncle Qiu has been in our family for so many years
I didn't expect
It's actually the inner seal of the power gang
I ask you
What did Uncle Qiu do today?
He is in charge of making sword stoves
He only went to the firewood house today
Still helped Auntie Zhang pick flowers
Just now the fire started from the firewood house
It's going to lead us there
Ye Ning
She went to pick flowers
It must be to poison
Pass my order
All the Xiao family
Don't water the well
You go and check
Is the well polluted?
Yes
Sword stove only has this one mouth
Now poisoned
That's going to get us all into a net
Oh, no
I just got someone to pour water
Made a bowl of soup and sent it to the main hall
You
go
Go
Hero Zhang
Hero Xiao
What happened
The well was poisoned
The soup just now can't be drunk
Hero Xiao
Please be at ease
I haven't used that bowl of soup yet
Since that's the case
There's no need to hide it anymore
Go
Call everyone here
Everyone
This is Mrs. Wu
Greetings, Madam
I'm here
I have a gift for you
Please be seated, heroes
Thank you, Madam
Please
Mrs. Wu
These are all the best results
Of our fight against the power gang
I've learned
That you're fighting against the power gang
I'm sitting here
And I'm in a deep sleep
That bowl of soup
I didn't have the appetite to drink
I was lucky to avoid some
Why did you come to the prison again
I was supposed to go to the Immortal Pass to find my son
Who knew that I was stopped by a gang
When I was passing by the well
I had to hand over the Order of Heroes
Thanks to Hero Xiao's help
I was able to hide here
Madam
I have something I don't understand
I'd like to ask you a question
Please
Madam
You're not from the underworld
But why do those people think
That the Order of Heroes is in your hands
13 years ago
The Northern Wilderness Army
Stole our great He Shan
And led the army to attack the Western Region
They burned and killed and robbed our land
They were so reckless
The people were so rude
Your Majesty
The Emperor was forced to leave the capital
The Western Region was in a state of panic
At that time, Shaolin, Wudang, Emei
Three sects of the sects gathered together
To build a wall
To build the Order of Heroes
And to establish the Blood Clan
If there's a person who can save the King of Wei
You should use this crystal stone to give him the message
In the end
Someone really did it
Yan Kuang Tu
That's right
Yan Kuang Tu broke into the Northern Wilderness Army
And killed 37 people to kill him
He almost killed the commander of the enemy
The Order of Heroes
Is in the hands of Yan Kuang Tu
But he was too arrogant
He was not allowed to fight
He was surrounded by the people on Mount Wuxing
And he disappeared
Until recently
He was not allowed to fight
A bird came to me with this order
The Order of Heroes
Was actually entrusted to Madam Wu by Yan Kuang Tu
That's right
I don't know how the Power Gang knew
The Order of Heroes was in my hands
And started to surround me
Yan Kuang Tu was innocent
And killed him
Hero Xiao
How is the situation outside?
This time the Power Gang did send a lot of people
But my sword furnace is heavily guarded
They can't attack
It's just
It's okay to say
The only water well in my sword furnace
Has been poisoned
I'm afraid the rest of the water
Can't last long
It's my fault again
That everyone is trapped
It's really hard to calm down
Madam, you can't say that
General Wu is loyal to the country
He is the hero in our hearts
All the officials in the Western Regions
Only General Wu deserves the Order of Heroes
This time
Our family can protect Madam Wu
It's our honor
If those scoundrels
Arrest Madam Wu
It involves General Wu's experience
And misled the front line
By then the North Emperor will be in need again
If we are not punished
Then we will be the sinners
Hero Xiao
What's your plan?
I trust the Xiao family
The Power Gang is trying to poison the capital
The purpose is to force us out
Outside the sword furnace
I'm afraid it's already set up
But according to the agreement
Two days later
We must send Madam Wu
To meet General Wu
This matter can't be delayed
We can't sit and wait
Go
Dad
If some of us leave the street
How long can the rest of the water last?
If some of us can get out
The rest of the water can last about 20 days
20 days
Okay
I see
Everyone
We still have to send Madam Wu
To meet General Wu on time
Only in this way
Can we get rid of the current situation
We can also get
The chance to rescue the various sects
Only by working together
Can we defeat the Power Gang
To save our family
But this sword is blind
The Power Gang has a vicious person
Send Madam Wu out in a hurry
Isn't it taking the life of the old lady to risk it?
Besides, now in the world
How many people dare to oppose the Power Gang?
Your arrangement is a joke
Just now, the sword furnace and the Power Gang fight
You forgot so soon
No matter how powerful the Power Gang is
Can it be bigger than our martial arts?
Not to mention
We are all people who oppose the Power Gang
Madam Wu, don't worry
I will do my best
To protect your integrity
I've heard about this child from Huishan
He is indeed the most like your parents
Qiu Shui is right
It's time for us to discuss how to get out of the way
It's just that the Power Gang is now
Surround the sword furnace
Must be heavily guarded
Can't guarantee everyone is safe
That's right
Hard break will only cause heavy losses
Besides, our only victory now
Is to know that the target of the Power Gang is Madam Wu
Why don't we give her a clever layout?
The sky is over the sea
Arrange people to pretend to be Madam Wu
As a bait
To confuse the other party
To ensure that Madam Wu is safe
There must be some people
Attract the attention of the enemy
That's it
The rest of the people do their best
Also ensure that Madam Wu is safe
But in order to let me go out
Let others be baits
I'm really worried
Madam, don't worry
I'll go and lure them away
Qiu Shui
Don't worry
Big brother and the others are not here
Besides, I've grown up
It's time to do something for the flowers
The power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power
of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the power of the powerimme
Everyone
Boxu Marder
Very bad
In use
We would rather take further lying
Quick
Jackey
Reconno Io
Uhm
Monk
Yes
Senior
You're already dead
This time
Jaoǎnyi
Lady Jin and Qiu Shui are rushing out of the prison.
Everyone,
this trip is very dangerous.
Please take care of yourselves.
I'll wait for you to come back
to drink and investigate.
Don't worry, Senior Brother.
Shui.
Mother.
The prison is very high up.
You must protect yourself.
Shui, don't worry.
The child has grown up.
Since he chose to take this important responsibility,
he must have his own thoughts.
Just listen to his opinion.
The children of our family
are not sure
that they will say those big words.
Father, mother.
I didn't accompany you well
on my return this time.
Don't worry.
I will protect myself.
Besides, mother,
I haven't eaten
Ni Chu's noodles yet.
Take this.
Mother,
besides the Three Judicial Offices,
there are also this white bag.
There are many mechanisms in it.
You must remember the secrets of use
and how to use them.
Yes, yes, yes.
Your mother is right.
I was also
seduced by your mother.
You are very good at it.
Shui,
when you were in the capital,
you said you were envious of those little things
that made you out of the world.
But, child,
have you ever thought about it?
Everyone is made of blood.
You should be afraid of death.
But why do these people
die for nothing
when they are in the hands of a hero?
This is because there is something more important
than life and death in this world.
Look at today.
There are so many friends
who are hurt or dead
for our Xiao family.
You must remember them forever.
Father, mother,
I will remember them.
After Madam Wu is out of danger,
I will ask for help from all the sects in the capital
to join hands and fight against the power.
Go.
Take care.
You must take care.
Father, mother,
in twenty days,
I will ask for help from all the sects
to help Jianluo.
Take care.
Your son
is back.
So cute.
My daughter.
All right, all right.
Your son has grown up.
He has become sensible.
Look.
He still has a lot
We should be relieved
that he has found his true love.
That's enough.
I want to see him again.
I understand.
Go.
Kill.
After we broke out of the dragon,
we were divided into four groups.
Uncle Qu, Uncle Mu, and Uncle Tie Li
were the ones who led the dragon tribe to attack the Japanese.
We tried to get away from the other three tribes.
Mrs. Wu also hid her identity in black.
The others were in the dark
and divided into three groups.
They were confused with each other
and took the enemy's soldiers.
Go.
Let them go.
We'll break through.
Go.
Everyone should try to escape as much as possible
to avoid exposing their identities.
We'll try to take more time
to help Mrs. Wu.
This way.
Taobao, Hong'er,
you and your parents
should protect Mrs. Wu.
Take the east wing's forest as a guard post.
Remember, you must bring a protective mask.
There will be a poisonous tent.
The people of the snow tribe will be suspicious.
Moreover, they will be accompanied by Mrs. Wu.
They won't be in danger of being killed by the bombs.
You'll be safer.
We're in the poisonous tent.
Put on a mask.
Go.
I'll go with Uncle Kang.
We'll lead the people of the power house
to the forest.
They're coming.
Protect Mrs. Wu.
Yes.
Go.
In that case,
I'll lead you all here.
Go.
Tang Zhong, Yuhan, Zuo Xiu,
be careful.
Find time to go up the mountain.
The people of the power house won't expect
someone to act against their will.
Go.
I'll stay
and live with you.
You?
One word.
Stupid.
Foolish.
You're dead.
You?
Go.
No.
Brothers,
stop fighting.
Go.
Let's go.
Third Master, go.
Go together.
Jin'an.
The Xiao family protected me.
Now I'm grateful to them.
Stop talking.
Go.
Third Master, go.
Kou Yangqing.
You're worse than Fu Tianyi.
You can't kill me.
Go.
The thing of Xiao Qiu Water is quite useful.
This is...
It's for anti-toxic.
Take it.
One for each.
It's safe.
Take it.
Protect the old lady.
Yes.
Go.
Stop fighting.
Retreat.
Go.
What?
Where is the old lady?
I don't know.
Young Master asked me to be dressed up like this.
Father, mother,
although Qiu Bo died,
but the power gang suffering double.
You can follow Feng Nuang
as the old lady.
Do I need to inform Mr. Feng?
No need.
Yes.
What should I do
if she's really the old lady?
Mother, I have another plan.
Why did Xiao Qiushui change her mind so suddenly?
Where is the old lady?
We'll know when we find Xiao Qiushui.
Let's go back to the source of the prison.
What do you come here for?
Xiao Qiushui is kind to me.
It's not right for me to help her.
You don't seem to care about
Xiao Qiushui's safety
since you came out.
Compared to her,
you care more about the old lady's whereabouts.
It's not right.
Oh?
Miss Tang,
are you here to steal people
and keep secrets from the Xiao family?
What did you mean by saving me?
It's nothing.
drank the wine for the people
and went to live alone.
Run.
Why don't you run?
Okay.
I won't run away.
Run away?
Are you afraid of death?
Not at all.
I'll kill you.
Kill him.
Yes.
It's
You're just playing your own game.
This is just a appetizer.
Tell me where Old Madam Wu is.
Or I'll use your body
to feed my insects.
The Pagoda of the Hundred Poisoned Demon,
this is where you created your body.
Or I'll use your body
to feed my insects.
The Pagoda of the Hundred Poisoned Demon,
this is where you created your body.
Or I'll use your body
to feed my insects.
Tang Rong,
you're good at
hidden weapons and mechanisms.
This time, you have to help me.
Okay.
What do you want me to do?
Boss,
I think what you've been doing lately
is really hard to understand.
Right?
The Pagoda of the Hundred Poisoned Demon has been killed.
The Xiao family has been surrounded.
I don't know how the future will develop.
I have to get ready earlier.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Where are the other guards?
You...
You're poisoned with the Pagoda of the Hundred Poisoned Demon.
I'll get rid of the poison for you.
No need.
Sister Xue Yi
gave me some poison-reducing pills.
I'll take one later.
What about Old Madam and Tang Rong?
Old Madam and them
should be safe now.
Tang Rong,
take Old Madam and Senior Zhang
to the cliff in the back mountain
and set off from there.
How do we get through the cliff?
Don't worry.
I have a way.
Let's go.
Qiu Rui is amazing!
She can really fly.
Old Madam.
Old Madam, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Young Master Xiao is really good at planning.
Let's take Old Madam to the Western Valley.
Okay.
Why did you change your plan?
In the Jianghu,
their combat performances were unique.
They seemed to be clueless
and distracted after leaving the battlefield.
I dared not avoid the Lady Yu as circumstances required.
So I changed my plan temporarily.
Tell me,
Hello?
Looks like my parents
and some uncles have safely returned to the πασκο writings.
It's late.
We have to battle with General Wu now.
I'm sorry.
So it's the arrival of the Red Phoenix.
You're the one who met the king?
Yes.
Who allowed you to meddle in the prince's business?
Did you see the whereabouts of Old Madam Wu?
My master only asked us to keep an eye on the Xiao family.
We never went in.
How could we know where Old Madam Wu went?
I see.
The King of the Sword has also come to see Old Madam Wu.
I have to report to the Prince.
King of the Sword
What about these places?
All of them are infiltrated by the power squad.
After Old Madam comes, she will rest.
Tao Fang, go to the outside of the town to receive her.
If you meet Old Madam, first wake her up.
I will go to Tongfu Inn to see what's going on over there.
Okay. Be careful.
Are you two eating or going out?
The people from the west are here.
You two are...
No one is here, but there's a letter that I must hand over.
There are always some people that are to blame.
X gloom.
Let's leave something unall clarity.
You don't marry anyone else.
They should have other ways to deal with them.
It's not easy.
Let's go.
Move aside!
Did you find anything?
No.
Guard every entrance of the town.
No one is allowed to leave.
Yes.
What are you going to do next?
Let's go.
How many sorrows are there?
How many hopes are there?
The tears fall, the wind is not strong.
The grey fog is like sand.
I can't find my dream in my life.
How many branches are in the world?
Where is the grass growing?
Love and hate are in the past, but the grudge is in the present.
The unbreakable bond is like a horse.
I miss the crossroads of time.
I can't find my destiny.
Who can give me a piece of the sword?
What's left of the ten years?
The sword is cut off by the sharp sword.
Flowers fall, the life is lonely.
The wind blows, the song is sung.
Who cares about love?
The moon is bright and the moon is bright.
The tears fall, the wind is not strong.
Who cares about love?
The moon is bright and the moon is bright.
The tears fall, the wind is not strong.
The flowers fall, the heart is chasing after.