gram.
making Health's
more convenient,
Hooping
and even gave the Heaven Book of Forgetfulness to him.
If you can't defeat me,
you'll have to listen to my order from now on.
undergraduate
Has anyone won?
And hurt us by sheltering?
I'm not playing with you anymore.
The Heaven's General's
Divine Spirit is helping the Xuan-Wing Order.
The Eight Wild Heroes are all in the capital.
Sui Feng, do you know what this order means?
Everyone in the world knows.
That's right.
Back then, the three elders of Shaolin, Wudang, and Emei
were helping the Xuan-Wing Order.
They were all in the capital.
The three elders of Shaolin, Wudang, and Emei
were helping the Xuan-Wing Order.
When the three elders were making this order,
they printed their own fingerprints on this sign.
Take a look at the fingerprints on it.
No fingerprints?
It's fake.
Actually, I have another thing.
There's only one Uncle Qiu in the prison.
How can you be sure that there's no other one?
Qiu Shui, what do you think?
What I mean is
everyone is trying to take the Hero's Order from Old Madam Wu.
In order to ensure that nothing is lost,
Old Madam, you have to make the decision.
Little Qiu Shui.
It must be him.
Chief, Liu Suifeng claims that there's nothing to be done.
How smart is he?
How could anyone lie to him?
It's clear that he hid the real order to fool you.
Chief, if we lose the troops,
and we lose everything,
shouldn't we have a say?
Chief.
The Marquis of Fire has taken another step
in the Xiu Li Qiankun that was with the wind.
Tell me,
should the petals stay on top of the map,
or should they be picked in your hands?
Chief, picking the petals
is only a matter of time.
Only by staying on the top of the map can we get rid of the wine.
The whole Li Gang is this flower.
We are all flowers.
If fighting is about leaving,
only the flower of Jin Yi can be the center of the whole family.
I believe that the wind is just a trick.
He has been too busy these years.
He must have his own reasons.
From now on,
let the King of Sword and the wind
investigate the whereabouts of the Hero's Order.
Chief, I will definitely take back the Hero's Order for you.
I will follow the wind and come to you again.
You are injured. You shouldn't drink.
I am the one who lost my brother.
I am the one who should drink.
It's my father.
I didn't protect you well.
Everything is impermanent.
What can you do?
At first, I thought
that this world is easy.
As long as you are smart and careful,
you can get through the difficulties.
I thought that in this world,
it was always a bit noisy.
As long as you treat your friends sincerely,
you can have unconditional trust.
I thought
that I could change my fate.
Unfortunately,
I thought that
in the end,
I did nothing.
I understand
why Tang Rou trusted you so much.
She didn't come home every day and had to play with you.
No matter life or death,
she didn't care about gains or losses.
She only cared about interests.
She did whatever she wanted to do.
Little Qiu Chen,
you are so attractive
that I can't help but envy you.
Yes.
I can't help but envy you.
The world is so vast.
It's hard to meet people.
How many people
are willing to help the world
and how many people
can be as honest and honest as you?
I don't know what's the rule.
But I know
that the wind and waves took me away.
You risked your life to save me.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have the chance to talk to you so much.
Don't forget what you said to Tang Rou.
We have to help her
to avenge her.
Hero Zhang,
please let the people
die in the world.
Hero Zhang
left the Hero's Order for me.
The wind and waves didn't take it away.
This chess
won't be full-fledged.
I'm not afraid of it.
The game
won't be full-fledged.
Hero Zhang
has been with me for many years.
I know
his intentions.
He has long been
in the world.
He's been with me
for a reason.
But now,
he's not with you
and he's seen the word.
When he was on his way back,
he told me that
if I could have a disciple,
I would be like you.
This dagger
is a personal item of Hero Zhang.
He asked me to give it to you.
If you become a real hero,
it's what Hero Zhang wants.
My son
is still borning it for me.
Even if life
doesn't match your character,
if you are destined to live.
없 concerns the future in the world.
Why bother to figure out your needs?
Even so,
I ordered them to save Jianlu.
But it can solve the Xiao family's problem.
Never.
Mrs. Wu,
I want to save my parents
and the Xiao family.
But the Xiao family's problem
is just a matter of the Jianghu.
If we use the cavalry in the army rashly,
the guards in the capital
will not have a conflict with the cavalry.
The people in the city will suffer.
The court
will also have more doubts about General Wu.
What should we do
about Jianlu?
I want to ask Mrs. Wu
to send a messenger
to the Guangling Plain
to send a letter to my brother.
Tomorrow, I will go to the capital to ask for help.
With the help of my brothers,
I will do my best.
I will save the Xiao family.
Okay.
I will send someone to the Guangling Plain tomorrow
to send a letter to your brother.
In the future,
you have to run for me.
I hope the Xiao family
will be safe.
Thank you, Mrs. Wu.
My Lord,
take this stone
Do as I ask.
There is nothing more that we should consider.
Yes.
It is Yong Jian.
I have been exclus issues with you.
This is not what I mean.
You must be careful minutes before 격护.
You may have lost
if you had put the effort
into becoming the
Undying Man of sect.
You should rest well. I'll leave first.
Don't make decisions on your own.
Song Ming Zhu.
Young Master.
Lady Hu has been in contact with the Xiao family.
The world's heroes are different.
They must be related to the Xiao family.
You should work with Lady Wu
and investigate it.
I understand.
Cao Rong.
Boss.
What are you looking at?
The flowers are falling
The life is full of sadness
Boss.
Do you believe in the future?
As if I'm going to say goodbye
I don't think so.
Who will be the one to end the love?
Why do you suddenly ask this question?
The sky is bright and the moon is bright
The tears fall and the wind is cold
If there's a future,
I'll still be your brother.
The flowers fall and the heart is with you
Ai Da Rong.
Falling for me
It's a deal.
Tick Tock
network power
I look like a demon.
Do you think I know the devil?
He is the big boss of the county bank.
Go quickly.
Daishuang
You haven't輸 even once,
но
If Tang Rou Electric Holy Re Goth
spiritual battery
You two
god
What happen take the
You should go to the manual
Hurry up
What's worse is that I didn't take a close look at the rejection after escorting Madam Lao.
I should be careful next time.
The most important thing now is to save Xiao Jia and the shop's leader position as soon as possible.
Only then will I be able to set up the model and have a chance to make a comeback.
The
Young Master Qiu Shui is afraid of getting others involved, so he insisted on going alone.
He didn't say goodbye to the lady. But he's a rascal.
The Jianghu is dangerous. The lady must return to Tang Gate as soon as possible.
He will take the position of Xiao Jia and avenge Tang Rou.
The three of them will meet at the Tang Gate and worship Tang Rou together at that time.
Brother Lin, it's been a long time since I saw you.
Boss, please help arrange the fastest carriage to Jinzhou.
When did you start?
Right now. I'm arranging it now.
You gave me so many silver coins.
Father, Mother, wait for me.
I will definitely think of a way to get the position of Xiao Jia.
Okay. Okay. Okay. A'Zhu! A'Zhu!
Boss.
Hurry. Hurry. Take this guest to choose a good horse.
Okay. Please, Brother.
I'm sorry.
Didn't you say that the white-skinned man is a rascal?
Did you see the horse?
It seems that you don't know anything.
No.
Seven times four times, that's all, Mr. stomach.
He can not play with your mouth.
Then what do you expect to do?
It's absolutely true.
18 times 30?
Jams people must fight hard.
That's it now.
Really get me mixed up with a horse.
What a bad luck.
Come down! Hand over the money!
Come down! Hurry!
Hurry!
Why didn't you say anything and left?
I have my own way.
You represent Tang.
Don't be too stubborn.
Little Qiu Shui,
you once said that in this world,
you live by your will. I also believe that.
Are you afraid of getting me involved?
Rou Di is no longer here.
I don't want to lose friends anymore.
What do you mean?
You risked your life to save me from Feng Lang.
I'm afraid that I'll get you involved and leave without telling you.
I won't owe anyone anything.
I won't leave the revenge to outsiders.
Since I chose to stay in Xiao family,
then I have to be loyal.
I understand.
I won't talk anymore.
You guys, come and get the carriage.
Walk faster.
Steadier.
Hurry up!
Move it!
Is this what the Jianghu people are like?
It's not a good idea,
but is it still the way to the Jianghu?
Miss, this fire is burning.
The firewood is also set.
You see, we can go now.
Hurry up and get the carriage.
Get lost.
Wait.
If I find out that you guys are doing these things that will harm the heaven,
I'll dig your eyes out.
Did you hear me?
Yes, we heard you.
Let's go.
You didn't let them cook before leaving?
Call them back.
Forget it. Stop yelling.
They don't look like people who can cook.
I don't know how to cook either.
Wait.
Here.
Sweet beef.
When I was young,
when I was young,
I was in a bad mood, so I would drink something sweet.
It doesn't smell good.
It'll be fine after half an hour.
Not bad, right?
It's fine when it's a little added on the HP.
Everyone should be really enjoying themselves.
They should do it.
But have I ever had the face of crowds or crowds of dumb people
I'm hungry.
If I can get some leftovers
from the kitchen,
we can cook together
and cook on the stove.
We can eat together.
It smells good.
What are thoseamed for?
It's said that a star
is a ruined star.
Tang Rong
How come?
It's like a child problem.
In our district,
everyone says,
different people and different individuals have different meanings of life.
This is called volcano practice.
Volcano practice?
Didn't you come from Jins ranges?
Then why haven't I heard about this?
It's normal that you haven't heard about it.
This is a relatively small piece of news.
You still don't understand it.
I guess Tang Rou is probably a natural born.
She's gentle, righteous, kind,
and a very good friend.
She's a good friend.
She should be in that direction.
Among the stars shining in the mountains,
there's only one.
And she's been looking after us,
and she's been watching over us.
rouxin has been into a boycott for a year
and that
Was I such aelesse in this picture?
It was why her missing analyses were so difficult to recognize.
Very pure.
I feel that you are a bit like Bai Yang.
That's interesting.
This is a symbol of nature.
Take it.
As if your boyfriend has been with you.
Of course.
After all these years,
He put in so much effort into this.
fu Cat Division
please,
what are you telling me
Be honest
I went to his best
Well all his good
Miss Tang Fang is also gone
Maybe this Hero Order
But even if he has the Hero Order
He definitely won't CON Inč
But unfortunately, this ambient martial arts sect
I dare not stand in our womanize
I'm going to practice Tang Song.
Tang Song dares to meddle in this matter?
Tang Song has never been promoted to the Tang family.
He has served the power of the power bank several times.
You don't look down on him at all.
Useless.
It's not completely useless.
Go and give Tang Song some advice.
Let him prepare well.
I understand.
I want to see how your master is sick and can't get up.
Do you want to be a coward now?
Tang Fang, don't be afraid.
Xiao Qiushui,
you brought Miss Manheng to my house
to take revenge?
I don't know if you have any plan to take revenge.
I just don't want to be a coward.
I just don't want to be a coward
and help those who have ulterior motives.
Who knows that your family
is like the rumored outside the world.
It's to steal the hero's order
that the power bank was incited to burn.
Don't talk nonsense.
The master of Dingmen is famous for his reputation.
He is also very ambitious.
Why do you want to take revenge on my family?
What the Xiao family has suffered today
may not be the fire of the Ding family in the future.
You!
You are talking nonsense.
You want to force us to fight?
You are so ungrateful.
Tang Fang,
don't talk nonsense.
You are so ungrateful.
Let's go.
You don't need to beg Ding.
He is just a coward.
We have other families to go to.
I'm afraid that all the people in the martial arts world
are the same.
Tang Fang,
thank you for your help.
Let's say goodbye here.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Mrs. Wu
has sent someone to send a letter to my brother.
Maybe my brother
can find the best swordsmen in the world
to save the Xiao family.
So I have to go back
and meet them.
There is another family in Jin.
You haven't asked about it.
You mean
your family?
But your family
never interferes with the affairs of the martial arts world.
As you said,
what the Xiao family said today
may not be a problem for the future.
Actually, Tang Rou asked me before.
Why didn't the Tang family
become the best in the world?
Instead, they let the rat-back of the power gang
to be the target.
I still want to persuade my father
to let the rat-back of the power gang
to be the target.
But if it doesn't work,
I'll go to Guangling with you.
What do you think?
Okay.
I can only try it first.
Tang Fang,
thank you for your help.
I don't dare to pack the tickets.
Let's try it.
Can't we really go?
Miss.
Where is my father?
Master is over there.
Please go there first.
Wait a minute.
I'll go get my father out.
Go.
Young Master,
please have a look.
Thank you.
Go.
Shi Qi,
it's been a long time.
Tang Song,
where is my father?
Master is of course
hosting the family affairs in the inner courtyard.
You're messing with your brother.
Aren't you afraid that the old lady will punish you?
You're the one who's messing around.
I'm not.
You're messing around.
You're not paying attention to the rules of the Tang family
because the ancestors spoil you?
How dare you talk back to me?
Shi Qi,
you dare to bring an outsider to the Tang family to seek reinforcements.
You're even embarrassed
to say in the family letter that you've made a good investment.
It's really ridiculous.
You dare to expose my private life to my father.
You want to use the Tang family's affairs
to solve the Xiao family's problems,
and get them involved in the grudge between the power and the power.
This is not a private matter.
I have my reasons.
If you have any questions,
let's talk in front of the old lady.
Do you really think
that the old lady doesn't know
that we're doing these things?
I'm holding you down
because I want to make a mistake
by promising you to seek reinforcements in private.
If you really want to get in the way of the ancestors,
you can't escape from the death penalty
of your father's death
for trying to take the treasure from the family.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're really tough.
I've received the information
that the power gang is being surrounded
because of the Hero Order of the world.
And the boy you brought
is being beaten up.
Do you think
the old lady's old man
doesn't understand?
You'd better marry me.
I can cover for you.
You're getting more shameless.
Why did you just say no?
Let's go.
Let's talk it out in front of the old lady.
I want to see
if she believes you two.
No hurry.
I've caught the boy from the Xiao family.
As long as I find the Hero Order on him,
Shi Qi Mei,
your crime is proven.
Don't blame me
for not being affectionate.
Master.
Young Master is back.
Father.
What?
You've caused trouble outside.
You can't get out of it.
Now you're back.
You still have a father.
It's not like that, father.
All right.
Go to the temple first.
Come back to talk to me
after five days.
Father.
I came back today
to ask for help from the Xiao family.
The power gang is being surrounded
by the Xiao family.
You know the power gang
is evil.
You're still going to
fight them with our family and our clan.
From the beginning,
you shouldn't have
made trouble with the three boys from the Xiao family.
But Uncle Xiao and Aunt Xiao
are in danger.
How can I just sit back and do nothing?
Do you think you can get away
from trouble by hiding?
What if the power gang
doesn't come to the front line?
Now,
it's not your turn
to worry about it.
I still lead the sword gang.
I used the sword to break the right and wrong.
I'm sorry that the martial arts world of the Central Plains has been open for three nights.
Although our family
is just a branch of the sword gang,
we never dare to forget our roots.
Father.
Since I was a child,
you taught me
to be a man and a man.
You're stupid.
You're still a man of justice.
I used to
be friends with Uncle Xiao.
We walked together,
fought together,
just like today's me and Qiu Shui.
But Father,
why did Secretary Lin
become so unruly?
If you don't want to fight,
I'll
do my best for the Xiao family.
You...
Stop him!
The moon is about to set.
The wind blows the long-lasting thread.
The past is left behind in the rain.
The first sight is like a snowfall.
The world is full of sorrow.
The city always the same.
The song of the rain is a song of the west.
The next one is in the heart.
The mortal world is just a little bit.
A few words to talk about it.
The sword is about to cut.
The wind and rain are far away.
But they are always so happy.
The mortal world is just
a little bit.
A few words to talk about it.
The song of the rain is a song of the west.
The sword is about to cut.
The small world真的是 a small ball.
The mortal world is just a little bit.
A few words to talk about it.
The sword is about to cut.
The wind and rain are far away.
running towards the road of happiness.
The world is full of ups and downs,
the good and the bad.
Drunk and drunk, the morning and the evening.
The sheep head is dry, the bowl of wine is dry.
The world is full of sorrow, the smile is bright.
The world is full of ups and downs,
the good and the bad.
The birds are singing, the birds are flying.
The moon crosses the thousand miles and is bathed in the rain.
Freedom is not just a gun, but also a silver
and a silver star.
The world is full of ups and downs,
the good and the bad.
The smile is bright.
The world is full of ups and downs,
the good and the bad.
The war is not over until this day.