Break through the abyss of light
Let this city and river be buried in the sea of stars
Let the lights shine on the true love
Let the end of the dark night be the middle of the night
So that we won't forget this 100
Let this great battle be the end of both worlds
The sword of the hero has never changed
Let the millennia of light follow me and bloom
Like a light that doesn't fade away, waiting for you to come
Here is the
Mr. Yu is great at catching people.
And I am Tigin's maid.
Why are youение?
Why am I
so capable?
How dare you say that?
Don't do that again.
I am your maid!
How dare you say that?!
She even married my father
Young Master.
Shi Yongqian.
Help him.
Tell the old man in the gang
to be buried in the river three days later.
Tell Wan Mi not to be buried.
Tell her Chen Zhou has gone to the mountain to practice.
I must avenge the gang leader.
I have something to do for you later.
Someone will come to make trouble in the hall.
You must be prepared
to let Chen Zhou go to the last city safely.
Yes.
Before Chen Zhou came to the capital,
he must have thought of the day.
I found the secret letter he left early in the morning.
It said if he met any trouble,
he would be buried with it.
Don't tell me.
Li Chen Zhou was poisoned and died.
He will be buried three days later.
Zhao Shirong wanted to bury the military uniform
in the Guan State.
He wanted to keep it secret.
But he said it was a long mountain.
This is the secret letter.
It's written in the letter.
Li Chen Zhou is really ungrateful.
He knew his identity
was inherited by the court.
But he still tried to persuade the emperor
to give up the peace with the north.
It's the same in the martial arts world.
He always opposed me.
He also found himself today.
It seems that I have to pay a good visit
to his spiritual hall.
I have to pay a good visit.
The power gang is always evil.
We'd better be careful.
Li Chen Zhou has been poisoned for so long.
He should be killed.
Besides, this news
was passed on by the internal bodyguards in their gang.
His news will never be wrong.
It's best to die.
It's okay to die.
But at this time,
it's better to take the military uniform.
Yes.
Go.
Chief Wang, sit tight.
Sui Feng.
Should I close it?
Your Majesty.
Come with me to the river to bury the body.
I'll go with you.
Sui Feng.
Yes.
Sister Rong.
We haven't had the banquet yet.
Why are you in such a hurry to bury the body?
Sister is here too.
Sister Rong.
Why don't you go back to Tang to perform for the ancestors
and give other people a hard time here?
You indeed came.
I finally managed to lure you out.
King of Water.
King of God.
Chief is so kind to you.
Even you are so cruel.
I have been secretly hiding in the underworld for many years.
I never miss out on finding information and secretly sending letters.
Since I knew Li Chen Zhou was poisoned,
and the medicine was hard to cure,
I knew that the power gang was running out of gas.
Today, the letter of the funeral
is the same as the one I gave
to Xiao Kai Yan.
Okay.
Then why did you do it?
We were always in disagreement.
When King of Jian died, I was against it.
Now Li Chen Zhou is dead.
You are the one who is following the trend.
How can you have my position?
You two shameless bandits.
I'll use the knife I left for you today.
Nangong Wusheng.
Even your family
is willing to sell your life for Xiao Kai Yan.
The Power Gang is running out of gas.
What can you do?
I'll take the ice talisman
and make a hand-to-hand fight.
Shi Yongjian.
You protect Lingqiu.
I'll clean up the mess.
mask, mask...
Will you
use me to wide your days of attempt
or
point out any obstacles
probabilities
Everyone has the heart of jealousy.
But your fault
is that you were controlled by your own jealousy
and used by others as a weapon.
I...
Father,
Xun Yi has avenged you.
Li Chen Zhou,
I don't care if you're dead or not.
I won't waste my time
killing you again.
Li Chen Zhou,
I don't care if you're dead or not.
I won't waste my time
killing you again.
Help me!
Chen Zhou.
There you are, Li Chen Zhou.
You really want to die.
I will kill you.
loop
Master
Your Excellency,
there should be some
open trials when you're informed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
This matter looks like
an order will be issued
to everyone in the palace.
This can be settled.
As a lamb.
Right as I say.
However,
but you,
who is placed the hand of De Jin's weakness
in the interests of another.
You are smart and justified.
What are you saying?
Li Shenzhou.
Thank you.
Young Master.
Brother Feng.
Chief is fine.
Don't worry, Sui Feng.
Young Master.
It's an important matter.
I've kept the fact that you were dead.
The social bureau
wanted to get rid of the mole in the gang.
But we didn't want
to hurt Sui Feng.
Young Master.
Feng.
How are you?
I'm worried about you.
I'm afraid that you'll be
misbehaved again and again.
Please don't be rash.
Young Master.
Brother Feng.
Dawang.
Yes.
Take Sui Feng to my study.
Take her to the dark room.
There's a broken jade lantern.
How can we save her?
Shenzhou.
Yes.
The rest
depends on her own luck.
Chief.
I have a request.
Go ahead.
I want to be with you only in the future.
I want to live and die with you.
As you wish.
Thank you, Chief.
Young Master.
Chen Zhaoyi.
The poison in your body hasn't been completely cured.
You can't use all your inner power anymore.
After we save General Wu,
let the King of Medicine
help you with your treatment.
Rong'er.
I agree to it.
What should we do?
The world
is stillva spread over.
If General Wu really falls in the hands of Jian Ning,
might be the best choice.
Why do you think so suddenly?
The traitor of the Power Gang has been removed.
We might have a chance to save General Wu.
I've made up my mind.
Chen Zhou,
is that what you really think?
I know what you really think.
I'll do this for you.
Young Master.
Young Master, be careful.
Why am I still alive?
It's the elixir from Chief's ancient book.
This is the only way to save Young Master.
Then what about Chief?
You can be at ease.
It doesn't matter.
He's commanded me to look after you well.
I was going to save Chief,
but I didn't expect
that someone şeked you.
It's true.
In the end,
you were saved by Chief again.
Thanks to Chief,
I will only
care about Chief and Shurong
in this life.
Then, in the spirit hall,
will you save me?
I'll go and get the medicine for you.
Penfall
distorting return sprinkle
I accept.
Miss Tang,
Qiu Sui
Theemantomb army has passed Xianren Pass,
it's time for centipedes to attack the town now.
push away Qin's troops
and destroy Xianyun Pass from inside
Yes
conversation right away.
Such a talent.
I will go with him.
Since Wu,
you
to gather the桃 probes
and make every effort
Miss Lu.
Stay away.
Wu Guan, I've Haven't know about all this.
There's not oneady place of the entrance.
I...
I'm a man of my word.
Come on.
A man of my word.
Brother Chengzhen.
Oh, no.
You sent people to watch the waterway.
We found the Northern Imperial Guards
hiding in the front.
They're
heading for the Immortal Pass.
It seems that the wild ambition of the Northern Imperial Guards
can't be hidden anymore.
General Wu is not here.
If the Northern Imperial Guards
make a big mistake,
the Immortal Pass
will be in danger.
Well.
Lord Liang.
Take some people
to the Immortal Pass to rescue.
I'll go to the waterway to save General Wu.
That's it.
Let's split up.
Okay.
Find the Prince
Since fate
Rong'er.
Chen Zheng.
You won't die.
No.
I...
I will return to the heaven with my soul.
Don't bother me anymore.
Rong'er.
I'll take you
to get General Wu out.
Rong'er.
Okay, I'll leave now.
You finally saved General Wu's life.
Your wish has been granted.
Shuhua, I'll be with you.
Life is like a game of chess.
The time is running out.
The wind and snow are running in the air.
The road is so narrow.
Life is like a game of chess.
The time is running out.
The world is so beautiful.
Life is like a game of chess.
The time is running out.
The world is so beautiful.
Life is like a game of chess.
The road is so narrow.
The world is so beautiful.
The moon is so bright.