I'll take you to save General Wu.
Gui Xun
Pl representing the northern bl viaje.
General Wu, what shall we do?
Send a message to General Yi of the Imperial Court.
Tell him that the Immortal Pass is in danger.
Yes.
The West and the North are in panic.
They have agreed to negotiate.
Why do you betray your trust?
You are just doing it.
The unnamed person is also worthy to talk to me.
The one who is promised to me is Wu Jie.
Now that he is not here,
the agreement will not be broken.
The general has not returned.
The military order has not been issued.
What should we do?
Behind the Immortal Pass is the fatherland of Daxi.
It is the home of you and my parents.
Even if you die,
you can't let the North Emperor enter the Pass.
You must keep guard at the gate.
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill!
wear out
kill
General!
Where is General Wu?
He's still fine.
We won't know until some time later.
Qiu Shui.
Ever since you entered this water village,
you've been sending him to the Yellow Spring.
Don't you think you're very capable?
I want to be a hero who can save the country and the people.
Today, I'll tell you
that you can't do anything.
Where is General Wu?
Do you think you can defeat me?
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
Tell me where General Wu is.
What's the hurry?
You don't have much time left for General Wu.
If you defeat me,
I'll tell you.
The last battle is over.
You can't go back.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll kill you.
General Wu.
You don't have to kill me.
I'll kill you.
General, the gate was broken.
We'll go back to the inner city.
Kill.
Xiao Kaiyin.
Your time is up.
Go!
Hurry.
Go back.
Xiao Qiushui,
I won't tell you
if you want to save General Wu.
What can you do to me?
Kill General Wu.
Father.
Kaiyan.
Kaiyan,
you're the most stable
among the three children.
With you in the Flower of Illusion,
I can rest assured.
Father.
Kaiyan, why are you back so late?
Are you hungry?
What do you want to eat?
I'll make it for you.
Brother.
Kaiyan,
I've asked for a good sword.
Come and have a look.
Brother.
Kaiyan,
we agreed to fight together.
Let's go now.
Xiao Qiushui.
You're greedy for the Mirror
and use your power
to kill so many innocent people
in the name of the Fire Tribe.
Only when you have no me in your heart
can you reach the end of the world
and make others suffer
so that you can feel the life.
You only see yourself.
How could you misunderstand
that the highest level of forgetfulness
is the love of friends.
Qiushui.
I saw
the snow.
Brother.
This is the last time I call you.
I'm the only one left in the Xiao family.
I'm sorry
for what you did.
I'll go to Tianbu for you now.
Tell me.
Where is General Wu?
General Wu.
He's...
Yes.
It's been fixed.
The Immortals' March
is now in Nanzhou in the North.
No matter what you do,
you only have one way out.
We will present our dead to the show
We will kill all of you!
You are just
a bunch of scoundrels!
You scum!
Get out of Daxi!
You are just a bunch of scum!
Daxi Emperor
will be cut off from the city
to keep the city safe.
Will anyone come to save you?
If you don't move,
I will kill all of you!
I, Liang Dou,
will lead Daxi's martial arts
to guard the country.
I want to see
whether Daxi's martial arts are powerful
or my best martial arts
are better.
Go!
Save Sui.
General!
It's the general!
All soldiers, listen這是
Yes, yes!
Let me kill you outside the city.
Kill!
Kill him!
answering變縮的再度
and they brought stopers there
Create a new generation
free them from theirgains
darling, your life is filled withciald
you deserve to be a hero
it's your turn.
Kill them!
I will not be afraid of death
The light of the CARP Center
Who is it?
From Li Chen Zhou
Let him return to General Wu at all costs.
Your Majesty!
It's a disaster!
The late official is in a disaster!
Your Majesty!
The late official has been killed.
Wu Jie defeated the Northern Imperial Army.
The general of the Northern Imperial Army,
He Lian Yan, was killed by an ambush.
The Northern Imperial Army was defeated.
They didn't let me go to Central Plains for 50 years.
That's great.
That's great!
Pass my order.
Reward Wu Jie and the front line soldiers.
Yes.
Wait.
And Chen Zhou.
He's also defeated.
Your Majesty.
The chief of the Li family, Tan Yu Jing,
was killed on the way to General Wu.
What did you say?
Chen Zhou...
The
speech of commanders of Northern Imperial Army
is still unknown.
And I'm thinking about
whether we can
classify our booty
to extremely explains or not.
Messengers among the mountains and rivers
who were from the Western States
might know
what other remained of their dessines.
you saved me
who understands?
Cheers.
For my bride
My army
is here.
Young Hero Xiao, on behalf of the whole Wu Family,
I hereby toast you all for your great achievements!
Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Thank you, Young Hero Xiao.
Good wine! Good wine!
Let's drink to our hearts' content!
Come!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Brothers,
this glass of wine,
I will drink to all the brothers who fought against the death of the Northern Emperor.
Today's victory
also has their share.
This glass
is for us.
For ourselves!
Good! Good!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Let's go!
Let's drink to all the brothers who fought against the death of the Northern Emperor!
Let me tell you!
From now on,
we are not only four bottles,
we are five bottles!
All five bottles!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Cheers! habr!
Let's drink! Let's drink!
Cheers!
Good wine!
Yes! You're right!
Cheers! Cheers!
Brothers!
Listen to their song!
Come on.
Come and try again.
Tang Feng.
Qiushui.
It's the happiest thing
I've ever done
to know you.
Why are you playing with me?
Come on.
Let's play.
Your family doesn't allow you to marry.
Do you want to marry?
Marry?
Boss, Boss, come here.
The car on the left is going to be a groom.
The car on the left is going to marry.
Is the child you're talking about
the one named Qu?
Yes.
What's wrong with the name Qu?
I don't envy him.
We have five coffins.
We'll go to the five coffins together.
Right?
Five coffins.
Go to the five coffins together.
We'll have five coffins.
Five coffins.
Boss, no more show.
Really.
Come on.
Drink more.
Boss, Miss Fang.
There's wine in the morning, and it's drunk.
I'll toast you.
Come on.
Right.
I toast you.
Cheers.
I made the river
I believe that
they are all
the heroes of the show.
Brother Qiushui.
Miss Tan,
I propose a toast to you two.
I wish you
a happy drink.
I'll drink it.
Cheers.
Brother Qiushui,
it's such a good day.
Let's sing a song together.
OK.
Brothers.
Let's sing together.
Sing.
OK.
The blue sea is small,
the two shores are rough.
Several concubines on this journey by the river.
Heaven is sweet,
history is bitter.
Who cares whoittering under theils of March?
Volcan.
I never meant to say this
So you didn't treat me well?
I didn't treat you badly.
you get to see the broad world through your eyes
yes
you need to go
that's why we have this Souvenirs
this is the case
have you ever been to it?
I am
it's so beautiful
my name ignored
the circle of life
Wijin Temple
wonderful waves
nom valorous
korom
we have wood
Lalalalalalala
Terre Tr sure is so Cerebris
Introduced by my son
The
So many
Love is a wound, hate is a wound
Falling into the cocoon
Really hope
No need to be a big
I don't care about the wine
Love is a wound, hate is a wound
How are you doing in the sea
From the mountains and seas
Qiu Shui, you know
The consequence of using the 15th layer of the Heaven's Book of Forgetting Love
Although it can explode
The power that exceeds several times
It's unbearable
But it's a momentary exhaustive of energy
Soon the meridians will be damaged and the energy will be depleted
Is it his life to pay for it?
The wind blows like a red leaf
The wine is more beautiful than the sword
Really beautiful
Sighing for the reason and sighing for the love
Like a red longan
Life is like a test
The world is like a
I'm curious about the past
The moon and the duck are hard to say
Continuous longing
Obviously, after investigating the river
Confirmed Li Nan's spy behavior
He was ordered by the spy organization outside the country
Steal the national secret
Unfortunately, I haven't waited for the criminal punishment
He died a few days ago
The water is like a test for the heaven
Love is a wound, hate is a wound
How are you doing in the sea
The war is hopeless, no need to be a big
The wine is more beautiful than the sword
Love is a wound, hate is a wound
How are you doing in the sea
The wind and the sea are like a cloud
It's better to be like the wind
Crossing the sea of ​​darkness and darkness
Only eating the world has never been far
It's better to be like the wind
Crossing the sea of ​​darkness and darkness
Only eating the world has never been far
It's better to be like the wind
Crossing the sea of ​​darkness and darkness
Only eating the world has never been far
I'm afraid that I can't protect you.
Who can break the spell of love?
How many loves do you have?
The more you love, the more you care.
The more you cry, the more you love.
The more you fall, the more you love.