♫ How can I leave you behind? ♫
♫ Leave you here alone ♫
♫ It's you who was here as I was desperate ♫
♫ and crying; I finally realized myself  ♫
♫ I can't ever be without you ♫
♫ You always don't like to say anything ♫
♫ It gave me a dream with you ♫
♫ How many times I wanted to confess from the bottom of my heart ♫
♫ How I lost to sadness and loneliness ♫
♫ As you are waiting ♫
♫ Never wanting to let go ♫
♫ A promise to grow old together while seeing the sunrise and the moon sets with a smile ♫
♫ How can I leave you behind? ♫
♫ Leave you here alone ♫
♫ It's you who was here as I was desperate ♫
♫ and crying; I finally realized myself  ♫
♫ I can't ever be without you ♫
I'll let you guys talk first. I'll come back in a little bit.
You look even worse than the guy lying inside.
Is he okay?
Still full of energy and asking where his man is.
I seriously think there's another place that Meng Shaofei is injured.
Where?
His head!
Because of you, he continues to get hurt and continues to wait for you to find him.
He's clearly the one that's injured but still worries about you.
You tell me. If his head isn't injured then what is?
Your personality of disregard for others,
I believe only someone like Meng Shaofei that the fates favor will not die because he's with you.
In order to help you avoid regret for the rest of your life,
listen to me, Brother.
Meng Shaofei has escaped calamity twice,
but this doesn't mean he will the third time either.
Love and life are both beautiful.
But both can disappear at a moments' notice.
If you cherish this relationship,
you may need to let go of things that must be let go.
Don't make it difficult for him.
Remember what I'm saying.
Hi, Little Uncle!
Is everything okay where you are?
I just got to Mali, it's pretty good.
Waiting for everyone to get ready then we're leaving.
When we find our first gem, I'll let you know first.
Okay. You said it. When you get your first gem, don't forget to take a photo for me.
I know.
By the way, Little Uncle.
Do you know what it looks like when an iceberg is melted by love?
Iceberg?
No, what does it look like?
Looks like that Tang Yi.
Tang Yi with the look of someone who died.
Shaofei!
Wake up!
If you worry about me, then don't let me die.
You're in a really good mood for someone who just got shot.
Then, as my boyfriend seeing that I'm okay, isn't your mood, too, not good?
It's very not good.
Fine.
Don't be mad at me.
Standing in front of a bullet is my natural instinct.
I'm angry at myself.
In that case, it's better if you focus your anger on me.
Next time, if you fire a gun again,
I'll still rush in front of it.
I know you're trying to stop me from killing anyone.
Yes.
Because I don't want to see you turn into a sharp and ruthless blade.
Revenge may grant you a brief feeling of peace and satisfaction,
but it will also worry and disappoint those that love you.
Including you?
No shit! Of course, I worry about you!
And I'm the one that's most worried.
Tang Yi,
let the truth come out
and let the killer be dealt with by the law.
This is justice.
This is giving back the victims their rights.
But if you take action and punish him illegally,
society will only see a mob boss killing a police officer.
Then all the things that Brother A-zhi did will be buried forever.
This is the result you want?
Not to mention,
you'd have to pay with your future.
Do you think this is what Master Tang wanted to see?
I will turn over He Hang to the police,
along with Jou Guanzhi.
Tang Yi,
I love you.
A-fei,
it's almost time.
Can I take him away first?
What's wrong with the two of you?
Sitting here all night long, not saying a single word.
Just keep drinking.
I really don't understand why everything had to turn out like this?
We used to all come here often for late-night snacks.
Now it's just the three of us.
I always looked up to Captain as an example.
I also believe Brother A-zhi was passionate about being a police officer.
But I don't know what to believe in anymore.
Will we ever be able to
have those days again?
It's okay,
We'll be better than before, right?
It's okay.
Why are you here?
You're drinking?
Drinking when I'm happy,
drinking when I'm also not happy.
You're not happy?
Happy.
I'm very happy.
Because I realized that to achieve some things,
some people will do what they're not supposed to do.
Turns out that everyone has another face.
Just realizing this point
is enough cause for celebration.
You're talking about what happened with your unit?
It turns out that Captain was covering for Brother A-zhi selling drugs.
It turns out that Brother A-zhi committed all those bad things.
We are the police.
Aren't we supposed to chase the bad guys?
How can he be worse than the bad guys?
Do you know why I became a police officer?
Because I believed that in this world there were no bad people.
The reason why they do bad things...
is because they're forced to.
So, by becoming a cop, I want to tell them
there are so many beautiful things in this world, waiting for us to discover.
Am I also wrong for thinking this way?
Are you also like them,
with a second face?
I came to see you today
to tell you
that I'm leaving in a few days.
You're really going?
Where are you going?
Why is everyone leaving me?
Mom and dad left me, Grandma left me,
Captain went to jail, Brother A-zhi is also in jail. Why are you leaving now, too?
But I already promised people that I'd go.
Then tell me, what I should do?
You're asking me?
If you don't want me to leave,
then I will stay.
Don't leave.
Where's my colleague?
In the washroom, I think.
Go ahead and eat first.
You guys aren't eating?
Captain.
How did it go?
Was she really happy?
Look. Wedding gown photos.
And now, the bride's brother, Jukuan, on behalf of their father, will walk the beautiful Little Ya
slowly towards the handsome and gentle groom, Yucheng.
Little Ya and Yucheng were in the same class in university.
Little Ya always tried to help...
Very successful and very warm.
Little Ya's smile looks really happy!
The two of them began to date sweetly.
Right now, her brother is giving Yucheng her hand.
Although her eyes were a bit swollen,
she was the most beautiful bride I've ever seen.
Now, let's have the couple bow to the brother to show their gratitude.
Gratitude for raising them all the way till now.
Thank you, Brother. Okay, after the bow...
Little Ya,
Daddy's very sorry.
Now let's use our warmest applause to bestow our greatest wishes to the couple, Little Ya and Yucheng.
You and Sister Lizhen have always been my examples.
I believed everything that the two of you taught me.
You once told me,
"Justice is lighting an oil lamp in the wind.
We are keepers of the lamp,
and we need to always be on alert.
Because even though this lamp is very small,
it is very important.
It will lead people to walk down the right path."
But...
you became a person that let that lamp go out.
You hid the truth from four years ago
and cast suspicions on Sister Lizhen's allegiance and unfounded criticisms.
I know.
I won't receive any of your forgiveness.
Because in between my role as a police officer and a father,
I selfishly chose to be a father.
You don't regret it?
Four years ago,
A-zhi told me he killed Lizhen and Tang Guodong.
At the time, I was very scared.
But...
at the same time, relieved.
Because in reality,
I saved my own daughter.
So that I can see her so happy at this moment
A-fei,
actually, I hated you at one time.
When everyone else gave up,
stopped looking into the details of the case between Lizhen and Tang Guodong,
only you held on to Tang Yi like a dog with a bone.
You kept asking for an answer.
Even if there was no one in the world willing to stand beside you,
you still stood steadfast and relentless.
But you never actually stopped me.
That's right,
I didn't.
Because these past years,
you reminded me every day of what a stupid thing I did.
I wanted to see when you would give up,
to confirm to me that you were like everyone else, and no different than me.
I had fallen
and wanted others around me to also be like me.
It wasn't like that at all.
You didn't stop me
because you were also waiting.
You were waiting for me to get all the facts.
You were waiting for me to tell the truth.
You just didn't have the courage to say it on your own.
You only chose to be a father
but never gave up being a police officer.
Don't think about it anymore.
How can I not think about it?
Even Captain's involved in this case.
Who would've thought that a drug and stolen goods case
would have such a big impact.
All of Brother A-zhi's things are here.
Thank you.
Senior, is everything okay between you and Tang Yi?
He's now out on bail but under house arrest,
neither good nor bad; just going by the book.
What if he needs to serve time in jail later? What are your plans?
I don't know what will happen in the future,
but I will wait for him.
Have you heard? The new personnel has been confirmed.
No.
Who is it? New team leader? Do we know who it is?
You guys don't know either?
When will they start?
Hello?
Yes, I'm Meng Shaofei.
Uncle,
I think I should return this to you.
I heard...
that you were Lizhen's favorite junior officer.
After she was gone,
thank goodness you were there to follow through with the case
and return her reputation.
Thank you for all you've done for Lizhen.
In Sister Lizhen's last years,
she was very concerned about the drug cases.
She often said
drugs have deeply harmed people.
But as soon as we find one channel,
we can save a lot of people.
Her last years,
her focus was all on drug investigation cases.
If you want to receive Sister Lizhen's forgiveness,
don't sell drugs anymore.
You can't help but go with the flow.
Lizhen...
must be very disappointed with me.
This lifetime,
I've done many things wrong.
The only right thing
was to love you.
At the time, the only thing that I thought I did right,
from where we stand now, was the worst wrong that I could have ever done.
My life...
probably started when I first stepped into the gang
and it sealed my losing streak.
Uncle,
have you gone to see Tang Yi?
He won't see me.
He said,
there's no need to meet.
Uncle don't worry about it now,
his personality is indeed like this.
You are with Tang Yi now?
Yes, Uncle.
I'm sincere.
I have no right to say anything.
God has given me back this son,
but our father-son relationship
will probably never be reconciled.
No, it will.
Tang Yi looks very cold and emotionless
because he lost a great deal.
In reality, he needs a lot of love.
As long as Uncle is willing,
I'm positive you will be able to get Tang Yi back.
Look.
Me and Lizhen.
The mob and the police.
Who would've thought that our son
would also be a gangster who was in love with a cop.
The path that you have chosen will be quite difficult in the future.
I'm very happy that
there's still you that is next toTang Yi.
What I can't do for him,
I hope that you can do for me.
No matter what, don't give up on him,
Okay?
Uncle,
you can rest assured,
I will never give up on him.
Then,
I will entrust him to you.
Why do you care so much for him?
Because he is your birth father.
I'm very thankful he brought you into this world,
to be able to meet with me.
Even though I know he's not the one that killed Master Tang,
I still can't
accept him as my birth father.
And after Hsin-Tien Group becomes legitimate,
I will not be able to have any contact
with those that sell drugs.
Actually, he's still very much
in love with Sister Lizhen.
For someone who is very emotional like him,
to suddenly find out that
he mistakenly judged his best friend and girlfriend,
his heart must be loaded with guilt.
He lost both love and friendship.
If he can't even get close to
his only remaining family,
then in this world,
he truly has nothing at all.
I'm done beating.
I know it's hard for you to forgive him in this short amount of time.
This isn't something that you can let go easily.
But when I saw Uncle
having to face such an unrecoverable pain,
a past that he can never make up for,
this type of regret,
I don't ever want to see you go through.
You need to pay attention when you're cooking.
See?
As long as you are willing,
you can always repair it.
Master Tang always used to say
ruling a nation is like cooking.
But after having experienced all of these things,
I finally realized that
people are not that simple.
He said he was going to go see Sister Lizhen.
How about you?
Do you want to go?
Tang Yi!
I don't know.
She's not in my memories.
I don't know where to
place her in my heart.
In her situation then
and during that generation,
I believe that she thought
sending you to a normal family
would be the best for you.
What happened later
was not something that she could foresee.
I don't blame her.
It's just that...
I don't know how
to have a connection to her.
Tang Yi,
not letting go of an obsession
is the trap that we make for ourselves.
Then regrets will only be regrets.
Maybe, you guys can have a different ending.
Thank you for not giving up on me.
Thank you for letting me know
that my existence in this world
has meaning.
Thank you for loving me.
Are you confessing to me now?
You can't tell?
You are Tang Yi.
Why would you confess to me?
And I'm going to be like you.
Be like me how?
First kiss then speak.
Don't try to get off that easy.
We're not finished yet.
Hurry.
What are you going to draw?
Eyes.
Mouth.
What about the nose?
Nose can wait.
Done.
Why do you need to also make your omelet rice
have the same stone face?
It eeds a smile!
I told you many times before.
Isn't this cuter?
These eyes!
What's wrong?
The eyebrows are crooked!
This is crooked.
This is you.
The one you drew is pretty ugly.
Jack,
why are you here?
Starting today,
I'm moving here to live with you.
Why are you moving to my house?
That day, you asked me to stay.
Yeah, you could say that.
But what I meant by stay was not this kind of stay.
You know, because of you asking me to stay,
I gave up everything.
What do you mean?
I quit my job.
So, I now have no salary and no home to go home to.
So... you need to take responsibility.
Wait. Where is your family?
People like us who live with danger with each passing day,
we don't have a family.
I'm alone wherever I go.
- So... take me in
- But...
Think about it.
I can share your rent and can handle all the housework.
Also, I'm a great cook and can help you prepare your every meal.
Aren't I a great bargain?
Seems that way.
Are you hungry?
Let me put something together for you to eat.
Actually, I can do all of these things, too.
You don't need to take everything on.
Housework is done with the family, that's why it's called housework.
Right.
We are a family.
So, we'll do housework together.
You can do Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
I'll be Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturday plus Sunday.
I'm hungry.
Will you give me something to eat?
You definitely loved me.
That's why you gave birth to me.
You must have wanted me to have a normal life.
That's why you sent me away.
But you never thought that
I would still end up on the path to become the mob.
[Beloved Mother, Li Lizhen's grave]
This is what you didn't want to see happen the most.
You have always been in my heart.
I have missed you very much.
Thank you for letting me know that you loved me.
Mom,
thank you for giving birth to me.
Do you still remember what this is?
This is the first present that I gave to you.
I recall that I was very poor back then.
I could only afford one flower.
But you still had a big smile on your face.
What should I say?
You lied to me for 28 years.
You even pulled one over on a trickster like me who did 24 years' of jail time.
The last time we met,
you told me you didn't love me anymore.
A lie, right?
Our family of three
is finally able to come together.
But who'd believe it turned out like this.
It really makes me sick.
Lizhen,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
She...
Your mother,
never let me know you existed.
But we still ended up meeting.
She really is very stubborn
and despises evil with a vengeance.
If she knew, she would be so angry.
If back then, I didn't choose to walk this path,
life would probably be so different.
The "probably" that couldn't have happened,
perhaps now is no longer important.
True.
Each one of us chooses our own lives,
we can't blame anyone else.
This was to get revenge on Tang Guodong,
to try and recruit Jack.
It contains all the information on Hsin-Tien Group.
I have no use for it.
Don't repeat my mistakes.
[This lifetime, I've done many things wrong. The only right thing was to love you.]
- Where's the Boss?
- The Boss and Dr. Jiang are chatting upstairs.
You guys are back.
Brother Daoyi.
Why are you still here?
Didn't you know that I live here?
Being together is being together,
but at least try not to be so blatant about it;
moving in and making it your home so quickly,
isn't it too without restraint?
Sister-in-Law. (T/N: older brother's wife)
What did you just call me?
Sister-in-Law.
Is there a problem with that?
I'm okay with you calling me that.
He really has no shame.
He actually admitted it.
What are you embarrassed about?
I'll talk to you later! I need to rush to get some groceries!
I'll be back in two hours! Stay for dinner tonight!
I'm cooking!
Bye-bye!
So, what did he mean by that just now?
I think, some things
can only be understood
but not said.
Then, what about us?
Only understood,
can't be said.
Is that okay?
Not okay!
Are you done smiling?
I specifically came over to see what an iceberg that is melted by love looks like.
Tang Yi in love is like an antique that has just been dug up;
so rare in this world
that I want to look at it longer.
Just drink your tea.
Why are you in love but still like an enigma?
You're like a closed up clam.
In this world, only Meng Shaofei
would be bored enough to try and pry open such a clam.
True love is invincible!
You're one to talk.
What do you mean?
Andy didn't tell you?
Tell me what?
I got Andy's message this morning.
There's an English guy that just won't let your Little Uncle go
and insisted on sharing the same tent with him.
F***! Why are you only telling me now?
I thought you knew.
Fine.
Why doesn't he answer!
It's still nighttime there.
I'm telling you! Get me a ticket to Mali right away!
I know there's no direct flight.
I'll give you an hour to find a way.
I want to be there in the shortest time possible,
You hear me?!
What are you looking at? You haven't seen me angry before?
Never seen you jealous before.
A jealous Jiang Jintang is like an antique that's just been found.
So rare in this world
that I really need to take a longer look at it.
Why are you copying me?
Jintang,
it's true that love requires you to guard it.
But if you can be with the one you love,
that's true happiness.
Some words are left unspoken.
Once you miss the opportunity, it will turn to regret.
I'm hoping you will not end up like that.
I never imagined you were capable of saying such emotional words.
Me either.
Not bad.
I'm happy for you; you're more human now.
The info is true.
I'm not lying.
You need my help?
Don't be polite with me.
No need.
I'm going back to go pack now.
- For you.
- Thanks.
- I want to drink this.
- No way.
That's mine.
What a coincidence.
How are you guys?
Why are you here?
You guys are here thoughtfully and lovingly picking up your partner.
I'm waiting for someone to get off work.
That's normal.
You said you wanted to quit.
There's got to be another reason, right?
I quit because I found something that I really want to do,
no other reason.
Chen Wenhao already told me.
Before, you unceasingly went after him.
Now, you've finally fulfilled your wish. Right?
Congratulations, ex-Boss.
You used me because you wanted to cooperate with Chen Wenhao?
What's in the past is in the past.
I have my own pressures and reasons to deal with, too.
Relationships between people are based on mutually using each other,
there are no real feelings attached.
In order to achieve one's goal, a moderate amount of lying is acceptable.
Don't get too hung up on the past, okay?
Easy come, easy go. That's the way to maintain peace in this world.
So, what we have between us is just a mutual using of each other
and no amount of true feelings are attached?
Zhao Zi,
that's not what I meant.
A-fei, I'm staying at your place tonight.
Tang Yi!
Zhao Zi,
I've never lied to you.
You're trying to lie to me again.
Let's go!
Put me down!
A-fei!
A-fei, save me!
Sit.
- Afei, save me.
- Sit.
- Let's go.
- Let me off!
Let me off!
Where are you taking me?!
We don't have helmets on,
we'll get stopped by the police.
For you, I don't mind getting caught.
When did they start seeing each other?
I don't know.
Zhao Zi!
Shorty!
- Let me go!
- Zhao Zi, listen to me.
Don't touch me! I don't want to be used by you!
Zhao Lian, listen to what I'm saying.
Everything that's in the past, I won't explain to you.
I admit that during this time, I've given you truths and lies.
But never once did I say them for the purpose of using you,
not one single word.
Do you understand?
I have never used you,
never once.
How do I know which words were real,
which ones were false?
How do I believe you?
At one time, my most trusted superior,
my most trusted senior,
neither one can be trusted now.
What do you want me to believe in now?
You can believe your heart.
Ask your heart,
"Are you still willing to trust me?"
You can believe in nothing,
but these two sentences,
you must believe in.
I like you
and I stayed because of you.
These two sentences, you better imprint them into your memory.
Shorty,
when I was first attracted to you, it was only a curiosity.
How can someone be so silly,
so naive,
at the same time, so horny.
I'm not!
You are.
You touched me... here.
That's because you wanted me to touch you.
I don't care.
Anyway, I was attracted to you.
Let me tell you.
This is the first time I've ever cared so much for someone.
I worried that if you didn't have me,
what you would eat for your daily meals.
I worried that if I wasn't waiting for you at home,
you'd be lonely when you come home.
This is the first time I'm so reluctant to give someone up.
So when you wanted me to stay,
I made up my mind to stay,
because I didn't want to leave you.
If you still don't believe me
or want me to leave,
I will leave.
But you need to prepare yourself,
because there will be a good chance that you will never see me again.
Are you trying to scare me?
I'm serious.
So, do you want me to go or do you want me to stay?
One word, I won't make a fuss.
- I'm leaving.
- Stay.
Nervous?
A little bit.
Wait for me a bit longer.
Are you ready?
Almost ready.
Okay.
Come on.
You're researching this?
Not... Not really.
Reading that won't help you,
I'm more of use.
Wait!
I think... we didn't close the window.
What are you doing?
This way... no one can see.
What do you want to do?
I'm going to devour you!
No!
Don't move so much!
That tickles.
That's not what it said in the book just now.
Slow down!
Don't be so hasty!
You're really ticklish?
Here, I come!
Zhao Zi, don't! Don't!
Zhao Zi, be more gentle!
Don't move!
I'm ticklish!
I always wanted to ask you,
why is that little house and that lighter
so important to you?
That little house was the first birthday gift that
I gave to myself after coming to Hsin-Tien Group.
I always wanted a home.
The lighter is my promise to Master Tang,
to legitimize Hsin-Tien Group.
To let all the brothers live a normal life.
It truly is a formidable task.
But this task will need to wait until I get out
in order to continue.
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
Thank you for agreeing to hand Brother A-zhi over to the police.
This way, I don't need to arrest you myself.
It's you that saved me.
I'm the one that should thank you.
It's you that showed me that not letting go of an obsession,
is the way to getting ourselves trapped.
And more importantly,
causing even more pain to those that love me.
It's you who saved me.
You need to report to them tomorrow.
No matter what happens on the inside,
you just need to remember,
I love you.
Then, will you wait for me?
How can I not wait for you?
Look at how many injuries I have suffered for you.
Look.
I took a knife on the mountains for you.
And this... saved your Zuo Hongye.
And here...
This one I know, don't say it.
You owe me this much.
Of course, I'm going to wait for you to slowly make it up to me.
I can make it up to you now.
Come on then.
Scared?
Are you afraid to let go?
Nope.
Don't you think you're conflicted?
Not at all!
Openly expressing your emotions is not difficult.
Thank you.
I said it, your reply?
You're welcome.
It's true that you're going to leave me.
It's true that you're afraid to let go.
It's true that you'll miss me.
But pretending you're feeling fine is fake.
You're the only one in this world that thinks so.
That's right.
Because I'm the only one in this world that understands you.
I'm telling you, don't pretend you're fine.
Don't be too afraid to let go
and don't miss me too much.
I will continue to watch you.
Continue to watch me?
That's right.
Both my eyes will be watching you.
Tang–
I will miss you.
[The End]
♫ Never thought I’d abandon with no regard ♫
♫ I’d care about jealousy  ♫
♫ I put you inside my heart ♫
♫ Never thought you’d latch onto every opportunity ♫
♫ In every corner always greeting me ♫
♫ I simply dared not to think, also did not know how to express ♫
♫ my true preference ♫
♫ How can I think about that? I simply shouldn’t be thinking of you ♫
♫ Avoiding your attention, I can finally breathe ♫
♫ What situation is this, I don’t want to be awake ♫
♫ Lonely (Lonely). Silent (Silent) ♫
♫ No longer able to guard the saint principle that is in the way ♫
♫ I just want to not care, not think, love till the end ♫
♫ My entire life is completely wasted away ♫
♫ No need to get hurt ♫
♫ We just want to mutually help each other ♫
♫ Steal a bit of savage ♫
♫ One more person to share with, why not? ♫
♫ Don’t mention love ♫
♫ Don’t mention love (It was just assembling some possibility) ♫