Final Episode
Tell them to go home.
Chairman.
- It's over.
I'm sorry.
Everyone,
please go back home. As soon as I hear an update,
I will let you know immediately.
I am really sorry.
No. No. We haven't even started the wedding yet.
Where do you think you are going?
Gun!
Aigoo, what happened?
Anyway, we have to have the wedding ceremony fast.
Aigoo, let's do that. Of course, of course.
We don't know what other things can happen. Aigoo.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
- Everyone be quiet and...
we'll begin right away.
Groom! Bride!
Enter!
I'm here!!
What is this?
I'm not too late, right?
- No, you're not late, lettuce wrap lady.
Aigoo, Mi Young.
Aigoo. Aigoo.
- Mom.
I'm really thankful.
Lady In-Law.
Aigoo, I apologize.
Mi Young.
This event is a wedding that is spectacular and
full of romantic suspense.
Then... can we start the real wedding?
Yes!
Bride and groom, for your beautiful...
happiness!
With strength!
Enter!
♬ I like the dazzling sunlight, ♬
♬ your smile spreads ♬
♬ My heart is rushing, ♬
The officiant is Mr. Lee Joo Yong, who serves as an advisor
at Jangin Chemicals. He's also a distant relative of CEO Lee Gun.
Then, we will have the ring exchange and the exchange of vows.
♬ seems like coincidence ♬
I, Lee Gun, will...
I, Kim Mi Young, will...
take Kim Mi Young as my wife.
take Lee Gun as my husband.
And cherish and love each other for the rest of our lives...
until death leaves us apart...
No, even if death separates us,
we swear to be together forever.
♬ I stand in place and talk to myself again ♬
♬ When I hold out my hand I only love you ♬
♬ My heart wants you, you who is like destiny ♬
♬ I love you ♬
It's exactly Jeju island. Exactly Jeju island.
What should we do first?
- Well, just
eat some local snacks and go up to Halla Mountain
and have some citrus fruit. Then our two days and three nights will disappear in no time, won't they?
Why are you acting like this since earlier?
- Do you know
how thoroughly I planned this honeymoon packed with
things to do for a month?
How can we only have a 3-night honeymoon?
Is giving me time so wasteful to you?
Since I have a new project starting next week, I didn't have too much time.
Can I
really seriously ask you something?
You are not going to ask a childish question like "Do you love me or your work," right?
That won't make any sense.
Look here, Kim Mi Young. It's me. It's me.
The 22nd eldest descendant of Jeonju Lee family
and the only son of the 9th generation,
that's me. I would never ask such a childish and absurd question.
Who do you think I am?
Are you feeling better now?
I didn't feel bad before.
When I am with you Mi Young, I always feel good.
Mi Young, can I show you a really fun thing?
- Okay.
Okay.
Do you know what this is?
A car key.
-Does a car move when you have this or not?
The car moves.
- What if you don't have the key?
Then the car won't move.
- Right?
You are going to see how far I can throw this.
We have to get to the hotel soon.
But you will notice that there are lots of traffic lights.
Every time we stop at the traffic light, you have to kiss me. How about it?
But there are so many traffic lights.
- There are a lot of lights.
Because I have this.
Ah! Mi Young!
Come back here! Come on!
A traffic light!
This is nice!
Mi Young, have you driven before?
Yes, I have a license, too.
But it's a closet license.
- No, it's a closet license!!
(never actually operates a car)
I got my license seven years ago.
- 7 years?!!
How do you drive now? Look forward!
Are you excited?
- Yes, yes. I am!
Mi Young, you're driving way too fast.
Slow down!
I just thought of something since we are like this.
There's a good thing about you driving the car.
What is it?
- I can kiss you anytime.
Gun!
♬ A love story like ♬
♬ the movies ♬
Don't stand up in the car.
Agent Dragon, the name of today's mission is...
"Revival Macao."
We came to Jeju Island because of Chairman's orders,
to do this operation without any mistakes.
Do you follow up to this point?
Yes, Chief Tak.
I mean, Agent Tak.
But...
I have a question.
Ask now.
- Why is the name of the operation
called 'Revival Macao'?
That's because...
Do you remember what happened to the CEO,
three years ago in Macao?
Ahh!
They met in Macao for the first time, and spent the night together,
and ended up...
- That's right!
On this honeymoon, the Chairwoman wants that to happen again.
-But...
Hyung and his wife...
I mean the snail couple. They don't need our help, they're already in love.
Why do we need to do this?
- It all began that day.
Lee Gun... No,
the Snail's husband greatly provoked the Chairwoman.
Gun, you know...
what you should do on this honeymoon with Mi Young, right?
- Know what?
Do it like you did before, and do it all at once.
You'll hand over a grandchild in my hands after 10 months, okay?
Not after ten months. It can't happen.
Why not?
I thought about it and realized my Snail and I have
never really enjoyed the time together as newlyweds.
So for about 6 months, I'm going to enjoy sweet time with her as newlyweds as if we're swimming in sugar water.
What? What, what? 6 months?!!!
No, never.
Even 6 days is too much.
- I'm going to enjoy sweet time, no matter what!
That's right, I'm all for a sweet time as newlyweds!
But the completion of such sweetness is ultimately
that, isn't it?
What is that?!
Then about 3 months?
No, no, no. I don't want to.
I'm going to have a fun honeymoon with my Snail.
Why would he say such reckless words?
The Chairwoman's long waited dream is the propagation of the species...
No, having an heir,
so she decided it's an emergency and called upon me.
That's why she sent me on this special mission.
Re-enact the glory of the past Macau event.
So the operation name is...
Revival Macao!
Mi Young, what are you doing?
This is room 2006 for sure.
We can't let it roll around or flip over.
What if someone misunderstands and comes in just like in Macau?
Check carefully.
It's good.
An ant won't even be able to bother us tonight.
What is it?
What? Oh, I'm going in. I'm going in.
It's amazing.
It's nothing. What's heavy?
Thank you.
It looks alright.
Let's see.
Gun!
You can see the ocean from here!
Why are you suddenly...
Mi Young, you only see the ocean.
And you can't see me?
Huh?
- Here, the two of us.
The two of us.
Gu-Gun!
What?
The sun hasn't even set yet.
Oh, the sun. Right.
♬ Let's leave, the two of us ♬
♬ Abandon everything ♬
When I was young, on days when my dad didn't go out to the sea,
I would sometimes dance with him like this with music on.
Really?
- While he was calling Princess Mi Young.
Princess Mi Young.
But when you usually hear those words,
you should feel as if you really became a princess
and think you'll meet a really cool prince one day.
But while I was thinking about those thoughts, I always gave up on it.
Why?
- I felt a princess and I didn't fit together.
More like a maid type.
Who says you, my Mi Young, are a maid?
My Kim Mi Young is a princess.
A very pretty and kind princess
who opened up the locked up Lee Gun Prince's heart.
I'll keep that in mind, Prince Lee Gun.
Aigoo. They're so happy.
I can't watch because I'm getting goosebumps.
Oh, so cheesy. So cheesy.
It's so cheesy I can't watch.
Did you make sure to get the hotel's help on music and lighting?
Yes, I surely prepared it.
Great.
And the moment they drink the cocktail...
To Secretary Tak, did you surely pass over our Yeoul-do's special item?
Of course! I wrapped it tightly and gave it to him.
What a waste. We should have followed them and created a Macau revival.
That's right.
- In Macau, we did hamo hamo.
Hamo Hamo.
- Hamo Hamo.
It was great.
- You're right.
I'll order this.
You don't know why the cocktail is coming out, right?
Yes.
The cocktails are supposed to come out first when you go to places like that.
At places like that...
Mi Young.
- Yes.
Today is our actual first night together.
It is.
- You don't remember anything from Macau.
Yes. I don't remember anything.
So,
today we need to keep our heads on straight.
Meticulously.
- Meticulously.
Oh, wait.
Let's have a love shot.
Love shot...?
There's people watching.
Last time, you did a love shot
with Daniel... holding each other.
You... Were you then...
You even went there to spy on me?
Who says I spied on you?
It was just a coincidence. I coincidentally saw it.
That's a bit harsh. How could you follow someone around?
Then you did a background check on me?
Since when did you do a background check?
No, it wasn't a background check.
I'm not allowed to have even that amount of interest when I like you?
Why would you call that a background check?
No, but at that time...
Give me another shot please.
Me, too.
Anyways,
mission, clear!
Kim Mi Young, this is alcohol.
What woman drinks so much?
This, this is just a cocktail.
And there is no law about women drinking well.
Were you always so rigid, Gun?
I said it for your own good.
Why are you getting mad?
My own...
I want to leave.
Go then. Go.
Either way you go up, we're going to meet at the same place. Sweetly.
What is this familiar taste?
Why do I feel so dizzy?
Gun, I'm dizzy.
That's right.
We had a love fight.
Gun.
It's a mountain, mountain.
This is also a mountain, mountain!
A mountain, mountain.
Ah~haha
Why do I feel like I've had 'deja vu' all day long today?
Why is the door not opening?
This is Room 2006.
That's not it.
It's room 2006.
It's room 2006!
- So why can't I open it?
Open sesame!
- No, no, no!
No, no, no!
No, no.
Nine! It's nine!
Nine!
- Is it nine?
Room 2006 is over there.
Here's 6.
- Over there!
Here. Here.
- It is 2006.
What?
- Oh!
Are you the mountain hikers? Mountain hikers!
The mountain! It's the mountain.
Go in! Go in!
Please go in!
Our mission is finally over.
Finally, it's time for Grandmother's dream to come true!
Hyung, I wish you the best.
Where's my Snail?
Honey, Father-in-law...
What our Gun said about playing sweet newlyweds...
never mind such nonsense.
The purpose of this trip is just for one thing.
Two go on a trip, but three should come back.
Give him some power, please!
Please, you got it, right?
Yong's da... No, Gun's dad.
I have nothing more to add,
while you're at it, let it be twins.
They have the same birthday and get morning sickness together,
so let's make it consistent, hmm?
You're actually good.
Mother, did you just compliment me?
Well, it wasn't a curse.
Tonight, for our Gun and Mi Young,
please gather up all the energy and...
Fighting!
Rice! Rice, rice, rice, rice, rice!
♬ Did one night pass? ♬
♬ Spin, Wheel. ♬
Barley.
♬ Even a burning candle looks lonely tonight ♬
Rice, rice, rice!
Barley!
♬ The spinning wheel ♬
Aye! What's this?
What happened?
I don't know either. Why are we like this?
Wait, this familiar picture.
Deja Vu?
Macao!
- Macao.
How could this be?! This is insane!
I've been waiting for last night for so long with big expectations. This can't be happening.
By the way, did we sleep?
We did. Of course, we did.
That't why it's already morning.
The sleep I'm talking about is not that kind of sleeping...
Like you know, that sleeping..
That... I'm going crazy!
I'm going crazy, too. I really don't remember anything.
How could this happen?
What nonsense!
On my way to the room after drinking the cocktail,
I was suddenly really dizzy.
After drinking the cocktail on my way to the room,
I was like that, too.
Wait a minute.
No way.
Gun! Why are you doing this?
You don't even know who's in that room.
Just wait. I'm sure those spies are in there hiding.
Open the door.
Open the door before I break it open!
1-2-!
Brother-in-law, Chief Tak.
Hello, Sister-in-law.
CEO... Hi!
This is horrendous! Hey, Chief Tak.
I won't forgive either of you.
They must have had a reason for it. Stop.
They're grown-ups.
Mi Young, you're flawless, but you're just too nice.
That's the problem.
Being a full-grown adult,
how can they do this sort of thing?
Do they have no dignity?
You dare deceive your CEO?!!!
It's because of what you said to Chairwoman Wang.
What did you tell her?
Nothing.
It's all because, you told Grandmother
that you'll raise a child later, because you want to have fun in your newlywed life.
Dragon, I'll tear off your wings!
Did you really say that? Why?
It's because we never had time as sweet newlyweds,
so I wanted to live with only both of us together.
Anyway...
I will never forgive either of you.
How dare you ruin the first night of my honeymoon?!
I can't remember anything of our long night!
CEO, you'll spend countless nights with her from now on.
Just the first night...
It isn't a big deal, right?
That's right. A wise answer to a foolish question, Chief Tak.
What are these people saying?!
- Calm down!
Chief, you can't do that! Brother-in-law!
Answer me!
Calm down! Calm down!
Daniel Pitt?
Yes, I am Daniel.
Thank you for coming out here despite the sudden call.
You said you had something to say regarding Se Ra.
What is it?
This picture is...
Can you recognize who this little girl is?
Please tell me. I beg you.
You're right.
It's my Se Ra.
Mom.
Se Ra.
Why are you crying?
Are you crying because you're sad that you're not my biological daughter?
Even so, I hoped I was your biological daughter.
It's true that I brought you from the orphanage.
What's wrong with that?
I did my best raising you.
I never neglected you.
So why are you pitiful?
Don't pity yourself.
That will help you be happier.
Mom.
- That's right.
I am your mom.
And you are my daughter.
Am I not fit to be your mother if I didn't go through the pain to give you birth?
Thank you, Mom.
For saying it like that.
This work is really powerful, and...
leaves a definite impression.
The person who did this even said he won't be able to do this again.
It's his masterpiece.
To say that means he put his everything into it. I'm jealous.
You can also do it.
Oh, actually my wife is also a very famous artist.
She's shy to say it herself.
From Paris, France, do you know Ellie Kim?
You're the Artist Ellie Kim?
She's really the artist.
- Oh, my. I'm really a fan.
Please give me a autograph. Of course.
Thank you.
Look at those stars.
Wow. They're really sparkling.
We did great to come to Jeju Island. We even get to see this.
If I listen to your words well,
I think we'll only be filled with good events.
If that's true,
then I think it all began the moment you called me the goddess of fortune in Macao.
I think our fate began
when we both started
running for the ring.
The ring!
I wish it really was that.
The thing called fate,
I thought it would be something special, but
I don't think it is.
Right now, the person in front of my eyes...
Everything will be fine if that one person is there.
The feeling of not even being able to imagine anybody but that one person,
I think that feeling is fate.
I'm okay even if we aren't fate.
Because I'll love you like you're my fate.
Mi Young,
as we live together,
later, because of me,
because of my problems,
a really difficult and sad day may come.
Gun,
don't be afraid.
Every day and every moment, let's do our best to love each other.
Let's also try our best to be happy.
I'll give an oath to those stars that you like so much.
Until the day those stars disappear,
every day, like you're my fate, I'll love you.
Let's do that.
Mi Young.
Ahh...This is great.
Mi Young,
thank you for staying next to me.
I'm very happy to be next to you.
I really love you a lot.
I also... love you.
♬ Don’t go away
When the long night passes and sun shines ♬
♬ I hope my warmth from my fingertips reaches you ♬
♬ My everything, my destiny ♬
♬ My heart keeps going to you ♬
♬ When I open my eyes, let me hear it ♬
♬ Let me hear you saying I love you
Sweet melody ♬
♬ I’m in love with you, ♬
♬ I’ve never felt this way ♬
♬ Do you know about my love? ♬
♬ You’ll stay in my heart, forever more ♬
♬ Let me hear you saying I love you
Sweet melody ♬
Oh, what did they say? What did they say happened?
What did they say? Did they say it's correct?
I... have twins.
Twins?!
They are really... really twins!
What do we do?
What do you mean what do we do?
What a cheerful surprise!
My Gun did it in one try again. Two strikes!
Aigoo.
But, wait.
It's great, but our new honeymoon life is over?
You took away my sweet honeymoon time!
You took it.
Hurry up and return it.
Aigoo.
- Ah, I don't care.
Sorry.
Who is it?
If you feel like eating ice cream,
come to the park in front of our house.
Your Oppa.
You called really fast. Within just a month.
It took some time.
From here on, we should be a brother and a younger sister.
I thought that both of us needed some time
to take care of our feelings.
Thank you for waiting and giving me time.
Because of you, I've become more at ease now.
By the way, who is that woman?
How is she? She's my younger sister. She's pretty, right?
Your sister seems to be a bit pretty.
Well, as you can see (me), my family does have good looks.
But.. where did your sister go that you're drawing her alone?
I,
while buying ice cream, lost her.
It's your fault then.
You should have come earlier.
Your sister must have waited so long.
Mi Young!
That's what I'm saying.
If only my legs then were as long as what they are now,
I could have run faster then.
Then I wouldn't have lost my pretty sister.
I'm so sorry it kills me.
Then why don't you just go there now?
I'm curious as to how fast you've become.
I will never go by myself again.
I have to go around while holding our Mi Young's hand.
Oppa...
3 Years Later
Dr. Octopus, so what does that mean?
How do you think it is?
- Quickly! Just tell me!
It's clean, as always.
- Is that true?
Seeing that there have been no signs or symptoms by your current age,
I think you can live the rest of your life
comfortably and happily.
I understand.
You can go now since I have an appointment.
Wait a second, Dr. Octopus.
By any chance, are you going to my mother-in-law to spout ink at her?
Well, that...
I have to eat dinner and...
I'm in a good mood, so
I will give you a really special tip. Come here!
Doctor, you also came today.
I'm sorry to come at this late hour.
I came to eat dinner.
It's a given to eat at a restaurant, right?
Please, have a seat.
Yes.
I will give you the rice wrap shortly.
Rice Wrap Lady.
What did you just say?
Gun gave me a tip.
He said when you're called that, you kind of like it.
'Ssambap' lady sounds way better, than 'Ssambap' grandma.
Rice Wrap Lady.
Well...
What is it?
Tomorrow, do you want to go and watch a movie with me?
Movie?
Tomorrow, I can't.
I'm sorry for asking that.
I was only going to eat and then leave.
I'm sorry.
I can't... Can... I can.
I can.
- Really?
You're really a miracle lady that makes the impossible work.
Wow! Our mother-in-law's flirting techniques are awesome.
Hamo! Dr. Octopus is hopelessly trapped.
But when did those two become like that?
Aigoo.
At that age, it's not like they're looking for their destined match.
Isn't it too late to find love?
Why does age matter? If A, who used to like B,
gets nicely involved with C, who used to like A,
that's love and fate.
What? What? Is there anything special about that?
By the way, why are you not seeing Secretary Tak these days?
That person is very busy.
Just a second!
Bravo!
Your dance was great.
Really?
Thank you. I think my skills are getting better
thanks to your compliment.
If you have lessons from Charles for one hour,
I think you'll be able to go and represent our dance class in next year's dance competition.
Really? The legendary dancer?!!
That's right! The legendary dancer! Leg-dan.
Really? Leg-dan?!!
That's why I invited the legendary dancer here today.
Oh, my what should I do? Really? What to do?
Come out. Legendary dancer!
Is that really him?
Wow! This is an honor! I really like and respect him.
Teacher Leg-dan. Are you really Teacher Charles?
I really love and respect you...
Lawyer Hong!
Here, people call me Charles.
Call me Charles.
Call me Charles? What happened here?
Living as a lawyer is very hard and boring.
You need to have an exciting hobby at least.
Now... let's put aside using petty human language for a bit
and start talking through dance.
I'll learn from your great expertise!
Alright.
Teacher, please accept my feelings!
Hey, Moon Woo Bin, you can't do this to your teacher.
Why? Why can't I? Is there anything impossible in this world?
Look at this. What kind of situation is this right now?
Oppa!
- Aigoo.
Did you come back from New York today?
- Yeah.
What's with this kid.
- Should I tell you about my popularity with my own mouth?
Aigoo. Really...
Ahjussi, who are you? What's your relationship with our teacher?
I'm the person who loves your teacher the most in this world.
Is it true, Teacher?
That's right.
He's also the person I love the most in this whole world.
Teacher, even so, there are no words called "give up" (pogi) in my dictionary.
Those words are only for when you're buying cabbages!
('Pogi' is used when counting napa cabbage)
That is a statement that I heard somewhere.
What should I do? Because of me, you might have missed the future match.
Kim Tae Woo, instead saying weird things, go date a woman.
Isn't it funny that your sister is the person that you love the most in the world?
Talk about yourself.
Kim Mi Young, who is pretty but useless.
I am telling you once more...
I didn't come out here because I wanted to.
I came because I feel like I have to show my disapproval once and for all.
Mom,
we are the only two fated for each other. Destiny!
Does destiny feed you dinner?
Yong! Mother!
Hello, I am Jun Ji Yun's father.
I think that with your daughter...
First, let's order.
Right, this restaurant is affiliated to the company I own.
I hope that you like it.
Ji Yun, why didn't you tell me?
I don't want somebody to like me because of money.
Chairwoman Wang.
Aigoo, hello.
Sit down, sit down.
Aigoo, I didn't know that Ji Yun is your youngest daughter!
Mother, how did you come here?
What do you mean how?
This is the meeting of the in-laws for my grandson.
Should the eldest of the house,
just stick her butt at her house?
Grandmother, thank you.
It's been a while since I've lived alone, and I'm sick of fighting with Ji Yun.
Now, I want to let her do anything that she wants to do.
Yes.
Of course. We should get them married as soon as possible.
They must be desperately impatient around each other.
Here, this is japchae.
What is this? Kimbab! And lastly...
And what could this be?
There are so many!
- It was really hard to make these.
Here, Suk and Yoon, let's eat fruits with Mommy.
- Wait a moment. What are you doing right now?
I already fed our twins food,
fruits, vitamins, and everything, so don't worry about anything
and just eat. Take this!
Thank you.
This is Mommy's. This is whose? This is Mi Young's.
And who is this? It's Mommy's. All of this is your mother's.
Don't touch the kids. I will take care of them,
so eat all of this here.
- Thank you.
Alright. What do you want to play with Daddy?
What shall we do?
Should we cook? While the food is cooking,
I will do something funny. High five me! High five!
Here, high five!
- That's right!
That time comes back. When we high five, what time comes back?
Story-telling time!
Today, I will tell a story that is the most beautiful
and happy in this world.
Look forward to it, look forward to it!
Eat food! Eat now!
- I got it.
Here. Princess Snail.
Princess Snail.
Here. Your dad is reading. Here, freeze!
Freeze! You guys have to listen to this!
Be quiet and listen.
A long, long time ago, there was a princess who lived on a small island.
But that princess was wearing circle glasses. The same ones as your mother!
It's the same as Mommy's!
But she was bad at studying; so bad that she'll be the worst in her class in math!
She was bad at studying.
What is this?
- She was bad at studying. What is next?
It's so interesting. Let's read the next page!
The princess has an illness, in which she can't refuse even a stranger's demands.
And second, she can't abandon the heart that she receives from other people.
What are we going to do? She was a strange princess who
has a strange illness in which she doesn't know that she's a princess
and thinks that she is a maid.
She was a princess.
As expected, there was a rude prince that lived in the neighboring land,
but that prince
first called that princess "Snail".
"Where is Snail? Did you see Snail?" Saying this...
Like a snail, the princess crept in slowly
and in the end, she took over the prince's heart.
One day, the prince became addicted to the princess.
And got an illness where he can't live without that princess.
People were worried about the prince and felt sympathetic,
but the prince wasn't afraid at all.
Because the princess was near him.
As long as the princess is next to him,
as long as she loves the prince,
the prince will never be sick again.
The princess and the prince had twins
and are living happily ever after. And forever more,
they will
live happily.
Yoon and Suk, be careful!
Aigoo!
Suk!
Thank you.
Mi Young, do you ever regret marrying me?
Why would I regret that? When you, Gun,
are in front of me right now.
Today and the moment right now, thank you for being next to me.
For being next to be from back then,
till this moment...
Thank you.
I love you, Princess Snail.
I love you, Prince Lee Gun.
Thank you so much "The Fated Team"
Thanks to all moderators for your hard work
Channel Manager: pilar_velasquez
Seggers: yolswels091, bjohnsonwong, auroratasya, TimberFan, narin78, gesti_lagi,mihaelagh, Wafaahs, Dudie,
babyinspiritestar1, AmyPun, SignsofSerendipity, kitty100
Subbers: deehudgens94, choco130, gpark6642, StarlightO
b_kim9_2, earthna, kdramalovers, juulie, xeunyoungie, leeseulcxcx, niore, hellodramalover, lilipopxlove, skahyun
lemonysweet, geneva68, gmtn96, peterlim28, AnoidsTheRobot, allysoo2000, xxjojoahnxx, mancixo, hannuhh830
Editors: bkiss, salz, victoria_s, jenners18, Arishia, hermoine77
Chief editor: kakashiandme
Page designer: Chelthias
Card designer: gesti_lagi
Thank you to all followers
Thank you and goodbye.