Episode 18
Jangin Chemical's CEO, Lee Gun, is about to enter to reveal his decisions.
- Grandma.
Where is Gun right now?
- Mi Young...
Our Gun... What are we going to do with our Gun?
CEO Gun of Jangin Chemicals holds a press conference.
- What are we going to do with our Gun? What should we do?
What's your relationship with CEO Lee Gun?
Did you know anything about CEO Lee Gun's hereditary disease?
Tell us!
Please move.
Stop!
Say something!
♬ I try erasing but I can’t erase you ♬
♬ You’ve become my everything ♬
♬ Oh you, I can’t see you, ♬
♬ I can't touch you, ♬
♬ But I’m okay ♬
♬ Even if goodbyes are sad ♬
I am Lee Gun,
Jangin Chemicals' CEO.
♬ But if you are happy, ♬
♬ If you can smile, then I… ♬
Taxi!
♬ The more I erase you, ♬
♬ I will miss you. ♬
♬ I will shed more tears than today ♬
Firstly, the rumors about
my genetic disease are all true.
However, all the vicious rumors about my disease
are not true.
And because of my disease, I understand
the stock holders' worries about my ability to run the company.
So I, Lee Gun, here today,
officially announce my resignation
as Jangin Chemicals' CEO.
♬ I will miss you the more I erase you ♬
I'm sorry for worrying many people because of my personal reasons.
♬ Like fate, I won’t ever have anyone like you ♬
Lee Gun!
♬ Only you♬
♬ Only you ♬
♬ As much as my tears, ♬
I found out everything.
♬ Good bye, my love ♬
The reason why you kept lying to me
and why you pushed and sent me away that viciously.
Look, Ellie Kim.
What are you doing at somebody else's press conference?
Lie to me while looking in my eyes.
Tell me that you didn't miss me at all for the past three years
and that I was not meaningful to you in your life.
Secretary Tak!
Get her out of this room.
What are you doing right now?!
Tell me.
If you are confident that you can live without me,
I will really let you go.
♬ Your smile spreads ♬
Fine. I lied.
If you are having a hard time, or if you are in pain, I will also be in pain!
That's why I lied!
Gun, are you stupid?
What did you say?
♬ I keep thinking of you,♬
♬ You, who just seemed like coincidence ♬
Why are you worrying in advance
about the hard times I might face?
Don't do that anymore.
Why...
Because of a disease that hasn't occurred yet,
why do we have to be sad,
be in despair,
or cry in advance?
We can cry when when we have to.
Look, Kim Mi Young,
don't misunderstand.
Even if you say that you found out everything,
nothing changes. My disease won't change,
and I...
♬ I shout out loud, I only love you ♬
I don't have the right to love you.
♬  You who is like destiny ♬
♬  I love you ♬
Why do you need a "right" to love?
I'm saying that it's okay.
That ticking bomb...
even if we don't know when it might explode, don't be scared in advance.
No matter what happens,
I won't let you be sick alone.
I love you.
♬ I miss you ♬
♬ So I turn around again ♬
♬ I think of you as I stop in place ♬
♬ When I hold out my hand♬
♬ And hug you tight ♬
♬ The twisted destiny will become love ♬
♬ I shout out loud, ♬
♬  I only love you ♬
♬ My heart wants you, ♬
♬ you who is like destiny ♬
♬ I love you ♬
♬ I only love you ♬
♬ My heart wants you, ♬
♬ You who is like destiny ♬
♬ I love you ♬
Room 2006 again.
Room 2006.
I thought that we have to talk by ourselves quietly.
So I asked Secretary Tak.
This is shocking, just shocking. Do you know where that place was?
In front of all those people,
you somehow took up courage.
Why did you act so coldly
and push me away?
Look, Kim Mi Young,
this disease is not a joke.
I don't know when I will not be able to remember you,
or when my body will be paralyzed and make me unable to move.
When there is a ticking bomb inside me, how can I ask you to stay with me..
so shamelessly?
Why can't you?
It doesn't matter to me.
Then Gun,
if there is a ticking bomb in my body, will you just abandon me and run away?
That makes no sense! How can that make sense?
If I have a pair of scissors, I would cut the red line, blue line, or all lines of the colors of the rainbow.
If that doesn't work out, I will see your face for the last time, hug you, and
after I do everything, we will explode together. How do you think that makes sense?
See. You will do that, too.
Why are you telling me that I can't do that?
Do you think that I can just abandon you?
There is no use now.
Even if you push me away,
I'm not going to move a step.
How can I be greedy about you?
When you are this nice
and stupid.
Gun,
sometimes it's better to be greedy.
In the press conference, CEO Lee Gun and Ellie Kim kissed
Is a Korean version of Notting Hill couple going to be born?
What is she doing?
What is this? Is she crazy?
Why? It's so romantic.
That level is considered erotic.
Hamo hamo. They are so into each other.
Oh my...
MBS news, This was Kim Soo Ryun.
- How could they.. over there..
Why?
It seems like I am dreaming right now.
Listen carefully.
A dove, dove, dove!
That's a dove.
There is one... No, two doves flying.
There is an another one.
Oh, there's another one flying high up over there!
Mi Young,
the fact that I'm eating with you on the same table,
seems like a dream.
Why are you like that to me? Are you taking your revenge on me?
Yes.
- What did you say?
For three years, you lied,
acted harshly, made me sad.
Consider this a punishment you're receiving because of those things.
Yes, I deserve this.
I deserve this!
Kim Mi Young,
can you take your revenge on me on this side, too?
Do it!
Revenge!
Poke.
Then...
are we sleeping together here?
Sleeping together?
Of course, we should sleep here.
Really?
If we come in, it costs the same whether we sleep here or not.
We have to sleep here so that money isn't wasted.
Yes!
Three years...
Those times that made me cool.
Great, great, great!
That's right. We should eat first.
We should eat.
Mi Young,
we are sleeping here
because you wanted to.
The distance between us isn't coming closer.
Since we already paid for the room...
Yes, we are conserving money.
You are so meticulous!
It's a yawn. I'm just yawning.
I'm so tired. I'm going to sleep.
You are tired, right?
Yes. I'm so tired.
Since so many things happened today,
I'm also tired.
I'm going to sleep.
Mi Young, look at me.
Before,
the thing we did...
The thing we did?
That thing we did.
In English, k-i- double-s.
K-i-s-s.
Yes, that.
There were too many people earlier, so I wasn't in my right mind.
So even though it still lingers in my body...
Yeah, we weren't in our right mind.
Can we try it again?
One more time, k-i- double-s.
Retry it once again.
Again?
Secretary Tak! Secretary Tak!
That damned Secretary Tak!
It might be an emergency, so answer it!
It's okay.
Then, Mi Young, up to here...
Stop the beat.
You are paused, until I come back.
Frozen!
- Frozen!
You really have to be frozen.
Frozen!
CEO, something big happened.
What now? What, what?!
All the big things that I know of already happened. What else is there?
You're the one in trouble!
The love story that happened at the press conference is melting the whole nation.
You are Gunmeo from Romeo and Juliet,
and Madam is Julmiyoung from Romeo and Juliet.
Julmiyoung? What, is she some julmiyeok(string seaweed)?
Just call her Miliet.
Yes sir. Oh, I forgot.
Chairwoman Wang initially collapsed,
but regained her strength because she thought that she can't be bedridden in your current situation.
As expected, Madam Wang.
And...
the board of directors doesn't seem to want to accept your letter of resignation just yet.
So everything is on hold.
Everything is because of your
ability to do work, which cannot be replaced, and people's favorable opinion of you.
This charm. I'm sick of it! It won't die out!
Then did you decide with Madam to go along the highway of love?
Without a speed limit, just straight on.
And kiss along the way
and the ending has to be dramatic!
Kiss? Hang up!
This rascal chatters like a sparrow.
Mi Young, I'm going! You can unfreeze now!
Yeah!
Mi Young.
Mi Young, Mi Young, Mi Young!
How can this person, in that short amount of time.
Don't be ice, not ice.
Ttang. Ttang (unfreeze)!
Aiyoo...
My snail.
With this small body.
How did you take up such courage?
Thank you.
Grandmother, from now on, I will stay next to Gun.
Mi Young!
- Even if it hurts when it hurts...
I'm not going to leave Gun alone.
No, you can't.
- Yes?
Knowing Gun's condition can recur again,
I, from now on,
won't be able to grab your hand again (and ask you to come back).
Grandmother.
- At a young age, with your grandfather,
I didn't know when I got married.
Later, when I found out everything, I was already in love with him.
But I don't regret it.
We loved each other, and it was enough for us.
But the regret could go on for a life time.
Without knowing anything, it was that difficult.
If you run to it while knowing everything,
how painful will it be for you?
Grandmother...
No matter how hard the road is,
if I am next to him,
I think I can overcome anything.
Please consent, so I can be next to him.
More than my consent,
should you not get your mother's consent first?
If that is what you will, and you have your mother's permission,
I will follow what you want.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Of course, we should let him go.
Didn't he personally say he would resign?
In fact, other than the time he temporarily lost his memory 3 years ago,
there have been no events pointing towards disease progression since then.
Furthermore, in the past three years,
our Jangin Chemicals has grown so much.
That's true. That's a fact.
He was actually diagnosed with the disease,
which can recur any time. We cannot leave
our Jangin Chemicals in such a person's hands.
Then, those who do not want CEO Lee Gun to resign,
raise your hands.
Look here! The majority does not want his resignation.
How can we vote by just raising our hands
even before we officially propose the agenda?
Why not? Why can't we do that?
Calm down, everyone.
Here, here, here.
Stop it already! You're having a bloody battle!
Have such fire and enthusiasm at a company meeting!
CEO Lee Gun, the words you said at the press conference,
don't you have to keep it?
I will decide my own fate.
I, Lee Gun, will resign
as Jang In Chemicals' CEO as of today.
But...
the time will be three months.
What kind of retirement is that?
I never said that I would retire. It's a vacation.
Vacation.
I thought about this long and hard, and realized that after I've become CEO,
it seems I never took a proper vacation.
That's absolutely absurd.
Then...
why don't we take an official vote to make it reasonable? I'm fine with either.
during the three months,
who will take responsibility of the company affairs?
Who will take responsibility?
Who?
A management specialist who will take on
the responsibility for 3 months,
whom you already know, I brought him here!
Chief Secretary.
It's the chairwoman.
Once I retired,
everyone's mouth became fast but the body became slow.
How our Jangin Chemicals has survived these past 50 years,
I will clearly show you.
This place has changed a lot.
I know.
It seems like just yesterday when we decorated this place.
But what's wrong? Bringing me all the way here.
If your getting in the mood that makes it seem serious.
Then, tell me. My heart is ready.
Thank You, Daniel.
If not for Daniel, I would have left without knowing his truth.
I know.
I looked so cool when I u-turned with one hand, right?
Thank you so much.
Daniel, without changing, was always next to me, like this.
But I...
won't be able to stay next to you.
I'm really...
really...
Sorry, right? Inside you're sorry to death, right?
And you regret letting such an attractive man go.
Yes, that's right.
I'm really, really, going to regret it.
I've been through a lot myself. So I thought of competing with him,
but I'm no match for him.
But really, I think my personality is too nice.
Maybe I need to change and be a bad guy.
But Mi Young.
I also need time to settle my feelings on my own.
I was with you for three years, I can't just say goodbye.
I'm really sorry, Daniel.
How will I be able to face you if you feel so bad like this?
Just for a little while.
Give me some time to settle things on my own.
Father,
I think I am pregnant.
Excuse me.
Cheer up.
- Father.
Don't be scared and cheer up!
That side is a little off.
No, no, not like that.
- Does it look okay now? It is. Good job!
To you,
I really don't have any secrets from you now.
That's why I feel so comfortable with you.
I want to gain courage to pursue you, Mi Young.
Mi Young, will you be my real family?
I wanted Mi Young to be my real family
so desperately,
but no matter how earnest you are, I guess it'll never work out if you're not meant to be.
Hey, what's wrong with you? Is something wrong?
Mom, what am I going to do?
I lost my wallet today,
and I don't know where I lost it. I searched everywhere.
But as it turns out, it was in my bag.
And so?
- Then while listening to music on my cellphone,
I looked for the cellphone for quite a while thinking
I lost it.
Well, that could happen. So?
I think I have the hereditary disease.
Why would that be the disease? You're just forgetful.
No, no, it's the disease. I'm sure it's the disease.
I'm also from the Lee family. It's possible.
Yong, about that...
I have something to tell you. Come here.
Madame Wang!
Brother-in-law!
Dragon, what's wrong?
I'll go after him.
Why is dragon like that?
Let's talk.
What is it that you want to say?
I'm sorry about your illness exposed on the media.
I didn't mean it to go that far.
That's a first. You apologizing to me, it's a first.
To you, I might be a thorn in your side and
the woman who made your mom's life miserable,
but in some way, I'm more pitiful than your mom.
What a ridiculous thing to say.
What are you trying to say?
- It's my unfortunate past.
I was going to forget about it all and throw it away,
but I still have these lingering feelings.
Why are you giving this to me?
For my failure to act like an elder all this time,
consider it my apology.
Brother-in-law!
Brother-in-law--
Are you okay?
Please don't call me brother-in-law anymore.
What do you mean?
Sister-in-law,
I...
am not a son of this house.
Who told you that?
What am I going to do? I was so happy I had a grandma and a brother.
I was so happy that I could finally be a decent brother
to hyung-nim and that grandma gave me compliments.
Also, I was happy that you were like my real sister.
But Mom says I'm not in the bloodline of the Lee family.
- Brother-in-law.
- My mom's more pitiful.
Keeping it a secret her whole life.
How heavy and difficult must it have been for her?
To me, once a brother-in-law is a forever brother-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
I tried so hard, but I ended up losing my memories again.
Honey.
- My wife doesn't know that I have such a secret.
Honey, don't go. What would Gun and I do? Don't go.
Please don't go.
And I... couldn't possibly
tell her I became ill with the disease.
- Honey!
My loved ones,
I didn't want them to be in life-long pain
because of me.
- Honey...
There came another person whom I was sorry to.
The person who's looking after me.
That woman.
I couldn't give her love, but
I wanted to at least give her and her son a place of comfort.
This is like a dream.
Aigoo.
Even though Yong was not my son,
I want to give him love, at least a little, that he didn't receive from the father he has never met.
Gun,
my son Gun,
I miss my Gun especially today.
What are you doing here?
Mi Young,
thank you.
For not going anywhere,
even though how harshly I treated you.
For staying with me till the end,
thank you so much.
I should be thanking you.
For accepting my feelings.
To me,
there isn't a second that I want to be away from you.
Starting now, let's stay together forever.
I will.
Every minute, every second is precious.
Madame Wang,
I have something to say.
What is it?
Now I don't budge at things that easily anymore.
I, from today on...
Right away,
I'm going to live with Mi Young.
Right away?
- Yes, right away. You don't want to?
No. I can't permit it.
Seriously, why? Why can't you?
Did you get Mi Young's mom's approval?
No, I didn't.
- That's why I can't.
As a person who's also a mother, that's not right.
Then, if I get permission, it's a go?
Yeah.
She said that's okay. She said okay.
Since my grandson left the company to me to go on his vacation,
I have to go to work early. You two, leave.
Yes, Grandmother.
Madame Wang, seriously. I'm disappointed. You were so cool before.
But now you care about what others think.
You've become average now. Average grandma. I'm disappointed.
Kids nowadays don't have romance.
Back in the days, if we fell in love, we would just leave home
and start a family so that no one could say anything.
Kids these days. I don't know if it's because we raise them so well or something..
It's a problem. They've all become bland.
Mother, what are you planning to do?
Are you okay with Sister-in-law
getting back with Lee Gun?
No, I'm against it.
I would feel iffy about them getting back together
even if he weren't sick,
so why would I let our Mi Young go to a sick person?
Based on the articles, he is fine.
They can be together if they like each other.
Hamo hamo. It's her life, let her decide.
It's not like we could live their lives for them.
- No, I'm absolutely against them.
How could you? CEO Lee Gun even received Dae Chul.
You shouldn't be like that.
That's that. This is this.
Be quiet! Everyone shut your mouths.
Oh! Mi Young.
Mom.
What were you thinking that you decided to do that?
I heard he has an illness.
And you still want to get back with him, really?
Mom,
I know too well what you are thinking and worrying about.
But can't I live the way I want just for once?
As you know, Mom, I've always minded the people around me,
and couldn't refuse things because I was afraid that
people would feel sorry.
But...
this time, I want to live the way I want.
Not knowing that he broke up with me for my sake
due to his illness,
I ended up hating him.
Now it's not hate anymore,
I really want to be good to him.
Mi Young.
- Huh?
I can't accept this. I will never approve of this.
- Mom.
- Are you the only one who likes that rascal?
I really like that kid, Gun.
But when I know first hand what being left alone feels like,
I can't do that to my own child.
After spreading your father's ashes in the sea,
you know how I raised you by myself.
It's not like you and Gun have a light relationship. You two love each other very much.
You'll live as if you can't live without the other.
But if one of you disappears,
how devastated you'll be.
I... can never approve.
Mom...
Mmm...
Our snail must be sleeping tight by now.
Look at you sleeping.
Yes, come on in.
Dragon, what are you doing here late at night?
What is this?
- I'm quitting the company.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm not even the CEO anymore.
I felt you should know.
Me and my mom are planning to leave this house
as soon as we find a place.
All these times, for all you've done,
I'm really thankful.
Hey, Dragon.
You...
Who said you can be out of the picture?
Huh?
Do you know how big of a societal problem it is
of the number of young unemployed these days?
If a company that's diligently paying you, you should be diligently working for that company. How dare you try to weasel out?!
You!
Who said you could leave this house?
I!... am leaving this house.
That's why you!
with your mother,
in this house,
with Madame Wang, instead of me,
you should stay well.
CEO.
I told you to call me hyung, you rude punk!
Hyung-nim...
- Freeze!
♬ Find those dragon balls, ♬
♬ the world's most mysterious secret. ♬
Oh.
Hi, Se Ra.
We see each other often lately, right?
Well, since you live next door,
I see you often.
Why did you drink so much?
Are you currently healing your broken heart?
Kang Se Ra, you must consider me pathetic.
I had a company dinner with my staff.
Not a broken heart, but a company dinner.
Don't emphasize it. It makes you look even more pitiful.
Aren't you on the same boat?
What did you say?
Let's not be harsh on each other.
It wouldn't even be enough to comfort each other.
Well, I guess.
Why isn't it coming?
Oh, you're going to fall.
Ah, ah! Really!
A little more. Just a little more.
No! No!
Just a little more.
Seriously.
Here. Here.
Why is he so tall like a pole?
Ah, so exhausted.
Look here, Daniel.
Just brush it off quickly and get back on your feet.
We are both hurt people. That's why I'm saying this to you.
So foolish.
You should throw it away.
- CEO Lee Gun.
- Yes.
For a person who said he'd take 3 months off to do some reading and renew his mind,
do you realize you've been looking at my face for an hour?
What kind of nonsense is that? I've been looking at this book.
I've been staring at this book the whole time.
It was for a second. Just a glance.
Lies.
It's upside-down. You should read it the right way.
How did this happen?
when did it become upside-down.
That's weird.
But...
How are we going to convince my mom?
It's weighing on my mind.
That ssam-bap lady...
is full of charm.
There is another side to her.
I will do whatever it takes to get her permission,
so just believe in me.
This is a precious time that's been so difficult to acquire.
We can't spend this time being full of worry.
I will try to convince my mom, too.
Okay.
What are you painting?
You can't see it yet.
- Why not?
- Why can't I see it yet?
- Not yet.
Oh, this...
I haven't finished it yet.
♬ Kiss...♬
♫ Kiss me darling, kiss me, kiss me tonight ♫
What are you doing?
What? What?
- I've caught you, I've caught you. Red handed.
Come here, come over here.
- I've caught you. Hahah.
Come here. Hurry up!
Your timing is unbelievable.
Unbelievable.
Wow. This is great! Great, I love it.
It's refreshing to see you here instead of work.
Ex-Madam... No, Comeback Gun.
Our madam who did that,
have you been well?
Since I couldn't see Chief Secretary Tak's face for a few days,
I've missed you.
"You've missed him, you've missed him."
You shouldn't say these kind of words rashly!
What do you mean she can't?!
Stop saying nonsense, and show us what you've brought.
What's all this?
These are places you two can have a nice time at, which I have
"select", have selected.
Since Chairwoman Wang won't let us go into her place, I thought we'll have to live somewhere else.
A place so expensive feels burdensome.
I'm on vacation right now, but it's not like I run a mid-sized company.
I'm CEO Lee Gun of the great Jangin Chemicals.
I've worked hard until now, and saved up a large amount of money.
So, these costs are just the cost of gum to me.
CEO Lee Gun of the great Jangin Chemicals,
I know a place where we can live closely to each other.
A place where we'll be close to each other?
Tightly?
- Tightly.
Ji Yeon, we're here!
Unnie! Unnie!
Welcome!
I'm honored to meet you, my VVIP client
and returning brother-in-law.
She's Jun Ji Yeon, right? Not, Ji Hyun but Ji Yeon.
Ji Yeon is going to lend us her house.
You are lending it to us?
As a couple manager, I'm happy to have brought you two together.
When did you bring us together? We were brought together ourselves.
Please don't get on her nerves.
Okay, of course.
Come inside.
As a couple manager with a strong sense of responsibility,
I am trying to complete my duties by giving you this house as the last step in creating this couple.
I know you'll be very grateful, so I will post
your ardent love story on my couple manager blog.
That, well.. You will have to talk to my legal team...
I understand it all, so make yourselves at home.
Ah, really?
But Ji Yeon, where are you going? Are you moving back home?
Unnie!
Don't you know who my dad is? If I go home now, I'll be on house arrest immediately.
Then where are you going?
Hello...
Are you saying that you are going to live
in this house from now on?
Yes, Chairwoman, could I do that?
No! With whose permission?
Is this your house? This is my house, I make the decision!
This is the house exchange contract
that I've signed with CEO Lee Gun.
Noona, are you serious?
Yong, what are they changing?
She exchanged houses with Hyung
and they are going to live in each other's houses.
No way. It's not like they're exchanging clothes.
Even though it's simple, a contract is a contract.
So you are saying that you are going to accept her living here?
Yes, it's written here in the contract.
It felt empty without Gun and Mi Young anyway.
It worked out well. Go and unpack your things.
Thank you so so much, Chairwoman.
You. Until when are you going to live here?
Until you like me.
Look at her. She's not your average girl.
Look how nice it is with a new blanket.
- The new blanket is nice.
- The blanket is here~
♬ You’re my girl oh my sunshine
Brighter than sunshine ♬
Tada! We're done.
♬ I wanna feel you I wanna be loved. Like a dreamy paradise ♬
Should we lay down to try it?
♬ A love story like the movies
since we met like destiny ♬
♬ I’m nervous, my heart races
Like I’ve been enchanted, I’m falling in love ♬
♬ I look for you like a habit
I think of like a routine ♬
Mi Young.
♬ My clueless ♬
You didn't need to push me away. Why are you being like this?
♬ heart didn’t realize it’s love ♬
The blankets are so nice.
♬ I’ll make you smile♬
There's no place for you to hide in this small place.
♬ forever ♬
Hurry, hurry! I'm almost catching up to you! Here I come!
♬ I’ll wipe away the tears. I promise you. ♬
♬ You’re my girl oh my sunshine
Brighter than sunshine ♬
Aigoo... Aigoo... Aigoo...
♬ I wanna feel you I wanna be loved
Like a dreamy paradise ♬
♬ A love story like the movies
since we met like destiny ♬
♬ I’m nervous, my heart races
Like I’ve been enchanted, I’m falling in love. You’re my love♬
Hello. I'm a mandarin duck.
Hello...
Didn't you say that they don't go with the house?
Aigoo, about that time, I'm sorry.
But this picture sure is pretty.
Where should I put them?
Put them wherever is pretty.
No. Where should I put them?
On the bed.
It's the chip that made you Lady Luck.
We can't always win the game of life,
but as long as you have that "chip,"
you will always have hope and the chance, so keep it well.
Mi Young! Mi Young! Out the window,
there's a swallow's nest. How can that happen?
Wait, Mi Young.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No.
If nothing happened, then why are you crying?
Tell me, what is it?
It's because I like it.
- You are crying because you like it?
What is it? Hurry up and tell me.
By any chance, do you remember this?
Ah, this. Isn't this the lucky chip that I gave to you in Macao?
You had this all along?
I can't believe that you are by my side now.
Because I can't believe it either,
I keep looking at you to make sure you're still there.
♬ I like the dazzling sunlight, ♬
But now you can't. You can't disappear during this precious time.
♬  your smile spreads ♬
You need to stay put right beside me.
♬ My heart is rushing, ♬
Just like super glue.
♬ I laugh like a fool ♬
Just like you said, I'll really be super glue.
♬ I keep thinking of you, ♬
♬ seems like coincidence ♬
♬ In case you see my heart, I secretly look at you from far away ♫
- Stay by my side for sure, forever.
Just like super glue, okay?
♬ I draw you out then I erase you again ♬
♬ I stand in place and talk to myself again ♬
♬ When I hold out my hand and hug you tight ♬