Release patient in Room 502.
Are you telling my mom to die!
That's why!!  Kneel before me...
and beg.
You were like that last time, too. Why do you keep on saying that you can't do surgery?
I have an eye disease.
I can't see well. I knew it was going to come someday, but I didn't expect it to be so soon.
What are you saying? National bankruptcy?
A Yeoido pipeline has collapsed and is filled with water.
In the worst case scenario, there may be sacrifices.
How can I tell my kids to go in and die, who will go?
Then are you saying it's okay for this country to fall into ruin?
Was being a firefighter just a job you did to earn money?
Episode 17
- Did you have no honor?
Does this make sense to you?!
Yes, Yes. I don't. Did you give me
this to show your pride and make us worthless?
My only crime is that I didn't wash, didn't eat, didn't sleep, and only rescued people!
We have only work to do our best to save people and for your order of not putting fires out!
Those who have families and children, tell them to go die?!
Would those words come so easy to you?!
Then what do you want to do? Huh?
In the maze like the Yeoido pipeline,
should I send someone who doesn't know what he is doing and make him suffer?!
Do you think saying this to you is easy?
I'm saying that we should save this country with the least amount of sacrifice!
I'm giving you the opportunity to save our people and the nation!
Aigoo, thank you.
Thank you so much  for giving me that chance. I'm so thankful that I'm tearing up.
I'm so thankful to the bones that words won't come out.
Chief Choi.
I...
I'm quick at putting out fires.
I'm not good at using people, so
please give me some more time.
Until when?
Until tomorrow.
Okay. I'll wait.
The patient's vitals are good.
The urine is coming out very well as well!
It was too chaotic at the animal hospital but
this patient looks familiar. Give me the chart.
- His name is...
Kim Pan Seong. Kim Pan Seong.
I looked into it, and there seems not to be a need for that.
Do you trust the internet more than me?
No, it's not like that--
I will assume you do not want the treatment and conclude our discussion.
Our conversation is recorded in here.
No, Professor.
You saved a patient that I abandoned.
What does that mean...?
He was in the primary stages of liver cancer and he did not want to follow my treatment guidelines so I refused him.
Is that true, Professor?
I did.
I live to save patients. That's a real doctor.
Hae Sung, thank you for saving this patient.
It was the patient's fate.
It's a life that even survived the earthquake.
He lived in such a difficult situation, how can you try to abandon him so easily?
Leave this patient to me and
everyone, you may leave now.
In Busan, I was known to be a pretty good doctor as well.
Doctor. Someone came from Busan.
Busan?
Dad!!
Ddol Mi!
Ah, it's really my dad!
Of course, I am your dad.
Daebak... how did you get here?
Daughter is working so hard.
As a father, do you think I would be able to let go?
I brought your clothes, too. After coming back to Busan, you only took a shower and left without even getting clothes.
Your mom is worried.
How long are you planning to stay? You brought everything.
Well, it'll take about a month for Seoul to find it again. One month or may be 2 months?
I'm planning on doing good things while I'm here.
What are you going to do if the company goes out of business?
It's enough that I raised that much money. It's enough for us to live.
Dad. Greet him. This is Doctor Lee Hae Sung.
Hello, I'm Lee Hae Sung.
I'm Ddol Mi's father, Jung Won Saeng.
Ah, you are quite tall. If I want to get a good look at your face, my neck will crack.
Ah, I'm sorry...
Don't say anything.
No, I'll just slightly go inside your mouth.
It got ripped a lot. Looks like we need to have 1 to 2 stitches.
Stay here. I'll get it.
Such a pompous ass. You idiot.
Tada!
What is this?
Makgeoli!
I brought it directly from Busan!
Wow, my dad is amazing. People would really love it.
I have one box of fishcake, too. I did well, right?
Dad, are you saying that is something to ask about?
Really? Us, too?
Yes, although there is only makgeoli and fishcake, let's have a nice drink.
Makgeoli? Boss, don't grasp the situation, and let's just have a drink.
I don't want to drink any makgeoli right now.
He's acting so polished again by himself.
You need to at least feed your babies.
Alright, let's do that. A machine functions with gas anyways.
- Thank you.
- Ah, it's nothing.
Excuse me, perhaps... are the nurses also coming?
Don't move it. Okay...
Okay.
-The Busan doctor's father?
-Yes.
He brought a fork crane and a bulldozer to do some service.
He even brought makgeoli and everyone is having a drink.
Well, they're doing it by themselves. There's nothing bad to that.
Ah... I, too...really like makgeoli...
I like it, too.
Yes. The alcohol you drink is important, but who you drink it with is more important.
After this earthquake is cleaned up, we'll need to clean up our hospital as well.
Yes, who are you planning on sending to Gaehuanal Samchung hospital?
Who else, the orthopedics.
Give me some. So rude to your sunbae
♫  Tonight's ♫
Ah, no. Hold on.
♫  stars, if you think about them ♫
Hey, hey Let me go
♫  My old love seem to be coming back ♫
Stop drinking.
I'm going in because I feel sick.
Oh, no, it's fine.
It's okay. Your nose is red. Wear this.
What is this?
Oh my!
If you can't drink, you should've said something. Why are you drinking everything that was given?
Hold on.
Why?
Are you okay?
What are you doing in the hallways? There are many eyes here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. For you to see me like this.
What? Tell me everything.
Tell me everything, I will hear you out.
Motorbike.
Motorbike? What about the motorbike?
Don't ride on another man's motorbike.
No matter what, even if it is Teacher Lee Hae Sung.
And... I wish that you don't ride other man's car, as well.
Pour me some.
Stop it now.
Who will give us this much makgeoli again and when?
But...why are you so stubborn these days?
It's because of Seo Yeon, right? Because you are concerned about her?
Receive this one drink.
Alright.
Work hard, okay?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Pardon? Do you need anything?
No, it's not that. By any chance, do you know Kim Jong Seo?
Kim Jong Seo?
What part is he in? Is he a nurse?
No, singer Kim Jong Seo.
Beautiful Restriction. He's a rock legend.
Of course, I know him. I like him a lot.
When I used to work at Hongdae awhile ago, I got to know him.
Oh, really?
At times, there are concerts in Hongdae, and he keeps telling me to come.
He gave me 2 tickets because I work hard as a firefighter.
So?
But during the concert day, there was an earthquake.
- You probably couldn't go.
- Yes.
It must have been a pity for you. You look like a big fan.
I have to go in now.
Oh, alright.
You can't be drinking, right?
I think Prof. Han...
It seems like you are lying so you don't have to perform any surgeries.
What are you saying?
I'm so glad I won't be seeing your face.
Is it true?
I can't believe it either.
Not being able to see as time passes, I wish this was a lie, too.
When I went to the surgery center, you were the one who started teaching me the tie.
I always worked my best to become like hyung.
Now, I'm working hard for my mom; although, I did lose my job.
Hae Sung.
It's all in the past now. Let's just give it up.
I...
would like it if you didn't get sick.
We looked at the ultrasound and CT scans
and did patient conferences together, too.
Where are you going?
To the ICU patient.
- Like this.
- Woah, you're really the god of stitching.
How can you make the spacing and the angles so accurately?
When will I be able to do it like you?
I'll teach you all of the surgery procedures and methods I know.
Really? Why?
Because I'm so thankful you came under a person who has a lot of strings. Lets go!
I'm going to catch up to you one day!
Like back then, those hard times,
I wish that we could do surgeries together and continue living like we are now.
Do we need to change, too, if the world changes?
If a building collapses because of an earthquake,
do our feelings collapse as well?
Teacher.
Can you recognize me?
Yes. It's been a long time. I've seen you at Busan, right?
That time, our Dol Mi got so touched by teacher that...
she wanted to become doctor.
- You must be very proud of her.
- Of course.
She is the first to become a doctor in our family.
- Well my uncle...
- That's enough
Get rid of your hands.
Here, take a drink.
- I'll bring some food.
- Oh, okay.
Here.
Here, here. Give me a drink as well.
Dad! Where did you put the squid?
That is in my bag.
Look for the squid! If you look closely, it's there.
Where's the bag?
Teacher Han, the makgeoli.
Oh my, it spilled.
Father, what are you doing not being careful?
Teacher, I'm sorry. I was looking away for a moment.
Professor Han,  do you have nyctalopia (night blindness)?
I'm sorry. Please excuse me.
Oh, yes.
- Aigoo...
- Father...
Doc...
Aigoo... that...
Dad, you should have held the cup well. What did you do that he spilled all the drink?
Making him embarrassed.
No...
I was just holding the cup.
Should the one holding the makgeoli put in the cup properly?
Who? Han Woo Jin?
Yes, Han Woo Jin...
At some time and place, I ...
Hurry up and go straight to the point.
It's definite that there is a problem with Han Woo Jin's eyes.
Eyes? These eyes?
Just like a blind person with his eyes open. Truthfully, last time, the reason why he said that he couldn't perform the decompressive craniotomy,
I suspected it's because of his eyes.
Don't tell me your suspicions, tell me the facts.
Fact. Makgeoli.
What's with the makgeoli?
He wasn't able to pour makgeoli properly.
Hey, Doctor Yoon. You need to ask the right questions to get to the top.
With this unclear information, how are you planning to take Han Woo Jin's place? Don't you think so, too?
That's right. Next time, I will bring you something more definite, a fact.
I don't need any dogs who can't hunt, they can't even be held as pets.
Go 'bite' something more definite. More definite!
Hunting dog?
His expressions make me offended. How can he say I'm a 'dog'?
How barbaric.
i was hopeful that this day wouldn't come...
Each day...I wish that it's tomorrow, the day after tomorrow.
The next year, and the next, and the next after that.
So every day was precious to me.
I wanted to finish, then leave. I went crazy to do as many surgeries and presentations as I could.
But all of a sudden like this...
Woo Jin.
That's why I'm going crazy.
Why me out of all people? What did I do wrong?
Why do I need to collapse like this in vain?
My mom who lived alone lonely with blind eyes.
I wanted her to stop her suffering.
I can become your eyes.
- Why would  you?
- Because I like you.
Because I love you.
This is plenty enough.
Woo Jin.
To Hae Sung,
because of me you knew everything, but lived silently.
And the director is your father.
Although you are not the one who did it,
you take all the responsibility.
You know my feelings, so why are you like this?
During the time I can see you,
I want to keep it as long as I can.
You who appear in my memory,
you will be the same always.
Your eyes that look at me.
Your tears.
They are still pretty.
In the maze like the Yeouido pipeline,
should I send someone who doesn't know what he is doing and make him suffer?
Do you think it's easy for me to talk to you about this?
I'm saying to save the nation with the least sacrificial victims.
For the nation and for the people. I'm giving you the chance to sacrifice.
You must wake up.
So you can protect Hae Sung.
The person who can protect Lee Hae Sung,
is only you, Chairman.
Wait a minute. Oh, Prof. Han.
You must be late because of the makgeoli party. It reeks, right?
Secretary Park, don't we need to stop by the 11th floor quickly?
Professor Han, press the 11 floor for me.
- Pardon?
- I'm requesting you to press 11.
Yes.
I'll get off first.
Press 3rd floor.
But what about 12-
I said to press 3rd floor.
- 3rd floor.
- Yes, I will press 3rd floor.
Prof. Han, look at you...
Why are you leaving so quickly? You didn't even get to sleep properly in the lobby.
Seeing so many people sleeping in the lobby, I felt so sorry looking at them.
Right?
Oh, Dad. Did you pack water and food well?
Oh, well. Don't worry about your dad! Is the sun coming out now?
I need to start going.
Alright. Be careful and go safely, Dad.
I love you.
You are sweet.
It seems he has nerve damage.
We need to wait for him to regain consciousness but in these cases, a disability to speak is certain
and his motor skills will be somewhat degraded.
As long as we find a different hospital and transport him...
Doctor Kang, you know an impaired brain can no longer be repaired.
So CEO Lee asked you to look for a hospital so earnestly.
I don't know the reason, but the radio became broken.
I'm sorry, CEO Lee.
Why did you go home? You should have just let Ji Hoon go.
What's so pretty about the kid that left before his parents,
that you wanted to see him off well?
My brother-in-law, in this cutting edge hospital,
he even has a brain surgeon as a brother and what is this?
How outrageous.
But I will take revenge for my brother-in-law.
In his situation, did the brain damage occur
from the earthquake that had
taken place at the site of the house?
I will certainly file a claims lawsuit.
This is because as I watched my brother-in-law
and also as a health professional,
it is something I must do.
As you stand in line for treatment,
if the patient is not present, the guardian must be present.
Each person receives one sheet.
And also, you must sign this paper to
receive any treatment.
Director! Director!
The firefighters just called
to bring patients right now.
Saying that since we are a public emergency hospital, we need to take the patients.
We don't have enough patient's rooms, what should we do?
And right now, there are hospitals being closed down.
Is that so?
Since we are a public emergency hospital, we should comply.
Section Chief Park, how many people in a vegetative state do we have in the hospital right now?
There are a total of 3.
If we make them leave forcefully, there will be problems.
File a form to the hospital commissions.
Director.
Do you have a solution?
They sent us patients since we are a public emergency hospital.
We can't be selective to our patients
and cannot be careless to them either.
We must focus on the patients we can heal.
- But-
- Director.
Please give us time until we look for a different hospital.
Time?
It's the best feeling when you trap the mouse.
I'm sorry that I keep asking you for favors.
I couldn't keep my mother in the hospital.
Different hospital...
Since the radio is broken, there's no method to transport my mother to another hospital.
I'm sorry, but it's no use if you ask me a favor.
Excuse me?
Ki Woong. Ki Woong!
Search a hospital for Teacher Lee.
Not Seoul, but Suwon or Incheon.
Me?
Well, you have better connections than I do.
It's because it's not a task that can be done in one or two days, you punk!
If possible, could you possible find out for me?
That... you should do it, too.
Stop making excuses.
You have to become a head firefighter one day, too.
You take responsibility and resolve it definitely, got it?
- Got it?
- Yes.
Thank goodness I made it in time!
So Yeon opened her eyes and we are changing her room right now.
Is that so?
That's good, I can see my daughter then.
Please make sure to not cry in front of the kid.
And also don't smile too much as if this is nothing.
Don't emphasize "you can do it!," "you must win this fight."
Just so she can fight for herself.
You need to take care of her. Do you understand?
I understand.
Thank you, Doctor. Thank you.
Mom.
Dad.
That's right, So Yeon. Mom's here.
What's the date?
I'm not sure. What date is it today?
I don't know either.
After the earthquake, we didn't see the time passing.
Did I sleep for a long time?
So Yeon, you slept a lot.
You were hurt a lot.
Wow.
My daughter...Dad is so thankful for overcoming that pain.
One and only dad's daughter,
I'm so thankful that
I won't say anything even if you get zero on a test.
Even if you go to dance practice, I won't say anything.
Dance practice?
Now, I won't have dance practice late at night so
don't worry, Dad.
So Yeon.
Yeonggwang's firefighter leader's daughter, Choi So Yeon.
You need to be brave like dad.
No matter what happens.
I request you, okay?
Okay.
I will be brave.
What's wrong if I don't have one leg?
I can just get an artificial leg
The doctor said.
That's right.
Wow. At times, Dad thinks our So Yeon is so pretty
that I wondered whether you are my daughter.
But you are my daughter.
You are Choi Il Sub's daughter.
Dad needs to go,
so stay well.
Why are you like this?
Like someone who is moving far away.
Of course, it's far away.
Just try going out there.
It's 1 hour with a car.
I don't even want to go. It's so dangerous.
I request you to take care of So Yeon well.
You, too, don't starve yourself because you are on a diet.
Why is this person like this really?
Doctor, I request you this patient as well.
Yes, I'm not going to give up on this patient easily after saving this patient.
He is probably the only patient who has had a surgery at an animal hospital.
You are very strong, mentally.
I'm envious.
Then, what am I supposed to do?
If I cry then,
my mom and dad...
their feelings will be hurt.
I wanted to show you my firefighter uniform.
I told you to open your eyes a bit.
Open your eyes later and look at it.
You will know how splendid mom's second son grew up like.
And I treated older brother really badly.
Later, help him forgive me.
That's your specialty.
Mom.
You have to open your eyes, okay?
Got it?
Alright, you can lower your hands.
There was a unanimous approval.
The removal of patients in comas have been decided.
With this, we will conclude our meeting.
Teacher, would you be able to get out?
You must be sad because of your mother.
It should be like that.
I don't know what to do either.
We should wait for the result.
Last time, other doctors helped us, too.
We should wait this time, too-
Go ahead...
You seemed to be waiting because you are curious of the result.
Unfortunately,
please get ready to leave.
Couldn't you help us with a warm heart?
It's something I can't do with my power.
This is decided by the hospital commissions.
Aren't we the same family working in the same hospital?
Let's go.
What do I...
What do I need to do?
Teacher Lee Hae Sung,
you should have kneeled when I said so.
Director! You shouldn't take this emotionally, don't you think?
Stop it!
I don't want to be in a hospital where they want to kick my mother out.
So, let's hurry up and get out.
Well, the two brothers should discuss and decide what to do next.
Will you be alright?
No, I didn't even get to tell him.
No, that's not it. The weather is getting cold now.
Oh. We need to hurry and move to a different place.
Mom dressed us, fed us, and put us to sleep.
But we can't even have a proper place for her to lie on.
Hurry up and earn money and place her in a good place.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
But mom should understand us.
Hey, Lee Woo Sung,
you've grown up. You grew up a lot.
I said don't do that kind of thing.
You know I hate you saying that the most.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Hurry and dye her hair. I don't like white hair.
I wish my mother is always pretty and young.
This rascal really grew up a lot.
Ah, seriously...do you want to die?!
Woo Sung, you punk!
What are you doing to your hyung?
He's just joking.
Teacher Lee, I heard. What should we do now?
Mother is moving here?
I'm sorry. No matter how I much I think about it, only this solution...
No, no...you did well.
We need to bring her alive.
Since this is not even inside the hospital...
Of course, this is the headquarters for firefighters,
it's safe.
That's what I'm saying.
So the director of the hospital won't be able to say anything about it.
Doctor Lee, me and Joo Ran will go around and watch your mother.
Don't worry.
Alright. Thanks.
What are you saying? Teacher Lee said it.
That friend's mother is my mother.
My mom will endure it well.
Just be careful of her arrythmia.
Chief, thank you so much for your understanding.
Aigoo, it's nothing.
Is she just anyone?
She is the mother of the doctor who saved my daughter's life and my minion's mother.
People who are alive right now are not even significant lives.
Aigoo, I'm tired of the earthquake. I'm sick and tired of it.
Captain, everything is ready. We can go now.
Oh, okay.
- DMAT Team will be leaving, too, right?
- Yes, we should.
Woo Sung, let's go.
I will go after visiting the hospital.
Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Have you seen Nurse Yeon So Hee?
Yes, she's in our team, but she left with the DMAT Team.
This please...
What is this?
I will be thankful if you just deliver this to her.
Yes, I got it.
- Hey there.
- Yes, I will give it to her.
No, it will be nice if you just put it in your pocket and deliver it to her.
Is there money inside here?
What is it?
It's something important.
Prof. Han, DMAT Team is leaving.
Professor Han, are you asleep?
I'm tired of it.
I want to rest.
Even if you say I'm a fugitive, even if you say I'm a loser,
even if you say I'm irresponsible, it's all fine.
I'm sorry to everyone.
Han Woo Jin.
What happened exactly?
Professor Han is not the person to do this.
What do you mean he isn't? He confessed all himself.
Fugitive, loser, and irresponsible. It is all written here.
Give it to me.
Do you think he is like you?
Do you think people don't want to work like you and run off like a coward?!
When I left, that was because they said the hospital was closing down.
- It was a emergency situation.
- You are so loud. Stop it. I don't even want to hear it.
So, what's going to happen to the DMAT Team?
What does the firefighter chief say?
He must be waiting as I told him we will go.
Leave as we can't go because Prof. Han isn't here.
Work hard in each field we are all assigned to. Okay?
Hold on, then-
I think I need to be the leader. Because Mirae Hospital has name-value,
I don't think it's right to give the head position to an outsider.
Yeah. You will be great if you are the leader.
As an outsider, I'll work hard to help as much as I can.
Director Kang,
I request you to take care of my mother well.
Yeah, don't worry about that.
Hey, Woo Sung. Walk, don't run.
Do well.
Thank you! You worked hard.
- You got everything, right?
- Yes.
Lee Hae Sung's  mom went to those tents?
Yes.
Aye, we should clear that from there, too.
But you need to be satisfied for at least kicking them out right?
I saw reporters, too.
Before any weird news come out,
make sure to emphasize it was decided by the hospital commissions.
Yes.
But I heard that they are not able to see Professor Han.
Really?
He really is a quick one.
Because he thought that I would make him take responsibility, he escaped.
I never imagined that Professor Han would disappear like this.
He must be gone so Doctor Lee can be safe.
Why?
Since he was not able to see properly and
allowed Doctor Lee to stand as an assist.
The director of the hospital was going to make him take responsibility.
What do you need to eat to be evil like the director of the hospital exactly?
Hey, be careful around here!
There is a water lane below these rocks.
Yes, yes.
Lets show Ddol Mi our strength!
Yes, I understand.
Aigoo, why is this like this?
We have arrived.
Hey, Woo Sung, tell me what happened?
I memorized it.
You need to write it down!
Repeat it for me!
- Yeonggwang-do, Yeonggwang
#189, an injury from a fork crane,
needs emergency treatment.
I know, hurry up and get in.
Let's go!
If it is left like this, Mega Construction can go bankrupt.
The Yeouido pipeline needs to be solved today.
You're too much. Be careful what you say.
Not only the savings from the company but also used loans.
If we cannot pay back the funding...
Then what?
Excuse me?
They live by their morals.
Whoever it is, someone will stand up to do it.
How long do we have?
They have set the deadline as tonight.
Rather than who, the problem will be when will they step up.
Where is Yeonggwang-do's Captain Choi?
Dad!!
We can't all go down so you guys bring the equipment.
Chief, chief. Where is my dad?
Yes, yes. Calm down a bit.
He is over there. You guide her.
Please follow me.
Hey, be careful! The ground is still a bit shaky
- Okay!
It's a mountain here, isn't it?
Please help us. Come here, please.
Sorry, I can't go
They're bringing the workers who got hurt right now.
Patients will come, so you need to treat them.
A leader decides whom to treat or not.
I am the leader.
Dad, how did you become like this?
Dol Mi, it's not your fault.
I know.
The floor broke down due to the earthquake.
I'll take care of you.
Calm down and wait over there.
Stay out here.
Heartbeat is 117 and the blood pressure is 50/120.
His breathing is fine.
I'm fine.
Is your arm or leg in pain?
I don't think anything is broken.
Nurse Park, look inside the bag here.
Monitor.
Something is ripped open...
Where do you think it ripped?
Is it the spleen?
No.. Dad...
I'm okay.
I'm your dad, nothing will happen.
Let's first move him to the hospital. Woo Sung!
I got it.
Vitals?
Blood pressure is 180/102, heartbeat is 130.
He has a high blood pressure but he looks fine.
Where does it hurt the most?
My stomach hurts.
Ah, here?
Here? Yes?
You're not going to use the ultrasound?
There's no blood, everything seems fine.
But it hurts?
It feels like it's going to rip.
Dad, don't worry. We're going to the hospital.
- I will fix you.
- Of course, you will.
My daughter is a doctor.
I won't worry.
- There must be a heart inside the stomach, huh?
- Nurse Park.
Why is the heartbeat so strong?
Doctor! Doctor! My dad--
Don't worry. He'll come soon.
Move.
This is my patient; I'm in the middle of treating him!
Shut up.
I'll look at your stomach.
- Does it hurt?
- Yes.
Have you ever heard that you had an aneurysm?
What is that?
With his age, do you think he could have one?
What I feel with my hands is very large.
Let's go to the hospital immediately.
Dad...does it hurt a lot?
No. I'm okay.
Because of me, you came to Seoul and got hurt.
It's all because of me.
Ddol Mi, don't say that.
In my whole life, I had participated in a lot of volunteering.
Seoul became chaotic because of the earthquake.
I'm sorry, I should've come earlier.
What about your waist? Does your waist hurt as well?
It feels like it's going to rip.
It's not going to yet, but the aorta is going to burst.
- The aorta?
- Yes, and its pretty big.
It's larger than 2 cm.
It can be even felt by just using your hands.
The patient is in critical condition.
The blood pressure is rising 150/100,  heartbeat is 120.
The blood pressure isn't good.
If this bursts...
Since we are not sure, lets limit this area.
Hyeong Woo,  Yeong Saek, Chang Hee, come here with your notes.
I understand.
Let's go.
Chief.
Yes.
Captain Choi, you know the Roman Forum, right?
Yes?
Have you never been to Rome? Rome?
I've never been there.
Ah, yes.
Well, if you go to the Roman Forum there are landmarks there called the aquaducts.
From the Palatine to the Colosseum,
aquaducts stretch under all the buildings.
For 1000 years,
it was the center of politics, economy, and culture of Rome.
For 1000 years.
I'm saying for 1000 years.
And?
Taejongi Construction has been in Korea for more than 600 years, but
to us, we are like the Romans.
We must show our children 1000 years of Korea's glory.
Who will do it? Who can do it?
Destruction is an opportunity for new buildings.
I've done construction before, so I know.
Captain Choi,
for 1000 years of Korea,
you need to make a decision.
There's no time.
Rome didn't become like that in one day.
Ah, that Rome, Rome, Rome!
1, 2, 3.
My father...
That's your father?
It's okay, don't worry. There's a surgery room, he can get surgery right away.
Do both patients need surgery?
This patient has an aneurysm and it's going to burst in any second.
Is that so? Intervention is not working, what should we do?
Doctor Lee, you are going to have to take care of one of the patients and do the surgery.
All the other surgeons are in surgery right now.
Who is it?
Is it Woo Jin?
Yeah, Mom. It's me.
Woo Jin! Woo Jin!
Ah, Woo Jin! Aigoo.
Aigoo. Are you okay?
I heard that there was an earthquake in Seoul,
I wanted to go see my son because I was worried, but I couldn't because of my eyes.
So I came. I came to show you that I'm well.
Aigoo. Our doctor.
Aigoo, you got thin. You got skinny.
You haven't eaten, right? Let's go in.
Crew members!
The nation won't ever forget the workers' sacrifice.
Firefighters! Fighting!
Have you gone crazy?
Why are you going into the Yeouido pipeline?
Then, what?
Who else knows the structure better than I do.
Because of the earthquake, I heard that place is filled with water. How are you planning to get in?
Don't you know how dangerous the base pump is?
I will go there instead.
- Hey.
- I'll go.
The only one who knows how to fix this, you, you and me. Amongst you guys, I am the most experienced.
The captain goes first.
If something goes wrong, you could die!
Ah, you--
Was it once or twice that we were on the verge of death?
What are you talking about, Woo Sung?
Tell me in detail.
Chief, this really isn't it!
Shut up!!
There's no time, so get the building map prepared.
The inside has lots of curves so I don't need a hose.
Make sure to prepare the wet suits.
- Got it?
- No way.
You know!
I'm doing it, yes?
What about So Yeon?
What about your 15 year old daughter?
What is happening exactly, Sunbae?
It's alright, don't worry. I can go in.
If Chief goes in, I won't stay still.
I won't go to your funeral.
I definitely can't go!
Vitals should be okay, right?
Don't worry. I will stay here.
Hello.
I'm sure the preparations are done...
Yes.
Dr. Jung.
Patient's family shouldn't participate in the surgery.
Doctor Lee, that is the position for the directing surgeon.
You need to stand next to me.
I am the directing surgeon for this surgery.
Yes?
Where's Doctor Lee?
Doctor! Why are you here?
Aren't you doing my dad's surgery?
Because of me, he came all the way to the hospital and got hurt.
Doesn't the Doctor need to do the surgery?
Let's go quickly. What are you doing?
Jung Ddol Mi,
I can't do his surgery.
Huh? Why?
This is the center of Korea's monetary funds.
Financial institutions need to live for Seoul to live.
If you go in, you can't last more than 30 minutes.
I'm going. I said I'm going! As a chief, I'm going!
I can't leave my father to a person who performs surgery with his mouth.
Doctor, please do it instead.
That sounds to me like you are asking me to commit murder.
I want to go to Busan after my father comes out of ICU.
Why are you treating me like I'm invisible?
Because you are that kind of existence to me.
Jung Dol Mi!
I don't think I will forget that you pushed back my father.
If the hand pump initiated the waves will be strong,
it will be hard to push against the current.
Let's just go.
If we turn that, it's suicide.
They said the water must go out, it will work.
It will work!