'Pursue Love' - Chen Zhuo Xuan
♫  Don't be afraid, no matter how long the journey  ♫
♫  Love embraces gentleness and care  ♫
♫  Those scars will eventually heal and turn into the blossoms gathering along time's journey  ♫
♫  Eventually, someone will take them away for you  ♫
♫  Don't feel lonely moving on  ♫
♫  Let time in on your story  ♫
♫  Expect a soft ray of light in response  ♫
♫  May you find her amidst the crowd  ♫
♫  May you find joy in simplicity  ♫
♫  Even though you know life is filled with regrets  ♫
♫  May you always carry your passion every Winter and Summer  ♫
What could be better for you than this French interpreter job?
No way.
I haven't tried it yet. Why do you say I can't do it?
Yes, Dr. Gu. Wei'an can do it.
She's very good at French. And she knows medicine.
She even saved someone today, didn't you know? You even helped us.
So you're the surgical genius.
That hole was very precise.
Working at a hospital is hard and poorly paid.
You can't keep it up. It's not suitable.
Can I apply for the job?
I know French, too.
Subarachnoid hemorrhage. Spinal cord injury classification.
Cranial nerve palsy. Translate, please.
I don't even know what they mean in Chinese. Not to mention French.
I...
But I have a heart filled with devotion.
I want to do my little part.
Well, your little part seems insignificant enough to ignore.
Forget it.
We just want to pay you back soon as possible, Dr. Gu.
- No need to repay it.
- No way!
Debts should be repaid.
Boss.
It's the first time I've seen someone with debts act so boldly.
Dr. Gu.
The patient has grade 5 muscle strength in the left upper limb and both lower limbs.
The neck is soft with no stiff-neck. Babinski sign is negative.
The patient is recovering well.
Pardon.
- Grade 5 muscle strength...
- Grade 5 muscle strength
in the left upper limb and both lower limbs. The neck is soft with no stiff-neck.
The Babinski sign is negative. The patient's condition is normal.
He's recovering well.
Is this our new interpreter?
See, I told you Wei'an can do it.
That's right, Boss. She's impressive.
We've found a treasure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You have a one-month probation period. I hope you won't give up halfway again.
Hold on.
Is there anything else to discuss?
Let's clarify the conditions first. Weekly pay with full board.
Also, Jiang Muying must join me in starting the job. And we're moving in tonight.
We only need one interpreter.
Boss, the more, the merrier.
- But professional French vocabulary...
- She can learn.
- I can learn.
- I can teach.
Arrange dormitories for both of them.
Wei'an, you were amazing just now.
You translated such a long list of medical terms.
It shows that even though you dropped out of school for three years, you haven't forgotten your expertise.
This knowledge has been ingrained in your bones and your instincts.
Not really...
Wait. It's only been a while. Where did you get the clothes?
Clothes? You dare mention it?
All my beautiful clothes in the suitcase are now all gone.
If I hadn't found a night market nearby, I wouldn't have any clothes to change tomorrow.
I've bought some for you too.
Take a look. Do you want to change?
Let's put them away.
All right.
Is this left by the previous doctor?
If you hadn't dropped out of school, you'd probably be a resident by now.
I'm sure you'd be wearing this white coat. How cool it would be!
I'll put this in the cabinet. You can try it later.
These guys are impressive.
They've been here for hours without moving, not even going to the restroom.
Maybe we should come back another day.
No. My hard-earned money is inside.
No way. We have to do something.
Make money!
Who is he?
- My employee.
- I miss you so much, Mommy An!
Okay. Don't speak anymore. I'm busy right now.
Sakun!
It's dangerous. Sakun!
Wait, Su Wei'an. You hired a child?
No. He just runs errands for me.
Like delivering milk to customers.
Sakun!
He just called you mommy.
He calls anyone who's nice to him mommy and daddy.
He has several siblings in his family.
And Sakun has been sick since birth. His mother doesn't care about him.
And his dad has passed away.
What illness?
AIDS.
Sakun!
- How do you know about this?
- I always knew it meant a lot to you.
Let's go!
Sakun.
Have you been good lately? Do you remember what I told you?
Don't get hurt or bleed.
Have you been taking your medicine on time?
No, Mom can't afford it.
- Do you feel any discomfort anywhere?
- Headache.
Why don't you go to the hospital?
Mom says it's too expensive. We can't afford it.
It's okay, Sakun.
- We'll make money.
- Great! Make money!
Sakun! Where are you?
Mom.
Be careful!
Where did you go?
Where have you been?
Who told you to run around? Go home!
I've got a headache.
If you go to sleep, you won't feel the headache anymore.
Have you seen An?
No, I haven't.
Tell me if you see her.
It’s a disaster! I shouldn’t have rented her the house. Does she not understand it’s a large sum of money?
What a waste! Such a large sum of money!
I must find her!
- What are you doing? You'll have to pay for it if you go out now.
- You understand? We must find her!
I'm going to compensate her. Sakun's treatment.
Are you crazy?
You work so hard to earn money just to treat a child who's not even related to you?
Are you nuts?
His own mother doesn't even care about him. Why do you take care of him?
Because those with the same illness empathize with each other.
(fig. misery loves company)
What illness!
Wake up, Su Wei'an!
AIDS is incurable. You know that.
What about him? Should he just wait to die?
He's still so young.
As long as he takes his medicine and controls his condition well, he'll be cured one day.
Wait! What's wrong with you?
I mean, even if you pay him money, will his mother take him to a doctor?
Yeah, you're right.
It's not just money. He needs medicine more than anything.
Dr. Gu.
- Are you okay, Wei'an?
- I'm fine.
You've dropped out of school. Why do you still keep your campus card from Huaren Medical University?
Why don't you throw it away along with your dream?
Why should I throw it away?
There's still money in it. I can use it when I go back to school.
Is it all right if I fold it up and put it in the box?
Okay.
Wei'an.
Why did you buy such a large amount of accident insurance?
And the beneficiary is your mom?
It's inauspicious to buy an accident insurance.
Why do you curse yourself?
Fortunes can change in an instant. I'm alone in a foreign country.
Who knows what might happen?
And you, if you insist on following me,
I suggest you get one too.
- Don't curse me!
- I'm not cursing you.
What are you looking at?
Let me show you.
She's gone square dancing again.
Sister Lan is so cute.
Jiang Jiang.
You've been in Lakaya for long enough. Why don't you go home early?
I'm really busy here.
Tell Sister Lan when you get back that I'm doing well in Paris.
Are you kidding me? It's so different from Paris.
It's not so bad.
Working in the city center and living in a double room.
The healthcare and catering are well-matched.
What's wrong with it?
All right.
Since it's so good here, I won't leave then.
I, Jiang Muying, have a job now. I'm also an interpreter.
Okay.
Go to bed. It's late.
What about you?
I'll go to sleep soon.
Okay.
Wei'an.
I feel like you've changed a lot in the three years since we last saw each other.
Oh, honey. I'm still at the office.
I don't have any plans for tomorrow. How about you?
It looks like it's going to rain heavily outside.
Okay.
The signal here is not good when it rains.
I'm going outside so I can talk to you.
Hello. Why don't you come pick me up?
I don't think I'm going to make it to your place today.
Okay.
Hey, Security. There was someone...
If the security guards catch her, she would be retaken to the police station.
It's all right.
But why don't you come pick me up? I want go to your place.
Yes, I miss you too.
You can come to the hospital to pick me up.
What are you doing?
Okay, I love you.
Bye.
Su Wei'an.
What are you doing here?
Don't you know that trespassing in the pharmacy can be a crime?
No, I didn't trespass. I... I'm here to see...
Etravirine,
the medicine to treat HIV.
You trying to steal the medicine?
Of course not. Don't say it like that.
I'm here to buy the medicine.
Stop denying!
Now, I have reason to suspect that you're selling drugs illegally.
No wonder you suddenly came to the hospital to apply for an interpreter job.
So this was your plan.
No, it isn't.
Dr. Gu. Dr. Gu, please listen to me.
Dr. Gu.
- Security! Is anyone there?
- Be quiet.
- Hello?
- W-W-We'll be caught.
You've got a lot of guts. You're still afraid of being found?
When I saw you acting suspiciously outside just now, I should have called security to take you away.
And we wouldn't be locked up here now.
Let me explain.
What are you doing?
Calling security.
No, please don't.
I forgot to tell you. The base station is unstable here when it rains. There's no signal.
It seems like fate.
I guess you won't take me to the police station again, will you?
Don't you know that the main switch controls the lights in the pharmacy?
What are you planning to do now?
Find something to break the window.
No! We'll be discovered if you do that.
What do you mean by "we"? What's it got to do with me?
You dared to come here to steal medicine. You should have thought about the consequences.
No, I didn't.
Fine. Go ahead. You recruited me anyway.
If we get caught, I'll say that you ordered me to steal
and sell the medication. We'll split the profit 70/30. Seven for you, three for me.
Wait.
Don't you have any morals?
What's that? Is it worth anything?
Snake!
Get your hands off me!
It's just a gecko.
This was a birthday gift from my mother.
What's the big deal? I just wanted to take a look.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. I'm really sorry.
Please don't be angry. I was just trying to scare you.
I won't get you into trouble.
Move aside.
That medicine isn't for me. It's for someone to extend their life.
Let go of it.
Let me help you put it back together.
Is this bracelet important to you?
You broke my bracelet.
It can't be fixed anymore.
You're annoying, and so is your mom.
Leave my house.
It's my house. You're annoying. Go away!
Go!
Yunzheng. Let go.
What are you doing?
Honey.
It's all Yuncheng's fault. Don't blame Yunzheng.
Yuncheng, apologize to your brother.
You child.
Try to put it together on this paper.
It will be clearer this way.
You can't do it like that. The letters are in the wrong order.
I've tried many combinations but can't get a complete meaning out of it.
Let me help you.
Okay?
Okay, it's done. Dark rainbow.
That's what it means in French.
Dark rainbow.
Yeah.
Dark rainbow. It's a rainbow in the night sky.
It's a super miracle.
The person who gave you this bracelet
probably wanted to bring you good luck.
Is it from your first love?
Or from your girlfriend?
No.
I've figured it out for you. You should be feeling better now, right?
You won't report me, will you?
It's a different story.
I know a lot of rumors the dark rainbow.
Would you like to hear them?
Like what?
Like...
Like the fact that the dark rainbow only appears under specific conditions.
If you're lucky enough to see it, it means
that somewhere in this world, a miracle
is happening.
It's so romantic, right?
And I also know where you can see it.
- Do you?
- Yes.
It's far away.
But it doesn't matter. As long as you take my vehicle.
For the sake of our friendship tonight.
Give you a 20% discount. How about that?
No, thanks.
Why didn't you push me away?
You're too heavy. I couldn't move you.
You could have woken me up.
You've been pressing on me all night.
I fell asleep at dawn. I just woke up.
How could I have been pressing on you all night? I'm not a mountain.
Are you sure you just woke up?
How can you be so tidy when you've just woken up?
You're so fresh and clean. Suspicious.
He's… good-looking.
Who is it for?
You said that medicine is for extending someone's life.
For a friend who can't come to the hospital.
Why can't he come to the hospital?
Not everyone is like you in this world,
with a stable income and good health.
Many people can't afford to come to the hospital.
What's worse,
even if they have money,
some diseases can't be cured.
Dr. Gu.
We were here last night, and...
I understand.
She said she understood.
Understood?
But I didn't finish explaining.
Don't worry, I didn't see anything.
Come with me.
Last night...
Thank you for helping me figure out the meaning behind those letters.
I should be thanking you for not reporting me.
You can't take these medicine away.
Please. I'll give you more money, okay?
Double the amount?
No need.
For a cheapskate like you to be so willing to spend money,
this person must be very important to you.
How about this? Can you give me a box first?
No, I can't.
Let me keep these medicine for now.
Bring the patient to the hospital within 24 hours.
No matter how difficult it is, we can work it out together.
But you can't
take these prescription drugs so easily.
Shut up, you're making a lot of noise.
Your crying is giving me a headache. Bear it.
Sakun, come on, get up.
- How are you feeling?
- I'm getting a headache.
Headache?
How dare you come back?
My house was destroyed because of you.
You have to pay me double.
I'll pay. But you have to take him to the hospital.
He can't stop taking his medicine, don't you know that?
Are you kidding me? We're poor, don't you know that?
We don't even have enough money to eat. It's even more impossible to get medicine.
Sakun.
You wretched child, why don't you just die?
You're a waste of food.
Sakun.
-  Do you feel any discomfort anywhere?
- Headache.
Oh no.
Let's go.
Put him down.
He needs to go to the hospital immediately. Otherwise, his life will be in danger.
You caused my house to be destroyed.
Even triple the rent won't be enough to compensate me.
Money! You only care about money.
Hello?
You said if I tell you where Su Wei'an is, you'll give me money?
She went to the hospital.
Dr. Gu, help him!
What happened?
The patient has a headache, with projectile vomiting and unsteady gait.
Fang Mingfan. Take him for a CT scan of his head immediately.
- Hurry up!
- Okay.
Be careful.
You're the surgeon with a zero mortality rate. Will he be okay?
Don't worry. Where are his parents?
- He might need immediate surgery.
- I'll sign it.
- You?
- Surgery fees and hospitalization fees. I'll take care of all the expenses.
You'll take care of it?
Please, I'm begging you. You must save him.
Boss. There's a shadow at the bottom of the third ventricle. It's hydrocephalus caused by obstruction.
I'm going to find the child's family to sign the consent form.
I'll sign it.
We can't get in touch with the patient's family at the moment. Let her sign it.
- Surgery now.
- Yes.
By the way, the patient is HIV positive. Take proper precautions.
The medicine you took last night was for him.
Fang Mingfan, notify the operating room for level 1 protection.
Replace all the nurses with wounds.
Yes.
What kind of person is she?
Interpreter Su.
You'll be the interpreter for this surgery. Is there a problem?
No problem.
Your posture is very standard. You really look like a doctor.
You just look like a doctor, Su Wei'an. Did you forget? You can't be a doctor for the rest of your life.
Start the surgery.
- Increase the electrocoagulation.
- Increase the suction.
I... I think I pressed on something.
Don't move. It's a cysticercus.
Dr. Fang, keep your hand steady.
The cysticercus wall is adhering to the basilar artery. If there's a hemorrhage, Sakun will die.
Interpreter Su. Who is this child to you?
A neighbor.
You didn't have money to pay your fine but had money to pay his medical bills.
Your neighbor is not ordinary.
Are you ready for the next surgery?
No problem.
As a dropout, you know that the cysticercus wall is adhering to the basilar artery.
I'm not a dropout. I graduated with a bachelor's degree.
You were directly admitted to a doctorate
but dropped out midway. Aren't you a dropout?
Since you chose to drop out, why are you still studying these specialized terms?
Su Wei'an. Why did you drop out?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Besides, in this world, there aren't so many reasons.
Can you tell me why a grown man like you wears such a strange bracelet daily?
Take her away!
- Let go of me! Listen to me!
- What are you guys doing?
I'll pay more to compensate for the General's wine.
Can you afford it?
You've ruined the General's banquet. He is furious. Take her away.
Don't move. Let her go.
Keep holding the knife if you can!
Gu Yunzheng, they have guns. Don't be impulsive.
Tell him that the Friendship Hospital is protected.
Who dares to hurt Chinese citizens here?
And tell him to control himself.
If he accidentally touches my scalpel, he'll get his clothes dirty.
Don't move. Or you'll die.
Friendship Hospital is protected.
I don't believe that. Doctors save lives. How can they kill people?
A surgeon's professional skill is that even if they stab you a hundred times, you won't die.
You'd better stay here forever.
Boss, what happened just now?
Are you idle now?
Have you finished writing the medical records and recording the course of the illness?
I just admire your heroic act. It's a once-in-a-lifetime hero-safe-beauty scene.
Oh no, it's a hero acting for a just cause scene.
Sakun hasn't been discharged yet. His guardian can't be taken away.
Boss.
I heard you spent the night with Miss Su at the pharmacy last night.
You spent the night with Dr. Gu?
No, I didn't. He's talking nonsense.
Hey, why are you talking nonsense here?
You're just making things up.
I'm not lying! The pharmacist saw you with her own eyes.
The scene was a mess.
Su Wei'an, explain it to me.
She must have mistaken me for someone else.
I'm new here. How could she know me?
She wouldn't mistake the boss for someone else, would she?
Wait. I don't mind you accusing me. But how can you throw mud at Dr. Gu?
Go over all the plans for tomorrow's surgery.
Memorize the approach and procedure. I'll do a spot check later.
Hey, Fang Mingfan.
Are you here to provide medical assistance or to gossip?
There's no conflict between the two.
What did you say?
Two tablets at a time, three times a day.
Dr. Fang.
- Interpreter Jiang.
- Dr. Fang.
Come over here.
Dr. Fang. Can I ask you something?
Interpreter Jiang. Just call me Mingfan.
- No need to be so polite.
- Okay, Mingfan. Let me ask you something.
Does your boss have a girlfriend?
Boss?
Yes.
He's in a relationship? With whom? Is she pretty?
Well, he’s not bad-looking.
But he is a medical expert.
God-like in my boss's eyes. It's not just love.
If she is a medical expert, wouldn't she already be in her seventies?
Can she still be in a relationship with Gu Yunzheng?
Who is she? What's her name?
- Cushing.
- Ku Xin?
Is there a girl with the surname Ku here?
Cushing, the father of modern neurosurgery.
Boss is obsessed with him.
You tricked me, Fang Mingfan.
My boss is not dating anyone.
But if you like him, I advise you to give up.
He only cares about medicine.
If it were possible to matchmake Su Wei'an and her idol,
when Gu Yunzheng's aid mission ends, they can return to China together.
Maybe Su Wei'an can regain her passion for medicine.
Jiang Muying, you're so clever.
Sakun.
What's wrong? It's okay.
I'll give you a checkup.
Sakun. Let me perform a magic trick for you.
Sakun.
Is it cute? Come on. It's for you.
Daddy.
What did you call me?
Sakun. Let go of Dr. Gu.
'Lost' - Zhou Shen
♫  The night guides the hands of time  ♫
♫  The hustle and bustle gradually drowns out the silence  ♫
♫  In the grand theater of life, we play out the scene of our encounter  ♫
♫  A rainbow brings a touch of magic to the darkness  ♫
♫  And the wind that crossed the desert  ♫
♫  They were once our witnesses  ♫
♫  Who among us is not a lost soul searching for that one-in-a-billion chance?  ♫
♫  And trapped in this city called fate, yet we're still chasing star  ♫
♫  Don't worry, my beloved lost love  ♫
♫  I'm like your glass of wine, always here to warm your lonesome soul  ♫
♫  Let me embrace your scars  ♫
♫  Your brilliance shines like a star, my beacon in the darkest night  ♫
♫  The night guides the hands of time  ♫
♫  The hustle and bustle gradually drowns out the silence  ♫
♫  In the grand theater of life, we play out the scene of our encounter  ♫
♫  A rainbow brings a touch of magic to the darkness  ♫
♫  And the wind that crossed the desert  ♫
♫  They were once our witnesses  ♫
♫  Who among us is not a lost soul searching for that one-in-a-billion chance?  ♫
♫  And trapped in this city called fate, yet we're still chasing star  ♫
♫  Don't worry, my beloved lost love  ♫
♫  I'm like your glass of wine, always here to warm your lonesome soul  ♫
♫  Let me embrace your scars  ♫
♫  Your brilliance shines like a star, my beacon in the darkest night  ♫