What are you looking at?
Seo-jin, you should take a look as well.
What do you think?
-Guesthouse Boulanger?
-Yeah.
Why, all of a sudden?
It's springtime.
I thought we should
redo the interior here.
So I'm looking around
for research purposes.
-This place looks nice, right?
-It's pretty and I like the ambience.
There, they give out bread
that the owner makes for free.
Really?
-That's great service.
-Yeah.
Hey, Dong-goo,
I'm going to step out for a bit.
Now? It's late. Where are you going?
I just have something to take care of.
-Sure. Go ahead.
-Okay.
Hi, Joon-ki. I'm here.
Where are you?
It's me, Seo-jin.
-What the hell? You scared me.
-Sorry.
Come inside.
Come here.
Is...
anyone tailing you?
What about Dong-goo?
He's at home.
You're ridiculous.
What do you mean?
Haven't you noticed
he's been watching us very closely?
We can't even go on dates.
I can't even tell anyone
I have a boyfriend.
What is this?
We have no choice.
I don't have to shoot this weekend.
Want to go on a date?
Really? You don't have to work
this weekend?
I'm off this weekend, too.
Then let's go on a trip.
-A trip?
-Yeah.
An overnight trip somewhere nearby.
How about it?
-Overnight? Isn't it too soon for that?
-What are you thinking about?
We'll get separate rooms.
You're crazy.
Oh, really?
Okay, let's do this!
Let's go on this trip!
Let's do this! Let's go on this trip!
Hide.
Damn it, I lost her again!
She disappeared somewhere around here.
There's something going on.
I'm sure of it.
Kang Seo-jin, Lee Joon-ki,
I will get you two for certain.
HIDE-AND-SEEK
Hurry up! Get every nook and cranny!
Spick-and-span!
We get guests once every blue moon.
Why do we have to clean every day?
Exactly.
The weather's so nice, I wish I could go
on a trip somewhere and get some rest.
Trip, my ass.
We don't have the money for that.
Clean already!
Hi, Hyun-joon.
I haven't been able to ask him yet.
I think it'll be tough.
I'm sorry. Bye.
What is it? What's going to be tough?
Well, the baking school
is going on a retreat.
I told him I can't go because of Sol
and work at the guesthouse.
Why not? You should go.
Everyone in your class is going.
You can't miss out.
She's right. You should go.
We can look after Sol for you.
When is the retreat?
This Saturday, for one night.
What? It's overnight?
Does this mean she'll spend the night
with Song Hyun-joon, that bastard?
That can't happen. It mustn't.
Wait!
Gosh, what are we going to do?
Your baking school retreat
and our offsite
are happening at the exact same time!
Offsite? We're going on an offsite?
Yes, we are.
It was a lot of hard work
doing the guests' laundry, dishes,
and cleaning, don't you think?
So I'd been planning
an overnight offsite for us.
Since when? You just said
we don't have any money.
I did?
I was acting so you'd be
even more surprised.
Surprise!
Anyway, Yoon-ah...
it's a shame,
but you'll have to miss the retreat.
That's all right.
There's nothing we can do.
Okay, then!
You're all free this weekend, right?
Wait!
You mean this weekend?
I can't make it.
Why? What's going on?
The thing is I have to cover
a story all night long.
I see.
I... I can't make it either.
I have to shoot all night long.
What? So the two of you
have something to do all night,
over the weekend of all times?
It's true.
Oh, really?
Which story are you working on
that you have to work all night?
Huh? It's...
I'm covering a funeral.
What? A funeral?
There's still a few days left
until the weekend.
How do you know when they're going to die
that you're covering a funeral?
-That doesn't make any sense.
-What?
Well...
it's going to be any day now.
-That's too bad.
-The consensus is
that he'll die this weekend,
so my seniors want me on standby.
-Are you serious?
-That's what I'm saying.
Then I'll call one of your seniors
to confirm.
What?
Jeez. There he goes again.
Fine. Go ahead.
Here. Call him. Do it already!
Oh, really?
I'll call him right now!
Call him. Do it!
You can check for yourself.
I'm dialing. I'm doing it!
I'm pressing the call button now!
Okay, that's enough.
Fine, I'll trust you.
The rest of you
all have to be there, okay?
-Okay!
-Doo-sik and I
have a photo shoot for our website
this weekend.
You can do that on the way there.
So, okay. We're leaving
first thing Saturday, and that's that.
-No more buts!
-All right!
-Clean up.
-Let's clean!
Hurry up! Come on!
-Come downstairs!
-Coming!
It's been so long since I've been away.
I couldn't sleep because I was so excited.
Are you that excited?
Totally. Where's Sol, Yoon-ah?
She's sleeping.
I don't want to wake her yet.
Good thinking.
Are you evacuating?
Are you emigrating somewhere?
What is all this?
What do you think?
It's the wardrobe for the shoot.
All this?
How much do you need to shoot?
You're taking so much.
Whose fault is this?
I said I didn't want to go,
yet you're dragging me there.
Of course we need to take everything.
Go get more!
Are you leaving now?
Have fun.
-Are you heading to work?
-Yeah.
What's with the backpack?
Well...
I have a lot to bring
because I'll be working all night.
It'd be really nice
if you came, too, Seo-jin.
I know.
I want to go with you more than anything,
but it just happens I have to work.
Hey, Seo-jin...
you know what will happen
if you hang out with Joon-ki
just because I'm not here, don't you?
He'll be attending his own funeral.
Is that what you want to say? Fine.
I'll stay at least 500m away from him
at all times, okay?
Great, well done.
Get going now.
Sol must be awake.
Let me go get her.
Sure, go ahead.
HYUN-JOON
Why the hell is this bastard calling?
Hello? Yes, it's Kang Dong-goo speaking.
Yoon-ah can't take your call
at the moment.
May I help you?
I heard you're going on an offsite today.
I called to tell her to have a good time.
Don't you worry about that.
Yoon-ah will have
a grand old time with us,
so you enjoy your retreat, okay?
Gotta go. We're leaving now.
Yes! I hung up while he was talking.
I'm here.
Huh? What?
Three o'clock position?
Where's that?
Oh, my goodness.
-What? You startled me.
-Get in before someone see you.
Just lift this up to get in. Come on.
Goodness gracious.
What is this, 007? Mission Impossible?
I don't know if I'm dating or taking part
in covert spy operations.
I'll take your bag.
Do you have to take it this far?
It can't hurt to be too careful.
What's that smell?
Something smells bad.
I don't know.
The car smelled funny ever since
Doo-sik and Soo-ah borrowed it.
Anyway, should we leave
for our first trip ever together?
Are you okay, Seo-jin?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Joon-ki, let's get you a new car
when you make money.
Why? Rebecca's still got what it takes.
Want to see?
Rebecca, you're fine, right?
See? She's fine. She's angry now.
Our trip starts now.
What is this?
-Are you sure we'll be okay?
-Rebecca!
The weather's nice, the view is nice.
It's even better because I'm with you.
It's paradise without
that devilish Dong-goo around!
I know.
That must be it.
-We're here.
-Wow.
Then shall I park the car?
This is great.
Let's do this!
It's so pretty here.
And it's called Boulanger?
What a pretty name.
How'd you find this place?
Dong-goo found it a few days ago
while he was doing research.
It was so pretty that I wanted to come.
With you.
My cute Bacca.
Did you want to come here with me
that much?
Stop teasing.
-Shall we go in?
-Okay.
I'm at your service, Princess.
-Let's do this!
-Are you okay?
-Of course!
Director Bong, are you okay?
I don't know.
I'm carsick.
We weren't even in the car for that long.
Stop being mean and help.
You're such a nuisance.
Ow! Be gentle.
-I'm about to throw up my organs.
-Fine.
Guesthouse Boulanger?
So we're staying at a guesthouse?
Yeah. Why?
Isn't it odd to go away to a guesthouse
when we run one ourselves?
A resort would've been better.
Do you know how much a resort costs?
I wanted to come here because they did
a really good job with the interior.
Yoon-ah, what do you think?
It's so pretty.
Okay, let's go inside.
-Jeez.
-Doo-sik, let's go.
Come on.
If you're done throwing up,
bring the suitcases from the car.
Hey, I'm so nauseous, it's killing me.
You do it.
Must the CEO do such menial work?
Shut up and do it.
What an evil boss.
Okay.
I have to look nice for Joon-ki.
Should I turn on my sex appeal?
Soo-ah, this must be the women's room.
-I think you're right.
-What?
I know that voice.
Goodness Sol, isn't this nice?
Shit!
They did a really good job
with the room, too.
It's cozy and nice.
There's another guest.
Is she sleeping?
-Let's unpack first.
-All right.
It's so nice.
What are they doing here?
What on Earth is going on?
My goodness.
I'm so tired from driving for so long.
But it's my first trip with Bacca.
It's going to be so much fun!
Doo-sik, this way.
Oh, okay.
I'm dying. I feel horrible.
What is up with that unpleasant voice?
Need help?
Why did she bring so much?
The room is spacious and clean. I love it.
-Don't you agree?
-I don't care.
Don't talk to me, I feel sick.
There's another guest here.
Is he sleeping?
Nope, but what the hell
are they doing here?
Why?
We can unpack later.
Let's go take a look around.
I want to rest.
We came all the way here. Let's go.
-I told you I'm not feeling well.
-Come on. Hurry up.
Oh, my God. Why are they here?
No way.
This is where they're having the offsite?
This is insane.
Wait. Seo-jin!
Yoon-ah, Soo-ah,
just leave your things and come outside!
Okay, we'll be right there!
-Shall we go, Yoon-ah?
-Shall we?
Let's go take a look, Sol.
-Go to Mommy.
-Let's go.
What the hell?
This is where they're having the offsite?
This is insane.
Damn it. I have to go see Joon-ki.
There's even a pool.
Did you bring your swimsuits?
It's incredible. It's really nice.
Isn't this place awesome?
-Hello.
-Towels for you.
Please tell me
if there's anything you need.
Thank you.
Your guesthouse is really pretty.
How do you manage
this place by yourself?
I didn't see any employees around.
My wife and I are running it by ourselves
because labor costs are high.
Actually, we run a guesthouse in Seoul.
Really?
Are you saying you came to stay
at a guesthouse
when you run one yourselves?
Excuse me? Oh, yes.
Then you should know better.
How come you called so late to book?
You're lucky we still had vacancies--
Aren't you busy, sir?
-You should get back to work.
-All right. Call me if you need anything.
That... really wasn't necessary.
So, anyway!
You've... what's it called...
You've done a great job
cleaning and doing laundry
and tending to the guests,
so forget all about the guesthouse.
Let's have a great time, all right?
What should we do?
I... I need to go rest
because I'm nauseous.
I'm dying, here.
Okay, then.
Let's all go in, then. I'll walk you over.
Joon-ki... are you here?
Where the hell is he?
Doo-sik, do you feel any better?
Shit. What the hell? Damn it!
Goodness.
Lie down.
-Thanks.
-Get some sleep.
I'll wake you up when it's time to eat.
That's all right.
I'm just going to lie down for a bit.
Don't worry about me and have fun.
Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
Gosh.
He's been sleeping for a long time.
Seo-jin... are you here?
Where the hell did she go?
Sol, it's time to eat.
-Let's go eat, Sol.
-What the hell?
Mommy will feed you, Sol.
What a good girl.
Were you hungry?
Mommy's going to feed you now.
Hold on one second, okay?
What?
Where did it go?
Is something missing?
My camera's gone.
I know I left it here.
You must've put it somewhere else.
No, I'm sure I put it here.
Where did it go?
Excuse me. I'm really sorry,
but have you seen the camera
that was here?
Then did anyone else come in
while we were gone?
Go.
What's with her? She's acting strange.
Excuse me. Shouldn't you answer
when someone asks you a question?
What's wrong with you?
What the hell? Joon-ki!
Dong-goo? What are you doing here?
Hey, Soo-ah!
Yoon-ah's here, too.
What brings you here?
What? We're here for the offsite.
Why are you here?
-I thought you had a shoot.
-What?
Well...
We're shooting on location today. Nearby.
I had so much time between takes
that I got myself a room to nap in.
Why are you in the women's room?
What? This is the women's room?
I just followed the owner guy.
He must not have his wits about him.
We should give him a piece of our minds.
He must've gotten confused,
working all by himself.
-There's your camera!
-Where?
I'm so glad!
You didn't even look properly.
Thank you.
Goodness, really.
I mean, what are the chances?
Wow.
Who knew we'd meet you here?
-What a coincidence.
-Seriously.
It's such a freaky coincidence.
If only Seo-jin didn't have to work,
we'd all be here together.
What a shame.
Yeah... you're right.
I guess we can't help it.
Isn't it nice here?
I can't believe they thought
of opening a guesthouse here.
Huh? What's this rope for?
It wasn't here earlier.
Is it a bell?
Mister!
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible.
I was cleaning.
How could you pull on the rope?
-That troublemaker. Jeez.
-I'm so sorry.
-Can I take you to the hospital?
-No, it's fine.
There's a group coming soon.
What will I do?
I have to clean and go buy groceries.
There's tons to do.
I'm really sorry...
Let me ask you for a favor, then.
A favor?
Good going, jerk.
You told us to forget about the guesthouse
and have fun.
What the hell is this?
What choice do I have?
He got hurt because of me.
Forget about us,
but you dragged Yoon-ah here
when she could've gone on her retreat.
Well done, you jerk.
I'm sorry, Yoon-ah.
Don't worry about it.
I feel like it's easier to fold towels
where the air is fresher.
It's only until the owner gets back
from the hospital,
-so just bear with it for a while.
-Okay.
It's him.
Hello, sir.
Excuse me?
I see.
Okay.
What? What did he say?
He says it'll take longer than he thought.
He asked us to take care of the guests
and to go buy groceries.
For goodness' sake. This sucks.
Sorry. I'll get the groceries,
so just finish up around here, please.
Are you sure you can go alone?
There's probably a lot to buy.
You two go ahead. We'll look after Sol.
-Okay, Joon-ki?
-Huh?
All right.
I'll leave Sol with you, then.
Mommy will be right back, okay?
-Let's go, Dong-goo.
-Okay.
-See you.
-Bye.
Sorry.
What's wrong with you?
You look like
you're about to shit your pants.
What? It's nothing.
There's nothing going on.
Joon-ki. Save me.
I'm trapped in the men's room.
Why did she go in there?
I'm done mopping the floors, so I'll go
change the sheets in the men's room.
Okay.
Joon-ki!
-Doo-sik!
-What are you doing here?
Don't you have a shoot today?
Yeah...
The shoot location is nearby,
so I decided to stay here.
Really?
What a coincidence.
I know.
I'm so dumbfounded, I could cry.
Why are you in bed?
You came all the way here.
Let's go out, Doo-sik.
That's okay. I'm nauseous and dizzy
from being carsick.
That's why you should get some air.
Let's go for a walk.
-I said I don't want to.
-Then you should sleep.
-I'm not sleepy.
-Then close your eyes or something.
-I'm playing a game on my phone.
-Leave, damn it! Why won't you go out?
That's none of your business.
Why are you mad?
Huh?
I'm just... worried about you.
I'm worried is all.
Since when did you care so much
about me?
Don't talk to me. I need to play this.
What the hell?
You punk.
Joon-ki, what are you doing?
The guests are here.
-Come on out.
-Okay! Be right there!
Well... then don't move a muscle
and stay here, okay?
I'll do whatever it takes
to get you out of here.
You trust me, don't you?
Just wait a while.
I'll be right back, okay?
What the hell?
Why is he saying he'll get me out of here?
What do we need to buy?
The group guests want to have
pork belly for dinner.
-Shall we get some vegetables first?
-Okay.
There's the produce store.
-Hello.
-Welcome. What would you like?
Lettuce and perilla leaves, please.
Enough for about ten people.
Sure thing.
You must be newlyweds.
You're quite a handsome couple.
-Pardon?
It's nice of you to come grocery shopping
with your wife.
Reminds me of old times.
You're so adorable
that I'll throw in some extra.
Well, actually...
Thank you so much. You're very kind.
My hubby loves him some lettuce.
It's great, isn't it, honey?
-Sorry?
-Goodness.
Your wife is so lovable.
You're a lucky man.
-Be happy together, okay?
-Yes, thank you.
Honey, let's go.
Pardon? Oh... okay.
What are you doing?
Why'd you call me "honey"?
She gave us extra on the house.
There was no need to say she was wrong.
We can have what she threw in for free.
Still, this isn't right.
It's wrong to lie, Yoon-ah.
Honey...
pork belly is what you love most
in the entire world,
but I'm so sorry I can only afford
to buy three pounds' worth.
My honey can eat that in one go.
It's too little. What will we do?
Honey...
apples are what you love most
in the entire world,
but I'm sorry I can only afford
to buy you this much.
What will we do?
I'm so very upset.
What is this? You told me I shouldn't lie.
But we got free meat and fruit out of it.
What else do we need to get?
Come with me for a sec, Yoon-ah.
-Why?
-Just come with me.
Where are we going?
Why are we here?
This one's pretty.
Come here.
Dong-goo...
Your bangs
keep on covering your eyes.
It'll only cause me trouble
if you fall because of that.
That's why I'm getting it for you.
Don't feel pressured.
It doesn't mean anything, really.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
Yoon-ah.
-You like sundaes, don't you?
-I do.
-Shall we go eat a sundae?
-Shall we?
-Hello. Two sundaes, please.
-Sure.
Why, would you like some makgeolli?
Pardon? No, it's just...
they make it look so tasty.
You should have a glass, then.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-One bottle of makgeolli, please.
-Okay.
-It's really okay.
-It's fine.
It's so good.
Do you like it that much?
Want another glass?
I might get drunk if I have more.
You're here to have fun.
Who cares if you get drunk?
-Just have another.
-Shall I, then?
I shouldn't have given her
any more makgeolli...
My eyes sting.
Did we come all the way here
to light up a grill?
This is ridiculous.
So why did you come here
for the offsite? Why?
Why are you taking it out on me?
It was Dong-goo's decision.
-Isn't it ready yet?
-Almost done.
There it is.
You can grill the meat on this.
Thanks.
That looks really good.
Would you like to join us?
We brought a lot.
Really?
I almost forgot.
Doo-sik hasn't eaten all day.
He must be hungry.
-I should ask him if he wants any.
-Wait!
I'll go ask him. You stay here.
-Thank you!
-Sure.
Sol, look. It's meat.
Hey, Doo-sik. There's meat.
Let's go out together.
That's okay. I'm still nauseous,
so I don't feel like eating.
The smell of cooking meat
is making me sick. I can't eat that.
Who knows?
Maybe you'll feel better after eating.
I don't want to. I told you I'm nauseous.
You punk! If you're so sick, then how come
you're playing on your phone all day?
Get some sleep instead!
I told you I'm not sleepy.
Why do you keep yelling at me?
You bastard.
Just hold on for a little longer.
You need to be strong, okay?
I'll find a way to get you
out of here, okay?
I said no. I'm not leaving!
What's wrong with him?
Stay strong? For what?
Gosh, this is good.
Why are you alone? Isn't Doo-sik eating?
No, he's not.
He must really not be feeling well.
-You should eat.
-What?
I don't have much of an appetite.
Joon-ki! I want to eat pork belly.
I'm starving!
Goodness. How can she think
about eating in this situation?
I'm speechless.
Give that to me.
Why are you taking that?
-You said Doo-sik isn't eating.
-What?
Well, yeah. It's...
There's a starving cat over there.
He's so pitiful.
-Do you mind if I take this to him?
-Sure, no problem.
Thank you.
Why are you back?
I told you I don't want to eat.
I'm not here for you,
so mind your own business!
-Then who are you here for?
-You don't need to know.
Just play your game, damn it!
Why are you getting mad?
What's with the paper cup?
Huh?
It's coffee.
Well... I'm off now
since I saw you in bed.
-Hold on.
-What?
Where's the coffee
you were holding in your hand?
What?
The thing is...
Ta-da!
It's magic.
It disappeared without a trace, didn't it?
Where do you think it went?
Wow, that's amazing!
It's fascinating! How did you do it?
Do it again.
Show me. Do it again.
Do what again? Get lost!
He was definitely holding it.
Where's the lettuce?
Damn it.
Don't be like that. Show me one more time.
It's so fascinating, that's why.
Are you serious?
Is that really what you want?
I do. I want to see it again.
Show me. Please?
Just a moment.
You said you'll do the magic trick!
Where are you going?
Ta-da!
Wow, that's amazing!
It's so fascinating!
Where did it go?
Show me. Do it again!
Do what again? Get lost!
Where did it go?
And the garlic and ssamjang?
Joon-ki, don't be like that.
Do it again. Just one more time.
Will you really be this way?
Are you serious?
Must you really have it all?
Does that make you happy?
What are you saying?
I'm really curious, that's why.
Show me just one last time, okay?
Fine. Is that really what you want?
Ta-da!
It's still so fascinating! So awesome!
How did you do it?
This is the last time.
Really, it's the last time.
I can't do it anymore!
Don't expect anything more from me.
Okay.
But it's really cool.
When did you learn how to do magic?
I don't know, you punk! Get lost!
You get lost! What's with the attitude?
Yoon-ah, I think you're drunk.
You should stop drinking.
I'm not drunk at all.
I'm totally fine.
Okay, so stop drinking.
We're not done grocery shopping.
Okay.
You know what, Dong-goo?
Do you like to play hide-and-seek?
Hide-and-seek?
I love playing hide-and-seek.
Do you want to play?
All of a sudden?
Let's get up. We're not done shopping.
-How much do we owe you?
-14,000 won.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Yoon-ah, let's--
What the hell?
Yoon-ah!
Where the hell did she go?
She's driving me nuts.
Yoon-ah!
Where did she go?
-You're the groom.
-Hi.
She's hiding over there.
Yoon-ah, what are you doing here?
You got me!
You found me, Dong-goo!
My turn to find you.
Dong-goo, go hide.
Why would I hide?
Sober up, Yoon-ah.
Your wife was fine earlier. What happened?
She had some makgeolli.
She must be drunk.
I almost forgot.
Can I have some green onions?
Okay, sure.
-It's 2,000 won.
-Here.
What?
Yoon-ah! Where did she go?
She's killing me. Goodness.
What are you doing here?
What? Oh, you got me again!
Okay! My turn to find you.
Go hide, Dong-goo.
This is insane.
You're just dying to play hide-and-seek,
aren't you?
You don't want to hide?
Okay, fine.
I get to hide again!
Where do you think you're going?
Dong-goo, let go.
-I have to go hide!
-What am I going to do with her?
Can you untie me, Dong-goo?
I really have to go hide...
Be quiet!
I've never seen such a crazy drunk.
Just follow me, okay?
Geez.
I'm going nuts, seriously.
But I have to hide...
Yoon-ah... Yoon-ah, sober up!
Gosh, you got me again!
Fine, you can go hide now.
I'll be "it."
She's driving me crazy.
Huh?
Okay.
I'll be it again
so you can hide again. Got it?
There's one place I'll never find you.
Do you want to know where?
Where is it?
It's right here. Follow me.
Right here.
So you're saying you can't find me
if I hide in here, right?
I sure can't.
Okay.
Okay, shh. Hide.
Dong-goo, I'm done hiding.
Come find me!
Coming!
Goodness, you did such a great job hiding
that I can't find a single trace of you!
What will I ever do?
I came all the way here for this?
What? You got me again!
Dong-goo, it's really your turn to hide.
I'll be it.
Enough, Yoon-ah.
Sober up, will you?
Are you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
But it seems like you are.
I told you I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry, Dong-goo.
You don't have to be sorry,
so please get some sleep on the way back.
Please.
-Dong-goo...
-What is it now?
I caused you a lot of heartache, didn't I?
I know that I did.
But...
I'm afraid.
I don't want to get hurt again,
so I'm afraid.
I'm so scared.
So please don't hate me, Dong-goo.
Don't hate me.
How do you feel, Doo-sik?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm feeling better now.
Really? That's great.
Then should we go out for some air?
Let me finish this first.
I'm on the last stage.
What's that noise?
Is he snoring?
He was sleeping when we got here.
How many hours has it been?
What's that?
-He's got really long hair for a guy.
-You're right.
-Wait.
-What?
Are those flowers on his shirt?
Flowers?
They are.
Actually, it looks like a dress.
Are you sure he's a man?
What are you talking about?
Can't you tell he's a man?
So many guys grow out their hair
these days.
And haven't you heard of unisex?
There's no distinguishing between
guys' or girls' clothing now.
Look, I have flowers on my underwear!
What the hell are you doing?
It's still strange.
He even has a better figure than me.
-What?
-She's right.
-You think maybe... it's a woman?
-What?
Soo-ah, you should check.
Shall I?
Why do you need to check?
Don't bother a sleeping person.
That's bad manners. Don't.
Get out of my way. I'll just sneak a peek.
I told you to move.
Oh, my God.
I guess not.
It's a man. He's got facial hair.
-Facial hair?
-Really? I thought it might be a woman.
-Wait.
-What?
Seo-jin's a woman,
but she's got facial hair.
-Seo-jin?
-Hey.
She's got to be the only woman
to have that much facial hair.
I guess.
Let's go out for the photo shoot
when Dong-goo gets back
now that you're feeling better.
Okay.
Yoon-ah.
Yoon-ah, we're here.
Oh, my.
Dong-goo...
what happened?
What do you think?
You got drunk and wanted to play
hide-and-seek,
so I had to run around the entire market
trying to find you.
Oh, no. Did I do that?
I'm so sorry.
I have a habit of playing hide-and-seek
when I get drunk.
Is that all I did?
I didn't make any mistakes?
-No, you didn't.
-I'm so glad.
I'm sorry, Dong-goo.
It's fine. Get some rest.
I'm all right.
There's so much to do.
Goodness.
Where did everyone go?
It's almost time for the guests to arrive.
Anybody there?
I think the guests have arrived.
Welcome!
Hyun-joon?
Yoon-ah. What are you doing here?
Is this where you're holding the offsite?
Yes. What about you?
This is the guesthouse my friend runs.
This is pretty cool.
So that's what happened.
What a coincidence.
Let's take these suitcases outside.
Okay.
Why is it so loud?
Are the guests here?
Let's go see, Doo-sik.
Hey, Seo-jin. Get up. Seo-jin!
What do you want?
Wake up!
How can you sleep in this situation?
Huh? What the hell happened?
I don't know. We don't have much time,
so let's go before they come back.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Why the hell is he sitting out there?
This is killing me.
I don't think you can go out this way.
What are we going to do?
Are you serious? What should we do?
Right. The window!
Open it.
What's wrong with this?
-It must be broken.
-What?
Damn it.
All hell will break loose
if Dong-goo finds out.
What do we do?
Yes!
Did you think of something?
-Seo-jin.
-Yes?
Go inside that.
You want me to go in the suitcase?
Are you crazy?
What else can we do?
Doo-sik's standing guard
and the window is broken.
Do you want to go back into bed?
What if you get caught? What will you do?
-Seriously, do we have to go this far?
-There's no other way.
Fine, I'll do it.
Good. Let's get you inside.
This is driving me crazy.
Get in, Seo-jin.
-Damn it.
-Get in.
Careful.
-I'll get you out right away.
-Okay.
It'll just be a short while.
Oh, no! Seo-jin!
I'm so sorry.
Let's go quickly.
-Joon-ki.
-Oh, my God!
You startled me! Why are you so surprised?
What are you doing with my suitcase?
Huh? Well... it's... I was going to...
You're helping us prepare
for the photo shoot? Thank you!
Why is this so heavy?
Hey... Soo-ah.
Shit!
Why is this so heavy?
-How much did you bring?
-Shut up!
Why are you following us?
Yeah, why?
I just want to help out.
Soo-ah, isn't the suitcase heavy?
Allow me.
Yes, please.
Okay!
Let's go!
-Hurry up!
-Coming!
It really worked out.
I was so upset you couldn't make it.
How did we end up meeting here?
Seriously. I had no idea that this place
was run by Hyun-joon's friend.
What should we do now?
It's too early for dinner.
How about a game?
That sounds good.
-What shall we play?
-How about 007?
-Electricity game.
-Bang, bang!
Come on now, everyone. You all know
that when you're at a retreat,
you have to play jokgu.
Jokgu?
How can you suggest jokgu
when we have ladies here?
There's no gender discrimination
in sports.
You could easily be misunderstood,
you know.
That's not what I meant.
It's just that everyone's tired.
I don't think a ball game
is the way to go.
What about a game of charades?
We can play it indoors.
There's nothing like jokgu
at a retreat, I tell you!
Don't you agree, Yoon-ah?
I'm still a bit dizzy,
so jokgu might be difficult.
Let's play charades instead.
You should join us, Dong-goo.
Well, I guess I can.
I'm really bad at this.
We've lived under the same roof
for quite some time now.
I can't speak for Hyun-joon,
but I can definitely get it right.
EGG
Answer! Fart.
Answer! Constipation.
You can't poop.
-Egg?
-Correct!
SHRIMP
Answer! Zombie?
A zombie with a broken back!
-Shrimp!
-Nah...
Correct!
What is that? What are you doing?
The Unbearable Lightness of Being.
"Even if the world goes to pieces,
I'd still plant my apple tree."
-Correct!
-Amazing!
-Hyun-joon, you're really good at this!
-How did you get that right?
It doesn't make any sense!
It doesn't!
Okay, let's go. Nice.
One more.
That's a bit pretentious. Something else.
Very nice.
-Do full body shots now.
-Joon-ki...
-No, stop it.
-Okay.
-Are you okay?
-How long do I have to stay in here?
My legs hurt and it's suffocating.
I'm sorry. Just a bit longer.
I'll do whatever it takes, okay?
Joon-ki, who are you talking to?
What? Well...
To this rock.
Gosh. It must be so frustrating
to be stuck in the ground.
You're a very hard-headed fellow.
What are you talking about?
Move. I need to get some clothes.
-I need to change into the next outfit.
-No!
Goodness. What do you mean, no?
No, not this suitcase. Never!
That's my bag. What are you saying?
-Get out of the way.
-I said no! I can't give you this. Never!
Have you gone mad?
Stop it and give me my suitcase!
No! Never! I won't!
What's wrong with him?
-Doo-sik, go get him!
-Okay!
Hey! Joon-ki!
What's the matter with him?
This is so heavy.
Where the hell did he go?
Why would he run off with my suitcase?
He must've really lost it.
He must be somewhere else.
-Let's go that way.
-All right.
They left, Seo-jin.
It's over. It's all over now.
Where did she go?
What happened?
No way.
Shit!
Seo-jin!
SHRIMP,
THE UNBEARABLE LIGHTNESS OF BEING
The Unbearable Lightness of Being.
Didn't that work up your appetites?
Shall we eat dinner?
Really?
Then you should all rest.
Men are supposed to cook
at a place like this.
I'll make us something.
Wait.
You can cook with the real man,
Kang Dong-goo.
-Do you know how to cook?
-Of course.
I've been CEO of a guesthouse for years.
Most chefs can't hold a candle to me.
Is that so?
Then please, join me.
Great. Let's go.
I'll show you the true taste
of a real man.
What are you going to make?
I'll grill some meat and make kimchi stew.
Oh, kimchi stew?
That's what I was going to make.
It's my specialty.
How exactly will you make it?
With some pork shoulder and kimchi.
Then I'll boil it. Isn't that enough?
A kimchi stew should be made
with none other than mackerel pike.
Isn't pork kimchi stew the easiest choice?
Goodness, you're mistaken.
Do you want to make a bet
to see which is tastier?
You're on.
Let's begin.
Why are there two kimchi stews?
Well, Hyun-joon and I had
a difference in opinion.
You should all try both
and let us know which one you prefer.
We placed a bet.
Really?
Shall I taste it, then?
Gosh, it's greasy.
This one's perfect!
You're right. I also think that
the pork kimchi stew tastes better.
-How about you, Yoon-ah?
-Oh.
This one's tasty.
And that one?
This one's also tasty...
but a little greasy.
To be honest, I'm not a big fan of fish.
Yes!
Why? Is the mackerel pike stew yours,
Dong-goo?
Who cares who the winner is?
What matters is that
we're all enjoying this food together.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
Let me get some air. Excuse me.
My goodness. The weather is great,
the fresh air is great,
but Song Hyun-joon is not so great.
Song Hyun-joon, that piece of shit.
Nothing works out because of him.
Looks like no one's eating this.
Shall I put it away?
Just leave it. I'll eat it.
-You said you don't like fish.
-Huh?
But this looks tasty.
I'll eat it.
I've always known he was nuts,
but I just can't understand him.
Why would he run off
with someone else's suitcase?
Did he hit his head or something?
Let him be. Don't try to understand him.
Just give up.
We couldn't even have a proper photo
shoot because of that jerk. What the hell?
-Joon-ki!
-Joon-ki.
Give me that suitcase.
What? Why do you keep doing this? Stop!
Just give it to me. Please.
What do you have against our suitcases?
Why are you doing this?
Cut the crap and give it to me!
-No, no. You can't. No!
-Give it to me.
Let go of my suitcase!
-Let go!
-What's wrong? Joon-ki, stop.
Give it to me.
Oh, my God! My clothes!
What are you going to do?
Seo-jin... Seo-jin!
Why are you yelling Seo-jin's name?
Damn it. Seo-jin!
Seo-jin!
-What's wrong with him?
-Seo-jin.
No, Seo-jin. No!
Seo-jin.
Wait. Why is he yelling Seo-jin's name?
I don't know. He's nuts.
What do we do?
Seo-jin!
-No, Seo-jin. Hang on!
-Why is he calling out for her?
-Joon-ki!
-Get out!
-This way. Over here.
-Come here.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Lift it!
Seo-jin!
What the hell?
Are you all right?
I'm all right. I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Is that Seo-jin?
Why is Seo-jin here? What happened?
No way...
Is it magic?
Wow, that's amazing.
Where'd you learn how to do this?
Magic, my ass!
What are you talking about?
Joon-ki, what happened?
Why is Seo-jin here?
-Well... the thing is...
-What are you all doing there?
-What's going on? What were you doing?
-Dong-goo...
Hey, Seo-jin! What are you...?
You said you were covering a funeral.
Dong-goo, the thing is...
Wait.
What's this ominous vibe I'm getting?
What's with this awful feeling
that I'll find out something
of great magnitude?
Well... the thing is... we...
Joon-ki, enough is enough.
Let's just tell him the truth.
What truth?
What are you talking about?
Well, you see... it's...
Will you be like this until the end?
Fine, forget it.
You son of a bitch.
What is this?
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you holding hands?
Dong-goo, I like Seo-jin.
What?
Excuse me?
What do you mean?
I, Lee Joon-ki,
like your sister, Kang Seo-jin.
No...
I'm in love with her.
What did you say? Love?
So, to summarize,
you and Seo-jin love each other?
-Are you serious?
-Yes, I love Seo-jin.
So...
kill me or let me live.
Do as you wish.
Kill you or let you live?
Fine.
-Then I'll kill you!
-Don't.
How can you do this to me?
You didn't say a word to me about it!
My sister?
You son of a bitch!
When did it start? Tell me!
So, you tricked me all this time?
-You're not my sister anymore.
-Dong-goo, let's talk.
As far as I'm concerned,
you no longer exist.
So don't even talk to me
or act like you know me!
I won't shave until you give us
your blessing. Got it?
What?
He's the Park Bo-gum
of the modeling industry.
My name is Min Soo-ah.
Bad rhinitis!
What's that smell?
It's so bad.
-I'm sorry!
-I won't do the shoot today.
Just stay here. You crazy bastard!
How about we go out
for celebratory drinks?
I should come with.
Didn't you want to say something,
Hyun-joon?
Actually, I...
Song Hyun-joon seems like a decent guy.
Do you know how foolish you are?
Yoon-ah...