(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(All characters, places, companies,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Rape and blackmail.
A thug with a hammer tattoo.
Seo Kyeong was the one who took her clothes off.
Did you ever kill a woman 20 years ago?
I heard you were a weirdo.
Gosh.
The Lord has created the skies and the ground.
No matter how much you deny it.
Humans must...
If I didn't kill anyone, what will you do?
Apologize?
Get rid of it!
Goodness.
He's the best.
Excuse me.
Please step back.
- Yes? - Where are you?
- I'm on my way to their office. - What?
Is that where she is?
They were just hired for the job.
What do you mean?
How could you beat him up?
The real culprit is someone who received sexual favors from her.
What?
Old Man, I need you to do a favor.
- The red pig? - Hurry up! Time is ticking!
Still, you shouldn't...
Baek? Baek!
I think someone's dead.
They must've jumped off this building.
- They took the person. - Look.
(Episode 2: Red Pig)
(24 minutes ago)
- Yes? - Is Seo Kyeong home?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
You should've broken the door open and checked!
Come on, the police station is right across the street.
Then you could've called a repairman...
and said you were her brother!
What if they report me?
Check this instant.
Wouldn't it be better to say that I'm her boyfriend?
Darn it. Just do it!
You should do it yourself.
We really don't get along.
Delivery.
Where is he?
Search the place!
- Yes, sir. - Go.
- Is he not here? - What is it?
Clear.
- Darn it. - Clear.
The place is empty.
(President Oh Yeon Tak)
Sir, we're in trouble.
If I didn't kill anyone,
- what will you do? - What?
Apologize?
I'll let you off for urinating in public.
Get rid of it!
What is that sound?
Darn it.
Go inside!
Gosh, it's a mess. Open that.
Open it.
Hey, you punk!
Stop what you're doing, you scumbag.
Don't get smart, or I'll kill you.
Darn it.
- Let's go! - 1, 2!
- Darn it! - 1, 2!
- 1, 2! - Hold on. No!
- Hold on. - You scumbag.
Did you think you could run away?
Did you?
1, 2!
Darn it.
10 percent?
There was a 90-percent possibility...
that the one with the burner phone was the culprit...
and a 10-percent possibility that we were wrong.
And yet, you investigated the latter as well?
There were no call logs on that phone.
She only used a secured messenger service...
that didn't leave any records.
- Why? - It was something unexpected.
Kim Seo Kyeong was assaulted six months ago.
Her ex-boyfriend had stalked her.
He claimed he beat her because she became corrupt.
"Corrupt"?
He had found out...
that she had been giving sexual favors.
The pimp's alibi has been confirmed.
- Then? - The culprit was a client.
He had planned to exploit her that night.
A top-drawer individual...
who had completely hidden his identity.
They're reporting in.
One of the suspects has fallen from the building.
What?
He was climbing down on a rope.
That will be all for today.
I pray that the Lord will be with you at all times.
What day is it today?
I was kidnapped on Sunday, so it must be Monday.
It's tomorrow.
What is?
The execution.
What? What do you mean?
He kills one every Tuesday.
The girl before you died on a Tuesday as well.
No way.
Brace yourself.
You must score 90 points or higher.
What should I do?
If you score lower than that, you'll die...
a gruesome death.
The culprit kidnaps his victims on Tuesdays...
and kills them a week after.
It'll be Tuesday in four hours.
Please do your best to locate her until the end.
(VIP Ward, Waiting Room)
I've been interrogating both of them.
But they're not caving in.
They've been separated, and we've been pressuring them.
Once one of them caves in, we'll be able to get a lead.
Hey, Lawyer Kim.
File a lawsuit again Dong Baek and the rest.
Make sure to teach them a lesson.
I'm too old for this.
Okay.
Who are you?
- Senior Superintendent Han Sun Mi. - "Constable"?
She's the senior superintendent.
"Senior superintendent"?
- She looks young. - Be quiet!
How dare you raise your voice after assaulting me?
Things have changed nowadays.
- Mr. Oh Yeon Tak. - What?
I don't care if you sue Mr. Superpower.
I'm only interested in the murderer.
And why would you ask me about him?
I also have no interest in your pimping.
At least, for now.
Who keeps spreading such rumors?
Kim Seo Kyeong is dying because of you.
You have tender hands.
But what can I do? I know nothing about this.
Your client is the murderer.
Tell me.
Whom did she meet?
What are you talking about?
The longer you stay silent, the more interested I'll become.
Are senior superintendents...
invincible or something?
You sexually assaulted and threatened wannabe actresses.
Do you have proof?
You think you're innocent since you got rid of the evidence?
But like you said, things have changed nowadays.
One testimony against you,
and you'll be found guilty.
Guess what?
I'm not the type...
to be easily intimidated by such threats.
You must feel safe...
since the powerful has your back.
That's how fools think.
Do you know how they're still so powerful?
It's all thanks to disposables like you.
Keep going.
One more victim, and I'll become completely obsessed with this case.
I'll make sure to find you guilty.
You will never set foot outside of a penitentiary.
At least, until you're allowed to receive your pension.
Rookies like you... Hey, I'm not done talking.
Where are you going? Hey.
- Should we provoke him more? - I'm not done.
He doesn't know.
What?
He doesn't know whom Kim Seo Kyeong met.
I really feel bad for her and want to help.
You scumbag, do you think we'd buy that?
You're in charge of the girls.
So how could you not know who she was meeting?
There's a separate organization that handles the clients.
You little...
I have absolutely no idea who our clients are.
How could you work...
with an unknown organization?
- How? - Answer.
So...
I think it was two years ago. Someone contacted us,
saying that he was interested in Seo Kyeong.
He had sent us 100,000 dollars right away.
Our president went money-crazy...
and searched for more pretty girls.
Kim Min Kwon.
Yes?
Try to remember.
- Look... - Because if you can't,
I'll make you take responsibility...
for their deaths.
I can't remember anything for the life of me.
Oh, right. Number 13.
He was addressed as Number 13.
- "Number 13". - It was the client's number.
What else? What else?
Why would you be here?
- Let me through. - Are you here to steal information?
I just want to see Kim Min Kwon, so move aside.
I won't. I guess you need to get more beaten up.
Is that what you want?
I'm fine. I let my guard down.
I beat him to a pulp earlier.
I let you do that so that I could read your memory.
Don't be ridiculous.
Gosh, this little punk. Hey.
Lim Chil Kyu!
Are you okay?
What is it?
- I want to see Kim Min Kwon. - This has nothing to do...
with Yoon Ye Rim's disappearance.
Don't you want all the help that you can get?
Sir.
We'll wrap this up soon.
My name is Han Sun Mi.
I don't think you should shake hands.
So you want to scan Kim Min Kwon's memory?
- Who are you? - Watch what you say.
She's a senior superintendent.
- Move aside. I'm in a rush. - You little...
You can talk to me. I'm the head of this case.
- Do you have the final say? - Of course.
I need his memory in order to know whom Kim Seo Kyeong met last.
What if there's nothing useful in his memory?
I still need to see it. There may be leads that he's not aware of.
You're going to pull out memories that even he doesn't remember?
No.
- What? - Lower your voice.
What an impudent punk.
I won't allow it.
- Why? - Aren't you suspended?
Why does that matter?
The court won't acknowledge any evidence found by you.
Don't waste your time. The victims are dying...
as we speak!
Show some respect!
The culprit won't be found guilty since it'll be an illegal arrest.
Then I could at least scan him as a means of rescuing the victims.
Exactly.
That's different.
You wouldn't need my permission.
- Are you saying... - Any information he finds...
won't be shared with us.
- However... - Kim Min Kwon will tell you...
what he remembers.
You're quite smart.
But if any problems occur, you must take full responsibility.
All by yourself.
Okay. Deal.
This is truly an honor.
It's a shame I'm in this state.
You do know what you're signing up for, right?
Yes, I'll be offering my memory.
- And the purpose of it? - To catch the culprit.
- Hey. - Oh, right.
To rescue the victim.
Wait.
It won't hurt, right?
- Not at all. - Will my memories get mixed up,
or will I suffer from dementia?
Never.
- Wait, wait. - What is it this time?
Last night,
I watched some porn.
Don't worry. If he tells others about your memory,
I'll arrest him.
All right, then.
- Who are you? - We're from...
the Northern District Prosecutors' Office.
This is an emergency arrest of Det. Dong Baek...
for repeated assault.
Grab him.
- Hold him. - What is going on?
- Stop him! - Stop him!
- All right. - Back away.
What is this arrest for?
- And who are you? - It's been a while, Sun Mi.
Have you been well?
Did we see each other for the last time...
at the institute?
Do you have a warrant?
Emergency arrests can only be carried out...
if the crime is worth at least three years in prison.
- Mere assault isn't one of them. - Goodness.
I'm intimidated by the top student at our institute.
Send me a petition of appeal.
Or request a warrant.
- Get out. - Hey.
Did you say that it was assault?
What? Yes.
He committed bodily harm. That's a maximum of seven years.
Don't be ridiculous. He was just apprehending the culprit...
and hurt him by accident.
We'll take our time and interrogate him.
Do your job.
- Escort him. - Hey, hey.
Move aside.
Give me just five minutes.
The kidnapped victims' lives are at stake.
- Five minutes? - After that, he's all yours.
What? Is he going to scan his memory?
But guess what? I'm not up for it.
People's lives are at stake here.
From now on, if any of you touch my men,
we'll charge you with obstruction of justice.
I don't know if you heard, but this isn't a threat.
How dare you lay your finger on a prosecutor?
If I annoy you so much, you should've become...
a judge or a prosecutor.
It's someone else.
- What? - The target.
It's not Det. Dong.
What are you saying?
Kim Min Kwon.
You're here to interrupt our investigation.
What are you saying?
Thanks to you, we finally found out.
The one trying to cover this is the culprit.
I'll reveal his identity.
I'll expose who that Number 13 is.
What is Number 13?
Let them through.
Let them.
- You better watch out. - Come here.
Darn it.
There are victims who were abducted.
At this rate, they'll all die!
Inspector. Inspector!
Starting this moment, our target has been changed.
To whom?
Northern District Prosecutors' Office.
(Professor Han Sun Mi)
Gosh, these punks...
are having such fun lives.
(Situation Room)
(While the Prosecutor's Office was taking Dong Baek away,)
(Han Sun Mi ordered an internal investigation.)
What is it? Is there a problem?
No, sir.
Professor Han's investigating...
the Northern District Prosecutors' Office.
She always had a good hunch.
Should we stop her?
You don't admit she's good, do you?
- Pardon? - You're calling her Professor Han.
I put her in that position so she could be your right arm.
I'm sorry, sir. I'm just used to calling her that way.
She is officially a professor...
of the Korean National Police University.
I'm sure you're jealous.
You rolled around in dirt for 20 years after graduating.
You thought you climbed up faster than your colleagues.
But a young person who passed the bar exam...
is now in the same rank as you.
No, sir. It's not like that.
Don't be so harsh.
I started off as a constable.
I'm sorry, sir.
Burn it after you see it.
It must not leak.
(Personal Information List)
(Emergency message, Situation Room)
(Western District Prosecutor's Office is the one in charge...)
(of Dong Baek's case. There is no record...)
(of Northern District Prosecutors' Office requesting transfer.)
We can't act so recklessly with the investigation.
We're against the prosecution.
His case is still with Western District Prosecutor's Office.
Northern District Prosecutors' Office came for no reason.
They just want to get attention through this case.
They are not the Crime Investigation Team.
- What? - Ace of...
Special Investigation Team barged in...
while ignoring the team in charge.
That's because this is about someone with superpowers.
Prosecutor Oh is dying to get some spotlight,
but there's someone who would never want to be in the spotlight.
The higher-ups.
The RIU is investigating a serial murder case in the capital,
and they turned the case into a public investigation this evening.
They also revealed the criminal's profile.
They suspect that the criminal used a claw hammer,
and there have been at least two victims until now...
Yes. We're on our way in.
Yes.
Mom, I'm scared.
- A pig? - Yes, a red pig.
It's okay even if it's pink.
- Could we look around? - Of course.
Please excuse me.
Actually, Baek jumped into investigating after seeing you.
He was suspended, so he had to do it in secret.
- Really? - Of course.
That's when he read "red pig" in the memory.
We came to see if there might be any clues here.
But, whose memory...
A testifier.
Don't worry.
Tell her what Baek is like.
He's the only detective in the world with a superpower...
who solved countless cold cases.
He's a superhero. There's nothing to worry about.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
- Thank you. - He'll bring her home soon.
- Of course. - Of course. It's Dong Baek.
What are you doing?
I skipped dinner, so my blood sugar level is low.
- Is the cafeteria closed? - Are you crazy?
Order me a soup. An extra large one. I'm hungry.
Shut your mouth.
- Where are you going? - Do I have to report everything?
Right. No.
Hey!
Hey! Punk.
Hey, wait!
Are you going up?
Don't you know your place?
- Are you going to the 10th floor? - No.
Then get off.
- Hey. - Hold on.
(Seoul Northern District Prosecutors' Office)
Who...
Hey!
Security, please hurry on over.
- Hurry. - Where did the jerk go?
Sir! Sir!
Sir.
It's him! Get him!
- Come here. - You.
Hold him down.
Get him.
He's really something.
- You should leave. - Get him.
Don't touch him.
Hurry up.
- Why are you getting on? - Pardon?
Shouldn't you clean this up?
Yes, sir.
Darn it.
Let go. Let go of me!
Hey...
Why are you getting on?
Shoot.
- Get off. - Pardon?
Block him.
I see. Okay.
What are you doing?
Me too?
- Go! - Hey, you!
Where did he go?
He's over there. Get him.
- Hey! - Stop right there!
Hey. Come here.
Hey!
Stay right there.
Come here.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
(Personal Information List)
What is this?
It's a confidential document from the Intelligence Agency.
Why were they following District Attorney Lim Joong Yeon?
The reason isn't important. What's important is the result.
If we don't know the reason, we can't trust the result.
This is the way Deputy Chief Lee survives.
Was he collecting his weaknesses?
He's using the Intelligence Agency like they're his men.
Let's focus on the result for now.
(Lim Joong Yeon, Northern District Prosecutors' Office)
District Attorney Lim is suspected...
of taking sexual favors?
Kim Seo Kyeong did not show up...
to meet District Attorney Lim that evening.
Probably because she was abducted by the criminal.
Since he was stood up,
he called his secretary whom he was having an affair with.
My guess was wrong.
We were able to close in on the number of possibilities.
I only wasted time.
(Do not ask anything.)
(If you resist, you'll be tied up.)
(If you cry, you'll fall into misery.)
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
You should all get some sleep.
You too.
I'm okay.
It's not for sure yet.
It's only what that Detective Superpower said.
No. There are more victims.
You're looking at the same thing over and over...
We'll be back.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
Please take a look at this.
Here.
Here. Please take one.
(Missing Person)
(Yoon Ye Rim, 25 years old)
(Korean National Police Agency)
It's a blanket.
I'm going out for fresh air.
What was that?
These are incident points related to the victims.
No, I mean the map before.
It is a map of secondary locations.
(Map of Secondary Locations)
(Related to Yoon Ye Rim's case, The last location of the victim)
Onha-ri, 6-gil.
The place where the phone was found.
Hey! Freeze!
Just one location.
There's just one location left...
1.5km away.
The first position where the teenagers were found,
(The place where Kim Seo Kyeong's phone was found)
and where Yoon Ye Rim went missing?
The fifth victim.
Yoon Ye Rim went missing on Sunday, so the chance is low.
Track the locations of the teenagers who found the phone,
and wake everyone up.
Okay.
(Analysis of Secondary Locations and Incident Points)
The station in charge said they already searched, right?
If they already searched...
Let's focus on the pigs.
I'll go west, and you two can go east.
Please search the pig farm and the feed factory.
- Onha-ri is huge. The farm alone... - Are you sure...
about the red pig?
I'm certain it was a recent memory.
It's something she saw after she was abducted.
We don't even know if that pig is in this neighborhood.
We don't have time. Let's start from the starting point.
We don't even know if this is related to Claw Hammer.
You're making assumptions.
I hope I'm wrong...
about this nasty hunch.
Do you really think...
there will be a murder today?
Claw Hammer kills on Tuesdays...
"Claw Hammer"?
The one the news is talking about?
No, no, no. What are you talking about?
That case happened really far away from here.
Was Ye Rim...
No, it's not related to your daughter.
I'll bring her back soon, healthy and sound.
Please do.
Please. Please, I'm begging you.
All right, we have to get to work now.
Let's go.
Wait.
Here. This is kimbap.
I'm sorry I made them with cold rice...
It's okay. We'll enjoy them.
Let's go.
Thank you for the food.
Please. Please help me.
This is hilarious.
Don't you think so?
- What are you doing? - Bo Hyeon isn't home.
What is he doing?
Hey. Are you crazy? Don't. I said, don't.
- Hey, run! Run! - Hurry!
Darn it.
(Beef and Pork Butcher Shop)
Can I help you?
Have you ever seen this picture?
Or a shop called "Red Pig" or a farm?
I've never seen this.
I don't know.
What kind of pork isn't red?
Have you ever seen this picture or a shop called "Red Pig"?
I've never seen it.
We'll be at the police station in eight minutes.
These eight minutes will be your last chance to talk.
You said you found this burner phone in Seoul, right?
But what were you doing in Onha-ri?
What? People from Seoul can't even go to Gyeonggi Province?
7 minutes and 45 seconds left.
From the moment we arrive at the police station,
I'll start grilling you for all your crimes.
- What if we tell you before that? - Shut your mouth.
I'll forgive you...
as long as you didn't kill someone.
We didn't kill anyone.
- We just... - I told you to shut it.
- 7 minutes and 30 seconds. - We can ask them to find her.
- Bo Hyeon... - There's no need!
Bo Hyeon?
It's none of your business.
You were looking for Bo Hyeon.
(Two weeks ago)
Guys who pay to have sexual relationships with minors...
usually all go to unmanned motels. But...
But on that day,
he kept driving on a secluded road.
Where are we going?
Stop the car.
Stop it!
Stop the car! Stop it now!
No, no!
Where did they go?
I don't know. The car disappeared.
We lost her there. At the three-way intersection.
You should've called the police right away.
For what?
Bo Hyeon did that often.
We thought she would ghost us after taking the money.
My goodness. You kids should know better.
This is the head of the situation room.
I have a notice for all the officers.
As of this moment, dispatch all your men to search Onha-ri.
The suspected vehicle is an old unidentified SUV.
Search all areas...
- where it might be hidden. - Hello, sir.
Search houses too,
and if the residents refuse, deem them as potential suspects...
and you may use force.
- Yes. - The RIU...
has dispatched all their men to search this area.
- Really? - What time is it?
You know those teenagers we caught at the three-way intersection?
They're thugs who lure men that date teenagers to extort money,
and they chased after a car that had one of their friends in it.
What?
They lost her at the three-way intersection,
and the RIU will start searching near the villas in Onha-ri.
There was a profiling result...
the perp might be from the upper class.
You should get here too.
Sir, you can go first.
You have to search all the villas and check.
- I have somewhere to drop by. - Hey, wait!
Darn it!
Shoot.
Come on, what is wrong with this?
What are you all doing? I told all of you to move out!
Senior Superintendent Han, we received orders to wait.
- From who? The chief? - No, someone higher up.
Why did you stop the search on Onha-ri?
You're here.
Gosh, you look really stressed.
Sir!
Show some respect!
Senior Superintendent Han.
Why don't we talk in Young Soo's office?
We have to start the search immediately.
Do you not know the owners of those villas?
Does it matter?
How are you going to search then?
Will you beg a judge for a warrant?
You'll search all 80 places...
including the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court's villa?
Lives are at stake here.
On what grounds?
Because Detective Superpower says so?
Was it so hard to keep that a secret?
It's my assumption.
So? Will you break into their homes illegally?
And make all these people here lose their jobs?
Focus on identifying the vehicle.
If I'm wrong, I'll resign.
Do you think this will end with you losing your job?
- Please give me approval. - If I don't?
I'll take full responsibility.
Responsibility?
Fine, then.
As of this moment, Senior Superintendent Han Sun Mi...
is dismissed as the head of the situation room.
- Sir? - Sir.
Please reconsider.
Senior Superintendent Han.
Giving orders is as important as the weight of my rank.
Changing orders with an indecisive attitude...
is something lowly people like you do...
and that's why you can't become a leader.
Do you understand...
the weight of my order?
Senior Superintendent Han will be punished strictly...
through a disciplinary committee.
But still...
Aren't you going to work?
Yes, sir.
What are you doing? Search the SUV now!
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Does that make sense?
Det. Dong... Det. Dong is the suspect of the claw hammer case?
It's been confirmed he ran away last night.
But how could that make him a suspect?
The prosecution has started to make a move,
- Move! - so find out where Dong Baek is.
Hello? Hey, Kang Ji Eun.
Kang Ji Eun!
- Get ready. - Her vitals are dropping.
They're dropping more.
It has been confirmed there has been a third victim.
The victim, Ms. Kim, who just passed away...
went missing two weeks ago and was found...
The mystery of the Claw Hammer Serial Murder Case...
- is starting to get out of hand. - Ms. Kim...
was initially assumed to be a victim related to the case...
According to the police, it seems there are at least...
two more victims that have been kidnapped.
Are there any additional updates?
The police are not revealing information on additional victims.
However, based on an exclusive tip we just received,
one of the two victims who were kidnapped...
is Ms. Yoon, who went missing in Onha-ri two days ago,
and she's in her 20s.
Ms. Yoon went missing on her way home,
but after her family reported her missing,
the police deemed that she had simply run away from home,
and there are suspicions that the police neglected their duties...
to miss the golden hour of missing cases.
(Yoon Ye Rim, 25 years old)
The Public Prosecutor General will make a public announcement.
Let's hear it now.
Wait!
Did you do well?
I don't know.
What about you?
There were too many questions I couldn't answer.
You'll be okay.
Those who fail the test are killed after sunset.
I think...
it will be one of us...
The side where the tail light goes out of view quickly.
They lost her at the three-way intersection,
and the RIU will start searching near the villas in Onha-ri.
(Onsang-ri, 3.6km, Onha-ri, 3.2km)
(Test, 90)
(Test, 75)
I... I scored 75.
I failed to score 90, so I'll study more.
I have to score 90 in order to die.
I can memorize everything. I'll try harder.
Why isn't there anyone from the SWAT team?
The police agency dispatched them to identify the SUV.
We won't be able to help. Come on, let's move!
I'll talk to you later.
Please help!
Was the Lord not aware of the foolish betrayal of humans?
This leads to a logical contradiction.
So was the Lord incompetent...
or really heartless like we thought?
Almost all religions in the world...
made the mistake of literally translating...
the symbolic teachings of these types of prophets.
As a result, this led to their blind and foolish faith...
which led them to lead their descendants...
to the path of wrong belief.
On the other hand, the words of truth...
that you're listening to today...
have a very simple message.
That symbols are merely symbols.
That will be all for today's...
words of truth.
May the Lord always be with you.
(Onha-ri Villa Complex)
(Onha-ri)
(Mount Jeonghong)
(Onsang-ri)
How did you get up there?
Quiet. I'll get out of here and call the police.
- I want to go with you. - Please, be quiet.
Please, take me with you!
I need to get out to save you.
I'm going to die before that.
Hurry! Pull me up.
Come on, take me with you!
Please, take me with you.
No, wait!
Please, I'm begging you.
My Lord, I'm begging you. Please save my daughter.
(Onsang-ri, 11-gil)
The perp will be hiding inside one of these 80 villas.
Are you saying your initial profiling was correct?
Murder is a very important ritual for the perp.
There was an order...
to dissolve the Special Investigation Team.
This won't end quietly.
I have one last favor.
I can't grant you that.
Doesn't that mean your investigation failed?
How dare you attempt a trick in front of a professional?
The RIU is beating up the perp.
Something is wrong.
I knew we'd meet since you are Detective Superpower.
Shall we talk?