Silence Wang - "An Alluring Smile"
♫ I always casually tell you my wishes ♫
♫ And give you looks that a thousand words wouldn’t be able to describe ♫
♫ In this world, there will always be people who are busy looking for treasure ♫
♫ But they mistake the blazing sun for it ♫
♫ And miss out on the manifestations of life ♫
♫ On the long bridge of this ancient city ♫
♫ There is a sea of people and cars going on their way ♫
♫ Your smile is like a ray of light ♫
♫ That suddenly lights me up ♫
♫ (Your smile is like a ray of light. That suddenly lights me up) ♫
♫ The wind blows gently; summer is not yet over ♫
♫ Bikes ring on the greenway ♫
♫ So this is what love looks like ♫
♫ Just admit that you were allured by my smile and couldn’t forget me after you first saw me ♫
♫ Saying that love is deep like the sea… you flatter me ♫
♫ The most romantic thing is to just watch the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ That’s the direction my heart goes in ♫
♫ (Watching the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder. That’s the direction my heart goes in) ♫
♫ I want to write the remaining chapters of life with you ♫
♫ Sharing the laughs and tears with you freely no matter the circumstances ♫
♫ Our story won’t end ♫
Third Brother, you have been to many places.
Choose one and let's go with Brother Mei.
Meet in the conference room in five minutes.
Are we having a meeting to decide the venue for seafood?
Kind of.
Why are we having a meeting?
If you ask me, we should go to eat Little Turtle's scallops.
The service may be slow but the food is great.
We can call to reserve and order. The food will be ready when we get there.
No, no, no. Their service is too slow.
It will take two to three years to serve the food. Why don't we go to Snail Seafood?
Whoever's picking up the tab can decide. Brother Mei!
I'm a Libra. You should know that I'm afraid of making decisions.
Furthermore, it's already hard for me to treat you guys, so how can you still want me to make the decision?
Third Brother, you can make the choice. I'm fine with anything.
Let's talk about something else before we eat.
I just received an email notification from  Feng Teng.
The date for the demo
has been moved up to September 1st.
That's what is called a switch of subject.
We were talking about seafood.
Why did they bring forward the date?
Isn't the date already fixed? Why did they change it so suddenly?
That's right. They are even bringing it forward by more than two weeks.
I've called Director Wang of Feng Teng. There were two reasons.
First, Director Ho, who was in charge of the original "A Chinese Ghost Story," decided abruptly
to have surgery in the U.S. on September 10th.
The preparation for the surgery and recuperation will require three months.
Before he leaves, he wants to participate in the decision for the development rights of "A New Chinese Ghost Story."
Can you tell him to change the date to September 9th?
It's an auspicious date. He can fly to the States for the surgery immediately after that.
What's the second reason?
The second is that Feng Teng's  highest decision maker, President Feng,
has been watching this project closely.
He will also be there for the presentation. He has a conference overseas from September 2nd to 9th.
Based on the original plan, there's no problem for him to attend the presentation in mid-September
but now the two events all happen around the same time;
therefore, the date has to be moved to September 1st.
Third Brother, at our previous meeting, you said that
you could only complete your optimization software on September 15th.
If we include the testing and revisions,
the quickest we can get it done is on September 16th. What should we do now?
Are we going to forgo on our optimization?
I think it's not much of a problem to forgo.
After all, with the display and playing options of our game,
we will be able to slay everyone else.
The current issue now is just with the usage of memory.
Moreover, it's not like we are not capable of doing it. It's just a matter of time.
That's right. The inadequacy of development time is not our fault. We can explain it to them.
The decision maker won't care about the reasons. They will only look at the end product.
So I don't plan on forgoing optimization, but rather I'm going to deal both in parallel.
At the same time, we will make other adjustments to the extensive memory usage.
Other adjustments?
I just received the email. The timing is of the essence.
I suddenly had an inspiration.
You really have a special way of coming up with new inspirations.
"The Automatic Map Generation Project."
Reading this inspires me.
With the division of labor among our teams, we should be able to complete this in ten days.
Ah Shuang,  time is really tight.  We can only test as we make the modifications.
You'll be in charge of all the testing issues.
Ah Shuang?
Okay.
Who is working with K.O.?
K.O. is working with me.  You and I will finish the optimization tool together.
I will be responsible for the weighted visualization reassessment algorithm
and pixel compression.  You optimize the model.
I can do it.
The normal mission has ended. The difficult mission is about to start.
I hope everyone's feeling good.
Does this mean I'm the only one still thinking about eating seafood?
Didn't you say that we'd talk about seafood at the meeting?
You are such a liar.
After everything I said, isn't it the key theme for this?
Shanghai. A celebration banquet.
Yeah!
Brother Mei, you got away with another meal!
- Okay, okay.
- Do your best.
Hey, how did it go? Did you decide where we're going to eat seafood?
What seafood? There's a big problem.
What's wrong? Did a problem crop up with the game?
Feng Teng in Shanghai moved the demo forward more than half a month,
but this isn't the key point. The key point is that your husband,
our classmate Xiao Nai, has gone psycho.
What do you mean by "psycho?"
It means a workaholic.
Go back and help me bring some clothes over.
I want both business and casual clothes. Also, toiletries.
So... you're going to live in the office?
That's right.
As you've wished, I'm going to start living in the office.
♫ I always casually tell you my wishes ♫
♫ And give you looks that a thousand words wouldn’t be able to describe ♫
♫ In this world, there will always be people who are busy looking for treasure ♫
♫ But they mistake the blazing sun for it ♫
♫ And miss out on the manifestations of life ♫
♫ On the long bridge of this ancient city ♫
♫ There is a sea of people and cars going on their way ♫
♫ Your smile is like a ray of light ♫
♫ That suddenly lights me up ♫
♫ (Your smile is like a ray of light. That suddenly lights me up) ♫
♫ Just admit that you were allured by my smile and couldn’t forget me after you first saw me ♫
♫ Saying that love is deep like the sea… you flatter me ♫
♫ The most romantic thing is to just watch the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder. That’s the direction my heart goes in ♫
♫ (Watching the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder. That’s the direction my heart goes in) ♫
♫ I want to travel to all four corners   with you to enjoy the views in all kinds of weather ♫
♫ I want to write the remaining chapters of life with you ♫
♫ Sharing the laughs and tears with you freely no matter the circumstances ♫
♫ Our story won’t end ♫
Are you cosplaying as a gecko?
I'm sick at heart, Junior Weiwei.
What are you sick at heart about?
Look. Those two won't play with me.
Are they discriminating against my IQ?
No matter how you say it, I was the top student in the province. Okay?
You're thinking too much, Senior Mr. Beauty.
Don't you have a lot of things to do?
My work is too light. At most, it can be considered a  chore of manual labor.
Besides, working alone is boring. You can only get excited from two people working together.
Look. If our opinions differ, we can bicker about it.
The most important thing is...
Those two act like they are on top of the food chain.  Isn't it too irritating?
Why don't I feel that way? Instead, I feel that they're quite handsome.
You don't understand the world of men.
Why do I feel that you and I are in the same world?
Who's in the same world with you?  Never mind.
Junior Weiwei, it is my last time today
to talk to you as a human being.
Starting from tomorrow,
this senior will become a coding machine.
Tired, huh?
Thanks.
Everyone, listen. The timing is critical.
Huh?
Everyone is so busy,
but I can't help in any way.
Didn't we agree to pose as The Thinker?
(Note: famous work by the sculptor, Auguste Rodin)
With the two of you posing like this,
how can anyone find any inspiration?
For these two male gods to stand in front of our library,
of course, there is a reason.
Keep watching.
I will shortly be able to connect with Aristotle's soul.
At that time, his wisdom will be communicated through this pair of hands and relayed to me.
At that point, who'd bother the inspiration for coding?
I would even be able to understand the meaning of humanity's existence!
In front of your master, where did you get that kind of confidence?
Your master has been giving you guidance all along.
As a person, one must not be too narcissistic or too arrogant.
When you're narcissistic, it is easy to make a mistake. When you're arrogant, it is easy to fail.
Master Plato, no, I mean Master Aristotle,
have you not heard
that the disciple surpasses the master?
I'm not that fortunate as you and have the option of lying on the beach to enjoy the good life.
"The disciple surpasses the master?"
From what I know, you even got the key point wrong.
Hence, you should leave this difficult programming problem to your master.
You, go and cook a bowl of noodles for your master.
I refuse.
How dare you hit your master? Watch your attitude.
The both of you can continue fighting.
I have an inspiration.
He has an inspiration?
- Should we switch to a new pose?
- Here.
Time to eat.
This is known as a hobby.
May I have five minutes of your time?
I need to talk to you about something.
Speak.
Although it's summer now, they can't just make do like this.
- Make do?
- Yes.
Look.  Those who are napping by putting down their face on their desk can easily get problems with their neck.
Also, those who sleep on the chair, either they fall off their chair,
or their blanket slides off. What if they catch a cold like this?
I know it's not a normal time right now.
People can't waste their time on commuting in the Capital City,
but it can't continue like this either.
Do you have any suggestion?
I think we can get some blankets and mats
for everyone to rest with.
After all, sleep is very important.
I was lacking in my planning.
You take responsibility for this then.
No problem. I can only do these small tasks anyway.
Your food delivery app is not bad.
It saved a lot of energy and time for everyone.
That's easy.
So... the money?
Why did you give me your wallet?
You take care of all of these.
Go now.
This is great. There's a bed to sleep on.
It's so soft.  I don't need to worry about my stiff butt anymore.
It's really different having a girl around.
In here, there's food, drink, and sleep.
There are even companions.
I don't even want to go back to my kennel anymore.
Third Sister-in-Law, you are like the Snail Girl in the legend.
Yugong, your mattress is in Master's office.
There's even a plan for this?
Of course. For you, Houzi, Ah Shuang and Ali,
your mattresses are in Master's office.
There are a few people and a lot of space.  It's the VIP treatment.
Junior Sister Weiwei,  you are amazing.
Based on my observation, she segregated based on who snores.
I'm doing this for your own good.
It's discrimination!
You are very detailed and thoughtful of everything.
I will be able to sleep peacefully then.
Where's my bed?
Over there.
Junior Sister, you actually gave him the worst spot.
I assigned your sleeping spots by drawing.
It's the same. I rarely sleep.
It's better for me to sleep there.
Thank you, Junior Sister.
No problem, no problem. I can't help you guys in any other ways.
My school starts on September 1st, I can battle with you guys until then.
If you need any help, just look for me.
Okay.
Junior Sister,
when the school term starts again, I think you can continue as our intern.
You can study and learn at the same time, and earn some pocket money, too.
I don't need a salary as long as there's food.
Then put your salary on my account.
Third Brother, you are ruthless.
Thank you.
- Cousin.
- What's wrong?
Everyone in the company is saying that our Manager Zhen
suddenly becomes this industrious and hardworking businessman.
Hence, I came to take a look.
I didn't expect it to be true.
Cousin, what happened to you?
What do you mean?
It's normal for men to strive for their career.
Cousin, if you really think this way,
Uncle must be extremely happy.
Frankly, I'm working hard because I want to defeat Xiao Nai fair and square.
That's why I'm going all in.
However, I later realized that designing games is so much more interesting than I originally thought.
I guess I found something I like to do with a stroke of luck.
Defeat Xiao Nai?
What does this have to do with Xiao Nai?
You are in the same school as Xiao Nai, so you probably know his girlfriend.
Do you mean Bei Weiwei?
Bei Weiwei? Isn't her last name Lu?
If you are talking about Xiao Nai's girlfriend, then it is Bei Weiwei.
Do you know her?
Great! I got tricked again.
Cousin,
do you know Bei Weiwei?
Why did she say her last name was Lu?
Did she tell you herself that her last name was Lu?
I know a lot of women. She's not the only one.
You should also know that women are eccentric.
It's normal that they like to play games with men.
Okay. I need to work now.
Feng Teng Technology is strange, too. Why did they suddenly bring forward the date by more than two weeks?
So busy.
Why does my cousin want to defeat Xiao Nai?
Did you say that Brother Shaoxiang knows Bei Weiwei?
And Bei Weiwei told Shaoxiang that her last name was Lu?
How dare she even try to get Brother Shaoxiang with her claws?
She's too shameless.
Did Brother Shaoxiang break up with his girlfriend because of her?
I don't know.
I think that is probably the case.
Bei Weiwei lied to Brother Shaoxiang that her family name was Lu.
She must be trying to hide her identity,
to hide from others that she's two-timing.
A girl who could even think of this method
is way too scheming.
On one hand, Bei Weiwei grabs onto Xiao Nai.
At the same time, she deceived Cao Guang in the game.
She's reaching for Brother Shaoxiang now.
She is just simply a super manipulative woman!
But didn't Cao Guang say that he mistook her for someone else?
Can you even believe this?
Isn't this too coincidental?
Cao Guang must have been fooled by Bei Weiwei
into deceiving us.
Initially, I believed Cao Guang,
but now, Cousin...
Forget it. I'm so confused now.
I can't be bothered with them. They can trick whoever they want.
Men are fools.
They were all toyed around by someone and even wrongly accused the innocent.
By the way, I know something else.
What?
A few days ago, at the entrance of the company,
I saw Cao Guang come to visit Zhao Erxi.
They were arguing there at the company entrance.
In the end, Zhao Erxi ran back to the office while crying.
For the past few days, when I saw Zhao Erxi in the office,
she seems to be a bit distracted.
Could it be...
Zhao Erxi likes Cao Guang
and Cao Guang likes Bei Weiwei?
Why is it so messy?
I must get to the bottom of this.
Cao Guang threatened us to keep quiet.
But if this comes out of Zhao Erxi's mouth,
he can't blame us, right?
- Bye-bye.
I'm leaving.
Let's leave now.
Let's go.
Erxi, we are from the same school.
We've also been interning at the same company for so long.  We ought to get to know each other.
These are the macaroons Yiran gave me.  I'll give you a box.
Thanks, but I'm on a diet. I can't eat sweets.
Erxi, I heard you had an argument with Bei Weiwei because of Cao Guang.
How did you know?
Stop spouting nonsense. There's no such thing.
In this world, no secret can be kept forever.
Besides, the winner will flaunt her victory.
The winner will flaunt it?  What do you mean?
What do you think I mean?
Other than you, who else knows about this incident?
But don't be too sad.
You aren't the only one she treated this way.
Manager Zhen and his girlfriend
were getting along really well before,
but she got involved.
Frankly, she just can't leave any man alone.
Actually, before, I already had proof of Bei Weiwei's two-timing.
Cao Guang could be my witness.
Unfortunately, the evidence is gone.
That foolish Cao Guang was also deceived by her.
He said that it was a misunderstanding.
He wouldn't allow us to tell the truth about it.
Also, that Xiao Nai. He clearly saw the video and still didn't believe it.
I really don't know what kind of magic potion that Bei Weiwei gave them.
Cao Guang found you and you gave the video to Xiao Nai to see?
Yes.
Such malicious behavior, of course, has to be exposed.
Cao Guang came to find us because of Bei Weiwei.
He just wanted us to keep our mouths shut.
But he didn't mention you.
So you looked for me just to say this?
I didn't want to see you so ignorantly kept in the dark
and still regard her as your best friend.
Although the evidence is gone,
I thought I should still tell you about it.
It's late. I'm going back now.
Okay, Yiran and I will treat you to a meal next time.
That foolish Cao Guang was also deceived by her.
He said that it was a misunderstanding. He wouldn't allow us to tell the truth about it.
Also, that Xiao Nai. He clearly saw the video and still didn't believe it.
Such malicious behavior, of course, has to be exposed.
Originally, there were so many unfounded conjectures and attacks
centered around Weiwei.
But she never complained about it at all.
She even helped me vent my anger.
Had it been me, I would have broken down.
Frankly, regarding Cao Guang, Weiwei didn't do anything wrong either.
I said I didn't blame her,
but in my heart, I still blamed her for everything.
Zhao Erxi, how could you still be angry at such a good friend and role model?
My brain must have short-circuited.
Erxi, I'm really sorry.
Just forgive me on account of Coffee.
Hello, Zhao Erxi.
You finally returned my call.
Cao Guang, you keep apologizing to me,
but have you apologized to Weiwei?
I always thought I was really being wronged.
But just now, I suddenly realized,
I wasn't the only one who was wronged.
Because of us, Weiwei
was accused of cheating,
but she never complained while letting me take my anger out on her and your accusation.
It's okay for others to talk behind her back.
However, the most laughable thing is that I have always thought of myself as her good friend,
but I have never considered her feelings.
Cao Guang, you should apologize to Weiwei.
She doesn't need my apology.
I dare not apologize to her, either.
You really do like Weiwei.
Cao Guang, you must remember,
the person that I like
is Wei Guang who thought I was the one he liked.
It's not Cao Guang.
I have never liked you. Understand?
In the future, when we bump into each other at school,
just take it that we don't know each other.
Cao Guang, I forgive you.
Goodbye, Wei Guang.
♫ I want to meet someone with a sincere heart ♫
♫ I'd like to see my heart never stop fluttering. I'd like to know ♫
♫ I am no longer an empty shell and let myself ♫
♫ be cherished and indulged ♫
Brother Mei, take this one and redo it.
Bros, you all must be tired. Here, this will refresh you.
Hello? Weiwei, are you busy right now?
This is Xiao Nai. Weiwei is sleeping.
Huh? Sleeping?
With you?
No, no. What I meant is...
We're at the office. She got tired from working overtime and fell asleep.
She will return your call when she's awake.
Okay, don't wake her up.
She will be very happy with your call.
Erxi called me?!
How did she sound?
I just hear the feeling of crisis that my girlfriend will leave my house.
Bike keys.
In the drawer, get them yourself.
You can take half of the day off.
Thanks, Boss! Also, I already ordered dinner.
You guys won't be hungry. Thanks for your blanket!
It's a robbery!
Master Er, I only have one cake.
Can I pay my toll with this?
I guess it will have to work. It's too small though.
It's not enough for me to eat in one bite.
Does it taste good?
It's really good.
For the past few days, I really felt that I was rather foolish.
Weiwei, do you know that I am truly regretful now?
From my understanding of you, you are regretting
about the cake that you throw out a few days ago.
How are you able to guess that?
So annoying!
Weiwei, don't tell Xiao Ling and Si Si about this.
Or I won't be your friend anymore.
I lost face, too.  Do you know? I don't want to talk about it either.
That's more like it.
A dark part of my past.
If the campus beauty's sidekick hadn't come and made mischief,
I don't know when I would have understood what was happening.
You have to forgive me. I have never dated before,
so I can easily get tricked.
About this, no matter what, it's still because of me–
It has nothing to do with you.
It's all Cao Guang's fault for being so dumb.
Just now, before you got here,
I sat here by myself and thought for a long time.
I was thinking
I'm probably a bit envious of you.
It wasn't easy for me to like someone,
but that person likes you.
But it's okay. Everything is clear to me now.
I don't want anyone who doesn't like me back!
I'm going to turn to a new page.
I'm going to look for a handsome guy who doesn't judge people by their appearance.
"Someone who doesn't judge people by their appearance," but why are you looking for a handsome guy?
Can't you just encourage me?
I haven't even interrogated you yet.
Did you really move to Master's home?
Have a few things happened that should have happened?
What if you lose your virginity to him? It'll be all because of me!
Master is a gentleman, okay?
I don't believe it.
For a guy who can steal the department beauty in three minutes,
how much of a gentleman can he be?
Tell the truth.  Have you guys kissed or not?
Why are you so close to me?
Tell me.
In any case, after I moved in with him, we haven't.
So, in the past, you have.
Why haven't after you moved in with him?
Could it be Master is afraid of starting something accidentally?
Why did you take away my cake?
I think you can use your imagination to get stuffed.
You can't have it!
Ah!
Come here. Look at you.
Weiwei, when you weren't around,
I totally messed up Xiao Ling's place.
You have to hurry and move back. It isn't good for you to live in Master's house.
You're right. I'll go and tell him.
Eat your cake.
Here.
I don't want it. I'm ignoring you.
If we go along this line of thinking, with all the battles in fog,
all the models of low color saturation under the default settings
can use the primary vector analysis to reduce the number of vertices.
Their movement data can be simplified into a limited set.
In the end, we can merge these player models with the dynamic graphics
and display them at once.
This can reduce more than a thousand requests for drawing.
The efficiency of memory usage and display can both be enhanced.
It's not an issue to merge the models with the graphics,
but about the primary vector analysis...
Can you handle the advanced mathematics?
I taught myself.
Excellent. There definitely won't be any problems.
I'm making a call.
Are you moving back?
Yes. I can't keep staying at your place.
What do you think my place is?
You can just come and go as you wish?
Move back when school starts.
Who's that? Who's going to move back when school starts?
You don't know this person.
So how?
Erxi, I suddenly thought of something.
Lately, Master hasn't been living in his apartment
but there are many valuable paintings in the house.
So, I have to keep an eye on them.
Just move those paintings to Xiao Ling's home.
What was Na Na's motive to tell you all those things?
Who knows what those crooked people were thinking about?
She certainly had ill intentions towards you.
I originally thought to just ignore them.
But it's annoying that they keep bothering me.
They even invited me to a meal.
Then I'll see what they have in mind.
Invited you to a meal?
Do you mean it?
Really. I got that when I asked her directly.
When she's here, let's console her.
Zhao Erxi will certainly give us the whole story.
Bei Weiwei, you just wait!
Welcome.
Erxi, over here!
Erxi, this is Yiran. You know her, right?
Yiran, this is Erxi.
- Hello.
- I know her. She's the school beauty.
Erxi, we have already ordered. See if there's anything you like.
Thanks.
Waitress.
Give me a French crepe,
a mango pomelo sago,
and two mango pancakes.
I'll also have one of the Cantonese egg noodles.
I didn't have lunch.
Did I order too much?
Not at all. We're all good friends. Don't be uncomfortable.
Okay then! Then, I'll also get a blueberry cake, a fruit platter.
And, do you have juice? Then, a glass of juice.
I'm done. Thank you.
Please wait.
Enjoy!
Why aren't you eating? Let's eat together.
I'm really envious of you. Your appetite is so good.
I'm using my heartbreak as motivation.
Yiran, you should know it better than I do.
You... really are heartbroken?
Is it because...
It's all because of that Wei–
However, I'm no match for her. What can I do?
You are such an innocent girl. How can you be her match?
The most detestable thing is that the boys actually help her
and prevent us from telling anyone the situation.
However, forget about us.  Our credibility is minimal,
but it's different for you.
If you said it, the credibility would be much higher.
Are you saying that I should bad-mouth her?
It's not that. This is not what we meant. We merely feel that,
it's extremely unfair for the evil people to be so full of themselves.
For this, it should be discussed at length.
Wait as I think while eating.
Erxi!
Yang Yang "Just One Smile Is Very Alluring"
♫ Rain drips on my jacket ♫
♫ Longing (for you) soaks the corners of my clothes ♫
♫ The signal you gave me, a smile ♫
♫ Came at just the right time ♫
♫ Are like grass blown by the spring wind ♫
♫ Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to ♫
♫ Chase away all the troubles ♫
♫ I want to take you to the ends of the earth ♫
♫ I want to listen to your heartbeat ♫
♫ I want to give you a hug ♫
♫ And make the whole world know ♫
♫ Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me ♫
♫ No one else can feel your sweetest smile ♫
♫ I don’t need to look for anyone else ♫
♫ Because I’ve already found (you) ♫
♫ Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us ♫
♫ Only we know how beautiful our love is ♫
♫ I want to be around you every minute and every second ♫
♫ You are so important to me ♫
♫ As I pass by you, the tips of your hair ♫
♫ Are like grass blown by the spring wind ♫
♫ Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to ♫
♫ Chase away all the troubles ♫
♫ I want to take you to the ends of the earth ♫
♫ I want to listen to your heartbeat ♫
♫ I want to give you a hug ♫
♫ And make the whole world know ♫
♫ Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me ♫
♫ No one else can feel your sweetest smile ♫
♫ I don’t need to look for anyone else ♫
♫ Because I’ve already found (you) ♫
♫ Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us ♫
♫ Only we know how beautiful our love is ♫
♫ I want to be around you every minute and every second ♫
♫ You are so important to me ♫