Silence Wang - "An Alluring Smile"
♫ I always casually tell you my wishes ♫
♫ And give you looks that a thousand words wouldn’t be able to describe ♫
♫ In this world, there will always be people who are busy looking for treasure ♫
♫ But they mistake the blazing sun for it ♫
♫ And miss out on the manifestations of life ♫
♫ On the long bridge of this ancient city ♫
♫ There is a sea of people and cars going on their way ♫
♫ Your smile is like a ray of light ♫
♫ That suddenly lights me up ♫
♫ (Your smile is like a ray of light. That suddenly lights me up) ♫
♫ The wind blows gently; summer is not yet over ♫
♫ Bikes ring on the greenway ♫
♫ So this is what love looks like ♫
♫ Just admit that you were allured by my smile and couldn’t forget me after you first saw me ♫
♫ Saying that love is deep like the sea… you flatter me ♫
♫ The most romantic thing is to just watch the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder ♫
♫ That’s the direction my heart goes in ♫
♫ (Watching the sunset with you shoulder to shoulder. That’s the direction my heart goes in) ♫
♫ I want to travel to all four corners   with you to enjoy the views in all kinds of weather ♫
♫ I want to write the remaining chapters of life with you ♫
♫ Sharing the laughs and tears with you freely no matter the circumstances ♫
♫ Our story won’t end ♫
What are you doing later?
I'm going to Zhen Yi Technology to get my internship pay. Who's coming with me?
- I've got plans with my Da Zhong.
- Uh,
I'm at that time of the month.
There's no love for your classmate!
Even if I had any, I wouldn't give any to you.
I'll be going first.
- Bye-bye.
Weiwei.
Okay. In any case, I don't have anything to do.
Yeah!
- Let's go!
- Wait for me for a second. I need to answer a call of nature.
Very fast.
Quickly.
Classmate Erxi!
Didn't I tell you to pretend that we were strangers? Don't you understand Chinese?
Wait a second!
Then, this classmate whom I don't know,
you should look up, because...
Ah!
Bei Weiwei.
I'm going to study abroad soon.
I'm here to do the paperwork today.
Congratulations.
I...
I'm very sorry...
for the troubles I caused you and Xiao Nai
with my immature behavior.
It's fine.  Actually, it's all right.
Wei–
Weiwei, I envy you.
Not just for your relationship with Xiao Nai,
but even more
for having true friends who treat you with sincerity.
Between friends, sincerity is the most precious.
If you really are sincere to others, the other party will definitely feel it
and treat you the same way.
I believe
you will also find your own true friends.
It's too late for me to recognize that,
but I think I still have opportunities.
Bei Weiwei, thank you.
I hope everything goes well for you.
Wish you all the best, too.
Bye-bye.
Weiwei! What did the campus beauty queen say to you?
Why do I feel that she is a little prettier than usual?
Nothing. She just told me she's going to study abroad in the next term.
Also, she is really envious of me for having a bad friend like you.
Who's a bad friend? I'm clearly the national best girlfriend.
Enough, already!
Weiwei, since she's gone, aren't you now promoted as the school beauty queen?
About that,
write an anonymous post to the forum,
saying that a married woman...
- What?
No, girls with boyfriends can't compete as the campus beauty queen. How's that?
Just forget it. Miss Married,
you are guaranteed to be the beauty queen.
Go ahead. I'll wait for you here.
Come in with me. Wait in the lobby. No one will notice.
I'll wait here.
Let's go. It's fine.
Sit here, I'll go up to get my salary.
If they dock my pay, you must fight your way up there once I call you, understand?
Got it.
This person seems familiar.
So he's from Zhen Yi Technology?
I got it! I got it! Let me pay you back.
Let's spend the rest on a feast!
This person... do you know who this is?
This is Director Li, the head of game development.
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
To ensure fairness, we must use the external server
provided by Feng Teng, under the conditions of the real network environment.
The rest is the same as our test in the office.  So don't be nervous.
But I'm still nervous, Third Brother.
Are you sure I should go up with you first?
You can't let me be the first to suffer a casualty because I am handsome.
Heck!  In terms of handsomeness, I am certainly number one.
Third Brother only brings you to serve as the contrast and to best show off how great he looks.
Very good. You still have the energy to joke around.
This means you're not too nervous.
We're still a little nervous,
but not as much as Ah Shuang who can't come due to diarrhea caused by anxiety.
Ah Shuang flaked out at this critical moment.
The number you dialed cannot be reached at the moment.
Why is his phone off?
- May I ask if you are the team from Zhi Yi?
- Yes.
Okay. Please follow me.
So President Xiao is here.
- Director Wang.
- Welcome, welcome.
Director He, sorry to keep you waiting.
No, not at all. We just got here, too.
Is this the team from  Zhi Yi?
Fresh college graduates, very young indeed.
That's right.
- Director Li.
- Welcome.
Director Wang,  Director He.
This is...?
We at Zhen Yi are led by the son of President Zhen.  This is Director Zhen.
- Director Wang.
- Welcome.
- Director He.
Welcome.
My goodness, it's true that every generation has its heroes.
Seeing such young teams is making me feel my age (old).
Since everyone is here, let's move inside.
Why are all their phones turned off?
Just what's going on?
Do you remember when we had a meal with Meng Yiran?
I bumped into someone familiar. He's of one Xiao Nai's staff.
I saw him with Director Li of Zhen Yi.
Isn't it strange for both of them to get together?
Erxi, do you think this will be harmful to Xiao Nai?
It shouldn't. Perhaps, it was merely a case of a casual meal because they know each other.
I don't think it's that simple. I still have to call to find out.
The number you are calling has been switched off.
Why is it still turned off?
Weiwei, don't panic yet. He must have turned off his phone as a requirement before the demo. That's why you can't get through.
Let's go home first.
Director Wang.
Since this is not a public presentation. I ask everyone to feel at ease.
Just relax. Once President Feng is here, we will start.
- All right.
President Feng is here.
President Feng.
Please sit.
President Feng, this is the team from Zhi Yi Technology and the other team is from Zhen Yi Technology.
They will be presenting separately their demos later.
President Feng's flight is at 1:00 p.m.; hence, time is rather tight.
Every team only has thirty minutes.
Okay, let's get started.
Director He and I have discussed in advance. We will go in alphabetical order. Hence, Zhen Yi goes first.
Okay. Thank you, Director Wang.
It's my honor to represent Zhen Yi Technology today
to present the product of our research.
Besides being the project manager for Zhen Yi,
I'm also a veteran player of "A Chinese Ghost Story."
At Zhen Yi, all of our design effort for "A New Chinese Ghost Story"
insists on placing the players' need as our top priority.
For a player to be attracted to a game,
it's not just because of repetitive battles and limitless level advancement.
More importantly is the interaction with other players
and their relationships. So, on top of the original game structure,
we've added even more interactive systems.
We will introduce to everyone a more complex and  interesting romantic relationship system,
family system, alliance system, and large missions that can scale up to hundreds of players, etc.
President Feng, let's look at our demo.
My presentation ends here. Thank you, everyone.
Not bad.
The online gaming technology has reached its peak at this stage.
Some minor breakthroughs cannot provide the players with new excitement.
To introduce innovation in the area of playing approach, I think Zhen Yi has done very well.
Zhen Yi's product is definitely very interesting.
Then next, it's Zhi Yi's team.
Hello, everyone. I'm Xiao Nai.
Next, my team and I will present
our design concept for "A New Chinese Ghost Story."
Your demo is so small. Did you have to rush it out?
I heard you don't have a lot of programmers.
We have eight.
Although they are all top students,
but with such a development resource, it's really...
Even though Zhi Yi doesn't have a lot of staff members,
but each and every one of them has the ability to lead in his specialty.
Also, the members know each other well and have a strong teamwork.
Moreover, a small client app
is not equal to the poor quality of the game.
On the contrary, it makes it easier for the player to download.
I hope I can demonstrate this point to Director He.
You can start.
Director Li, everything is going smoothly.
Feng Teng provided us with a server of the same configuration.
Zhen Yi had no problems with the connection. Why is there a problem with Zhi Yi?
Could it be that there's a flaw of the game itself?
This is not right. I can't even connect through the physical link.
Physical link?
Where did it go wrong?
Could there be a problem with our server?
What's going on?
- Check with IT now.
- Yes, Director Wang.
President Feng, Director Wang,  IT has checked.
They said that the server we allocated to Zhi Yi is experiencing issues.
They are not sure what caused the server to have this abnormal shutdown.
It might take them half an hour to restart it.
Half an hour? But President Feng needs to rush to the airport in forty-five minutes.
We can't delay President Feng's flight. We either decide now or change to a different time.
It's not practical to change the time. We need to check Director He's schedule.
Director He will be in the States for three months. This can't wait.
Why don't we decide now?
I think that Zhen Yi's product has done a fairly good job.
Zhen Yi's ideas are really creative.  Zhi Yi's may not be as good as Zhen Yi's.
- Moreover, it's important for the collaboration to run smoothly. It didn't go smoothly from the start.
- That's right.
Connect it to the mirror server.
- You have a backup server?
- You are using your own server,
but the configuration of your server is different from what's provided by Feng Teng.
This is not fair to Zhen Yi.
Prior to the presentation, we prepared a backup on a server
of the same configuration.
The reason is to mitigate the potential risk.
President Feng, this is the login credentials for the remote server.
The IT staff at Feng Teng can log in anytime
and check all the configurations of the server.
Online games are a commercial product.
Every second of its operation will affect the reputation and revenues of the company.
That's why stability is crucial.
Recently, we had many mishaps on the internet.
In order to prevent the negative impact of this risk,
Zhi Yi, when designing our server architecture,
took into account the real-time failover at the alternate site.
Under this infrastructure, in case of a catastrophic event,
another mirrored server will be activated immediately to allow the players to continue.
This will allow the game to continue its normal operation to the largest degree
and to the extent possible, to minimize the occurrence of accidents.
This is always a goal we at Zhi Yi pursue.
It's also our promise for our joint operation in the future
to Feng Teng.
They are a such young team yet so detailed and reliable with their work.
Really beyond my expectations.
They came prepared.
Director Wang, I don't believe in coincidence.
I understand.  I've already asked someone to investigate this.
Next, I would like to ask our team member
to share the special features of "A New Chinese Ghost Story" with everyone.
We've redesigned our game engine
from using a single threaded logic to multi-threaded.
The biggest limiting factors are the calculation capabilities of the CPU and graphics processor.
President Feng,  changing a single threaded to multi-threaded means–
I know. No need to explain it to me.
Between the individual computer game and the online game,
the biggest difference is in
the interaction between NPCs and the players.
If the NPCs roles are very rigid, then the players will naturally lose interest.
As a result, for our NPCs, we have specifically
created complex behavior trees.
We've done all we can to make them more intelligent.
Both parties can have livelier interactions.
Interesting, right?
The weather in our game will simulate the actual weather to the maximum extent possible.
There will be four seasons: spring, summer, autumn, and winter; as well as days and nights.
There's warm and sunny weather. And, of course, there's also an extended rainy season.
Our main objective is to allow the players to feel the joy of the changes of weather
without even stepping out of the house. Thank you.
With such complex graphics changes,
it must place a high demand on computer hardware.
However, if playing games require upgrading their computers,
could it become, to our players,
inconvenient and difficult to play?
Director He's question is the key point of what we want to present next.
Without lowering the quality of the game, yet reducing the requirements of the computer,
it has always been the objective of our effort in optimization.
Next, we will use the large-scale, "He Bo Flood Quest"
(Note: He Bo is the river god of the Yellow River)
as an example.
In the game, since there is extensive rain,
they will naturally cause floods to occur.
The "He Bo Flood," a full-server disaster relief quest that we've set up.
Within the time limit, players, not only have to
escort NPCs to safe areas,
they, also, have to address post-disaster reconstruction and drought relief as part of the content.
This features a dynamic mission chain to ensure that the players
will not develop the dislike or boredom toward the quest.
Next, we will simulate the scenario when thousands of player start the mission
to really test how the server performs under pressure.
Wow, that's amazing.
President Feng, I feel that this...
Okay, I know you understand. I won't explain then.
10,000 people were playing simultaneously online yet it runs so smoothly.
This is so difficult.  Not just for "A New Chinese Ghost Story,"
if we integrate this technology into other games as well,
then our revenue will really be...
Above are some of the new concepts and designs for "A New Chinese Ghost Story."
Before I conclude our presentation,
we would like to share with everyone the ideals of Zhi Yi Technology:
Insistence on original innovation and proliferation of our culture.
From the day we chose to start up our own business and established this gaming company,
the majority of the people had doubts about us
because we were young and inexperienced.
Also, many people view gaming as something people do without a constructive purpose.
But in my eyes, a game is the same as a book, a movie
or a museum.
It's not only just entertainment,
it's also a carrier that is a medium to spread our culture.
They are all an avenue to expose people to our culture,
fostering their understanding naturally.
While playing the game, players can come into contact
and experience all the nuances of Chinese culture.
Hence, the goal of Zhi Yi is not only just to produce popular games,
but we also hope that through the world we construct
is to help make more people understand Chinese culture.
So that is the reason why we always insist on creating our own engine.
Only by having our own engine can we create
completely different from other cultures,  and a world that belongs solely to the Chinese culture.
We want to build a world
that originally only existed in literature and imagination.
Of course, we wouldn't impose our ideas and opinions on the players,
but instead, present and enrich them through all the details of the game.
This is what constitutes the entire structure of our game
and our worldview.
Feng Teng is also devoted to spreading traditional culture.
Zhi Yi's thoughts on this
happen to match ours.
Thank you, President Feng. This concludes our presentation.
Thank you, everyone.
Of course, Zhi Yi Technology's ideas are pretty good,
but I personally believe marketability is still the first priority.
When compared to the interactive system's playability and continuity that Zhi Yi emphasizes,
it's a little better.
My view is different from Director He.
"A New Chinese Ghost Story" isn't just a simple continuation of "A Chinese Ghost Story."
If there aren't any marked differences, there's no need to launch a new product.
The superiority of the engine that Zhi Yi Technology developed is obvious.
We can apply it to our future games.
President Feng, it's almost time.
My gratitude to both young teams
for showing us the result of your own development effort.
Everyone, please wait in the waiting area outside the conference room.
We will announce our decision in a short while after our internal discussions.
Uncle Li, your pacing is very annoying.
The situation is not beneficial to us now.  My heart is...
It's already done. We have tried our best.
If we lose, it means we were not good enough.
Did you discuss this in advance? Why didn't I know about the backup server?
Of course, you wouldn't know.
Before we came, Third Brother told me to take precautions.
I really didn't expect a problem would really crop up.
At that time, I panicked and almost forgot about our backup.
But talking about this, it's strange, too. Why is there a sudden problem with their server?
I'm flying to New York now.
Let's talk about our contract when I'm back.
I will be available at your convenience, President Feng.
Thank you for your support of Feng Teng.
I could feel your sincerity.
I hope we will have the opportunity to collaborate in the future.
Thank you, President Feng.
Director He, escort me downstairs.
Sorry about our embarrassing incident.
Although I don't want to admit it, you won this time.
I admit my defeat without complaint.
Let's go.
- Yeah!
Don't act so depressed.
Although we lost, we must lose with grace.
Zhi Yi was better than us with their design and technology.
I fully accept their win.
However, you should not be discouraged, either.
Although we lost this,  if we learn from our experience this time,
we can come fully prepared next time.
We will definitely create an even better game and defeat Zhi Yi.
You have been working overtime. It has been tough. Go home and get some rest.
Sorry, manager.
It wasn't your responsibility. Don't blame yourself.
I am the one in charge of the project. Hence, it's my responsibility.
If Feng Teng didn't bring forward the presentation date,
I believe we could have done even better.
Take three days of leave with pay and then come back to work.
Where is Director Li?
Wasn't he behind us just now?
Fine. I'm going to find him for some other matters. Go back to the hotel first.
Yes, Manager.
President Zhen, sorry.
We didn't get the project.
I didn't expect this either.  I though we would definitely win.
didn't expect Xiao Nai to be so formidable. He even prepared a mirror server.
I think Director He was exposed as well.
Yes, I understand.
I will console Young Master.
All right. I will hang up now, President Zhen.
I wonder how they are doing.
You are back.
I'm here to buy you a midnight snack.
We won.
That's so great!
Here!
Comrades, we got the project.
Isn't that great?  Isn't it?
Good job! It was so easy, without any doubt.
So easy!
Thank you for your effort during this period. You worked hard.
Here's a toast to everyone.
Come! Let's drink.
I thought you would celebrate in Shanghai.
Why did you come back?
Isn't it because we missed you?
Anyway, we can have a feast in Shanghai when we are there to discuss the contract.
Okay?
Eat more tonight. Anyway, someone's picking up the tab.
- No one is allowed to leave until you get drunk.
- Yes!
Let me tell you.
I didn't eat anything on the plane just to save my stomach for this feast. I'm so starved.
Order more. We must not make it easy for Third Brother today.
- There are still lots of food here.
- Are you stupid?
It's so rare that we get to extort a meal out of Third Brother today.
Furthermore, I'm the core force of this team.
I must eat more to replenish my brain cells I lost during this period.
Order and eat more.
Okay, gorgeous. We are adding orders.
Expensive restaurants usually have lukewarm services.
Eat more. Someone is treating.
Everyone, do you have any suggestions? If not, I'll take care of it.
Sure.
Two dozen raw oysters, two dozen scallops,
two dozen clams,
and... two servings of river snails.
Hey, does anyone want some beer?
Make it red wine. Beer doesn't mix with seafood.
Fine, red wine then. Make it quick.
Third Brother, let me give you a toast
for treating everyone to the feast today.
Isn't Hao Mei the one paying today?
Huh...
Why is it me?
I remember that before the meeting that day, we were all discussing
about where Hao Mei would take us for seafood.
The reason is... two houses.
Right, right, right. I almost forgot.
Brother Mei, don't be a person who goes back on his promises.
- This meal is on you.
- That's right. A man must keep his words.
Right? Right!
Help. Can I cancel my order?
Brother Mei, be more generous.
That's right. Don't be so petty.
Then you guys would let Third Brother get away this easily?
Next weekend, I will take everyone on a trip.
Woah!
So Brother Xiao is the generous one.
I love you!
Brother Mei, what else do you have to say?
I'll check my bank account...
Third Brother, you are too evil.
You are too kind.  I am at most a dust storm
Here, here, eat some crab.
No one will dare offend you again.
Too late. You just offended me.
I didn't think I would be paying for this.
This is all my money;
the money I've earned with my blood and sweat!
Are your blood and sweat worth this much?
Your blood and sweat.
Brother Mei, shouldn't you be telling us about your houses now?
- Huh?
- That's right.
Didn't my parents come last month?
I didn't want to return to my old village to work.
My parents bought it for my future wife.
Then, why did they buy two?
Could it be...
- Do you want to marry and have two wives?
- Third Brother, you–
Dust storms don't happen only once.
Have this.
We don't even have a girlfriend,
and he's going to marry two?
That's right!
W-W-Wait a minute. I almost forgot.
M-My house still has some room.
You can stay there if you want. I won't collect rent.
Me!
But... uh, the room's very small.
Only one person can live there. You all...
Brother, we've lived together for four years.
- It's enough.
- You wouldn't abandon me, w-would you?
I even have showered with Brother Mei before.
Can you match that?
Yugong, you better think carefully.
If you bring your girlfriend there in the future,
- wouldn't Brother Mei steal her?
- That's right.
I will take my girlfriend and go to take refuge with Brother Mei.
Your feet stink. Brother Mei won't be able to take it.
- I will go.
- His feet stink more than mine. He doesn't even wash his socks.
W-W-Wait a minute. We're all brothers here.
No matter who stays, my conscience won't rest easy.
How about this? You guys discuss a bit and tell me the results.
Just like that, okay?
Come. Let's drink.
Here. Have another one.
Why is Senior Ah Shuang not here?
He resigned.
So did he really betray everyone?
How did you know?
When I was meeting Erxi, I saw Ah Shuang with another stranger.
When I went with Erxi to pick up her pay today,
I found out that the person was in charge of the game development at Zhen Yi,
so I called you because I thought there was something suspicious,
but your phone was turned off.
It's not convenient during a demo meeting.
But why did Ah Shuang do that?
Come. Let me give you a toast.
Come. Another one.
Third Brother, I'm here to see you regarding some matters.
I want to know the reason.
So you know it all already.
I have a childhood friend,
who developed a small game,
but his girlfriend
betrayed him and sold it to Zhen Yi.
In a burst of anger, my childhood friend
still released the game.
He was subsequently sued by Zhen Yi for stealing trade secrets.
Zhen Yi found me because of this.
This friend is really important to me, so I had to betray Zhi Yi,
but I only told them about our progress on the game, nothing else, so can you–
Boss, I'm sorry.
So that's what happened.
Then, do Yugong and the others know about this?
They don't need to know.
You've worked hard.
Raw oysters?
What's wrong?
Nothing,
Grow up soon, my wife.
Since everyone's done eating, let's go singing next.
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Let's go to sing!
Coming!
I'm going first!
- Who's going first?
- I'm going first!
Let's go. I'll take you home.
-Then they–
There's no problem, I already called taxis for them.
Come on. Let's pay the check.
I thought Brother Mei was picking up the tab.
I just pulled a prank. Let him have some fun.
Let's go.
You guys have fun, we're going to leave first.
- Are you leaving?
- Yeah!
- We're leaving.
- Goodbye!
Okay, let's party.
Come on, let's party!
It's already 3:30 p.m.?
So late.
Who is it?
Coming!
Coming, coming.
Who is it?
K.O.? Why are you here?
Come to get a favor.
Yang Yang -  "Just One Smile Is Very Alluring"
♫  Rain drips on my jacket  ♫
♫  Longing (for you) soaks the corners of my clothes  ♫
♫  The signal you gave me, a smile  ♫
♫  Came at just the right time  ♫
♫  As I pass by you, the tips of your hair  ♫
♫  Are like grass blown by the spring wind  ♫
♫  Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to  ♫
♫  Chase away all the troubles  ♫
♫  I want to take you to the ends of the earth  ♫
♫  I want to listen to your heartbeat  ♫
♫  I want to give you a hug  ♫
♫  And make the whole world know  ♫
♫  Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me  ♫
♫  No one else can feel your sweetest smile  ♫
♫  I don’t need to look for anyone else  ♫
♫  Because I’ve already found (you)  ♫
♫  Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us  ♫
♫  Only we know how beautiful our love is  ♫
♫  I want to be around you every minute and every second  ♫
♫  You are so important to me  ♫
♫  As I pass by you, the tips of your hair  ♫
♫  Are like grass blown by the spring wind  ♫
♫  Romance is fermenting. For you, I’m willing to  ♫
♫  Chase away all the troubles  ♫
♫  I want to take you to the ends of the earth  ♫
♫  I want to listen to your heartbeat  ♫
♫  I want to give you a hug  ♫
♫  And make the whole world know  ♫
♫  Only after meeting you did I realize how important you are to me  ♫
♫  No one else can feel your sweetest smile  ♫
♫  I don’t need to look for anyone else  ♫
♫  Because I’ve already found (you)  ♫
♫  Our fate just happens to not let anyone else disturb us  ♫
♫  Only we know how beautiful our love is  ♫
♫  I want to be around you every minute and every second  ♫
♫  You are so important to me  ♫