Do you believe in parallel worlds?
I’ve finally found you, Phu.
If he doesn’t know me
in this world, I’ll start over.
I love you, Phu.
From now on, I’ll be the one
to play the flute for you.
Are we officially a couple now?
If this doesn’t make us
official, I’ll be mad.
Who are you?
The one who’s been with you for four years
the one you said you wanted
to protect, isn’t this Phukan.
Please tell the person I love that
'I love you, P' Cir.'
I really love you.
Another fucking dream?
I keep having nonsense dreams these days.
Get well soon :)
Don’t!
Is he a cat or something?
What’s he hiding for?
Are you gonna come out?
Then I'll throw these away.
If you wanna see me,
come out and talk properly.
What a fucking annoying brat.
P’ Cir took the snacks today.
I’m so happy.
That alone makes my day.
Once we notice something…
I've reviewed the project you sent me.
Revise it based on my comments.
I think it's fine as it is, professor.
You haven't changed since your first year.
Listen to others for once, Rames.
Just revise it.
Ai Phu, you off in la-la land?
Achi, he’s noticed me.
And I got to talk to him too.
Phu, just because you hide in the corner
doesn't mean you talk to him.
And just because you walk him
to his car, his faculty, or his room
doesn't mean he knows you.
Yeah, just because he walks past you
doesn't mean he likes you.
But I really talked to him,
and he remembers my name too.
Man, this is bad.
Should we take him to the doctor?
Will the university infirmary treat him?
Phu, I know you've had
a secret crush on P' Cir for years.
You’ve like him since high school,
and you even followed him here.
But we've known you
for almost two years now.
You’re too shy to talk to him, make
eye contact, or even look at his face.
So when could you have talked to him?
In your dreams?
I'm not lying.
Sure, you're not lying at all.
I believe you. Really.
You don’t sound like you believe me.
I would've believed you
if it weren’t for that one brave
thing you did that we all saw.
Damn, I still remember it.
“The Legend of the Great Thief, Sisira.”
Whoo!
I’m not a thief.
But you stole something,
and it was university property.
COME JOIN US AT THE STUDENT UNION
Damn, that was fucking hilarious.
He ran like a dog.
I didn’t mean to steal.
Then return it.
How’s he gonna return it?
He’s probably kept it as
his family heirloom by now.
Hey, Ai Phu.
How could you like P' Cir?
I admit he’s handsome,
but he’s foul-mouthed as hell.
Everyone says he's handsome,
but only when he shuts up.
How could you like such a foul-mouthed guy?
So here’s the thing…
Back in high school, I dropped a paper cup,
and it fell to P' Cir’s classroom below.
So I went to retrieve it and overheard
him talking on the phone with his dad.
P' Cir wasn't foul-mouthed at all.
He was very serious and
gentle when he told his dad
he’d take care of both
his little brother and him.
His parents got divorced.
P' Cir lives with his mom,
and his brother with his dad.
Not only did he tell his dad
he’d take care of his brother and him
but he also said...
‘Dad, it's me, Cirrus.’
‘I can take care of myself, and
I’ll take care of you and Ozone too.’
‘Wait for me, Dad.’
He was so cool!
Like… super cool!
And when his friend, P' Wim, had a cast on
even though P’ Cir called him a burden,
he still helped him carry his stuff.
Seriously, how can he be so cute?
His voice is attractive too. I like it!
Oh guys! I gotta go.
P' Cir’s probably done with class.
I’ll go check if he’s really sick.
Later!
Bye-bye.
Phukan’s usually timid.
But why is he so talkative
when it comes to P’ Cir?
He’s gonna end up in the loony bin
with how head-over-heels he is.
Being head-over-heels is one thing.
But I doubt P' Cir has really noticed him.
The prof. let us out so late.
- True, I’m fucking starving.
- Yeah. He said he’d let us out on time.
Why save a spot when
there are tons of tables?
This is my favorite table.
Great spot, good lighting.
And most importantly, this is
where I look the most handsome.
- Handsome?
- Yeah.
Who says you’re handsome?
Fuck, you look like a foot with a face.
- Is being handsome gonna feed you?
- Well, no…
...no one asked for your opinion.
Just save your mouth for eating.
C’mon, I’m starving.
- What should we eat today?
- Let’s go to Auntie Daeng's place.
You’re Auntie Daeng's son or what?
From your fan again?
I really gotta hand it to them.
How do they put up with
your sharp-ass tongue?
Damn, they left a note this time.
“Enjoy the drink!”
Tell your fan to not
forget about your friend.
Gimme, I’ll drink it. I know you
don’t touch stuff people give—
Who the hell are you?!
You’re not my friend!
My friend doesn’t touch stuff
people give him. Who are you?
Today I feel like… having it.
You’re acting weird.
Or should I throw it away?
Or should I keep it?
Here, I’ll let you have it.
- Or not.
- You asshole!
Why are you so
indecisive over just a drink?
If my fish were here,
you know what it would say?
What?
Glub-glub, why the fluff
aren’t you drinking it?
Gimme if you’re not drinking it.
Fuck you, it’s mine.
I’m drinking it.
Bastard.
It’s for me, so I’m drinking it.
Hey, hey, hey, that’s mine.
Ai Jin, over here!
How’s P' Cir doing?
Is he fully recovered?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
I think he wanted to talk to you today.
No way. No.
Can’t do that.
Why?
Well... I’m too shy.
Are you gonna keep being like this, Ai Phu?
What do you mean by ‘keep being like this’?
You asked me to join the student
union to keep track of P’ Cir.
And now P’ Wim knows you like him.
When P' Wim offered
to help, you refused him.
You keep insisting that watching P' Cir
from a distance is enough for you.
Is it really enough, Phu?
I still remember when you
found out that P' Cir was sick.
You were losing it, like you were
about to get sick instead of him.
You know, if you wanna know
about him, just get close to him.
I... don’t have the guts.
I’m fine with just watching
him from a distance.
P’ Wim’s here.
Phu, I’ve got good news for you.
Good news… What good news?
Ai Cir asked me if I knew
someone named Phukan.
Huh? Me?!
Your years of effort are paying off now.
P’ Wim, what should I do?
Happy, aren’t you?
P’ Wim, this means I can’t
follow P’ Cir around anymore.
He must think I’m a stalker who
follows him like a creepy weirdo.
But I never took his
used coffee cups or straws—
Wait, wait, wait. Calm down.
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
Don’t you have something to tell him?
That’s right! Phu.
Yes?
You know our student union goes on
a volunteer camp this time of year, right?
I’ve heard about it.
Ai Cir has agreed to go this year.
You’re going too, right?
This is your chance, Ai Phu.
I’m going on a camp with P' Cir.
COME JOIN US AT THE STUDENT UNION
If I’d been bold enough
to talk to you that day
how would things be now?
You’d probably still not know me.
What if I told you…
that I liked you since high school?
Would you believe me?
I like you, P’ Cir.
I like you so much.
I like you so, so, so, so, so much.
Hey, don’t make that face.
I’ve never forced you to do anything.
Remember that goddamn poster?
C’mon, it’s just two favors.
What’s going on?
Asshole, am I that gross to you?
Were you talking about the poster?
Man, it’s still funny
when I think about it.
What were you thinking
putting a dog on a poster?
Was it worth getting
chewed out by him for two days?
Fuck, being a dog is better than
being a foot with a face like you.
- I’m a foot with a face?
- Yeah!
So tell me, where's the big toe at?
- Here.
- This is the big toe?
- That’s cubicle.
- Fuck you.
It’s called cuticle, idiot.
The fuck are you doing?
Did you just fart?
I didn’t fart, jackass.
Get on the bus now.
I’m a jackass?
If I’m a jackass, then
I guess you’re Moo Deng?
- Moo Deng my ass!
- Don’t touch me!
Don’t touch me!
Out of the way, out of the way.
- Dude, hold on! Let’s have a chat.
- You shitting me? Everyone’s on the bus.
Er… well…
You sit here, Phu.
You know, if you get on last,
you’ll stand out more.
Stand out my ass!
(Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin)
Hey, aren’t you sitting with me?
I’ll sit with P' Wim. I’ve got
something to discuss with him.
Then who am I gonna sit with?
You’ll have company soon enough.
The fuck’s wrong with you?
Quit jerking. You’ve got a seizure or what?
Can we get on now?
- Still at it?
- Okay, fine! Let’s get on.
It’s the only seat left.
Are you nuts?
I like sitting like this.
Please ignore me.
Besides, it’s cold.
It’s hot as hell. How can you be cold?
It’s cold. Please don’t mind me.
What if I do?
Why did you run away from me that day?
I didn’t run away.
But you ran like you’d seen a ghost.
If you wanna know if I’m better yet,
just ask. That’s what mouths are for.
I don’t like talking by myself.
You’re gonna die sitting like that.
Just ignore me. I’m a turtle.
Come out now. I’m gonna sleep.
"Baan Rai Por Piang Camping"
Alright, everyone!
Welcome to the Watershed Forest
Development Volunteer Camp of 2025!
I bet you’re all excited.
Hey! What are you waiting for? Applause.
That’s enough.
And Today, I’ve got good news for you.
Here we go again.
It’s always a disaster
when he announces good news.
Bastard, don’t interrupt. Listen first.
Alright, everyone.
You won’t have a place
to sleep tonight! Applause!
But hold on!
Since we’re at a volunteer camp,
we might as well get adventurous, right?
So, everyone here gets to take in
the fresh scent of dirt and grass by…
sleeping in a tent!
P’ Wim, P’ Wim, can I say something?
What’s the meaning of this?
This isn’t what we agreed on.
Well, it wouldn’t be
a surprise if I told you.
Ah!
Don’t you worry because every tent
comes with a full set of bedding.
What kind of tents are we getting?
Ah! I was just about to get to that.
We’ll be pairing up
to play a Route Check game.
The first pair to find all three numbers
will win a big prize, which is…
The. Biggest. Tent.
So you can sleep comfortably without
having to squeeze in with anyone.
However, those who finish last
will get just tiny sleeping bags.
- P’ Wim. P' Wim.
- I thought this was a fun trip.
P’ Wim, how are we going to pair up?
Ah! I was just about to tell you
that I’ve already taken care of it.
How so?
Whoever you sat with
on the bus this morning…
that's your partner.
What?!
Ai Wim. Ai… Ai Wim. Ai Wim.
I sat alone.
You're such a hassle.
You sat alone,
so you’re sleeping alone.
Stop making a big deal.
Jeez, asshole. Easy for you
to say, you've got a partner.
But I like your idea. Works for me.
Well? What are you waiting for?
Get up and pair up!
P’ Wim.
It’s settled then.
Let’s draw the first clue now.
And most importantly, don’t forget
that the first place gets the biggest tent.
Those in last place
will only get sleeping bags.
And don’t come complaining to me, alright?
Because our pavilion is ready
to welcome everyone to sleep in.
P’ Wim.
Please change the rules.
Pretty please.
No.
P’ Wim.
Don’t ‘P’ Wim’ me.
Why are you still here?
If you lose, you'll be sleeping
all cramped up in the pavilion.
You want Ai Cir to have a hard time?
That won’t do.
I know, right? Therefore...
focus on the game.
This is your chance, Ai Phu.
What do you mean?
It’s your chance to show him
that you can be reliable too.
Who knows, you might go from being
a stranger to becoming his close junior.
Just like me and P' Wim.
Really? Will he really see me that way?
Yeah, trust me.
So this is where you’ve been hiding.
What’s taking you so long?
Let’s get moving.
Let’s finish these assholes’ bullshit game.
Hey! I’m not an asshole.
It wasn’t me.
Wait till I’m done with this game.
Brace yourself, you son of a bitch.
Come.
Do I have to play the game too?
Why don’t you just read my mind?
I want to hear it from your mouth.
Though I can read just your mind,
I still want to hear it directly from you.
Then why would you play the game?
You'll be sleeping with me.
Will people think I’m using connections?
Well, as the SU president’s boyfriend,
you’re entitled to some privileges.
I’m sleeping in the cabin…
and you’ll be sleeping with me.
Why sleep uncomfortably in a tent, right?
“Find the guardian angel under the
big tree. Head toward 3:32 o'clock.”
What kind of fucking clue is this?
When the game’s over,
you're dead meat, Ai Wim.
Burden.
I’m sorry.
You’d better keep up.
Alright, Ai Phu.
Don’t be a burden.
You've got this!
P’ Cir, the guardian angel.
Oh, so dumb! The sleeping
bag’s gonna be yours.
P’ Cir, I’ll go check it.
Found it.
Damn! You kicked like a bull!
Hey, I found it!
Hey! What the fuck?
You want a piece of me!?
I mean, you can have that piece of paper.
Thanks for finding it.
Just one more left,
and this damn game’s finally over.
It’s your chance to show him
that you can be reliable too.
Who knows, you might go from being
a stranger to becoming his close junior.
You've found two numbers,
I'll take care of the last one.
You should take a break.
I'll… I’ll be back soon.
“In the deep forest, the little bird
has stolen something precious.”
“Look lower than before,
for the little bird waits not far away.”
It’s gotta be around here.
‘The forest’ means it’s in the forest.
And I’ve followed the bird sounds.
It’s gotta be one of these branches.
I’m sorry! I didn’t mean to trespass!
I’ll make an offering for you.
Please don’t haunt me.
What offering? I’m not dead yet.
P’ Cir.
I knew it, I can't count on you.
So... what are you doing here?
I’ve been following you all along.
Then you suddenly
started running, so I ran too.
I thought you were a…
- a...
- Ghost?
You’re not supposed to call out
to the tiger in the forest.
I didn’t call the tiger. I called…
P’ Cir, no. Don’t say it.
Don’t say it.
I said…
Hey!
I found it!
I’m not a burden to you anymore.
You won’t have to sleep in the pavilion.
This is it! The last number!
I got up too quickly.
Ouch!
What a burden.
Get on.
No way, I can’t do that.
Are you getting on,
or should I make you?
No, I can’t do that.
You’re just gonna stay here
and let the ghost drag you away?
C’ mon.
I’m sorry.
So you know you're wrong?
Yes, well…
I’m… a burden.
I couldn’t help you at all.
And now you’re stuck carrying me.
I’m sorry.
That’s true.
But I think I said one thing wrong.
I’m useless, right?
I know.
You’re not a burden like I thought.
Well done for finding it.
How did you end up like this?
I fell.
No. I mean, how did you
make Ai Cir carry you back?
Well… I fell, and P' Cir was
nice enough to carry me back.
That's exactly what I wanna know.
Someone like Ai Cir actually went that far?
But when your leg was broken,
he still helped carry your stuff.
That was ages ago.
It doesn’t matter. P' Cir has
always been a good person.
You’re probably the only one
who sees him that way.
When you’re done being nosy,
come help me so you can finally shut up.
What the hell? It’s not my job.
I’m the vice president.
This isn’t my job either.
Jeez, you’re just
the vice president in name.
Now that I think
about it, I’m still pissed.
I only asked you to model for
the poster, but you gave me an earful.
What do you even do anyway?
You’re too lazy to even move your ass.
All you ever do is make that Jin kid
do everything for you, dumbass.
If you won’t help, I’m leaving.
C’mon, you’re just gonna leave?
Well, here’s a wake-up call.
I’ve got all the car keys.
I just need to call for a ride and
wait for two hours, then I can leave.
Fucking bastard.
Damn it.
How could he like this jerk?
- How do I do this?
- Let me do it.
Help me hammer this in.
Quit moping.
I just feel bad.
I couldn’t help with anything at all.
I didn’t do anything either.
Ai Wim and your friend did all of it.
I just want to be of some help.
You did help.
How?
You brought me the medicine.
Thanks.
Can you see my face clearly now?
Phukan.
What’s up?
Hmm.
What kind of response is that?
Ai Jin, what should I do?
I wanna hear your thoughts.
P’ Cir is so mean.
Didn’t you say he was nice?
He makes my heart flutter.
Weren’t you already feeling that way?
Now it’s even worse.
He was so mean to call me that.
Not only are you a thief,
but you’re a liar too?
You’re actually happy.
See?
Just seeing him already
makes you happy, Ai Phu.
We wanna hear you sing, P’ Cir.
That’s right, can you sing us a song?
Hey, this is your moment.
They’re practically begging.
You can’t let them down, you know.
Sing us a song, P’ Cir. Pretty please.
Hey, just one song. C’mon.
Sing it! Sing it! Sing it!
Will you guys shut up if I sing?
He’s handsome if he…
If he shuts up.
Fuck, he’s handsome when he shuts up.
The moment he talks,
it’s like a bunch of barking dogs.
Hey, hear that?
You’re handsome,
but your mouth’s full of dogs.
Should I take them out?
What song do you wanna hear?
Me?
Tell me what song you wanna hear.
“You know who.”
That’s all.
If you wake up in the morning
And find a big bouquet of flowers
You have no idea who it belongs to
Don’t be surprised
Because it belongs to you
At night before bed
A number you don’t recognize
Sends you an 'I miss you' message
Written with such gentle words
(Watch on www.kisskh.la or www.kisskh.co to support Admin)
Wishing you sweet dreams and an early night
No need to wonder if it was sent by mistake
Stop guessing and just accept it
Please don’t doubt
the sincerity behind this gesture
It’s from the same person,
you know who it is
The one who’s always
watched over you from afar
Do you remember?
That person still cares about you
You know who it is
What to do, Ai Phu?
What to do?
Ugh, what should I do?
What should I do?
You’ve been ignoring me today.
C’mon, don’t sulk.
But it’s true.
So...
What do you want me to do?
Don’t you know those two are together?
They’ve been together for a year now.
I had no idea.
You know now, so let’s go.
Why are you so shocked?
I didn’t think those two were...
Are you shocked because you
just found out they’re together, or…
because you saw them make out?
Er…
I’ve got something to ask you.
What is it?
If you wanna talk to me, look at me.
I... I can… I can talk to you like this.
Look up and face me.
Do you like me?
Don’t look away.
Look me in the eye.
Well?
Do you like me?
Yes.
What?
I didn’t catch that.
I like you.
I like you a lot, and…
and I’ve liked you for many years.
You've got me noticing you.
♪ Only when I met you did I understand ♪
♪ Why flowers bloom so beautifully ♪
♪ Making me realize that no matter what ♪
A World Where We Don’t Know Each Other
♪ I need to hold you close ♪
A World Where We Know Each Other
♪ Can I keep you safe? ♪
Phu, what’s wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
Phu, what’s the matter?
I don’t feel shy.
That’s right, we’ve been
together for months now.
How could I feel shy by your kiss
that I’d nearly have a heart attack?
Hold on, Phu.
What’s really going on with you?
P’ Cir, I think I dreamed
of myself in a parallel world.
P’ Cir, I dreamed of myself
and you in another world.
In the dream, you were harsh
with your words, but super kind.
Just like the one who took
over your body that time.
And I was super timid.
Oh, and they went to
a volunteer camp together.
It looked like the place we visited around
here because the view seemed familiar.
Perhaps it’s like you said,
that every world has similarities.
Perhaps, in another world,
we’re setting up a tent around here.
I’m not sure either.
Since I got hit by the car that day,
I haven't dreamed of the white room again.
So why did I have that dream?
Mabye I have powers to
travel between worlds like you?
I won't let you go.
So did he do anything to you?
What do you mean?
Did he touch you or…
do something more than that?
Are you jealous?
You’re jealous of someone
from another world?
What if I say I am?
Jeez, Mr. Jealous.
So are you going to tell me or not?
I’m telling you right now.
No, I mean, in that dream,
when you dreamed.
Did you dream as if you were there
and saw those two, or...
did you experience the dream
as if you were that Phukan?
What if I told you I actually
became that Phukan?
And what if I told you
the other P' Cir kissed me so rough?
And what if I told you my heart was
racing like crazy when he sang to me?
What would you say to that?
You’re angry?
Let’s make up.
Okay? Okay? Okay?
Please?
Can we make up?
Let’s make up, P’ Cir.
Punish me until you’re satisfied.
I don’t want to punish you.
I’d love to know, between Cirrus from
this world and the one from that world...
who’s rougher?
No more, P’ Cir.
My lips are all sore now.
You said you kissed someone else.
It was the other Phukan.
And that someone else was you.
But there’s only one of me in this world.
There’s only one Phukan in this world too.
That Phukan has that P' Cir.
And this Phukan has this P' Cir.
You said his kiss was rough.
I can be rough for you.
I want to go for a walk in the morning.
We're here on a trip after all.
And I’m already tired.
Please.
Fine, I’ll tell you.
I didn’t feel like I was being kissed.
It felt more like I was just
standing there watching them.
That Phukan seemed
really excited about P' Cir.
And he was kinda cute too.
I bet he freaked out
after they were done kissing.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, believe me.
C’mon.
Let’s turn in. I’m sleepy.
P’ Cir.
What do you think both of us
would be like in other worlds?
They’d probably be
as happy as I am right now.
Morning krub, Phu.
My guess was correct, right?
That’s my line.
I knew you were going
to say that, so I said it first.
Morning krub.
Morning krub, Phu.
Let’s get up.
Can I have two more minutes?
Please?
Can I?
I’ll give you five.
I want to go for a swim.
Didn’t you want to go for a walk?
I do, but I also want to swim.
What’s wrong?
I was just thinking about
the first day I met you.
I mean the first day we actually met.
I remember you being all wet,
standing in front of my door
saying you were my lover
from a parallel world.
Now that I think about it,
no normal person would buy that, right?
That’s because you’re someone special.
Heh, so you’re saying
you sounded convincing, huh?
That's not what I mean.
But I’m glad that I believed you.
Because it’s brought me...
to where I am now.
And I want Phukan from
every world to believe like I did.
Someone told me that Phukan
will be my light in every world.
But... I believe that
no matter which Phukan it is
he’d never leave P' Cirrus.
Then I’ll make a wish
for the world I just dreamed of.
I wish for Phukan in that
world to become braver.
Seriously, if I got kissed like that,
I would've gone all the way.
But I guess all he can do is freak out.
Are you happy, P’ Cir?
Am I not making it clear?
I want to hear you say it.
Of course.
I’m the happiest I’ve ever been.
As long as I have you by my side.
Then I’ll stick by your side forever.
I’ll look forward to it.
♪ If you wake up in the morning ♪
♪ And find a big bouquet of flowers ♪
♪ You have no idea who it belongs to ♪
♪ Don’t be surprised ♪
♪ Because it belongs to you ♪
♪ At night before bed ♪
♪ A number you don’t recognize ♪
♪ Sends you an 'I miss you' message ♪
♪ Written with such gentle words ♪
♪ Wishing you sweet
dreams and an early night ♪
♪ No need to wonder
if it was sent by mistake ♪
♪ Stop guessing and just accept it ♪
♪ Please don’t doubt
the sincerity behind this gesture ♪
♪ It’s from the same person,
you know who it is ♪
♪ The one who’s always
watched over you from afar ♪
♪ Do you remember? ♪
♪ That person still cares about you ♪
♪ You know who it is ♪
♪ You know, right? ♪
♪ Please don’t doubt
the sincerity behind this gesture ♪
♪ It’s from someone,
and you know who it is ♪
♪ The one who’s always
watched over you from afar ♪
♪ Do you remember? ♪
♪ That person still cares about you ♪
♪ Please don’t doubt
the sincerity behind this gesture ♪
♪ It’s from the same person,
you know who it is ♪
♪ The one who’s always
watched over you from afar ♪
♪ Do you remember? ♪
♪ That person still cares about you ♪
♪ You know who it is ♪
If I told you that I’m your
lover from a parallel world
would you believe me?
What if I don’t believe you?
Then I’d say…
I love you.
Then my answer would be…
I love you too.
English Subtitles by Saowalak K.
Finally…
we've met at last.
What the fuck?