[English subtitles are available]
[Fox Spirit Matchmaker: Red-Moon Pact]
[Episode 33]
Hu Weisheng.
Come here.
What's going on?
He's proposed marriage to me.
Why can't I retrieve it?
Is Mother wrong?
Was his proposal
not out of true love?
Let's
part here.
It's safe here.
The Ximens won't be able to catch up to us soon.
You...
What do you mean?
I won't ever like spirits.
I'll never like you
or go to your house to propose.
You can't go.
We are engaged.
Then... I'll follow you
wherever you go.
Out of countless men in the world,
why do you have to pester me?
I...
Because I like you.
I don't believe it.
You don't have a twin sister.
It was just you
from the beginning.
You clearly wanted to kill me.
Later, you lied to me that you like me.
Then I...
I fell in love with you later, okay?
What kind of reason is that?
Do I need a reason to like someone?
Conditional love is shallow.
You don't need a reason to love someone!
I won't like spirits anyway.
Fine.
You can leave.
Leave!
Anyway,
you don't truly like me.
Darn it.
He really left.
Forget it.
Let's find another way.
In this world,
I think...
you're the only one who loves me.
How about...
I try to make it work?
♫The red leaves set us ablaze♫
♫The snow drains our warmth♫
♫We keep parting and loving each other again♫
♫Living life like a dream♫
♫My heart and mind are always conflicting♫
♫I have passed by so many people♫
♫All that is left♫
♫Is my reflection in your eyes♫
Tushan Honghong.
This is the power of hatred.
Black Fox.
To think you'd enter the circle through Grief Tree.
You noticed?
But it doesn't matter.
We'll be the same kind soon.
The power you depend on deep down
is the same as mine.
Am I wrong?
After seriously injuring Dongfang Luo,
didn't you harbor hatred in your heart?
You hate yourself.
And you'll always be this way.
You and I will never be the same.
There are two emotional forces: love and hatred.
Grief Tree absorbs emotional forces
and supports itself with love.
But the truth is hatred is more common than love.
The hatred from the bottom of our hearts
is enough to devour the six realms.
So you're ruining
the peace between humans and spirits
to use this hatred
to become powerful?
Black Foxes respect those with strong hatred.
To control Black Foxes in the circle,
you have to absorb hatred.
Tushan Honghong, do you dare?
Your deepest love will become your deepest hatred.
You'll definitely experience
being invincible again.
What you saw when you were in the Mist Formation
will happen.
Dongfang Yuechu will join us.
It's easier for him to hate you than love you.
He killed Tushan Buzui.
He'll keep killing more and more.
You'll hate him so much
you'll want to kill him yourself.
By then,
you'll be our best ally to invade the six realms!
So Grief Tree's
the passage for Black Foxes to invade the six realms.
Then everyone
in the six realms
must see Black Foxes' true colors.
Give it to me.
I want to play.
Before I knew it,
they were only an inch away from me.
They thought Yuechu saved me.
Actually, I saved him.
How can these spirits be so happy?
They even hang out with humans.
I should teach them a lesson.
Darn spirits.
Fu Cheng!
-Where's Yuechu?
-Yaya.
I'll kill him to avenge Elder.
Yaya.
Yaya, calm down.
Elder was killed
by a Black Fox, not Yuechu.
Yaya.
Once a Black Fox possesses a fox spirit,
it'll devour the host's spiritual consciousness.
He had no choice.
Yaya.
Let's just send Elder off so he rests in peace.
I don't care.
Honghong just came back,
so Yuechu must still be around.
Yaya!
Hang on.
Let her go.
After what happened,
they both must feel awful.
Her making a scene
might resolve
their emotional turmoil.
I hope so.
What did you call me?
Tushan Jiaojiao!
Tell me.
Come and get it!
Stop there!
Return my wine!
Come on!
Old fox.
Back then,
you said you left the mountain for Honghong.
But ever since you became the director,
do you still care about Tushan?
I do.
But I'm also Yiqi Alliance's director.
In my heart,
humans
and spirits
are the same.
So,
to protect Yiqi Alliance members,
you killed Elder yourself.
I...
I won't make any excuses for what I did.
I'll take...
full responsibility.
Take responsibility?
How?
Can you bring Elder back to life?
Or...
can you pay with your life?
If I can
exchange my life for his,
I'd do it.
Dongfang Yuechu.
Has Tushan ever wronged you?
That's Elder.
He's our elder who taught us
and accepted our teasing.
There's trouble in Peace Village.
Fu Cheng!
What's wrong with you?
Wake up!
Fu Cheng!
Kill them.
Fu Cheng...
Liushang!
Liushang.
Jiushuang.
Liushang!
Tell Yuechu...
I believe
peace between humans and spirits
will happen.
Liushang.
Liushang!
Peace between humans and spirits?
Impossible!
Liushang.
Liushang, you can't die.
Liushang!
It's me?
I killed them?
I killed them.
Stop pretending!
Did Yuechu send you here
to kill everyone?
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
What's the use of apologizing?
Can you bring these innocent victims back to life?
Will it atone for you ruining the alliances' cooperation?
No matter what,
I must make you pay with your life.
It's my fault.
I can't cause any more trouble for Yuechu.
So...
I don't need your help with it.
No!
Fu Cheng!
Dongfang Yuechu.
See?
Tushan forced Fu Cheng to death.
Got the news so soon?
Elder's death and today's matter
must be settled.
She hates you
for killing Elder
and for bringing humans to Tushan.
For today's matter,
Fu Cheng has died.
As for Elder's death,
I'll take the blame.
So you want Tushan
to take the blame for Fu Cheng's death?
Tushan Honghong.
You'll never catch the Black Foxes.
Fox spirits respect the strong.
Only by absorbing hatred
and letting it spread all over your meridians
can you force the Black Foxes driven by hatred
to appear.
But Honghong,
do you dare?
Or
do you doubt that the love in your body
can overcome hatred?
Chief.
Are the preparations for Liushang's funeral settled?
Don't worry.
Rongrong's taken care of everything.
But these successive incidents
are obviously the Black Foxes
trying to sow discord between the Spirit and Yiqi Alliances.
You seem to be in a bad mood.
Did something happen?
Do you know
how Black Foxes enter the circle?
Could it be...
Right here.
Grief Tree's roots link to the outside.
In that case,
they destroyed the Heaven Sect Pass
as a cover-up.
The real passage to enter the circle
is here?
Yes.
When I returned to Tushan that day,
I followed a Black Fox I saw
with my spiritual consciousness into the roots.
Outside the circle,
there's a Black Grief Tree.
Black Grief Tree?
Black Grief Tree absorbs hatred.
The greater the hatred,
the stronger it becomes.
That's why Black Foxes can control others' emotions
and arouse hatred.
If that's the case,
why did you force Yuechu to leave?
Tear of Void is cultivated with vitality.
I see.
You don't want Yuechu to sacrifice himself
to form the Tear of Void,
so you forced him to cut ties with Tushan.
But without this tear,
how can we deal with those Black Foxes?
Fox spirits respect the strong.
If I absorb enough hatred,
I can control the Black Foxes.
But in this way,
you'll be dominated by hatred.
You won't just fail to destroy Black Foxes
but also become their helper.
It doesn't matter.
I have my own plan.
When this matter is over,
please give
this spiritual butterfly to Yaya and Rongrong.
Thank you.
What about Yuechu?
He won't agree if he knows about this.
So don't let him know.
[Divine Flame Villa]
I know
that if you were me,
you'd have done the same.
I'm sorry.
I won't make it
to our promised future.
Only two died
and Honghong and Yuechu have fallen out.
At this rate,
before the month's over,
the entire Tushan and the six realms will be mine.
Yours?
I mean Black Fox Empress', of course.
What should we do next?
Honghong has entered the game.
We just need to win over Yuechu
as we planned.
Wait.
Why did you stop me?
Don't rush to kill them here.
What do you mean?
If
Yueti Chun
knew her daughter died in Tushan,
what would happen?
Can we really fall in love here?
Trust me.
Tushan is where all spirits get attached.
Grief Tree can help humans and spirits fall in love.
If we pray sincerely
under Grief Tree,
you'll truly fall in love with me.
Then...
What about you?
Me?
Don't you already...
know how I feel for you?
Here are the noodles.
Be careful.
Here.
Eat up.
I'm sorry.
I usually entertain customers who drink wine.
I only have simple dishes.
It's not simple.
No shops are open now.
I'm grateful for something to eat.
Wait!
Noodles taste good
when they're thoroughly mixed.
Besides, you always scarf down your food.
Don't burn yourself.
This fool
is quite considerate.
Done.
By the way,
did you pester me
because of the Seven-Treasures Bark?
Calm down.
I mean,
I thought you seized this magic tool.
But you kept nagging along the way,
saying that once you get it,
you'd go back to see your mother.
That means you don't have it.
So...
you came to me for that,
right?
No?
That's right then.
Neither you nor I
nor the Ximens
have it.
It means
someone else
stole it!
Right?
Who could've stolen it?
Actually,
I did come to you
to find the magic tool.
But...
I became attracted to you later.
Why are you
bringing this up suddenly?
Nothing.
I was thinking about it
and figured it out.
Eat your noodles.
Come in!
A human?
How dare you!
How dare you come to our turf?
Sirs...
Well... Sirs...
Well...
The human and spirit alliances are working together.
Why can't I come here?
That's right.
Kid,
what you said is in the past.
Now your director
has killed Tushan spirits.
We're sworn enemies!
Calm down, sirs.
Calm down!
Wait, wait, wait!
Calm down.
You...
Does everyone in Tushan listen to Chief?
Yes, yes, yes.
Listen to Chief.
Of course.
Then
did Chief say
humans can’t come here?
No, she didn't.
Right? I'm sure.
Did Chief say
humans and spirits can bond under Grief Tree?
It's a good thing, isn't it?
It's a good thing.
To kill him,
you've to get my permission first.
Sirs!
Chief's ordered
-not to stir up trouble.
-But we can’t spare him!
Don’t hurt humans.
Let's obey Chief, okay?
I’ll give you some good wine for free.
How can we let him off lightly?
Spare him for my sake.
I'll spare you this time!
Come to my little tavern next time!
Haven't you always been afraid of spirits?
How were you so bold just now?
Was I?
I think
since you've been protecting me,
I should try to protect you too.
Besides,
you're a spirit.
Since I chose to be with you,
then...
I should know these spirits
and integrate socially.
After thinking for so long,
have you gained clarity?
Don't be anxious.
I'm here to help you clarify things.
Do you know
why Honghong took you in in the first place?
Do you really think she sympathizes with the weak?
There are so many human orphans who lost their parents.
Why did she only take you in?
Because Dongfang Blood can be sacrificed to Grief Tree
to stop the invasion of hatred.
Nonsense!
Of course you don't believe it.
Do you remember Tushan Buzui
setting up a trap to kill you?
He could have killed the Dongfangs long ago.
Why did he wait for you to enter Tushan?
In that case,
why did Honghong save me from Elder?
Because she still
needs to use you for a greater cause.
Without you,
how could she gain the humans' trust?
how could she enter the humans' territory
and deal with Jin Renfeng and me?
Do you think I'll believe you?
Honghong loves me.
Yes.
She loves you.
But even this love
was designed by her.
Because falling in love
boosts a spirit's emotional power.
She was also
inspired by Bu Tai and Shi Kuan's love,
when she found that human-spirit bonds produce more power.
So she fell in love with you, an infatuated human,
to become stronger to compete with me.
Anyway,
you have always been
just a tool to her.
Still not convinced?
Fine.
I'll ask you one more thing.
Did she tell you
you'll exhaust your vitality
to cultivate the Tear of Void?
I've studied Emptiness Magic repeatedly.
[Emptiness Magic]
There's no problem
with the methods in here.
You can continue cultivating.
She didn't tell you, right?
She only cares about Tushan.
Even if you gave her your heart,
to her,
you're just an expendable human.
Protecting Tushan
isn't just a duty to me.
There are so many hardworking spirits here.
All the memories
in this land
are inseparable from my life.
I'm protecting it willingly at all costs.
Check it and you'll know if it's true or not.
I won't say more.
The truth hurts,
but it will...
wake you up.
Tushan Honghong.
Have you made up your mind?
Even if I absorb hatred,
I'll never forget my original intention
and be blinded by hatred.
In this world,
who can live without suffering and hatred?
But even if there's endless hatred,
as long as there's a ray of love,
darkness and coldness can be dispelled.
Hatred
can never overcome love!
Let's wait and see then.