[English subtitles are available]
[Fox Spirit Matchmaker: Red-Moon Pact]
[Episode 36]
Sacrificial Formation.
Tushan Honghong.
If I were you, I would just give up.
The love you believe in doesn't exist anymore,
does it?
Dongfang Yuechu
is on his way here...
To kill you!
They're coming.
These are not normal humans!
What should we do?
Well...
When do we attack?
We've been waiting for so long.
When can we attack?
No one is allowed to act rashly.
Act according to the Director's signal.
Sacrificial Formation.
Why is this formation so resistant to my approach?
Shi Ji.
For your own ambition,
you tore apart humans and spirits
and created tension.
You even caused chaos in the six realms with external power.
Many people's happiness has been ruined by you.
Many innocent children lost their parents because of you.
Many beautiful and peaceful places
are in chaos because of you.
Everything you did,
I will end them
today.
You can draw thunder with hatred to kill Weisheng.
Today, I will let you experience the same pain!
I'll let the Black Foxes you lured over
to kill you off.
Have you forgotten that I have hatred too?
All my hatred will be passed on to you.
Tushan Honghong.
When you are completely swallowed by hatred,
at that time,
I will destroy the six realms you protect myself.
Come and die with me!
This is...
hatred.
In this world,
there are so many evil people doing evil things,
and so many bad things happen every day.
Diseases.
Disasters.
Deaths.
Humans and spirits hate each other.
Love...
will always be destroyed by hatred.
The six realms are doomed to be destroyed.
Your protection
is meaningless.
In this world,
there are many innocent and kind people.
They work hard and love peace.
As long as they are around,
there will be endless love
and the six realms will be protected.
It's useless to talk more.
You still won't come to your senses!
Tushan Honghong.
You are too naive!
Heaven & Earth Thread...
When you took back Heaven & Earth Thread,
it was for this?
To fuse my blood into Love Seed
and have Grief Tree recognize me...
Even if you forget me,
no one will sacrifice me.
Yuechu!
Yuechu...
As long as I kill you,
the Black Foxes can enter the six realms.
You care so much about the six realms.
Why can't you bear to part with Dongfang Yuechu?
As long as he coagulates the Tear of Void,
he can give the Black Foxes a form
and don't let them enter other dimensions.
You...
still have a chance to turn the tide.
I've been consumed by hatred.
Only by coagulating Tear of Void
can I release my hatred
and be saved.
I will protect both the six realms
and him!
I don't understand.
Why you are still struggling?
When you're about to die,
can love save you?
What's going on?
There seems to be hatred within them.
This hatred is stronger than before.
To be able to make them into an existence that can't be killed
is beyond Shi Ji's capabilities.
Director has given a command.
When the Black Foxes show up,
we'll join forces with the Spirit Alliance
to kill the external Black Foxes who have been killing humans and spirits.
They are the origin of the six realms dispute.
Spirit Alliance, listen.
Humans and spirits are equal.
We fight for the six realms together!
We fight for the six realms!
Tear of Void...
You're fine now.
Why are you so silly?
I didn't tell you
because I don't want you to waste your vitality on me
to coagulate the Tear of Void.
I've already thought about using this
to give the Black Foxes a form.
Peace between humans and spirits
is not only your belief,
but it has also long become
mine.
But I want you to live.
I know.
I understand everything.
When we first met,
it's as if my world changed.
But this time,
you don't have to protect me anymore.
This time,
let's protect
the future of the six realms together.
With my blood,
I will burn your bones
with no fear of death.
This is the last thing
I can do for you.
♫A coincidental meeting is like a dragonfly touching water lightly♫
With Dongfang Spiritual Blood as the key,
it can save your soul.
♫Going through the shadows you left♫
♫Tugging on the tide of what's on my mind♫
Lady Fairy.
I want to spend four seasons with you.
♫My past is being displaced endlessly♫
To enjoy the moon together
under the mountains' shadows.
I, Dongfang Yuechu, love Tushan Honghong.
♫I see your traces in my eyes♫
From now on, in this life,
♫What's there to be afraid of the changes in fate?♫
for the rest of my life, and my next life,
I am willing to keep accompanying you
♫Wild flowers and the wind embrace♫
and protecting you.
♫Entangled with the world♫
♫Not letting down anything I've met with in this lifetime♫
♫Love in this vast world is fire♫
♫Burning endlessly for each other♫
♫The moon and the sea embrace♫
♫Reflecting each other's loneliness♫
♫Entangled till the end of the world♫
♫Travel through the obstruction of the clouds♫
♫To return to your embrace♫
Grief Tree,
♫Parting is the start of darkness♫
I'm willing to
bind myself here.
I don't ask for anything else.
I just ask that as the time goes by,
♫I've seen the scenery in your eyes♫
and the stars rise,
♫It fills the gaps of life♫
they can light up the night for her
so that she's never in grief.
♫The four seasons change, the stars move♫
♫Love is so subtle♫
Grief Tree,
♫If it's a dream, why are you afraid of losing it?♫
if you can hear us,
I want to use
all our memories
♫Wild flowers and the wind embrace♫
♫Entangled with the world♫
and all my power to swear to you...
♫Not letting down anything I've met with in this lifetime♫
♫Love in this vast world is fire♫
so that I can bond with him.
♫Burning endlessly for each other♫
♫The moon and the sea embrace♫
I'm willing.
♫Reflecting each other's loneliness♫
♫Entangled till the end of the world♫
I've been willing...
♫Travel through the obstruction of the clouds♫
since many years ago.
♫To return to your embrace♫
Since he fell in love with the spirit,
he is no longer lonely
♫Wild flowers and the wind embrace♫
and no longer afraid.
♫Entangled with the world♫
♫Not letting down anything I've met with in this lifetime♫
He will protect his spirit
♫Love in this vast world is fire♫
forever and ever.
♫Burning endlessly for each other♫
♫The moon and the sea embrace♫
♫Reflecting each other's loneliness♫
♫Entangled till the end of the world♫
♫Travel through the obstruction of the clouds♫
♫To return to your embrace♫
Originally, I wanted to use Tear of Void to control spacetime
and let us enter and leave the circle as we wish.
But you used it to force us to show our form.
But it's not up to you
who the Tear of Void will be used by!
We don't know
who wins or loses yet!
The queen of fox spirits,
Tushan Honghong,
you are rapidly losing your spirit power.
Meanwhile, my body
can recover quickly.
It's really easy to kill you now.
If you die,
Dongfang Yuechu can never revive.
You are destined to die in my hands!
You planned everything
for us to kill each other.
But what you don't know is, a complete Tear of Void
needs true love.
Yuechu...
With my spirit power,
and your spiritual blood,
let's protect our future together.
The Black Fox has left the body.
Don't think you can run!
You...
Fool.
I'm not a fool.
I fell in love
with the best spirit
in this world.
That's all I want
in this life.
You did everything this life
for me.
For me,
you left Tushan.
you rose the ranks.
For me,
you did everything to stop the fight between humans and spirits.
Just for me...
someone who always prioritizes the six realms over you.
No.
It's you...
who is always...
thinking of ways to protect me.
You're the most beautiful scenery
I've seen
in my most desperate abyss.
I am willing...
to follow you
for my whole life.
Lady Fairy...
Give me a hug...
Can you?
♫Staring into the moonlit sky♫
♫Memories whisper softly in my ears♫
♫Borrowing light♫
In the past,
♫To illuminate you♫
it's always you who came to look for me.
♫A thousand years feel like a fleeting moment♫
♫This isn't our first time around♫
From now on,
♫Despite all the hardships♫
♫The warmth of love still remains♫
I'll come to you.
♫If you forget everything in your next life♫
♫Miss someone but no one is coming♫
♫If you look back♫
♫I'm afraid I have to see you leave once more♫
♫If I make a vow, and the snowflakes fly♫
♫To bury my entire life♫
♫Looking back, how can I make it worth it?♫
♫If you forget everything in your next life♫
♫Miss someone but no one is coming♫
♫If you look back♫
♫I'm afraid I have to see you leave once more♫
Yaya.
Rongrong.
I will summon the Black Fox with hatred
to activate the formation
♫If I make a vow, and the snowflakes fly♫
to burn the Black Fox with the Grief Tree
♫To bury my entire life♫
and cut off all the passages for external invasion.
After I leave,
♫When I look back, you're under the tree of longing♫
I'll leave Tushan to you.
The peace of the six realms will be in your hands.
After the attack of the Black Fox this time,
I believe humans and spirits
will abandon prejudice
and cooperate.
One day,
the peace we want
will come.
Yaya.
Yiqi Alliance sent an alliance letter
[Alliance Agreement]
expressing their willingness to join hands with the Spirit Alliance
to make the six realms a place where humans and spirits can coexist in peace.
Honghong and Yuechu's wish
has finally come true.
When Honghong set up the illusion formation,
it was to hold back Yuechu
and stop him from risking his life.
Since Honghong started absorbing hatred,
she had decided to fight the Black Fox alone,
and close off all the passages for external invasion.
Yes.
He is the same.
He broke the illusion formation and rushed to the Grief Tree
just to coagulate the Tear of Void,
so that people gathered here
can see the Black Foxes with their own eyes.
He then use the Tear of Void to control the Black Foxes
and have the human and spirit clans to join forces
to get rid of the Black Foxes.
Both of them
have never stopped protecting each other.
Yes.
When are you leaving?
You know everything?
Rongrong told me.
The messenger of Aolai Kingdom is just outside.
All right. We shall part ways here.
So...
soon?
In the past,
I can leave Tushan with you
and travel around the six realms with you.
But now I must stay
and protect Tushan.
For Honghong,
I will turn this place
back to what it used to be.
You're strong enough now.
You can shoulder the responsibility to protect Tushan.
Yaya.
If you need,
I can stay.
Lai can belong to me
and stay with me in Tushan.
But Aolai Sanshao can't just be Lai.
You belong to the six realms.
You will have a bigger sky
and more important responsibilities than Tushan.
I'll leave this Dinghai Rod
to you.
If you need anything,
I'll be back anytime.
See you.
I've sent Lai's expenses in Tushan
to Aolai Kingdom.
Honghong lost a lot of spirit power
and turned into a child.
She doesn't remember anything.
We need to find a way to make her recover as soon as possible.
Everything aside,
she keeps asking me what her name is.
Yaya,
why don't we tell her everything?
No!
She is so naughty.
If she knows
she is our elder sister,
how can we make her cultivate?
But we can't let her have no name.
Just call her Susu.
[Ya]
Brat.
You still haven't added this stroke you missed.
No matter what,
I have to keep and eye on Susu
so that she can recover to what she used to be quickly.
We can't waste this brat's
spiritual blood.
Susu,
I'm counting on you to complete the divine mission.
The divine mission?
This mission is to...
With the help of the Tear of Void,
this new Grief Tree
will help all the humans and spirits
who bond under it
continue their previous affinity.
Princess,
I'm here to take you home.
You promised to let me stay in Tushan for half a month.
It's only been a few days.
Looks like for this matchmaking event,
more humans and spirits
are coming to Tushan to bond.
Princess.
I...
So beautiful.
[Bond Wine]
Look, it's so beautiful.
Look how beautiful the fireworks are.
This is so bright.
So beautiful.
Princess.
I fell in love with you
at first sight.
All these years,
I cultivated day and night
and studied to handle politics.
I also worked hard to make the humans and spirits
get along peacefully.
I did these
because I want to be with you forever.
You know
my feelings for you.
The whole Beishan knows too.
I want to marry you.
Will you marry me?
When did you become
so eloquent?
So...
will you?
Yes, I do.
I want to
be with you forever,
until we grow old
and until the end of the world.
What are your capabilities? How can I use you?
I
can make people happy.
If you use me,
you'll be happy for the rest of your life.
How dare you
tease me.
Isn't this too shabby?
What if your mother
doesn't agree to our marriage?
Will you give up on me if she doesn't agree?
Then your love is too fragile.
How is that possible?
I like you.
I'll be with you forever.
That's right.
If my mother doesn't agree,
just cry hard.
If you cry, she will agree.
Really?
Of course.
I know my mother best.
She's soft-hearted.
She hates to see people cry.
So when you cry,
she will lose all her principles.
In that case,
she's quite like you.
Hu Weisheng.
I couldn't tell.
But you're quite smart!
Yes, I think so too.
Do you want a beating?
You want a beating?
There are eggs! Don't touch it!
Come back!
The other dimension opened up by the Tear of Void
is over there.
Our story
will continue.
Susu.
Did you learn the magic properoty
from the academy today?
Yes.
I've studied it for a hundred times.
What are you hiding?
A handsome guy gave it to me.
A handsome guy?
Where is he?
He was here just now.
Why did he disappear in a blink of an eye?
It's okay.
Maybe you can see him again.
Let's go.
♫When my gaze passes through the long night♫
♫Under the cold moonlight, you swear♫
[Happiness]
♫I've waited till the stars went out♫
♫Until the snowstorm rages on♫
♫We have to borrow our affinity from our past lives♫
♫Who can hear your breath♫
♫As you pour out your thoughts♫
♫It's my longing♫
♫Who can hear the passion♫
♫Your fingertips are playing?♫
Why are you here alone?
♫That's my heartstrings going round♫
Honghong.
♫Strumming out tears♫
How many years has it been
♫Flying past you in a flurry♫
since I came to Tushan?
This is the 27th year since you came to Tushan.
♫Listen♫
♫The wind blows, the longing rain♫
27 years?
♫Spreading the memories of longing across the sky♫
I've been in Tushan for 27 years.
♫They are all my longings and feelings♫
♫My unresolved woe♫
Am I dreaming?
We really defeated the Black Fox
♫Listen♫
and saved everyone?
♫The wind blows and makes my heart flutter♫
♫But it's using falling leaves to prepare for this life's parting♫
You're not dreaming.
♫All my love and hate has something to do with you; our meeting was not in vain♫
It's all true.
That's good.
I'm so afraid
♫Who can hear my gaze♫
all of this is just a dream.
♫Speaking about love♫
♫Silently yearning♫
♫Who can hear my world♫
Don't be afraid.
♫The landslide of the mountain♫
Everything
has passed.
♫That's my troubles roaring like thunder♫
♫As I run towards you♫
I've been waiting for this day
♫I missed you silently for a moment♫
for my whole life.
Silly.
♫Listen♫
♫Listen, the wind blows, the longing rain♫
♫Spreading the memories of longing across the sky♫
Your life
has just begun.
♫They are all my feelings♫
♫My unresolved woe♫
♫Listen♫
♫The wind blows and makes my heart flutter♫
♫But it's using falling leaves to prepare for this life's parting♫
There will always be someone
♫Love and hate are related to you♫
who would scale mountains and come from afar
♫Our meeting was not in vain♫
for you,
and to protect you.
Spacetime
can't stop them.