Name: zhong xiao. age: 27.
Ah! 17.
A strange thing happened to me recently.
at 27 I feel like I'm stuck at my 17.
I finally got the dress for tomorrow's meeting.
I don't know who came up with the idea of ​​wearing a dress to a meeting.
I go home first.
go back to China.
why are you making noise.
Haven't seen you in years, I have no idea.
If you have an idea, I'm 17 and you're 18.
is different.
zhong xiao, you can hide it from others, but not from me.
who chased everyone around with a camera every day in high school?
Where is it?
I don't know if it's bad or not.
xiao zhou, here!
Hey, where is the bathroom here?
there!
thanks.
The third.
did you not say,
when you bought the clothes, that it is absolutely impossible to clash with the new clothes?
I decided to change.
happens, that My clothes are in the car.
Hey, guess what I just saw.
when he came, all the girls came.
do you really say that?
have you seen his girlfriend?
girlfriend dreamed that they were together.
that said, I don't know if I'm wearing a limited hasty dress.
Ah, I don't know how many girls will break their hearts.
Oh, are you leaving now?
in fact, you also know that I came today to give the DV.
So since he has a girlfriend, it's not appropriate for me to see him again.
I'm right on the way out, can you help me deliver the DV? Okay okay.
Are you sure you put it on the table here?
why?
I'm coming now.
Still don't see?
I go there.
how long to see you.
Today is the monitor's birthday.
where are all the presents?
because it will not be considered a gift for the monitor, right?
I'll get the medicine.
will you come back this time?
currently there is no return track.
good to be home.
after everyone is here, we often get together.
she is stealing something.
you stop there!
pretending to be a lady of etiquette, right?
you're brave.
zhong xiao? smiled at me. I thought I was stealing.
you work here?
I flapped my shirt.
long time without seeing you.
yes, long time no see you.
Hey, today is the monitor's birthday and all the gifts are together.
do you want to ship separately?
What is that?
Isn't that the humble DV you picked up in high school?
This is an antique, can it still be used?
hey, can't you look.
No!
give me back!
Careful!
take care!