♪I can do anything for you♪
♪I will give my all♪
♪The faint light of the night flickers♪
♪Guiding me step by step towards you♪
♪Two independent hearts beat♪
♪Too closely as destined to me♪
♪You're in all my dreams♪
♪With eyes so mesmerizing♪
♪When you look at me, I'm very sure♪
♪It's love♪
♪I can do anything for you♪
♪I will give my all♪
♪We roam among stars♪
♪We sleep under the most beautiful sky♪
♪We hold hands, saving each other♪
=Step By Step Love=
=Episode 1=
Welcome to the manuscript exhibition
of Mr. Taylor,
the top-tier interior designer.
This exhibition is held
by the Yihua Group.
We'll interview their President...
Hurry.
Mr. Yi Mincai.
Yihua is already
the leading company in town.
But you still
have a bad habit
of backstabbing your partners.
Verbal assault
won't drag Yihua down from the throne.
(You)
(are not qualified to talk to me.)
(The unfinished building
shall pass the inspection)
(and be sold at a premium price.)
(Let me show you.)
(The fabrication looks authentic, huh?)
I have something on your grandson.
Can we talk now?
(You'd better agree
to the terms I proposed.)
Otherwise, the journalists
who came today
might have some unexpected gains.
Not here. Go.
Okay.
What are you looking at, lecher?
Nice moves there.
Hey.
What are you filming?
I'm in a crisis!
They are chasing you.
It's for self-protection.
Delete the video.
Chill, I put the beauty cam.
Delete the video!
Give it to me!
Delete it.
Throw yourself into someone's arms
in a better place next time.
You tore your clothes apart
to snatch my phone.
What a clumsy thief!
Thief?
I'm a thief?
That Taylor guy is the real thief.
I was pointing out that
he stole my work.
That's why they
chased me here.
Give me my phone.
You can have it back.
But I must see you delete the video.
Otherwise, I...
I'll accuse you of harassing me.
This is why I recorded the video.
Whoever saw you climbing
the booth in the men's room
wouldn't believe you were harassed.
You...
You can dress yourself, right?
Put it on.
I...
Once I'm sure you want nothing from me,
I'll delete the video.
My business card in the pocket
has all my contact info.
Call the police if I go back on my word.
Return my coat.
What a small world, Mr. Lu.
You guys, guard the exits.
Don't let anyone
disturb our little conversation.
Mr. Yi, you brought
so many people to greet me?
Haven't you learned the lesson?
Don't be so smug.
You really think that video clip can
bring me down?
Get him!
I bet you don't know
what I did
before I established Pinshang.
What are you waiting for? Get him!
Hello to everyone
watching my livestream.
Today, we're checking out
Taylor's manuscript exhibition.
As you can see,
the gallery is crowded with visitors.
There you are. Get her.
Get both of them!
See? So crowded.
Hello, handsome.
Why do you look so serious?
There are 5000 viewers online right now.
Come on, face the screen
and say hello to our online friends.
This handsome young man
is too nervous to speak.
It's alright.
Over here, there's another handsome guy.
May I interview you briefly?
(Ten viewers, impressive.)
I'd love to. This way, please.
Handsome, want to join us?
Alright.
Let's stop teasing him.
Now,
let's head to Taylor's
manuscript exhibition.
There are over 20,000 viewers now.
Twenty thousand.
I'm not sure who's the charming one,
Taylor or the handsome guy next to me.
Please
give us a good interpretation
of the exhibition.
No problem, this way please.
(Conference Room)
Brave lady, you've got the guts
to fool Mr. Yi with your
ten ghost followers.
Mind your own business.
Anyway, it worked, didn't it?
Why did you help me?
You helped me in the men's room first.
You pissed me off by calling me a thief,
but
a favor received must be repaid.
It's in my nature to step forward.
Now we're even.
(Delete Video)
I have to go now.
Mom.
Do you realize the damage
you did to Yihua by being careless?
Mom, please calm down.
Grandma.
I could have stopped Lu Cenyang.
But that traitor Bu Ran sided with him.
Bu Ran?
Do you have a brain?
You think you can stop him
by catching him
in the art gallery?
He has something on you.
How did you happen to be there?
Grandma.
Mom.
A few years of
overseas education made her
quite something.
She caused a scene
on her first day back home,
framing Taylor
for stealing her design work.
The exhibition
went into utter chaos thanks to her.
Seven years ago,
you played tricks
and made me the guarantor
for your student loan.
You want to play
the same old trick again?
Let me ask you, Grandma.
Do you know?
Uncle and his family
are utter hypocrites.
They cut off the loan
when I was about to graduate,
and told my mentor
to harass me in exchange for his "help".
Mom...
Don't listen to her.
If you can't settle such a minor issue,
there's no point in continuing school.
You've failed to tell right from wrong.
No wonder you still can't
retire at this age.
Mom.
I'm okay.
You just got back. Greet Grandma.
Go on, be good.
Look how sharp-tongued you are.
You're just like your father.
You don't get to mention my dad.
You know why he's in prison.
He took the blame for you.
And how did you treat my mother and me?
If my dad knew you were bullying us,
he'd surely regret his decision.
Your father defied and betrayed me first
and gave up on you all afterward.
Mom.
Mom, what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
Get her to the hospital.
Mom, answer me.
Don't let her die here.
Son, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Mom, wake up.
Mom.
Doctor, please save my mom.
(Operating Room)
Family of Bu Huiyun.
(Cashier)
The balance is insufficient.
Please pay up.
Okay.
(Operating Room)
Doctor, how is my mom?
Cardiogenic shock
from coronary heart disease.
Thankfully, you brought her in on time.
Or she'd be in serious trouble.
She is no longer
in a critical condition.
Thank you, Doctor.
Considering the risk of infection,
we suggest the patient
stay for observation.
Okay.
(No Entry, Please Keep Quiet)
(Your mother needs further treatment.)
(Please pay the fee tomorrow.)
(Okay.)
(Yihua Group)
Greetings, Madam.
Speak up.
You can't afford to waste my time.
***
I can be valuable to the Yi family.
What can you prove with just a common
business card?
Grandma.
I guess you want to
deal with Lu Cenyang.
And I'm the only one in the family
he doesn't guard against.
I'd like to be your henchman
and a valuable member of the family.
Please cover my mom's medical expenses.
Come and talk to me when you truly
get close to him.
Bu Ran.
If you dare deceive me,
I will destroy everything you have.
Do you understand?
As long as
certain people don't interfere,
you can wait for good news.
Mr. Lin.
Mr. Liu.
Long time no see.
Cheers! Please sit.
(Hai Shi Construction Industry Summit)
Interesting gathering this year.
Yihua owns half of Hai Shi.
After all these years,
finally, someone can't stand it anymore.
You're talking about Lu Cenyang,
the boss of Pinshang Group,
who just showed up, right?
Mr. Lu.
(Hai Shi Construction Industry Summit)
Thank you.
He's here.
Mr. Lu.
Great to meet you.
I'm Lin Yaohua from
Yongsheng Building Materials.
Greetings, Mr. Lin.
I'm Lu Cenyang from Pinshang.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Liu Xu from Haohan Stars.
Mr. Liu, pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
I've always found Pinshang's designs
cutting-edge and trendy.
It turns out
there's a mastermind behind it.
Let's hang out more.
Alright.
Alright, of course.
As far as I know,
all of your businesses
are deeply tied to Yihua.
Pinshang may not be a large company,
but stylization
has always been our pursuit.
You're quite straightforward.
But it's hard to make it
without Yihua's support
in the local market.
Yihua leans on capital
and monopolizes the market.
If you choose to work with them,
you can only
remain as their followers.
The prosperity belongs to Yihua.
But you all take the blame
if anything goes wrong.
I wonder if any of you have the courage
to join me in creating something new.
Well...
I guess I was hasty.
We're making friends today.
No business talk.
Yeah.
Hello, everyone.
Isn't this Kerry from
Ruige Building Materials?
Sorry, Mr. Liu.
I got delayed.
This is...
Mr. Liu.
Aren't you going to introduce me?
You're putting me
in an awkward position.
This is Mr. Lu from Pinshang,
a promising young man.
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Nice to meet you.
I heard about your ambition just now.
I'm willing to side with you.
I hope we can
join hands to stop the Yi family
from monopolizing
the local market.
Mr. Lu, excuse me for a second.
See you around.
We have other guests, too.
Kerry, have a good chat with Mr. Lu.
Communicate.
Mr. Lu.
Shall we talk about the details
over a drink
somewhere quieter?
Of course. Please.
Alright.
Where are you?
Come back now.
I figured out
how to deal with Lu Cenyang.
It's the monthly
industry summit tonight.
Have Zihe find a social butterfly
to entertain Lu Cenyang.
I'll make him fall from grace.
Uncle's family always plays dirty.
But it offers me a chance
to get close to him.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Lu.
I admire your courage and insight.
You're much more pleasant
to talk to compared to those
old and cowardly foxes.
The price and quality of
the building materials I can offer you
are as tempting as my figure.
Aren't you afraid of
being blacklisted by Yihua?
It depends on
whether you are worth my trust.
You are a lady with stunning beauty.
I dare not enjoy your favor.
Otherwise, I'd become
the common enemy here.
I'd like to make friends with you.
Let's drink.
Cenyang, so you're here.
***
I've come to admire
the honey trap here.
Don't drive me away, okay?
Hello, I'm Bu Ran,
Cenyang's friend.
I'm Kerry.
Ms. Bu.
A nice figure is natural.
You can't force it.
A woman's beauty comes from within,
not from exposure.
I heard that Mr. Lu is immune to women.
It seems Ms. Bu is an exception.
Of course.
(Still not leaving?)
(Here's my lethal strike.)
I took a fancy to Cenyang
the first time I met him.
His handsome face
with its distinct features
and his robust chest muscles
caught my eye.
I simply couldn't resist.
Mr. Lu, I wish to collaborate with you.
But this confidante of yours
doesn't seem to welcome me.
You know
I'm the only one who would
choose you over Yihua.
You can't look down on me
just because I'm a woman.
Ms. Kerry.
I certainly didn't think that way.
Then we will be one after this drink.
Kerry.
I'll take Ran home later.
(Ran)
I really can't drink.
Mr. Lu, are you rejecting me?
I'll get you a designated driver.
Cenyang says he'd
drive me home, which means
he doesn't want a third wheel.
Ms. Bu.
Mr. Lu is so sweet to you.
Don't utilize his favoritism.
Mr. Lu, show me some respect
and finish this champagne.
I assure you that I'll offer
greater help than
Mr. Lin and Mr. Liu combined.
Mr. Lu is never the passive one
waiting to be chosen.
I drank it for him.
See you around.
Kerry, Ran can't drink.
I have to take her home.
Excuse us.
Hey, don't...
Don't touch the steering wheel.
Hey, sit properly.
It's too hot.
Do you know how dangerous it is?
It's just a champagne. Seriously?
I...
Are you seriously so drunk?
You do look quite handsome
from this angle.
You...
Stop it or I'm going to be mad.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
We will be one after this drink.
Calm down, I'll go get you some water.
Don't go.
Calm down. I bet it was Kerry.
Hey.
Slow down, be careful.
I need some air. It's too hot.
I have to tie you up.
Otherwise, you won't behave.
Don't move.
Breeze.
Come down from there.
Calm down.
Have some water.
Here.
Kiss me.
Come on. Give me a break!
I'm not kissing you!
Kisses. I want kisses.
Kiss kiss.
Don't come in. Sleep outside.
Control yourself.
Help!
Where am I?
Lu Cenyang, you hypocrite!
Come out!
How dare you
bring a girl home without permission!
Are you sure?
"Are you sure"?
Lu Cenyang, you're dead.
I will send you to prison.
Just wait
until you watch this.
You see?
Who forced her way in?
Who threw herself into my arms?
By the way,
pay for my clothes
you tore apart
and puked on.
You stayed over for one night.
Let's say it's 300 yuan
for a standard room.
And my mental distress...
I'll let you off
since you are a lady.
Reasonable demands, right?
How did you know I was there last night?
And how did you know
someone was setting me up?
Was Kerry the schemer?
Were you also trying to benefit?
I went there...
(I can't tell him
I'm from the Yi family.)
Because I saw someone
filming you sneakily!
You should
be grateful to me!
Besides, I agreed to compensate you.
It's your turn.
I basically saved your life.
How will you thank me?
If I knew you'd do this to me,
I might as well go with Kerry.
Stop.
I did that because
I was drugged, okay?
I knew you were drugged.
That's why I suffered
without complaint.
You saved me.
I can pretend nothing happened.
Hey.
Don't make it
sound like you're bullied, okay?
I...
I haven't even dated anyone.
I've lost out big time.
That's enough.
Get out.
I-I still have things to say.
Hear me out.
Don't... Hear me out!
Are you done?
No matter how you put it,
I sacrificed a lot for you.
Let's call it even.
But you must promise me something.
As long as you don't cling to me,
go ahead.
Who wants you?
I want to join Pinshang.
Pinshang
is not a place just for anyone.
There is no shortcut.
(If Grandma knew I failed,)
(she'd let my mom die.)
(No way. I have to get into Pinshang!)
♪Don't pity the journey
we agreed to embark on♪
♪For it has expired♪
♪There are too many
uncertainties and worries♪
♪It's okay. I'm especially clear-headed♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪And let the emotions pause
for a moment♪
♪I'm fortunate
to encounter such serendipity♪
♪I wish to be alone♪
♪In the boundless sky
that's just cleared up♪
♪And rinse my mood clean♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪Then give it a good thought♪
♪Whether to stop or continue loving you♪
♪I believe that solitude
is the night's message to me♪
♪It's pitiful for it
to become a trace of love♪