♪I can do everything for you♪
♪I will do everything for you♪
♪The faint light of the night flickers♪
♪Guiding me step by step towards you♪
♪Two independent hearts beat♪
♪Too closely as destined♪
♪You're in all my dreams♪
♪With eyes so mesmerizing♪
♪When you look at me, I'm very sure♪
♪It's love♪
♪I can do everything  for you♪
♪I will do everything  for you♪
♪We roam among the stars♪
♪We sleep under the most beautiful sky♪
♪We hold hands, saving each other♪
=Step By Step Love=
=Episode 21=
(Old Pal's)
(It turns out I only think of Qin Xun)
(when I'm upset.)
(I shouldn't treat him
like my emotional trash can.)
The most explosive news
on today's bidding site
is the video of Bu Ran
getting slapped by Ms. Hua.
I also heard
that Carry's sudden resignation
was also Bu Ran's doing.
It was her?
Of course, it was her.
What good do you think she is?
Mr. Lu doesn't like it
when colleagues talk about each other.
Yang,
do you have business
coming to the company so late?
I-I forgot my keys.
I've come back to get them.
Bu Ran finished the blueprints
for the ancient alley.
Be careful with your operations.
I don't know if she saved it.
Okay, I know.
You took leave
to do another set
of blueprints behind my back?
With what we learned
from the orphanage incident,
it was natural for me
to make an extra set
of alternative plans.
So you suspect
that it was Bu Ran
who leaked the blueprints?
I can only say what happened today
was an accident.
I simply asked Chen Manni
to innovate on Bu Ran's version.
This could indeed
increase the odds of winning.
Ultimately,
it was Yihua that embarrassed Bu Ran.
Not Pinshang.
And certainly not me.
Yes.
Today, you had the foresight
to turn the tide for the company.
But we have so many designers.
Even if you distrust Bu Ran,
why did you turn to Chen Manni?
Cease all collaborations
with Chen Manni.
As you started the company,
you said those of us
in the architecture industry
should always put the designers first.
Yet today, for Bu Ran's sake,
we have to turn away
such an excellent designer
as Chen Manni.
Mr. Lu,
you never used to
act so impulsively as you are now.
With such a big mistake,
don't you suspect Bu Ran at all?
Why do you want me to suspect her?
Do you expect me
to suspect that she leaked
the blueprints to Yihua?
We have known her for a long time.
She isn't that kind of person.
Fine, then you tell me.
Who did it?
So you had guessed it all along.
Why did you do that?
To drive Bu Ran out of Pinshang.
She is from the Yi family.
She shouldn't stay here.
You're being completely unreasonable.
Siqi has lost her memory.
But you might still remember
how Siqi got injured.
Dad jumped down from upstairs back then.
When I arrived at the scene,
I didn't react immediately.
I didn't notice a car coming towards me.
It was you who pushed me away.
You got this scar
because you got hurt in my place.
Do you remember anything now?
No.
Since you remember so clearly,
you must not let Siqi down, right?
Even if the person standing
in front of me today were Siqi,
my attitude would be the same.
Here are my little building blocks.
Thank you.
Here you are.
And mine too.
What a coincidence!
Not really.
I saw you pass by my shop.
You clearly wanted to see me,
but you didn't get in.
I thought you must have something
on your mind.
You followed me here?
You are impressive.
Did you get wronged?
It's nothing.
I have survived the Yi family.
I'm not someone who gets wronged easily.
There's just a little issue at work.
I need to reflect a bit.
You've come to see the kids.
It couldn't be a little issue.
It's been a long time
since I've seen the kids.
Being with them
makes me feel particularly at ease.
I even danced,
making up for the lack of exercise.
Don't hide it.
The kids can only heal your mood.
They can't solve the problem.
You should have told me.
An advisor who doesn't receive orders
for a long time
will get rusty.
That makes sense.
Actually, I do need you for something.
Find out
who leaked my blueprints to Yihua.
Okay. What about the reward?
I'll have my mom make
the world's most delicious
sweet and sour pork for you.
Deal.
Then
you go investigate.
I'll have my mom get ready.
Let's split up to increase efficiency.
Okay, fine.
I must have owed you in a past life.
Here.
I've been busy all day.
Being able to eat the food you made
is simply fantastic.
Come on.
If you like it, eat more.
Thank you.
She has just recovered from her illness.
As soon as she saw you,
she immediately had the energy to cook.
Thank you.
But you came alone this time.
Did you have a fight with Ran?
Yes.
That's why I came
to seek help from both of you.
You're quite frank.
I think before making Bu Ran believe me,
it's necessary to first gain your trust,
Mr. and Mrs. Yi.
My wife is swayed by good looks.
Seeing a handsome guy like you,
she'll certainly be easy to talk to.
Cenyang, to be honest with you,
when we knew Ran went to Pinshang,
we had once warned her
not to fall for you.
Of course, it wasn't because
we distrusted your character.
It's just that there are
too many misunderstandings
and hurt feelings between our families.
However, it's quite comforting that Ran
can learn something from you.
Mrs. Yi, rest assured,
I will definitely not let Bu Ran
suffer any harm.
Between her and me,
it was I who fell for her first.
She is the most sincere,
the kindest, and the bravest person
among the people I've met.
Today, at the renovation bid
for the ancient alley,
we competed fiercely with Yihua,
and many side issues
occurred in the process.
But the one thing I am certain of
is that Bu Ran won't be used by Ms. Hua.
After all, she is your daughter, Mr. Yi.
And she's the only daughter-in-law
my father ever approved of.
Cenyang,
you should know
that your father's death
had an inseparable connection with me.
I want to know
how you could come to forgive me.
Mr. Yi,
it was you who made
those anonymous warning calls,
right?
You already know?
Those things are easy
to find out if I wish to.
Over these years,
I've also been trying to understand
what happened back then.
Seven years ago,
you advocated for the merger
of the two companies,
utilizing Yihua's financial advantage
and the Lu family's project superiority
to join hands
through the industry's winter.
But someone introduced
harsh cost control standards
into the confirmed contract.
You know,
my father had an excessive pursuit
of details.
And they deliberately provoked him.
If he wanted to breach the contract,
he could only turn to you,
and you resigned at the crucial moment.
Later on, the Lus
were sued for a high amount
of damages for breach of contract.
I originally intended
to use my own resignation
to force Yihua to back down,
but as a result,
I have been separated from my family
for seven years.
And what's more unexpected is that
Mingyu didn't want
to be coerced by Yihua
and was forced to end his life.
Regarding this,
I am filled with regret and guilt.
Cenyang,
Ran and your father
are the same kind of people.
They only think about doing things well.
I can
guarantee my life on that.
Mr. Yi,
please rest assured.
Even if you
don't say these things today,
I would never doubt Bu Ran.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't come here for a meal.
We all know Ms. Hua's schemes.
If I let Bu Ran down,
she would instigate you to deal with me.
So...
That is not possible.
We won't become those kinds of people.
Mrs. Yi, please rest assured.
To take down the Yi Family,
given Yi Mincai
and Yi Zihe's capacities,
I could've used them
to make Ms. Hua doubt her life long ago.
The reason I didn't do that
is because I don't want
to become like Ms. Hua.
If the Yi family falls,
it will implicate
countless employees and customers.
I don't want
the tragedy of the Lu family
to be repeated by others.
Aren't you afraid
the Yi family will retaliate
because you're soft-hearted?
Being softhearted is not my weakness,
but the reason I hone myself
to become stronger.
I will become strong enough
to change Yihua's business philosophy.
As I have Bu Ran
and the support of you both,
I am very confident.
Today's accident
serves as a reminder for me.
I should not allow Bu Ran
to be vulnerable to blackmail.
Mrs. Yi,
I will take care
of all your future treatments.
We can't hide anything from you.
Don't worry about Ran.
We won't let outsiders
come between you two.
Mr. Yi,
actually, I can't find Bu Ran.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come
to you looking for a solution.
Can you ask Bu Ran where she is?
I'm really worried about her.
Okay.
I haven't found any concrete evidence
on my end.
But I think
Carry also used to work for Yihua.
After she left,
is it possible
that someone from your company
who was close to her
has taken over her role?
You're here.
Bu Ran.
It's pretty clear
that she betrayed the company.
Yet Mr. Lu has always favored her.
I have no idea
what tricks Bu Ran has used.
If she has any self-respect,
it would be best for her
to leave the company quietly.
Thinking about having to work with her
is simply unbearable.
Yang,
how do you know
that Mr. Lu is favoring me?
The video of you getting slapped
by Ms. Hua has been posted online.
And your conversation is very clear.
What else can you argue about?
Did you hear clearly what Ms. Hua said?
Ms. Hua said
that if I sold out Yihua,
she would not forgive me.
In other words, her attempt
to buy me out was unsuccessful.
Mr. Lu knows the full story.
And that's why he believes
in my loyalty.
Yet you continue to gossip here
and talk about favoritism.
That's right.
Favoritism means
he knows I'm wrong
and still covers for me.
But the video has already proven
I'm not wrong.
So why do you
insist on saying I'm wrong?
Only the guilty
call out 'Catch the thief'.
It couldn't be you
who stole the blueprints, could it?
Nonsense!
Last Saturday,
I saw you sneaking into the company
with my own eyes.
You even turned on the computer.
You were stealing the design.
I drew all the blueprints.
Do I need to sneak around on a Saturday
to steal them from the company computer?
You remember the time, location,
and what I did so clearly.
I think you're the one who stole them.
You!
By the way,
there is no surveillance
in the design department,
but the surveillance at the entrance
can tell us how long
you stayed at the company.
Stop falsely accusing me!
Before there is substantial evidence,
none should make unfounded remarks.
Are you all so idle?
Go back to work.
Ms. Yao,
how did you know Yihua would
steal my blueprints?
And you even prepared a second set
in advance.
Because I am clear about your identity,
as the secretary of Pinshang,
I have reason to suspect anyone
from the Yi family.
So you chose Chen Manni
just to upset me
and turn me against Mr. Lu, right?
Bu Ran,
everything I did was for the company.
As for what you think,
that's your business.
By the way,
Mr. Lu hasn't come to the office today.
If you want to complain,
go home and do it.
You are here. Have a seat.
(CEO Meng Kexin)
What are you doing?
I had someone steal the blueprints.
So what?
Mom should be very clear now
about who is more important
between you and me.
I am now the CEO of Yihua,
responsible for the company's
overall operations.
But I spoke well of you to Mom.
You can have my old office.
You are now the office director of Yihua
for internal affairs.
You wench!
You're even stealing
your husband's thunder.
I took this position
all for Zihe.
You'd better work with me
and do your best.
(CEO Yi Mincai)
Hello?
I've given you the money.
How dare you ask me for more?
Where are you?
Wait for me.
Leave and lay low.
Don't call me again.
Okay.
Mr. Yi,
you met with my employee secretly.
It was you
who made her steal the blueprints
from my company, right?
What stealing of plans?
We're having an affair.
Mr. Yi.
Nowadays, you can even
have an affair so openly?
That's truly admirable.
Yang,
if I disclose what happened
between you and Mr. Yi
to his wife,
do you know the consequences
of offending the Meng family?
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu, I was wrong.
Please spare me.
That depends on what Mr. Yi's stance is.
Mr. Yi,
let's make a deal.
If you promise me
that you won't make things hard
for Yi Minde and his family anymore,
I won't hold your bribing of Yang
against you.
We'll record a verbal guarantee
and call it a deal.
M-Mr. Yi,
I don't want this money anymore.
Please let Mr. Lu spare me.
Mr. Lu,
actually, I was very hesitant
at the time.
I didn't want to do that.
If...
If it weren't for Ms. Yao
reminding me at that time,
- I...
- That doesn't matter.
I only care about now.
If Mr. Yi doesn't agree,
Yang, as long as you agree
to be my witness,
I'll still let you go.
Lu Cenyang,
I agree.
I, Yi Mincai, assure you
that I will no longer pick
on the Yi Minde family.
Or else what?
You have plenty of ways to deal with me.
So what need is there for 'or else'?
M-Mr. Lu,
I-I will resign right now.
And I promise
never to speak ill of Bu Ran again.
Please spare me.
I want to marry my boyfriend.
But my boyfriend is average.
And my family is against it.
I want to seize love.
That's why I took the risk
of taking Yi Mincai's money.
Love is important.
But you caused a misunderstanding
between Bu Ran and me.
How do we reckon it?
I'm sorry, Mr. Lu.
I wish you and Bu Ran all sweetness
and happiness forever.
Please spare me this once.
She spoke to my heart.
You decide.
Yang,
take back your blessings and leave.
Wait.
Her blessings are quite nice.
Why take them back?
You really have a way.
I simply suspected Yang.
Yet you specifically followed her here.
If you want to express gratitude,
just say it.
I did it to help clear you
of the suspicion
of betraying the company.
My suspicion has been cleared.
But the company's actions
have left a designer,
who's been loyal to you,
disheartened.
Wait, the car is over there.
No, thank you.
Are you still mad?
Ms. Yao's actions did put you
in a difficult position.
I apologize for her.
You don't need to apologize
for her behavior.
I just want to know
if it was your idea for her
to do the second set of plans.
Of course not.
And you didn't choose Chen Manni?
Isn't that obvious?
I already told Ms. Yao
to terminate the collaboration
with Chen Manni.
There's no need for that.
After all, the design in the bid
was drawn by her.
But that was an adjustment
based on your groundwork.
If it weren't
for your all-night work earlier,
they wouldn't have finished
such complex blueprints
so quickly later.
Are you still mad?
Not really.
I just feel a bit uncomfortable inside.
Business competition is no child's play.
Ms. Yao was considering
the company's interests.
And I can understand.
After all, my identity is special.
Don't worry about your identity.
Your identity
doesn't matter to me at all.
All I care about
is that you are you.
If you're still feeling uncomfortable,
I'll take you
to a place where I usually
relax and unwind.
If it's singing,
foot baths, or massages,
I will pass.
It's too tacky.
Bu Ran,
is that the image
you have of me in your heart?
♪We sleep under the most beautiful sky♪
Let's go. It's really fun.
Come on!
It's 25 yuan for each net.
Alright.
Hello.
This is a game for kids.
You want me to play this?
I want to play too.
What? Do you feel embarrassed?
So you brought me here
to toughen up my spirit, huh?
If you feel uncomfortable
using Chen Manni's
design,
you should toughen up
your own inner strength.
Let me show you my special skill.
How about that?
Don't mind how others see you.
Just focus on catching fish.
Kido, let's have a competition.
Look, I caught another one.
Having you by my side,
I feel like my luck is better today.
You just touched it, and my net broke.
Our auras do not align.
Come on.
Have another one.
See?
By working together,
our might is doubled.
Over here.
Another one.
Let go. I'll play on my own.
You've been wronged the most today.
So, you can do whatever you want.
Have you really never doubted me?
Never.
We've agreed to trust each other.
After the incident,
the only thing I worried about
was that you would avoid me.
That's why I ran to your home
to ask your parents for help.
You seemed
to have asked the wrong people.
They haven't even made a single call
to speak well of you.
That's because
they trust the relationship between us.
Don't get too cocky.
Then, let's have a competition
to see who catches more fish today.
If you catch more than me,
I'll let you
join the ancient alley's renovation.
Okay.
Then I'll show you
whether my heart is strong enough.
I forgot to tell you.
To earn the tuition for studying abroad,
I used to run a fish-catching stall.
Impressive.
♪I really want to take you
to the castle♪
♪I hope you don't easily
reject my invitation♪
♪Without any other disturbances♪
Watch out.
♪Let the castle be surrounded by love♪
Son,
what are you doing?
Picking up girls.
All you know is that.
Do something serious.
Mom has already told me
that you've been reinstated.
But grandma gave you the chance
because she lost again
to Pinshang
and had no one else to use.
Dad,
you need to work hard.
You brat!
You're lecturing your dad now, huh?
Do I need your lecturing?
I'm only responsible
for the internal affairs now.
I can't directly confront Lu Cenyang.
So I will have to borrow your hands.
But I need to pursue Yao Lefei.
I don't have time for you.
Why her?
She is Lu Cenyang's secretary.
However,
it's not like it's impossible.
Have you ever thought
that with Lu Cenyang in the way,
you won't have an opportunity?
So you need to cause some trouble
for Lu Cenyang
to keep him busy.
Dad, do you have any ideas?
I've looked at Pinshang's proposal.
They demand that the ancient alley
be restored to its original state.
The residents
are already sick
of those dilapidated houses.
They want to take this chance
to build tall buildings.
We, on the other hand,
should stir up their emotions
and encourage them to protest.
Lu Cenyang wouldn't dare
to be assertive with them, would he?
Bribing a few residents
wouldn't be hard.
But
I'm out of money now.
I have some.
I'll give it to you.
I told you to rest for a few days,
but you came too.
Ms. Wang invited me to eat.
And you came uninvited.
You think I'm a burden?
You've prepared hangover medicine
and filled
the thermos with honey water, right?
You followed me here because you knew
why I came.
It's your work time.
And yet, you came here.
There must be a problem
with the ancient alley project.
And Ms. Wang is hosting. It means
that you are negotiating
with the residents.
Drinking will be involved.
It's worth bringing you along
since you've guessed so much.
It's not a big deal.
Some residents disagree
with our choice to use old materials
to preserve the cultural charm
of the ancient alley.
We'll have a meal with them
and explain our design philosophy
to them
so that we can feel a bit closer
to each other.
It won't be an easy meal.
If there's something like this again,
remember to bring me.
Or you're treating me like an outsider.
I'm not treating you like an outsider.
How about I take care of the drinking
and you drive me home later?
Remember not to drink a drop of alcohol.
(They don't seem to be)
(the type that we
can easily get close to.)
(It's alright.)
(If we get into a fight, I have you.)
(If you get drunk later,)
(you go back on your own.)
Gentlemen, let me pour the wine for you.
Mr. Lu,
we
have lived in this alley for years.
The truth is,
we've long been tired
of these decrepit houses
with their broken tiles.
The renovation
of the alley is meant to serve us.
Yes.
Most of the young men who have stayed
in this alley
aren't even married yet.
That's right.
Why is that?
It's because the women
despised our poverty.
We do not even have a decent place.
Marrying us would mean
a life of hardship.
At least now there's an opportunity.
So, in terms of building materials,
you must use the new types,
and they need to be eco-friendly.
Right.
Mr. Lu, the thing is,
we didn't want to trouble you too much.
We want our places
to be like what's on TV:
a bit more upscale, spacious,
and attractive.
And that's enough.
Don't leave us with something old
by spending all the money,
manpower,
and resources. It will be meaningless.
Right?
Mr. Lu, you wouldn't want to see us
remain single for life, would you?
Exactly.
I have no ill intent.
I know you often come for acupuncture.
I want to keep you company.
I'm serious about pursuing you.
What joke are you making?
I simply helped you out at the bar.
And you fell for me?
That's ridiculous.
It has always been me
stepping in for women.
It's the first time a woman
has helped me out.
Who else would I fall for?
Love is mutual.
And I find you extremely repulsive.
You just work for Lu Cenyang.
No need to distinguish the factions.
You can quit your job
and let me support you.
If you want to work,
we can open a family-run shop.
Still no?
Do you like Lu Cenyang?
Shut up.
If you like Lu Cenyang, just give it up.
He won't dump Bu Ran.
Listen.
He announced
that she is his girlfriend,
and he still loves her even knowing
she is a Yi.
He disregards even Pinshang.
And you?
He has never fallen for you.
You're just a secretary to him.
Here.
You all know Mr. Lu.
And this
is Bu Ran, the designer
who renovated my house.
Look.
How beautifully my house is designed.
Now, my son and his family
are also visiting more often.
You guys should listen more
to the experts.
They are all nice folks.
Feel free to say whatever you want.
The reason you guys can't get married
is not simply because
your places are not good.
In my opinion,
there are two issues
that need to be addressed.
The first is income.
As long as we increase
the alley's tourism appeal,
your income will naturally increase.
The second is mindset.
Your good taste is nurtured
by such beautiful surroundings
every day.
Just maintain that.
Make sure not to be easily led astray.
I have some similar cases on my phone.
You can all take a look at the effects.
The actual results are really beautiful.
Here.
Sir, have a look.
This is not bad.
It's good, right?
Look.
Look at this. It's really nice.
It is good.
Hello, Ms. Yao.
What's up?
Brother,
it's Siqi.
Wait for me. I'll be right over.
Okay.
Sorry, everyone.
It's urgent.
We need to go back first.
Mr. Lu,
your call came at quite a coincidence.
You don't want to drink with us?
Wait, Mr. Lu.
Ms. Wang has the wine and food ready.
And you're leaving us now?
That's disrespect.
Gentlemen,
I'm the person in charge
of this project.
I will stay.
Mr. Lu's presence
will only affect my performance.
Don't talk nonsense.
Cenyang is one of our own.
He must have urgent business
to attend to.
Ms. Bu's presence
represents Mr. Lu.
- Okay.
- Fine.
Mr. Lu,
if you have something to do, go ahead.
Sir, Bu Ran cannot hold her liquor.
I hope you can...
Rest assured.
Everyone understands.
We're here to be happy. Don't worry.
Don't overdo it. I'll be right back.
Ms. Wang,
don't let Bu Ran drink.
Call me if you need it.
Okay.
The boss who loves to nag has left.
Shouldn't we give him a round
of applause to send him off?
Let's continue.
Where were we just now?
Brother!
You brat, you're finally back.
Haven't I always been here?
Finally, the day has come.
You siblings should have a good talk.
Thank you, Dr. Ma.
Thanks to her
being more cooperative lately,
my reputation has been saved.
By the way,
did I interrupt your work
by suddenly calling you over?
You're my sister.
You've regained your memory.
I'd leave behind any work for this.
Brother,
let's find a time
to pay respects to Dad.
We should also inform Mr. Li.
Also,
I will tell the Yi family.
Haven't they always wanted to find me
and then use me against you?
I want to tell them in person
that they can dream.
Okay.
As long as you're happy,
you can do anything.
Whatever else you want to do,
just tell me.
There's a tricky matter at hand
that requires your help.
You have to help me
get rid of the annoying Yi Zihe.
Yi Zihe?
♪Don't pity the journey
we agreed to embark on♪
♪For it has expired♪
♪There are too many
uncertainties and worries♪
♪It's okay. I'm especially clear-headed♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪And let the emotions pause
for a moment♪
♪I'm fortunate
to encounter such serendipity♪
♪I wish to be alone♪
♪In the boundless sky
that's just cleared up♪
♪And rinse my mood clean♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪Then give it a good thought♪
♪Whether to stop or continue loving you♪
♪I believe that solitude
is the night's message to me♪
♪It's pitiful for it
to become a trace of love♪