♪I can do everything for you♪
♪I will do everything for you♪
♪The faint light of the night flickers♪
♪Guiding me step by step towards you♪
♪Two independent hearts beat♪
♪Too closely as destined♪
♪You're in all my dreams♪
♪With eyes so mesmerizing♪
♪When you look at me, I'm very sure♪
♪It's love♪
♪I can do everything  for you♪
♪I will do everything  for you♪
♪We roam among the stars♪
♪We sleep under the most beautiful sky♪
♪We hold hands, saving each other♪
=Step By Step Love=
=Episode 18=
Qin.
Don't be mad at me, alright?
Why would I be mad at you?
Don't mess with the stuff in the store.
If Xu sees it later,
I'll be punished again.
I should have told you
about the night before last.
I promise it won't happen again.
You value a lover over friends.
We've washed so many
dishes together overseas.
Will you talk to me again?
I have chores from yesterday.
I have to do them.
If you'll excuse me.
Then, I'm leaving.
I'm off.
I'm really leaving now.
It seems to be raining.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Qin.
Here you go.
♪In the muggy weather after rain♪
♪So quiet that I can hear my breath♪
♪The migrating clouds and birds
fly solo, a seat now vacant♪
♪Drifting on their journey♪
♪Our memories are about to expire♪
♪Time teaches us a lesson♪
Before your friend forgives you,
take good care of yourself first.
♪I become more and more afraid
to confirm our relationship.♪
♪Should they intersect or remain
parallel without meeting♪
♪Take a deep breath
and pause the emotions.♪
♪I'm fortunate
to encounter such serendipity♪
♪I wish to be alone♪
♪In the boundless sky
that's just cleared up♪
♪Rinse my mood clean♪
♪Take a good breath and think it over.♪
♪Whether to stop or continue loving you♪
♪I believe that solitude
is the night's message to me♪
♪It's pitiful for it to become♪
♪A trace of love♪
You're burning up.
Do you have a thermometer?
Look at you,
not checking the weather forecast,
not putting on more when it's cold,
and not using an umbrella when it rains.
Caught a cold, right?
It's okay. I'll just drink more water.
Don't move.
Stay put, alright?
You will rest well.
And I will take good care of you.
It's just a cold.
Don't make a fuss.
Overbearing much?
Take the medicine.
Come on.
Take the medicine and have a good sleep.
Sweat it out,
and the fever will go away.
Why take a photo when you're sick?
I want to record
every little bit of our lives
for us to look at when we're old.
That's a nice idea.
My girlfriend is so cute.
I want to take a photo too.
(Post to Moments)
Are you crazy? Delete it now!
The more aboveboard we are together,
the more it reassures
those who care about you.
I made it official.
It's no big deal.
Let's go. I'll take you to bed.
Do I look handsome?
Not handsome, but stunning.
Come on, have a good sleep.
Let's eat something good
when you wake up.
But I can't sleep.
When the children
at the orphanage can't sleep,
do you comfort them this way too?
You're sick today.
That makes you a child too, Bu Ran.
Go to sleep.
Mr. Lu made it official.
Did you see it?
The way Mr. Lu looks at Bu Ran
is full of love.
So envious.
When will it be my turn to be in love?
Right?
So it's true.
Yes, look, look.
Look, oh my Gosh!
Ms. Hua, I just found out...
How come it's you?
Ms. Hua knows everything
on Bu Ran and Lu Cenyang.
So it's because you've been
keeping an eye on them.
Ms. Meng, what can I do for you?
Sit down.
I wanted to talk to you
because I want you to cooperate with me
and break up Bu Ran and Lu Cenyang
so that Ms. Hua will be utterly
disappointed with Bu Ran.
Ms. Meng, you went
to great lengths to find me
just to have me break them up?
Bu Ran seems not to be
regarded highly by Ms. Hua,
but she is not entirely forsaken.
If Bu Ran climbs up
the ranks of Pinshang,
Yi Minde would have a chance
to turn things around.
By then, Ms. Hua
will be even less tolerant
of our family.
But you can't poach from Ms. Hua.
What if she finds out?
My mother-in-law is getting old.
How could she get angry
at her daughter-in-law for helping out?
Even if she did get angry,
she couldn't do anything to me.
But as for you,
if you refuse me,
I will let Lu Cenyang know
that you are Ms. Hua's spy.
When that happens,
you will be completely useless.
Between two evils, choose the lesser.
Just be a good fence-sitter,
and you will benefit from both sides.
Why not do it?
Ms. Meng,
if you want me to break up
Lu Cenyang and Bu Ran,
I might not be capable.
However, there is someone
who can help you out.
I heard that Ms. Hua
is currently investigating
Bu Ran's close friend, Qin Xun.
I'm sure you're aware of how important
Qin Xun is to Bu Ran.
I will talk to him.
But you are also
an important part of my plan.
Ms. Meng.
A token of appreciation.
You know I'm not helping you
for your coffee beans.
You helped me solve
the trouble my child faced abroad,
and I am very grateful to you.
This is just a small gesture from me.
You know what I really want,
so stop beating around the bush.
Lu Cenyang is very tight-lipped.
I brought out Mr. Lu's old photos,
but I couldn't find out about Lu Siqi.
Say something useful.
Why did you keep
Bu Ran's lackey, Qin Xun?
He is the child
of an old friend of mine.
He's handsome and sweet,
perfect for attracting customers.
I waited for so long
before coming to you.
Do you think
that's what I wanted to hear?
Even if you don't think about yourself,
think about your child's future.
If you continue to be evasive with me,
I cannot guarantee
that your daughter
will graduate smoothly.
Qin Xun...
Qin Xun is the biological
son of Lu Mingyu.
He hates Lu Mingyu.
That's more like it.
Thank you for the coffee.
Best wishes to your child.
Hey, this is Old Pal's.
Two cups of Blue Mountain
coffee delivered where?
Sure thing.
If you pay the delivery fee, I'll do it.
Mr. Yi didn't look for me
just for Old Pal's coffee, right?
Ever since you helped
Lu Cenyang deal with Taylor,
I have started investigating you.
I also know
that you are the biological
son of Lu Mingyu.
Your father has never acknowledged you.
Our Yi Family defeated him,
indirectly helping you get some payback.
I do think
we can have a pleasant talk.
You've investigated me so thoroughly.
Could it be that you want my help
to take on Lu Cenyang together?
Lu Cenyang has stolen
your father's love,
and he's also taken Bu Ran.
Let's join forces.
As long as you help me break up
Lu Cenyang and Bu Ran,
then,
the Yihua shares that Lu Cenyang wants,
you can take them for a dime.
Once a man has money,
naturally, he'll have the confidence
to vie for a woman.
Sorry, but you have
the wrong person.
Don't be in a rush to refuse, eh?
You can't make the decision now,
but soon enough
Lu Cenyang will take
everything that's yours.
Yi Mincai is going to make a move again.
I must tell Bu Ran ASAP.
Navigate to Pinshang.
I'll go get your phone for you.
Thanks!
When you came with colleagues
from the Design Dept.,
you didn't take pictures.
But this time, you had
to use up your battery.
What if someone needs to find you?
Wouldn't it be good if you
could find me straight away?
Did you talk to the boss
about takeaway?
Of course.
You said Qin Xun
loves vegetable with pork,
stewed duck, and deep fried tofu.
I've ordered them.
Good.
Remember the noodle shop
I told you about?
I've packed the best dishes
they have for you.
Don't have lunch yet.
I'll bring them over to you.
Where are you now?
I need to talk to you.
Noodle shop?
Seeing your good appetite
makes me relieved.
You've spent so much time with me.
If I don't get well,
the company will lose
so much big business.
You sound like the boss's lady now.
I have to think about you.
You're thinking so much about me.
You weren't at the company
when I went this morning.
Did you go to Old Pal's?
I guess you were, while I was working,
dealing with the distractions first.
One should not
underestimate the insight
of an excellent designer.
When I went there,
Qin Xun had already gone out.
Qin Xun must be waiting
to forgive me in person.
I'll find him myself.
Thank you for your efforts and trust.
And for the feast.
That's it? Saying thanks verbally?
Close your eyes.
Why?
Just close them.
Hello, Mr. Yi.
I'm interested in your proposal.
Ms. Yao,
Have you noticed
that Bu Ran and Mr. Lu
left the company together at noon?
Bu Ran's true identity in the Yi Family
is no secret anymore.
Why wouldn't Mr. Lu's sister
make any moves?
What reaction do you expect from Siqi?
To have a big fight
with Mr. Lu at the company?
That's not what I meant.
I was just thinking
someone should come out
to advise Mr. Lu, right?
We can't let Bu Ran
be the lady of Pinshang alone.
Besides, the boss dating an employee
can definitely affect work performance.
Otherwise, why would there
be so many companies
that explicitly prohibit
office romances?
Bu Ran has made
many contributions to the company.
Besides, as the secretary,
how could I go about sowing discord
between the boss and his younger sister?
You've already been made an ally
by Bu Ran's PR, haven't you?
Forget I said anything.
Hello? Who's this?
Lu Siqi.
I'm your brother.
Go tell Lu Cenyang
that I have found you.
Bu Ran, you go back to work first.
What happened?
Someone called me claiming
to be my biological brother.
They knew my identity
and wanted to meet with me.
Is it the person
Dad has been looking for?
I'm not sure yet.
I don't know if it's true.
Dad's been searching for so long,
yet he hasn't shown up.
Regardless,
I'll go and meet him.
Okay.
But...
Don't worry.
Hello?
Boss.
He said he saw you appear
and refused to meet.
Mr. Lu.
Hello?
Who is this?
How can you not recognize my voice?
It's Yi Mincai.
Did you make that call?
What call?
Mr. Lu, before my call, were you aware
that Lu Minyu's true son
has appeared?
Speak. What do you want?
I don't want much.
Just break up with Bu Ran
and make it public.
Do you think I would agree?
If you refuse to do as I say,
everyone will know
that Lu Mingyu abandoned
his wife and child.
With Lu Mingyu's son's announcement,
don't even think about covering it up.
What do you think
your sister Lu Siqi
would feel about that?
What's the situation?
The person
who made the call used a voice changer,
and I had the IT and Security department
look up the phone number
and found out it was spoofed.
People who know you're Lu Siqi
didn't just appear out of nowhere.
So, what Yi Mincai said
might actually be true.
The person who called you
was indeed your half-brother.
Dad always used to mention
him in front of me,
but I've never met him.
Why would he show up like that?
By the way,
how did Yi Mincai know about it?
Could he know that I am Lu Siqi?
Rest assured,
given Yi Mincai's personality,
if he knew you were Lu Siqi,
he would come to find you immediately,
instead of calling you.
I'm guessing your brother,
for some special reason,
chose to cooperate
with Yi Mincai for now.
But he didn't
tell him that you are Lu Siqi.
Which is why Yi Mincai wants
to use this to blackmail you.
He wants me to break up with Bu Ran.
Did you agree?
No way.
Right now, we don't know
what kind of tactics he will use next.
But what I can be sure of is
someone would know.
Carry.
So you don't need to worry.
Take good care of yourself.
For the sake of caution,
don't be alone
starting today.
In that case,
can I stay at Fortune Pavilion?
Bu Ran still doesn't know your identity.
So you have to stay
at the company's appointed hotel.
Rest assured.
I'll send men on point duty.
Bu Ran had someone deliver it at noon.
It's gotten cold now.
(Remember the noodle shop
I told you about?)
(I've packed the best dishes
they have for you.)
(Don't have lunch yet.)
(I'll bring them over to you.)
♪The start of a story is always perfect♪
♪Savoring each moment over and over♪
♪No matter where I go,
I'm followed by your presence♪
♪Deciding on someone so absolutely♪
♪I held back tears to bring you back,
but you stepped away♪
♪Some fulfillments can also be♪
♪Just a bit less than perfect♪
♪Each time I deliberately
turn my back is because♪
♪I'm afraid of my tears being seen♪
♪What exactly is wrong
and what is right♪
♪I should step back♪
♪Every time you smile
so beautifully, I will♪
♪Deepen the sorrow in my heart♪
(You and I)
(have never been of a romantic nature.)
(Although we've been through
a lot together,)
(I can't mistake being moved
for being in love.)
♪I'm afraid of my tears being seen♪
♪What exactly is wrong
and what is right♪
♪I should step back♪
♪Every time you smile
so beautifully, I will♪
♪Deepen the sorrow in my heart♪
♪Your love is too perfect♪
♪I should defend it♪
You're still up.
I can't sleep.
Did anything happen
with Ms. Yao and you?
I've never seen you so nervous.
It's nothing.
Just some work matters.
Although I don't know
what happened between you.
But when you're in trouble
and I can't help,
it feels terrible.
I know.
(Yi Mincai)
Uncle.
Don't worry.
Good night.
It's me, Yi Mincai.
For the industry gathering,
you should come in person tomorrow.
As long as you declare that you have
no connection whatsoever with Bu Ran
in front of the entire industry,
I will preserve some dignity
for your foster father and sister.
Was that a threat?
Mr. Lu.
Between Bu Ran and Lu Siqi,
someone has to get hurt.
If I had to choose,
the sister is more important, right?
Was my uncle involved in today's matter?
What is he doing now?
Just some ridiculous petty tricks.
It's not your turn to take action yet.
Since we've already started dating,
we should
face difficulties together, right?
I know.
I am capable of solving it.
Can I take care of this matter?
What exactly are you hiding from me?
Either it's because my uncle
did something again,
or it's because of my identity,
that you can't tell me.
What do you mean by that?
I mean you're wary of me
because I'm from the Yi Family.
Or that you have a relationship
with Ms. Yao that I can't know.
Do you not trust me that much?
It's you who doesn't trust me.
Ms. Meng,
you went to great lengths to find me
just to have me break those two up, huh?
Bu Ran seems not to be
regarded highly by Ms. Hua,
but she is not entirely forsaken.
If Bu Ran climbs up
the ranks of Pinshang,
Yi Minde would have a chance
to turn things around.
By then, Ms. Hua
will be even less tolerant
of our family.
Ms. Meng, what do you
want me to do then?
It's simple.
Find someone to pretend
to be Lu Cenyang's girlfriend
and accompany him
to our industry's monthly gathering.
Do you want Lu Cenyang
to publicly dump Bu Ran?
Mr. Lu.
We should get going.
It's you.
You're dressed
just like the leading lady
in a palace drama.
When declaring sovereignty,
being the leading lady
is very satisfying.
A large sandwich.
A large fruit salad
and a strong cocktail.
Are you still mad at me?
It's not worth it.
You're eating a lot.
Can't you tell I'm
in a really bad mood today?
Being with Lu Cenyang,
getting upset was bound
to happen sooner or later.
The sandwich can satisfy you.
If you want to drown your sorrows,
don't look for me.
I won't let you do it.
Don't think that Lu Cenyang's
post on Moments
is such an amazing thing.
In my opinion,
he's using the fact
that you've never been in love.
Haven't you seen the gossip news?
Those who are truly recognized
by the CEO as girlfriends
are openly taken to social events
to meet more people.
You
are the hidden mistress at Pinshang
at most.
I've been upset all day.
Did you have to make it worse?
Is there any wine or not?
Your discomfort has only just begun.
Drink this first.
If you don't serve, I'll order takeaway.
Today, I need drinks
to have the strength
to contend with Lu Cenyang.
I just don't get it.
What on earth is going on
that he just has to keep it from me?
If he's hiding it,
there are matters
that you shouldn't know about.
Matters that I shouldn't know about?
Mr. Lu, long time no see.
(Hai City Construction Industry Summit)
Mr. Lu.
You never bring a female companion
whenever you come.
Always alone.
Mr. Wang, you are wrong there.
Mr. Lu is a young talent.
How could he possibly
not have a girlfriend?
Speaking of which, I've recently
heard a piece of gossip
saying that Mr. Lu
is dating the designer Bu Ran, right?
You seem quite interested
in my private life.
We're just curious
that what kind of woman
can date you, Mr. Lu?
- Why come here?
- Ms. Yao.
I am more suitable
to play this act with you.
What are you doing here?
Carry, you got it wrong.
I should be the one here today
for this occasion.
What do you know?
I know what you're to do today.
So, for your mission today,
I'll take care of it.
I thought you were never
interested in Mr. Lu.
I know that Mr. Lu
came under pressure today.
Compared to you,
the identity of a girlfriend
is more convincing on me.
You...
You don't know the story behind today,
so you can't replace me.
Is that so?
I heard that Mr. Yi and Ms. Meng
will both be here today.
Aren't you afraid of revealing
your identity in public?
Listen to me.
I'll take care of this matter.
You can complete the task
without getting involved.
Win-win, right?
This is Ms. Yao.
I suppose you have met her.
Hello, Ms. Yao.
Carry has put effort into her task.
I thought she would come herself,
but unexpectedly,
she actually found someone
more suitable than her.
♪Don't pity the journey
we agreed to embark on♪
♪For it has expired♪
♪There are too many
uncertainties and worries♪
♪It's okay. I'm especially clear-headed♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪And let the emotions pause
for a moment♪
♪I'm fortunate
to encounter such serendipity♪
♪I wish to be alone♪
♪In the boundless sky
that's just cleared up♪
♪And rinse my mood clean♪
♪Take a good deep breath♪
♪Then give it a good thought♪
♪Whether to stop or continue loving you♪
♪I believe that solitude
is the night's message to me♪
♪It's pitiful for it
to become a trace of love♪