[English subtitles are available]
[Follow Your Heart]
[Episode 21]
[Jingsheng Hall]
Why are you all at my house?
What happened to my face?
Surprise!
You don't need to wear your mask anymore.
My nose!
I performed
plastic surgery on your nose.
Plastic surgery!
You...
Jiang Xinbai!
Don't think
that you can decide everything for me
just because we've become allies!
Why are you
only scolding me?
Get out!
From now on, we'll stay out of each other's business.
Yan Nanxing.
His nose is fixed,
but he has lost his mind.
All of you, get out!
I don't want to see you!
Could you please
excuse us?
Okay.
Bieli.
Gaya and I hope
you can let go of your obsession
and stop wearing your mask.
Brother.
Gaya is gone.
You should move on,
and so should I.
Mr. Shang,
you're a great hero.
You can definitely pull yourself together.
No matter what happens,
I'll be with you.
Mr. Shang.
Did you stay up all night?
Sai'er.
Go somewhere with me.
Gaya.
This mask
is made of the ore from your hometown.
It carries your love for your hometown.
I buried it here
facing your hometown.
When you get homesick,
look into the distance.
I will protect Brother.
Please bless him
and keep him safe.
Gaya.
I'm not coming here again.
I'm moving on.
Lady Gaya,
please bless Mr. Shang.
[Steps Towards Success]
There's no need to clean this place today.
You may leave.
Chancellor.
Why are you here?
I'm here to...
You followed me?
Why would I?
Since you knew my name,
you could find out
that I'm a chancellor at the Imperial Academy.
You came here
to make me notice you.
That's not true.
I've seen many people like you,
a calculating social climber.
Just give up.
Although I don't despise you because you're a slave,
it doesn't mean
I'll like you.
This...
This is my uniform.
I'm supposed to be here.
You passed out that day.
I took you home to let you rest.
I didn't know you were a chancellor
until we had dinner together.
But I had no other intentions after I found out,
nor did I think too much.
I just thought of the meal
as entertaining a friend
at home.
A friend?
You
consider me a friend?
Yes.
A friend.
Do you know
what kind of friends I need?
What kind of friends do you need?
Only those who can
always stay by my side
and be my people
no matter what happens
can be my friends.
Be your people?
So,
stop saying
that you can be my friend.
It has nothing to do
with whether you're a slave or not.
Suoluo.
Dean Yan.
I asked you to clean this place up.
How dare you slack off
and disturb the chancellor?
You asked him to clean this place up?
Yes.
His name is Liu Ruoqian.
He's the slave student the Imperial Academy
made an exception to admit.
He told us
he wanted to work in order to earn tuition.
So, we asked him
to do some physical labor.
However,
as a slave,
you're not qualified to take the imperial exams
and can never be an official.
What's the use of studying
at the Imperial Academy?
Why are you still standing here?
Go away.
Is becoming an official the only purpose of study?
People study to make themselves
upright,
well-mannered, and benevolent.
Dean Yan, as a teacher,
how can you judge your student
based on traditional values?
I didn't mean to humiliate him.
I just wanted
to teach him some rules.
Chancellor.
Dean Yan.
Please don't argue about me.
Since I was a child,
I've heard many humiliating words
like this.
If I cared about these words,
I wouldn't be studying at the Imperial Academy.
Although I'm a slave,
I'm not ashamed of it.
No matter what others say,
it can't hurt me.
I'll take my leave.
Suoluo.
Give some of my salary
to Liu Ruoqian
as his pay.
Don't tell him it's from me.
Just tell him he got a pay rise.
Suoluo.
You are too kind!
-He‘s just a slave...
-We're at the Imperial Academy.
Please call me Chancellor.
Yes.
Chancellor.
I brought you some fresh fruit.
No, thanks.
I have something to do.
[Shang Residence]
Although your nose has grown back,
it will take some time
to get your sense of smell back.
It's okay.
I got this.
I will get
Mr. Shang's sense of smell back.
I never owe anyone.
If there's anything you want me to do,
just let me know.
Don't mind if I do.
Actually,
I want you
to find someone for me.
I know who you want to find.
Boss,
you want to find
the boy who saved you, right?
The Inspection Office
is better
at finding people than the Jinwu Guards.
Why don't you ask Jiang Xinbai to help you?
I don't want him
to worry about this anymore.
So,
I can only ask you for help.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bravo!
Chancellor.
We meet by chance this time.
I didn't follow you.
I know.
I misjudged you
at the Imperial Academy today.
Don't worry about it.
I really don't mind it.
Chancellor.
Let me take these.
Thank you.
Chancellor.
Someone from the academy told me
you gave me a pay rise.
Thank you.
You deserve it.
Are you going this way too?
I'm carrying these books for you.
Let me walk with you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bookstore.
Then I'll go to the bookstore with you.
It's late.
Why isn't he back yet?
Even if he doesn't want to come home for dinner, he should change his dressing.
Ms. Yan.
Where is your lord?
He's been reading the file
on Li Wufang's case
in the file room since noon.
You can go in.
I'll stay out.
Thank you.
You only care
about the case.
Why didn't you go home early to change your dressing?
Sit still.
Let's do it.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Taking off your clothes.
How can I change your dressing with your clothes on?
I don't think it's appropriate.
What are you shy about?
I also
changed your dressing at home.
We're not at home after all.
We're at the Inspection Office.
What are you afraid of?
There's no one else here.
Anyway...
This feels strange.
You're so troublesome.
Okay.
Let's get started.
What now?
Actually,
my wound
has almost healed.
I knew it.
If you don't want to change your dressing,
you should at least take the oral medication.
Luckily,
I was smart.
See? I've prepared it.
Alright.
It hasn't turned cold.
Here.
Let me feed you.
It's not hot anymore.
I'll blow on it for you.
Okay.
It's cooler now.
Wait.
I see.
Is Chief Constable Jiang
afraid
of bitterness?
Who said I'm afraid of bitterness?
Then drink it.
Drink it.
Here.
The bitter taste is gone, right?
♫Sit with you at night and listen to the wind♫
Yes.
♫When the wind flutters, the heart does too♫
♫Step by step, no words are spoken♫
♫Barged into sight♫
♫When did your figure grow hazy?♫
♫And how clear is it?♫
♫I don't intend to break your heart♫
♫Silently fall into my arms♫
Mr. Yao.
Are you going home?
Yes.
Well,
has Mr. Jiang gone home?
It's very late.
I think he has gone home.
Take a look around and lock the door.
Okay.
You were so stupid.
You went there
just because Li Wufang asked you to?
What else could I do?
I couldn't just watch you get hurt
and do nothing.
What if he was trying to scare you?
What if I was fine?
I couldn't take the risk.
Back then,
when my father was investigating
the Zornia case,
he found
a very important witness.
As long as the witness testified,
he could have removed
the force behind the Zornia.
However,
the night before the witness testified
against the Zornia gang,
the witness died.
His whole family was killed.
Was the murderer found?
This matter
became my father's lifelong pain.
That witness
had the same surname as you.
His surname was Yan too.
His name was Yan Zhizhong.
Actually...
Actually, my surname is not Yan.
My mother said
she named me
after my savior.
His surname was Yan.
Yan Nanxing.
Although
you're not related to Yan Zhizhong,
and although you are not my witness...
Whenever I
think of how
Li Wufang kidnapped you
and forced me to submit,
whenever I think of
how you almost got hurt
because of me,
whenever I think of...
But I trust you.
I believe
you are no longer
the Jiang Xinbai from before.
Now,
you can save the people from danger
and rescue every person in front of you.
You can also protect me.
I will.
Are you hungry?
Let's go home and eat.
I feel so hungry.
Why is the door locked?
Is anyone here?
I think it was locked from the outside.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Tomorrow is the Doors Open Day.
It will open
two hours earlier than usual.
What is the Doors Open Day?
The Inspection Office
has a Doors Open Day
on the 1st and 15th of each month.
We open our doors
and if the common people
have any injustices,
they can come and complain.
Let's make do with it tonight.
Tomorrow,
as soon as
the door opens,
I'll take you to eat something delicious.
Okay.
But
we...
I know
you want to protect me,
but I still hope
that if you face any difficulties
you can face it with me in the future.
Don't bear everything
or make decisions
all by yourself.
You should at least tell me.
Okay?
I'm talking to you.
Are you asleep?
Don't pretend to be asleep.
I'm not gullible.
Are you really asleep?
You're injured
and you still worked so hard.
You must be tired.
Why are you so pretty?
[Guangyu Hall]
Zhiyi,
you can't sleep at all
for so many nights.
This can't do.
It breaks my heart to see it.
How about
we call an imperial physician for a checkup?
What for?
When I entered the palace yesterday,
Her Majesty told me
that half a month ago,
Xinbai and Shang Bieli
were both called by His Majesty.
His Majesty even lost his temper.
I wonder
what happened.
Just thinking about it makes me nervous.
It hurts.
I didn't do anything.
It still hurts.
Okay, it's my fault.
Don't worry.
It's been a long time since then.
It will be fine.
Being with a king is like being with a tiger.
You know how Xinbai is.
Since childhood,
he only tells us good news.
We don't even know
what happened.
We can't help at all.
How about
I go to the Inspection Office
and ask what happened?
No.
It's been so many days
and he hasn't even come to see me.
Why would you go to see him?
Don't go.
Fine.
I won't go.
Is today
the Inspection Office's Doors Open Day?
Don’t move. It’s not done yet.
I'm going to report my son
and say my son is unfilial
and shows off at home.
So early?
I'm done.
You need to look proper.
It's not done yet.
I won't. I'll just be improper.
My lord.
My lord?
My lord,
why did you two sleep here?
Don't tell anyone
about this.
It's too late.
Right? Look.
Yes.
I can explain.
Shut up.
Speak up.
Mr. Jiang,
what's going on
between you and Ms. Yan?
Are you two
together?
Is the rumor true?
We have to face
what we must face.
Zhiyi!
Don't be angry.
Zhiyi.
Let go!
Yan Nanxing.
It's okay.
No matter what happens,
we'll face it together.
I...
Didn't she leave the capital?
Were you hiding her
these days?
Yes.
During this period,
Yan Nanxing
has been living in my house.
She is a traveler,
but she's been freeloading off of you.
What else
have you two done?
We even—
We reconciled and patched things up.
I want to talk to Yan Nanxing alone.
Get out.
Will you be okay?
Sure.
Have a good chat.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything stupid.
Go.
You're not leaving?
She almost discovered me.
This girl
is quite similar to your mother.
She's smart,
gentle,
and kind.
Right, Mr. Yan?
Name your price.
What price?
How much money do you need to leave Xinbai?
I didn't expect
such cliche words
would come from
the princess.
So tacky.
You're too shy to do it?
Fine.
I'll name the price for you.
One hundred taels of gold
is enough for you to live a good life.
As long as you leave,
I'll pay you immediately.
What is this?
You said you would give me 100 taels of gold,
but I don't see anything yet.
I'm different.
I'm a woman of my word.
I'll give it to you now.
Since I promised you,
I will reward you with gold
as long as you leave.
If you give me 100 taels of gold,
I'll give you 100 taels of gold
and one copper coin.
If you give me 1,000 taels of gold,
I'll give you 1,000 taels of gold
and one copper coin.
You!
I'll always give more than you.
Why are they speaking nonsense?
Are they going to fight?
Let them spill their hearts out.
Wait for them to
release their emotions.
After that,
everything will be doable.
That makes sense.
Let's listen more.
You're a traitor.
I treated you as my best friend,
but you seduced my son
and cheated me of my feelings.
How did I lie to you?
I met your son
before I met you.
How did I lie?
You!
What?
You said I was your close friend.
I'm not good enough for you.
You are heartless.
They're fighting.
When did I ever look down on you?
Never.
You say you don't mind,
but your feelings are honest.
I'm your best friend when I say nice things.
I'm heartless when I don't.
You're such a wicked mother-in-law.
Wicked...
Wicked mother-in-law?
Wicked mother-in-law!
Okay.
I'll be the wicked mother-in-law.
You hit me?
Wait a bit more.
I'm so worried.
Just wait.
Okay.
Yan Nanxing!
Hurry up!
Let go!
-Enough, Yan Nanxing.
-Stop fighting!
Zhiyi!
Why are you fighting?
You are the princess.
What are you doing?
Are you helping me or her?
It has nothing to do with me.
Zhiyi.
Can't sleep?
What's wrong?
I'm angry.
Actually,
I’ve been thinking of Yan Nanxing
every day,
but she said those things about me.
What did she say?
She said I only listen to what I want to hear.
She said I'm arrogant.
She said I'm unreasonable.
She even said I'm a wicked mother-in-law.
I'm not a wicked mother-in-law,
right?
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'm not that kind of person, am I?
You're not usually like this.
But
you care more about the people and things
around Xinbai.
Your concern makes you anxious,
so
you treat Yan Nanxing
a bit more strictly.
Look,
so many people
saw Xinbai and Yan Nanxing
together today
and you made a scene too.
Who knows what the people
are saying
about this now?
What should I do?
I was just angry.
I couldn't help it.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
At most, those ignorant people
will say
that Blossom Beauty closed
because you abused your power
and bullied a commoner.
But it's okay.
How about this?
Yan Nanxing is living with Xinbai
because she has nowhere to stay.
In my opinion,
you should let Yan Nanxing reopen Blossom Beauty.
Suoluo told me already.
Xinbai has taken the title deed.
How come even Suoluo
is biased
toward her brother now?
That's good.
It's sibling love,
right?
Fine.
Blossom Beauty can reopen,
but Yan Nanxing
can never be my daughter-in-law.
Why?
You don't understand.
When Xinbai
went on a blind date with Ms. Pei,
I asked Yan Nanxing to be the matchmaker.
If Pei Linfu
realizes that Xinbai
brought his ex-wife
on a date with his daughter
and made up in the end,
he might get angry and treat Xinbai badly.
Then what should we do?
It's that complicated?
Yes, it's that complicated.
Let's put Pei Linfu aside.
Yan Nanxing herself
is a troublemaker.
Xinbai is already treading on thin ice.
I can't let him be harmed by her.
So,
I must break them up
and be a wicked mother-in-law.
Why is love
so hard?
It's as hard as flying in the sky.
I ask the world,
what is love?
I just—
All right.
Stop talking.
Just remember one thing.
Keep an eye on Blossom Beauty.
If anything happens,
tell me immediately.
I'll keep an eye on her.
What happened to your face?
Who hit you?
Let me see.
Why is it so red?
Is it five fingerprints?
Yes.
Stretch out your hand and check.
Compare it.
Isn't the size just right?
It wasn't me.
You're playing dumb.
You haven't eaten anything all day.
Eat some first.
These drumsticks and scallion pancakes
are all your favorites.
I didn't come to save you in time
because I wanted to give you two some space
to
vent your anger
and be honest with each other.
What trick is this?
To be honest,
it's good that you two
made a scene like this.
How is it good?
First,
for the sake of the people,
my mother won't target you anymore.
Second,
since everyone knows
about our relationship now,
Yuejiang's Residence
won't ignore it either.
Li Wufang
already has his eyes on you.
This means
the people behind him
will be after you too.
I'm afraid
I won't be able to
protect you by myself anymore.
So,
you wanted us to make up
and make it public
so I can be
protected by Yuejiang's Residence?
Then
is there
any other reason?
What other reasons do you think
there could be?
You
are so weird.
How would I know?
You're so smart.
How could you not know?
I'm not smart.
You have to tell me.
What is this?
Blossom Beauty can reopen.
Now that I'm your Boss,
no one
will dare to kick you out again.
How did you get it?
I have my own ways.
When Li Wufang
arrested me that day,
was this
the important thing that you wanted to
talk to me about?
Well...
Well, thank you.
What do you mean "well, thank you"?
You're still unhappy?
Wait.
Look what this is.
What is this now?
I got the title deed
of your residence too.
You...
really...
can do anything you want.
No, Yan Nanxing.
I'm not—
I'm not kicking you out.
Enough. Stop it.
If you think
you like living here,
of course you can stay.
No need.
I don't like it here.
Anyway, you gave me
the title and land deeds.
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow,
I'll move back.
No, Yan Nanxing.
You haven't eaten yet.
Thank you.
Yan Nanxing!