[English subtitles are available]
[Follow Your Heart]
[Episode 4]
My lord,
you worry me so much.
Why did you
drink with Nan Jifeng
when I wasn't here?
If anything happens to you,
I might lose my head
when I return to the capital.
I had no choice.
If I didn't drink,
all our efforts
would have been in vain.
Even then, you still shouldn't drink.
Don't you know
about your situation?
Not only are you a lightweight,
but you also have face blindness.
If you expose yourself
and something happens to you,
how will I explain to the princess?
Yao Qianshu.
Yes.
Are you lecturing me?
I dare not.
I just feel bad for you.
You don't even socialize in the capital.
Why must you lower yourself
in a small place like this?
If you want to get things done,
you need to learn
to dance to the tune
of the people you meet.
It's not about lowering oneself.
While I was gone,
did Nan Jifeng send someone to keep an eye on you?
No.
Even if he did,
I could get rid of them.
What have you found?
There are three major clans in Heman City,
which are Tumen, Gongye and Moqi.
They're all rich clans
with century-old foundations in this area.
The Tumen clan has been county magistrates for five generations.
The Gongye clan occupies the county lieutenancy
and follows Tumen's orders.
The Moqi are quite mysterious.
They've been doing business in Heman for generations
and are outstanding,
but the head of this generation
has never appeared.
Because Zornia has only entered the country
in recent years.
You can't be too brazen
when dabbling in such a business.
By the way, my lord,
I didn't find
the head of the Moqi clan,
but I've recorded
all of the Moqi clan's stores
in Heman.
Please take a look.
Pawnshop,
villa,
casino, tavern...
They do quite a lot.
I have a second piece of intel.
Do you want to hear it?
What?
My mother went into General Nan's study before.
She said there's something fishy in there.
There must be a secret room,
but she didn't know how to get in.
Why did your mother sneak into
the study of the General's Residence?
Ask what you should.
Don't ask what you shouldn't.
I didn't force you
to tell your secret either.
You're trying so hard to enter the General's Residence.
You must want to know something.
The thing you want
must be in the secret room.
There must be
what you're looking for too, right?
Does Nan Jifeng interact with
the three major clans often?
Two years ago
when Nan Jifeng was transferred to Heman,
he interacted frequently
with the three major clans.
It's not as frequent now.
Nan Jifeng's position is stable now,
so he naturally
avoids suspicion on the surface.
My lord,
what should we do next?
Find the evidence
of Nan Jifeng and the three clans' crimes.
[Jingteng Hall]
I'm not leaving.
You leave if you want.
Anyway, I'm not leaving.
The general asked Her Ladyship to go back to her maiden home
and irritated her again.
Mr. Xi.
Madam.
Mr. Xi,
are you here to see the general?
I’m afraid he...
It's fine.
Actually, I came here today
to
pay my respects to you.
To me?
I bet you must want to see Dr. Yan instead.
Your Ladyship, you must be joking.
You're just in time.
I've saved you a bowl of the herbal soup
I made for Her Ladyship.
Try it.
It's good for your health.
What?
Are you afraid I put strange things in this?
That's right.
Trust me.
Our cooperation
has been put on the agenda.
Are you sure?
To be precise,
this time,
you need to help me more.
However,
you don't need to pay
or use your looks.
When the deed is done,
name your price.
I don't have to pay
or use my looks,
and I can even name my price when it's done?
Why do I think
it sounds
even more dangerous?
Listen to me.
Dr. Yan.
Madam.
Sorry to bother you again.
No, no, no. It's no bother.
I'm just here to deliver some fruits.
Madam.
I want to take Yan Nanxing
for a stroll.
Is that okay?
Yes,
but Dr. Yan,
you won't run away again, right?
Madam, you must be joking.
I will definitely return her.
Let's go.
Thank you, Madam.
This is not bad.
I didn't take a closer look last time.
It's quite elegant.
Last time?
When were you here before?
I mean
when I passed by last time.
When I pass by the river,
I often see
many similar pleasure boats here,
but I never looked carefully.
Isn't it dizzying to sleep
on a boat?
Why don't you stay in an inn?
Heman is a waterfront city.
It's rare for me to come here.
Naturally,
I must live in a representative place.
Have some tea.
Got it.
Pleasure boats are places to spend money
and get pleasure.
Here, you can drink some tea,
listen to music,
then drink some wine
and have some beauties in your lap.
You'll be as happy as a god.
How come
you sound like
a jealous wife?
Wife?
Are you willing to let your wife
work for you outside
and tell her
to name her price
after the deed's done?
Alright,
I'll stop joking with you.
I was afraid of eavesdroppers
at the General's Residence,
so I invited you here.
It's totally necessary.
You
lack awareness
and can't read the room.
It's because I don't care.
Tell me.
What's the matter?
Tonight,
I want to ask you
to keep General Nan away from the study.
Two hours is enough.
Distract General Nan.
After I find the secret room,
I'll exit and help guard for you.
Then you can go in
and find what you want.
Working together
and protecting each other.
It sounds
like a pretty good plan,
but why do I feel like...
I'm at a disadvantage?
For example?
For example...
Look.
Working alone,
if I fail and get caught,
I can make amends
due to my medical merits
and save myself.
But if you're added, with your mysterious background
and ulterior motives,
General Nan might get unhappy
and kill us.
It's not worth it for me.
Tell me.
How much money do you need
for you to take this risk?
Money is not a problem for you.
I don't want something that you don't value.
Then what do you want?
I want to know
if you have
relatives or friends
who were hurt by Zornia before.
Heman is where Zornia enters the country
and you came here to investigate it.
Are you suspecting
General Nan
has something to do with the bad guys
who killed your family?
Or
do you want to find them
through General Nan?
Or maybe...
Your enemy
includes General Nan?
Am I right?
Yan Nanxing,
it’s a waste for you
to be a traveling doctor.
You should be a storyteller.
You're trying to gloss over things again.
Mr. Xi!
Mr. Xi,
we meet again.
Our girls earn
30 taels of silver a month here.
I only gave you a discount
because you pay monthly.
Madam,
are you here
to collect rent?
No.
It's just that
you rent my pleasure boat
and pay despite not wanting the girls.
I feel
so uncomfortable inside.
It seems
you
don't like our girls.
You must think they are not pretty enough.
We got two new girls today.
They're beautiful.
Greet Mr. Xi.
Hello, Mr. Xi.
No need.
Mr. Xi, don't hold back.
Let them
accompany you tonight.
It's really unnecessary.
Today,
I have something else to do.
You must know that a moment of love
is worth thousands.
Go!
Mr. Xi,
I missed you so much.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Let go! And that one too, let go!
Do you own this pleasure boat?
You think you can come in as you want?
Mr. Xi,
is she your maid?
You're dressed prettily.
Do you have bad eyesight?
Do I look like a maid to you?
No.
You look like a maid's mother.
You have bad eyesight.
I know you.
You are that
volunteer female doctor?
Right.
I'm not only a female doctor,
but also
Mr. Xi's wife.
My husband
came to Heman for business.
I worried
some weird girls would pester him,
so I followed him here.
From what was said just now,
you've been a good boy.
Good job.
I'm relieved.
No wonder
Mr. Xi is so obedient.
He's married to a tigress.
You're so smart.
I really am a tigress.
Tigress!
I'll prick you to death.
I'll prick you to death!
Don't come over!
Yes, I'm so uncouth.
Go away!
-Run! Are you scared?
-A tigress!
Don't prick me! Go away!
Tigress!
Gosh.
She has bad eyesight.
I don't look good?
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm helping you.
If I didn't help,
they would've
eaten you alive.
Look at the way they looked at you.
It was like wolves seeing meat.
That hand kept stroking
your body.
Be careful.
Don't get seduced.
Are you jealous?
I mean...
So,
you called yourself my wife
and even disregarded your reputation?
You really don't know me.
In this martial world,
I remain untainted
by the environment.
We just met by chance
and take what we need.
When we get out of Heman,
we will never meet again.
Why would I be jealous?
So,
you agree?
Yes,
but let's make it clear.
I want to enter the secret room
of the General's Residence too.
We'll take what we each need.
Okay.
Deal.
[General's Residence]
Dr. Yan.
Is this the general's hangover soup
from Her Ladyship?
Yes.
You're alone today?
Where's Yue?
She should still be in the kitchen.
Okay.
Not bad. It's quite hot.
Quickly send it to the general.
Go ahead.
What did you
sprinkle into that bowl?
You won't know even if I tell you.
It's medicine that you don't need.
Fine, I'll tell you.
When the general comes out later,
you have to hurry in.
You must be quick.
My medicine works well,
but they
are not young anymore.
It'll be
two hours at most.
You know.
Two hours.
Good job, Dr. Yan.
Madam,
the peonies
in the garden are blooming these days.
Yes.
Look.
You're almost healed
and it's a lovely night.
How about
you invite the general over tonight?
I haven't fully recovered.
So what?
The general loves you deeply.
He won't mind.
Plus, you said
he has been wronged these days.
Gaya.
General?
[Zhang Hui]
[Yuwen Wu]
The doors and windows are closed,
but there's a draft.
What are you doing?
Killing me after using me?
Put it down.
It's you?
You're pretending you don't know me?
Let's go.
Let's go back first.
Why?
Now it's your turn to guard.
I haven't entered yet.
Stop messing around.
I'm not.
I have to go inside.
Come back with me.
I haven't...
What are you doing?
Why can't I go in?
Are you burning bridges?
Someone passed by the door of the study.
I think you're just wary of me.
What's in the secret room?
I think
Lady Gaya
has almost recovered.
How about
you leave tonight?
What's wrong with you?
Why should I leave tonight?
I haven't entered the secret room yet.
What exactly are you looking for?
You tell me first.
What's in the secret room?
Money.
What else?
Money,
money,
and more money.
Nothing else?
If you're not looking for money,
there's nothing in the room that you want.
No.
I have to check it out myself.
You don't trust me?
It's not that I don't trust you.
I have to see it myself
before I give up.
I'm not joking.
The secret room
doesn't have what you're looking for.
Things are about to change in Heman.
You shouldn't get involved in this mess.
It's a matter of life and death.
Tonight,
you must leave.
Yan Nanxing.
I don't want to get you involved.
You...
Are you
showing concern for me?
What do I have to say
for you to leave?
No, you don't understand.
I can't leave tonight.
Stubborn!
You have to at least
promise me one thing.
Do not
leave your room tonight.
What?
Is he crazy?
Lieutenant General Li,
what are you doing?
General Nan,
even if the deal fails, the righteousness remains.
Why the murderous intent?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
What's going on?
Is there a misunderstanding?
How about we untie Lieutenant General Li first?
Untie him.
Tell me.
What happened?
General,
I saw this man
sneak into your study
and this woman helped him.
I was worried
he would harm you.
That's why I acted on my own impulse
to get rid of him.
Your own impulse?
I'm curious
what horrible things
your general has done
that you need to hide for him
by killing me.
Follow me to the study.
I'm afraid there's a trap.
I've already searched the study.
There are no traps.
Nan Jifeng can't kill me anyway.
I'd like to see
how he wants to dispute this.
Watch over Yan Nanxing.
Don’t let anything go wrong.
Stay with my people.
Don't trust anyone else.
Then you...
Don't worry.
Wait for me here.
It's fine.
Jifeng, be careful.
Jifeng!
Jifeng, are you alright?
Don't panic.
The knife is poisoned.
Take him inside.
Hurry!
Help the general in.
Hurry.
Madam.
Where is the magical medicine of your tribe?
Quickly take them out.
I can't.
The magical medicine is gendered.
Mine is feminine medicine.
The general can't take it.
What are you doing?
Yan Nanxing!
Countering poison with poison
can lure out some of the poison
in the general.
Your blood is poisonous?
I almost died when I was young.
I ate all kinds of weird herbs
and quite a lot of toxins built up in me.
So you're the Poison Girl?
Madam.
Do you have Zornia?
Zornia?
What?
Although it's poisonous when it's processed,
it's not an ordinary thing.
All poison is also medicine.
A small amount of Zornia
can also help detoxify his body.
I won't take it!
Even if I die by poisoning,
I will never touch that thing again.
Jifeng!
Jifeng.
Madam, here.
Have the general drink this.
Jifeng,
come. Slowly.
Slowly.
Yan Nanxing,
must it be Zornia?
Is there no replacement?
There is.
There is another way.
We can use human blood as the guiding drug.
Then use my blood.
No, Madam.
Women's blood has yin energy.
It doesn't match men's blood.
Then what can we do?
You can't let me
watch him die like this.
Dr. Yan,
I beg you.
You must find a way
to save him.
Please.
Treatment with human blood?
I've never heard of this before.
This is a folk prescription.
First, I'll use my blood to counter poison with poison
and force out some toxins.
Then I'll use fresh human blood as the guiding drug
for detoxification.
How much do you need?
At least
one bowl.
What should we do?
Is there any other way?
Mr. Xi.
Yan Nanxing,
use my blood
and save Nan Jifeng.
Are you
really not afraid of death?
You've lost so much blood.
What if General Nan can't be saved
and you collapse too?
You said
there are things you fear more than death
and there are things
you want to do more than to live,
right?
In my life,
there's also a mission
that makes me not thirst for life
nor fear death.
Mission?
Yes,
a mission.
Without General Nan,
the mission I came here for
won't be completed.
Besides,
I brought the murderer here.
It's my responsibility.
Do you know
why I won't
open an actual clinic
and instead wander around
as a traveling doctor?
It's because I don't want to face
these life-or-death matters all the time.
I've been practicing medicine
with my mother since I was little
and traveled everywhere.
Actually, my mother saved many people.
But there were also many
who couldn't be saved.
If one person died,
an entire family would fall apart.
I didn't understand.
My mother was doing good deeds,
but why did she feel burdened
like she was carrying people's lives?
From then on,
I made up my mind
that I wanted to be
a doctor who didn't deal with death.
Sometimes, I thought
healing skin diseases
or giving acupuncture for facial paralysis was nice.
Even if I couldn't cure them,
I wouldn't kill them,
right?
But
you never gave up on
any patient.
Sometimes,
you seem like
you're running away,
but it's never true,
right?
I know.
You want to say that
I'm a benevolent doctor.
I am indeed
a good doctor,
both talented and pretty,
Hua Tuo reincarnated,
and I provide good service.
You envy me.
Have a rest.
Thank you.
Actually...
Actually, you don't have to thank me.
I didn't even tell my mother
what I said to you just now.
But I'm happy.
Telling you these things
feels like...
Feels like...
I made a friend.
Maybe...
Maybe we’re not friends.
My name is Jiang Xinbai.
It's from the poem,
"the autumn moon in the heart of the river is pale."
My father's surname is Xi,
but I took my mother's surname.
What exactly do you do?
You're quite greedy.
I told you all of my
inside thoughts.
Can't we have a heart-to-heart exchange?
What you said just now
was what you wanted to say.
I didn't ask you to say it.
You...
You only say that after you heard everything.
My hand is still injured.
Stop pretending.
You look fine.
It hurts so much.
Who...
I don’t believe it.
Thank you, Dr. Yan,
for taking care of our boss.
Just call me Poison Girl.
I think you're very creative.
If I say that,
I'm afraid some people won't like it.
It doesn't matter if he likes it or not.
I accept it.
What a personality.
If you're done, let's get down to business.
My lord,
I've checked the supplement roster
of soldiers under Nan Jifeng.
In the two years
since Nan Jifeng was sent to Heman,
other than casualties
and discharged soldiers,
there are five unidentified deaths.
Yuwen Wu, Zhao Li, Du Tong,
Zhang Hui, and Zhu Ziquan.
[Yuwen Wu]
[Zhao Li]
[Du Tong]
[Zhang Hui]
[Zhu Ziquan]
These five died in the first year
of Nan Jifeng's term.
Meanwhile, Nan Jifeng
only started pretending
to be alcoholic in the second year.