[English subtitles are available]
[Follow Your Heart]
[Episode 22]
Commander Shang,
you shouldn’t be like this.
Do you know how much
effort we put in
for your nose?
Sai'er, I...
Stop talking.
Let me finish.
I'm sure if Lady Gaya
and General Nan
see you like this,
they'd be very sad too.
We all want you to be well.
Why can't you
be brave?
Commander Shang.
Trust me.
You look really good
with a nose.
I won't lie to you.
All right.
To celebrate today,
I’ve decided to cook you
a new dish I just learned.
Wait for me.
Don't you think it smells great?
Let me tell you,
it's also super crispy.
It's crispy. Try it.
Is it good?
It is, isn't it?
Then I'll leave this for you.
No one else has it.
Not bad, right?
Are you not used to it?
I'm not used to it either.
Regardless, this is a good thing.
Congratulations, Shang.
Thank you, Suoluo.
But,
it would be nice if it were
as pretty as your nose.
I'm curious.
Which miracle worker
managed to restore your nose
to what it was before?
This miracle worker...
This...
Is it Yan Nanxing?
We are sort of like
friends now.
In just a few days,
you two became good friends?
What about Jiang Xinbai?
Jiang Xinbai...
Jiang Xinbai
and I are also kind of
on the same side now.
What?
When did you form an alliance?
Half a month ago,
His Majesty summoned me.
Jiang Xinbai saved me
and my brother.
His Majesty
ordered me to investigate the Zornia case with him.
Half a month ago?
He came to my house five days ago
and asked for Blossom Beauty's title deed.
Why didn't he mention anything about it?
Did you guys
decide on everything
before telling me about it?
I knew it. As long as Jiang Xinbai is involved,
I will be treated as an outsider.
Suoluo.
Suoluo...
In the end,
you and Jiang Xinbai are family.
I think he’s devoted to investigating the Zornia case
and has no intention of competing for the succession with you.
Do you mean to say that
he doesn't care about me?
That's not what I mean.
I just suddenly find
your conflict
meaningless.
What do you mean?
Am I just
a willful child
in your eyes?
That's not what I meant.
Shang,
are you still my ally?
As long as you're willing,
we'll always be confidants.
I see.
No matter what you do,
it won't hurt our friendship.
Suoluo.
Suoluo!
[Blossom Beauty]
Mrs. Bao.
Aren't you good at gathering information?
Ask her about it.
Is it true between her and the Duke?
I'm also good at curing all sickness
and keeping you content.
You are closest to Ms. Yan.
You're most suited
to ask her.
That's right, Mrs. Bao.
Go ask her
about her relationship with the Duke.
What's their relationship?
Ask her.
You can ask her yourself.
You're already filled to the brim with gossip.
Quit it.
Get up.
Fine, we'll stop.
Boss,
are they talking about you?
I feel that they are afraid of you.
Good news never spread,
gossips never stop.
I guess they heard that
I'm the ex-daughter-in-law
of the Jiang family,
so they are treating me differently.
They've heard about it already?
Of course they have.
Why are you here?
Don't you have school today?
Today, the ex-chancellor
is teaching at the Imperial Academy.
He has always had societal prejudice
and wouldn't let me attend class
because I'm from the slave class.
Just because he said so, you relented?
What did your chancellor say?
You're right.
I answer to my chancellor.
[Master for all ages]
You are now
the chancellor.
I am
proud of you.
You taught me well, Sir.
My achievements are thanks to you.
Everyone,
as the old saying goes,
the husband advocates
and the wife follows.
A woman
should obey her husband
and take care of her family.
But nowadays, improper trends in society
make women show themselves in public.
What do you call this?
Turning the world upside down!
In my opinion...
Mr. Cui.
I would like to ask a question.
Go ahead.
I don't understand.
Since His Majesty has appointed the worthy,
there is no distinction between classes
and gender.
So, how can you call it improper?
A woman is as knowledgeable as a man.
So why must she blindly obey her husband?
You have no right to speak.
Leave.
It doesn't matter.
Which family are you from, young man?
I'm Liu Ruoqian.
I was born into a slave family,
not an aristocratic family.
A slave family?
A slave family!
It has been barely
two years since I left.
When did the Imperial Academy
start recruiting from the slave class?
His Majesty is a wise emperor of Daqi.
I may be born a slave,
but after studying at the Imperial Academy,
I can be a teacher or an official
in the future.
It is all thanks to His Majesty.
Mr. Cui,
are you questioning His Majesty's decision?
Mr. Cui.
The disciples I taught
were familiar with the etiquette of the emperor-subject relationship
but didn’t learn the etiquette of the teacher-student relationship.
Please forgive him.
It's fine.
Do you admit your mistake?
I was just discussing knowledge
with Mr. Cui.
The chancellor didn't blame me for that.
Don't try to save yourself by mentioning her.
I told you to go away.
How dare you come back?
The Imperial Academy recruited a slave
like you to put up a display.
Do you really think
you can be a teacher
or official in the future?
Dream on!
Whether I stay or not
depends on the chancellor.
How dare you dodge?
Hold out your hand!
Stop!
Chancellor.
Dean Yan,
the ruler in your hand
is for upholding the rules of the academy.
How dare you disregard the rules?
Hand over the ruler.
I was too angry
and offended you.
Ruoqian,
I'm sorry.
Chancellor,
I'll accept my punishment
and copy the student handbook a hundred times.
I'll take my leave.
Thank you.
From today onwards, come to my class.
Thank you, Chancellor.
You
irritated Dean Yan on purpose, right?
You seem gentle and weak,
but you are quite scheming.
Do I seem weak?
Chancellor, have you forgotten?
My family members are ironsmiths.
I really forgot.
You provoked
Mr. Cui today.
Weren't you afraid?
For you,
I'm not afraid.
Why?
Because I'm on your side.
You...
You're good at saying nice things.
It's my honor to be able to
listen in at your classes.
I won't let you down.
I'll take my leave.
[Assistant Minister of Revenue, Yan Jinglun]
Biqing,
your chess moves are messed up.
Why go that far
for a woman?
Father.
I...
Tomorrow night,
the Yuejiang's Residence is holding an appreciation banquet.
Wasn't Mr. Cui your mentor
for a few months?
You're considered his student, then.
You should attend it.
How about this?
I'll accompany you to the banquet.
Let's fix
the situation.
[Shang Residence]
Commander Shang!
Commander...
Ms. Sai'er.
It's late.
You're still up?
Well,
why hasn't Commander Shang
returned yet?
Commander Shang has something important to do today.
He may be coming back late.
You're an hour late.
You'll know soon
how worth it it was
for you to wait for an hour.
Li Wufang mentioned
an agent for the fake calligraphy and paintings.
I found him.
How?
I found a friend who knows calligraphy and painting
to examine the works for me.
We found that
those fake calligraphy and paintings
were made by the same person.
Then I found
the painter behind those fake works
and got his ledger.
Commander Shang's efficiency
is truly formidable.
Mr. Jiang is taking his time with recovery.
Someone has to do the work in the meanwhile.
The results of the work
have yet to be seen.
Fine. It's okay if you don't want to take a look.
You see?
He's jealous of me.
I can do
what he can't.
I'm jealous of you?
Why would I be jealous of you?
That your nose is fake?
It may be fake, but it is perfect.
Can you smell anything with it?
Of course he can.
I'm working on it.
He'll be able to smell things in the future.
No hurry.
Let's get down to business.
You're right.
You two...
Let's get down to business.
Give it to me.
Lu Bo'an.
He is Li Wufang's agent.
Lu Bo'an?
Lu Dingzhao's grandson.
That's right.
He is also
a student of the Imperial Academy.
One grandson sold fake paintings.
The other grandson secretly embezzled money.
Lu
is going all out.
Lu Dingzhao
never personally participates in Zornia trading.
If anything happens,
he can completely distance himself
from the situation.
In the end,
we still have no evidence.
You're holding the ledger in your hand.
What more do you need?
This can only prove that
our deduction is correct.
What else can it prove?
In my opinion,
we should arrest
Lu Dingzhao
and beat him up
until he fesses up to his crimes.
Kidnapping an imperial official
and torturing him without permission.
How many heads do you have for something as risky as that?
Find clues
and evidence.
How much time do you have for that?
Two months?
We don't have that luxury anymore.
What two months?
If we can't make Lu budge,
we'll start with his grandsons.
I'll find a way
to arrest Lu Bo'an.
Lu Bo'an is a student of the Imperial Academy.
He did nothing.
What right do you have to arrest him at the Imperial Academy?
Do you have an idea?
Tell me.
You have no idea either.
Mr. Jiang.
Is anything happening
in the court lately?
Especially regarding the Ministry of Personnel.
The officials assigned by the Ministry of Personnel
were all sent to the northwest recently.
It's such an important news.
Why didn't you mention it before?
There is a general outside the Pass
called Yi Yuanshan.
He contributed to eliminating the bandits.
Originally, Li Jun recommended him
to Heman
to replace you.
But after the dispatch notice was sent,
Yi Yuanshan
took office in Tingzhou instead.
So for them,
Tingzhou
is more important than Heman.
It's possible.
But we know nothing
about Tingzhou.
Mr. Jiang,
it's inconvenient for you and Bieli to leave the capital.
Why don't I go to Tingzhou
and find out
what they are up to?
It's a good idea.
Brother,
it's not safe for you to go alone.
I'll send some Jinwu Guards
to accompany you.
The Jinwu Guards take attendance regularly.
Once they find a member missing,
it'll be hard for you to explain.
Why don't you let Yao Qianshu
go with you?
You can take care of each other on the way.
There's no time to lose.
General Nan,
leave with Yao Qianshu as soon as possible.
As for Lu Bo'an,
I'll talk to Suoluo
and see what I can find
before we make the next plan.
Tonight,
the Yuejiang's Residence is holding an appreciation banquet.
Suoluo will be there too.
I'll make a trip back home.
Wait for me here.
I have something to tell you when I come back.
Okay.
See you.
Dr. Yan.
I have some progress regarding the person
you asked me to find.
How is it going?
I'll tell you about it
when I make more progress.
[Yuejiang's Residence]
Greetings, Your Grace.
Thank you, Your Grace.
I can't drink much.
I can't drink anymore.
Tonight is the appreciation banquet.
How can you not drink the appreciation wine?
Thank you.
Mr. Cui, please.
Your Highness.
I...
Are you drunk already?
You haven't eaten much yet.
The wife must follow the husband?
How dare you bully my daughter?
I'll show him.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
The Duke and Duchess are both trusted and valued
individuals of Daqi.
His Majesty thinks highly of you.
The Yan family is so fortunate
-to be in-laws with...
-Father.
You're drunk.
I'm drunk?
Am I drunk?
Didn't you say
you are preparing the
betrothal gift for Her Grace?
Mr. Yan,
you are really drunk.
What nonsense are you talking about?
At this point,
hiding it any further
would be an act of disrespect
to the elders here.
Your Highness.
Three years ago,
Suoluo came to the State of Miluo to study.
We fell in love with each other,
so we got engaged there.
Nice!
What?
Is that true?
You...
Why didn't you tell me
such big news?
Your Highness.
It's not Suoluo's fault.
It's because I just came back
and haven't established a foothold in the court.
So we discussed and decided
to keep this secret for now.
How considerate of you, Mr. Yan.
Yan.
Your Highness.
For now, only our two families
know about this matter.
Please don't speak of this
to the outsiders.
Because
getting engaged without the parents' knowledge
is not quite a glorious matter.
Your Highness is right.
Since it's a happy event,
let's have a toast!
Biqing!
Thank you, Your Grace and Your Highness.
Mr. Yan.
Xinbai?
Didn't you say you had work tonight
and couldn't come back?
I'm here
to ask Suoluo about something.
Xinbai,
I'm afraid tonight
is a bad time.
Something bad happened to Suoluo.
Say it!
Mother, I know I was wrong.
You're wrong?
You're only quick to admit it!
-Do you know...
-I know.
I shouldn't have been engaged
without permission.
I shouldn't have hidden it from you either.
It's not about hiding the matter or not.
Do you know...
I know I'm immature.
I didn't get along with Xinbai,
so I
went to the State of Miluo
alone back then.
I studied alone in a foreign state
and had no help or support.
Yan Biqing
took great care of me back then.
He also promised me the support
of the capital and the noble families when I returned.
I...
I made a mistake.
It's not just a
simple mistake!
It's called being foolish!
I know I was wrong.
You know?
What do you know?
The Yans are nothing.
He doesn’t deserve you!
The Yans are not
a wealthy family,
But because of that,
our engagement
will reassure His Majesty.
Aren't you thinking ahead of yourself?
His Majesty might be satisfied.
But am I, your mother, satisfied?
You can marry anyone
except for that vile man!
You think Yan Biqing is a vile man?
It's written all over his face!
His father
buttered up to authority and went from
a low-ranking official in the Ministry of Justice
to where he is today.
The apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
That brat
only stayed in the
deserted State of Miluo
for a decade or two
and dared to brag about how well-read
and knowledgeable he was.
Shameless!
Mother, don't be angry.
It's bad for your health.
How can I not be angry?
Xinbai
got married secretly in Heman.
And you...
got engaged secretly in Miluo.
Who exactly do you two
take after?
Since Xinbai
can get married in Heman
before divorcing his wife,
at worse,
I'll divorce Yan Biqing after our marriage
and remarry.
Nonsense!
Marriage is a major milestone in life.
You're already thinking about divorce before marriage?
Isn't that a joke?
You are the princess's daughter! My daughter!
Suoluo.
Tell me.
Do you really like
Yan Biqing?
That's great.
Remember.
A good marriage is hard to come by.
You must
choose a man
you genuinely love.
If you don't want to marry,
no one can force you.
Mother.
No one can force you
to marry anyone.
You must treasure yourself.
Don't make me worry.
Don't let me down again.
Suoluo?
Suoluo.
You didn't have time to attend the banquet,
but you have time
to rush here and lecture me?
I've been lectured enough
today.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
Suoluo.
I've heard about it.
If you are doing this
just to spite me,
there is no need.
I hope you understand.
Don't do anything
you'd regret.
I never regret what I do.
Neither do I need anyone's advice.
If there's
nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Suoluo!
How did it go?
How was your talk with Suoluo?
She has her own matters to worry about.
Let's think of another way.
You told me to wait for you.
What were you going to tell me?
The moon is full tonight.
Yes, what about it?
Come home with me.
We'll sleep together.
Have you forgotten
our promise?
I'll watch you shapeshift.
You once said
you didn't know
what you would shapeshift into.
You didn't know
what kind of danger you would be facing.
I want to be with you
so that you won't be lonely
or afraid anymore.
Well?
Are you going back with me?
This is what you meant
by sleeping together?
What else?
Then...
You're just gonna sit there and watch me?
Yes.
Go to sleep.
Are you really going to
sit and watch me all night?
But I don't think it's appropriate.
I can't bear to let you do that.
This is your bed.
But I'm lying here and you're sitting there.
That's inappropriate.
How about this?
We'll each take
half of the bed.
We'll sleep together.
This can't do.
I have to keep an eye on you.
Zhiyi.
You didn't sleep well again, did you?
Have some ginseng soup.
Here.
My two kids
are taking turns to worry me.
How can I be fine?
Honey.
I asked you
to keep an eye on Xinbai.
Is he
up to anything lately?
Don't cry.
Xinbai
has grown up.
Is Yan Nanxing staying at his place again?
Is she?
Yan Nanxing...
You didn't shapeshift.
If not today,
it'll happen tomorrow.
It's either before or after the full moon anyway.
Really?
Yes.
Well...
Since I haven't shapeshifted,
I'm going back to Blossom Beauty first.
I'll be back tonight.
Again?
Yes.
Yan Nanxing!
What's wrong?
Your mother!
My mother?
Hurry up.
Come on.
Why is my mother here?
How would I know?
Hurry up.
Where do I go?
Hurry.
Coming, Mother!
Close the door for me.
Where is Yan Nanxing?
She...
I saw her open the door.
Where is she?
No, she...
Calm down.
Were you sleeping together?
I agreed to let you run Blossom Beauty together,
but I didn't say you could sleep together!
We did sleep together,
but it's not what you think!
How else do you want to sleep?
Why couldn't you control yourself?
What do you mean by that?
It's not like that!
Mother.
Mother!
Yan Nanxing!
Mother...
I can explain...
You...
He... He!
You!
You are...
I'm not.
He's not...
I am.
He is...
He's not...
You...
Mother.
It's not like that.
He...