I said no is no.
There'll be no drugs in my territory.
Whatever you do is your business.
But I don't want any of these in my area.
Okay. Chill, I’m just asking.
I thought it’s a win-win for both of us.
I could expand my business and you get the profits.
But if you don’t want it. Fine.
You sure you won't change your mind later?
I have my word. You know me well.
Don’t ever bring those evil drugs in my area!
Hey, Stop!
Huh. You really want to do this.
A guy like Sakkhee won’t back off this easily.
Boss, you have to be careful.
Let him come. I’m always ready.
I'm only concerned about one thing.
Yes, Father?
You want me to be a bodyguard?
Argh. Why ringing that damn bell so many times.
Don’t you have it at your house?
Excuse me
Who the hell are you?
Father sends me here to look after you,
young master.
So I have to live here with you.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, what the fuck are you doing? Let go!
Wait, What are you trying to do? Stop!
Ouch ouch
♪Tremble, you made me feel tremble.♪
♪Just realize what it is♪
♪What called ‘Love’ is blooming and coming for me♪
♪It begins with you and our connections.♪
♪just you and me untill now♪
♪it's coming, a wonderful love♪
♪love that doesn't hurt anyone♪
♪baby comes to me, enormously♪
♪to over flow my heart♪
May I come in?
I apologize.
Hey, wait, you wait. Hey,
this is my house!
A bodyguard? Dad,
I am a grown-up not a kid anymore.
Sky, it's not that big of a deal.
Hey hey, you, that one is pricey.
Hold it tight.
I made an effort to choose the one
who is nearly your age.
When you go on campus no one would notice.
What? You want him to go to school with me?
Really? Dad, my friends are going to make fun of me
being a daddy’s boy. I'll pass.
Tell other that he's a relative or something.
I enrolled him in the same faculty as you,
there's nothing to worry about.
But I don't like this.
You have to bring your underling back.
You have to keep him.
Listen to me, Sky.
I permitted you to study there.
But you can only go there under my conditions.
As a compromise.
But I don’t want anyone to keep an eye on me.
Sky, You must live with him.
Non-negotiable. Understand?
Hey, what? Really?
Hey, this is my house.
What are you doing?
I am doing a security check for you,
young master.
But it's annoying.
It is my duty and my responsibility.
Please understand that.
It is my duty and my responsibility
Please understand, huh.
Alright, do whatever you want.
A bodyguard? Urgh,
you are just a guard dog.
Just walking being a smart-ass in someone else's house
makes you look cool? Damn it.
If you want to stay here.
Fine. I will go somewhere else.
Fuck, did I forget my key?
Hey, STOP!!
Ouch
Sun, This is Bank.
My buddy.
Bank, This is Sun.
My cousin.
He got accepted to the same university as us.
Wait. Why have you never told me
that you have a relative?
Ahh well..
He's a distant relative of mine.
So when my dad knew that we’re going to the same university
he sent him here.
Right, Sun.
Yes
Then why did he have to take me down like that?
He might have thought that you were going to attack me.
Sun has just left the monkhood.
So he is kinda naive.
and wasn't realized that just a joke,
so he misunderstood.
Where did he be ordained?
Kang-fu Temple or what?
Shit. He was so strong.
So why are you here?
I was going to invite you to lunch, Sky.
Mr. Bank,
Mr. Bank, how did you get into this housing estate?
Do you have a keycard?
Just call me Bank.
Sky gave me a copied keycard.
So I can come anytime.
I think you..
I am full. Anyway, thanks for coming today.
See you tomorrow.
I will walk you out.
Yeah yeah.
Don't you think I'm not going to fight back?
Have you realized
that you almost hurt my friend?
I apologized.
I thought that guy was going to hurt you.
Listen to me. A housing estate with this level
is not that easy to  enter.
If my dad didn’t give you the keycard,
you wouldn’t be able to pass the security guard.
Not at all.
For me, it’s not that hard to pass by.
Whatever, oh, and one more thing.
When we are not alone,
don’t call me “young master”. Understand?
Then how should I address you?
You are father’s son.
Father?
You called my dad “Father”?
Yes, sir. He wants me to call him like that.
Damn it. I suddenly have a brother.
Anyway, since I couldn’t get rid of you.
Just simply “you”, not “young master”.
I don’t want anyone to know that my dad sent me a sitter
and know that I’m a mafia’s son.
But being a mafia has nothing to be ashamed of.
Father is influential, but he doesn't run any illegal businesses.
But I dislike it.
Yes, sir.
May I stay in the room on the mezzanine?
Please excuse me. I’m going to unpack.
He did whatever he wants, go wherever he likes.
Is this really my house?
Damn it, who brought this rascal into my life.
Hey, this is not funny.
Come on, man.
What the hell on earth?
Young master!
Who is that?
Sun?
Yes, is everything alright, young master?
The water is not running, can't you see?
Ouch, my eyes hurt.
Let's get out of here.
Wait wait wait, do you see anything?
Nothing
Why can't you see? I'm naked.
It's covered with bubble.
Bubble?
Did you just say I'm tiny? Huh?
You want to get into trouble? Sun.
Not tiny.
Yeah right. Wait, so you saw it.
Did you lie to me, Sun?
I think we should go outside.
All done.
Just now I locked the door. How did you get in?
Just picked a lock. It's very simple.
Wait, Sun.
Just now you didn't see my thing right?
Young master, try closing your eyes.
Close your eyes
Do you see anything?
No
Absolutely
What the?
Good thing he didn't see it.
Don't ever do that again.
Even though you wanted to help,
but at least knocked first.
I was naked.
I've prepared your clothes for tomorrow.
I'm going to put them in your room.
Nevermind. I can do it myself.
I'm not a little kid.
Young master,
Tomorrow is your first day.
Don't forget to pack your bag.
Is he going to be a bodyguard or a dad?
Serious, straight face,
not friendly, unsociable
Sun is just like that,
but he can do everything.
So I entrust him with you.
Dad, it's like having another dad.
That guy is even stricter than you.
That's good. It gives me peace of mind.
Anyway, son, you find anything strange lately?
Find What? The weirdest thing is the bodyguard
that you sent me.
or you mean something else?
Nothing, everything's all good. Call you later.
Anything abnormal happened, boss?
Sakkhee is untrustworthy.
Order our guys to keep an eye on their moves.
Yes, sir.
Great!
Now we know where his beloved son lives.
What's your next move, boss?
I want to give him a lesson.
What he will get if he did not cooperate.
Please be careful, young master.
How did he do that?
Thank you, bro
My pleasure
We come here to study not to battle.
You don't have to be this serious.
I must be.
Whatever you like. Let's go
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Sun, why you did that. so reckless
Let me help you.
Here you go
What's your name?
Woah, your combat pose is so scary.
Bank, what the heck are you doing?
That freaked me out
I saw you were alone,
so I dragged you here.
So it means you just escaped from Sun?
Something like that.
You know, it's so frustrating.
I get how you feel.
Your cousin is kinda scary.
Are we going to the classroom now?
What a sunny day.
Pardon me?
Are you looking for class?
I can take you there.
I'm fine, but thanks.
Come on, let's go together
Don't be shy. I'll carry that.
Nevermind
I think she's not shy,
but more like disgusted.
None of your business
Try me.
See you later
Thank you
No problem
I'm Toktaeng.
Toktaeng? What a cool name you have.
My parents are interior designers
that's how I got my name.
Well, do you know where is room 413?
Room 413? We're going there too.
Want to come with us?
Really? Sure.
Mr.Bank, does your dad work in a bank?
Yeah Sun, how do you know?
Sun?
Why do you want to study Fine Arts?
I like to draw since I was a kid.
Really? I like it since birth.
Like to draw?
Like you, TokTaeng
Urgh, so lame, Bank.
Man, just kidding
-Juno
-TokTaeng
Oops!
Are you okay?
-Did I almost fall and embarrass myself?
-Yep
-Thank you
-Sure
Toktaeng's friend?
I'm Sky. This guy's Bank and that one's Sun.
Hey, you can sit here.
Thanks
Just the first day and you already made a move on a girl.
What a hot guy.
What do you mean, young master?
Don't be sneaky, Juno has eyes on you.
Don't you think I can see that?
If she could stick with you she would already do.
I'm not interested. What's on my mind,
is only your safety, young master.
You're very determined with your job.
I'll tell my dad for you.
to give you a big bonus.
What were you talking about?
Nothing, I was thinking about what to have for lunch.
Hurry, those girls are waiting.
Wait for me
Wait.
Wait guy.
Just now, did you see how Sun helped me?
Yeah, he's as fast as a spy in the movie.
Yeah right, he's so cool,
I'm going after him.
Sure, I can see how you like him from Saturn.
How irony
Just as same as the eyes you have for Sky, girl!
All good, we like different guys, no drama
Pitty Bank. He's an odd.
Yeah, right.
Who's an odd? I can be a pair.
I'm Pitch. A junior.
We haven't introduced ourselves.
This time I won't miss.
Sorry, but I don't care.
Excuse us, we have to go.
Wait girls, we want to know about you.
Aren't you going to tell us at least your name?
No answer? Then I'll call you
Babe.
Toktaeng, Juno, are you guys coming?
Professor's waiting
Yeah, the professor wants to see us, let's go.
Excuse us.
Go go
Hurry
This is a second time.
That was close.
Thanks again for saving us.
No problems.
You guys shouldn't be alone just the two of you.
We should stick together, it's safer.
If anything happens, you can call us.
Should we exchange contacts and line ID?
-Since we are in the same faculty.
-Sure
Here's my number, you can call me 24/7.
and you can add my line ID.
Give your number to her.
Can I have Sky's number?
Then can I have Toktaeng's too?
Thanks
Hey, this noon
You didn't meet the professor, right?
Hey!
A senior is talking to you.
Why don't you say anything?
I'm sorry, but my words
worth more than talking with someone like you.
Ouch
Ouch, that's hurt.
Enough, Sun
-But he was going to attack you, young master
-I know
I said enough is enough. If he gets injured,
what are you going to do?
Ouch
You'd better watch it
Hey
I apologize
Sun
Let me ask you something.
If I didn't stop you,
what would you do to that guy?
-Break his arm.
-What?
Does it have to be that big?
Yes, sir. Because he dared to hurt you.
I know, but that's too much.
No, sir.
If I don't take care of them first.
Later, they will pick a fight with you again.
I know that,
but I don't want anyone to get injured.
But you seem to disagree with them.
I know that you'll protect me,
so I challenged them.
Why did you tell my dad about Toktaeng?
My duty is to report your daily life to Father every day.
But it doesn't have to be everything.
What if he doesn't allow me to have a girlfriend,
what'd you do?
I respected all Father's decisions.
But I don't. The reason why I want to study in Bangkok
is because I want freedom.
I'm a grown-up and I don't want him to control everything,
you know?
I don't get it.
I only know that I must do everything Father's ordered,
and nothing else. I don't care.
What a loyal servant.
What did he feed you?
Dog Food?
It's an obligation.
I was a left-over orphan.
If not for Father,
I would be dead or live on the street.
Whatever I can do for him, I would do it with no doubts.
Dodge like a monkey.
Stay still!
Why don't you dodge that?
Isn't it your order?
I accepted that.
I'd better go shower and dinner will be ready soon.
You told others that we are cousins,
then I'll ride shotgun.
but...
Can you relax
just a little like we are the real cousins?
Yes.
Just like that.
[Freshmen Initiation]
Our next activity is
we want a pair from each group
to compete in dance battle.
Which pair with the best move will get a reward.
Quick, c'mon.
Sun, come with me.
Are you ready?
Ready!
Ready, set, music
Go go go all out!
Sky, Sun fighting!
Sun, do it better.
Sun, break your legs.
Sun, go all out or we'll lose.
Sun, you make a big one.
Sun!
Where did he go?
Don't know.
Let's go after him.
Are you Boss Sakkhee's underling?
Can I have a look at that phone?
Excuse me.
Hey, Sky! Let's go!
Sun.
What's the matter?
Nothing
Are you sure?
Yeah sure
Really?
Are you okay?
Ask him.
Why did he suddenly run...
Are you okay, Sun?
What happened?
why you ran away?
It was nothing.
No? He said nothing.
Sun, I knew you chickened out. You can't dance.
What's up? Why do you stop laughing?
Wasn't it funny?
It's not funny anymore.
Here, we might as well
eat out together.
What tricks are you playing?
Why so, you've never eaten?
Toktaeng, it's my treat.
Wow, a rich type,
aren't you interested?
Shut up
Sky, are you coming?
Yeah, sure, what a lucky day to save money.
What are you waiting for?
let's go
-Yeah
-I didn't mean you.
But I'm starving, too.
You're crossing the line here.
You're just a bodyguard,
not my father.
But night clubbing is
putting yourself in danger, young master.
I've told you that the reason
why I study in Bangkok is for freedom.
You want me to just stay home
and go to classes?
It's freaking boring, you know?
I understand.
But your safety is my priority, young master.
What is so dangerous in going out with friends?
or there is something else you didn't tell me?
No, sir.
Then, just let me go.
I really can't allow that.
Boo!
Where are you going, young master?
Nowhere, do I look suspicious?
Sun, let go!
Hey, what are you doing?
I won't allow you to go out.
I'm not a prisoner.
You're not.
Your safety is my responsibility.
Let go!
Please understand
You better watch out.
Hey
Are you for real?
Anything I can help, young master?
Nothing, I'm hungry and ordered a delivery just now.
You sure?
Yeah
Look at me,
I'm wearing pajamas where can I go?
If that so, I'll go downstairs with you.
I'm worried.
Up to you
Come on
Good day, sir.
Just a moment
Okay, all this is 480 baht?
Where's my purse?
Sun, go grab it.
I left it in my room.
Go on, he's waiting.
-Yes
-Just a minute.
He can use mobile banking.
Bye bye
Enjoy eating, I left a snack for you.
Phew, I almost had a heart attack.
Come on.
Thanks, bro
Here, have this.
The clothes are pricey.
Thanks for helping.
Tonight, drinks are on me.
The night is still young.
Let's go, man
Man, looking good.
What a shame. You didn't see his face just now,
freaking hilarious.
You're laughing, but it scared the hell out of me.
Afraid he'll take me down, again.
Last time is still haunting me.
Come on, if anything happened I'll handle it.
Okay?
Sound easy, huh,
where else in the world for a good friend like me.
If not for you, I wouldn't help.
Okay, okay, tonight is my treat.
Aw, you know your role for tonight, come on.
Don't keep the girls wait,
or they'll be mad.
I can't tell at all, really
Ops, you knew then.
Yeah, look how you're craned.
I just want to know when Sky is coming.
He'll arrive soon, calm down.
Cheer's to you, beauty?
May I?
Sure.
One is cute, another one is gorgeous,
I can't choose.
Let me get through.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, not at all. We've just arrived.
Did those guys bother you, Toktaeng?
None of your business.
Yeah, it's none of your business.
It's our business with these two beauties.
Sweetie, so you're Toktaeng?
Want to come with us to our table? My treat.
Pardon me,
today we're together
and I'll take care of the bill.
Maybe next time, if so
What's the matter?
Do you have any problem with my juniors?
Yeah?
What now?
Do you know, young master
How precious your blood is?
Here, have them.
Wait Sun, do you dislike Juno that much?
Nothing goes as planned.
Young master!
Subtitle translation by:
Chanapa Sorachittiyothin