I think that's enough.
Do you love me, young master?
A lover...
No, we are not.
Maybe in the future.
Hey, ant nest!
Right now, just watching the stars...
makes me feel happy.
I apologize.
Did I make you uncomfortable?
Nah, I was just surprised. No harm done.
I'm afraid you'd feel uncomfortable.
I'm okay. It's fine.
Did you remember anything last night?
Sun...
Can I ask you something?
Last night, did you recall anything?
Nothing at all.
I was heavily drunk.
Did anything happen, young master?
Nothing.
Just asking.
What if,
you are not my bodyguard.
Would you still help me out like this?
Absolutely, I will.
Because I...
You what?
Tell me.
=Golden Blood=
Finally done for the day.
Pitch, bro.
Can we switch places?
Why?
I'm having a backache.
Alright, alright.
I'm so sleepy.
Bro, can I switch back?
Why?
There are rocks poking me.
There, there.
Hey, bro!
What is it?
My legs hurt.
I just switched places with you.
It's because I played football.
Hurry, your last chance.
Hold on, bro!
What the hell is it?
Can I get some sleep?
My body is aching.
Damn, do you have to be tired
before you can sleep?
Hey, what are you doing?
-You ask for it.
-What?
Godzilla.
A Godzilla?
Ticklish Godzilla,
you've ever heard of that?
You aren't sleepy?
You can't sleep?
Hey, stop it, bro.
Others might've heard us.
Pitch, what was that?
I'm sorry.
Why did you apologize?
We should head back.
It's getting late.
I can stand by myself.
Young master, why are you upset?
How do you feel about me?
Bro, what was that?
I don't know.
What did you just say?
I said I don't know.
How can you not know?
You just kissed me.
I don't know. I don't. You understand?
Yeah, it was my fault. Sorry.
Hey, you've got to have a reason.
Why did you kiss me?
What do you want? It was just a kiss.
I'm sleepy.
Can we talk about this tomorrow?
Where are you going?
Why aren't you answering? You tell me.
How do you feel about me?
How do I feel? It's not important.
You're talking to me.
Look at my face.
Tell me, what does "not important" mean?
I'm just a bodyguard.
My only duty is to protect you.
So, you only think of me as your boss?
I have no right to think otherwise.
Can you stop being stubborn?
There is no one else around here.
I know that you feel something for me.
Otherwise, you wouldn't ask me that
last night.
Do you love me, young master?
Just tell me truth.
Just admit it, how do you feel about me?
I'm only a young master's bodyguard.
No right to think other things.
Alright.
If you said so, I won't ask you again.
Where are you going, young master?
It's my business.
You only have to take care of my safety.
You do your job.
Other than that,
don't pry into my business.
I apologize, sir.
Then, I'll be checking the area.
Fine, go wherever you want.
Sun!
This represents my heart.
And this is yours, young master.
I'm just a bodyguard.
My only duty is to protect you.
I have no right to be something else.
You brought a lot.
We won't finish these by today.
Sun.
Mr. Bank.
Have you seen Sky?
I don't know. I haven't seen him today.
I thought he was packing up with you.
Sun, come sit with us.
Hey, Pitch, come over here.
There's room.
Hey, can I sit here?
What?
It's yummy.
Thank you.
Bank.
Bro, can you pass me the chilli paste?
Shrimp paste chilli.
You look starving.
Bank.
I...
Bank, are you full?
Yeah, I'm full.
Young master.
We should get on the bus.
We're heading back.
Does anyone sit beside you, Toktaeng?
Can I sit here?
Yeah, sure. I save this seat for you.
Thanks.
Sun, you can sit with me.
We're all here. Let's take off.
Hey, aren't you guys going to sing?
I don't need supper today.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Bank.
Are you calling
just to sigh all night long?
I'm bored. I thought it
might help if I call you.
But damn, it's getting worse.
What's wrong?
And what's wrong with you?
I asked you first.
Don't answer me with my question.
So what? You tell me first.
It's nothing.
Bullshit, stop being tongue-tied.
I'm not tongue-tied.
Dang it.
I hate it when people don't say
what they actually feel.
Right, I fricking hate that too.
So, what do you feel about me?
Why are you not answering?
You tell me,
what do you really feel about me?
Yeah true, it's frustrating
to be with that kind of person.
What was that?
I don't know.
How can you not know?
You just kissed me.
I don't know. I don't.
What does he want?
I can't figure it out.
Same here, I can't figure it out.
Hey, who did you talk about?
I was talking about you.
Who do you think it is?
I was just saying random things.
Talk later, I'll go to bed.
Alright.
Finally done.
After this class, let's play football.
Have some sweat to shake things up.
Sure, let's play.
Are you going to play football?
I'll go watch.
Hang on, before you go watch those men,
send me to the restroom first.
We'll be back guys.
Hey, hold on.
Sun, let's play.
You don't have to invite him.
He'll follow me anyway.
He has to stick with me.
Sun, is it okay
if Sky goes play football?
Why did you ask him permission?
Whatever I want to do is my business.
Calm down, man.
You were always listening to him.
Hey, wait, man.
Sky!
Go, go.
Sun, aren't you going to play?
I'm good.
Watch out!
Pitch, you want to play with us?
Yeah, sure.
I'll leave this with you.
Sky,
if you have more players,
then it's not fair.
Sun, come play with my side.
Yeah, Sun, let's play together.
There's not enough players.
Hurry up!
Go!
Go, Sky!
Hey, Pitch.
Watch out!
I didn't give you an order to play.
Well, you're the one who said...
that I have to stick with you.
That was close.
Hey, bro, you alright?
Whoa!
I'm fine. It was just a scratch.
No problem.
Scratch your ass, it might get infected.
Better go check at the infirmary,
I'll go with you.
Where have they gone?
Bro, you sit there.
Give me your hand.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at a kind person.
Kind? Okay.
Ouch.
What's up? Isn't it just a scratch?
Bank, can you properly dress the wound?
Who would use alcohol,
they use saline solution.
Ouch, it stings.
I didn't know that, sorry.
I'll find a saline solution.
Here.
Are you worried about me?
No, I'm not.
I just take responsibility for what I did.
Not like someone.
How do you know I'm irresponsible?
Bank.
What's up?
I'm asking,
do you want to go home with me?
Yeah, sure, sure.
Bank will come home with me.
Hold on, bro. When did I say that?
You are the one who hurt me.
It's your responsibility.
So, are we going?
Alright.
Okay, I'll leave first.
Can I see your wound?
-Are you naughty?
-Ouch!
Bye.
Wait for me!
Damn it all!
Dinner is ready, young master.
What about yours?
I thought that you'd like to eat
by yourself,
without having me.
I didn't give the order.
What right do you have to decide that?
I think it's more appropriate this way,
for us.
Why?
Because you think
you're a bodyguard. Right?
Fine!
If you want to be like this...
Get out of here, go!
Seeing your face ruins my appetite.
Go, get out!
Do you want to come inside?
No.
There's no reason to go inside.
Get off, get off.
Give it back.
Hey, wait!
I have something to tell you.
What do you want?
That day you asked me.
What was that?
I don't know.
How can you not know? You kissed me.
I don't know. I don't!
I can't answer it myself. What it was.
I only knew that
I've never felt this way towards anyone.
I only have this feelings toward you.
Are you satisfied with the answer?
Yeah.
You're not mad anymore, right?
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Not yet, your answer is fine
but not in the right spot.
See you later.
Aren't you going to come in?
No is no.
Bank...
Drive safe.
I'm worried.
Thanks, Pitch.
Bye.
Who the hell are you?
Father sent me to protect you.
I'll be staying with you here.
May I come in?
Just admit it, what do you think of me?
I'm just a young master's bodyguard.
No right to think otherwise.
I'm sorry. I broke your treasure.
I'll buy you a new one.
It's okay.
It's late and windy.
You should get inside, young master.
Are you doing this because it's your job?
You should get to bed.
There'll be an early morning class.
Don't stay up late.
Stop ordering me around.
I'll sleep or not
is none of your business.
I was listening to you,
because I thought
you actually care about me.
But now I know,
you're just doing your job.
There isn't going to be any trouble.
I will tell my dad to change a bodyguard.
-Young master...
-I don't want you...
to be my bodyguard anymore.
I don't want to see you again.
Who are you calling?
I'm reporting to Father.
No need.
But they're acting more violently.
I'll tell Father to take care of it.
What if I ask you not to tell dad.
Why is that, young master?
Your life is in danger, young master.
Please don't be stubborn.
I'm not stubborn. But I know too well.
You know how my dad is.
Take revenge in a vicious cycle.
I don't want to see that anymore.
More importantly, having you is enough.
I believe that you can protect me.
Alright,
I won't tell Father.
May I have my phone?
What's the matter, Sun?
Father, the other day,
Sakkhee sent his guy
to beat up young master.
The other day? Why did you just tell me?
It's young master's order.
He's afraid you might be worried.
So why tell me now?
Young master wants a replacement.
Replacement? What to replace?
Did you make him angry?
Dang my son,
he's really been spoiled rotten.
Out of all my underlings,
you are the best of them.
I want to be his bodyguard
until you get rid of Sakkhee.
Perhaps.
Will young master agree with that?
You don't have to worry about it.
I'll handle that.
Do your best, taking care of Sky.
I'll protect young master with my life.
Shane!
Yes, boss.
I have an order for you.
Gather everyone here.
Yes, sir.
On that shelf too!
Hurry, pack that too.
What's that smoke?
This is bad, this is bad, Boss!
The factory is on fire.
Our warehouse burnt down to ash, Boss.
Holy shit!
Hey, you fool, quickly pack them up.
Hurry up,
my goods, it's all burning out.
Hey, hurry up.
Phu.
Is this your doing?
I warned you, Sakkhee.
Don't mess with my son.
But you didn't listen.
Boss, the cops
have cordoned off the building.
Phu, I won't let you get away with this.
Mind your own business.
Damn it!
We need to leave now.
Sun!
Did you call my dad
saying I want another guy?
-Young master.
-Why?
You want to leave so badly
you had to tell him?
You're happy now?
Dad said after everything's clear,
he'll send another guy.
I want to ask you out on a date.
(Next episode)
What is your problem?
Just admit it,
that you also have feelings for me.
Your dad has stabbed me badly.
I'll wipe him off.
Wake up now. Can you hear me?
How can I live without you?
Sun!