This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
If you get rid of Jeong Do Jeon, I will also get rid of Lee In Gyeom.
Please keep him by your side
and judge him by his talents and as a person.
Go with Jeong Do Jeon.
I will go with Lee In Gyeom.
Just enter the Do Dang instead of plotting schemes in the dark.
General! If you talk to me...
Episode 19
He said that he will get rid of Lee In Gyeom if I also get rid of you.
So what did you say?
I told him that the two of you cannot be compared.
I need to see General Choi Yeong right away.
Father. Gaegyeong Mother has returned from her parents' house.
Is that so?
Father!
Aigoo, right. How are you?
General Choi Yeong knew everything?
Please tell me in detail.
That is all.
Okay.
(Boon Yi)
You've worked hard, Brother.
Boon Yi.
I...
I wish that you wouldn't get deeper into this work.
(Lee Bang Ji)
I need to see General Choi Yeong. Let's go to his house.
Let's go.
Excuse me. I saw, on my way here,
General Choi Yeong palanquin going to Hwa Sa Dan.
Did you do as I requested?
Yes.
We are not accepting any guests other than you today, General.
(Cho Young: Hwa Sa Dan owner)
Please don't worry and go in.
I'm sorry. We are not accepting any guests today.
Isn't General Choi Yeong inside?
Yes. It was reserved a long time ago.
It appears to be really important so please make an appointment for another day.
Minister Choi Yeong is waiting. Please go in.
It was definitely a Mongol. He looked like a merchant.
Why would General Choi Yeong meet with a Mongol merchant?
The man beside him is a swordsman.
Swordsman?
The way he walks and how guarded he was with me say so.
That's what I felt. He's a swordsman of considerable level.
In the Hwa Sa Dan, where General Choi Yeong wouldn't let anyone enter,
he privately met with a Mongol merchant accompanied by a swordsman?
What?
Jeok Ryong gave the ledgers of his dealings with Hong In Bang to General Choi Yeong.
He probably learned about everything that happened all this time.
So?
It appears that General Choi Yeong criticized our General for it.
The arguments have become bigger.
What is going to happen now?
Now, it's impossible to avoid a battle with General Choi Yeong.
(Lee Bang Won)
I need to see Teacher.
This is Young Master's private space.
(Min Da Kyung: Future Queen Wongyeong)
How can a Ga Byeol Cho girl come and go in Young Master's private space whenever she wants?
How come you're not answering?
I'm sorry but this place is an official space to me.
Young Master Bang Won and I have the same goal and are working together.
I have heard that you also know about this.
Also, I heard from Young Master that you are objective and wise.
I think of you as a person who won't misunderstand useless things.
That's right. I didn't think of that. I apologize.
But using informal speech?
You dare speak to Young Master using informal speech.
Is that also official?
You have different status from Young Master and he is a man.
If you marry into a Sadaebu noble's family,
even if the two of you were close before, you still have to use formal speech.
What do you think?
Yes. I didn't think about that.
I will seriously think about it.
Then...
Lee In Gyeom has no crimes and his collected contributions to Goryeo are not small in number.
Also, how would his old body be able to endure severe punishment?
So he will be sent to exile in Gyeongsan
in order to correct his misbehavior.
Gyeongsan? Gyeongsan is Lee In Gyeom's hometown.
What kind of exile is this?
Then what about Lee In Gyeom's assets? Are you going to confiscate his assets?
There was no separate discussion about the assets.
So the lands that Lee In Gyeom took from the people all this time
(Po Eun: Jeong Mong Joo)
will not be returned to them?
That's His Highness' will.
This must not happen!
The Do Dang should discuss this again
and send another petition to His Highness.
That's exactly it!
What crime do you all think those three people committed?
Their biggest crime was covering His Highness' eyes,
letting the Do Dang waver as much as they want, and discounting royal authority.
I, as the Prime Minister, am delivering His Highness' command right now,
but how can a royal command's prestige fall down to the ground like this?
If you challenge His Higness' will and defy all His orders,
you will be punished by law.
This will raise the royal authority again and raise Goryeo's dignity!
All of you, keep that in mind.
We are very pleased with  Lord Lee In Gyeom's decision.
Yes. Since you were speaking loudly
they could not speak of that problem anymore.
The do dang already became the elder's.
From now on no matter which group we are part of
we will manage everything according to your will.
I! do not have a single intention to work with you guys.
You guys just have to follow my plans.
This is the reason why you guys are safe in the Do Dang. Do you understand?
You, what did just say? Do Dang is mine?
This Do Dang if only for His Highness!
If you say that ever again, you'll be the next one I will send to Hong In Bang, who was your leader.
You are not feeling well. Why
you are taking the Hamguh to Gyeong San?
(Hamguh: a wagon for criminals).
With the blessing from His Highness, I am going to my hometown in my old age.
Why would there be any smoldering grudge?
I was born as a boy and had Dohajun on my hands.
I did everything that can possibly be done.
Lee In Gyeom
Do you feel regret about not being able to kill me?
That is right.
Every time I see you, you remind me of the words scholar Jo once said.
That Chojujigah has a very bad fate.
(Chochugigah: a family that has betrayed it's owner)
You bastard. To whom are you saying something like eating dog shit?
You! Act like a sinner and go inside with your head down and your mouth shut.
Go. Rest your mind and body well.
You'll have to live long so that I can sentence you to your punishments again.
The answer to the question I had when I first entered the Dohajun,
I'm leaving without knowing that answer...
I am Eunuch Kim Nae Pyung.
There is a big problem in the palace right now.
What about the guy Kim Nae Pyung?
They said there is no man named that.
Who in the world could they be,
and for what reason did they help me?
The righteous general Choi has saved an old burglar because of his personal feelings.
Yes. Since the big burglar has escaped the net and we only caught Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi,
I am worried that the people's despair will rise even more.
General Choi talks about sovereignty but
how can sovereignty be set right when the people don't feel right.
On top of that, right now the King is...
You already know.
King U; Goryeo's 32nd ruler.
You...
You were off by a halftone again.
Your Majesty. No, that is not the case.
Then your saying I was wrong?
You are saying this country's king is wrong right now. Am I right?
Your Majesty. No...
Then are you saying you are wrong or am I wrong? Answer me.
Please spare me. Please spare me!
Please save me.
Please spare me. please spare me!
Please spare me!
No matter what, he is the king of Goryeo. I am going to awaken this country again with him.
- Your Majesty!
- Please spare me!
Please spare me!
Welcome, sir.
This wench who plays the instrument had her note wrong, so I was giving her a punishment.
Your Majesty, even if the musician made a mistake
it is too much to take a person's life for that.
You enjoy killing people so much, but then
why do you only stop me from doing that?
From what I heard, you killed more than thousand people that were part of Gil Tae Mi and Hong In Bang.
Please put away your sword.
Everyone step away by a hundred steps.
What are you guys doing? I just said go away!
Strengthening the sovereignty? What do you mean by that?
Giving  more power to a king who has no interest in governing and is inadequate means that
Choi Young's power will solidify.
Furthermore, Choi Yeong, unlike Lee In Gyeom, won't care about the benefit of others,
so the government will only flow the way General Choi wants it to.
Then...
Goryeo has met a new type of czar
that it hasn't seen for years.
A new form of czar?
A czar with no greed.
A czar where the country has more priority more than his life or the lives of the people.
Therefore, a dangerous czar that can sacrifice anything for the country.
Excuse me.
There's something a bit strange going on.
During your reign, the Japanese pirates have attacked this country every ten days, and
with the continuous sickness and famine, people are dying. And
the Ming Dynasty, which is growing continuously every day,
is  threatening us the same way.
Your Majesty, now you have to personally participate in governing.
Take care of everything and recover your sovereignty, Your Majesty.
Ah, yes.
If that is what you want, I'll do that. That won't be hard to do.
Your Majesty!
However, then
put in some money in naetangeum for me.
(Naetengeum-money in the personal possession of the king)
What do you mean about naetamgeum?
Didn't you take possession of Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi's money?
Take some of that and give it to me as naetamguem.
Their possessions were more than the royal family right?
Is this a country? This is why the sovereignty breaks down.
So, give me a little bit of that.
The royal family is not well off so those musician think of me as a laughing stock.
Why?
You are probably thinking, "King Gong Min's bloodline is definitely not like this."
"He's definitely Shin Don's child."
Isn't that what you think?
Why are you not answering?
"Your Highness! That is nonsense!"
"That is complete nonsense!"
"How can such difficult words come out of your mouth?"
Aren't you supposed to say this?
I don't care from which bloodline you came from, Your Highness.
The only important thing to me is
the fact that you are the king of this country.
With Your Highness, I will surely
settle the past hundred years of disgraced history.
(time when the Yuan dynasty ruled and the King's authority dropped to the ground)
What is that?
At ten o'clock last night, a cart secretly came out of Hong In Bang's house.
Sam Jo from the Northern district saw it.
Isn't that the management place at Byeong Bu?
Did a thief get in?
Ah! It's not that.
The Byeong Bu soldiers handed the cart over to some people.
Deok Chil and I saw that. When we secretly saw it yesterday,
I came here to report to Leader Boon Yi
and our Deok Chil followed the cart
to where it's going.
But,
it has been two days
and Deok Chil hasn't come back yet.
Of all times, it was during curfew hours that a cart came out of Hong In Bang's house.
That cart was sent to someone
and the person who followed the cart went missing.
That's why some of our members have been looking for two days,
but it somehow feels strange.
What brings you here, my dear?
Gaegyeong Mother has come back.
Preparations have been done so let's go and give her our greetings.
I see.
I'll be back.
Bang Seok needed to recuperate some more, but
(Lee Bang Seok is Bang Won's youngest half brother.)
you had to hurriedly come here because of my message.
Not at all.
(Consort Kang: Lee Seong Gye's second wife)
If we make medicine out of walnuts, and he takes it long-term, he will get better soon.
At times like this, I need to be by your father's side.
Yes.
Since you know Gaegyeong better,
Please be supportive of my father.
Child. Do you know of Noble Gathering?
Yes. I haven't been to one but I have heard of it.
It's where noblewomen gather at Hwa Sa Dan to cultivate friendship.
Now that you have also become a part of the Lee Family of Jeon Joo,
you should go with me.
But I'm still not used to going into a place like Hwa Sa Dan—
The next meeting is on the fifth of next month.
Keep that in mind.
Ah... She can't win against her.
Do you know how strong Gaegyeong Madam is?
No, no, no.
Even if you say that, a woman's instinct is never wrong.
The way I see it,
Young Master Bang Won's wife is a lot stronger.
(Myo Sang: Moo Hyul's Grandmother)
What do you think, Master Hong?
This is a really strange place.
What's strange about it?
In this place, whether you're older or younger,
higher or lower position, man or woman, everyone's strong!
This is my first time in a place like this.
Even Boon Yi is strong!
At times like this, people like us should just...
(Hong Dae Hong: Moo Hyul's Master)
The wisest thing to do is to quietly live and die.
Let's go.
Yes.
So the cart went from this side over in that direction.
Yes, it seems so.
This is neither the way to the palace nor the Byeong Bu storage.
Just where is it headed?
If we're going to find Deok Chil,
we must find that cart.
Does that make any sense?
"The whole region of Goryeo's Northern and Western sides are originally Mongol territory
and now that the Ming have pushed the Mongols out of the border,
It is only right for the Ming to have control over it."
Why is the Ming Emperor making unreasonable demands?
In the year 1356, since King Gong Min reclaimed it.
It has been our Goryeo's land for over 30 years.
Of course!
Many Goryeo citizens are occupying that land.
The Ming Emperor's command has already been sent.
So, about whether or not we will hand over the northern side to the Ming,
let's listen to your opinions.
Relinquish the land?
How much blood was spilled by our Goryeo to reclaim that land?
If the Ming provoke a war,
my Ga Byeol Cho, to the last man, will fight
and protect the Northeastern side.
However,
there's no way of knowing the Ming's real intentions.
At a time when there's a sudden change in the continent, there is a high possibility that the Ming
are the ones to mentioned it.
In conclusion, I think that we have to diplomatically solve this problem.
How is it that General Choi Yeong is responding to this issue like this?
Then with your position of being in charge send them a letter about it.
But...
Are you not going to do it, Prime Minister?
Minister Lee Seong Gye and I have an appointment to serve and go hunting with His Highness.
Hunting? Me?
Hunting at a time like this. Isn't this strange?
I haven't told you about it yet. Just know that and make preparations right away.
Hunting. At a time like this, Minister Choi Yeong is going to hunt.
I learned that a portion of the confiscated assets of Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi
(Yeon Hee)
have been transferred to the King's personal fund.
How... It's something that cannot happen unless Choi Yeong overlooks it.
(Nam Eun)
Didn't General Choi Yeong's daughter get married to His Highness recently?
(Lee Shin Jeok)
Can becoming a relative to the royal family really change a person like this?
No. If Choi Yeong has changed,
he will at least pretend to be in more of a rage.
Choi Yeong is hiding something right now.
Minister Choi Yeong is waiting. Please go in.
Our Deok Chil's corpse,
from all the way up there, was taken down here...
Oh my. We've been looking everywhere and he was found so far away here.
Do you remember
the face of the person dragging the cart?
Of course. Not only do I remember.
From the time our Deok Chil disappeared,
I kept on seeing it a hundred times a day.
Please take our ajussi to Father Geol Sang.
How long will it take to produce 30 copies of a facial composite?
It only took half a day before.
Sungmoon-dong, Jeongseung-dong, Seojae-dong, Namdae, and Shipja.
Also Tanhyeon Gate, Jangpae Gate, Hwibin Gate, and Seonui Gate.
Please gather and command every member of the group.
The time will be tonight at the hour of Sool (7:00-9:00).
Yes, I got it.
A few days ago, Minister Choi Yeong emptied the whole Hwa Sa Dan and met someone there.
Do you know anything about that?
The whole Hwa Sa Dan was emptied?
What kind of person did he meet?
There were two of them. One is a warrior of considerable level.
I got it.
Sir...
Deok Chil of North Group 3
has been found dead.
How is it that a cart was secretly dragged out during that time of the night?
Also, if the person who followed it got murdered...
The police are thoroughly guarding Hong In Bang's house.
It's something that cannot happen without Minister Choi Yeong's permission.
Even murder at that.
General Choi Yeong, just why...
We need to trace the people who have the cart.
Yes. We need to expose this case.
You will be in charge of that side. I have something to look into.
A few days ago, General Choi Yeong met someone in an empty Hwa Sa Dan?
Yes. He looks like a Mongol merchant but I don't know who he is.
Aren't you the one recording guest access at Hwa Sa Dan?
The owner personally did it on that day.
Why are you being like that?
Never mind.
Just go.
Boon Yi! Boon Yi!
Boon Yi..
Boon Yi, I'm sorry, but...
So this person killed our Deok Chil?
That's not yet confirmed. This person is only a clue.
We don't know who those people are or what their goal is, but
we are sure that they messed with our people.
We definitely have to catch and punish them. We also have to know the reason behind it.
Ah, how can we just thoughtlessly listen to your orders, Leader Boon Yi?
Even if we have to split our bodies into two, we will find them so don't worry.
Please take care of yourselves.
As soon as you find a clue, please contact Father Pal Bong.
- Yes, we will follow your orders.
- Yes, we will follow your orders!
- Let's go!
- Alright..
What the... You aren't going?
About Lady Boon Yi. She seems like a Ga Byeol Cho General.
(Moo Hyul)
The Llady directs them efficiently so those people follow her.
Those people, don't they all look like the lady's subordinates? Right?
Ah, Master...
When did those people from earlier start to call you Leader Boon Yi?
The people from the Western district originally called me Leader as a joke.
There were only three people gathered today who were from the Western district.
The other people just copied them for fun.
The people gathered today
are all Heads of the Gaegyeong branch. Under them are about 20 other people.
So I'm saying that you're commanding hundreds of people around Gaegyeong.
What do you mean I'm commanding them? They're all people I work with.
Why are you like that?
It's dangerous..
What?
Never mind.
You're cool. You're cool, Leader Boon Yi!
Oh, right.
- By the way..
- What?
The Lady has caught me talking to you in informal speech.
Should I serve you as a young master?
No. I would like it if you continue speaking informally.
Why? It doesn't matter to me.
After thinking about it,
I am speaking informally so that person is also speaking informally to me.
A person who is like that to me,
there's only you. Isn't it amazing?
But thinking about such a person disappearing,
I feel upset.
I understand.
I will do it when there's only the two of us then.
But now that I think about it, I also go around biting people.
But in the whole world, you're the only one who bit me back.
Hey, do I go around biting women here and there?
I also only have you.
That, that... It's not good.
It's not right. It's not right.
Just like Bi Guk Temple, Hwa Sa Dan also has a record of people going in and out of there and everything that happened on that day.
But on that day, the owner personally did the records.
Even the other spies didn't know about it?
The record would be hidden in the owner's room so we have no choice but to look at it.
Then, let's try to do this.
Choi Yeong told Lee Seong Gye to get rid of Jeong Do Jeon but he declined.
So there is now a gap between Lee Seong Gye and Choi Yeong.
Owner, Jeong Do Jeon is looking for you.
I must not be caught here.
Stay here for a bit and secretly get out.
I will keep Jeong Do Jeon here.
Sam Bong, you must feel very confident
to think that you have the best swordsman in the country as your bodyguard.
Yes. He's a bodyguard who's burdensome and not worthy of me.
Then, please have your conversation.
Once you get out of the room, walk ten steps to the left and owner's office will be there.
How's it going?
Still..
I came to strike a deal.
A deal?
Because Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi left like that, didn't Hwa Sa Dan lose big customers?
You probably know that I work under General Lee Seong Gye.
Is it okay for you to serve Minister Choi Yeong?
He's originally a stubborn person so will he correctly pay for the information?
It's something that I welcome! Does wealth have eyes?
Whether it is Elder Prime Minister Choi Yeong or Elder Minister Lee Seong Gye,
I don't discriminate against wealth.
That's the spirit.
Then, I will be requesting more help of you in the future.
Until Ddang Sae comes back to the room, you need to keep on talking to Owner.
Ah, also—
Leader, Chang Sun has come.
He wants to meet you.
I need to excuse myself for a few moments.
Ah, yes. I still have something to say so please make haste.
I found it!
Someone's coming.
- Hurry up.
- Nothing.
The person whom General Choi Yeong met on that day...
He's just listed as a person with no clear identity.
She's almost in front of the door.
I guess she already got out.
What are you two doing here?
That's what I want to ask.
Warrior-nim, it's a misunderstanding.
I was going to quietly get out with this wench
but it worked out well. Just why is this woman in Hwa Sa Dan?
What are you thinking of doing by making her approach Elder Sam Bong?
So my prediction was right.
You wench! So, as I expected, you were a spy sent by Hwa Sa Dan.
We found him! The man who was dragging the cart.
He is called Man Bok from a thug hideout close to North Marketplace.
Please help me.
Ah, please give me some too. Please!
Who is the guy called Man Bok here?
Why are you looking for Man Bok?
You don't have to know.
Where is Man Bok?
Are you a government agent?
If we tie him up and beat him to a pulp, he'll talk right away.
Guys!
You bastards are not qualified as thugs in the back alleys.
What are you saying?
I'm talking about the most important ability to survive in the back alleys.
The ability to recognize who's strong.
You guys don't have that...
Are you saying that you are strong?
Me?
I'm just...
Hey, what are you doing?
Ah, yes.
Well..
Let's get this quickly over with.
Strike!
So, from the beginning, this is the reason why you came here?
It was partly that.
That woman's actions have been suspicious all this time,
and now that General Lee Seong Gye has become one of the top two powers, I thought we needed an information seller.
What do I need to do?
Don't you have nothing but information?
For this to end nicely, let's make a deal and hand over one bit of information.
What kind of information are you talking about?
On the first of this month, the doors to Hwa Sa Dan were all closed
and General Choi Yeong met someone in private, right?
Who is the person who met with General Choi Yeong?
I did catch the guy who was following us but I didn't do it to kill him.
It just happened...
I can kill you immediately here,
but if this person confesses just like that, it will end by being transferred to the investigation bureau.
Whether you live or die after going to the investigation bureau is out of my hands,
so you can hold on to your life for now.
Ah, yes. Yes. I will speak.
To whom did you give the cart you were dragging?
I really don't know who that person was.
What was inside the cart?
Everything, all of it, was gold.
Where did those people take the things transferred from the cart?
I also don't know anything about that.
Oh my, please spare me.
I really have no idea.
They just said that there was a deal that night.
Deal? What kind of deal?
I-I don't know...
What did the person who received the cart look like? Tell me in detail.
Yes. He was wearing a hat and a robe worn by monks.
So he's a monk?
I really don't know who that person is.
You emptied the whole Hwa Sa Dan for a person you don't even know?
It was an order from Minister Choi Yeong.
What did they talk about?
We also tried to listen to what they were talking about,
but they talked through writing so we don't know.
"I will not give away any information," was that it? Well, there's nothing I can do.
I will take that spy and will do as I see fit.
Wait.
One more thing...
On Minister Choi Yeong's way out,
he clearly answered in Mongol language, "On the 7th."
Besides that, there's nothing that I know.
On the 7th?
It will be hard to pay for this spy's life with just that...
I do know who connected Minister Choi Yeong to that Mongol merchant.
Who?
Clothes, monk robe... A bandana...
What else?
He looks like a monk but he has make up on his eyes.
Don't we know one person like that?
It was Jeok Ryong.
Bi Guk Temple's Jeok Ryong.
I don't have anything else that I know.
That was lacking but I will end it here.
I wish for good relationship with Hwa Sa Dan  in the future.
Please use this woman as a contact in the future.
Let's go.
General Choi Yeong took Hong In Bang's assets and made a deal.
He even used Jeok Ryong.
Aren't we supposed to find out the details of the deal anyway?
If a cart was filled with gold, just how much would that be?
What does he need to buy to need that badly?
Whatever it is, wouldn't it be in Bi Guk Temple?
Why are you looking at me?
Ahh, we need to tell the General first.
Father went hunting with His Highness.
That's right. I don't think we should give them more time.
Let's hurry and go.
Ah, I don't think this will do.
As expected, you have great archery skills.
I'd only heard about it but it's amazing.
That's too much, Your Highness.
Since were talking about archery skills, there's no need to be humble. Who could dare deny you as an archer?
Okay, okay. Let's have some rest. We've been riding horses the whole day.
Yes. Let's go inside the barracks, Your Highness. It's getting cold.
Looking back to when I got caught, there were a lot of storage rooms.
Can we find which room they kept the things from Jeok Ryong's deal?
We can just rummage through storage rooms, one after the other.
If we're lucky, we can find it on the first try too.
That has never happened even once in my life.
Please don't worry. I am always lucky.
On the 7th. What could it mean?
Also, why would Choi Yeong meet a Mongol merchant through Jeok Ryong?
What is this?
I think we really found it on the first try.
What did I tell you?
Let's quickly open them.
Here.
Eh? This... What is this?
These are water buffalo horns.
Are these all water buffalo horns?
What are they used for?
Composite bows.
It's the best material for making composite bows. They are all imported.
Just why?
This is the item exchanged for gold during the trade, right?
This is where I was kept before but there was nothing like this back then.
Also...
There's not much dust so they came in recently.
Young Master. Now we know so let's quickly get out of here.
Quickly.
There are intruders in the storage!
Let's go!
Run!
There! Right there!
Stop!
Oh!
Well...
Wait. Who is this here?
Ga Byeol Cho's Confucian scholar.
There's also a familiar face.
It's great that we're meeting this way.
Yes, I know.
Put down your weapons. They're guests.
Guests?
As you know, I am an information seller. Aren't you here to buy information?
Didn't you come here to learn about something?
What is so urgent for you to infiltrate the Bi Guk Temple?
You even brought the rat-like spy girl who escaped last time.
A rat-like spy, you say...
Listen, Monk Jeok Ryong.
If you don't apologize immediately, and are not careful with your words in the future,
I will put the reputation of Ga Byeol Cho's 20,000 soldiers and the Lee Family of Jeon Joo on the line
and kill you.
I swear it on the name of my deceased mother.
Jeok Ryong: Bi Guk Temple's Head Monk
Lady. I sincerely offer you my apologies.
Yes, please be more careful in the future.
Can we continue talking?
You said you're selling information, right?
What information? We already know a lot.
You took out gold bars from the state, at General Choi Yeong's command,
and acquired water buffalo horns, right?
It was in the first storage room we entered among the many storage rooms in Bi Guk Temple. We were quite lucky.
It's not that you're lucky.
Whichever storage room you go into, it will be the same.
All the storage rooms are filled with that many water buffalo horns.
Why are you smuggling such a large amount?
I don't know. General Choi Yeong probably knows.
I thought you have become General Choi Yeong's person, so why are you telling me this?
That person never pays for things like this.
No such thing happens to me. So,
I am going to strike a deal with General Lee Seong Gye.
Should I say that the information I am giving you is a present for the first deal?
We are the ones who found out that you smuggled water buffalo horns on General Choi Yeong's orders.
It's not information you gave us.
Ah... The present I will give you is different.
General Choi Yeong secretly met a Mongol merchant in this place.
There was charcoal and paper here. They talked through writing with that.
I think they did that so that I wouldn't be able to eavesdrop.
So?
They took all the papers they used with them.
There were some traces left on the next paper from the charcoal being pressed on it.
The writing can be faintly seen on the last piece of paper.
There were only three characters.
What were they?
Yalu River.
(the river between China and the border)
I did as ordered by that person.
Yalu River?
Yes. He definitely said so.
The information that I acquired from Hwa Sa Dan  is the 7th day.
Yalu River, on the 7th.
Isn't it some sort of an appointment?
Should I send someone there on that day?
On the 7th...
There were a lot of water buffalo horns there. They are used in arrows, right?
For what reason would they do that?
Isn't that just preparation for an invasion?
The Ming keep on going about something.
Still, it's too large an amount.
Yalu River...
No way!
Could it be? Teacher, you also mentioned it.
General Choi Yeong, who's supposed to be the most enraged about the Northern land problem, is not reacting.
Furthermore,
at a time when the Ming are provoking us, he is just calmly going on a hunt.
If our guess is right...
Sir, there's something strange going on.
Two months ago, at Yang Gwang and Gyo Ju's government offices,
there was a secret message for them to do a census for enlistment.
Not today but from two months ago.
Teacher... This!
Yalu River
You should speak now. You're taking too long.
Do you have something to tell me?
General Lee.
Yo Dong
It wasn't a Mongol merchant that he met.
It's definitely a high-ranking Mongol officer.
He's already contacted the enemy from the inside.
No way...
This is madness!
What? What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
We have already told the Yuan dynasty about this. Our Goryeo army will be crossing the Yalu River.
We will conquer Liaodong.
Choi Yeong to Liaodong...
He's going to conquer Liaodong.
Six Flying Dragons
Just do what I say, General Lee.
Conquering Liaodong. It's impossible.
This is not the right time for a small country to be attacking a large one.
It's a revolution.
Are you going to be the King?
I, Lee Seong Gye!