This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
The An Byeon Chaek has been approved.
Now, the base of revolution has been established.
Hong In Bang, in the end, your ambition has set fire to revolution.
Episode 10
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
The Flying Dragons Team at Viki.com
Why are you like that?
I'm sorry.
Did something go wrong?
Boon...
Ah, hurry and speak up! How did it go?
The An Byeon Chaek...
(An Byeon Chaek: a strategy to stabilize the national defense of the Northeastern border)
has been approved!
Hey, what are you doing? People are staring.
Is that important now? When I'm this excited!
Did it really get passed?
Yes. Everything went well. Everything!
The An Byeon Chaek has been approved.
Now, the distribution of power in Gaegyeong will be greatly restructured.
The ones who made this amazing feat possible were us. We did it!
But that was forged. What are you going to do?
Hey, it's not the time to worry but the time to celebrate victory.
You... As a person lives life, this kind of moment doesn't come often.
If you don't enjoy this kind of moment, you'll live a depressing life.
I don't want to live like that. No, I  can't  live like that.
Aigoo. Aigoo. Is that so?
Well, I'm like that too.
You bastard, you back stabbed me?
Back stabbed? Who is it that planned an assassination and is now getting mad at me and putting the blame on me?
Assassination? When did I try to kill you?
(Lee In Gyeom)
Not me, but my In-law. You sent an assassin last night!
(Gil Tae Mi)
Assassin?
What are you saying right now?
Forget it.
If it's not you, then it's probably General Choi Yeong.
No, what is this...
You bastard. Do you know what you have done?
Do you think that I don't want Lee Seong Gye to enter the Do Dang because I hate him?
Did it look like I was scared of my authority being in danger if Lee Seong Gye sides with Choi Yeong?
Well, it doesn't necessarily have to be that, right?
What kind of place is the Northeastern region?
It's a place that can decide what will happen to Goryeo.
To the down-to-earth guy from that Northeastern region,
you give him an autonomous region and if he advances to the center,
that man's strength will finally be out of our control, you stupid bastard!
If it was that important, then you shouldn't have sent an assassin.
I said that I never sent one!
General!
You knew about it, right, General? What exactly happened?
(Po Eun: Jeong Mong Joo)
I voted in favor of the An Byeon Chaek so that it gets approved.
Wasn't it the same for you?
That wasn't the case though. How is it that those people
You can ask them that then. Why are you asking me?
Are you going to release Hong In Bang's servants?
Are you going to cover up what happened in the Western district?
For a strategy to work, it needs to follow a sequence.
I just followed the sequence.
Then what are you going to do after that?
He'll probably strike me afterwards.
That is not a strange thing. Isn't General Choi Yeong originally the best person for defense?
(Hong In Bang)
The thing I'm curious about isn't General Choi Yeong's thoughts
but yours.
Instead of offering your assets, you chose to get the An Byeon Chaek approved.
Your hidden agenda, that's what I'm curious of.
Could it be that you are thinking of getting General Lee Seong Gye on your side?
Are you thinking of that?
Just watch.
It's Bu Jeon Swae Jeon.
(Bu Jeon Swae Jeon: "Pick up a stone, hit the stone."
The world alleviation plan has really started now.
Hong In Bang is a stone you are holding in your hands, Elder Bon Won.
But why is your face like that?
Who could that warrior be?
Are you talking about the person that poured down Heaven's rain on us?
It's said that you can't predict where a Pok Doo will bounce to.
(Pok Doo Bul Ga Ji: it's not possible to predict where a bean will bounce to when it's being fried.)
When the Heaven's rain falls down next time, we don't know if we will be Sima Yi or Zhuge Liang.
Are you referring to that man as the Pok Doo?
(Pok Doo: fried bean)
In this situation that I perfectly created,
only that suspicious warrior is not included in my calculations.
In this moment, the most dangerous thing is an uncontrolled variable.
I will look into it.
You have to go to Ham Joo now.
I have to.
Now, I have to meet Lee Seong Gye and let him know about the whole plan. It's time to discuss the system of establishing a country.
Then, should I go to the cave in Ja Nam Mountain?
Yes.
Inside the cave, if you look through the bookshelf, there will be papers inside a wooden chest.
Please take all of it.
You! Did you lie to me or not?
What are you saying? How would I dare do that to you?
(Cho Young, Hwa Sa Dan's Owner)
To make Hong In Bang crawl back,
I said that I will bring in Lee Seong Gye.
Still, that bastard brought a gift
and even said that he will lower the taxes.
If he was thinking of being allied with Lee Seong Gye in the first place,
shouldn't he have used it as his advantage, when I said I was going to bring in Lee Seong Gye?
But he didn't do that. Instead,  back stabbed me at the Do Dang today.
Also, what did the person you sent say last night?
Gil Tae Mi and Hong In Bang decided on offering half of their assets?
Yes, Hap Ha.
I personally heard that.
They surely decided on doing that.
But all of a sudden, an assassin came...
Wait, wait...
They already decided to offer half of their assets
and an assassin came in?
They misunderstood that I sent the assassin
and changed their mind?
This situation
was not planned by Hong In Bang.
Yes?
What did Gil Tae Mi say about the assassin?
When their swords met, he said this, "So what happened to Baek Yoon was your doing."
Like this, he speculated that he was the one who killed Baek Yoon.
In this palace, there is an influential force that I am not aware of.
There is someone controlling Hong In Bang.
A power in Gaegyeong that neither of us know about?
It must be the person who leads that assassin.
Gather all your information.
After the attack, Hong In Bang definitely met with someone.
Yes, Hap Ha.
Just who?
Wait...
Who will benefit the most from this happening?
Could it be...
Are you thinking of the same thing as me?
But it's not in Lee Seong Gye's nature to do this.
Lee Seong Gye...
What?
The An Byeon Chaek has been approved at the Do Dang.
If the An Byeon Chaek has been approved...
Teacher's Sam Bong's plan worked.
It's not because I don't trust you, Young Master.
(Moo Hyul)
Gyo Ui Bang Gwa said that "Buk Doo 2nd rank" or something doesn't exist...
Well, my position or my housing,
how will you provide it, if you break it down...
How many times did I tell you that is not the important thing, Warrior-nim?
No, it's not important. Ah, I'm really hungry.
Owner, please give me one more chicken. I'm hungry.
It's nice to enjoy life but you should stop now.
(Boon Yi)
Tell me. What are you going to do?
Father will not be able to withdraw the An Byeon Chaek.
How did you know?
My father is General Lee Seong Gye.
But saying, "I wasn't able to control my own child so things became like this.
I will cancel the An Byeon Chaek." Do you think he will do it that way?
Then how can he govern the Ga Byeol Cho?
(Ga Byeol Cho: Lee Seong Gye's secret private army)
He'll probably be enraged but he will just keep it in.
Of course, I'll probably get something broken somewhere or get cut off from the family.
That, I can handle.
You're sure, right?
There's no way that the An Byeon Chaek will be withdrawn, right?
You're going to withdraw the An Byeon Chaek?
That's it. That is the Northeastern region's standpoint that will be presented at the Do Dang.
So you, immediately get the horse running to the Do Dang and let them know that.
What are you standing there for?
Father, if the An Byeon Chaek gets enforced, then the people coming into the Northeastern region,
the families of the Ga Byeol Cho soldies who died,
even the dying people from the places our power couldn't reach,
we will be able to watch over them.
Is that everything? Ho Bal Do and his Yeojin tribe,
(Ho Bal Do: Yeojin tribe's Chief)
we  can raise a military power that can push them north of Yalu River.
More than that,
the Goryeo you have been protecting, it will be Goryeo's defense that will stabilize.
Are you also thinking of not listening to your father's words?
I have the same thoughts as Bang Gwa.
If the An Byeon Chaek is enforced,
wouldn't you be the one who can do it best, Hyung-nim?
Are you going to waste the Northeast's tax revenue like those stealing bastards in the Do Dang?
I will use it.
In my entire life! For the first time, I will use them in vain.
When I said I'm not going to go into politics, did you think it was because I didn't know what politics is?
Politics is like that.
To get the An Byeon Chaek approved, whether it is Hong In Bang or Lee In Gyeom,
we got help from one of them.
Then, it becomes a situation where I joined hands with those people.
But I, Lee Seong Gye,
because of my son's arrogant behavior and the words of a scholar I somehow met,
do you think I will do that? I will never do it.
If I, Lee Seong Gye, didn't make up my mind to do something, I never act on it.
So Bang Gwa, get a horse running to the Do Dang and let them know that.
And Lee Shin Jeok, tell Jeong Do Jeon not to dream in vain.
- And Young Gyu.
- Yes.
Secretly tell Bang Woo to capture that bastard Bang Won and bring him here.
Yes.
Why did they arrest me?
How are things going?
Did I get caught for nothing?
Excuse me. What's going to happen to me?
Look here. Hey!
Is Monk Juk Ryong still not here?
Yes.
But where did you send Monk Juk Ryong?
Things went well so he'll be back soon. Is Sam bong inside?
He's in the Monk's room.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
The Flying Dragons Team at Viki.com
The two of you didn't have a good relationship, right?
Ah, well... kind of.
Well, how can I have a good relationship with someone?
(Sam Bong: Jeong Do Jeon)
In-law persuaded me so I voted in favor of the An Byeon Chaek
but what are we going to do?
I am going to leave for Ham Joo in a while.
When I get back, I will have the proof of my alliance with General Lee Seong Gye.
I'll be expecting it.
Then, this time, when you get back from Ham Joo,
I'll see you in Gaegyeong.
It's an access tile to Gaegyeong.
I cancelled the Gyeong Wi Jong Pyeon against you, Sam Bong.
(Gyeong Wi Jong Pyeon: order that prevents one who is exiled from going into Gaegyeong after release.)
This...
I'm a Su Shi Joong so something like this is not much.
(Su Shi Joong: The highest ranking political figure in Goryeo - like a prime minister.)
I'm so happy I'm almost in tears.
I can now meet you more often.
That's right.
But Sam Bong, when you go into Gaegyeong, you should also be careful.
If not for me, we, including In-law, will be on our way to the underworld. You know that, right?
I was going to ask about that anyway.
Who do you think that assassin is?
You are familiar with all the distinguished warriors out there.
That's why it's driving me crazy too.
There's no way that a person of that skill just suddenly appeared.
A warrior is bound to be revealed during the process of building their skill.
So you also don't know about it?
It's obvious.
Don't you think that Hap Ha secretly trained him?
The Elder is secretly having different thoughts for when he abandons me.
That assassin is not under Lee In Gyeom.
He doesn't have any reason to do that to Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi.
Just who's authority is he under?
Hae Dong Gap Jok? Those people don't move for something like this.
(Hae Dong Gap Jok: a noble family of 10 generations during the Unified Silla Kingdom.)
Who exactly is giving him orders?
Elder Bon Won!
Regarding the Pok Doo you were talking about. That assassin.
(Pok Doo: fried bean)
I found out who's controlling him.
Who is it?
That... It's you, Elder Bon Won.
What are you saying?
Inside the cave in Ja Nam Mountain, this letter...
Sam Bong, I killed Baek Yoon according to your Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye.
(Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye: a plan to alleviate the world)
But this world is becoming worse.
Who exactly is this person?
You don't know?
(Yeon Hee)
How can a person you don't know be mad at you?
Also, how did he know about that place and the Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye Chaek?
I only talked about that plan to you and Hong In Bang.
Who exactly is he?
Did you go to Ham Joo and came back?
Hyung-nim, by any chance, did Bang Gwa Hyung or Young Gyu come here?
They are probably in Ham Joo. Why would they be here?
(Lee Bang Woo: Lee Bang Won's older brother)
What are you doing and not greeting him?
Ah!
I am Young Master Bang Won's 2nd rank Buk Doo bodyguard,
Moo Hyul.
- Buk Doo... what?
- Bodyguard.
I gave a position to him.
I saved Young Master's life not once, but twice,
I am warrior Moo Hyul.
- Is that true.
- Yes. It is true.
Also, this lady,
I, twice...
Did this lady also save you?
No.
She bit me twice. On my arm.
It would be great if you can arrange a place for them here at the military troop in Gaegyeong.
That person has an amazing innate strength.
I think it will be great if you can train him under you.
And this lady... Well, she'll do well with errands.
Ah, well. It's not a hard thing to do, but...
Excuse me. If you're going to do that, can my family also...
Family?
Ah, because I saved Young Master's life twice now,
I couldn't look after my family.
Hey, you also have family.
At the Western district.
Hyung-nim, she also has a family.
They are all persevering. They will work hard for their food.
Yes, hello. Yes, I'm part of the Ga Byeol Cho. Ga Byeol Cho!
(Ga Byeol Cho - living quarters)
We're staying here?
Hey, do you know how hard the training is here?
You don't even know that you're widely opening the door to hardship.
Hardship? That's something I always do. You said that food will be served on time?
Wow. Seriously, Goryeo is really about connection, wealth, fame, and family!
Among those, connections are the best.
How did you keep the family intact in the middle of that?
It's my grandmother's method of discipline.
Then, I will be back.
Thank you. For taking care of my village people.
It's just me returning the favor for you keeping my secret.
Let's go.
Where?
Where are we going?
Pick one.
Look here. Please choose a pair for her to wear.
If you brought your girlfriend here, the man should be choosing for her.
Is that so?
You choose and then put it on her, that's how you do it.
We're not in that kind of relationship to pick out shoes
Try them on.
Does it fit or not?
Well, I'm not sure.
Give it here.
Is this a bit small?
Just because I was being nice to you!
It's strange!
It feels ticklish.
Is that a woman or a thug?
♫  Even during the times when I abandon myself  ♫
♫  you are on my side  ♫
It's strange... it's strange...
♫  I recognized you a few times
Thanks to you, I am alive  ♫
♫  I restlessly follow your voice  ♫
♫  Even if for a thousand times  ♫
Do you like them?
♫  I pushed you down  ♫
You like them?
♫  I get captivated  ♫
♫  In your eyes, I am shining  ♫
Where did Ajussi say he would be?
Didn't Hong In Bang release him from the Gyeong Wi Jong Pyeon?
(Gyeong Wi Jong Pyeon: order that prevents an exile from going into Gaegyeong after release)
What are you going to do when you meet Teacher Sam Bong?
I can't believe what your telling me.
How can you guarantee that General Lee Seong Gye will not withdraw the An Byeon Chaek?
So I have to hurry and report this to Ajussi.
I'm going to meet him first and tell him.
For something like this, the one who caused the problem has to say it.
That's your problem.
Hey...
To be honest I haven't met Sam Bong Teacher even once.
But this time, we made the plan succeed together.
This time I'm going to meet him and get scolded if he wants to scold me or complimented if he wants to compliment me
That's why the person he needs to discuss the next step with
is not you, but me.
I also have my duty as a member.
I'm going to meet him first.
You don't even know where he is.
You, do you know something?
He's coming back to Gaegyeong after eight years.
I think I know where he would go.
Because of the one word you said, I bet my life,
but where are you?
The letter is gone.
Does that mean Sam Bong has finally come?
New Jo Seon
Finally! Finally we get to meet.
Okay
This is how men meet.
A historical meeting is like this.
Ddang Sae: Lee Bang Ji in the future
Just who is he?
That idiot.
Who are you?
I have waited for such a long time to meet you.
Me?
Yes.
Teacher.
A disciple I don't even know.
Then is the man behind me waiting to meet me as well?
What?
I've waited a long time.
Sam Bong.
You. You are...
You came as well!
Do you
know me?
Of course I do.
I know you very well
But I don't know you.
Who are you?
Well who are you?
The one who had his life stripped away because of you.
I don't know you. I've never seen you,
yet I scammed you?
Who are you?
I know both of you.
And very well at that.
Who are  you?
Right, who are you?
I am
Lee Bang Won.
Lee Bang Won?
But after listening to the two of you speaking,
it appears that the swordsman didn't move according to your order.
To think this great cause was put into motion by tangling with the inevitable, as well as a coincidence.
This is like Heaven's "Un" and Land's "Myeong" meeting.
(Un: fortune, Myeong: order/God's will, Un Myeong: fate)
In each battlefield, he comes like the wind and defeats Japanese pirates,
The Viper.
How do you know?
The Viper?
I followed the Viper and found this cave.
I came to know your will.
You followed me?
The day that you killed Dae Sa Seong Baek Yoon,
I was there.
Also,
this letter.
I saw this and to find the owner of this room.
I went out to find the Viper.
Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye.
(Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye: a plan to make a fair and righteous world)
Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye?
How did you know about the Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye?
Does it matter how I knew about it?
The only important thing is,
I followed your plan but this country has become more chaotic.
This rotten Goryeo is far from ending.
It is getting more rotten and is collapsing.
Your plan
was wrong.
No.
I might not know what the Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye is,
but if it's a plan to smash this rotten Goryeo,
that is going well.
The day that you killed Baek Yoon, it was started.
And yesterday,
because of your attack on Hong In Bang, the An Byeon Chaek got approved.
The three of us created this situation.
Now Goryeo will
begin a new era.
New era?
What's a new era?
Faultless people who cultivated a wasteland getting killed?
Or taking lands from the people with the excuse of protecting them from Japanese pirates?
That.
is that the new era you are talking about?
It's a process that we have to go through.
For every great cause, hardship follows.
Cause...
Hardship...
Teacher, what you said was right.
You said that the thoughts of people in politics are of little value.
Look at the big picture? Don't look at the tree but the whole forest?
The wild grass that gets stepped on there
doesn't even have peace.
is it going well?
In that process that's going well,
how many people need to die?
How many more need to die for that damn Pyeong Jeong Ji Gye
to end Goryeo?
But,
"it's going well".
I started it?
It was my fault.
I
placed a bet on something I shouldn't have bet on.
Shouldn't you listen to my explanation as well?
I was going to do that, but
just now I realized,
even if I listen to what you are going to say,
there's no turning back.
We
will not see each other again.
We will meet again.
If I meet you again,
I might kill you then.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
The Flying Dragons Team at Viki.com
It's that person. The one who left a letter for Bon Won.
He will come back.
He trusted your plan and executed it.
Don't you think he's someone who has a lot of rage against this Goryeo?
Did you say you are Lee Bang Won?
Yes.
I,
General Lee Seong Gye's fifth son,
am Lee Bang Won.
No difference. No difference.
Ask the world...
When deciding life and death, between politics
and a sword, what difference is there.
♫  Nameless bird in the sky  ♫
♫  why do you cry you mournfully?  ♫
♫  The ground where the flower wilted  ♫
♫  can't be found anyway  ♫
Where did you go that you're only coming back now?
Don't smile! I'll fall for you.
I'm hungry.
Do you have rice?
You should know shame.
You're missing performances every day, so why are you talking about food?
We don't have rice.
Sorry.
From tomorrow, I won't skip and I'll do everything.
Give me some rice. I might die from hunger!
Whatever.
Give me some rice. I said I might die from hunger!
Give me some rice!
- I don't want to.
- I'm so hungry, I might die, Gab Boon!
I said I don't want to!
I'm going to die from hunger!
What exactly are you doing that you haven't eaten yet?
Please give me some alcohol!
Don't do that just to anyone!
- I'm dying if hunger.
- Go perform and earn money for food.
Aigoo.
You...
Ddang Sae, you...
You were that warrior?
You killed Baek Yoon,
attacked Hong In Bang...
Why? Just why would you?
Why? Why? Why did you get swept away?
Just why?
Whose son were you?
General Lee Seong Gye is my father.
When you chose Father back in Ham Joo,
I was also in that place.
You eavesdropped?
I'm sorry. But,
the first time I saw you, Teacher, was in the year of Eul Myo at Jangpyeong Gate.
So I went to Seonggyungwan.
But that place has already been filled with the people of the three high ministers of the Do Dang
and Sadaebu who have renounced their belief.
So in whatever I did, I climbed
and got stepped on.
I climbed again and got stepped on once more.
'I might also
change like this.'
That's when I found this place.
I have seen all of your thoughts.
My heart raced again.
I looked for you.
That wind brought me to Ham Joo,
and finally I got to meet you like this.
I want to do this with you. I want to serve you.
In this great and heart pounding placement of the foundation of the great cause, even just at the edge of it,
I would like to join you.
Please accept me.
It is disrespectful for human relationships to start this way.
Be careful of what you do
and don't come into this room without my permission.
I will keep it in mind.
I will be mindful.
But what you said about me not going into this room again,
please take it back.
I already,
according to your plan,
acted on it.
Acted on it?
What did you do?
My father would never
stamp something like the An Byeon Chaek.
What are you saying?
The An Byeon Chaek that General Lee Seong Gye stamped has already been approved by the Do Dang...
Father did not stamp that An Byeon Chaek.
I was the one who stamped it.
I used his stamp without him knowing
and gave it to Lee Shin Jeok.
That An Byeon Chaek got approved.
So there was a different Pok Doo.
(Pok Doo: fried bean, you can't predict where a bean will fly to while being fried)
If you waited for Father to stamp the An Byeon Chaek,
nothing would have happened.
The great cause wouldn't have moved even by one step.
Yes. I stamped it.
Because Father is a person who will only move if something starts to happen.
As for taking responsibility,
I am already prepared for that.
What taking responsibility are you talking about?
If the General didn't stamp it,
then we're still that far away from it.
I have to persuade him, have patience, and be on the same page.
Even if it's hard, the first step to this great cause is to build trust.
But what did you do?
In a chaotic country,
didn't you say that their is a way in this turbulent time?
It is Nan Se Ji Geom
Yoo Byeol.
(Nan Se Ji Geom Yoo Byeol: A different sword is used in turbulent times)
Year of Shin Chook (1361).
When the Red Turbans invaded,
Gaegyeong was set on fire and suffered a fall.
At that time, there were four heroes who saved Gaegyeong.
Yes.
They were Generals Jeong Se Woon, An Woo, Kim Deuk Bae, Lee Bang Shil.
General Kim Deuk Bae
is your teacher, right?
But all four of those people died.
Did you know? During the time when Gaegyeong was re taken and the soldiers were singing a song of victory,
all four of them died.
I do know.
Why are you telling me that?
Generals An Woo, Kim Deuk Bae, and Lee Bang Shil
killed Commander-in-Chief General Jeong Se Woon after they won back Gaegyeong.
Then, those three Generals,
were beheaded for that sin
not even three days after Gaegyeong was taken back.
Do you know why?
It was because of one letter.
One letter that's not even great or long.
Privy council Kim Yong.
Because he was afraid that his power would be taken by those heroes,
he forged the King's name and sent a fake order against the three generals.
It happened because of that.
Are you saying that what I did is the same as what Kim Yong did?
Do you think that only four heroes died because of that letter?
Goryeo's politics also died. Why?
Subjects, the king. Everybody stopped trusting each other.
Even the king's name can be forged so what is still true in this world?
Because of that one letter,
that kind of world was made.
The result of that
is this Goryeo that we are both looking at.
A fake letter made Goryeo into this but
through my fake document, the An Byeon Chaek got approved
and the fire of the great cause has been lit.
Will lighting the fire of the great cause be the end of it?
The numerous plans that you have seen in this room,
a new country's establishment system.
Didn't you see the things that the General and I need to do together?
But you ruined it from the start.
Because of your careless actions, General Lee Seong Gye will not trust me now.
Father
already knew that it was I who did it without discussing it with anyone.
Then, he would think that I played along with you.
If it is you, would you trust someone who did that?
Also, what I need to gain is your father's, General Lee Seong Gye's, resolve.
His resolve to achieve the great cause together, that's what I need.
You
took away your father's purpose and resolve.
A chaotic world using a different sword?
There's a way in turbulent times?
There are three kinds of people in turbulent times.
The victim, the one who fights it,
and someone like you who goes along with it.
Anarchy's sword?
No. That is just a bug you are raising in your heart.
A person in politics usually raises a bug inside of him.
If you think that right now is a turbulent time,
that you have to survive in it, that there's nothing to do, it will probably be whispering softly.
But if you listen to what that bug says and follows it,
in the end, you will become a bug.
Those who go along with turbulent times make this world worse.
Even the government inferiors
who think that they need to survive during turbulent times,
will live stealing, killing, and spoiling.
How are you different from those people?
How is it that I...
How can you say that I am the same with those people?
Your father is not acting on it but you purposely forged his stamp.
You ridiculed the settlement between your father and I. How are you any different?
This place.
In this room,
you don't have a place.
It was this place.
My great cause that has to start in this room,
is not for going along with turbulent times
but for fighting them.
Leave.
I...
The thing I have committed,
please let me settle it.
That's what I have to do.
For you,
there's nothing more.
In this room,
you don't have a place.
I am General Lee Bang Shil!
You must be kidding! I am General An Woo!
I'm Kim Deuk Bae.
Look at this.
Ah, what is this?
You Red Turban bastard! Take my sword!
Why am I a Red Turban?
I will also be a Goryeo soldier.
Yours don't even have eyes, nose, and lips.
That's why you are a Red Turban.
I defeated a Red Turban!
Ajussi, why is it that mine don't have eyes, nose, and lips?
Ah, you guys, please be quiet!
You're really taking the life out of a person.
Ajussi, is it true that the Red Turbans were defeated?
That's right. The Goryeeo soldiers have completely defeated the Red Turbans
and won back this Goryeo.
Wow, then we can go home now?
Not yet.
We don't know where some of the Red Turbans are still hiding,
so we have to be the most careful now.
Yes.
You are the leader now, so you have to take care of the younger ones.
Really? I'm the leader?
That's right.
For now, endure with this.
I will go and check the situation outside.
You must not go out before I get back.
Do you understand?
Yes. We will never go out.
I will also make sure that the other children don't go out.
Okay.
I will be back.
Why are you crying again?
Because mine doesn't have eyes, nose, and lips
they say mine is a Red Turban.
When I come back, I will make eyes, nose, and lips for this.
Yours will be... ah!
I will makes you the highest position, General Jeong Se Woon.
Really?
Of course. It's true.
How is it that taking care of children is harder than looking after students of Seonggyungwan?
Ajussi.
Ah, what is it again?
You have to come back quickly.
We'll be waiting.
I know, I know.
What are you saying, Teacher?
To General Jeong Se Woon,
what did you do to him?
There was a royal order to kill General Jeong Se Yoon yesterday.
(Kim Deuk Bae)
So with Generals Lee Bang Shil and An Woo,
we killed General Jeong Se Woon yesterday.
Wasn't he the hero who won Gaegyeong back?
How can such a royal order...
I wanted to look into the royal order to know whether it was true,
but how can you check on a royal order?
Ah, this... This is impossible.
How can this be?
General Kim Deuk Bae, we arrest you for the crime of killing General Jeong Se Woon. It's the royal order.
What are you saying? I only received a royal order.
I clearly received documents signed by the King to kill General Jeong Se Woon.
- Hurry and arrest him!
- Yes!
You bastards! Don't touch me.
Take him!
You bastards, you bastards!
Why are you doing this? Why?
Please release me! The children might die. I need to go!
Please release me. I have to go. Please release me!
At the bottom of Ja Nam Mountain, there is a cave.
There are children I was taking care of there.
Please go and save the children.
I beg of you. Please.
They said that the bastard Kim Yong forged the royal order.
Because the four Generals are earning merits, he was afraid of his power being taken away from him.
No, no, no.
No, no. Those children nowadays don't listen.
Children these days... They don't listen to what adults say...
Those bad kids, really bad kids!
They probably went out of the cave. They porbably did.
No, no.
They were children who survived even during the rule of the Red Turbans.
It's nonsense. They would even fight with the higher ups.
Impossible. No, no.
Why did you think of that again?
How can you talk about that terrible day?
In the end, Kim Yong achieved Heung Wang Sa incident and succeeded in assassinating the King.
(Heung Wang Sa incident: fortress invasion incident by Kim Yong to assassinate the king)
Please stop.
You couldn't forget what happened on that day and you won't leave this terrible cave.
This is where you started.
So you always carry that woodcarving soldier that you couldn't complete the eyes, nose, and lips on.
That will do.
From now on, don't let your past disturb your present.
Just think of getting out in the future.
If it's because of that Pok Doo,
I will make that person take responsibility.
He's someone who would do that.
That Pok Doo is not the problem.
Another serious Pok Doo exists.
What you said was right.
That night, after Hong In Bang's attack, he secretly met with someone.
Who was it?
It was Lee Bang Won.
Lee Bang Won? Who is that?
Lee Seong Gye's fifth son.
What?
Also, that night, he came from Ham Joo.
Hap Ha. There was a report that Ho Bal Do has invaded the North.
A serious Pok Doo? Who is that?
War. So Lee Seong Gye is tied to the battlefield.
Did you say Lee Bang Won?
Yes, Hap Ha.
Fifth son.
Could it be?
Ajussi, you are an evil person.
Do you know him?
Lee Bang Won...
But if you listen to what the bug says and follow it, then, in the end, you will become a bug.
People who go along with the turbulent times make the world even worse.
I know that I did wrong.
But... It's not the time to receive punishment,
it's the time to settle it. I will go to Ham Joo.
A person who goes along with turbulent times.
A person who fights it.
It's cool.
So cool.
That's right, Lee Bang Won. From here on, you will fight chaos.
It's Lee Bang Won. The Pok Doo that's hard to control, and is linked by blood to the person that I am going to serve as my lord.
According to military strategies,
if you want the commander to collapse,
then aim for his horse first.
Teacher Sam Bong.
My place in that cave, take good care of it.
I will definitely go to it.
A serious Pok Doo.
Lee Bang Won... Lee Bang Won.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
The Flying Dragons Team at Viki.com
Six Flying Dragons
-You there!
-On the charge that you secretly made an illegal deal with Dae Sa Sung, Hong In Bang, to pass the An Byeon Chaek.
The shadow behind Lee Seong Gye...
Try to react to this move.
A bug has also started to crawl into my mind
Let's kill him. Lee Bang Won.
Don't die.
What are you saying?
Lee In Gyeom has declared war.
What are you going to do?
I will turn the tables.