As soon as I begin
my examination,
we'll find
what you're looking for.
We're going to make
some enemies here, Doc.
You should fear the living
more than the dead.
Vincent is not like
Matthew and Edward.
The more he's cornered,
the more he's going
to fight.
We received a tip that illegal
drugs are being sold here.
- No, sir!
- Men, arrest them!
- That's not true, sir!
- You must be mistaken!
Walter's death isn't caused
by blunt force trauma.
Fentanyl?
Walter was poisoned.
Mama Mona?
Mama Mona. Mama Mona.
What are you doing here?
Of course, I came here
to comfort you.
You know, Stella...
I've spent half my life
in this club.
This is where I started to work
and build dreams.
This is where I learned
to love
and got my heart broken.
You are all like
a family to me
but I failed all of you.
Mama Mona.
You only lost the club.
I'm still here.
How can I get up again?
The owner
is kicking us out
and then they'll
sell this property.
It's a sign.
You're good
in managing a business
and dealing with people.
And most of all...
you're good
in handling money.
Money?
I don't have money.
Well, I do.
Stella...
That money
is for your siblings.
Mama Mona.
I've already set aside
some money for them.
We'll put up a restaurant
instead of a club.
We can be business partners.
I guess this is also
our chance...
to start a new life.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
This is a pleasant surprise,
my friend!
Oh.
The group said we're having
a meeting later.
- Are you going to attend?
- Yes, Arthur.
So what brought you here?
Is there a new
business opportunity
that you want to discuss
with me?
No, not business.
Something more important.
Something personal.
Family.
What about family?
You see, we're both fathers,
but you don't have
a daughter.
Because if you did,
you'd understand...
that one of the things
I hate
is when someone
makes my daughter cry.
Oh, I don't have
the full picture yet.
But once I do...
I'm sure I'll be able to help
you and your daughter.
Daphne is very close
to us after all.
That's good to hear, Arthur.
Really good to hear.
We've been through a lot
together,
and you owe me
a debt of gratitude.
It'd be a waste
to ruin everything
because of something
so trivial.
Edward.
We need to talk.
About what, Dad?
About Daphne.
Her father talked to me
and I didn't like what he said.
You know very well
how our family ties with theirs.
Dad, I'm not leading Daphne on.
She knows
that I'm courting Catherine.
Did you know that you're
the most sensible of my kids?
But you also know
that Daphne's family
is our biggest business partner.
And you're putting it at risk
just for a woman.
Dad, how do you expect me
to do anything I don't want to?
Edward.
You know how tough I am
as a father.
Do you think I'd want
to see you suffering?
I'm just saying.
Look at what's happening
with Vincent.
Do you think he will
have it easy with Stella?
Learn from his shortcomings.
Edward, what is this?
You resigned from your job?
What's going on?
Are you going on a trip?
I'm going to stay at the condo.
Uh...
You're leaving home?
Honestly, Mom, after
everything that's happened,
especially between us,
and Dad's pressure,
I want some space.
I'm tired of all the fighting.
This'll help me
be more independent, too.
T-there's no reason
for you to do this.
Uh... I won't be at ease.
I'd only get worried about you.
Mom, let's not argue
about this, too, please.
Alright, just... Just give me
some more time, okay?
I'll have the condo cleaned up
so you can be comfortable.
And I need to make sure
of your safety.
Mom, no need.
N-No, I... I insist, okay?
I'm still your mother.
Just do this for me.
So that I'll have peace of mind.
Claudia.
Where's Bea? I just wanted
to give her these books.
Uh, she's still showering.
I'm sure she's gonna be happy
to see you.
Maybe, you can stay,
and have lunch with us?
Alright.
We need to talk, anyway.
Really?
Tell me. I'm all ears.
Given your intimate relationship
with Walter,
I'm sure he'd told you
about himself, his plans,
and his connection to our family
and about his job.
Stop this, Vincent.
What game are you playing?
Whatever I say,
you'd still get hurt.
This isn't about us, Claudia.
I just want the truth
so I can clear up my name.
It's unfortunate for you
that you're closest to him.
And I'm hoping to get
the answers I need.
Well, then,
don't keep your hopes up.
Walter and I didn't share
anything deep.
You know that.
Not like us.
We didn't do drugs together.
So, that's what
you came here to say
while I'm here,
trying to connect with you?
Because that's the real cause
of his death.
Wait...
So, you're accusing me
of drugging Walter to death?
He supplied you with it.
You'd always sneak out and
do stuff with him, didn't you?
Well, you're truly desperate.
I'm giving you a chance
to clear your name.
I'm this close to finding out
about the truth.
You know what?
If you're here to accuse me,
I'd rather you leave.
Claudia, I know you know
something to clear up this mess.
Now, tell me what it is.
Get out.
I'll just give these to Bea.
No.
And you can't see her anymore.
Leave!
Didn't you hear me?
I said, leave! Now!
Crap.
Matthew. We need to talk.
To be honest with you,
I'm so nervous right now.
What if I get blamed
for Walter's death?
Vincent has a reason
to bring me down.
We were right.
I'm an easy target!
Relax. I'll talk to Dad.
He'll figure it out.
Besides, we've been following
Vincent for a while,
and we're still safe.
You should stop panicking.
They're just waiting
for Dad's orders.
That means, Dad is the one
hiding the truth...
Because he knows
what really happened to Walter.
Good luck, Sir Edward.
Thank you.
Edward!
Why did you resign?
You'd always tell me
to follow my dreams.
I just thought,
what if my dreams
aren't here at Fides?
Is that the real reason?
You're the real reason.
Then, I'll resign!
I won't let you do that.
If I leave, they won't go
after you anymore.
Not even Daphne nor Mom.
I love you, Catherine.
I don't like
seeing you hurting..
You got your wish.
You will never see me again.
So, that's it?
You made me feel special.
You told me you'd fight for me.
Just to leave me behind?
You're even throwing away
our friendship.
It's not easy for me
to just treat you as a friend.
Why?
Life isn't easy..
Do you think it's easy for me
to deal with your mother?
Do you think it's easy to accept
that you deserve Daphne?
You know what, Edward?
It's so hard to love you!
So you love me?
Edward...
No take-backs.
Oh, my god!
So, who's going to be the CEO?
Vincent.
Vincent? Not me?
I thought we had a deal.
Teresa Lopez.
That's the name
of your real mother.
She used to work for me.
Look, I became an orphan
because of you.
And I stay true to my promise.
It's payback time.
I won't let you get away
with what happened to her.
You've been stealing
from my company for years.
Stealing?
No.
I wouldn't call it stealing.
I'd call it...
a payment.
Why didn't you tell me
about your real identity?
Did you ask?
I will fucking bury you.
And how exactly
will you bury me...
if I know where
all the skeletons are?
Remember her?
I know everything
you did to her.
And she just happens
to be my newest...
my newest exposé.
if I don't get
the CEO position.
I'm glad you kept your word.
And don't worry,
your secrets are safe with me.
Dad.
We have a problem.
Vincent knows something
about Walter's death.
Vincent is onto me.
He asked me if I drugged Walter
the night he died!
Why would he ask you that?
Dad, I don't know!
He was talking about drugs
like it was
Walter's cause of death!
But it's not, right?
He was hit in the head
for God's sake!
Where's Dad?
He's in his office, sir.
He's speaking to Sir Matthew
and Ma'am Claudia.
- Okay.
- Alright, sir.
I'll go there by myself.
I'll keep an eye out here.
Go ahead.
Blunt force trauma.
That's what
the autopsy report says.
Do you have any idea why Vincent
is asking you about drugs?
Did he show you anything?
No, Dad.
He showed me nothing.
But he seems so sure.
Maybe Vincent's
pressuring Claudia, Dad.
But I did not kill him!
This can't be happening, Dad!
Come on, you have to protect me.
Please.
This will ruin my life!
We need to know
what Vincent has.
Stella?
Uh...
Good evening, ma'am.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for Vincent.
Where is he?
I don't know.
I think he's looking for you.
Wait!
Dad, remember,
we all know what happened
to that Dr. Castro, right?
She did a re-autopsy
on Walter's body.
Vincent was there
when that doctor died!
Maybe he found out
something from her?
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe she's right.
Vincent did see her
at her clinic, so...
I'm so confused!
Why is the re-autopsy result
so important?!
Was the initial findings wrong?
Let me handle this, okay?
- But, Dad--
- No, please.
Claudia, do as I say,
Don't say another word
to Vincent.
Okay?
Wait!
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Arthur.
I have something important
to tell you.
About what, Stella?
Let's talk over there.
Come on.
I don't take orders from you!
Are you going to tell me why
you and Vincent are here or not?
Madam, what I have to say
is very, very important.
Mom.
Oh, Vincent.
It's good that you're here.
I need to speak
with you and Dad.
Oh, come on, Vincent!
Stop this drama.
What are you going to say now?
What's going on here?
I've had some time to think
over the last few days.
So I would like to start with...
an apology.
I shouldn't have
gone against you.
I owe a lot to this family.
From now on, I won't be
saying anything against you.
Oh, yeah?
But you confronted me
about Walter, right?
Remember?
And you accused me
of drugging him.
Because you discovered
something about his death.
And now, what?
You're acting like this?
- I'm not buying it!
- Claudia.
I'll let the police
uncover the truth, Claudia.
What about our deal with her?
I'm giving everything up...
except Stella.
She's my one request.
Now, we wait
for someone to slip up.
But then what?
You promised them
you'll stop investigating.
That's why we have
to be extra careful,
so they don't find out what
we're doing from here on out.
Andres?
Hello, Vincent?
Do you remember a case involving
your mom around 30 years ago?
No. Why? What happened?
I don't know. I just saw
her name in an old logbook.
The report said she came to the
precinct with physical injuries.
But she's not the type
to get involved in that.
Here's what's odd.
It never became a case.
It's like it was covered up.
Vincent?
Where are you, Edward?
I'm actually on my way
to my unit.
Where's Mom?
On the way there too.
She has my stuff.
I'm moving in today.
- Mom.
- Oh!
Oh my god.
You startled me.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Edward's a grown-up.
You don't have to
baby him anymore.
I'm just trying to talk
some sense into your brother.
He's impulsive, like you.
I'm not even done
renovating this unit.
What are you doing here?
Edward said you'd be here.
Truth is...
I want to talk you, Mom.
About what?
You filed a report at a
police precinct 30 years ago.
What happened?
How did you find out about that?
You came with
physical injuries
asking for help
from the police.
It was nothing.
Why didn't you file a case?
And why was
the report incomplete?
Listen, I was
a victim of a robbery.
I fought back
that's why I was injured.
But it was a waste of time
to press charges.
Please, don't be paranoid.
Not everything
is some bad conspiracy.
You only feel this way
because of Walter's case.
What's the matter?
Vincent found out about
what happened before.
What do you mean?
He knows about the incident
30 years ago.
What do you mean?
What does he know?
Not a lot.
The police have no records.
But I had to lie
to Vincent again.
We kept this a secret
for so long, Arthur!
I can't go back.
I can't.
It's been 30 years.
But I remember it
like it was yesterday.
Wait!
Who is it?
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't I be asking you that?
- Whose house is this?
- Wait.
- Jacqueline, let me explain.
- Huh?
- What are you hiding?
- Wait.
- Who's here?!
- There!
- Wait.
Arthur?
- I knew it!
- Arthur?
Jacqueline, wait!
How dare you!
We have children,
you homewrecker!
- He loves me.
- What?
You whore!
Rebecca...
Arthur...
Vincent cannot find out
about what happened.
I know, I know.
I will not let that happen.
Vincent won't find out
about anything else.
Only Walter knows the truth,
and brought that
with him to the grave.
Let me.
Sir, wait.
As usual,
please sign here first.
Thanks.
Alright, sir.
- Bro!
- Sir, sir!
- Please sign here first.
- Wait.
George Tobias.
Done. Thank you.
- Okay, sir.
- Bro.
I discovered a file.
Condominium Certificate
of Title. CCT.
Here.
The condo is under
Walter's name.
Yeah, and why was
he given a condo?
That's what we need to find out.
Bro. What are we going to do?
If anyone knows what his life
in the condo was like,
it would be his neighbors.
I've got an idea.
Bro.
Do you think this will work?
George, not everything can
be done the easy way.
We can't talk to
every single person here,
but we can find a way
to make them come to us.
How long have you
been living here?
Um, four years now.
I've been here
three years.
Actually, our units
are on the same floor.
Okay. So, how was
Walter as a neighbor?
Um, he was okay.
He didn't really mingle much
with the other homeowners.
- Yeah.
- Well, hopefully,
my sibling will mingle
with the other homeowners.
Congrats, Eddie Boy!
- Hey, Matt.
- Yeah!
Hey, Vincent!
George!
What are you doing here?
I saw this at home.
I should probably be offended.
What's this? Just you and
Eddie Boy having all the fun?
You don't want to invite
Mighty Matthew to celebrate
Eddie Boy's newfound
independence?
Enough talking. Let's party!
The lighting is so boring!
There we go!
Let's set the mood!
This is a housewarming
party, right?
Everybody!
Mighty Matthew brought
the drinks!
Let's party!
Edward.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I saw Matthew's story.
You're having a party
and didn't even tell me.
So what's going on here?
Housewarming party.
I live here now.
Where's Katherine?
She's not here.
Yo, Katherine!
Excuse me.
Good thing you made it.
- Katherine.
- Oh.
Katherine.
I'm so happy you're here.
Guys, this is Katherine.
My girlfriend.
When I say mighty,
you say Matthew!
- Mighty!
- Matthew!
- Mighty! Hey!
Drink more, drink more!
Yes!
Ma'am.
Is there a problem?
You guys are so loud in here.
You're disturbing the neighbors.
Sorry, we're just having
a housewarming party.
If you want,
you can eat here.
No, it's fine.
You're being a nuisance.
I thought it would be
quiet once Walter left,
but apparently not.
What did Walter do here before?
Walter was such a huge
nuisance when he lived here.
He loved throwing parties.
I even reported him to
the admin a few times.
I could see all sorts
of women coming over.
But there was one woman
who came over all the time.
Is she the one who
came here all the time?
Not her. This one.
She's the one
who was here often.
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
I don't know what was
going on between them,
but she came here often.
Whenever I reported
Walter to the admin,
she was the one who
came to handle the mess.
Mom!
Vincent.
Why did you want
to see me, dear?
I thought Walter was just
one of the people dad helped?
What are you talking about?
We found out he was
bringing women to the condo,
and you were one of the
people who visited him often.
What are you talking about?
Did you really think
we wouldn't find out
that the condo is registered
under Walter's name?
Who exactly was
Walter in our lives?
Was he Dad’s protégé,
an employee,
or a family friend?
What are you hiding?!
Enough, Vincent. Stop!
Mom, answer me.
Did you have an affair
with Walter?
- Mom!
- In the past!
Yes, I had an affair
with Walter.
I just met your mom recently,
but it never crossed
my mind that
she could do
something like that.
If Walter really did have
an affair with my mom,
that would be reason enough
for my dad to want to kill him.
Stella...
No one crosses Arthur Cabrera
and gets away with it.
If your dad knew about their
relationship from the start,
why did he wait so long?
Maybe he had another reason.
Or perhaps...
Walter had something
on Arthur Cabrera
that kept him from being killed.
That's what I need to find out.
Vincent, come take
a look at this.
Katherine and I
found this, Vincent.
I told her we'll only tell you.
Since we don't yet know
what's hidden behind that wall,
it might be dangerous.
You made the right decision,
Edward.
The less Katherine knows,
the safer she's going to be.
There's a room
behind the wall?
I know, right?
Have you checked the other side?
Not yet. I don't know
if it has that.
What the hell was Walter up to?
Vincent.
What do we do now?
I know someone
who can help us.
Bro.
He's still working on it.
But it's almost open.
You're just in time.
Where's Stella?
She'll be here. She just
had to stop by somewhere.
Oh! There you go!
It's done.
Thank you, Mister.
- I'll see you out.
- Okay.
Mister Johnny,
Edward will pay you.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
Let's go.
It's all bank documents.
And the amounts are huge!
Everything is under
Walter's name.
Vincent.
It's your birth certificate.
Since I was
just accidentally found,
I didn't have
a birth certificate.
I only had an official
birth certificate
when I got adopted.
It's indicated there that
Mom and Dad are my parents.
I'm just wondering
why this is in Walter's safe
when everyone knows
that I'm adopted.
Is that real?
We already know
how Walter worked.
This was all part
of his plan.
But...
what was he planning to do
with this birth certificate?
He wouldn't have been
able to use this against us.
This is my mom.
The woman in the picture
is my mom.
Wait.
Why would your mom's picture
be in Walter's safe?
What is it doing here?
Your vital signs
are still normal.
That means
you'll still live longer.
Well?
What are we going to do
with that patient?
That's what
I'm thinking.
How are we going
to get paid?
You know,
if we weren't getting paid big,
I wouldn't stay here
and do this.
Now I know why he hasn't been
calling or visiting.
He's already dead.
What the heck is this,
Sir Walter?!
Tend to your patient.
Look.
Sir Walter is already dead.
The problem is,
we don't know how to get
our payment from him.
My mom...
isn't like other moms.
She doesn't care about her kids.
She'd go with different men
every time.
So, after she left you,
she never tried to contact you?
She disappeared like a ghost.
Did you try to find her?
Why should I?
Do you think
that was the first time
she abandoned me?
When I was a kid,
she would always leave me
with our relatives.
And whenever she'd come back,
she'd bring a new kid in tow.
So...
Why would Walter have
your mom's picture?
Do they know each other?
I don't know.
That was an old picture of Mama.
I wonder what connection
she had with Walter.
Are you sure
you're her firstborn?
Vincent.
It's indicated
in Walter's records
that his mom is Teresa Lopez.
Walter wouldn't have
flirted with me
if he knew
that we're siblings.
Walter warned you
about our family.
I wonder how they're
all connected to each other.
I think it's unlikely
for my mother
to have any connection
to your family.
That's impossible.
Their worlds are too far apart for their paths to intersect.
Uh... I-I badly need some
right now.
Where are you?
Okay.
Where are you going?
Um... I just...
have some errands to do.
Why don't you just let Fiona
run your errands?
Why? Am I being held
as a prisoner here?
After all that's happened,
I don't want anything
to happen to Bea.
And you know,
you're going back to your...
old bad habits.
Are you using that against me?
Not at all.
I'm stopping you because I
don't want you to ruin yourself.
Not just for Bea but because
you're part of this family.
At this point,
I don't know what family
means anymore.
And us being a united front?
I don't think so.
Because everyone here
has their own agenda.
What are you talking about?
What do you know
about Walter's death?
Who really killed him?
I have a feeling
that Claudia's up to something.
She's plotting something
behind our backs.
What do you think she can do?
Did you talk to her?
Maybe you've said
or done something
that's making her act this way.
Arthur, she's been acting up!
I still have
all the evidence here.
I'm afraid.
Claudia may be playing us.
Maybe she's just waiting
for the right time.
Remember, she had
an affair with Walter.
It's possible she knows
everything Walter knew.
"Complainant: Jacqueline Cabrera
Respondent: Unidentified Male"
"Nature of Complaint: Rape"
Vincent.
Are you really sure about this?
Only my mom
can answer my questions.
Stella, just stay here.
Vincent...
Mom.
- Vincent!
- What are you burning?
Uh, it's nothing.
- Uh, let's just stay inside.
- Answer my question.
I said it's nothing!
Claudia's becoming a liability.
She is the weakest link.
Is the evidence we've gathered
enough to use against her?
Why do you want
to burn this?
I was just decluttering stuff.
T-That's nothing.
Mom, you told me
this is just some petty crime.
- What are you really hiding?
- It's really nothing.
And you think I'll believe you?
Did you really come here
to visit me,
or to accuse me?!
I came here because
I need answers from you.
About what?
About my identity.
About who
my real parents really are.
Come on, Vincent!
After all this time?!
Why do you want
to know who they are?
Why the sudden interest?
Do you know them?
Mom, did they try to find me?
What's going on with you?!
It's because of this.
What are you doing here?
I-I just came along
with Vincent.
He wants to talk to his mom.
Just let them talk
to each other in private.
- Get out of my sight!
- Ow!
How did you get this?
How did that end up with Walter?
He was blackmailing me.
He wanted more cash.
He wanted more property.
And this is the proof
of what a terrible person he is!
And how could he use that
against you, Mom?
Hold on.
Is it true that you and Walter
had a relationship?
Are you and Dad both going
to keep feeding me
nothing but lies?!
Vincent.
Mom!
Vincent, get out of here!
- Mom!
- Leave!
I'm not leaving until I get
the answers I deserve to know!
Just tell the truth.
Don't you care about
your son's peace of mind?
Shut up!
- You don't get to speak!
- Hey, why are you so mad, Dad?!
What are you and Mom
hiding from me?!
- Shut up!
- What are you hiding from me?!
- Arthur, stop!
- Shut up!
- Aah!
Arthur, stop it! No!
Vincent!
Vincent. Vincent.
Just tell me the truth!
Don't listen to him.
You're my son, Vincent.
I'm your real mother.
If you're my real mother...
Hold on...
Who's my real father? W-Why
isn't his name on the document?
Mom!
Mom, just answer me!
You've kept this from me
my entire life!
Just answer me!
Mom, just answer me!
- Is it hard to tell me?!
- Shut up! I said, enough!
- Stay out of this!
- For so many years...
Mom, just tell me.
I couldn't tell you who your
father is because I don't know!
Because I was raped!
What?
Your dad and I had problems.
I went to a bar
to drown my sorrows.
Excuse me, miss.
Hi.
I just noticed you took off
your wedding ring.
Looks like you have a problem.
It's nothing.
You know what, miss?
I have time for you.
And...
I'm willing to listen.
Miss, what happened to you?
Miss?
I was raped.
Who did that to you?
I-I don't know.
You don't know the name
of the guy you slept with?
I didn't have proof.
I couldn't prove it.
It would do more harm than good.
So, I dropped the case.
Mom, why did you hide
all this from me?!
Your mom did nothing wrong!
I made the decision
to hide your true identity.
I agreed to accept you
as a Cabrera!
Because that's how much
I love your mom!
I agreed to hide
your true identity.
Because I wanted
to protect this family!
Because I don't want
this tragedy to define us!
Now you know!
I do!
And I'm a constant reminder
of this tragedy!
That's how you see me,
right, Dad?
Now...
Now I understand everything.
Mom...
I'm so--
I'm sorry about
what happened to you.
I'm sorry it had
to reach this point.
Mommy, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry my existence
caused you so much pain.
But thank you.
Mom, thank you
for telling me the truth.
And thank you for loving me.
And now...
We all know the truth.
You don't have
to pretend anymore.
And I don't have to force myself
into this family anymore.
Because from now on,
I'm no longer a Cabrera.
Vincent.
Vincent!
You think this is
what I wanted to happen?
Don't make your mom
feel any worse!
Isn't this easier for you,
instead of tolerating my
existence in your family?
After everything I've done
for you, Vincent...
I hope this isn't your way
of being ungrateful.
I'm grateful for everything.
Mom loves me.
But you?
You could never accept me
into the family.
And not a day went by
you didn't make me feel that.
You know what, Dad?
Now I understand why I'm being
caught up in Walter's case.
Because I was
the easiest fall guy.
You're still not done
accusing me?
I am protecting our family.
I am protecting all of you!
With all your digging,
you've ruined us!
Do you understand?!
You've ruined all of us!
- You've ruined this family!
- You're ruining my life!
And even if you don't admit it,
I know everything you're up to.
All I need to know
is what Walter had on you
that made you do all this!
And I'll eventually
find that out.
Vincent!
Vincent.
Aah!
Vincent, Vincent, Vincent.
Vincent. Vincent. Vincent.
Vincent.
I'm here for you.
You won't face this alone, okay?
Vincent.
Despite...
Despite all the bad things
in my life...
You're the only good thing
that's ever happened to me.
No matter what...
I'll never leave your side.
That's my promise.
Okay?
I promise you won't be alone
in this fight.
I know you still have
a lot of questions on your mind.
Of course, this is painful
for your mother too.
I hope you two
can talk again soon.
Vincent? Vincent.
Claudia?!
Vincent, I need your help.
Help me, please!
What's going on?
You need to get me
out of here!
Please help me.
Help me.
Gah!
The evidence I have
is so important.
If Vincent finds out,
he'll never forgive us!
We need to find her first.
Are you sure you don't know
where Claudia is?
She'll eventually
come out of hiding.
Finding Claudia is
our top priority.
- She's safe.
- Where is she?
What if she's just
deceiving us?
I'll tell you
everything I know.
We're on our way, Claudia.
Stay where you are, okay?