Timing and subtitles brought to you by 💕Passionate Mechanical Hearts💕 @ Viki.com
♫  I can't help but feel a little happy  ♫
♫  I can't help but feel a little nervous  ♫
♫  The earth is turning because of you  ♫
♫  Without you, the earth stops  ♫
♫  You are the rainbow that fills up the black and white  ♫
♫  I was once obsessed with the legend of the four-leaf clover  ♫
♫  I dreamed of a white-horse carriage and
you becoming my prince  ♫
♫  Your gaze is too seducing, please save me  ♫
♫  I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire  ♫
♫  Your smile is dancing on your lips  ♫
♫  Am I the happiness you're looking for?  ♫
♫  The doe inside me is lost  ♫
♫  Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness  ♫
♫  I can't help but be a little fragile  ♫
♫  I can't help but feel a little gloomy  ♫
♫  The sky is bright because of you  ♫
♫  Without you, the sky is grey  ♫
♫  You are the angel who takes away all loneliness  ♫
Boss. I'm sorry, Boss.
I not only got drunk yesterday but also left early.
I went to bed right after I got home.
I only checked my Wechat when I woke up today.
I'm used to it.
Are you sober now?
Let's go.
Yes, Boss.
In the design proposal, we should add some features of Chinese gardens.
This afternoon, come visit a teacher with me.
Okay.
Just the two of us?
Yes. We are going out of town.
We'll fly back at night.
Is there a problem?
No. No problem.
Recently, you're not doing your job very well.
You used to buy me breakfast and drinks.
Now, you just wait for me standing next to the car.
These days, I've been thinking about the responsibilities of my position.
Did you come up with anything?
I think I'm just a driver and a personal assistant.
I shouldn't interfere with your personal business.
Moreover, I always lose interest in things quickly.
Jiang Xiaoning, what the heck are you talking about?
You just don't know how to face your feelings for Boss.
Young people nowadays are all like that.
They lose their passion quickly.
This is urgent. You need to deal with it now.
Make sure it's done as soon as possible.
Leave us.
Hello, Director Xu.
Director Xu, what brings you here?
Take a seat.
There is a small problem with money from last time.
Accidentally, somebody involved got the goods on us.
He won't say anything, right?
No, he won't.
I have seen a lot of people like him.
They only ask for money. You just need to pay them with enough money.
So I've prepared some cash.
Get it solved with Assistant Liu, when it's time.
Director Xu, is it really not going to cause any trouble?
Tang Xu, you are the kind of person who will accomplish big things in the future.
You need to be able to stay calm.
Don't panic when nothing has happened yet.
Otherwise, how can I leave my business to you in the future?
Okay. I understand.
You're seeing someone?
Who is the lucky girl?
No... No, Director Xu.
It's just for a little sister.
Little sister?
It's a good thing.
Why are you nervous?
I'm happy for you. But remember, bring her around.
I'll help you find out whether she's a good girl.
- See you.
- Director Xu.
Take care, Director Xu.
Brother Xu.
Why did you come visit me at noon?
I'm going on a business trip in a few days. I may be gone for about twenty days.
I'm a little worried about you, so I came by to check on you.
Oh, right. How's work going for you these days? Is everything going well?
No, it's not. I've caused a lot of trouble and always make my boss angry.
I see.
It's all right. My company's door is always open for you.
You're welcome anytime.
It's okay. I'm just venting.
I really like my company.
Look at you. Asking you to work at my company feels like I'm kidnapping you.
You already helped me so much. I don't want to cause you more trouble.
Brother Xu, you don't look well.
Are you working too hard?
I've got too much going on recently.
There are too many things I need to think about.
You've been like this all these years.
You don't look happy
and I can't help you.
I miss the good old days.
We were so carefree back then.
Oh right. This is for you.
Your birthday is coming up in a few days.
I'm afraid I can't make it back in time, so I'm giving this to you in advance.
You know I never celebrate my birthday.
You don't celebrate your birthday. You don't buy cakes.
You should at least have birthday presents. Take it.
Thanks, Brother Xu.
I'm leaving soon.
You're not going to say goodbye to me?
Have a safe trip.
Jiang Xiaoning.
Boss, when did you come down?
I just came down and happened to see you.
Why are you still here?
If we don't leave now, we'll miss the flight.
Miss the flight?
Brother Xu, I need to go now.
Thanks for your present.
Hello, Miss.
Hello.
Hello. This is the identification card for my mechanical heart.
Okay.
Thank you.
- It's done.
- Okay, thank you.
It's sour.
Wang Kai, where is Jiang Xiaoning?
She's on a business trip.
A business trip to where?
She is on a business trip with Director Gu.
Why do I always see you in our Design Department?
What do you mean by "your" Design Department?
This is our company.
We, the Administrative Department,
need to understand every department's daily lives.
To better serve you.
Serve you.
Jiang Xiaoning.
The suitcase.
What's wrong with you?
I just don't understand
why you're bringing me on a business trip?
What do you think?
I hope it's because you like me,
but...
I'm probably the most useless person in the whole company.
Other people have important tasks to complete.
Jiang Xiaoning, is there anything wrong with your brain recently?
The Jiang Xiaoning I know is always positive
and never has low self-esteem.
Not to mention being sarcastic in front of her boss.
I'm sorry, Boss.
I have no filter.
I look down on myself.
I indulge in fantasy.
I do not engage in honest work.
This time, I'm bringing you to visit one of my teachers.
He is very important to me.
Didn't you say you wanted to study architectural design?
I hope this visit will be helpful to you.
Boss.
I think you have potential, so I'm willing to help you.
Don't let me down.
Yes, Boss.
Mr. Wang is a master of Chinese garden design.
We met when we were working on the same project.
We found that we clicked in many aspects,
so we became teacher and student.
However, for me, we're more like close friends across generations.
In other words, this place is full of Boss's memories?
Yes.
This place feels familiar to me.
Really?
Really. I think I've been here before.
Gu Chuan.
Mr. Wang.
Long time no see, Mr. Wang.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've been too busy to come and visit you.
I understand.
People always say that we architects
have no love lives, no friends,
and no families.
But...
This girl is...?
Hello, Mr. Wang. I'm Director Gu's assistant.
I'm Jiang Xiaoning.
Oh, an assistant.
When Gu Chuan came to visit me before, he never brought an assistant along.
You are a big boss now.
You now have a secretary, an assistant, and what else?
Mr. Wang.
When my wife heard you were coming, she regretted it so much.
She had just gone to Jiuzhaigou County with a bunch of her friends.
When she saw the video,
she started to complain so much.
She had already planned out what good food
she was going to make you once you were here.
Would you look at this?
You've missed each other again.
It's okay, Mr. Wang.
I'll come and visit you more often in the future.
Come on, let's go inside first.
Okay.
I bought you a bunch of delicious fruits.
Mr. Wang, I can help you wash the fruits.
Sounds good.
Mr. Wang, you just have some rest.
I've got this.
Little girl, you're pretty smart.
Really?
But when we were at the airport just now,
Boss said I had become dumber.
Really?
Your boss knows how to make jokes now?
He was very serious.
In the past, I was worried that he may develop depression or something else.
It seems like I was worried for nothing.
No way. He scolds me every day and seems to enjoy doing it.
I'll have a talk with him later.
Thank you, Mr. Wang.
Boss, have some fruits.
What are you looking at?
I'm just looking around.
I always do this every time I'm here.
This is me as a kid.
Me and my dad.
You're saying this is your father?
Is this really you?
Yes.
You know my dad? Jiang Guangda?
You-You're Guangda's daughter?
He was my student.
When he first came to the university,
I thought he had great potential.
I really liked him.
I invited him to come to my place for meals quite often.
This picture was taken when he came to visit after he had graduated.
It's the only picture I have of us together.
Who would know...
I'm sorry, child.
I brought up your sad memories.
It's okay, Mr. Wang.
It's been many years.
I won't be sad anymore.
On the contrary, I'm very happy to have met you today.
Mr. Wang, when my dad was young, was he handsome?
Yes.
A lot of girls were chasing after him.
But my mom got him in the end.
Mr. Wang, is this Boss when he was young?
Yes.
Boss, should I call you Martial Uncle?
(T/N: Shi means teacher, Shu means uncle)
Martial Uncle?
I have something to show you.
Martial Uncle.
This is the work notebook that I've been using for years.
There are a lot of design drawings in it.
Many of them
were completed with your dad, Guangda.
Since you are Guangda's daughter,
I should give this to you.
Maybe it'll come in handy
for work in the future.
Mr. Wang, this gift is too precious.
I can't take it.
You're Guangda's daughter.
It should be yours.
I hope you will work hard
to become an outstanding architectural designer.
One that's better than Gu Chuan.
No, no, no.
Mr. Wang, you're too biased.
I haven't even seen this notebook.
You're already a big boss.
You don't need it.
I do.
Thank you, Mr. Wang. I will work hard.
I don't dare to be compared to Boss, but I will be as excellent as my dad.
Of course, you will.
Come on.
Have some fruits.
Okay.
Help yourself.
Pear? Apple?
Both are fine.
I have some good tea, too.
It's where it always has been. You know the place.
Ah, I see.
I'll go look for it.
In a bit, ask Gu Chuan to take you out for a walk.
The view here is gorgeous.
Mr. Wang, which is my dad's handwriting?
Look here...
I just don't understand
why would Mr. Wang give the notebook to you.
I can't help it. I'm a good person.
Boss, I'm in a good mood today.
What do you want to eat? My treat.
Well, I'm not in a good mood.
If you want to buy me something, buy me ice cream.
But you never eat things that are too sweet.
None of your business.
Boss. Yours.
Boss, maybe I've been here too.
Doesn't it say in the movies that "all encounters
are reunions after a long time."
Think about it.
We've both been to Mr. Wang's house, both walked this stone road,
both taken photos in the same room.
Now you've become my boss and we're having ice cream together.
Suddenly, I feel like the ice cream has become special too.
Boss, what's in your mind?
Nothing.
Why did you buy this flavor?
This is the newest flavor.
Do you want to try it?
I mean... this is the newest flavor.
Do you want to smell it?
Nothing more.
Not bad.
Was that an indirect kiss?
This is so awkward.
What should I do?
Should I bring up some other topic?
What to chat about?
Boss, you looked pretty handsome in that photo
of yours when you were young.
Only when I was young?
No. I mean.
When you were young, there must have been a lot of people who liked you.
Someone who fits you must be talented and beautiful.
Born with natural beauty.
Jiang Xiaoning, what are you saying?
Chen Wenwen is my ex-girlfriend.
Why are you suddenly talking about this?
I've never asked.
Also, I don't really care about that.
You don't care?
Fine.
I won't talk about it then.
But it's fine if you want to talk about it.
It's raining and we can't leave anyway.
Chen Wenwen and I started dating after graduating high school.
After that, I went to study abroad.
We had been managing a long-distance relationship
in two different countries.
During the summer break of my first year in university,
I came back to China.
However, something happened and we broke up.
After that, we've never contacted each other.
It never occurred to me that you would bring her to the office.
Yes. It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
I'm a crow who always brings misfortune.
But it's fine.
I consider it has come to a full stop.
A full stop?
Isn't it a comma? Or an ellipsis?
I mean who would be willing to have a full stop
with someone like you who shines this brightly.
Jiang Xiaoning, I just realized that your flattering skills are really
much better than any other people.
I won't decline this honor.
Boss, there's a cat.
Hold this for me. Come on.
It's so cute.
Baby.
Boss, it's so cute.
Do you want to pet it?
No.
I don't like animals that shed.
Trust me, pet it. You'll fall in love with it.
Just pet it once. Come on.
How do you feel? Isn't its hair so silky?
What does it mean when it looks at me in this way?
It likes you.
It knows that following the right owner will allow it to eat well.
It doesn't have an owner.
It looks like it's a stray cat.
Boss, why don't we take it back and adopt it?
Adopt it?
Boss, look at you.
You're handsome, talented, and kind.
Moreover, your apartment is spacious.
If I bring it back, I won't have time to take care of it
since my grandma and auntie are not in good health.
Boss.
- Well, let me think about it.
- Okay.
If you're thinking about it, I need to make it clear.
If you adopt it, you can't abandon it.
You should feed it good food, bathe it, be responsible for it.
Otherwise, you shouldn't adopt it.
If it knows how good it feels to be taken care of by an owner,
it won't be able to revert back to its current lifestyle.
Temporarily. It can stay at my place temporarily.
Then can I go visit it frequently at your place?
Of course, you need to come and visit. Otherwise, am I supposed to raise it by myself?
Great. Thank you, Boss.
Should we give it a name?
Look, your last name is Gu and my last name is Jiang.
Gu Gu?
Jiang Jiang?
- These names don't work.
- We can call it Ice Cream.
We ran into it while we were having ice cream.
Why don't we call it Ice Cream?
Okay.
From now on, your name will be Ice Cream.
Ice Cream, Ice Cream.
Boss, give it some ice cream. See if it'll have any.
Feed it. Come on.
- Come on.
- Do you want to have any?
How about this one?
You can choose.
You should behave, understand?
Adapting to the environment is basic.
Don't think I can't hold you accountable even though you look cute.
If you want to stay at my place, you must have a bath.
Come here.
I asked you to come here.
You're smart.
You know this is the bathroom.
Come, come, come.
From now on, here is where you take baths.
Ice Cream is so cute.
I feel happy when I see you.
But what makes me happier
is being able to visit you at Boss' place often.
Miss Crow and Mr. Lizard.
Boss.
Suddenly behaving so well.
I hope you won't lose your passion too fast.
Thank you, Boss. I'll try to keep it up.
If there's nothing else, I'll go back to keep reading Mr. Wang's notes.
Okay. When you're done with it, let me take a look at it, too.
Boss, I really do want to let you have a look at it.
However, this is Mr. Wang's private belongings.
It's not good to pass it around.
I noticed that after we came back from the business trip,
you've become more and more bold.
Director Gu... Xiaoning is here, too.
I was just looking for you.
This is a critical period for the art gallery.
I'm needed at the site quite frequently.
I'm afraid I won't have time for Chen Wenwen's exhibition.
Why don't you let Cheng Dong take charge of it?
Cheng Dong has his own projects to complete.
I'm not quitting.
I'm just asking for an assistant.
Who do you think is suitable for the job?
After careful consideration, I can only borrow your assistant.
I think this is a great learning opportunity.
I'm afraid I'm not capable of taking on this role.
You can practice your skills.
Okay. Thank you, Boss, for giving me this opportunity.
Sister Manlin, should I contact Sister Wenwen for anything?
Take it easy. I'll let you know in advance.
Jing Xiaoning, you've got this.
Mine is good, too.
- Really?
- I'm going to try some.
Why did that just feel like a martial arts film?
I think something big is about to happen in the martial arts world.
A reign of terror is inevitable.
No matter what happens, no matter how many years have passed,
no matter who the leader is,
I only follow my own path.
This hero, would you mind me asking you what path?
The path in your heart.
You can't walk the path in my heart.
To you, there will always be road traffic control.
Why?
Look, you're Empress Dowager.
I'm Commander Ju.
Even our snacks look like a couple.
We were born for each other.
We'll talk once you've become extremely rich.
Can you not act like this?
- What did I do?
- Why are you discouraging me?
Is Gu Chuan in his office?
Yes, yes, yes.
Jia Jia, Jia Jia, Jia Jia.
Jia Jia, don't think about it.
All the girls in this building want to marry him.
There are too many wolves and too little meat.
Nothing is impossible.
Why leave me hanging?
My Chuan.
Who bought this for you?
It doesn't look delicious at all.
I bought you fresh-from-the-oven cakes and it's your favorite flavor, vanilla.
When did I start liking vanilla?
You don't?
It's not important.
These are fresh from the oven, way more delicious than this, which clearly looks stale.
Do you have a favor to ask me?
Hey, do I need a reason to come visit my Chuan?
Me buying cake for you. Isn't it normal?
Of course, there is a small favor I'd like to ask.
Get to the point.
I want to borrow someone from you.
Borrow a person?
What's with today? Why is everyone asking to borrow people from me this morning?
Other people asked to borrow people from you, too?
But the person I'm asking to borrow shouldn't be very important to you.
Who is it?
How are we supposed to work?
Meng Jia.
Director Xu, why are you here?
I thought I just saw a ghost.
Well.
Be my girlfriend.
Be your girlfriend?
Come with me.
Get on with your work. Do your work. Nothing is happening here.
- Today...
- Brother Kai.
Brother Kai, what's the matter?
Brother Kai. Mr... Mr. Cheng.
- Brother Kai.
Director Xu, I'm not ready for this.
This is too sudden.
Calm down.
I'll explain everything to you.
Don't touch me.
What... Give me three seconds to calm down first.
I can do this.
Director Xu, although I'm not fully prepared,
go ahead and say it.
Look.
- Can I...
- You can.
- Can you...
- I can.
Wait until I finish my sentence.
Can I ask you to pretend to be my girlfriend?
Pretend?
- It's fake?
- It's fake.
I know it's not good to ask anyone to do this.
At least you are the company's employee and we've known each other for a while.
I also believe that you can play the role well. Right?
I can make our fake relationship look real.
Let's start with the first ploy of the play.
We'll start with how the role and the actor should...
Okay, okay, okay.
We can talk about it next time.
So... you're in?
I am.
Great.
Do you need me to prepare any costumes or props?
No. I have everything.
- You do?
- I do!
I'll ask Gu Chuan to assign you less work later.
Thank you in advance.
No problem. I'm more than willing to do so.
I won't waste too much of your time. I need about two episodes.
Two episodes?
I can do more.
We can discuss this later.
You need to go out with me this afternoon.
I've got you on leave.
Go get ready. I'll wait for you downstairs.
No problem.
Fake.
I forgot to talk about the pay.
Not important.
Not important, not important.
Brother Kai.
What's wrong with you?
You've been lost in thought for a while.
Get up. It's my seat.
What's actually going on?
Someone's life is at risk.
Director Xu asked me to pretend to be his girlfriend.
I finally have a chance to get into acting.
- Really?
- Really.
So it's actually fake?
It's fake.
Yes!
I knew Director Xu couldn't be this blind.
No, no, no. A slip of the tongue. He has sharp eyes.
Great taste.
- You're good now?
- I'm good, I'm good.
- Are you all right?
- Go back to work. It's fine, it's fine.
Everything is fine. Go back to work.
Let me tell you. Don't be so happy this early.
What did I say?
- Everything is...
- Impossible. Impossible.
Come on, come on, come on.
Eat, eat, eat. This, this, this.
Pretending to be his girlfriend.
Sister Yan Yan has met her match.
Manger Wei, please sign this.
Did you review it?
Yes, there are no issues.
Wait until I have time.
Manager Wei, are you busy right now?
Did you knock?
If you're in a rush, go ask your boyfriend who acted crazy after getting drunk to sign it for you.
He's not my boyfriend.
And it was our fault last time.
My apologies.
This is going to benefit our company.
Thank you.
Zhao Yan, let's go have lunch together.
I'm on a diet.
So aggressive.
If she doesn't want to go, let's go together.
Cool, let's go.
Your treat?
Do you want us to bring you some food?
Zhao Yan? Zhao Yan?
Just leave her alone. Let's go.
Let's go.
Yan Yan, what a coincidence.
What a coincidence. Were you waiting for me?
I just got here. I was just passing by. It was a coincidence.
So you like acting?
Let me tell you about acting.
- Hello.
- Iced Americano, thank you.
Okay. It tells you about the rhythms in the performance.
Do you know the categories of rhythms in performance?
Internal rhythm and external rhythm,
and the relationship between internal rhythm and external rhythm.
Don't you think it's amazing?
Guess what internal rhythm is.
Your lipstick.
Is it ready?
It's ready. Your coffee.
Thank you.
- That's the girl?
- Huh? Yeah.
She doesn't seem to be better than me.
All right. Today's work is done.
We're done?
I haven't even started to act.
I... I changed into a dress for this.
Director Xu, let's do it again.
- I'll do better.
- Next time. We'll have other opportunities.
Do we have other opportunities?
There is no next time. Today's work is done. Let's go. I'll walk you back.
Director Xu.
Boss, I'll leave first.
Are you going to leave just like that?
I'll pick you up on time tomorrow.
Do you want to go up and visit Ice Cream?
It has been having a poor appetite recently.
I don't know why.
How can it have a poor appetite? What did you feed it?
I don't know what I gave it.
I'll go take a look.
Ice Cream.
Come. How come you have a poor appetite?
Having a poor appetite while gaining weight?
It looks chubbier.
Did it become chubbier?
I was busy revising design drawings. I didn't see it eat.
You didn't see it eating doesn't mean it didn't eat.
I see.
Its fur is so soft. Feels so nice.
It also smells good.
Of course. I bathe it every day.
Cats can't take baths every day.
How can it come onto the couch without being bathed? How can it come into my bed without being bathed?
Ice Cream, rooming with him must be hard for you.
How come it's hard for it?
It's hard for me.
Okay, okay, okay. Boss, you also worked hard.
Let me tell you.
I didn't treat your VIP poorly.
I prepared a room only for it.
How nice!
I want to see it.
Let's go.
Ice Cream, you're so happy.
This is too luxurious.
Some other stuff is on the way.
These are all based on my drawings.
I also bought some small furniture for Ice Cream.
I have a question.
Why are all its toys pink?
Don't girls like pink? Don't you like pink?
But Ice Cream is a boy.
You bought pink stuff when you don't even know its sex.
Are you sure?
Isn't... isn't it...
At least they look cute.
Ice Cream. Ice Cream.
Ice Cream, why are you so lazy?
Come on, come on, come on.
Hello?
Hello. Is this Mr. Gu Chuan?
Yes.
I'm the person in charge of the Jin An Award in the Greater China region.
Did you see our email?
Email?
Let me take a look now.
(T/N: "Jin" means "Golden", "An" means "Shore")
Mr. Gu?
Mr. Gu, are you there?
Yes, I am.
I just finished reading the email you sent.
Congratulations on winning the Annual Design Award of the Jin An Award.
Pardon me, I have a question.
This design is from three years ago, so...
is it possible that you guys made a mistake?
Because that project has only been completed this year,
it is still on our nominee's list for this year.
We have already sent out the official notice and the awards ceremony invitation.
You should be receiving them shortly.
I called to congratulate you and also to confirm
whether you will be able to attend the awards ceremony.
Mr. Gu, will you be able to attend the ceremony?
Yes.
Great. Congratulations again.
Our staff will be in contact with you shortly to confirm the details of the awards ceremony with you.
I won't bother you any longer. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by 💕Passionate Mechanical Hearts💕 @ Viki.com
♫  Destiny is a little annoying  ♫
♫  It takes those I care about  ♫
♫  Away from me  ♫
♫  If memory is bright  ♫
♫  It would hold up a lamp in my heart  ♫
♫  And light up the night  ♫
♫  Sunshine alternates with moonlight  ♫
♫  Returning to life in time  ♫
♫  Gift me with a dream  ♫
♫  A dream with you in it  ♫
♫  The one who caught me off guard  ♫
♫  Steps foot into my life...  ♫
♫  It's you...  ♫
♫  If it weren't for parting  ♫
♫  How can we meet again?  ♫
♫  It's you...  ♫
♫  Exchanging sunshine for moonlight  ♫
♫  Exchanging fortune for the past  ♫
♫  Exchanging my heartbeat for you  ♫