Zhinian,
come in.
Come in.
Linglong,
you're awake.
Zhinian,
take a seat.
you saved me again.
I don't know how to repay you.
Since you can't repay him,
why not just marry him?
Anyway, the two of you
already have feelings for each other.
You just haven't made it official yet.
Linglong,
there's no need to thank me for saving you.
But...
By the way,
near the teahouse that night,
did you notice anyone suspicious?
More than suspicious.
It's concrete evidence.
When that man attacked,
I saw him with my own eyes.
He was around 40 years old.
As for his build,
he was a head taller than you.
He had small eyes and a narrow nose bridge.
On his left cheek,
there was a scar.
The man had very dark skin.
He must have knocked you out with knockout gas first,
then poured tung oil all over the room,
and planned to kidnap you.
If I hadn't accidentally knocked over the oil lamp,
he would have succeeded.
There was indeed such a person.
He looked to be around 40.
A bit taller than me.
Dark skin and small eyes.
And a distinct scar on his face.
He didn't want to kill me to silence me;
he just wanted to take me away.
But when the teahouse caught fire,
he ran away.
Linglong,
don't worry.
Now that we know what he looks like,
we can definitely find him.
It's only a matter of time before we find him.
We must report this to the authorities.
Linglong,
I will help you look for him.
The person who hurt you,
I will never let him go.
By the way, Zhinian,
I haven't asked you yet.
The teahouse caught fire at night.
Why were you there?
Linglong,
you shouldn't overthink right now.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you about it later.
Okay.
I...
Let me feed you the medicine.
Linglong...
I...
I'm sorry.
It's my first time feeding someone medicine.
I'm a bit clumsy.
I'm...
sorry.
You're both adults.
Watching you two date is so frustrating.
You're grown-ups.
Yet you're so shy just holding hands.
Hey.
That's right.
Aunt.
Mother.
I...
I'll take my leave.
Zhinian.
I'll walk you out.
Aunt.
I can tell you have something to say.
Please speak your mind.
Zhinian.
You saved Linglong.
I am very grateful to you.
I also know
you two grew up together
and are very close.
But...
But Linglong's current status is special.
And she made a vow in the ancestral hall.
You can be friends,
but you cannot overstep the bounds.
You know your limits,
don't you?
Aunt,
I understand.
I'll take my leave.
Didn't you say that if I left this to you,
it would be foolproof?
Now Hu Linglong is not dead,
and the arsonist has escaped.
If Hu Linglong finds the witness,
what should we do?
Father,
it's not my fault.
That old teahouse is unvisited all year round.
I didn't expect that in the middle of the night,
Xu Zhinian would appear there.
Xu Zhinian.
Xu Zhinian again.
Yes.
Mr. Yamamoto.
Since that day in the ancestral hall,
I began to suspect.
Hu Linglong and Xu Zhinian,
in the middle of the night,
must have been doing some
shameful deeds.
The most urgent task
is to find the arsonist
and silence him.
Yes.
Is there any information about him,
Mr. Yamamoto?
The man is called Wang Song,
the bandit leader of Qingfeng Stronghold.
He has done a lot of things for us before.
Since he failed that day,
he just
disappeared.
He's very cunning.
He probably knows
we won't let him go,
so he
hid
hid away.
He knows this matter is related to me and your father.
We must not leave him alive,
otherwise there will be endless trouble.
Understood.
What are you waiting for?
Go now.
If you mess this up again,
I will no longer consider you my son.
Yes.
Get out.
You
are from the Hu family,
here to silence me,
right?
You are not from the Hu family.
Who are you?
Who I am is not important.
Just answer what I ask.
Do you hear me?
Spare my life!
That night at the teahouse,
why did you take Hu Linglong away?
What's the grudge between you two?
I...
I don't understand.
I know a lot of things.
Don't even try to lie to me.
If I find out you're lying even a bit,
I'll take your pathetic life.
Understood.
I have no grudge against Hu Linglong.
It's...
Someone else wants her dead.
Who?
Hu Wenyi of the Hu family,
and that
Japanese guy named Yamamoto Toru.
What exactly do they want?
I...
I don't know.
I only know that
Hu Wenyi has always
wanted to kill Hu Wenzhong's entire family.
He poisoned Hu Wenzhong.
Next in line is naturally
his daughter.
Who?
Who poisoned him?
Hu Wenyi of the Hu family.
Long'er.
Why aren't you resting?
Why are you up?
Mother,
I've been in bed for more than three days.
I'm fully recovered now.
As for the medicine,
you don't need to bother brewing it anymore.
I can't let your efforts go to waste.
Today,
this is the last bowl.
Uncle Zhao said
a lot of work has piled up these past few days.
I have to go deal with it right away.
Sigh.
This child...
How come she is different from before?
Linglong.
Zhinian.
I am about to take up my new post.
The future of this journey is uncertain.
I don't know when we'll meet again.
Before I leave,
let's make some more beautiful memories.
Let me do it myself.
Look.
Zhinian.
Do you...
have anything you want to say to me?
Oh.
There is a small cabin over there.
Do you want to go take a look?
There's a man-eating monster in the cabin.
If you want to go, go yourself.
There are no monsters in this world.
Linglong,
we'll know once we go.
Mm.
Zhinian.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I'm here.
Ah!