Run away from the wedding?
No.
But you killing someone is even worse.
If I'm not mistaken,
you plan to kill Hu Wenyi at the wedding reception,
and then take your own life.
Right?
I...
You just want to keep your mother safe,
killing Hu Wenyi to end the trouble forever.
But have you ever thought about it?
You are her only close relative left in the Hu family now.
If you leave her too,
wouldn't she be even more heartbroken?
But about escaping the wedding,
we are almost at the Zhang family.
There's no time to worry about that.
Stop!
Hu Linglong,
what are you doing?
It is inappropriate for a bride to yell like this.
I ate something bad last night.
I need to use the toilet and can't hold it.
If you don't let me go,
I'll do it right here in the sedan.
I'm not the one who will be embarrassed anyway.
You...
Hu Linglong,
don't play tricks with me.
It's a taboo for the bridal sedan to touch the ground during the procession.
Hold it in.
Lift the sedan and keep moving.
The sedan can't touch the ground. Hold it steady.
Hu Linglong!
Go after her!
Why are they like leeches?
I can't shake them off.
Chase her!
Hurry up!
Chase her that way.
Hurry!
Linglong.
Why are you here?
Zhinian.
You shouldn't have come.
I just escaped from the wedding procession.
They are trying to catch me and take me back.
Zhinian,
you should go first.
I don't want to drag you into this.
I won't leave alone.
I came today to take you with me.
Linglong,
we are already married now.
We should go through thick and thin together.
Zhinian.
She's over there.
Catch her quickly!
Get on the bike quickly.
Let's go.
I'm not very good at riding.
Linglong,
you can ride a bicycle now.
Get on quickly.
Qiao Xin,
this bicycle is a rare item.
Ordinary families don't have it.
Where did you learn to ride it?
Hmph,
don't forget,
I am an immortal.
I can naturally master things in your mortal world
without a teacher.
Oh no.
Why at this time?
Ah.
Zhinian.
Linglong, what's wrong?
I don't know how to ride a bicycle.
Ah.
You've ridden so far.
Hey.
Linglong.
Are you okay, Linglong?
Zhinian,
I think I sprained my ankle.
Let me carry you.
Look.
Isn't that the cabin from before?
Yes.
Ouch!
Dad!
Dabao.
Elder.
What happened to you?
I...
I went to catch Linglong,
but she hit me with her bicycle.
Look.
Ouch.
Hu Linglong.
You have no respect for family rules.
You've tainted our family and caused trouble.
Your sins are grave.
If I am
lenient with her again this time,
after I die,
I won't have the face to see our ancestors.
Dabao.
Yes.
Go find your father immediately.
Take Hu Linglong
and escort her to Hu Wenzhong's memorial tablet
to kneel in punishment.
Without my permission,
she is not allowed to get up.
If she disobeys even a bit,
tell her
I'll hold her mother accountable.
Okay.
Understood.
I'll go right now, Elder.
Go.
Oh!
Ah.
This old man
finally believed it.
Oh my.
Hu Linglong,
let's see how you hide.
Mm.
Good tea.
Smell it.
Smells good.
Mm.
Zhinian.
If time could stop at this moment,
how great would that be.
Even if time doesn't stop,
we can still be together.
But we have to go back eventually,
don't we?
What is he...
I'll give it to him.
Here.
What does he mean?
He seems to be saying
that this house is his.
Linglong.
I want to marry you.
Not like last night.
I will follow all the traditional customs,
formally marry you,
and carry you home in a grand sedan chair.
Actually,
I have been hiding something from you.
It's about taking up my post in the Beiyang Fleet.
You've always been smart and observant,
so naturally you could guess it.
Actually, half a month ago,
I already received
the letter from the Beiyang Fleet notifying me to take up my post.
I was originally scheduled to leave in seven days.
If you are willing to marry me,
I can give up the post,
stay in Qimen from now on,
and live a good life with you.
Zhinian,
you shouldn't be here.
You are an exceptional talent and a pillar of the country.
You shouldn't do this for me,
nor for personal romance,
and waste your bright future.
Today, my mother warned me not to regret it.
That was when I realized
what the most important thing is to me,
and who the most precious person is.
It's the things related to you.
It's the person right in front of me now.
Linglong,
I don't need you to give me an answer right away.
No matter when,
I will wait for you.
Linglong.
Let's...
Let's go.
Bad news!
Bad news, Clan Elder!
What is it, Wenyi?
Something terrible has happened.
What about the Zhang family?
Master Zhang is furious.
The Zhang family canceled the engagement!
Canceled the engagement?
Yes.
Then our tea orders...
The tea orders they promised...
Naturally, they are...
canceled too.
Wenyi!
What are you standing there for?
Hurry and bring her back!
Yes, Clan Elder.
Linglong. Zhinian.
Benefactors.
Wow.
You two look so beautiful today.
Come, let me pour you some tea.
Extra! Extra!
Japan has attacked without declaring war!
Paperboy!
Sir.
Would you like a newspaper?
Give me a copy.
Extra! Extra!
Japan has attacked without declaring war!
Zhinian,
what's wrong?
Japan has attacked without declaring war.
They ambushed our troop transport ships.
Can we win?
Yes.
Xu Zhinian.