What's going on?
Look.
What exactly is this situation?
Is it someone's prank?
This...
What is this?
An illusion?
Wait.
Clan Elder,
I have something to report.
What is the meaning of this behavior?
Today, our Hu family
is about to hold
the succession ceremony for the head of the family.
You barging in like this,
shouting and yelling,
wouldn't it make outsiders
laugh at our Hu family?
We can discuss everything tomorrow.
Clan Elder.
This is a matter of great importance.
We cannot delay even for a day.
Hu Wenzhong and his family
for many years
have deliberately
deceived our clan members.
If I wait one more day,
the entire Hu family
will be deceived for another day.
I...
I really
cannot feel at peace.
Hu Wenyi,
do you know
the weight of those words?
Tell us,
how did the mother and son
deceive our clan members?
Clan Elder,
everyone.
Standing before you
is
the daughter of Hu Wenzhong,
Hu Linglong.
Brother was pushed into the water.
Hahaha.
Absurd!
The Hu family...
Which clan member
doesn't know
that Hu Linglong, over a decade ago,
drowned and died young?
How is that possible?
Clan Elder.
This is the scheme of Hu Wenzhong's family.
After Hu Qingyun died,
Hu Linglong has been dressing as a man
in front of the clan members for years,
pretending to be the young master.
Now,
she even wants to make it real
and inherit our Hu family's estate.
Hmph!
Letting our Hu family
fall into the hands of
a lowly and contemptible woman.
Hu Wenyi,
you have no proof,
stop talking nonsense here.
No proof?
If we had no proof,
how would we dare speak nonsense before the Clan Elder?
You two,
do you remember this person?
Doctor Xue.
You are?
Replying to the Clan Elder,
I am a doctor from Jishi Hall in Qimen County.
Today, I come
at the request of Master Hu Wenyi
to bear witness.
Go ahead and speak.
Hu Qingyun,
she is indeed a woman.
What should we do?
It was twenty years ago,
on the 9th day of the 10th month.
That day, Hu Wenzhong
suddenly carried a drowning Hu Qingyun
to seek my help.
Unfortunately, it was too late.
At that time, Hu Qingyun had already stopped breathing,
and there was nothing I could do.
Entrusted by him,
I have kept this matter a secret
and never revealed a word to anyone.
Doctor,
how is my son's injury?
Please don't worry, Madam,
the young master is fine.
Doctor,
why haven't I seen Dr. Xue today?
Haven't you heard?
He went to the Hu family ancestral hall with Hu Wenyi,
supposedly to serve as a witness
to prove that the Hu family's young master, Hu Qingyun,
is actually a woman.
Zhinian,
where are you going?
Young Master.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Elder,
say no more.
Now,
I would like to hear
what Hu Linglong has to say.
No.
No, Elder,
he is talking nonsense.
He is lying!
I
am willing to guarantee with my reputation from years of practicing medicine
that every word I said is true,
without any falsehood.
It's not true.
They are lying.
Are you saying
what they said isn't true?
Then let me ask you:
Why,
why is the name on your father,
Hu Wenzhong's suicide note,
not Hu Qingyun,
but your real name, Hu Linglong?
Didn't you want me
to be Hu Qingyun for the rest of my life?
Why in the suicide note
did you write my real name?
Dr. Xue.
My husband treated you well when he was alive.
Now that he has just passed away,
you...
how could you do
such a treacherous thing?
Madam,
you can't blame me.
My family has faced disasters recently,
and it was Master Hu Wenyi who helped us.
I'm just returning the favor.
Since I have already testified,
the rest is your
Hu family's private matter.
I...
I will take my leave first.
Farewell.
I'm sorry.
Sigh.
Go.
Farewell, Master Hu.
Clan elders.
Everyone knows that our Hu family tea
is the best in Qimen.
Everyone knows that our Hu clan
is wealthy and prosperous.
Hu Wenzhong's family,
out of selfish desires,
wants to monopolize the family business.
That's why they came up with this trick
of a woman dressing as a man.
Yes.
My father is right.
Everyone.
If you are unwilling to believe
our one-sided story,
you can just take her
to another doctor.
Have him check her pulse and body,
and the truth will be revealed.
Somebody come!
Take her away.
Yes.
Let go.
Don't grab her.
Don't touch me.
What are you all doing?
Let go.
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
Let go.
Linglong.
Daughter, what's wrong?
Wake up.
My child.
Linglong.
Wake up.
So many of you
bullying a widow and her child.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Linglong.
No!
Where...
Where am I?
How did I end up in a place like this?
Who is in my body?
Why does it look different again?
These clothes...
This hair...
Did I time-travel?
What dynasty is this?
Why did I turn into a man?
How was my body taken away?
No.
I need to get out of here.
Ah!
Who exactly are you?
Why are you in my body?
Could it be that I've been hit by
the legendary body-snatching spell?
What should I do?
Wretched girl!
How dare you disguise yourself as a man to steal my position as head of the family.
Today,
I'll tear off your mask.
Ah.
Father.
Hey.
You must never admit it.
Do you hear me?
Where is this?
Just now,
it was the jade pendant speaking.
Somebody come!
Strip off her clothes
and pull her hair!
Let everyone see
if she is a good man,
or a shameless,
deceitful
wench!
No!
Stop!
Let's see who dares to touch her.
Zhinian.
Why is he back?
Remember,
the one who drowned that day
was the Hu family's daughter,
Hu Linglong.
The one alive today
is the Hu family's eldest son,
Hu Qingyun.
Linglong,
for your father and mother,
and for the Hu family,
you must live on behalf of your brother.
Why do you wear boys' clothes?
You are obviously a girl.
Father told me to do so.
He said I must live on behalf of my brother.
You must never tell anyone.
Wait for me.
These are all the memories of the original owner of this body.
No.
Xu Zhinian.
Humph.
This is a family matter of the Hu family.
You're just a wet-behind-the-ears brat.
What right do you have to interfere?
I don't care about the Hu family's affairs.
But if you try to hurt Qingyun,
I won't just stand by.
Humph.
Qingyun.
Hu Qingyun has been dead for a long time.
Did you know
that your own brother
is actually a woman?
Zhinian.
Great.
So you knew all along.
Ah.
Hu Linglong.
You have deceived the Hu family in every way,
yet you confided in an outsider.
You really don't know who your true family is.
In my opinion,
she and Xu Zhinian
have been having an affair.
All she thinks about is romance.
If she were really made the head of the family,
the Hu family would be handed over to outsiders.
Such a person
is truly
shameless.
Full of feudal dregs.
No wonder they say women are trouble.
I really need to sort out this Hu family.
Despicable.
Exactly.
Women are lowly.
Then weren't you also born of a lowly person?
What does that make you?
A bastard.
A coward.
See that?
Ah.
This is outrageous.
You curse me?
Even if I am truly a woman,
so what?
Father.
This...
Then you don't deserve to be the head of the Hu family.
Sigh.
Right.
Since things have come to this,
I might as well admit it.
I, Qiao Xin, don't need to pretend to be a man anymore.
You absolutely cannot admit it.
Do you hear me?
Hey.
She can actually hear me.
Fine.
Then I will tell you today.
You can't tell them.
Hey.
Child.
You must not say it.
Master.
Seeing those layers of white gauze around Long'er's chest,
my heart aches.
Yun'er is dead,
and you can no longer have children.
If I don't sacrifice Long'er,
how can we protect the Hu family business?
If the Hu family
falls into the hands of a villain like Hu Wenyi,
it will be doomed forever.
I, Hu Linglong,
am indeed a woman.