Here, serve the tea.
Miss!
Something bad happened.
Today they held a clan meeting.
Madam went to the council hall alone
to plead for you.
But now they are
forcing Madam to her death.
What?
Hurry,
let's go to the council hall right now.
Miss,
please slow down.
If you walk this fast,
my legs will be ruined.
Come on, Aunt,
drink the tea.
I must save my mother.
What's wrong,
Li Nianci?
Are you scared?
Don't dare to drink it?
Otherwise,
let Hu Linglong drink it instead.
Aunt,
just drink it.
If you don't drink it,
won't Linglong be the one to suffer?
Am I right?
Ah, it hurts.
Someone, come!
Strip her clothes and pull her hair.
You have to agree
whether you want to or not.
Ouch.
You...
You drank it too fast.
You were in a hurry.
Long'er.
In our next life,
let's be
mother and daughter again.
Alas.
Wenzhong,
I've let you down.
Mother!
Mother, wake up!
What am I going to do alone?
Mother!
Say something.
Say something, Mother.
Mother!
Li Nianci committed suicide as a sinner.
She shall not enter the ancestral shrine after death.
She cannot taint the dragon vein of our ancestral graves.
Her funeral shall be simple.
From today on,
Hu Wenyi will act as the head of the Hu family,
handling internal and external affairs.
In seven days, a ceremony will be held at the Hu family shrine
to officially succeed as the head.
Boatman!
Yes?
Where are you going, sir?
To Xiuning.
Alright.
Get on board.
Come,
be careful.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Before I leave for my post,
I have one unfulfilled wish.
I hope to seek your help.
What wish?
The former master of the Hu family,
there's a hidden truth behind Hu Wenzhong's death.
I need to go to Xiuning County nearby
to gather evidence.
I hope you can help me with your contacts there.
Nonsense!
Haven't I told you
not to have any contact with Hu Linglong?
You taught me since I was a child
to finish what I start.
This is unfinished business for me.
If I can't fulfill it,
I won't be at peace.
If I succeed,
I'll follow your teachings in every word and deed,
do nothing reckless,
and put the affairs of
the family and country first.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Congratulations, Mr. Hu, on getting what you wanted.
Thank you, Mr. Yamamoto.
Oh.
Just a small gift.
Thank you.
This time,
thanks to
Mr. Yamamoto's advice.
From now on,
we will work together.
With me as the master of the Hu family
and your power and connections,
the tea business in Qimen
will be ours.
As for those British merchants,
they are nothing to worry about.
Mr. Hu.
Yes?
Speaking of cooperation,
I mentioned to you before.
Can I have a look
at the secret recipe for Keemun black tea?
I have more professional people
who can help research
and improve Keemun black tea,
so that we can expand planting
and increase sales.
Mr. Yamamoto,
no problem.
No problem.
Good.
Then I'll
wait for your good news.
Okay.
By the way, Mr. Hu,
Yes?
you have taken the position of master.
It's a big event in your life.
Why not hold a big banquet
to celebrate?
Celebrate?
Of course we must celebrate.
Come, drink.
Congratulations, Master Hu.
Look,
Long'er's makeup
is so beautiful.
This skirt
is the one
you liked best when you were little.
This is the first skirt
Mother bought you.
Mother can't bear to let you go.
Row, row,
row,
row the boat to Grandma's bridge.
Mother.
Mother,
please say something.
Everyone, follow me to Juxian Restaurant for a drink!
Great!
Come, everyone!
Keep playing!
Oh.
What's going on here?
Oh, it's quite quiet here.
Why don't you
join us for a few drinks?
Makes sense.
Auntie died a few days too early.
Alas.
Otherwise,
she could have made it to today's banquet.
Hahaha.
Are you going or not?
Hu Dabao,
you and your father will die a horrible death!
You're the ones who deserve to die!
Hahahaha.
I won't stoop to your level.
If you don't want to go, fine.
Come on, keep playing outside! Let's go.
Mr. Xu.
Inspector Zhang,
please have a seat.
No need.
Please.
Sit.
Mr. Xu.
Your father has already explained it to me
in his letter.
I have found out what you asked me to investigate.
According to the pharmacy owner,
there is indeed someone
who often comes from Qimen to buy medicine.
That person is...
Oh.
Long'er. Mother,
why are you here?
You've been helping Uncle Zhao manage the accounts these days.
It must be hard work.
Oh,
I made something delicious especially for you.
Guess
what it is.
Mother,
you know I can't smell anything.
Aren't you making it difficult for me?
Here,
your favorite black tea pastry.
It's delicious.
You're the best, Mother.
Are you okay?
Linglong.
Qiao Xin.
I want to be alone.
But you look...
I said I want to be alone.
Can't you understand?
Whenever I see you now,
I think of how you stole my body.
I think of my running away from the wedding,
and how my mother died because of me.
But,
didn't you say at the ancestral hall
that it wasn't my fault?
That was because I didn't know my mother would die.
I never wanted to drag her down.
Why didn't you just let Hu Wenyi and me
perish together?
Why do you interfere with me time and time again?
It all started from that day.
Everything my father said was a lie.
This is no auspicious object at all.
You
are also a jinx.
I am a jinx.
Hu Linglong.
If it weren't for my help,
you wouldn't even have won the tea competition,
and you would have been kicked out of the Hu family by Hu Wenyi long ago.
Without my help,
you can't do anything right.
Help me?
You just want to use me
to achieve your own goals
and return to heaven.
Do you think I don't know that?
Fine.
Hu Linglong.
Since you hate me so much,
we will go our separate ways.
Then go.
From now on, I'll take my high road,
and you take your low road.
This Hu Linglong
really doesn't know a good person when she sees one.
Mr. Xu.
You're finally back.
Here is a letter for you.
It arrived three days ago,
but you have to receive it in person.
I heard from Madam that you'd be back today.
She was so right.
The official seal of the Beiyang Fleet.