THE FOURTH, YOON DUJUN
THE ELDEST, KIM MINSEONG
THE SECOND, DAVID LEE
-The weather is cooling down.
-I agree.
I wore my jacket.
It was cold in the morning.
A BREEZE IS BLOWING
OVER SEOKCHON LAKE
I hear the crowds screaming.
A MAGICAL THEME PARK IS
FLOATING ABOVE THE LAKE
-It's going to drop.
-Here it goes.
VERTICAL DROP
I CAN'T LOOK
Hello, David and Minseong!
-How have you been?
-How's it going?
-How is everything?
-It's good.
We are here at Jamsil.
We can hear their screams from behind us.
-Do you like rides?
-I'm scared of them.
You couldn't pay me to ride them.
-I'm relieved to hear that.
-It's a "no" for me.
Who invited today's chef?
-I invited today's chef.
-All right.
Give us a small hint.
-Chef Side Dish.
-What?
There are many chefs with that nickname.
-But he's a rising chef.
-Got it.
If you make side dishes,
you have to be an expert at everything.
-That's right.
-From stir-fried dishes to braised ones.
And have tons of knowledge.
I'm excited to go to the restaurant
that this chef recommends.
-Absolutely.
-It's bound to be good.
-He should be here soon.
-He's a bit late.
A MYSTERIOUS GUY COMES RUNNING FROM AFAR
BUT HE'S TOO SLOW
HE'S SLOWER THAN SOMEONE WHO'S WALKING
LIGHTLY
He's here.
Are you running or walking?
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
Hello.
-He looks like Sean from Jinusean.
I thought Sean was running.
Slow jogging is popular these days.
-Really?
-Yes, I exercised before we eat.
I'm Song Haseulram,
and I make side dishes.
-Nice to meet you.
-I'm glad to meet you.
RATHER THAN EXPENSIVE
AND FANCY FINE DINING DISHES
HE MAKES EVERYDAY SIDE DISHES
HE RESEARCHES THE INFINITE POSSIBILITIES
OF FAMILIAR INGREDIENTS
CHEF SIDE DISH, SONG HASEULRAM
I know that you sell side dishes.
How is your store doing?
It's in Seongsu-dong.
I sell on the first floor.
The second floor is a pub.
-A side dish pub is cool.
-What's that?
-Are side dishes the bar snacks?
-Exactly.
I used to cook in Spain.
-They're like tapas.
-Right.
-I think tapas are similar to side dishes.
-I see.
You can pick the side dishes
and eat them on the second floor.
I've also been receiving requests
to develop dishes with local ingredients,
so I'm creating recipes with them.
That's awesome.
You're here to introduce your go-to place.
Can you tell us about it?
Since I usually make side dishes,
I can guarantee that they are great.
And the rice that complements
the side dishes is absolutely scrumptious.
A side-dish chef guarantees others' sides.
-He's piqued my curiosity.
-Same.
-You must have high standards.
-I'm excited.
I'm sure you will all love it.
It's a ten-minute walk from Seokchon Lake.
-It's nearby.
-How long will it take if we slow jog?
-If we slow-jog…
-About 30 minutes?
-Thirty minutes?
-Then let's slow jog.
-Let's go.
-Off we go.
I feel like walking would be faster.
Power walking is way faster, isn't it?
-My knees are starting to hurt.
-Mine too.
-I'm just going to walk.
-Let's go eat.
EXERCISING BEFORE EATING
The weather is amazing.
-It suddenly cooled down.
-It sure did.
This is an intersection
with many academies.
-There are so many of them.
-Right.
I see math, English, concept-focused,
and creative learning academies.
This neighborhood has been here
for a long time,
so there are
many hidden old-school eateries here.
You bet.
Where is today's go-to spot?
-It's right over there.
-"Ahn Jae Korean Restaurant"?
That's right.
THEY SELL KOREAN FOOD
It looks neat.
It just has a simple sign.
FINALLY ARRIVED
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello, sir.
We also met a few days ago.
AHN JAEMAN, OWNER
-Hello.
-I feel like we're friends.
THE OWNER ALSO HAS A SHAVED HEAD
The restaurant is nice and neat.
And you can tell they sell Korean food.
-It looks like they have stone pot rice.
-Really?
"Stone pot rice made fresh
from good rice."
-I love it.
-I haven't had it in a long time.
I'm excited to try it.
I'll take care of ordering the food.
-That's the best.
-Absolutely.
I love it when the chef orders.
-Sir.
-Yes.
He's confident about his choices.
-We'll order four basic set meals.
-Sure.
And 400 grams of Eonyang-style
charcoal-grilled bulgogi, please.
Got it. I will prepare them with care.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
GLAD TO SEE A SHAVED HEAD
How did you become a regular
at this restaurant?
I heard of a restaurant
that gets high-quality ingredients
from all over the country
and makes its own side dishes.
I sell side dishes, so I was curious.
I loved the food here,
so I come once in a while.
What side dish would you pick
if you had to eat only one?
-I love leaf mustard kimchi.
-It's the god of kimchi.
That's hilarious.
I'll serve the side dishes first.
WOW
-That's the leaf mustard kimchi.
-It sure is.
Enjoy.
-Can you introduce them to us?
-Of course.
You probably already know this,
but it's from Yeosu.
-It's kimchi from Yeosu.
-It's the best.
LEAF MUSTARD KIMCHI
And these are pine mushrooms.
BRAISED PINE MUSHROOM
This is Gwangcheon salted baby octopus.
Pickled chili and seasoned chili
made from chilis sourced from Miryang.
Stir-fried summer squash.
My mouth is watering.
The jangjorim looks amazing.
KOREAN BEEF JANGJORIM
And seasoned young radish greens
from Pocheon.
WOW
-And there are more side dishes.
-Where are they?
-Let's get them together.
-Sure.
WHOA
Look here.
You can have refills.
-Can you get unlimited refills?
-Definitely.
PLEASE FEEL FREE
TO HELP YOURSELF TO REFILLS
Get a ton of everything.
UNLIMITED REFILLS
-Get heaps of it.
-There's everything here.
This one is new.
Right, these are
eggplant kimchi and geotjeori.
-I'll get the geotjeori. Looks delicious.
-I'll get the eggplant kimchi.
MORE SIDE DISHES
Eggplant kimchi is interesting.
TWO MORE SIDE DISHES COMING
Ta-da.
We brought eggplant kimchi and geotjeori.
TEN SIDE DISHES ARE SERVED
-Let's try each one's favorite one.
-Sure.
You know, I'm from Jeolla-do.
My family home is in Suncheon and Yeosu.
-I'll start with this.
-Of course.
CHOOSES THE YEOSU LEAF MUSTARD KIMCHI
YUM
I just had the leaf mustard kimchi.
And I can't stop eating it.
It's like how my mom used to make it.
-Really?
-It's nice and clean.
The unique aroma
of the leaf mustard comes through.
It's perfectly fermented.
You can really taste
the natural ingredients.
I'm loving this.
THE YEOSU LEAF MUSTARD KIMCHI
HAS A PIQUANT AFTERTASTE
I want to try
the stir-fried summer squash.
I loved it whenever my mom
made this side dish.
I should compare them.
WILL IT SUIT DUJUN'S TASTE?
-Is it good?
-Oh, it just melts in my mouth.
It tastes incredible.
The summer squash is unbelievable.
It's nicely stir-fried and seasoned.
-What's unique about this is that--
-It's sliced thick.
Yes, it's thicker than other places.
He slices it thick on purpose
so we can taste the sweetness.
Looking at these side dishes,
I can tell the owner wants to bring out
the natural flavors of the ingredients.
HE LIGHTLY STIR-FRIES THE SUMMER SQUASH
HE ADDS MINCED GARLIC
HE ADDS THE SPECIAL INGREDIENT,
SALTED SHRIMP
HE STIR-FRIES IT AGAIN, AND IT'S READY
The sweetness from the shrimp shines.
And then the saltiness kicks in.
Of all the salted shrimps,
like ojeot, yukjeot, chujeot,
yukjeot is regarded as the best.
Why is it called yukjeot?
Because it's made with June shrimp.
The shrimp are at their fullest in June.
Its sweetness fills your mouth.
If you make salted shrimp with it,
the juice is sweet as well.
UNBELIEVABLY RICH WITH UMAMI
I don't think I've ever seen yukjeot
this big used in ordinary side dishes.
This isn't just a common side dish
you eat with rice.
This side dish is like a main dish.
That's why I think he used
this expensive yukjeot to season this.
I can't help it. I have to try this one.
-The pine mushroom?
-Let's try this.
I'm curious how this will taste.
MINSEONG TRIES THE PINE MUSHROOM
-It looks like he's chewing on meat.
-I agree.
I should try it, too.
THE FOODIE BROTHERS ALL TAKE A BITE
Wow, it's incredibly tender.
It's amazing.
It looks like he didn't use
too much oil to make this.
He just stir-fried them
with a bit of oil and water in a pan.
HE ADDS IN PLENTY OF SOY SAUCE
HE SIMMERS THEM UNTIL THEY TURN BROWN
THE YANGPYEONG
BRAISED PINE MUSHROOM ARE READY
I'm not familiar with pine mushroom.
What is it like?
It's more chewy
than an ordinary shiitake mushroom.
It has a firm texture.
Shiitake mushrooms are more common
because pine mushrooms are expensive.
You don't need meat
if you have mushrooms like these.
They'd be perfect
with just rice and kimchi.
This is excellent.
THIS SIDE DISH TAKES MUSHROOMS
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL
I'll choose the seasoned
young radish greens.
-Let's try it.
-You try it first.
I love the fragrance of young radish,
so I'll try this.
It's tender.
-The aroma is nice.
-Right.
HOW DOES THIS SIDE DISH TASTE?
It's refreshing.
DUJUN ALSO TAKES A BITE
How do I put this? It tastes fresh.
This is the stuff.
It's like Korean arugula.
-Exactly.
-It's quite peppery.
Absolutely.
People love young radish greens.
The younger the greens,
the spicier they are at the end.
It's rare to eat young radish greens
as a salad like this.
-It's very tender.
-It's so good.
-You have to use the new sprouts.
-Definitely.
In Jeolla-do, they wrap sashimi
and even meat in young radish.
-Really?
-Yes, they do that.
It's served when you go
to a ssambap restaurant.
At first, you think it's arugula,
but it's just young radish.
Gosh, since you're experts,
you explain it so well.
And the owner received green plum syrup
made by his mother in Miryang.
It's homemade green plum syrup,
which he uses as a dressing.
This green plum syrup tastes
like fresh tomatoes.
-Yes, there's also garlic.
-I thought he mixed in tomato juice.
So, this cleanses your palate
before you eat the other dishes.
And then you can eat
the rest of your meal.
ACTS AS AN APPETIZER
This is bad.
I'm going to need so much rice for this.
REMARKABLE SIDE DISHES
The owner gets the ingredients
from all over the country
and prepares them.
For the Gwangcheon salted baby octopus,
he goes to Gwangcheon himself
to get the ingredients.
He has done business
with them for seven years,
so he only gets it from them.
SIDE DISHES MADE FROM LOCAL INGREDIENTS
FROM AROUND THE COUNTRY
At first, it's challenging
to find new suppliers.
-It's very difficult.
-Right.
-It's hard to find good ingredients.
-True.
It's even harder
to constantly do business with them.
-That's the hardest part.
-It's such a hassle every time.
-He knows all about it.
-I agree.
It's hard when you have lots of suppliers.
Wow, I can't even imagine.
I'm obsessed with these dishes.
-Bring rice.
-I'm craving more.
When will the rice come out?
STONE POT RICE FOR THE FOODIE BROTHERS
COOKS FOR EIGHT MINUTES
ON MY WAY TO MEET YOU
Wow, it's here.
The stone pot rice is ready.
-It's Suhyangmi stone pot rice.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
Be careful. It's hot.
There's no scorched rice in there.
It's Suhyangmi stone pot rice
without the scorched rice?
-Right, we don't scorch the rice.
-I see.
-Is there a reason for that?
-Yes.
Is it because of the smell?
That's one reason.
The other reason is that
if you heat it over high heat,
it overcooks,
and the texture just isn't great.
So, I wanted to preserve the texture
and fragrance of the rice.
-That's why I don't scorch the rice.
-I see.
The rice smells so rich and nice.
It smells nutty.
GIVES OFF A DEEP, FRAGRANT AROMA
I made this barley tea
from the barley my mother grew.
Add the barley tea
so you can drink it like sungnyung.
-That sounds great.
-That's a good idea.
Is there soup as well?
DRIED POLLACK SEAWEED SOUP
Is there a reason you source local
ingredients from all over the country?
Vegetables and other ingredients
are auctioned and sent to wholesalers.
And in the process,
they lose their original flavor.
So that's why we always
source them straight from the farm.
You must have very high standards.
The last time I came here,
he boiled the bamboo shoots himself.
-Really?
-That's right.
He seasoned them with perilla powder,
which was so good.
I want to serve you
some other side dishes.
So, I would love to bring out
some of the autumnal side dishes
and the pickled wild greens
we served in the spring.
-Really?
-It's an honor.
These are chili chips made from chilis
my mother dried in Miryang.
-Okay.
-It's made with chilis.
-And this is--
-Dried persimmons!
MIRYANG PICKLED DRIED PERSIMMONS
And these are ogapisun
picked in the Gyeryongsan Mountain.
An herbalist there sends them to me.
This is all that's left.
There will be more next year.
-Wow, thank you.
-We're lucky to have these.
The rice is the main dish.
Why don't you try the rice and soup first?
-All right.
-Got it.
TAKES A BITE
It's so nutty.
What makes Suhyangmi so different?
The aroma is very rich and intense.
There are more kinds of rice these days.
-That's right.
-It has a nice aroma.
And this rice is more moist and sticky
when compared to other varieties.
Like the owner said,
if you try to overheat this
to make scorched rice,
I think it will interfere
with the rice's natural aroma.
-Is this dried pollack seaweed soup?
-Yes, it's good.
TIME TO TRY THE DRIED POLLACK SEAWEED SOUP
This is top-quality soup.
How is the soup, everyone? I love it.
It's light and tasty.
He only used dried pollack and seaweed,
so it's very light.
It's not too strong.
I feel like it balances out
the other dishes.
The overall seasoning isn't too strong.
It goes down easily.
And it's fantastic.
HOW DO THE SEASONAL SIDES TASTE?
Are these the new ones
the owner served us?
-What did he say this was?
-Pickled dried persimmons.
DRIED PERSIMMONS
Whoa, try this side dish.
It's spicier than I expected.
He mixed dried persimmons with gochujang.
COMBINED DRIED PERSIMMONS WITH GOCHUJANG
PICKED PERSIMMONS GROWN
UNDER THE HOT MIRYANG SUN
MADE INTO DRIED PERSIMMONS
The dried persimmons are sweet.
The owner enjoys natural sweet flavors.
He mixed them
with green plum syrup gochujang.
-I can smell the green plum.
-Me too.
THE MIRYANG PICKLED DRIED PERSIMMONS
ARE READY
If you taste the food here,
you won't find any artificial sweetness.
I like the fact that the flavors
come entirely from the natural sweetness
of the vegetables and other ingredients.
-Shall we try the ogapi?
-Sure.
-Have you seen this?
-No.
I've never seen
pickled thorny ogapi, either.
Oh, the fragrance…
The ogapi…
Is the scent coming from the ogapi?
It's very aromatic.
How can I explain this smell?
It has that unique bitterness
and aroma that wild greens have.
-It's extremely appealing.
-Look.
This would be the fanciest side dish here.
Wow, this is…
Ogapi has all sorts of scents.
You can smell the aroma
even from just a small bite.
It's so cool.
Wow, I'm in trouble.
I'm going to need so much rice.
A SCOOP OF RICE WITH PICKLED THORNY OGAPI
ANOTHER SCOOP OF RICE
WITH SOY-BRAISED CHILI
Salted baby octopus
on a spoonful of warm Suhyangmi rice.
A SCOOP OF RICE WITH SALTED BABY OCTOPUS
This is a work of art.
A PIECE OF EGGPLANT KIMCHI
I've never heard of eggplant kimchi.
This is cool.
I'm loving the wild greens.
There isn't much texture
if there's only eggplant,
so he added chives.
We need a foreign guest on the show.
-To bring them here?
-Exactly.
What led you to become a chef
specializing in side dishes?
I used to work
in a fine dining restaurant.
I spent some time cooking
in a M*chelin restaurant in Spain.
I used to cook in a M*chelin restaurant
in Korea as well.
Fine dining restaurants
are often hard to access
due to price and other factors.
"How could I make my food
accessible to more people?"
I kept contemplating this.
Even if they aren't
the ingredients we usually eat,
I wanted to use them in Korean dishes.
So I decided to run a side dish store.
HE USES UNFAMILIAR INGREDIENTS
Is it common for chefs to switch careers
and start making side dishes?
It hardly ever happens.
There aren't many chefs who want
to take the time to research ingredients.
Here is the main dish.
This is Eonyang-style bulgogi.
TODAY'S MAIN MENU
This looks insane.
My mouth is watering.
ALL OF THE DISHES ARE FINALLY SERVED
I'm taking a high-angle shot.
It's the trend these days.
The whole table has to be in full view.
A TABLE FULL OF SIDE DISHES
-I can smell the charcoal.
-The scent rises.
It's different from the bulgogi
we usually eat.
It looks extremely crispy.
This is called crispy bulgogi.
-In fact…
-I've heard it before.
Eonyang-style bulgogi is crispy bulgogi.
There are three types of bulgogi
in this country.
First, Seoul-style bulgogi,
which has a bit of broth, veggies,
and glass noodles.
ADD VEGGIES AND GLASS NOODLES
TO THE BROTH AND LET IT SIMMER
Second, Gwangyang-style bulgogi.
It's not marinated in advance
like spicy stir-fried meat.
You season it on the spot and grill it.
Lastly, Eonyang-style bulgogi.
Marinate it and grill it
until it's crispy.
MARINATE THINLY SLICED MEAT
AND COOK UNTIL CRISPY
This is Eonyang-style bulgogi
among the three.
This is premium Korean beef.
TOP-QUALITY KOREAN BEEF
-It's made with top round beef.
-This is a luxury.
TIME FOR A TASTY TREAT
Let me try it.
I love the smoky aroma.
TAKES A BITE WHILE ENJOYING THE SMELL
Wow, it's scrumptious.
How is it, Minseong?
Don't talk to me.
AT A LOSS FOR WORDS
This sweetness brings me joy.
It tastes healthy.
-It's not too strong.
-No.
The key lies in how he balances
the sweetness.
And the secret to this bulgogi
is that he doesn't use soy sauce in it.
Wait, he didn't use soy sauce?
-No.
-Then what…
BULGOGI IS GRILLED
OVER HIGH-QUALITY CHARCOAL
A DELICATE, SWEET AROMA SEEPS THROUGH
It's seasoned with salt
that has been refined for eight years.
The owner adds green plum syrup
for sweetness.
And it's grilled over charcoal right away.
THIS COMBINATION ENHANCES
THE NATURAL FLAVOR OF THE MEAT
Bulgogi is usually sweet.
-Is the sweetness from green plum syrup?
-Yes.
I can keep eating this.
The smoky aroma is amazing.
Why don't you try the bulgogi
with the young radish?
-Sure.
-It's a great pairing.
-Let me try it.
-Yes.
Place a piece of bulgogi on top.
-Bulgogi and…
-Add a bit of salted baby octopus.
-Really?
-Yes, add a bit on top.
I'll wrap it with this.
WRAP EVERYTHING UP
IN POCHEON SEASONED YOUNG RADISH GREENS
It pairs well with the refreshing
young radish greens.
It's so yummy.
DUJUN ADDS THE SALTED BABY OCTOPUS
ON TOP LIKE DAVID
Sir, can we get
more salted baby octopus and…
-I'll get some more.
-Oh, is it self-service?
-Yes.
-Let's get some more summer squash.
What else do we need?
Let's stop here. No need to be greedy.
We shouldn't waste food.
SCOOPS SOME SALTED BABY OCTOPUS
We need more summer squash.
Take a generous portion.
-Yes, I'll get a lot.
-It tastes unbelievable.
ADDICTIVE SUMMER SQUASH
This is the best side dish I've had today.
-The summer squash?
-Yes.
I'm obsessed with it.
ONE MORE BITE
The salted shrimp
is salty and sweet as well.
It's perfectly balanced.
If side dishes were served
in other countries,
no one would eat them.
They would wait for the main dish.
Are foreigners not familiar
with the concept of side dishes?
They're not.
They think that, if they eat them,
they will be charged for the sides.
They'd be curious, though.
These side dishes are
a unique culture of ours.
-This is the true warmth of Korea.
-Exactly.
In other words,
the owners are exhausted from cooking.
WORN OUT FROM MAKING THE SIDE DISHES
Dujun, what is your
favorite side dish pairing?
I just tried the jangjorim
with the quail eggs.
-It's not salty at all.
-It's light.
I'll place a piece of meat atop the rice.
-Nice.
-What will go well with this?
-Try it with the summer squash.
-Got it.
-That's it.
-Add a piece.
ADDING STIR-FRIED SUMMER SQUASH
Let's try it.
ENJOYING IT IN A SINGLE BITE
The jangjorim is a bit salty,
and the summer squash is sweet,
so it's perfectly balanced.
Let me see…
-I'll go for a dark pairing.
-What does that mean?
-You mean the mushroom.
-Yes.
BRAISED PINE MUSHROOM
-And pickled chili.
-Okay.
For a bit of acidity.
I loved the aroma
of this pickled thorny ogapi.
Add a bit of fragrance.
Together on top.
-It's a vegetarian pairing.
-Exactly.
EASILY DEVOURS IT IN ONE BITE
We're having enough food,
but why does my mouth water?
Me too.
MOUTHWATERING
I ate a mouthful of greens.
-I see.
-I could feel its fresh energy.
Right, he ate mushrooms and ogapi.
And chili.
My pairing is simple.
I'll start with bulgogi.
Place it on top of the rice.
Meat as always?
He chose the leaf mustard kimchi.
Dang, this is the stuff.
It's a classic pairing.
MOUTHWATERING AGAIN
If it's too bland, add a piece of chili.
ADD SEASONED CRISP CHILI
IF SOMETHING FEELS LIKE IT'S MISSING
WOW
I'm not just full…
-I'm happy.
-…I feel healthy.
I haven't had a meal like this
in a long time.
It's hard to come by.
When you have a Korean course meal,
there are only a few side dishes you like.
There are so many good dishes here
that I don't know what to eat next.
WHEN YOU CAN'T CHOOSE WHAT TO EAT NEXT
TRY THE BRAISED PINE MUSHROOM
AND SEASONED CRISP CHILI
JUST DON'T STOP EATING
Try this.
-Wait…
-Did you try it?
-Not yet.
-Try it.
-It's not spicy.
-There's a reason he made it this way.
-He blanched it briefly.
-It's full of flavor.
Yes, the spiciness really comes through.
EVERYONE STARTS DEVOURING THE FOOD
EVERYONE STOPS TALKING AND DIGS IN
Wait a second.
-We have never been this quiet.
-Definitely.
We have to talk for the show,
but it's hard because the food is insane.
WHAT WILL THEY FINISH THE MEAL WITH?
The barley tea is nice.
There's no need for scorched rice.
CLEAN AND NUTTY BARLEY TEA
DRINKING STRAIGHT FROM THE STONE POT
I get super full when I eat too much rice,
but I feel great today.
A FILLING BUT NICE MEAL
Side dishes are so familiar to us
that we often take them for granted.
Personally, I really enjoyed trying
all of these new side dishes.
I cleaned my plate.
-I ate every last bite.
-Me too.
I ate it all. I even ate all of the soup.
Wow, we devoured everything.
This is insane.
It was an amazing meal.
-Thank you.
-Thank you for the food.
Chef Song Haseulram,
what does this go-to spot mean to you?
This place? Let me see…
Like you said, blood sugar spikes
and low-sugar foods are hot topics.
People are concerned about their health.
We're all trying to eat healthy.
But rather than eating a lot of good food,
it's more important to avoid bad food.
Mothers usually want to provide us
with healthy food.
Just like that,
even when we can't go home,
this go-to spot lets us enjoy
homemade food just like our mothers'.
That's what this place means to me.
-It's a substitute for your mom's meals.
-That's right.
Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
-It was awesome.
AHN JAE KOREAN RESTAURANT
THANKS FOR THE MEAL
I want to bring my family here.
THE MAIN CHARACTERS OF A MEAL,
A NEW APPRECIATION FOR SIDE DISHES
Translated by Heewon Sim