GIL-DONG, GANGDONG-GU, SEOUL
WHICH FOODIE BROTHERS CAME
TO GIL-DONG TODAY?
THE FOURTH, YOON DUJUN
THE THIRD, LIM TAEHOON
THE SECOND, DAVID LEE
We came to this area
because it's packed with good restaurants.
It's been a while since I've come to
a neighborhood with so many restaurants.
LINED WITH RESTAURANTS
SERVING VARIOUS KINDS OF FOOD
Who invited today's chef?
-Not me.
-I did.
-Oh, Taehoon did.
-That's right.
The chef I invited today is
the first foreigner on this show.
Is that so?
-Really?
-Yes, he is a foreign chef.
THE FIRST FOREIGN CHEF?
Who is it?
TALL
Buongiorno, my friend.
Buongiorno.
-He's here.
-He sure is.
I brought drinks.
He's turned into a complete Korean.
How could an Italian bring Americanos?
-He's totally Korean.
-Exactly.
Not Korean, I'm Kotalian.
-You're Kotalian.
-That's right.
COOKS CLASSIC ITALIAN DISHES
Fabri-style ragù pasta.
AN ITALIAN CHEF
WHO IS ALSO PASSIONATE ABOUT COFFEE
I already drank three cups of this.
FABRIZIO FERRARI
I'm addicted.
-Do you like iced Americano?
-Yes, I love it.
-Seriously?
-He's not Italian anymore.
I'm an original Kotalian.
-I'm the original.
-Got it.
Do you come to Gil-dong often?
-Yes, I do.
-Really?
Of course, I have a go-to place here.
-I see.
-But it's a secret.
I'm curious. Is it an Italian restaurant?
-Even Taehoon doesn't know this spot.
-Really?
Wow, I'm curious.
Let's get going.
Off we go.
HERE WE GO
OF ALL THESE RESTAURANTS, WHICH ONE IS IT?
Take a guess.
Maybe it's an authentic Italian restaurant
that Chef Fabri likes.
No, it doesn't serve Italian dishes.
Isn't Gil-dong udon famous here?
-It's beyond anything you can imagine.
-I see.
-Beyond anything?
-Exactly.
Maybe it's a classic Korean dish
that Kotalians like.
-I'll give you a hint.
-Sure.
I drank too much alcohol last night.
A DISH RELATED TO ALCOHOL
You eat it after drinking.
It's that place.
Read it out loud, please.
-"Hangover soup."
-There.
-Yeonghwajeong?
A HANGOVER SOUP PLACE WITH AN OLD SIGN
It's a hangover soup spot that
you confidently recommend to Koreans.
I can't imagine you
enjoying hangover soup.
Absolutely not.
-Let's go in.
-Let's head inside.
-Chef, after you.
-Sure.
Hello, sir.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
-He seems charismatic.
-Hi.
-This sure is a good restaurant.
JUNG SANGJIN
RUNS THE SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP SPOT
-Please sit here.
-Okay.
-What do you think of this place?
-I love the vibes here.
-Isn't it like an old-school eatery?
-Yes.
It's easy to order
since there's only one menu item.
There's only one dish on the menu.
-Seonji hangover soup.
-Exactly.
It's 9,000 won.
9,000 WON
Jjajangmyeon costs around 8,000
to 9,000 won on average.
Wow, it went up a lot.
It's about 11,000 won
if you go to a fancy place.
But 9,000 won for hangover soup
is unbelievably cheap.
Interesting. You can only order it
for dine-in until 2:30 p.m.
and takeout until 3:00 p.m.
-Really?
-Then what about after 3:00 p.m.?
After 3:00 p.m.,
we have to start prep for tomorrow.
The fact that you prepare it every day
means that the ingredients are…
-Fresh.
-Right.
We also make kimchi every day.
Wow, that's amazing.
FOOD MADE WITH FRESH INGREDIENTS
HE ONLY SELLS SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP
DURING LIMITED OPENING HOURS
So, shall we first order
four servings of the soup?
-We'll have four of that, please.
-Got it.
-You're an Italian chef.
-That's right.
How did this hangover soup place
become your go-to spot?
I was always curious about hangover food
because we don't have that in Italy.
We don't have that culture there.
What if you have a hangover?
We just drink coffee for hangovers.
-I see.
-We drink very strong espresso.
That's all we have, so…
I was surprised when I came here
and found out there's a hangover culture.
So, when I tried hangover soup
for the first time,
I felt much better.
It was so effective. It was incredible.
So, if I drink too much these days…
If I get wasted…
If I drink too much soju, I come here.
I come here right away.
That's why it's my go-to spot.
Now I get it.
-It's here.
-Yes.
Oh, never mind. They are side dishes.
CLASSIC SOUP SIDE DISHES:
TWO TYPES OF KIMCHI
SPICY NAPA CABBAGE KIMCHI
REFRESHING DICED RADISH KIMCHI
Wait, they have twisted peppers.
You're right. That's cool.
The stir-fried twisted peppers
and anchovies are a unique side dish here.
These three dishes look good together.
He looks so happy.
They all go well
with seonji hangover soup.
I love them.
SUPER MOUTHWATERING
-I can't wait to try them.
-Me too.
I'll try the twisted peppers first.
This is the stuff.
-These are anchovies.
-Yes, I know.
TAKES A BITE
WHAT DOES IT TASTE LIKE?
-It's tasty.
-It's perfectly seasoned.
-Let me have some.
-It's yummy.
-Oh, but it's spicy.
-It sure is.
It's not an ordinary side dish.
THE STIR-FRIED TWISTED PEPPERS
AND ANCHOVIES ARE SEASONED WELL
-It's scrumptious.
-Try the kimchi, too.
TAKING A BITE OF NICELY FERMENTED
NAPA CABBAGE KIMCHI
It's unbelievable.
They used good chili powder.
And ginger adds the kick here.
-The ginger aroma is strong.
-It's tasty.
-That also helps with hangovers.
-Absolutely.
GINGER SOOTHES HANGOVERS
It's homemade kimchi.
BEFORE AND AFTER OPENING
THE RESTAURANT EVERY DAY,
HE STARTS BY PREPPING ALL THE INGREDIENTS
HE MAKES NAPA CABBAGE KIMCHI,
DICED RADISH KIMCHI
AND OTHER SIDE DISHES AS WELL
EVERYTHING IS MADE FRESH
THE OWNER MAKES JUST ENOUGH FOR THE DAY
THE SAME GOES FOR THE SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP
SIMMERED FOR A LONG TIME,
WHICH ENRICHES THE OVERALL FLAVOR
TENDER, WELL-COOKED UGEOJI
AND CREAMY SEONJI ARE ADDED
A BOWL FULL OF RICH BROTH
HE ADDS SLICED GREEN ONIONS,
AND IT'S READY
THE SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP IS FINALLY SERVED
Wow, it looks so rich.
-Doesn't it have a rich color?
-Yes.
It looks like red bean porridge.
IT'S THE COLOR OF RED BEAN PORRIDGE
WHAT WILL THE BROTH TASTE LIKE
WITHOUT ANY SEASONING?
-Thank you for the food.
-Enjoy.
I've never tried anything like this.
-How is it?
-It's amazing.
-It's beef bone broth.
-Exactly.
UNBELIEVABLY DEEP AND RICH IN FLAVOR
-Look at this.
-Wow, it's rich.
-Doesn't it taste like milk?
-Yes, it does.
-It's very creamy.
-Absolutely.
-And it's very thick.
-It seeped into the broth.
It has a deep flavor.
EVERYONE CAN ENJOY THIS SOUP
Is this seonji made from pork or beef?
-It's beef.
-Beef.
-This is awesome.
-Attention, everyone.
Please look at this big piece.
A LARGE CHUNK OF SEONJI
It's firm when you hold it
with chopsticks.
It's firm, yet very tender in your mouth.
It's like pudding.
BOUNCY LIKE PUDDING
TAKING A BITE OF SEONJI
CAN'T HELP BUT EXCLAIM AT HOW GOOD IT IS
YUM
-Isn't the texture so nice?
-Yes.
THE TEXTURE IS VERY NICE
The quality of this seonji
is incredible because…
It usually gets stuck between your teeth.
-Of course, but this has a nice texture.
-Right.
-It cuts easily.
-Yes, I'm loving it.
The texture is insane.
THE SEONJI HERE BREAKS APART NICELY
Is this chalseonji?
Chalseonji is made
without adding water to the blood.
It's pure, fresh blood,
so it's different from ordinary seonji.
CHALSEONJI
RICHER THAN ORDINARY SEONJI
When you see seonji in hangover soup,
-it usually has a lot of holes in it.
-Oh, yes, I know.
-It's because they mix it with water.
-Right.
REGULAR SEONJI HAS TONS OF HOLES
-I don't see any holes here.
-You're right.
CHALSEONJI HARDLY HAS ANY HOLES
Chalseonji is way better for hangovers.
-Does it help more?
-Yes, it does.
-And I think it's a healthy meal.
-I agree.
-It has hemoglobin and iron.
-Everything.
-That's right.
-It has everything your body needs.
PREVENTS ANEMIA,
BOOSTS IMMUNITY
-Let me see.
-This is great.
-Let me try it with kimchi.
-Sounds good.
It goes very well with kimchi.
I'll pair it with kimchi.
WHAT WILL THIS TASTE LIKE?
With seonji.
YUM
CAN'T EAT IT QUIETLY BECAUSE IT'S SO TASTY
This is unbelievable.
Try it with this.
-The twisted peppers and anchovies?
-Yes.
The texture of the stir-fried anchovies
complements the seonji.
-Because the seonji is tender.
-Right.
-And the anchovies are chewy.
-Exactly.
ADDS TEXTURE
EYES WIDE OPEN
Try it with this.
They're perfect together.
-It's slightly salty.
-Right.
It's sweet and salty at the same time.
I'm loving it.
It's bursting with flavor.
At first, I thought it was bland.
But it's not if you eat it
with the side dishes.
ENJOYING VARIOUS TEXTURES AND FLAVORS
WITH DIFFERENT SIDE DISHES
Everyone, please look here.
-That's the ugeoji.
-Exactly.
It's awesome.
UGEOJI
Just what I thought.
-Geez, this ugeoji.
-Ugeoji, geez.
DAD JOKES SIDE BY SIDE
This is it.
THIS IS THE STUFF
DEVOURING
I'm loving the ugeoji.
I don't usually eat ugeoji,
but this is super tender.
You can tell it's good for you.
This is a diet food.
REFRESHING NAPA CABBAGE
AND BEEF BONE BROTH
Different regions in Korea
have their own styles of hangover soup.
-Sure.
-That's right.
Tell me the ones you know.
-Jeonju bean sprout soup.
-Exactly.
JEONJU BEAN SPROUT HANGOVER SOUP
SOOTHES YOUR STOMACH
-Busan pork and rice soup.
-Right.
BUSAN PORK GUKBAP
WITH RICH BROTH AND PLENTY OF PORK
-Yangpyeong hangover soup.
-That's right.
HANGOVER SOUP IN GYEONGGI-DO,
MADE WITH BEEF INTESTINES AND SEONJI
Gangwon-do moray eel stew.
BURSTS WITH THE REFRESHING TASTE OF FISH
There's one from Jeju Island, too.
-It's bracken hangover soup.
-Wow, I've never had that.
In Jeonju…
Naju beef bone soup.
-Isn't Naju beef bone soup from Naju?
-My bad.
EMBARRASSED
NAJU BEEF BONE SOUP HAS A CLEAR BROTH
SOUTH KOREA IS SERIOUS
ABOUT CURING HANGOVERS
DAVID IS PASSIONATE ABOUT IT, TOO
I don't want this place
to be featured on the show.
I WANT TO KEEP THIS PLACE TO MYSELF
Do you like this place?
-Yes.
-It's scrumptious.
THUMBS UP!
And guess what this is.
There's something else in here.
Don't look.
WHAT'S IN THE METAL JAR?
-Salt?
-Salted shrimp?
-Garlic?
-Perilla powder?
-Taehoon got it right.
-Wow, it's minced garlic.
-Yes, I love it.
Do you put this in?
HOW DO YOU USE THIS MINCED GARLIC?
-Add it to the soup.
-Got it.
-You have a certain order?
-Yes.
MIX PLENTY OF GARLIC
INTO THE SOUP AND ENJOY
WHAT WILL IT TASTE LIKE NOW?
-Let me add it.
-Add lots of it.
-Look at how he does it.
-Lots of garlic.
Italians also love garlic.
It's interesting.
-It tastes sweet.
-It changed.
-Isn't it sweet?
-I agree.
It's like when you add onions.
It was slightly creamy,
but now it has a kick from the garlic.
-Yes, it's pungent.
-It has a sharp kick to it.
It's nice and clean.
CLEANSES THE PALATE
THE FOODIE BROTHERS CHOW DOWN THE FOOD
I should bring my parents here.
I think my father would really like this.
It would be nice
to deliver this to your house.
I would order it
when I've lost my appetite.
You know we mixed garlic in the soup.
What do you usually add after the garlic?
Do you put this in?
I add this as well.
SAUCE THAT WILL MAKE IT SPICY
-Let's try it.
-Sure, why don't we?
Aren't you adding too much, Fabri?
No, this is the right amount.
ADDED A SPOONFUL OF SAUCE
TAEHOON IS LOST IN THOUGHT
Look at that.
BEFORE THE FOOD WAS SERVED…
-"The red sauce is super spicy."
-Super.
…TAEHOON TRIED THE SAUCE
-The spiciness really hits at the end.
-Yes, it sure does.
-He's sweating.
-Don't drink water.
-Dang, it has a spicy kick at the end.
-Look at your sweat.
Let's go, Taehoon.
But it was too…
TAEHOON IS FLUSTERED
Isn't that too much?
HE'S HESITANT TO TRY IT
Let me add some.
Wow, that much?
-Yes, I can handle spicy food.
-Really?
THE KOTALIAN IS CONFIDENT ABOUT SPICY FOOD
I'm confident, too.
THAT'S CUTE
WHAT DOES THE FUTURE HOLD FOR HIM?
THOROUGHLY MIX THE SAUCE INTO THE SOUP
It turned slightly red.
It looks like spicy beef soup.
THE BROTH TURNED RED
WHAT WILL THE SOUP TASTE LIKE
AFTER ADDING THE SPICY SAUCE?
SWEATING RIGHT AWAY
Wait a second.
Wow, it tastes different again.
-It pops your eyes open right away.
-This is it.
-This is what hangover soup is.
-Right.
FABRI ENJOYS THE SPICY TASTE
At first,
the rich flavor fills your mouth.
-And then it's got a spicy finish.
-Exactly.
It has a healthy spicy flavor.
-It's like when we eat Cheongyang peppers.
-It's nice and spicy.
You get to eat three types of soup
for just 9,000 won.
That's right.
Isn't that incredible?
-Right.
-They all taste different.
It's amazing.
AT FIRST, IT TASTES CREAMY AND RICH
ADDING THE PUNGENT GARLIC
DEEPENS THE FLAVOR
AND ADDING THE SPICY SAUCE MAKES IT SPICY
IT'S TIME TO ENJOY THE COMPLETED VERSION
OF THIS SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP
THIS IS IT!
It's unbelievable.
I like having all of the different
textures and flavors in one bite.
How come he eats so well?
MOUTH FULL OF FOOD
ABSOLUTELY DELICIOUS
YOU HAVE TO DRINK IT FROM THE BOWL
Bravo, David.
It looked like a scene
from a Joseon dynasty drama.
And they offer unlimited refills
for everything.
-We can have more.
-Exactly.
UNLIMITED REFILLS
This is a nice restaurant.
I can't believe it's unlimited.
RESPECT TO THIS PLACE
I ate everything.
Already?
DUJUN HAS NEVER EATEN THIS FAST
-It was scrumptious.
-Let's get a refill of this.
CLEANED HIS PLATE
Sir.
Could we get refills?
I'm sorry.
I'm a bit embarrassed to say this.
But could we please get some more?
-A big portion, please.
-Sure.
THANK YOU FOR THE REFILLS
-Can we get them separately?
-Of course.
-We can order only seonji.
-Right.
Sir, are you okay with offering refills?
Yes, it's all right.
I haven't changed
the price for three years,
and I still offer unlimited refills.
How long have you run this place?
My elementary school friend's mother
had been running this place for 40 years.
-Here?
-No, in Cheonho-dong.
Oh, that's why it says
"From Cheonho-dong" out front.
Yes, we moved from Cheonho-dong to here.
-There's history behind it.
-Right.
THE RESTAURANT MOVED HERE 20 YEARS AGO
-I've been running it for six years.
-I see.
HE TOOK OVER THE RESTAURANT
-I come here often.
-Right.
The broth is usually clear,
but now it's very thick and rich.
It looks like red bean porridge.
It's clearer in the morning.
Why is that?
-You know, the seonji is a bit salty.
-Okay.
So, I only add
a little seonji in the mornings.
You usually come here at that time,
so it's clear.
THE MORNING BROTH IS LIGHTER AND CLEARER
THAN THE AFTERNOON BROTH
The broth is clear at first,
but it gets richer as I add more beef
bone broth and seonji throughout the day.
It draws out the rich flavor,
making it thick.
SIMMERS THE BROTH EVERY DAY
THE SECRET TO HIS RICH HANGOVER SOUP
BEEF BONE BROTH IS CONSTANTLY
POURED IN WHILE IT SIMMERS
ADDS MORE SEONJI AS WELL
THE BROTH CHANGES
TO A DEEPER COLOR OVER TIME
CLEAR BROTH IN THE MORNINGS,
RICH BROTH IN THE AFTERNOONS
So, you can have
a clear broth in the morning.
And you can have
a rich broth in the afternoon.
COME IN THE AFTERNOON
IF YOU WANT RICHER FLAVOR
Hold on…
4 EXTRA BOWLS OF SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP
-It comes in a new bowl.
-It looks the same.
It's the same amount.
EVEN THE BOWLS ARE SIMILAR IN SIZE
-This is insane.
-We're starting all over again.
ALMOST THE SAME PORTION
THE FOODIE BROTHERS HAVE ANOTHER BOWL
-Whoa, this is rich.
-I'm loving this.
Honestly, I don't enjoy drinking alcohol,
but I might consider drinking
if I could have this hangover soup.
And the soju and beer are only 4,000 won.
You can't find that anywhere.
And the makgeolli is 3,000 won.
THAT'S A REASONABLE PRICE IN SEOUL
After seeing that it's only 4,000 won,
I'm suddenly craving alcohol.
-What do you want?
-The hair of the dog.
-Really?
-Yes.
After having this spicy broth,
I would like some alcohol right away.
-Would you like some?
-Of course.
-Could we please get a bottle of soju?
-Got it.
-Soju and beer?
-No, just soju.
You should take a straight shot of it
with this soup.
Just soju.
A BOTTLE OF SOJU IS BROUGHT OUT RIGHT AWAY
FOR A HANGOVER DRINK
MAKING A WHIRLWIND IS A MUST
It's not working.
Gosh, hand it over.
SUCCEEDED ON HIS FIRST TRY
TAP
-Let's go.
-Is he Korean?
I can't do this stuff.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
PERFECT DRINKING ETIQUETTE
-Here you go, David.
-Thanks.
-I'll pour some for Fabri.
-Is Fabri older than David?
-Yes, he is.
I'm a middle-aged guy, okay?
In Brindisi, we say, "Salute."
-Salute?
-Yes, that's what we say.
-We say it when we celebrate.
-I see.
It means, "To your health."
-But we're drinking alcohol.
-And we say that.
That's contradictory.
-Salute.
THIS IS THE STUFF
Do I have to turn away
from the viewers or from you?
I'll just drink it.
Dang, it's sweet.
I'm loving this.
Now this is the perfect meal.
Soju…
-Soju and…
-He's totally Korean.
IT'S HILARIOUS EVEN TO HIM
THIS SOUP MAKES EVEN A KOTALIAN CRAVE SOJU
-I made this earlier.
-Okay.
We usually dip meat
in ground pepper and salt.
Try dipping it here
since we have salt and ground pepper.
-It's tasty.
-Like sesame oil and salt?
Try it.
DIP
-Dip it.
-I love the smell of pepper.
-Hold on.
-It's good.
-The ground pepper pairs well with this.
-It's great with soju.
THE PERFECT SOJU SNACK
It's excellent.
-It's like pork liver.
-Absolutely.
-That's what I thought.
-Definitely.
It's like very tender pork liver.
-It's the perfect bar snack.
-Exactly.
THE SEONJI BECOMES A BAR SNACK
You really enjoy eating food.
-You try different cuisines.
-Of course. I'm a chef.
What made you want to become a chef?
Let's see.
When I was four years old,
my parents opened a restaurant.
And I grew up in that restaurant.
I didn't go to a culinary school
or anything.
I was a student when my parents
were running the restaurant,
so I helped them out.
HE LEARNED BY HELPING
I enjoyed cooking while helping them.
That's what made me want to become a chef.
-Was that the turning point?
-Yes.
FABRI DREAMED OF BECOMING A CHEF
AT HIS PARENTS' RESTAURANT
After I started cooking in the restaurant,
we got a M*chelin St*r
after only two years.
-You got it after teaching yourself.
-Right.
IMPRESSIVE
After that, I became Chef Fabri.
FABRI ACHIEVED HIS DREAM
AFTER COOKING SERIOUSLY FOR TWO YEARS
I maintained
the M*chelin St*r for 15 years.
Wow, that's incredible.
-I needed a sous chef.
-Okay.
Just by chance,
Koreans were my sous chefs.
I worked with Koreans a lot.
And I got to learn a lot
about the Korean food and culture.
That's what happened.
In 2016, I participated
in a Korean food contest in Milan.
-And I won.
-That's amazing.
The winner's prize was a trip to Korea,
so I traveled to this country.
HE FELL IN LOVE WITH THE CULTURE
AND MOVED HERE
Dang, this is insane.
This is the heart.
HE KNOWS KOREAN FOOD
EVEN BETTER THAN KOREANS DO
It's not gamey at all.
THE ORIGINAL KOTALIAN
WHO LOVES KOREAN FOOD
Nice.
HE'S CURRENTLY PROMOTING KOREA
AS A KIMCHI AMBASSADOR
And now, we add rice.
Oh, that's why you didn't eat rice.
-Right, that's the fourth way to eat this.
-You saved it.
Now, add the rice to the soup.
Mix it in and eat it.
-It's gukbap.
-Yes.
This is the fourth way to eat this soup.
-It's a hearty meal.
-Exactly.
TURNED INTO SEONJI HANGOVER GUKBAP
YUM
-It tastes different.
-Absolutely.
The rice adds a different texture.
I love the mix of textures.
GOBBLES IT UP
This is the perfect finish to the meal.
You introduced us
to a fantastic restaurant.
I absolutely agree.
I've had this dish countless times,
but this one's totally new.
I've never had seonji this fresh.
VERY GLAD
What makes a place your go-to spot?
Do you have any standards,
such as price or taste?
-My personal standard is…
-Okay.
-…the sign.
-I see.
It needs to have an old sign.
That means the owner
only focuses on the food.
Don't you agree?
And the second standard is
having one item on the menu.
-Just one?
-Yes, one or two dishes are okay.
Those are my standards.
-Focusing on a single dish.
-Exactly.
That's a distinctive feature
of Korean restaurants.
Regular restaurants in Italy
always have various dishes on their menu.
I was shocked when I first came here
and found out there was only one dish.
I thought that was so cool.
But there's a charm to it.
They put all their effort
into one dish, right?
-It's like true craftsmanship.
-Exactly.
Honestly, I have lots of good restaurants
I want to share with you.
-Tell us.
-In Korea?
I've learned a lot
while living here for six years.
I spend a lot of time researching.
It's too bad.
FABRI IS SAD TO HAVE SHARED
ONLY ONE RESTAURANT
If you invite me one more time…
-Oh, yes.
-Of course.
-I'll gladly introduce you to them.
-You're welcome anytime.
Let's grant Fabri's wish.
I would love that.
I hope we meet Chef Fabri again.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thanks.
WE WILL BE WAITING FOR CHEF FABRI'S CALL
YEONGHWAJEONG HANGOVER SOUP
EPISODE 11: KOREAN COMFORT FOOD
SEONJI HANGOVER SOUP
THAT CALLS FOR A DRINK