SPECIAL EPISODE 2
OF SACHEON, GYEONGSANGNAM-DO!
CONTAINS SCENES OF ALCOHOL CONSUMPTION
-Man, it's hot.
-Gosh, it's sweltering.
HEEBAB AND THE FOODIE BROTHERS
HAVE ARRIVED AT A FISH MARKET
We're right in the heart of Samcheonpo.
It smells like fish here.
There will be a lot of them over there.
We had amazing pork last week,
so I hope we get some seafood this week.
There's gizzard shad.
Summer is the season for gizzard shad.
There's a Gizzard Shad Festival in August.
-Oh, here?
-They hold it before fall comes.
-We think fall is the only time to eat it.
-Nope.
-It brings back a runaway daughter-in-law.
-Any daughter-in-law would return for it.
Runaway daughters-in-law
come home sooner in Samcheonpo.
-Hey, what's that?
-Look at that.
The 12 animals from the Chinese Zodiac.
They recreated The Tale of the Turtle
with seafood.
-The Tale of the Turtle?
-The seafood are…
Multeombeong is the name
of that cubed snailfish.
Himjangi is the eel, and Agu the monkfish.
-Jeoni the gizzard shad.
-And that's an octopus.
-I don't know who Halbae is.
-Halbae is the Dragon King.
Gamdungeo is the black sea bream.
The black sea bream.
-Kkumteulhae is the sea cucumber.
-The next one is an anchovy.
Ppollaegi is a rockfish,
and those two are filefish and stingray.
-It's like the Chinese Zodiac.
-It's like the 12 zodiac animals.
The 12 animals of the sea.
FISH MARKET
-Let's go in.
-This is Samcheonpo Yonggung Fish Market.
-They modernized the traditional market.
-Lead the way.
I heard that
it's the biggest market in the country.
-It's super clean.
-It's so long.
There's more around the corner at the end.
There's more? It's well-organized.
It's not like a maze.
-It's in a straight line.
-The sea breeze is so cool.
-The sea is right out front.
-How refreshing.
It's nice.
THE CLEAR SEA RIGHT BEFORE YOUR EYES!
FRESHLY CAUGHT SEAFOOD
-There are live fish over there.
-They've got shrimp, too.
There's sashimi.
The octopus fishing season has reopened,
so there's plenty of it now.
-Are these Manila clams?
-They're huge.
They're squirting water.
This is so cool.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Do you have some horaegi?
-What's horaegi?
-We should have some.
-They're baby octopus.
-Baby octopus?
-There.
-Are they the small?
-Can we eat them now?
We can eat them now
if they were freshly caught.
-We could just dip them in chojang.
-I agree.
I WANT SOME
-Do you want a piece that's prepped?
-Yes, we'd love that, please.
-What?
-She asked if we'd like some prepped ones.
I told her we would like to try some.
Please give me one.
How many horaegi can Heebab eat?
-I can't eat that much sashimi.
-Really?
It looks so fresh.
You might eat a lot if you like it.
You try it.
SLURP
-It tastes better than in Seoul.
-I bet.
-What do you think?
-Isn't it good?
-It's sweet.
-How many should we buy?
HOW MANY BABY OCTOPUSES CAN SHE EAT?
A hundred?
She says one hundred.
I think some of the seafood
at today's go-to spot can be found here.
-I think I see some.
-Are we going to a sashimi restaurant?
-It's still a secret.
-I guess we're having seafood today.
-This one might be on the menu.
-Are we going to a sashimi restaurant?
-Is it rare in Seoul?
-Yes.
-Then it's worth visiting.
-They have it in Tongyeong and Masan.
Let's go.
SUPER CURIOUS TO FIND OUT!
I really want some gizzard shad.
It's a three-minute walk from here.
-Really? It's nearby.
-It's around here.
WHAT WILL TODAY'S GO-TO SPOT BE LIKE?
-Is it that place?
-We're here.
-"Silbi."
-Look at the name.
What's up with the name of this place?
"Vienna Hideout Silbi."
-It's like a sign for a coffeehouse.
-The name appears to have a backstory.
Has anyone ever been
to a place like this before?
It's my first time.
I'm so curious. It's my first time, too.
-Let's head inside.
-I can't wait.
-It doesn't look like a restaurant.
-I agree.
-Is this how I should open the door?
-It's like a karaoke bar.
Hello.
EMPTY TABLES
-Hello, Auntie.
-Welcome.
JUNG HAENGJA
RUNNING THIS SPOT FOR 25 YEARS
-Where should we sit?
-Are there four of you?
-Yes, should we sit here?
-Sure.
Why did you wear a mask today?
Show us your lovely face.
Why are you wearing a mask?
I told you you're beautiful.
You look absolutely amazing.
-Absolutely amazing.
-Amazing.
-It's so unique here.
-It sure is.
It feels cozy here.
There are a total of eight tables
with more than 50 seats.
It's packed at night.
-Really? Why isn't it packed today?
-Today, I asked for a favor.
Since this is my hometown, I asked her
if she could clear out the restaurant.
I asked her to close it down for us.
I booked the whole place.
-The whole place?
-That's why the owner said yes.
-How do we order?
-We pay per person.
It's 40,000 won per person.
Then it's 160,000 won for four people.
Each person gets two bottles of alcohol.
So, we get eight bottles?
-Including the alcohol?
-Yes, it's 40,000 won per person.
-Then it's very cheap.
-That's a bargain.
That's why this place is called silbi.
It means they only charge clients
for the actual cost of the ingredients.
-That's why it's called silbi.
-Cool.
-I didn't know.
-Like the dazzi in Tongyeong.
-I've heard of that.
-They're famous.
This is common around here.
There's tongsuljip in Masan
and dazzi in Tongyeong,
then we have silbi here in Sacheon.
-That's cool.
-So, we'll have various types of dishes.
-Are they all seasonal dishes?
-That's right.
It's up to the owner to decide.
-Auntie, we'd like a set for four people.
-It's easy to order this way.
I can't wait to try their food here
after seeing all the seafood earlier.
That was a good warm-up.
I'm really looking forward to it.
FRESH SEAFOOD SOURCED DAILY
SEASONAL DELICACIES PREPARED
WITH THE OWNER'S TOUCH
WHAT DISHES WILL SHE MAKE TODAY?
-It's here.
-Already?
-I love it.
-Abalones.
BRAISED ABALONE
It's parboiled octopus.
WATER KIMCHI, BEAN SPROUTS
-Conch.
-Octopus and conch.
PARBOILED OCTOPUS AND CONCH
-Enjoy.
-Do you have any small plates?
Yes, I'll get you some.
Was her voice always this friendly?
She sounds too nice today.
-Look at that.
-That is unbelievable.
Are we allowed to be served this much?
-What is all of this?
-Here, it's gizzard shad sashimi.
It's gizzard shad!
-I wanted some.
-Gizzard shad and hamo.
Hamo and gizzard shad.
CONGER EEL AND GIZZARD SHAD SASHIMI
-Gizzard shad and hamo.
-Is this horaegi?
-Yes, and this is a horned conch.
-Horned conch and sea squirt.
This is jijim, my favorite.
KOREAN MINT CHIVE PANCAKE
-Is this steamed ray?
-Is it not seasoned spicy?
-It's cooked with soybean paste.
-I see.
It's braised with soybean paste,
so it will taste different.
-What's this?
-Those are pancakes.
-Maybe fish pancakes?
-Frozen pollock pancakes?
-Auntie, what type of pancake is this?
-It's Dory fish pancakes.
-Dory fish?
-Also known as moon fish.
DORY FISH PANCAKE
AND PAN-FRIED BATTERED MEATBALLS
14 DIFFERENT FRESH SEAFOOD DISHES
-Are these regular dishes?
-No, they're different every time.
They vary by season.
-Nothing is made from frozen ingredients.
-Where do we start?
-I don't know what to eat first.
-Since I'm a regular here, just follow me.
-Lead the way.
-Okay.
We'll start with the ones with no sauce.
-Let's start with sashimi first.
-We're starting with seafood.
-Should we order alcohol now?
-We can't eat this without it.
We don't need to order it.
Water and alcohol are self-serve.
Tell me what you want. I'll grab it.
Dujun is the youngest, so he'll get them.
-What would you like?
-Run for it.
-Some soju, please.
-Bring what you want.
-Wait, if the food is this fresh…
-We can have up to eight bottles.
-We shouldn't mix drinks.
-Let's drink them separately.
-Let's start with soju first.
-Got it.
We can mix drinks when it gets greasy.
There are dishes here
that you can't find in Seoul.
You can't easily find
conger eel sashimi or horaegi.
These are rare to find.
Help yourselves.
I'll plead for more if it's not enough.
Let's get started. Gosh, I'm excited.
-Thank you.
-Cheers.
GULPING DOWN THE REFRESHING SOJU IN ONE GO
-This is hamo.
-It's sweet.
Let's eat horaegi.
STARTING WITH BABY OCTOPUS SASHIMI
DIP CHEWY BABY OCTOPUS IN CHOJANG
SUCKING THE JUICE
CAN'T HELP BUT EXCLAIM
I love the chewing sounds.
-It sounds great.
-Are we supposed to chew the bones, too?
No, spit it out.
HEEBAB ALREADY HAD TWO BITES
WHILE THEY CHATTED
-I love the horaegi. It's fresh.
-It's sweet.
It's fattier than I thought.
A SWEET AND SMOOTH FLAVOR
Man, it's delicious.
I usually don't enjoy fishy dishes,
but this is just nice and sweet.
SUPER SWEET
What are some typical
seasonal seafoods, Chef Minseong?
-These two dishes on the table.
-The gizzard shad.
They're seasonal sashimi.
GRAB PLENTY OF FRESH CONGER EEL SASHIMI
Wow, it's so rich in flavor.
SUMMER SPECIALTY, CONGER EEL SASHIMI
CHEWY AND TENDER TEXTURE
DELICIOUSLY SAVORY THE MORE YOU CHEW
-Octopus is also a seasonal seafood.
-Octopus?
-This is the season.
-The chojang is tasty, too.
-It sure is.
-She makes it herself.
The horned conch is pleasant, too.
-Do you like it?
-It's sweet.
-Is it sweet?
-It's more savory than sweet.
-It is savory.
-I don't know how else to describe it.
WHAT DOES HE MEAN?
The ingredients' natural sweetness.
That's what I call pleasant.
When we dip food in sugar,
we think it's sweet.
-But it's sweet with umami.
-That's right!
That's it. I meant to say
it's sweet with a rich umami flavor.
My mouth is filled with the flavors
of the waters of Samcheonpo.
-Right?
-Really?
-Everything is fresh.
-I just imagined something.
Heebab can devour everything
from the waters off Samcheonpo.
ABSOLUTELY POSSIBLE
-It's incredible.
-Next is gizzard shad.
-Summer gizzard shad.
-They're rich in fat.
Gizzard shad in Seoul come
from the West Sea,
so they smell a bit earthy.
But there's no earthy scent in these ones.
SOUTH SEA GIZZARD SHAD
SLICE THE SUMMER SILVER-COLORED
GIZZARD SHAD BONE-IN
GIZZARD SHAD SASHIMI IS INCREDIBLY CHEWY
CRUNCHING
It's savory.
It's so rich with flavor.
-Right?
-Yes, it's rich in fat.
AFTER A BITE OF FATTY GIZZARD SHAD
DRINKS A GLASS OF SOJU
I love crunching the bones.
THE TEXTURE OF THE SMALL BONES
IS IRRESISTIBLE
This place knows what's up.
SATISFIED
-I'm happy.
-It's unbelievable.
Eating gizzard shad sashimi
when it's in season
"BEST IN PEAK SEASON"
-is so good.
-You can only get it here.
I never knew you could eat this
in the summer here.
COME TO SAMCHEONPO
FOR SUMMER GIZZARD SHAD
Eating this in the summer makes me feel
like I'm at a movie premiere.
Doesn't it feel like you're at a premiere?
Like we're the first ones to try it.
-Definitely.
-That's exactly it.
Heebab told us last week
that she didn't enjoy seafood, but…
-I realized I--
-Your face lit up.
She's suddenly energetic.
I usually don't like seafood,
but this is good.
-What did you say this was?
-Steamed ray.
This is the next dish to try.
-How do we eat this?
-Look, the meat rips apart easily.
-There's Korean mint in the seasoning.
-Why?
Korean mint and soybean paste
pair well together.
It's also great in soybean paste stew.
KOREAN MINT: A UNIQUE AROMATIC SCENT
USED IN THE SOUTHERN COASTAL AREA
FOR AROMATICS
ADD KOREAN MINT TO THE SOYBEAN PASTE SAUCE
FULLY STEAM THE STINGRAY
ADD THE SPECIAL KOREAN MINT
SOYBEAN PASTE SAUCE ON TOP, AND IT'S READY
Is this a Gyeongsang-do-style
soybean paste?
Yes, they don't make it like this
in Jeolla-do.
TAKING A BITE
It seems to have a milder taste this way.
-It's not that spicy.
-It's delicious.
-The Korean mint is fragrant.
-They go well together.
-There are many people…
-It's minty.
…who say cilantro smells like soap.
This smells way stronger than that.
It's almost like chemicals.
-Isn't it pungent?
-Yes.
In Gyeongsang-do, they add it to dishes
like braised spicy monkfish.
I take it out.
They add it to spicy fish stew,
pancake dishes, and everything.
It tastes bland for us if we leave it out.
-I love Korean mint.
-Me too.
Try this. It has mussels and clam meat.
WHAT WILL THE KOREAN MINT
CHIVE PANCAKE TASTE LIKE?
ADD MINCED MUSSELS, SHRIMP, AND CHIVES
ADD PLENTY OF KOREAN MINT
SHE EXPERTLY MIXES THE BATTER BY HAND
CHEWY SHRIMP, RICHLY FLAVORED MUSSELS,
AND FRAGRANT KOREAN MINT
CRISPY AND AROMATIC
KOREAN MINT CHIVE PANCAKE IS READY
I think Korean mint
is stronger than cilantro.
-Many think that.
-Is this Korean mint?
There's probably a little.
-No, they're chives.
-Auntie.
-Yes.
-Did you add Korean mint to the jijim?
-Yes, I did.
You didn't put much in, right?
-Not too much.
-I can hardly smell it.
Try it. She didn't add that much.
I can barely taste it.
-This is fine for me.
-Told you so.
-It's tasty.
-It's good.
AMAZED AT THE NUTTY TASTE
IT SEEMS LIKE HEEBAB LIKES IT
I wasn't sure if we could finish this.
-We ate a lot.
-There isn't any left.
WE FINISHED
But nobody ate the sea squirt.
-This is also nice, though.
-I'll devour the aroma of the sea.
-Sea squirt soju?
-This is the stuff.
MAKING SEA SQUIRT SOJU
FILLED WITH THE AROMA OF THE SEA
-I'll smell the sea every time.
-It doesn't look too bad. Let me try it.
-It's like drinking Oyster Shooters.
-Should I try it?
-Put it in.
-They add oysters to vodka in Europe.
Let's go!
WHAT DOES SEA SQUIRT SOJU TASTE LIKE?
-Incredible?
-Try it with the pork.
To fully embrace Samcheonpo,
you have to drink it like this
-You think so?
-It has been embraced.
-It has been?
-I'm afraid you can't drink this.
IT'S TOO STRONG FOR HEEBAB!
-You'll spit it out, so don't drink it.
-He knows me so well.
-Auntie, please give us the next dish.
-Coming.
It's shocking that there's more.
I want to try living
in Samcheonpo for a month.
Sounds like fun.
Let's say I stay here for a week.
I could eat 28 meals
if I ate four meals a day.
She's right.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Look at that.
-The black sea bream is here.
-Is it fried fish?
-What's this?
-It's rockfish.
GRILLED ROCKFISH
What's this?
-It's namakseu.
-Sorry?
It's the Gyeongsang-do dialect word
for bottom-dwelling cod.
-Bottom-dwelling cod?
-Do you call that namakseu here?
It's called namakseu when it's dried flat.
-It's fermented skate.
-You're right.
-It's hongeosamhap.
-This is so much food.
-This is unbelievable.
-There's more.
-Is that a yellow croaker?
-It's grilled gizzard shad.
The "daughter-in-law"!
GRILLED GIZZARD SHAD
There's even cutlassfish.
I want to eat these with rice.
-Squid salad?
-That's right.
-Wait, that's a lot of grilled fish.
-Let's dig in.
-I know we're filming, but I need a photo.
-Can I take one, too?
-Too much food.
-I should've taken one.
Isn't it amazing?
-Can you share the photo later?
-Of course.
DAVID LEE'S PHOTO
YOON DUJUN'S PHOTO
-More food coming.
-There's more!
There's no room left. We're out of space.
-What's this, Auntie?
-It's sea eel.
STIR-FRIED SEA EEL
-This is braised pomfret.
-Sea eel and braised pomfret.
We're in trouble.
BRAISED POMFRET
-There are so many fish dishes.
-I'll eat them all.
-These are LA ribs.
-We even have Naseong ribs.
LA RIBS AND BULGOGI
Are we getting more
because Chef Minseong is here?
-Is this normal?
-It's always like this.
-It'd be funny if she serves gimbap.
-Corn cheese?
But honestly, her voice is
a bit more gentle because we're shooting.
MINSEONG THINKS IT'S FUNNY
HER VOICE CHANGED
Honestly, it's softer.
We didn't give them
gimbap and sticky rice.
SECOND ROUND OF DISHES: TIME FOR FISH!
-This is too much.
-Gimbap?
What should we eat first?
Let's start with the grilled ones.
Among all grilled fish,
my favorite is grilled rockfish.
I see.
I was about to eat japchae.
-Get a grip!
-I was going for…
Corn cheese? Snap out of it!
There are a ton of things to eat.
Let's get rid of this plate.
We need to make room for more.
Everyone, she's helping us out.
BITING INTO GRILLED ROCKFISH
PICKING OUT THE WHITE MEAT
YUM
-Man, the rockfish is tasty.
-It's mild.
EATING WITH HER BARE HANDS
-It tastes so clean.
-Absolutely.
Grilled fish is expensive in Seoul, right?
ENJOYING PLENTY OF GRILLED FISH
THE FISH MELTS IN THEIR MOUTHS
-This is insane.
-The fish is so tender.
-Auntie, can I please get a bowl of rice?
-Sure.
Minseong, rockfish was part
of the 12 animals, right?
It had a name. What was it?
-Is it a specialty here?
-Ppollaegi.
AUNTIE IS BACK WITH A TRAY OF FOOD
-We really got gimbap!
-Here's sticky rice.
Ask for more if it's not enough.
They really served gimbap.
They have everything.
Gimbap…
They want us to eat rice
to soothe the stomach.
-That's right.
-Thank you.
This is quite a bargain
for 40,000 won per person.
Let's try the bottom-dwelling cod.
This is so good.
-Is it namakseu?
-It's called that when it's dried.
Is it called namakseu?
A BIG CHUNK
-Can I try some?
-Dig in!
I'll ask for more if it's not enough.
I love the way
Gyeongsang-do people say, "Dig in."
-Dig in.
-Time to eat.
Dig in. I'll debone it for you.
CRISPY GRILLED BOTTOM-DWELLING COD
FIRM BUT MOIST
Minseong deboning the fish
reveals his warmest side.
-I'm a warm person.
-He's an expert at this.
-I'm caring.
-He's the best.
Get a spoonful of rice.
Put it on some sticky rice.
ADD A BIG PIECE OF BOTTOM-DWELLING COD
ATOP STICKY RICE
-This is…
-There's more fish than rice.
Eat a big mouthful of it. That's it!
How scrumptious.
Isn't it good?
This is out of this world.
It's unbelievable.
-The cutlassfish is amazing.
-It sure is.
-It's fresh.
-Of course.
DUJUN IS FOCUSED
-Were they frozen?
-No, frozen ones can't be this soft.
MORE TENDER SINCE IT'S FRESH
CUTLASSFISH GRILLED IN PLENTY OF OIL
Frozen ones aren't easy to eat,
but fresh ones just melt in your mouth.
TAKE A GOLDEN BROWN PIECE
I should get you a bowl for the bones.
STRAIGHT IN!
ONE SURPRISE AFTER ANOTHER
DEBONE THE CUTLASSFISH NICELY
-Here's some. Grab it and eat it.
-Of course.
Isn't it good?
This is insane.
It's that scrumptious.
-Gosh, it's incredibly soft.
-It's so good.
A TEXTURE LIKE SOFT SPONGE CAKE
I'm obsessed with this. It's awesome.
I'll push these tiny bones
down my throat with gimbap.
Pushing it down with gimbap.
-That's a risky way to eat.
-Definitely.
DEVOURING THE GRILLED CUTLASSFISH
-I mean, this place is…
-It's terrific.
-Come here when you're having a good day.
-Yes.
This isn't the place to come with a friend
to drink when you're having a bad day.
You can't have a conversation
to resolve a problem here.
Exactly.
It's just a place to laugh
when you want to celebrate.
Your friend won't listen to you here.
NOBODY IS LISTENING
THROWING A FISH PARTY
-The cutlassfish is excellent.
-The pork reduces the smell.
Can I eat two pieces at once?
-It's not over until it's over.
-Look here.
-Is there any soup here?
-You bet there is.
OF COURSE THERE IS
-Auntie, bring us some soup, please.
-Coming.
What an amazing meal.
It's over if you say that.
IS DUJUN COMPLETELY STUFFED?
Destroy the gizzard shad!
Where does all that food go?
-Impressive.
-In my stomach.
We've had two meals with her,
and it feels
like she's eating a normal meal.
When you take one bite,
I take three or four bites.
-People don't notice that I do that.
-I really can't tell. I had no clue.
-Another dish is here.
-Is that lobster?
UNBELIEVABLE
-What's this?
-Abalone porridge.
-Abalone porridge?
-Enjoy.
I love this.
-This is amazing.
-Is that octopus?
-It's a small octopus.
-But it's so big.
It's the size of a big octopus.
-This is clam soup.
-Why are the Manila clams so big here?
-The Manila clams…
-I've never seen them this big.
Divers caught these themselves.
-So, do the divers go underwater?
-Yes.
That's why they're so meaty.
There's even lobster!
GRILLED LOBSTER
-Wow, this meal is a great deal.
-I agree.
-It's 50,000 won for a table of two.
-That's still cheap. This meal is a steal.
ROUND 3: SOOTHE YOUR STOMACH
-It's enormous.
-It's smaller than usual.
JUICY AND MEATY MANILA CLAMS
-I've never seen Manila clams this big.
-It's yummy.
They look like short-neck clams.
Try the broth. It's fantastic.
Seafood doesn't really fill me up.
Gosh, the soup is good.
The soup is rich.
FALLING IN LOVE WITH MANILA CLAM SOUP
It's helping with digestion.
Gosh, I'm loving this.
SCOOPING UP HEAPS OF ABALONE PORRIDGE
EATING NONSTOP
The porridge is great.
This is insanely good.
It's a clear version.
Today I ate the most seafood ever.
This is good for our health.
SEAFOOD REVITALIZES US
The ingredients here are all huge.
I'm really loving Samcheonpo.
It's awesome that we can eat our fill.
Yes, the people here are generous.
CAN'T HELP BUT ADMIRE THE TASTE
Eat with your spoon.
FIRM AND CHEWY SMALL OCTOPUS
-Dip it in sesame oil and salt.
-Exactly.
-It's so chewy.
-Gosh, it's still alive.
DAVID LEE SHOWS FUNNY MOVES
BEFORE SLURPING THE BABY OCTOPUS
This is also tasty.
Seriously, she eats so much.
Talk after you eat.
She'll still be eating,
and we are completely stuffed.
HER MEAL BEGINS
WHEN EVERYONE ELSE GETS FULL
Since there are so many dishes,
let's team up for the game.
I'll team up with Heebab.
Wait, I have to think
about the food pairing.
-I have one.
-You do?
-Heebab is eating it all up.
-I'm not.
What should we use for our pairing?
-What ingredients…
-Should we ask for more?
Auntie, can we get
a refill of these dishes?
Sure.
-Will you eat more?
-Yes.
-She'll eat more.
-That was just an excuse.
-We finished the Manila clam soup.
-We sure did.
-And the ribs.
-Yes, there was a lot at first!
-Absolutely.
-It's all gone. This is incredible.
THE REFILLS ARE HERE
I can start again.
Is this common at this place?
HONGEOSAMHAP, DORY FISH PANCAKE, MEATBALLS
KOREAN MINT CHIVE PANCAKE
Are there customers
who eat all of these various dishes?
There aren't many people
who finish all of this.
I think you're eating a lot.
-They don't ask for more, right?
-They do once in a while.
Some people ask for more.
MORE MANILA CLAM SOUP
Why don't we try making the food pairing?
Heebab, let's quickly--
We need squid salad, gimbap,
and seasoned bean sprout.
-Hold on.
-Will you mix them?
-Impressive.
-A dessert for Koreans.
Add the gimbap to a bowl with sesame oil.
That's against the rules.
That can never fail.
-It's yummy if we cut it up.
-You're good at this.
Should I cut up more?
-That's good. We need texture.
-Is this it?
NOW, IT'S HEEBAB'S TURN
This was Heebab's idea.
-This seasoning was so delicious.
-Right.
-It's like squid salad bibimbap.
-It will be sweet and tangy.
Sweet and tangy.
-There.
-Aren't you cutting it?
-Should we cut it up?
-Sure, let's do that.
-You're helping them.
-Why'd I say that?
-Why are you helping them?
-I shouldn't have given them that tip.
-It's like raw fish bibimbap.
-Everyone, watch.
Mix it up.
This will be delicious.
-I'll try it.
-Show them how it looks.
It's amazing. I mean it.
It's so good.
ANXIOUS
Man, this is…
-We have to beat them.
-This is a classic flavor.
-The seasoning did it all.
-We have to win.
THE SQUID SALAD SEASONING IS KEY
-What are you looking for?
-Do you have a rolling mat?
Are you making gimbap?
Let's roll some gimbap.
MINSEONG HAS BROUGHT
A ROLLING MAT AND PERILLA LEAVES
Are you making futomaki?
He's using his main skills.
-It's not that.
-He's making a Japanese dish.
I'm curious.
Using that instead of seaweed?
HE IS USING THE ENTIRE JIJIM
-This is against the rules.
-I'll wrap it up with this.
What's wrong?
I'll do my best to catch the rabbits.
These two rabbits are trying to win.
He's adding the perilla leaves.
You're adding japchae?
This is full of carbs.
It's not good for the owner's health.
JAPCHAE INSTEAD OF RICE
-Wow, it looks good though.
-Looks great.
Add sesame oil and salt.
It's seasoned well.
Hold on, Minseong!
It might get in the way while chewing.
It's tender, so it's probably okay.
TESTING THE TEXTURE
I told you it's all right.
It needs some chewiness.
It needs texture.
That's it.
IN SYNC WITH GIMBAP
-Please.
-Wow, he's skilled.
It looks amazing.
It's his specialty.
He's thrilled.
TIME TO SLICE IT
We just need one good piece.
Her mouth might burst.
GIGANTIC
It's kind of like
an inside-out version of stuffed squid.
-It looks nice.
-But Auntie's the one eating it.
It's a bit too big.
IT'S READY
TRYING TO ADD THE OTHER PIECES
No, take it out.
Give it to me.
She's helpful.
THE REST IS FOR HEEBAB
-Silbi gimbap.
-Ours is Silbi-bimbap.
-Silbi-bimbap.
-Right.
SILBI-BIMBAP VS SILBI GIMBAP
Auntie, can you be the judge
for our contest?
It's made from today's ingredients,
so choose the pairing that tastes best.
The losing team will wash the dishes
and clean up afterward.
-Thank you for judging.
-I'll be fair and square.
TRYING THE SILBI-BIMBAP FIRST
How is it?
WILL SHE LIKE IT?
-It's good.
-That's great.
It's nutty.
And the fact that you made bibimbap
with all our various dishes
makes it very special.
-She likes it.
-She enjoyed it, Chef Minseong.
It's the best.
But she only ate a tiny amount.
Do you think she can eat this in one bite?
-I can't.
-She can't.
SULLEN
Cut it in half and try it.
You can eat that in one bite. Try it!
GETTING READY
TAKES A SMALL BITE
-Wait, she didn't finish.
-It was too big.
THEY LOWER THEIR HEADS IN UNISON
Wait, you can't cry, Minseong.
Which food pairing
would you recommend to a customer?
I like this way better.
SHE CHOSE THE SILBI-BIMBAP
The gimbap was fine, but this was better.
HEEBAB AND DUJUN WIN!
I told you it was too big.
If only her mouth were bigger.
MEANWHILE, HEEBAB TRIES THE DISHES
Auntie has betrayed me.
How many dishes did we have in total?
We can't count them. There are too many.
Auntie, how many dishes did we eat?
Today, we served 41 dishes,
including the refills.
-Forty-one?
-What?
-I told you.
-Wow, he was right.
-This was amazing.
-I'm stuffed!
That was a great meal.
THEY HAD A TOTAL OF 41 DISHES
What does this go-to spot mean to you,
Chef Minseong?
First of all,
I'm confident in bringing anyone here.
-Not everyone will like the food I like.
-That's true.
But this place
will never disappoint anyone.
It's a place
where people can truly enjoy the food.
It's a place where people say,
"I'm absolutely stuffed."
You're full, but you keep eating.
-Incredible.
-I feel that.
-I'm happy.
-I had a great meal.
-Was it good?
-Yes, it was awesome.
It's a practical utopia.
I'm sorry to even say
the word "practical."
-What a bargain.
-A hearty meal.
I agree.
I haven't been somewhere like this ever.
How was it, Heebab? Are you stuffed?
-I'm pleasantly full now.
-Really?
Thank you for the meal.
HEEBAB WON'T STOP EATING
SHE'S CALM AMID THE CHAOS
I'm so happy.
HEEBAB'S HAPPY MUKBANG IS NOT OVER
Gosh, I told you the bite was too big.
It's because she can't eat chili pepper.
Minseong, when was the last time
you washed dishes?
It's been a while. I haven't done it
since I opened my own restaurant.
Well done.
DONE IN A FLASH
Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose.
Let's hit the slate.
-Thank you.
-Great job.