CREATOR OF FLAVORS
AND THE MAESTRO
OF THE KITCHEN IS
THE CHEF
BUT WHERE DO THE CHEFS GO
WHEN THEY EAT OUT?!
OUT OF SOUTH KOREA'S 560,000 EATERIES
WHAT DO THE CHEFS EAT?
TO VISIT THE REAL GO-TO EATERIES OF CHEFS
HERE COME THE FIVE FOODIE BROTHERS
THE DRAGON KING OF YEOUIDO
THE ELDEST CHEF KIM MINSEONG
"THE INGREDIENTS DECIDE
THE FLAVOR OF THE DISH"
That is salted seafood.
It's the muscle that hold the…
IMPARTING ALL KINDS OF FOODIE KNOWLEDGE
You can't say that stuff
when we're eating.
You need to know what you're eating,
Self-Made Chef.
MEAT MASTER
THE SECOND CHEF DAVID LEE
It's chicken gizzard.
A SWEET GUY WHO PUTS OTHERS FIRST
It's everywhere.
THE FATHER FIGURE OF CHEFS
It tastes like
hot spicy fish soup. Try it.
-It's spicy but light.
-It's got a kick.
SELF-MADE CHEF
THE THIRD CHEF LIM TAEHOON
I have a nickname for Minseong now.
The Omnivore Chef.
You don't need
to make it obvious you're old.
Turn the cameras away.
I was going to keep this recipe to myself.
If I have perilla leaves,
I grill them here.
COOKING MANIAC
THE YOUNGEST CHEF YOON NAMNO
If I had a straw this big,
I'd just slurp it like this.
To fully enjoy the food,
make sure to get a good mouthful.
Can I get a bit of soy sauce
in that plate?
FROM SPECIAL SAUCES
It thickens up.
It's like a Korean mojito.
TO EVEN COCKTAILS
You've lost too much weight.
ACTOR FROM LET'S EAT
THE FOURTH YOON DUJUN
I have a small appetite.
DEVELOPS AN APPETITE FOR FOOD
This is insane.
It's so good I can't stop eating.
How do you eat it?
Could you share some flavor pairings?
Like tapioca pearls in bubble tea,
you can't stop eating them.
WHICH CHEF'S GO-TO WILL IT BE?
-Let's go find a world-class auntie.
-Okay.
She's like my secret sister.
They're the best teppanyaki chef.
Nobody I've taken here
has ever been disappointed.
It's been over 30 years.
As a child, I went with my mom.
-There's always a line.
-To eat here?
Are we almost there?
Hello.
-Is it here?
-The vibe here is amazing.
It's this place.
COMING RIGHT UP
CHEF'S GO-TO
DONGDAEMUN-GU, SEOUL
THE FOODIE BROTHERS VISITING
GYEONGDONG MARKET ARE?
THE SECOND: DAVID LEE
THE FOURTH: YOON DUJUN
THE YOUNGEST: YOON NAMNO
THE THREE FOODIE BROTHERS HEAD
TO THE FIRST CHEF'S GO-TO PLACE
-We're here at Gyeongdong Market.
-We are.
We're going to meet today's guest chef.
Which of you invited them?
It was me.
I was thinking,
if we're introducing
chefs' favorite eateries,
we might as well start
with our favorite auntie.
Is she at Gyeongdong Market?
Yes, she's the Gyeongdong Auntie.
-Isn't she a world-class auntie?
-Are we making it
-too obvious?
-I think I know.
-Of course.
-Yes.
GYEONGDONG MARKET'S WORLD-CLASS AUNTIE
WHO COULD SHE BE?
If you don't know her,
you deserve a nuggie.
-Let's go see.
-Everyone knows her.
We should look around
Gyeongdong Market too.
Let's go.
LET'S GO MEET AUNTIE
I haven't been to a market in ages.
It feels so nostalgic
to come to a market again.
They have a lot of pig trotters here.
It's fried on the spot.
FROM CRISPY FRIED DISHES
Markets are all about
the sweet pancake, aren't they?
TO SWEET PANCAKE
A lot of young people
come to markets these days.
-You're right.
-Right.
Young students, too.
-But markets…
-Gyeongdong Market,
Gwangjang Market, Mangwon Market.
-They're date spots now.
-True.
Wow, that looks dangerous.
GULP
FRIED CHICKEN THAT LOOKS DANGEROUSLY GOOD
GOLDEN AND CRISPY
This is great.
Do you hear that?
-Looks delicious.
-This sound.
-Is it raining?
-It sounds amazing.
That frying smell is amazing.
THE SOUND ALONE IS COMFORTING
The large portion is 18,000 won.
-It's a bargain.
-Is that the large?
The portions are huge.
It's enough for one person.
MARKET FRIED CHICKEN LOOKS INSANELY GOOD
By the way, our guest chef…
-Isn't she waiting in the rain?
-She'll be waiting for us.
Let's eat as we go, right from the bag.
-Shall we?
-Yes.
ENDED UP ORDERING A LARGE FRIED CHICKEN
Ma'am, can I pay with this?
A WHOLE CHICKEN GOES INTO THE POT
Local chicken joints used to fry them up
like this back in the day.
WITH SWEET POTATOES
Looks delicious.
-What's that? Chicken gizzards?
-Yes.
-They fry them with chili peppers?
-How unique.
Rice cakes, too.
Five ingredients.
It looks so good.
A GENEROUS MARKET PORTION
You just know it's going to be good.
That oily aroma is driving me crazy.
I really missed that paper packaging.
The brown bag, right?
I love how they roll it down like that.
ROLL THE BAG DOWN
I'm sold on that vibe alone.
PREVENT IT FROM GETTING SOGGY
Try it.
It smells amazing.
The chili pepper smells so inviting.
Wow, you're right.
A BAG FULL OF DELICIOUS AROMA
WITH A HINT OF CHILI PEPPER
THE YOUNGEST GETS THE FIRST BITE
That flavor is so nostalgic.
BLOW TO COOL IT DOWN
It's chicken gizzard.
-It's fine.
-My gizzard!
NOD OF SATISFACTION
WING, I CHOOSE YOU
It's way too hot.
I heard someone roar.
Hot food like this
tastes even better when it burns you.
You have to burn the roof of your mouth.
It needs to scorch your throat.
It's delicious.
THE ROOF OF HIS MOUTH IS GETTING BURNED
-It's so good.
-It's really good.
Shall we keep going?
They'll be waiting for us.
How was the fried chicken?
-I approve.
It's so good.
WHERE IS OUR WORLD-CLASS AUNTIE?
Where is it?
This way. If we go here…
-It's in the basement?
-Yes.
THE BASEMENT OF GYEONGDONG MARKET?
At this point, it really is…
so obvious.
This place was always popular, right?
-Yes.
-Always had a line.
It's always been famous.
WHO IS OUR FIRST GUEST CHEF
WAITING IN THE BASEMENT MARKET?
Chop-chop, get a move on. Honestly.
Sis!
Because of you, I can't get off--
-Hello.
-…welcome.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Welcome. Oh my, hello.
Oh my, hello.
TODAY'S GUEST AT LAST
THE K-AUNTIE CHEF
FAMOUS FOR HER GYEONGDONG MARKET NOODLES
WHO ALSO RUNS A KOREAN CUISINE OMAKASE
AND HAS BEEN COOKING KOREAN FOOD FOREVER
WORLD-CLASS AUNTIE
KIM MIRYEONG
You kept me from clocking out.
-Sorry.
-You should've hustled.
-We got sidetracked by fried chicken.
-On our way here.
Why did you eat that before coming here?
We were told we couldn't just pass by.
Honestly.
What do we do? Do we sit down?
Sit down for what? I need to get off work.
Where are we going?
Can you give us a hint?
What hint? Just follow me.
You came here to visit
my favorite place, didn't you?
-Yes, we did.
-We did.
-That's correct.
-Then, come.
Just trust me.
-I'll…
-She sounds confident.
This place must be really good.
Come on, let's go.
WHERE IS CHEF KIM MIRYEONG'S GO-TO?
I have walked this path
since I was in middle school.
I'd be wearing my backpack
and would eat there when I was hungry.
After I became an adult,
I would go there to drink soju.
Then,
-this is Auntie's go-to place.
-Yes.
Auntie's go-to place.
-A real auntie's place.
-Yes.
Auntie Omakase's go-to place.
After I close up for the day,
I walk this way
and stop by on my way home.
It's your regular hangout.
Yes, exactly.
It really is my regular hangout.
And most importantly,
I went every day back then,
and I still do now.
-You know each other's history.
-Of course.
And so,
I always walk this route, and…
Hello.
-Is it here? Hello.
-Here?
-The vibe here is insane.
-Nice, right?
This place is a vibe.
AUNTIE'S GO-TO IS?
I love outdoor dining.
Should we sit here like this?
What really struck me was that
there's no sign.
IN A GYEONGDONG MARKET ALLEY WITH NO SIGN
A HAVEN FOR HUNGRY PASSERSBY
How many years has it been?
You moved in after Gyeongdong Market
first opened, right?
-Of course.
-So, 40 to 50 years.
Exactly.
A SPOT WITH 50 YEARS OF HISTORY
HOW LONG HAS OUR GUEST CHEF
BEEN A REGULAR?
I ate here back when I was a student,
when I was on dates,
after I got married and had children.
-Even now.
She came with her belly this big.
I'd come here and quickly eat
with my husband before returning home.
Because my in-laws are home.
If you go home too late,
-they won't like that.
-Exactly.
We never got to sit down
and enjoy a drink together,
but we were always welcomed here.
It was like your safe haven.
MY GO-TO, MY SAFE HAVEN
Then, did you see
all the boyfriends she dated?
I only had one boyfriend.
Can we each get a bottle of beer and soju?
Look at her changing the subject.
CHEF KIM MIRYEONG'S FIRST ORDER
SOMAEK, SOJU AND BEER
SOMAEK TO COOL YOU DOWN
That's going to taste so good.
After I get off work,
especially in summer,
nothing beats having a glass of this.
It's like being rewarded
for your hard work.
-First, on an empty stomach.
-Yes, exactly.
Come in.
COME FILL MY EMPTY STOMACH
FIRST DRINK AT THE CHEF'S GO-TO
I'm very picky about somaek.
This is the most perfect ratio
of beer and soju I've had this year.
First of all,
the soju and beer came from the freezer.
AN ICE-COLD DRINK TO BLOW YOUR MIND
She always gives me the coldest ones,
whether it's winter or summer.
WHAT'S AFTER THE GLASS OF SOMAEK?
I sell noodles, but what else do I serve?
-Omakase.
-That's right.
We'll be having omakase here too.
KIM MIRYEONG'S RECOMMENDATION
5-COURSE OMAKASE
-A plate of my usual sundae, please.
-Okay.
PLUMP SUNDAE, KOREAN BLOOD SAUSAGE
RICH PORK LIVER
TENDER PORK LUNG
CHEWY PORK MAWS
SEOUL-STYLE SALT
AND A SPRINKLE OF NUTTY SESAME SEEDS
OMAKASE SECOND DISH
ASSORTED SUNDAE WITH SESAME SEEDS
-Have a taste.
-You first, David.
Please, go ahead.
Let's eat.
DIP THE SAVORY SUNDAE IN SESAME SALT
Delicious.
I've been craving this kind of sundae.
-Real market stall sundae.
-Exactly.
THE SECOND STARTS WITH A PIECE OF LIVER
It's really fresh.
It doesn't smell at all.
THE YOUNGEST CHECKS THE SMELL FIRST
With sundae, you can tell right away
if it is fresh,
when you try the liver first.
-The liver?
-Yes.
TO CHECK IF THE SUNDAE IS FRESH,
CHECK THE LIVER FIRST
I always order this first
because I miss meals while working
and I'm really hungry
by the time I get here.
So I order what can be served quickly.
All she has to do is cut them.
So I get the sundae first.
The soup comes out right away.
TO SATISFY YOUR POST-WORK APPETITE
THE ASSORTED SUNDAE
IS SERVED IN AN INSTANT
Shall we try the next dish?
On to the next dish.
You've never tried lung slices
and pork skin before, have you?
-Lung?
-Have you tried it?
-Only in pork and rice soup.
-The one in pork and rice soup
-are pork lungs. This is beef.
-Beef.
-Beef?
-This is beef lung.
PORK LUNG
MAY HAVE A STRONG SMELL OF PORK
BUT HAS A SOFT AND TENDER TEXTURE
BEEF LUNG
HAS A CHEWY TEXTURE AND NUTTY FLAVOR
People tend to mix them up.
This is beef lung, not pork lung.
PEOPLE ENJOY IT AS A DELICACY
AFTER STIR-FRYING THE BEEF LUNG WITH SAUCE
Then come the perilla leaves.
That's how it's done,
with garlic and chili flakes.
All of them look so good.
She adds in the pork skin
as a special treat for regulars.
Pork skin and beef lung.
JIGGLE
OMAKASE THIRD DISH
STIR-FRIED BEEF LUNG WITH PORK SKIN
OMAKASE
1. PRE-MEAL SOMAEK
2. ASSORTED SUNDAE
3. STIR-FRIED BEEF LUNG WITH PORK SKIN
…it becomes tough.
CAN'T HELP BUT SQUEAL
It melts away.
THE YOUNGEST TAKES A BIG BITE
OF BEEF LUNG AND PORK SKIN
COVERED IN SAUCE
-Miryeong.
-Just look at him.
-Look at him.
-Namno.
What? Do I have…
It's all over your face.
This sauce looks spicy and strong.
But it's not at all.
Not at all.
In fact, it has that kick,
but it's still delicate.
-It tastes like hot spicy fish soup.
-You're right.
-It's spicy but light.
-It's got a kick.
SPICY YET LIGHT STIR-FRIED BEEF LUNG
And the pork skin.
-It's so big and thick.
-But it's not tough at all.
-Yes, it's soft.
-It's soft, right?
SOFT AND TENDER PORK SKIN
We need to put these away and go for soju.
CHEF KIM MIRYEONG PAIRS
THE DRINK TO THE DISH
I should really blow off some steam today.
STIR-FRIED BEEF LUNG PAIRED WITH SOJU
This is where it really starts.
Let's drink a glass of soju.
-Cheers.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
-It feels great to be with you all today.
It's nice out today with the soft drizzle.
The rain makes it perfect.
-Yes.
-It really does.
PERFECT RAINY NIGHT FOR A DRINK
A GLASS OF SOJU TO THE SOUND OF RAIN
This is new for you, isn't it, Dujun?
Yes, a real old-school place like this.
It's your first time, right?
I'm glad to see you're happy.
THE FOODIE BROTHERS ENJOY NOSTALGIC DISHES
AT AUNTIE'S FAVORITE SPOT
Auntie,
can I have some perilla leaves?
Wrap this in the leaves. It's delicious.
You know this, right?
You shouldn't discard this bit.
-Okay.
-I eat that bit.
This is where most of the nutrients are.
-The scent is strongest there, too.
-Exactly.
This show is really great.
I get all the pro tips.
I WANT A PERILLA LEAF WRAP TOO
Hold on. I'll make you one.
A BIG SLICE OF BEEF LUNG
THE PERFECT SIZE FOR NAMNO'S MOUTH
I see you two have gotten really close
since I last saw you.
-We were always close.
-Always.
Still, isn't feeding each other
a bit too much?
PONDERING
WHAT DO I DO?
It's for you.
-It's too big.
-What?
She rejected it.
FIRM REFUSAL
-It's too big.
-What?
She rejected it.
But they're all big.
"It's too big." You're so stern.
THE REJECTED WRAP GOES INTO MY MOUTH
No need to be so serious.
SORRY, DAVID LEE
"It's too big."
-It's good.
-Is it good?
The thin noodles…
-What are they for?
-For the banquet noodles.
-Yes, please.
-No, not yet.
We need to have umutgasari first.
We need to eat umutgasari,
then the banquet noodles.
What exactly is umutgasari?
UMUTGASARI: TYPE OF SEAWEED RICH IN FIBER
AND LOW IN CALORIES
-That's all umutgasari.
-Like konjac noodles?
A little like that.
Is this seasoned with soy sauce?
With a sweet and tangy soy sauce.
With seaweed flakes.
ADD SAVORY SEAWEED AND CHILI FLAKES
FINISH OFF WITH FRESH CUCUMBER
AND A SPRINKLE OF SESAME SEEDS
The color is like a premium champagne.
OMAKASE
4. UMUTGASARI
To fully enjoy the food,
make sure to get a good mouthful.
That's true.
ONE BIG MOUTHFUL
Just slurp it?
DUJUN FOLLOWS SUIT AND SLURPS
-It's all washing down nicely.
-It's delicious, right?
Some people might not like this texture,
but the cucumber and soy sauce is…
-It's sweet and tangy.
-Sweet and tangy.
FRESH CUCUMBER WITH A SWEET-AND-TANGY
SOY SAUCE FOR THAT LITTLE KICK
If I had a straw this big,
I'd just slurp it like this.
Like tapioca pearls in bubble tea.
-Yes, right.
-Exactly.
You can't stop eating it.
Personally, I would order the umutgasari
with the stir-fried beef lung together.
Yes, that'd be good.
-When it gets spicy, this cools it down.
-Yes, true.
A COMBINATION THAT BALANCES THE SPICINESS
DEVOURING THE ENTIRE BOWL
While the nutty flavor is still there,
you wash it down with soju.
Chef Yoon likes
to take a bite and then drink it down.
-It's a must for me.
-Really?
What about you? I'm just…
I'm the same.
Really? I'm the type to drink first,
then eat some food.
EMPTY GLASS
NAMNO IS WORRIED ABOUT DUJUN
I should really blow off some steam today.
Do you have another glass?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Use this one. I'm not much of a drinker.
I'll take sips from this.
Just say cheers. No need to drink.
-You can just toast.
-Okay.
-Just say cheers. Don't drink.
-Got it.
Dujun.
You're not great with alcohol,
so I'll use what's here
to make a Korean mojito.
A Korean mojito?
There's usually mint in mojitos.
-But this is good, too.
-That's true.
And these are field-grown,
-so the scent is amazing.
-True. They in season.
It's great going to places with experts.
INTO THE GLASS IT GOES
ADD A LITTLE SOJU AND MASH IT
Are you juicing it?
He's crushing it to bring out the aroma.
THE RATIO OF ALCOHOL IS
1 PART SOJU
2 PARTS LEMON-LIME SODA
MIX IT WELL AND IT'S DONE
If you add a slice of lemon,
-it'd be perfect.
-Exactly.
It's a shame.
But this should be okay.
What an honor, truly.
HOW IS THE KOREAN MOJITO?
-The aroma is…
-Where's mine?
How is it? Is it good?
Would you like a sip?
It's really good.
You only need lemon-lime soda.
The perilla leaf aroma is so strong.
But it does feel like mint.
-I'm telling you.
-It has that minty aroma.
-Exactly two to one.
-Two to one?
Yes, two parts soda.
-One part soju.
-It's good.
Then ice.
AUNTIE IS CURIOUS
Is it good?
No, it's all right.
CURIOSITY GOT THE BETTER OF HER
-Just a little.
-You were cooking up something?
That's enough.
-He was.
-I was.
You were?
I should drink it like this too.
It's good.
It's delicious. No, really.
My, it's good.
-Isn't he brilliant?
-He sure is.
THAT'S RIGHT, I'M MR. BRILLIANT
Now, we've eaten quite a bit.
We always finish with banquet noodles.
-Of course.
-Banquet noodles?
BLANCH THE COOKED NOODLES
INSIDE THE ANCHOVY BROTH
FINISH BY ADDING THE RICH BROTH
THAT HAS BEEN SIMMERING ALL DAY
OMAKASE
5. BANQUET NOODLES
Here, the kimchi.
-You have to add this on top…
-It's a must.
…to make the banquet noodles come alive.
ONE SLURP OF NOODLES
This is what you call real anchovy broth.
Usually, people use anchovy flavoring.
THE RICH BROTH HAS HIM
SQUEALING WITH DELIGHT
It's so delicious.
I think I get why
-the noodles come at the end.
-Right?
It settles everything.
FINISH IT OFF WITH NOODLES
WITH SPICY MINCED SEASONING
We started with sundae.
It was rich in taste,
but still mild
because it wasn't marinated.
-We only had salt.
-Exactly. That's how you should start.
The second dish was beef lung,
which was spicy in flavor.
Next came umutgasari,
which cleansed the palate.
Lastly, the noodles.
It wraps everything up
and settles the stomach.
You can carry the warmth home.
A SIMPLE YET SPECIAL
BOWL OF BANQUET NOODLES
A PLACE TO ENJOY OMAKASE MADE WITH WARMTH
The reason I love coming here
isn't just the delicious food,
but for the energy and love.
What I mean is, in these harsh times,
she's stayed right here,
serving food with the same warmth.
It must be so comforting.
I run a restaurant myself.
But I come here and think I should serve
customers with the same warmth tomorrow.
That's the resolve this place gives me.
You know, your regular spot
is like a friend.
That's so true.
After I hit 40,
I scanned my contacts list,
looking to see who I could meet up with.
Friends I can just casually
call for a drink
are few enough to count on one hand.
Of those friends, my closest one fell ill
and passed on.
Oh dear.
So when I saw you here today,
with your very own auntie…
AN AUNTIE I CAN ALWAYS VISIT
-She really is my very own auntie.
-…I felt
a little envious that you have this joy.
It must be really comforting.
MY AUNTIE'S PLACE IS LIKE AN OLD FRIEND
I CAN SEE THEM WHENEVER I WANT
I sell noodles too, but I still come here
to eat banquet noodles
because I love her warmth.
It's my way of wrapping up my day.
A PLACE THAT WRAPS UP MY DAY
I don't understand why someone who sells
noodles eats so much noodles here.
But she always finishes
with banquet noodles.
When I look at those boiled,
slightly soggy noodles,
I think, "They had a hard day, too."
That's how I want to wrap up my day.
A BOWL OF SOGGY NOODLES THAT MIRROR MY DAY
I feel tears coming on.
They're old memories.
CHOKING UP FROM OLD MEMORIES
I SPENT MY YOUTH RUNNING
A RESTAURANT WITH MY HUSBAND
THE AUNTIE WHO ALWAYS COMFORTED MY WEARY
HEART AS I JUGGLED PARENTING AND WORK
AND AUNTIE'S BANQUET NOODLES
THAT SO CLOSELY RESEMBLES WHO I AM
It'd be great if you could
share some flavor pairings?
-Oh, flavor pairings?
-How to really enjoy the dishes here.
-Just what's here?
-Yes.
Using the dishes here.
FLAVOR PAIRING USING THESE DISHES?
-Namno versus David.
-And Miryeong is the judge?
Yes. The loser has to do a dare.
COOKING MANIAC YOON NAMNO
VS. MEAT MASTER DAVID LEE
Then I'll be judge. Maybe together?
-Be strict.
-Okay.
Then what will the dare be?
-Something hardcore.
-Hardcore?
You like it wild.
What would be good?
A dance challenge?
THE LOSER WILL FILM AN ADORABLE DARE VIDEO
Do you both have social media accounts?
Yes, you have to upload it there.
-The starter often faces the end.
-Really?
THE LOSER WILL POST
ON THEIR SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT
But for me,
these ingredients aren't enough.
I'll go out and buy something.
Buy what?
-He's up to something. Go on, then.
-He does.
I've been going around TV shows
doing flavor pairings.
-The Man of flavor.
-His know-how of pairing.
If you keep combining things
on TV like that,
you might become
a master of matching games.
WHAT WILL HE BUY?
NOT LONG AFTER
Onion, chili pepper, garlic.
Those are usually the basics.
-He's back.
-What did you get?
-What did you buy?
-That was quick.
A color that suits you well.
Which color is that?
A COLOR THAT SUITS CHEF KIM MIRYEONG?
-Which color is that?
-Red cap.
Sesame oil!
-I love it.
-Sesame oil.
Do you have any soy sauce?
Is this too much?
No, it's good.
MIX EQUAL PARTS SOY SAUCE AND SESAME OIL
ADD MINCED GARLIC,
SESAME SEEDS, AND CHILI FLAKES
If you stir like this,
oil doesn't normally mix with liquid.
No, it doesn't.
But if you do this,
-they call it soy-sesame sauce.
-Yes.
It thickens up.
SOY-SESAME SAUCE
EQUAL PARTS SOY SAUCE AND SESAME OIL
Hold on, and then.
-Is it good?
-It even goes well with soju.
Really?
It'll be good with sundae.
WILL IT GO WELL WITH SUNDAE?
ONE BITE OF THE SUNDAE DIPPED IN SAUCE
WILL LEAVE YOU SQUEALING WITH DELIGHT
Wow, it's delicious.
This is like the perfect bite.
It's really good.
THE SECOND HAS A TASTE TOO
It's good.
I don't think I can win against this.
I think I won.
-Game over already.
-What will you do?
Come up with something.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Chef David Lee,
were you cooking up something?
-Yes.
-He was.
I was.
-I was.
You were?
Could you blanch some noodles
and put them…
-In a bowl, please.
-In a bowl.
Don't you need some kind of sauce?
This sauce is here, the one you made.
The sauce inside this dish.
-You want that sauce?
-Yes, with cucumber,
some noodles, and this sauce.
ADD GREEN ONION, SEAWEED FLAKES, CUCUMBER
TO THE BLANCHED NOODLES
THEN ADD SOME SWEET AND TANGY SOY SAUCE
Perilla gives it that kick.
ADD PERILLA LEAVES AND SAUCE
It's amazing how you can just
build new flavors in your head.
I'm jealous.
HOW ARE THE BEEF LUNG NOODLES
DAVID COOKED UP?
-Auntie, this is good.
-Is it okay?
WOW! THIS IS LEGIT
It's like eating warm spicy mixed noodles.
The perilla aroma really comes through.
Because it's been cooked.
The aroma has been fully released.
It's spicy but that hint
of vinegar comes through,
so it reminds me of spicy octopus noodles.
Now, please make your pick.
-Shall I pick?
-Who's the winner out of our two chefs?
THE YOUNGEST YOON NAMNO'S
Red cap.
Sesame oil!
-I love it.
-Sesame oil.
SOY-SESAME SAUCE MADE
WITH OIL FROM THE MARKET
OR THE SECOND DAVID LEE'S
Perilla gives it that kick.
SPICY MIXED NOODLES
WITH AROMATIC PERILLA LEAVES
Out of our two chefs?
-One must do a dare.
-To be honest, earlier,
when he asked for noodles,
I made up my mind.
The reason being,
chefs never stop at the sauce.
-Miryeong.
-But it's true.
-I'm right, aren't I?
Stop at soju? I even made a mojito.
-No, stop at the sauce.
-Exactly.
You said we can't stop at the sauce.
-But I also made a drink.
-No, this drink
-was an accompaniment.
-Right.
You need to make a complete dish,
but with Chef David Lee…
-His was a complete dish?
-Yes.
I didn't back down.
So you can wrap things up today,
while we go home.
THE YOUNGEST YOON NAMNO LOSES
-Okay. I admit defeat.
-Today,
just like this gentle breeze,
I revisited old memories
and could savor the joy of this moment,
so it was really nice. Wasn't it?
-It was really nice and made me happy.
-Be honest.
If I get a girlfriend,
I want the first date
-to be here.
-I'll make you a reservation.
Here? I don't think
she'll take reservations.
THE FIRST CHEF'S GO-TO
WAS FULL OF WARM MEMORIES
EPISODE 1
OMAKASE AT AUNTIE'S REAL GO-TO PLACE
Why are you taking the filming
so seriously?
-I always take work seriously.
-It's just a dare video.
Let's start.
AVRIL LAVIGNE- HELLO KITTY
APOLOGIES, THERE IS NO MUSIC
DUE TO COPYRIGHT RESTRICTIONS
YOU CAN CHECK OUT THE FULL VIDEO
ON CHEF YOON NAMNO'S SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT
Look at you go!
Do it properly!