- Gosh, it's spring. - Seriously.
- Spring is here indeed. - Yes.
Flowers are especially beautiful.
This week is the peak.
So we're in Guri.
I filmed one of my shows yesterday.
I saw cherry blossoms at the Han River.
- Seokchon... - It was super crowded.
- Couples are holding hands... - It's crazy.
- A lot of couples were on a date. - Right.
- What about you? - That's why I didn't go there.
(Avoiding cherry blossoms)
Anyway, spring is here.
- We started our season last fall. - Right.
- How... - It's spring now.
Today is the last episode of this season.
- Right. - Gosh, time flew by.
Can't we just keep filming?
Apparently, you have a busy schedule.
- Why... - Your agency...
(Attorney Shin Yi Rang is busy.)
My gosh.
They said you couldn't keep filming because you had to film a drama.
- Seriously. - I need to make a living too.
Right. You should.
Our staff can use this time as a little break.
They need to come up with new games too.
- You know? - Right. They must invent new games.
So this is the last episode of our current season.
I wonder who our Whenever Friends are today.
I was sort of informed about today's Whenever Friends.
For our last episode... How should I put it?
We need...
- mega stars to join our show. - Mega stars?
- So you heard? - But a mid-star will join us.
(A mid-star?)
- Come on. - Really?
He's not a mega star.
- He's not? - A mid-star is joining us.
Really?
Gosh, the cherry blossoms are so beautiful.
I guess I can skip the cherry blossom outing this year.
- We can only see them now. - Right.
Hello.
(Two Whenever Friends walk alongside the cherry blossoms.)
By the way, the cherry blossoms are super pretty.
- I can see him from here. - My gosh. Look.
- Who's that next to him? - I can spot him right away.
- Who's that? - I didn't hear about a mega star.
- I only heard about a mid-star. - Wait.
- Is that Bo Young? - Who's that?
(Giggling)
- Hello, Jae Seok. - Is that Bo Young?
- Gosh, is that you, Bo Young? - Hello.
- A mega star is here. - A mega star is here.
We've got a mega star and a mid-star.
What? What did you say?
- A mid-star? - My gosh.
- Bo Young is a mega star. - Bo Young.
- It's been so long! - Bo Young.
- Kwang Soo. - My gosh.
- Here's our mega star. - Hello.
- Our mega star is here. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
What's that around your neck, Bo Young?
- Do you have a sore throat? - What?
- I didn't want to catch a cold. - You...
- For the fine dust? - A sore throat? Not to get sick?
- I'm protecting my neck. - A mega star is here.
- Hello. - Okay.
No one is welcoming him.
- Come on. - You know what?
- Let's welcome him. - You should say hello back. Why...
Why didn't you know he was coming? You're at the same agency.
Why didn't you know? I knew that he was coming.
- I didn't know. - How did you know?
- I knew you were coming. - How did he know?
They told me not to tell you.
Someone told me.
- Who told you? - That you were coming.
- The staff did? - No.
You guys told me not to tell anyone.
You said it was a top secret.
What was that yesterday?
You and Sun Bin were doing some kind of marketing trick.
- It wasn't a marketing trick. - No.
- Why is that a marketing trick? - So you're not faking it?
We're dating like a real couple. We're not tricking anyone.
- They went to the Han River. - Why...
- Really? - With the puppy.
- Why did you bring the puppy? - Really?
- You were faking it? - What...
- We just took the puppy there. - Really?
- It's part of our day-to-day life. - I see. It's...
We weren't using the puppy...
- for marketing. - No?
- Why would we need to do that? - No?
- Let's move down and sit. - Let's do that.
- Gosh, Bo Young. - Let's sit.
- It's your first time joining us. - Please sit.
Yes. It's my first time being on the show.
- Bo Young, it's been so long. - Yes, it's been so long.
Gosh, seriously.
- They shot "A Werewolf Boy." - Right.
- Really? - It was ages ago.
- It was a long time ago. - Yes.
- We filmed it in 2012. - Right.
- It was 2012. - Yes.
- Since then, we haven't been... - You haven't met since then?
- No. We saw each other... - Here and there.
- Yes. But we haven't been... - We met in passing.
- together in a long while. - It's been so long.
I met Hyang Gi recently.
I bet Hyang Gi grew up a lot.
She's past that point. She's just...
- Hyang Gi is a grown-up now. - Right.
- She's a lady now. - The topic is getting too personal.
- It's getting too personal. - No.
- But everyone knows Hyang Gi. - Don't you know Kim Hyang Gi?
- Actress Kim Hyang Gi. - Why are they talking about her?
I'm sitting right here.
- Kwang Soo was with us... - My gosh.
- when we kicked off our show. - That's right.
- He was in our 1st episode. - I was in Episode 1. Yes.
Things were a bit shaky when you were on our show.
- What do you mean? - What?
- Why would you say that? - We needed a more popular guest...
for our first episode.
What are you talking about?
I'm pretty popular.
- How much more popular must I be? - Well,
- back then... - The ratings were great.
- And people liked the episode. - It was...
good. No?
- The ratings were a bit low. - Really?
Your greed is the problem.
Things look different based on how you think.
But our short-form videos went viral.
- Kwang Soo was funny then. - Kwang Soo...
Why do you have your leg up?
- Why did I cross my legs? - Why did you cross your legs?
Don't people typically do this?
- You look arrogant. - So...
- Everyone looks so polite. - Right.
- I don't have to cross my legs. - Look at Bo Young.
I thought I should cross my legs given the weather.
Gosh, no.
I'm sorry.
Seriously.
You guys are very close too.
- We're old friends. - Right.
I hear Kwang Soo teases you...
the way we tease him.
- She's a good junior. - Really?
- Yes. - He disciplines me a lot.
About what?
He hates it when I don't answer him...
- right away. - Right.
When I don't text him back fast, he says,
"You've changed." He says that all the time.
Seriously. He told me...
that I had changed after filming "Strong Girl Bong Soon."
- He told you that a lot? - He told me that all the time.
- I heard that a lot. - Kwang Soo didn't tease people.
But a lot of his older friends teased him.
- I get why they tease me a lot. - Do you get it now?
- There's a thrill to it. - Yes.
There's a thrill. It happens to everyone.
When he calls me, it's like getting a call from my parents.
I'll be doing something. And I say, "Wait. Let me answer this call."
- When he calls you? - "Hey, Kwang Soo."
Right. So there's a strong hierarchy.
- Yes. - I see.
So did you film a movie with Bo Young?
- We filmed a drama. - It's a drama.
- A drama? - It's an original series.
Tell us about the drama.
- It will be on a streaming service. - Okay.
- It's called "Gold Land." - The tooth!
- Yes. It was for this drama. - It's finally going to be released.
- "Gold Land." - In the drama,
my character accidentally ends up...
with 100 gold bars,
- each weighing 10kg. - What?
(A gold-fueled survival thriller where greed and betrayal collide...)
(as they fight over a smuggling ring's 150 million dollars in gold)
(She obtains 150 million dollars in gold by chance.)
(Kim Hee Ju played by Bo Young, a woman whose greed is awakened)
(Director Park played by Kwang Soo, a man chasing greed)
Sir, I really don't know.
(A fueled crime thriller about those who fight for gold bars)
A third is your cut.
(I'll take it all the way.)
(A star-studded cast)
(Kim Sung Cheol, Lee Hyun Wook, Kim Hee Won, Moon Jeong Hee)
Our drama is about greed.
Tell us about your character in the drama.
- I play... - The gold tooth?
No. There's more to my character than that.
- Do you work at a pawnshop? - No, I don't.
My character is...
- Why can't you describe your role? - a loan.
- He's a loan shark. - I see. A loan shark.
- A loan shark. - So...
It's a loan shark, not just a loan.
(He's struggling with a simple introduction.)
- It's my first time... - Are you okay?
Talking about my character.
- This is our first time... - I suddenly... Yes.
- promoting the drama. - It's my first time...
- describing my character. - Yes.
When will it be released?
- On April 29. - On the 29th.
(It will be released on Streaming Service D.)
- We're in Guri. - Guri.
- Kwang Soo grew up in Namyangju... - That's right.
- Right. - and Guri.
- Kwang Soo... Yes. - I'm from Namyangju.
- I went to school in Guri. - I see.
Right here in Topyeong-dong.
- You went to school here. - Yes.
I went to Topyeong High School.
I was in the first graduating class.
My gosh. Really?
- The first graduating class? - Yes.
I was so surprised when I got here today.
- What a beautiful place. - How nice.
It's nice. We can see cherry blossoms here.
Guri is a great place.
Where do you live now?
Jamsil. You know where I live.
Why did you ask me that?
By the way, people who are proud...
- What was that? - about their hometown...
live someplace else.
- No, my parents still live here. - I see. They still live here.
Your father retired from a furniture company.
- Right. - He's retired now.
- Yes. - Right.
- Was it Company D? - Yes.
- You don't have to share that. - You know everything about him.
- Why share detailed information? - So he had furniture only from...
- that company. - Yes.
- I still have them. - Right.
Bo Young, what are your interests these days?
Me? I kind of understand why my mom always takes pictures of flowers.
- You get it now. - I do that a lot too now.
- So you started liking them? - I...
Yes. I take so many pictures of flowers.
- She gets it now. - My gosh.
I keep posting flower pictures in my family's group chat.
- Flower pictures? - You do?
- "Mom, this place is beautiful." - Right.
I know I shouldn't do this. Azaleas in my house bloomed.
- I took a picture of them. - Did you take a picture?
- Right. - I posted it in a group chat.
I can't help but do that these days.
- I started to notice flowers. - It's so odd.
- You start to notice nature more. - Yes.
- Sky and so on. - Yes.
- Tell us where we need to go. - Let's get going.
Let's go and look for our Whenever Guests.
- "Ji Young Ran." - Young Ran.
"My mom has never skipped a day..."
- "for 40 years." - What?
"This summer will be..."
- "her last semester at school." - Her last semester?
"Her lifelong wish is meeting Almighty Yu."
"I want to make that happen for her retirement present."
"So I'm writing this letter for my mom."
- "Please give her a present..." - She's retiring.
"she'll revisit whenever possible."
She's about to retire.
- "Her last semester." - "Semester?"
- A school? - Is she a schoolteacher?
- Is she a schoolteacher? - She might be, right?
- She might be. - Yes.
We must be there by 10:20am.
- We can walk for 20 minutes. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Gosh, today...
- The weather is great. - feels like spring.
This is the perfect weather.
(The perfect spring day for a walk)
This spot is so beautiful.
- It's so beautiful. - Now...
- You can only see them now. - Right.
We can see them next year.
That's not what I meant.
(Stopping for a moment)
- Right, we'll see them next year. - We'll see them next year too.
- I was talking about this year. - Next year...
The guys are fighting. They're bickering.
Come on.
- Did you really not understand me? - That's not the point.
We'll see them next year too.
- This isn't the only time... - I was...
It's impossible not to talk about how fast time flies by.
It's already April.
Right. We'll pass...
- the halfway point pretty soon. - Soon, it will be...
summer. You know?
- Time goes by so quickly. - How is this possible?
- How old are you now, Bo Young? - I'm 37.
- You're 37? - Yes.
You don't look like you're 37.
I'll be 40 soon.
- What are you talking about? - You still have time.
Hear me out. I was happy and excited...
- about turning 30. - Of course.
- But turning 40 feels different. - It's a bit different.
- "I can't believe I'll be 40." - Right.
I met Kwang Soo when he was in his 20s.
- Right. - I can't believe he's in his 40s.
I vividly remember it.
- It was when I was turning 30. - Yes.
I said, "Jae Seok, this feels weird."
"It does, right? But it feels weirder once you turn 40."
I still remember what you said.
I remember it so clearly.
- That happens. - Right.
Look. These cherry blossoms are in full bloom.
- What a beautiful spot. - The willow tree looks great here.
Oh, my. It's so beautiful.
How beautiful. Seriously. It looks so pretty here.
It's so beautiful.
This place is so picturesque.
Gosh, how beautiful.
Should we take pictures?
- Shall we? - Let's take some pictures.
- We should take a picture. - Wait.
You can stand right here.
- In the middle. - Nice.
- You know what I mean? - Bo Young, stand there.
- So this is... - Great.
Right here.
(It turns into a movie scene in 1 second.)
(Crouching down)
We must look like three uncles.
(Uncles are taking pictures of their niece.)
- She should pick her favorite one. - Wait.
- All right. Bo Young... - I didn't include the apartments.
What? My gosh.
- This looks good, right? - Yes.
- I also look tall in the picture. - Right. You look so tall.
(Photo by Yeon Seok)
- She looks super tall in the photo. - Hey.
- Hey. You're a giant in my photo. - She looks super tall in the photo.
(Photo by Kwang Soo)
You didn't include my feet in the photo.
- Why didn't you include her feet? - You're out.
- You're out. - No, you're wrong. My feet...
- That way, you look taller. - Why...
- They all... - This is what you should've done.
- Seriously. - We should let her take...
a photo of us.
- Us three? Yes, let's take it. - Yes.
(Bo Young will take their picture this time.)
Wait.
One, two, three.
It feels weird that the three of us are taking a photo.
We don't have time. You can't take individual pictures.
(Smiling immediately after)
(Three men under a cherry tree)
That's good. We should take a picture of Yeon Seok. Go ahead.
He likes taking selfies.
He does this when he takes selfies.
You know the way he opens his mouth?
You also have your go-to selfie look.
- He opens his mouth. - He...
He always turns to the side when he takes pictures.
- Like this. - The group he's with...
is always in the background.
And he's in front of them.
They're fighting.
Hey, step back. I'll take a picture of you.
Let's take pictures of him. Look. He likes that.
- Yes. Let me take one for you. - Not bad, right?
- I don't want to. - Let me take it for you.
No, I don't like...
- I don't like taking them alone. - He likes that.
- Gosh, I... - Look at him.
- I... - He looks so awkward.
- Gosh, I don't like... - Jae Seok.
- taking pictures alone. - You look great.
Really?
(In that case...)
I don't like taking pictures by myself.
(An awkward pose)
(He keeps tilting the camera.)
Hey. You're not taking pictures of me.
You look great.
- Let me take a picture of you. - The cherry blossoms...
- Yes. Come on, do it. - I'm really good.
I'll take one for you.
- Let's take a photo of Kwang Soo. - This is going to be great.
(The mid-star reluctantly poses for the camera.)
(Gazing)
He's getting so close.
(What's this guy doing?)
The cherry blossoms have to be in the shot.
They are in the shot.
(Laughing)
What...
Kwang Soo.
Your face looks so long.
Gosh, that was hilarious.
We got to take pictures...
- with cherry blossoms. - Yes.
- We enjoyed spring. Right. - You can only take them now.
- I wouldn't have if I were alone. - Right.
- Right. - True.
(They're on the move again to find the Whenever Guest.)
- Hello. - Hello.
You must be a model.
- Me? - No.
- Gosh. - No?
"No."
- "No." - We had... Here's the thing.
- "No." - Our eyes met when she said it.
- She didn't mean you. - "No."
She didn't mean Kwang Soo.
This is why I like hanging out with Kwang Soo.
When I'm with him, funny things like this happen a lot.
Right.
- There are always stories. - There are stories.
- He's a generator of stories. - "No."
(The four of them pass by the park.)
- I guess there must be schools. - Yes.
Wait. The school I went to was somewhere around there.
- Do you remember it? - Yes.
I see. This is the place.
Did you walk this path when you were in school?
I took the bus here.
That's the back gate.
(The path Kwang Soo took when he was in high school)
- Gosh, this area improved a lot. - This is the place.
- By the way... - This is the school.
Where?
- It's this school. - Wait! This is my old school!
- Really? - What?
- This is my alma mater. - This is your alma mater?
- You're right. - Really?
- "Topyeong High School." - Yes. "Topyeong High School."
- We're going to your old school. - Is this your school?
- Really? - Yes.
- It's Topyeong High School? - That's where we are going?
For real?
(Will they spend their first spare time at his alma mater?)
Here?
It looks the same.
- It must feel so surreal. - Nothing has changed.
- Right. - You never came back...
- after you graduated? - Usually...
- No. - Really?
(Kwang Soo feels warm and fuzzy inside at his alma mater.)
This is the back gate.
So that's how the gate looks now.
Back in the day, we easily climbed over.
(The student of the 1st graduating class is feeling sentimental.)
Wait. That's...
Is that also Topyeong High School?
- I don't think so. - It's a middle school.
Wait. Then we're going to Topyeong Middle School.
I see. We're not going to Topyeong High School?
- Come on. - All of a sudden,
- his mood is ruined. - It was Topyeong Middle School?
His sentimental mood is gone.
- He's demotivated. What do we do? - They're next to each other.
- Come on. - He's so demotivated.
- I got goosebumps. - But...
- Come on. You jumped the gun. - We have to walk a bit more.
- I... - I was getting so emotional.
Kwang Soo, you totally jumped the gun.
- It's right there. - Come on.
- But we're not going there. - We're not going there?
- No. - But we got the letter...
from Topyeong Middle School.
(The letter came from the middle school, not the high school.)
Kwang Soo was ready...
- to share his school stories. - My gosh.
I thought...
(Here's what went through his head.)
it could be my teacher.
- Your teacher? - Yes.
I thought I might meet my teacher.
- That would've been so nice. - My imagination ran wild.
- You... - I found myself...
getting ready for it.
But that wasn't the case.
This middle school was here when you went to school, right?
At first, it wasn't here.
- It wasn't here back then? - Not when I was in school.
- So it was established later on? - Was it when I was in 12th grade?
Oh, this middle school?
I think so.
Is it really here?
This is it.
She's on the second floor.
It really wasn't my high school.
- Do you remember it, Kwang Soo? - Yes.
I always took this path.
(The Whenever Guest is waiting for them here.)
Gosh, this place...
(Feeling sentimental)
- They're next to each other. - Do you remember it?
Yes, I do.
That building wasn't here before. That's new.
(His eyes are fixed on his alma mater.)
- Why can't you look away... - Kwang Soo seems to...
- Right. He's got that longing look. - from the high school?
It's been so long. Seriously.
Why is it so empty here?
- Wait. Today is... - Are they in class?
(Current time, 10:17am)
It's on the second floor.
(Heading to the 2nd floor to find the Whenever Guest)
My gosh. "You're the prettiest."
"You're my sunshine."
- I haven't seen this in a while. - "I want you to be happy."
"You're so cute."
- They look hand-drawn. - I think students drew them.
- It's bringing back memories. - How pretty.
- Those signs... - Hello.
- Hello. - Gosh.
- Gosh. - Are you Ms. Ji Young Ran?
- Yes. - You're Ms. Ji Young Ran.
(First Whenever Guest: Ji Young Ran)
Hello.
Thank you.
- I can't believe this is happening. - Hello.
- Kwang Soo, Yeon Seok, Bo Young. - Hello.
- Hello. - Gosh.
- He went to Topyeong High School. - Topyeong High School.
- How did you know? - You knew?
- You're famous here. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - Hello. I'm Park Bo Young.
- Should we go in? - This way.
It's so quiet here.
How nice.
(Holding his hand tightly)
(She leads them to...)
The principal's office.
Gosh, the principal's office.
- She's the principal. - You're the principal.
- Gosh, it's spacious. - Oh, my.
I've never been inside the principal's office.
We rarely have a chance to be inside the principal's office.
But my students come in here quite often.
- Really? - Yes.
Since this is the principal's office,
- I see all kinds of trophies. - Right.
On our way here, we saw a lot of banners...
celebrating the school's win...
- at a bowling match. - Yes.
- With bowling? - You have such a small face.
Okay.
(Giggling)
- It's an honor. - Gosh, no.
- What an honor. - My gosh.
(The principal is happy.)
Wait. So students these days...
can freely come into your office?
Whenever they have something to say, they come in...
and talk to me.
And my name is Ji Young Ran.
They call me Ms. Young Ran.
- Although you're the principal? - Yes.
I guess a lot has changed.
Back in my day, I'd be running around with my friends.
- Around the principal's office, - Right.
- we'd walk quietly... - Right.
- or slow down. - I used to run away...
- when I saw the principal. - Me too.
I didn't know what to say.
The letter said that you're going to retire soon.
Yes. I'm retiring...
- on August 31. - My gosh.
I started my career on September 1, 1987.
So I'm retiring after 40 years...
- at the mandatory retirement age. - I see.
- Gosh, congratulations. - Seriously. Congratulations.
- Seriously. Right. - Thank you for all your hard work.
Out of the blue, my son asked me...
when I had some spare time.
I told him I could make some spare time if I wanted.
I guess he was watching Whenever Possible on TV.
He said he would write to the show for me.
I said, "I love that idea."
Actually, I'm a huge fan of Jae Seok.
- Right. It said so. Gosh. - She's his big fan.
When I first saw Jae Seok on TV,
he wasn't as cool as he is now.
Why did you say that...
- while looking at the staff? - That's true.
- You don't have to feel bad. - You can say it to my face.
I...
- Why... - By the way,
you also dressed up as a grasshopper.
- Right. I did. Yes. - You remember his younger days.
- He ran against Line One. - Yes.
- You also went coal mining. - Right.
- You worked so hard in the sun. - Yes.
But look at you now.
You've become so successful that people call you Almighty Yu.
How nice is that? I'm so proud of you.
- My gosh. - I'm so proud of you.
- She's indeed the principal. - Listen.
It's like she's narrating the growth of a student.
- She talks like a principal. - Right.
- It's like visiting... - Yes.
A principal's office after a long time.
It's like getting a compliment...
- after making the school proud. - It's like a triumphant return.
I came back as a successful student.
Bo Young looks like she'd be the president of the student body.
- I'm her aide. - Right.
The president of the student body.
How does it feel...
now that your retirement is around the corner?
I entered my 1st school at the age of 8.
And I've been in school since then.
- That's right. - That's true.
So schools have always been a safe place for me.
Now that I have to leave this place,
I'm feeling a sense of anxiety and sadness at the same time.
You have to spend the rest of your life...
- outside the school. - Yes.
Even if you try to get ready for it...
- I've been getting myself ready. - Okay.
I even got the barista certificate.
- My gosh. - Really?
Will you run a cafe?
I'm confident that senior citizens will like talking to me.
So I can treat it like counseling.
(The future barista is great at counseling.)
You've been a teacher for 40 years.
Do you have any habits because of your job as a teacher?
- There must be occupational habits. - Right.
Of course.
I tend to tell my family what to do.
(Like she does to her students)
You do that to your family?
For example, just this morning, I told my husband,
"Dress the baby."
"Wipe the eye booger."
(She calmly bosses him around with honorifics.)
- She speaks with honorifics. - She did.
She's telling him what to do.
He usually does what I tell him. But he got mad today.
- My big sister is a piano teacher. - Okay.
I was chatting with my family.
All of a sudden, my brother-in-law exploded...
and said, "Stop ordering us around!"
I agreed with him. "Right, you need to stop that."
- Right. - That happened.
- She can't help it. - Right.
- It comes with the job. - But my sister didn't get it.
"I did that?"
- Right. - She talks to us...
as if talking to her students.
Yes, something like that.
As Ms. Ji already mentioned,
this is her last spring at school...
- Yes, last spring. - before her retirement.
Coincidentally,
- the weather today is... - It's pretty.
I know, right?
- It's amazing. - Yes.
The students are taking photos.
Yes.
Photos are taken under the cherry blossoms every year.
Even though it's not a special day?
(Laughing)
I'm sure the cherry blossoms...
will think, "New kids this year!"
- The tree is always there. - Exactly.
- But the students... - Yes, the students change...
- every year. - How pretty.
- We never took photos in my days. - Me neither.
Things like that show...
- how things have changed. - Exactly.
- They've got freedom. - True.
Our students, in particular,
- Are they free? - are freer than others.
They're not in high school,
so the pressure to study is less.
Middle school students should be happy first.
You're happy, right, Kwang Soo?
- Sorry? - "You didn't study, right?"
- Is that what you mean? - Why me?
No.
- No? - "You're happy, right, Kwang Soo?"
Look at him,
- and he's already bright, no? - "You're happy, right, Kwang Soo?"
- Why change the subject to me? - I had no idea.
- "That's what happiness is." - Yes.
"It's fine as you're happy."
- Exactly. - Right?
Yes, I'm happy.
Ms. Ji will soon retire.
We're here to give you a gift.
- A gift of good memories. - For real.
The final moments are critical.
- Topyeong's pride is here with us. - Yes.
This school didn't exist back when I lived here.
- Back in high school... - So what?
Are you saying Ms. Ji...
- is your junior? - No.
- Kwang Soo. - That's not what I meant.
- What a strange thing to say. - No, listen.
- She spent 40 years in education. - Hear me out.
I totally respect her, okay?
Why don't you, the Topyeong's pride, roll it?
- Shall I? - Yes.
- Two is the best. - Yes.
- He's right. - There's also zero.
(The dignity shown off by Topyeong's pride)
(0 bonus coupons)
(A spoilsport)
(Reading the room)
You should've been bolder.
The dice only has one zero.
(Got the only 0)
- All right. - A fortune cookie.
Yes, a fortune cookie.
"Students always drop by the principal's office."
"Make good memories over some tea until the last day."
"A tea set from W brand."
A tea set from W brand.
A tea set.
(A tea set, tea time with students until the last day)
What a thoughtful gift.
She even has a barista certificate.
You're totally right.
- How pretty. - It's beautiful.
It looks classy.
Isn't it nice, Ms. Ji?
My gosh.
- It suits you so well. - How pretty.
(Cooperative relay gonggi)
(Each player is to play one level of gonggi at a time.)
(1st player: Level 1)
(2nd player: Level 2)
(3rd player: Level 3)
(4th player: Level 4 and toss and catch)
(Time limit: 30 seconds)
- Only 30 seconds? - In 30 seconds?
Have you not played gonggi?
Only when I was in elementary school.
- I haven't practiced in ages. - Same here.
I used to play gonggi, but now that I don't...
But you were good at it last time.
But the toss and catch with five stones...
- after level four is... - That's not easy.
I've never caught five stones.
Really?
- Let's give it a shot. - It's going to be tough.
- Practice. - It's hard.
- Like this? - Bo Young is good at it.
As expected, Bo Young is good. She's skilled.
- You're good. - Bo Young is good to go.
- My hands are shaking. - Hold on.
If you drop some stones, you can start again.
- Within 30 seconds. - In 30 seconds.
The toss and catch is important.
I keep dropping the stones.
- Try it. - How do we do it?
We should each take charge of the level we're confident in.
- Here's level 1. - Level 1.
Say that I try level one.
- One at a time? - Don't throw it tight.
Throw them apart.
- Nice. - You're good, Yeon Seok.
- Yeon Seok. - The next player.
- Level Two. - The next person...
- In 30 seconds? - does level 2.
- High, low, okay. - Nice.
- Okay. - He's terrible at it.
- Sweep, yes. - Good.
- He's bad at it. - Okay.
- But he's got the biggest hand. - It's...
- If you don't play gonggi... - My fingers have gone stiff.
It's hard if you don't play gonggi.
(Trying level 3)
- All right. - Jae Seok will do level three.
- Level 4 is... - Level 4 is left.
Level four. You have to do it, Bo Young.
- Sorry? - If you're the last player.
- Done. - First, level four.
And this.
Even if I toss five, I can't catch all of them.
- No, you can do it. - I have to treat them gently.
You've got to do it.
- Catching them all is... - How is this Round One?
- Nice. - She's good at gonggi.
Yes.
That's it. You're the one for it.
(Successfully tossed and caught 5 stones)
- You should do it. - Bo Young.
- My heart is pounding. - It's yours.
- Go last, Bo Young. - Do the last two.
Bo Young will go last.
- Do you want to do level one? - Yes.
Will you do level two?
- I'll do two. - Okay.
- Then I'll do three. - Got it.
- Let's go. - Let's cheer together.
- Come, Ms. Ji. - Oh, dear. Please.
- In 1... - We have a total of 10 tries.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
All right.
We only have 30 seconds, so hurry.
- Okay. - I'd better do level one fast.
Here I go.
Thirty seconds will be too short.
- I'm nervous. - Ready.
Set.
Here I go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(1st try)
They're too...
- It's too tight. - Don't worry.
- Good. - Nice.
Next. Hurry.
(Advanced technique)
That's quite sly.
- His other hand. - Kwang Soo.
What's up with your left hand?
- Success. - Okay.
- Come on. - Kwang Soo.
- Ten seconds left. - What?
Nice throw.
Start again.
- Five, four, - Here.
- three, - Bo Young.
- two, - Here.
- one. - Toss and catch.
- Oh, no. - There's not enough time.
Give me a bit more time.
Sorry, Bo Young.
- It's because he dropped some. - I've got it.
- The earlier players should... - Give me two more seconds.
- Don't place the stones down. - Okay.
This one's challenging.
What do you think is the cause, Ms. Ji?
The cause of our failure.
It was your first try.
- The first try. - Exactly.
- The first try. - It's only natural, right?
- The time limit... - They need to warm up first.
- Let's focus more. - Oh, no.
- Bo Young. - We should use less time...
- so that Bo Young... - Exactly.
- can play at ease. - I'm at a loss.
(Practicing the toss and catch)
- This is bad. - If there's time,
- she can try again, right? - All good.
- You can try again. - All right.
- Bo Young. - Our second try.
- Let's use less time. - Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
- I've got a good feeling. - Just one.
We're good.
Hold on.
- Ready. - We were close just now.
Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
(2nd try)
Nice.
Yeon Shik is on a roll today.
- Here. - Next, Kwang Soo.
Hold on.
- Okay. - Here.
We've got plenty of time.
- It's... - Hurry, Jae Seok.
Done.
- Bo Young. - Ten seconds left.
- It's more than enough. - Start again.
Ten seconds left.
(A major blunder)
- Start again. - Again.
- The time. - It's too...
- Hold on. - Where is it?
- It's under the couch. - Five, four,
- three... - How did it...
(Failed due to missing gonggi stones)
- Hold on. - You said it too loudly.
- Really. - Bo Young got startled.
The game itself is scary already.
I can't do level four.
We should push the couch back.
(It must've been quite frustrating.)
- Ms. Ji is... - Yes.
- She's frustrated. - Totally.
Let's push the couch back.
- Earlier... - Ms. Ji.
- It's hot, right? - Why are you taking it off?
Bo Young is good at it during practice.
- My hands shake when we try. - But...
when the producer starts counting down...
I can't do it.
The last player... Jae Seok.
The pressure is unbelievable.
- How about going last, Jae Seok? - Did you find one?
- Oh, dear. - Level four and toss and catch?
- Try it, Jae Seok. - But Bo Young was good at it.
(Looking for a player to replace Bo Young)
- Bo Young was good at it. - Let's give her a break.
The last player feels great pressure.
His hands are shaking.
- Your hands tremble like mad. - Let me try.
- Going last is... - Let me try.
Go ahead.
Toss it first.
- That was too high. - You can't do it.
Try again, Bo Young.
Calmly.
- That's it. - Nice.
- Good. - Well done.
- No, please. - Let's try.
(Back to being Bo Young)
- Just keep that up. - Practice, Bo Young.
- But... - Stop practicing.
But I can't even do level four.
- Don't use up your energy. - Pull yourself together, Bo Young.
- Don't use your energy. - Pull yourself together, Bo Young.
- Listen to us. - Right.
Yes, stop practicing.
- Go first, Yeon Seok. - First?
- Again? - Let's try it.
Let's cheer.
Let's cheer, Bo Young.
- Here. - We can do it.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
- I want to go home. - What?
Let's go.
Ready.
- Here we go. - Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
Good.
(4th try)
Yeon Shik is good at it.
It's not easy at all.
- Here. - Okay.
- Start again. - Again.
The time...
All right, here.
Nice throw.
(Passed level 3)
- All set. - Relax.
You've got time.
- Relax. You've got time. - Good.
Ten seconds left.
- Bo Young. - Again.
Go ahead.
- Good. - Nice.
- Good. - Toss and catch.
Five, four...
Four, three...
- Oh, no! - Oh, dear.
(Failed)
- Three... - Oh, no!
Oh, dear.
(Failed the toss and catch again)
We're always so close.
Being pressed on time as the last player is...
That's a first from Bo Young.
"Oh, no!"
(Hearing Bo Young's first-ever scream)
- I'm sorry. - Being pressed on time...
Unexpectedly,
- you're the type to get nervous. - Yes, extremely.
I freeze up totally.
When the producer calls ten seconds,
she loses the stones.
- Hold on. - It's not easy.
The hard desk is the problem.
- You're right, Ms. Ji. - It's too slippery too.
- If only we had a cover. - Exactly.
- The desk is too hard. - Yes.
Where is this desk from?
Topyeong Middle School.
We three can't make any mistakes.
- Yes. - Bo Young needs enough time.
- We can't make mistakes. - You're right.
How about the one who makes a mistake...
- gets a noogie? - Okay.
- A noogie? - Yes, a noogie.
We three can't make a mistake.
- Let's leave it to Bo Young. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- All set. - It's your last...
toss and catch chance.
This is nothing but gonggi.
Relax, okay?
Okay.
But you don't look relaxed, Ms. Ji.
- We haven't passed Round One. - You're the most restless one.
We'll succeed no matter what.
- Don't worry. - We'll pass Round One.
- Here. One, two, three. - Forty years in education.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- No mistakes, okay? - Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
(5th try)
It's a noogie.
- Oh, no. - A noogie, for sure.
You really...
Is it a fist noogie?
Okay. Next.
(Barely passed level 1)
(5th try)
Okay.
- All done. - Good.
- Good. - Ten seconds left.
All set.
- Calmly, Bo Young. - You've got time.
- Five... - You've got plenty of time.
Five, four...
Okay!
Four...
(Bo Young did it!)
Okay!
(Bo Young's legs gave way right away.)
Ms. Ji.
Well done.
- Good. - Ten seconds left.
(Staying calm even after the 10-second announcement)
Five, four...
(Succeeded the toss and catch in one go)
(Succeeded Round 1 and secured the tea set)
I thought we were going to fail for sure.
Bo Young saved me.
She saved me.
- Near the end... - He was going to get...
nooged for sure.
Imagining that I wouldn't make it...
made me relaxed.
- You thought like that? - "I'll fail."
- That you won't make it? - Thinking that...
After giving up, right?
We have 5 tries left. Tries 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10.
Five tries left.
Whether to stop or go for Round Two.
Go, no questions asked.
- Go, no questions asked? - Yes.
Fail, and you'll lose everything.
- It's okay. - Are you okay with it?
This takes up a lot of energy.
(Tired from just Round 1)
"Last day of school after 40 years!"
"It's time to shift..."
"from neat to glamorous."
"Cat-eye sunglasses from G brand."
Designer sunglasses?
(Cat-eye sunglasses from G brand, )
(a glamorous transformation after retirement)
I'd love to gift them to her.
When you go on trips...
- How pretty. - Oh, my.
- Do you like it? - Will you be able to succeed?
- We'll succeed no matter what. - For sure.
- Bo Young. - Okay.
- Will we get less time? - She mentioned you in particular.
What's for Round Two?
(Round 2)
(Each is to toss and catch.)
(All 4 must toss and catch at least 15 stones.)
What?
(Everyone has to toss and catch?)
(The weakest has become solemn.)
- We must... - In total.
- No other levels? - Just toss and catch?
- So... - And the time limit?
- No time limit. - No?
If 3 players catch 5 each, we're done.
Let's say I only tossed three stones.
- You must catch all 3. - We only get 3 points.
- Correct. - Say that I got five stones.
- But I can't catch all 5. - Take 1 out?
- Can I drop one down? - Yes.
- Okay. - You can drop some.
We can toss as many as we want.
- Yes. - From what I see,
two players...
- must catch five stones each. - Yes.
I've never tossed and caught five stones in my life.
- While playing gonggi. - To get 15 stones,
we can go for 4, 4, 4,
and three.
You tossed them too high, Kwang Soo.
One must get five stones.
- Too high. - Slightly.
I've been telling you that you've been tossing them too high.
(The soft-hearted youngest has gone evil.)
Wasn't it low just now?
How low must I toss them?
That's it.
- Just catch the 3. - Gather the 3, and catch them.
Three should be good for you.
Catch all three.
- That's it. - Yes, all set.
- That's it. - Good job.
Bo Young should go first.
- Yes, 1st. - I want to go 1st.
- Get 5 points first. - Yes, get 5 points.
Get five.
The rest can get the remaining points.
Let's go for Round Two right away.
Round 2. In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go! - Here we go! Bo Young starts.
Is this my last try?
- We're on the 6th try. - Only 1 chance at toss and catch.
One chance per player.
Think about why that's been there since earlier.
I only saw it now. I didn't spot it earlier.
Nothing came into my sight.
(Backing down)
- Don't annoy her. - Bo Young is on edge.
Bo Young is on edge.
- Move it. - She's edgy. Don't annoy her.
(Queen Edgy before the game)
- Ready. - Okay.
Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
Please.
- Get all four. - Drop it.
- If you can't catch it, drop it. - Just catch four.
- Can you get 4? - Or just catch 3.
Just do three.
(Her head is spinning.)
- It's at an awkward spot. - True.
- Good. - Oh, no.
If Jae Seok gets 5, we get 8 points.
Go wrong and...
(6th try, Jae Seok)
- Hold on. We're doomed. - This is bad.
- Six. - Six.
- Nine left. - Shall I go?
- Five, four. - I...
- Five, four. - You...
- You... - Can you catch five?
I can't do it.
- I can't do five. - Everything is on you.
- No, I can't do five. - Try it, Yeon Seok.
(6th try, Yeon Seok)
(He tossed all 5 stones!)
(Will he...)
(Yeon Seok caught all 5!)
Gosh, really.
- Kwang Soo, four. - Really.
(Everything is up to Kwang Soo now.)
Kwang Soo, four.
- As expected. - It's up to you now.
- It's up to you now. - As expected.
- Four, and we'll succeed. - Just four.
Toss them up, and it's a success.
- You can do it, Kwang Soo. - Good luck.
Ms. Ji's sunglasses are in your hands.
Good luck.
We must get her those sunglasses.
- Good luck. - Let's go.
(He must catch at least 4 to pass Round 2.)
You can do it.
Four, and we'll succeed.
No, wait. Drop one.
(He tossed all 5 stones!)
(He did it!)
No, wait. Drop one.
(One stone is on the line.)
- No, just do it. - Drop it.
- There's no need to catch five. - Go for it if you want to.
- Drop it or don't? - Do it.
- Drop it. - Just do it.
- Just do it! - Bend your thumb.
- Drop it or don't? - Do it.
- Drop it. - Just do it.
- Just do it! - Bend your thumb.
- Do it! - I can't decide. Decide for me.
- Do it! - I can't decide.
- Hurry. - Jae Seok.
- Quiet. - Do I bend my thumb?
- Drop it? - Bend your thumb.
Should I drop one or not, Ms. Ji?
- Bend your thumb. - Just do it.
- Yes, just do it. - Stay calm.
Just do it. Give it a shot.
Oh, dear.
- What do you want to do? - Hurry.
- Choose. - Hurry.
You want to drop one, right?
- I'll try. - You've got big hands.
It's okay. You've got big hands.
- I did it! - Okay!
(Kwang Soo did it!)
(Jumping)
(Caught a total of 16 stones)
(Pushed him out of joy)
Why...
Why did you just push me?
Well done.
You did really well.
(Mr. Topyeong is moved.)
I feel dizzy.
- You did really well. - I feel dizzy.
- Incredible. - Good job.
- Round Two, success! - Success!
Well done.
The son of Topyeong!
- It's the son of Topyeong. - The son of Topyeong.
- Great job. - You did it.
Goodness.
- Oh, dear. - He's never caught five stones.
I had never caught five stones in my life before.
The miracle in Topyeong.
No one would...
team up with me when we played gonggi.
- Gosh. - You did so well.
- The miracle in Topyeong. - Great job.
- That was... - You overcame the pressure.
We passed Round 2 in 1 go,
- and now it's... - It's a tormenting choice.
- We have... - Round Three?
We have...
- four tries left. - Go.
- What? - Ma'am.
- Just go. - You might lose all the prizes.
You lose all of them.
That's okay.
We go, no matter what.
- All right? - All right.
- She wants us to go for it. - Yes.
Gosh.
(They begin Round 3 without being able to stop her.)
But this is...
You're really enthusiastic.
(Exclaiming)
- What? - What is it?
"The Principal's treat for everyone!"
"It's sweet churros time during lunch."
"A special snack truck is coming to Topyeong Middle School."
(Round 3's prize, a snack truck for Topyeong Middle)
That means so much.
(Young Ran's treat, a churros truck for the whole school)
If this truck comes after we succeed...
This would be...
It would be so nice.
It's such a good memory.
Indeed.
- For the students, I mean. - Yes.
Please succeed.
(Please succeed.)
- Oh, no. - All right.
- What's Round 3? - What's Round 3?
(Round 3)
(Same as Round 2)
(But they get 20 seconds.)
- This... - But the toss and catch...
- sounds a bit unfair. - doesn't fall here.
You only give us one try.
It's so unfair.
- It's only 15 points, right? - Yes.
(They must toss and catch 15 in 20 seconds.)
Bo Young, do you want to go last?
- Yes, she'll go last. - What? No.
- Because... - Yes.
You can catch as many as you can.
Then, I'll go first.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's all play. - All four of us?
- We'll all do it. - Just go last.
Rock...
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
- You're going last. - Last.
Rock, paper, scissors.
That was meaningless.
(Why is she going last when she won?)
Shoot.
- You're going... - First.
- First? - First?
(He lost, but he gets to go first, which is less pressure?)
Does the loser go first place?
(He senses that something's off.)
Does the loser go first?
I don't know. You let me go first.
You should go first.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- I'm 2nd. - I'm 2nd.
- What does winning and losing... - Why are we playing this?
Determine?
- You said losers went first. - I won, so...
You might as well...
just say when you want to go.
Why did we even play?
First, second, third, and fourth.
Please.
(Practicing in the air)
(Swoosh)
(She tried pulling her fingers.)
(She even went against the wall...)
(and stretched while she watched them play.)
First, second, third, and fourth.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
In 1, 2, 3.
- The time limit... - Twenty seconds.
We have to go right away.
(It's all about speed since they only have 20 seconds.)
- Here I go. - Okay.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
(7th try, Yeon Seok)
That's good.
- You dropped them. - Do I go again?
- No, we move on. - Move on.
- Really? - That's it?
We fail if you don't get five.
(The remaining 3 have to catch 5 stones each to win.)
(If Kwang Soo can't catch 5)
(they fail instantly.)
(He put 5 stones on the back of his hand again.)
You got it.
I'm good at gonggi!
(Everyone's surprised.)
(7th try, Jae Seok)
(Exclaiming)
Failure.
I ruined this round.
(Intimidated)
This makes you feel so small.
And it makes you uncomfortable.
Let's not get too greedy.
(He's on his high horse.)
Okay? Just drop them if you can't catch them.
- What happened to you? - No idea. I'm so good at this.
You've got talent.
- You're good. - You have a gift.
I have to gather them first.
- Is this try number eight? - Yes.
- So, we have three tries left. - Three tries.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
- Just forget about the time limit. - Yes.
- Here we go. - Here I go.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 8.)
(8th try, Bo Young)
Just catch 4.
- Great. - Well done.
(8th try, Jae Seok)
Three? That's seven.
- Seven. - Seven.
We got seven.
(8th try, Kwang Soo)
(He put 5 stones on the back of his hand again?)
(Kwang Soo caught 5 stones.)
- Wait, how many? - Just do it.
(They need 3 more stones.)
(Please get 3 stones!)
- Five, four... - Three more.
We only need three more.
- Three more. - We only need three more.
(He put exactly 3 stones on his hand!)
(We succeed if he catches them.)
- Three more. - We only need three more.
(8th try, Yeon Seok, 3)
(They succeeded with 2 seconds left!)
Okay!
Yes!
- You did it? - Yes!
You did it?
Success!
Oh, my gosh.
(Yeon Seok made it exactly 15 stones.)
The son of Topyeong!
Well done.
- I was so startled. - Gosh.
- Oh, my gosh. - I...
(The toss and catch hero who caught 5 stones)
Oh, my gosh.
It's the son of Topyeong.
(Moved)
- How did he get five? - What?
- I mean... - That was precise.
You were impressive.
What's gotten into you?
- You did so well. - You're good.
I know, right?
I'm so excited right now.
- You're so hot and wet. - Seriously.
- Did they win all the prizes? - Yes.
All right. Round Three is...
- a success! - Success!
(They passed Round 3.)
- Great job. - We did it!
- Even the snack truck. - The snack truck!
- That was awesome. - Congratulations!
Amazing.
My students will be so happy. Thank you.
- Thank you so much. - The teacups, sunglasses,
- and the snack truck! - Even the snack truck.
Kwang Soo, those five stones...
- I should try them on. - Sure.
- Go ahead. - I'll try on the sunglasses.
- Go ahead. - Right now.
Let me see. How do I look?
- It's perfect. - It suits you so well.
(Cheering)
- It suits you so well. - What do you think?
- It's perfect. - It suits you so well.
(Greatly satisfied)
Also, the snack truck.
(A perfect finishing touch of the snack truck)
I couldn't thank you enough.
You look like Marilyn Monroe.
(The best retirement gifts)
(The snack truck came to the school a few days later.)
(It was an unforgettable day for the students as well.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(We wish all the best for the future of Topyeong Middle and Young Ran.)
Seriously, though. Kwang Soo...
Bo Young finished the Round One, and...
(He dominated in Topyeong, his home ground.)
The dopamine rush...
- Lee Topyeong. - The rush.
You are Lee Topyeong from now on.
- Kwang Soo, what's gotten into you? - That was incredible.
I had never put five stones on my hands before.
- Hey, Lee Topyeong. - I'm going to call you Topyeong.
I haven't heard Bo Young's real voice...
in so long.
(Laughing)
When I failed?
(We also have to commend Bo Young for her struggle while roaring.)
I feel proud.
- Totally. I'm so refreshed. - Absolutely. I feel so good.
And she's resigning, so...
- I know, right? - Yes.
- I think we had good energy. - Indeed.
It was dramatic.
It really was.
I won't be eating lunch in a bad mood.
- I'll eat so well. - Yes!
Is there anything you want to eat, Bo Young?
What do you want?
- It's ten minutes on foot. - I'd like some kalguksu.
We should go this way to find restaurants.
- Then... - This way,
there's only Jangja Lake.
- Come on, Yeon Shik. - We have to go this way.
There's a kalguksu place.
Where?
Shabu kalguksu.
- I like the sound of that. - And they make their noodles.
- Shabu kalguksu. - It's the main store.
(Screaming)
Did we...
(They suddenly hear shrieks.)
Kwang Soo graduated from Topyeong High School.
- I'm from Topyeong High. - Topyeong High School.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- It's Bo Young. - Hi.
Park Bo Young.
(He keeps smiling like a school senior.)
Kwang Soo is...
smiling like a handsome man.
(Lee Topyeong acts good looks.)
I'm a grand senior.
- Kwang Soo. - All right?
The very first graduating class of Topyeong High!
- Lee Kwang Soo! - Good luck, guys.
- Lee Kwang Soo! - Lee Kwang Soo!
Take care, guys!
Watch Whenever Possible.
When they watch this on TV...
Yes.
(After greeting the juniors at Topyeong High, )
(they look for a restaurant.)
Is there a good restaurant?
I'm fine with snack food too.
I feel so good that I'll be able to enjoy anything.
I actually feel good.
- I mean it. - I'm exhilarated.
I haven't felt this proud in so long.
I know, right? It's new.
Kwang Soo will be happy,
- no matter what he does. - Kwang Soo...
did so well for a mid-star.
What are you talking about?
There's no such thing as a mid-star.
(This mid-star did as well as a superstar.)
You really were the pride of Topyeong High.
- That was... - I know.
- Exactly. - That was...
When we went to Sejong University...
(Yeon Seok could have become the pride of Sejong University.)
I still remember how we couldn't get...
- the snack stand owner any prizes. - Right.
Hyang Gi went to promote her movie, right?
Hyang Gi? Yes, you're right.
Wait, a movie?
- Is it? - Why does he only talk to Bo Young?
- Yeon Seok. - A drama... Yes?
Can you stop talking about Hyang Gi?
- I mean... - Why...
She's not even on this show.
- Bo Young asked! - Why do you keep mentioning her?
You've been talking about Hyang Gi for hours!
- Hyang Gi and... - What are you two whispering about?
- What does she have to do with me? - What are you trying to do?
- They're so scary. - You two can't...
- Stop talking about Hyang Gi. - Okay.
You're going to put Hyang Gi on the spot.
(Yes, sir.)
- The weather's so nice. - Topyeong-dong is...
- It's such nice weather to walk in. - Yes.
How about this restaurant?
- Should we eat snow crab? - I'd like that.
Snow crab for lunch?
- Right. You like snow crab. - Yes.
Should we splurge today?
Only one of us will pay, after all.
A combo for 3 to 4 people is 290 dollars.
What?
- That's pretty expensive. - For lunch...
- It makes me... - What do you say?
- want to stop. - That's pretty expensive.
That's a high price.
I can't spend 290 dollars on 1 lunch.
How far is the kalguksu place?
It's about nine minutes from here.
(9 minutes?)
And our next spot is seven minutes on foot from there.
Really?
It gets hot in the afternoon.
I know, right?
There's a kodari naengmyeon place.
What's kodari naengmyeon?
- That sounds tasty. - Kodari naengmyeon?
We have to cross the street here.
Kodari naengmyeon also sounds pretty good.
We have to cross from here.
- What do you think? - It's a place with tradition.
- But this is... - Directly managed by headquarters.
The owner is waving at us to come and eat.
(Come and eat kodari naengmyeon.)
- The owner is waving at us. - Oh, you're right!
- Let's eat kodari naengmyeon. - Steamed half-dried pollack...
- One steamed half-dried pollack. - Kodari naengmyeon.
We're coming!
- I was also craving that. - Right?
- It must be delicious. - Yes.
- Kodari naengmyeon sounds great. - It does.
Kwang Soo resembles a half-dried pollack.
What do you mean by that?
How does one resemble a half-dried pollack?
- What even is that? - Now that you mention it...
- He's... - What kind of fish is that?
You look like a half-dried pollack.
You can find out over there.
Why did you gesture with your nose?
Is it a fish with a nose?
(The tall guy with impressive nose is upset.)
Great choice, by the way.
- Why, hello. - Hello.
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
One boiled pollack...
- Yes. - and one naengmyeon each.
- Sounds great. - Thank you.
- We have to get kodari naengmyeon. - Yes.
- It must be delicious. - I'm hungry.
So am I.
- I... - I got hungry all of a sudden.
- spent too much energy. - Thanks.
Bo Young, do you cook?
(Shaking her head)
You usually order in, right?
Right.
- I see. - I order in,
but I started living with a friend of mine.
Now that I have a roommate...
- You have a roommate now? - So, I started...
- cooking at home. - A childhood friend.
- Really? - A high school friend...
- lived in Cheongju, - Okay.
- She came to Seoul? - but she came to Seoul,
looking for a job.
I offered to stay at my place...
so that she could take her time looking for her place.
We've been living together for a short while, and I love it.
That's incredible.
You've been best friends since childhood?
She's literally my best friend.
- That looks so good. - Great.
- Please wait for a moment. - It's exactly what I need.
That looks delicious.
- It was the greatest choice ever. - Yes.
It looks scrumptious.
- A bit of cold soup... - What's that?
It looks great.
(Smacking his lips)
It's been so long since I last had naengmyeong with fish.
It looks so tasty!
The sesame oil scent is strong.
I'll eat this first.
Naengmyeong tastes great after some time.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
(He puts his face in the bowl and eats it.)
(Exclaiming)
(She wraps the noodles around a piece of pollack...)
(and puts it in his mouth.)
You like it?
It's so good.
It tastes great after some time.
Wait, what?
- What is it? - That's huge.
- That's... - Thank you.
Thank you.
I didn't know it'd be this big.
The boiled pollack looks good.
Hold on.
Eat up.
It's too big.
(Tender fish...)
(and spicy sauce)
Ma'am, can we have two bowls of rice?
- Sure. - Goodness.
- How do we eat this? - You wrap it in laver.
In the dried laver?
(Bo Young is experienced and demonstrates.)
We only found out about this place because Yeon Seok went,
- "Kodari naengmyeon?" - Right.
(Bean sprouts)
It's nice and spicy.
It's the ultimate rice companion.
You have to eat rice with this.
(She neatly puts it in her mouth.)
(Exclaiming)
You wrap it?
(Jae Seok copies Bo Young.)
It's really good...
wrapped in dried laver.
When I go to my parents' house, my mom...
gets braised half-dried pollack as takeout.
I think it's this place.
- Really? - Because their house is nearby.
- I see. - I see.
- You remember the taste. - I was thinking...
about where I tried this food and side dishes.
- It was this place. - Yes, my mom would...
You're right.
(He already finished a bowl of rice.)
- I had never tried it, but... - When you eat it here...
It's really tasty.
That was such a good meal.
But we have to decide who will pay.
You brought your cards, right?
(Deciding who pays)
We did this the first time I was on this show.
- We did. - Who's paying for this?
(He was present in the very 1st lunch game.)
(It was also intense at the time.)
(That's how they started...)
(playing games to decide who pays.)
We could all hold a piece of dried laver...
- And rip it? - Yes.
The one with the smallest piece pays?
- The smallest piece? - The smallest...
- The one with the smallest piece. - Okay.
- We pull on the count of three. - We pull.
You grab it first.
- Don't move. - Okay.
- The smallest piece pays? - Yes.
(Putting his entire knuckle on it)
- You can't hold it like that. - Not this.
- With your fingertips. - You can't...
- Okay. I didn't know. - That's cheating.
- Oh, gosh. - Come on.
This is it.
(Jae Seok is next.)
It's cramped.
- Are you coming in? - You also lose if you let go.
I can't let go because of you.
You're holding my finger down.
That's too deep, Yeon Seok.
Hey, you can't come underneath me.
- Why not? - You can't...
- You can't do anything about that. - We didn't say we couldn't.
- You'll take my piece away. - Which way should I go?
Oh, my gosh.
You pull it toward yourself.
Toward yourself, okay?
The smallest piece pays.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Screaming)
You have the smallest piece.
(His piece is obviously the smallest.)
- Obviously... - Let's compare.
- This is... - Look.
- You can eat this laver. - Thank you for the food.
- Thanks. - Thanks for the food.
- But I grabbed a big piece. - It tastes good.
You're certainly the son of Topyeong.
- Thanks, Kwang Soo. - Thanks.
- Thanks, Topyeong. - Thank you for the food.
Lee Topyeong.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You're so pretty. - Kwang Soo will pay.
- It tasted good. - Thanks for the food, Kwang Soo.
Thanks.
Thanks, Kwang Soo.
Coffee would taste so good right now.
Kwang Soo is working hard for the local economy.
(Lee Topyeong revitalizes the local economy.)
He is.
Right?
A bakery.
It looks so pretty, doesn't it?
They look so tasty.
There are so many tasty foods in this world.
Are we playing rock-paper-scissors?
Coffee's on me.
- Yes, the last episode... - Yes.
- It's the last episode, so... - Thank you.
Can we pay for the bread?
Boosting the local economy.
This is fig, and this is cream cheese.
- I'll eat this later. - What are you going to eat?
Cream cheese?
Which one do you want?
- Cream cheese. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
I also want cream cheese.
- The winner... - The loser eats the fig flavor.
- Okay. - Okay.
Rock...
- I kind of want to win. - Rock, paper, scissors!
(Fig, cream cheese, and cream cheese)
I think this is wrong.
(What did she see?)
- I'll... - No, Yeon Seok.
- I also like figs. - So do I.
- I actually like figs. - No.
What was the point of playing rock-paper-scissors?
You should learn to accept it.
(He ate all the cream cheese bread.)
You really are...
- You're the worst! - It's so tasty.
- You're the worst one... - It's so good.
- of everyone I know! - Yeon Seok...
He ate all of it to block Yeon Seok from eating.
- Seriously... - It's so tasty.
You're so mean.
It's not a regular egg tart.
Kwang Soo is something else.
- I suddenly hate you. - It was...
It was the best egg tart I've had.
- I hate you so much. - You're so...
All right, Lee Bo Ram and Kim Yong Ji.
"I used to be the nation's ace, always winning on the field."
"But these days, I'm constantly losing to my stingy husband."
"I can't even choose what to eat out,"
"and spontaneous drives are just a dream."
"With no one to talk to, I'm keeping..."
"this bittersweet marriage story to myself. Care to listen?"
- They must be a married couple. - An ace?
Was she an athlete?
- Is this it? The sports club? - A sports club?
She said she was an athlete.
You're right. I think this is the place.
(Banging)
- Is it badminton? - I think so.
Listen to it.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Are you Bo Ram? - Yes. Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello!
(Second Whenever Guests, Lee Bo Ram and Kim Yong Ji)
Badminton!
You're playing with your husband.
(Run by a husband and wife who used to be athletes)
This was a badminton academy.
I guess it hasn't been that long since you got married.
Yes, it's been five years.
- Yes. - Five years?
Did you two meet...
- while playing badminton? - Yes.
When I was in elementary school,
my wife used to be so good.
You've known each other since elementary school?
Well, I knew her, but she didn't know me.
- I see. - I see.
You wrote in the letter that you were the nation's ace.
- Right. - Yes.
She must have been really good at badminton.
She was good and pretty,
so she was famous.
But I wasn't that good at badminton.
- So only I knew her. - Okay.
In middle school, she began training with my team.
That was when she came to know me.
I went to train in middle school.
The back of his head looked so cute.
- The back of his head? - The back of his head?
The back of his head looked like Dooly.
- I guess it's round. - Yes.
The back of his head looked so cute.
He was very skinny compared to me.
He was like scallion kimchi with his big head.
I just thought there was someone who looked like scallion kimchi.
- But he kept contacting me. - He made a move...
- on you. - Yes.
I expressed my interest.
- How did you do that? - How did you express your interest?
We couldn't meet up when we were students,
so I contacted her through Cyworld.
- Cyworld. - I haven't heard that in a while.
You could follow each other by being "Relatives."
- You followed her, left comments, - Yes.
- and reposted her posts. - Yes.
After exercising, I logged on to an instant messaging program...
- You did that. - to see if she was logged on.
- Right. You could see that. - You could see that.
- Right. There was a function... - Yes.
Like that in such websites.
- I did that. - Then you guys go years back.
Yes. It has been about 21 years.
- I've known her for 21 years. - Yes.
You've known her for 21 years. You've been married for 5 years.
(They've spent more than half of their lives together.)
(They decided to spend the remainder of their lives together as well.)
What does Bo Ram say the most?
She calls my name.
Usually, she goes, "Honey."
- She calls you "Honey." - When I've done something wrong,
she goes, "Yong Ji."
Bo Ram, how do you call him?
When disappointment piles up,
- I go, "Yong Ji." - Hold on.
- That was different. - That was so different.
- "Yong Ji." - I get it.
- That was so different. - I get it.
Yong Ji, what do you say the most?
"How much is it?"
- This should be edited out. - Why?
- Why? - Why?
- Are you criticizing him? - In the story we read...
Right. Now that you're married, you can't do the things...
- you've wanted to do. - What can't you do these days?
Firstly, we can't go to nice restaurants.
We do now!
- Don't you dine out? - You don't dine out.
We rarely dine out.
Dining out isn't...
- It isn't important to him. - That's right.
If I've lived diligently for 20 days of the month,
I want to relax for two days by going to the beach...
or eating something tasty.
It's nothing big, really. It's nothing big, isn't it?
I told him one time, "We don't need to go anywhere."
- "Let's just go for a drive." - That's right.
My husband said,
"How about the gas price? Gas is too expensive."
He is really against any unnecessary expenditures.
- It wasn't about the gas price. - Okay.
I just ended up saying that.
- You'd know since you're married. - Right.
I'm the head of the household.
I've lived that way. So...
- Such words are hurtful. - Exactly.
- Thank you. - The comment he made just now...
- I see. - is so hurtful.
- You know... - Still, he could look after her.
You know, they say...
a soft answer turns away wrath.
- Boo. - Seriously.
- Boo. - You know...
- Boo. - Yong Ji.
We're making an effort to find the middle ground.
- Thank goodness. - That's what marriage is about.
That's what marriage is about.
I'm the only married man in this group,
- so let me tell you this. - Okay.
- All married couples do that. - You're right.
How do you spend the weekends?
On the weekends...
- You're sighing too much. - We eat tasty food.
Hold on. On the weekends...
Hold on. Why are you so nervous?
You keep trying to stop her.
- By her side, you keep... - Why are you so nervous?
You must order something like fried chicken or chicken feet.
We eat them.
- We eat them. - I...
He wasn't asking you, Yong Ji.
- Go ahead. - You know,
in the beginning of 2026,
- a beautiful baby came to us. - Gosh, congratulations.
Yes. The fetus name is Jelly.
- Jelly. - When I want to eat something,
he lets me order 2 deliveries per week for the 1st time.
- He isn't so stingy anymore. - No, I'm not. I'm trying not to be.
On the other hand, I understand Yong Ji's stance.
- He wants to save up money. - Yes.
- It's for the family. - It's for the two of us.
That's right. It's for the future.
- I understand both perspectives. - That's right.
Who applied for Whenever Possible?
I did.
What was the reason?
- This was the reason. - She was suffocating.
- She wanted to let it all out. - She wanted to talk about this.
- This is a good opportunity. - She wanted to talk about this.
When you and your spouse talk alone,
you seem to lack objectivity.
- But when others agree, - That's right.
- he might accept things easily. - That's right.
Yong Ji, compared to when you were playing badminton,
you look skinnier.
- He looks more haggard. - He is becoming skinnier.
Aside from what I've said, he is perfect.
He is very nice.
Seriously, I...
- Despite everything... - You told us that he was nice.
Bo Ram, did you invite us here to do this?
- I mean... - We get that he is nice.
He is nice.
- He takes good care of himself. - He takes good care of himself.
He only takes care of himself.
- So... - Hold on.
- I mean... - You can complain more.
- Seriously. - We can't do anything.
- "He only takes care of himself." - "He only takes care of himself."
He only takes care of himself, but he is nice.
I could really save up money...
- after marrying him. - He is diligent.
- Yes, he is diligent. - Seriously.
- I love him. - Right.
Yong Ji, how about you?
- Firstly, she is pretty. - Right.
I married her because she was pretty.
When I look back on it, I'm the most thankful...
for how she has adjusted to my ways despite being different.
She has adjusted to my ways...
in order to live together.
That explains how you've been married...
- for five years. - That's right.
For Bo Ram...
- and Jelly, - That's right.
- we want to finish Round Three... - For Jelly.
Successfully today.
- I'll roll it. - Okay.
We need bonus coupons.
- Please. - The two of them are athletes.
(The last spare time of this season)
Where will it stop?
(How many bonus coupons will they get?)
- Two! - Two!
(They get 2 bonus coupons.)
(The golden hand, Bo Young did well.)
- Bo Young is on fire today. - Yes.
- Thank you. - Yes.
We have two bonus tries.
I hope we succeed in it.
- Let's check the Round 1 prize 1st. - Okay.
"It's my dream to eat at a nice restaurant..."
"with my husband who cares a lot about what's cost-effective."
"Hotel buffet dinner for two."
(Round 1 prize, Hotel buffet dinner for 2)
- That's perfect. - It's exactly what they need.
- It's free! - That's perfect.
The hotel for this coupon is nearby.
- It's nearby. - It's in Jamsil.
- Bo Ram's face lit up. - It's for a special occasion.
- Bp Ram, do you like it? - Yes.
We need to succeed in this round.
The prize is for two people,
but Jelly can eat as well.
(2 servings that are like 3 servings!)
(Gift certificate for hotel buffet dinner)
(The last mission of this season)
(Shuttlecock Poke!)
(Hit shuttlecocks with a badminton racket...)
(to knock over the targets.)
(Round 1)
(The time limit is 30 seconds and the number of shuttlecocks is 10.)
We need to hit the targets.
Hit the targets?
You know,
- thank goodness we got two. - Listen.
- We're confident. - Yes.
Besides, we have the two of them.
- Exactly. - We have bonus tries.
It's hard to hit the targets.
- We have bonus tries. - We have two bonus tries.
- Each guest can go. - That's right.
Those are the targets.
It won't be easy.
The 2 of you should take turns joining in for 1 of the tries.
Like this.
(Yeon Seok practices first.)
- There you go. - He is good.
That's better.
(It isn't easy to aim.)
- A few more. - Bo Young, hit a few of them.
- The direction is... - To the right.
Hit it to the right. Don't throw it.
- I don't think I can do it. - Hit it in front of your face.
- Hold on. - Get some rest.
You aren't good with your body, are you?
- Oh, no. - Bo Young, get some rest.
You want to hit it and send it to the right,
- Bo Young. - but you keep throwing it.
You aren't good with your body.
You should not let the ball fly so high.
(A few tries are enough to show how unathletic she is.)
Don't give up. You're just tired.
- This is hard. - They need to aim well.
- It'll hit the target as it falls. - It won't be easy.
We haven't hit the targets once.
(Jae Seok practices the backhand drive.)
That won't have enough strength.
The targets won't get knocked over.
It got knocked over!
- You can hit it lightly. - It gets knocked over easily.
- Is this more accurate? - Shall I do this?
This is a serve you do in doubles.
- It has higher accuracy. - Really?
It's more accurate.
Like this?
But it lacks strength.
It'll get knocked over if you hit it.
It lacks strength.
All right. Let's go for Round One.
Let's do a cheer first.
- Let's go. In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's begin right away. - Shall we begin?
- I'll do 3. - I'll do 3.
- Let's go. - You guys can do two each.
- Okay. Here I go. - When will you go?
- I'll go last. - Okay.
- Ready. - I'll help you.
- Set. - Hold one.
(1st try)
Jae Seok, you'll get one.
- Gosh. - You'll get it this time.
- Gosh. - Hit one more.
(He is out of 3 shuttlecocks.)
Go.
(The 2nd player is worried.)
(1st try)
- I don't know what to do. - Kwang Soo, go in there.
Hit it hard.
- Go in there. - Go.
Come on.
What should I do?
- All right. - Go.
(The 3rd player, Kwang Soo)
What should I do?
Okay.
(1st try)
All right.
- Hit it hard. - The last one.
(The last player, Yeon Seok has 3 shuttlecocks.)
- All right. - Don't do that.
Grab the cock head.
- For goodness' sake. - One more.
Had I taken out one...
(Crying)
Seriously. Had I taken out one...
(Had I taken out one before he went...)
Seriously, this mission is hard.
You've tried it, right?
Why are you doing it now?
Jae Seok!
I'm doing a better job now that I'm angry.
Things work better when you're angry.
He does well during practice.
Shall I hit it from the side?
That didn't work.
When the swing becomes long, the shuttlecock goes to the side.
That's right. Go, "It's hot."
- "It's hot." - What's "It's hot?"
Hit it as if it's hot.
(Hit it quickly as if it's hot.)
- It's hot. - It's hot.
It was a good aim.
- It flew close to the box. - This is hard.
(Really?)
It's hot.
- That's right. - The shuttlecock is closer.
- The shuttlecock is closer. - It's hot.
It's hot.
(That's it.)
- I see. - Jae Seok, don't push it.
Keep the contact brief.
(I see!)
That isn't it.
I'll keep the contact brief.
(She begins to practice hard by herself.)
It's hot.
(Laughing)
(Snorting)
It's hot.
(After the rigorous...)
(It's Hot Practice, )
(it's time for the performance review.)
That's right. Keep it brief.
- Hit it upward. - A bit upward.
- A bit upward. Be confident. - Okay.
I think I should sit out.
It's hot.
Nice.
(She finally hit it!)
- That's it. - Well done.
That's good. We're nearly there.
It'll suddenly work.
- Here we go. - Here we go.
Let's use a bonus coupon if we fail this time.
It's very difficult.
- It'll be hard for us too. - I don't think I can do it either.
- Seriously. - Here we go.
- Here we go. - This is the third try.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(3rd try)
- Gosh. Hold on. - My goodness.
Slowly.
(3rd try)
- Just one. - That's good. Slowly. That's it.
Ready.
That's good.
- We got this. - Hit it one more time.
- Hurry up. - No.
- Go. - One more.
Just one.
Seriously.
Okay.
Just one.
Hey.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
Hit just one.
(Jae Seok is the 3rd player.)
Hit just one, Jae Seok.
Gosh.
Go ahead.
- Just one. - Go.
- Gosh. - Five,
four, three,
- Two, - two...
Take this!
(Take this!)
(She shouted again.)
- It's too hard. - Seriously.
- It's too hard. - It's extremely hard.
- It's too hard. - How is it so hard?
This won't do. One of them should enter.
- Let's use a bonus coupon. - Let's use one.
- One of you will join. - Kwang Soo, move.
You'll replace one member.
- Okay. - I'll sit out.
I'll sit out.
- Okay. - I need to sit out.
Come on in.
Bo Ram, have you done this before?
I was...
on "Life Experts."
- Were you on the show? - Really?
- Really? - Yes.
- Yes. - Why didn't you tell us before?
Why didn't you tell us that you were a life expert?
We got this.
- We got this. Bo Ram, try it. - I mean...
(It was 5 years ago.)
(She starred in the show in 2021 as a badminton expert.)
It's the most useful defensive drill.
On the mark,
she puts the shuttlecock right inside the cup.
(It's an incredible trick.)
(Not only that...)
What we need to focus on is...
(Hitting a quail egg between chicken eggs)
(Before marriage, Yong Ji starred in the show as a colleague.)
She swings the racket with all her might.
The shuttlecock that flew at an incredible speed...
hit the quail egg with accuracy.
(She hit the quail egg as well.)
(The best and golden bonus coupon in the history of the show)
We can give her all the shuttlecocks.
If a life expert fails...
We can give her seven shuttlecocks.
- We can do one each. - That sounds good.
Bo Ram, you can hit seven shuttlecocks.
- Let me practice. - You're a life expert.
- Practice all you want. - Let me practice.
Let me practice.
We got this.
The way she does it feels different.
- She should've done this earlier. - That means...
she is a family member of SBS.
How did it go between the boxes?
I know. What should I do?
- I know. What should I do? - Shall we put the boxes together?
- Shall we do that? - Hold on.
(A sneaky member appears.)
- Can we do that? - We can't do that.
- We can't put the boxes together. - We can't do that.
Can't we do that?
- They aren't touching. - We can't do that.
Come on.
What?
- They aren't touching. - Seriously.
(They go back to how they were.)
It's so tricky.
They're adjusting them again.
It's different.
- I can't hit the targets. - Hit from the bottom.
- From the bottom? - Yes.
The shuttlecock will go up.
(Lee Bo Ram, the expert of badminton tricks)
After the onlooker's exclamation...
How do they keep going so close to the boxes?
- The height... - She got it.
(She zeroed in!)
(Assisting the life expert)
Bo Ram.
I got this.
(She serves with one hand!)
(Her secret gets revealed little at a time!)
Shall we begin right away?
Life expert.
Oh, no.
Jelly's mom will challenge herself.
- We can take one shuttlecock each. - That's right.
Bo Ram can take seven.
Okay.
All right. Hold on. Are there 6? There are 7, right?
Yes. This is the seventh one.
Good luck.
(We're in your care, Jelly's mom!)
- Here I go! - Ready.
Life expert.
Oh, no.
(Bonus try)
- You have enough time. - Okay.
She did it!
(She knocked out both targets by herself!)
Okay!
(A problem solver has appeared.)
(Cheering)
She is a life expert.
"Life Experts."
I got goosebumps.
She didn't disappoint.
How did she...
This life expert still has it!
(Her husband is proud as well.)
- Wait. - SBS is the best!
Round One was...
- a success. - A success.
(Round 1 was a success.)
This life expert still has it!
(They acquire the gift certificate for the hotel buffet dinner!)
She really is a life expert.
- That was the best. - Seriously,
- she is cool. - We don't need the presents.
(He feels like they've achieved everything.)
She knocked out both of them once she zeroed in.
- Seriously. - We have one more bonus coupon.
We have one more bonus coupon.
Let's use it at the end...
- in case we do badly. - Let's use it at the end.
Let's do that.
- All right. - That was thrilling.
- We have many tries left. - We're on the third try.
Decide whether to keep going or stop.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Go! - Go!
There are a lot of chances left.
This time...
"Both the pregnant wife..."
"and the husband with a foot injury want to clean the house easily."
"A robot vacuum."
(Round 2 prize, a robot vacuum)
- A robot vacuum is much needed. - A robot vacuum?
(It's a must for the busy couple.)
- We need it. - Seriously.
All right. What's Round Two?
(Round 2)
(The targets are smaller.)
- Exactly. - Will they be Pepero boxes?
I'm completely useless.
- What am I going to do? - We need to get lucky.
They're so small.
It's the same for us.
In the end,
- we'll rely on the bonus coupon. - That's right.
If we succeed in this round quickly,
we can use...
- the bonus coupon in Round Three. - That's right.
- That'll be better. - We can do that.
- That'll be better. - They might stop after this round.
In Round Three, we'll get the Pepero boxes.
- Let's practice. - Here is what I think.
Judging by Yong Ji's style,
he'll stop at Round Two.
(Did he get caught?)
- What are you saying? - That's his style.
I think he is planning...
- to stop at Round Two. - Okay.
(We're in your care.)
I'll send it upward.
(Yeon Seok begins to practice in a sitting position.)
(He succeeds in it in one go.)
- That's good. - Let's begin right away.
- Let's begin. - I think he'll succeed in it.
It'll be incredible if he does.
(He hits it again!)
Yeon Seok, I think you got the hang of it.
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
- Let's go. - Let's do a cheer for Round Two.
- Please. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
I'll go first.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
- Yeon Seok needs to hit it. - I'll take four shuttlecocks.
Here I go.
(He loads up 4 shuttlecocks.)
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
(4th try)
The shuttlecocks go near the boxes now.
Next.
(The 2nd player, Kwang Soo has 3 shuttlecocks.)
(4th try)
- Bo Young. - Three remain.
- It's doable. - Three shuttlecocks.
Ten seconds remain.
- Slowly. - Jae Seok, you have time.
You have enough time.
- Five, four, - Hit one.
- three... - Gosh.
Oh, no.
(They fail without hitting any of the boxes.)
- It's too hard. - It's okay.
I can tell that it's the last mission.
Jae Seok, let's use a bonus coupon.
- Hold on. - Already?
- We can't use it now. - No?
It'll be difficult for us to succeed in Round Three...
- by ourselves. - Once we get past Round Two...
This is driving me crazy.
Let's try it once more.
- But this is... - Like this?
I'll aim like this.
- All right. - That's good.
Everyone is improving.
- They're getting the hang of it. - Hit it more gently.
A bit upward.
- A bit more. - You'll hit it.
A bit more upward.
About 5cm upward.
There you go. A bit more.
- You're nearly there. - Zero in.
Hit it with a bit more force.
- Hit it with more force. - A bit like this.
It's hot! Do it before we put something hot in your hand for real.
It's hot!
- It's hot! - It's hot!
- One more time. - You did well just now.
- Yes. - It's hot!
- No! - My goodness.
It's hot.
- It's hot. - There you go.
- There you go. Keep going. - You got this.
She is exhausted.
Keep going.
It's like Taereung Training Center. It's so scary.
It's hot!
- No! - Get some rest.
(Coach Kwang explodes.)
It's hot!
Imagining that you're touching something hot.
- That's so funny. - Is this Taereung Training Center?
I bet athletes don't train this hard at the training center.
Seriously, I feel like I'm at the training center.
(Refilling the shuttlecocks)
We've hit multiple boxes of shuttlecocks.
We've hit two boxes.
We've never practiced this hard.
(Practicing by himself)
- We're training hard. - Let's train hard.
Jae Seok needs to train hard.
Jae Seok, you need to train hard. You need to do well.
- You're training hard. - It's hot!
(He hits the target!)
Jae Seok, stay still.
Stop. Stay still.
- Jae Seok, let's begin. - Let's begin.
- All right. - Here we go.
- Do it like that. Don't move. - Here we go.
- Three. - You can take three.
- Here we go! - Here we go!
- Ready. Set. - They can do it.
(6th try)
- Move a bit forward. There. - Forward.
(For goodness' sake!)
(It brushed past the box.)
- Hit one more. Take mine. - You never know.
Hit one of Kwang Soo's.
(Jae Seok takes out one target!)
- One more. - Hurry up.
Calm down, Kwang Soo.
Calm down.
Oh, no.
Bo Young.
One more.
A bit lower! It's hot!
It's hot.
- One more. - Come on.
- How many shuttlecocks remain? - Ten seconds.
- How many? Two? - My hands feel hot.
(2 shuttlecocks remain.)
Five, four,
(The last one!)
three...
Please.
- Please. - Three...
(Failed)
What are we going to do?
I'm so devastated.
It's so difficult.
- Seriously. - It's so...
It's impossible.
I'll take badminton lessons after this.
- Seriously. - She'll take them for real.
- She'll take them for real. - Seriously.
This won't do. It'll be hard to go home feeling this way.
I don't think we'll be able to succeed in Round Three.
Succeeding in Round Three...
- It won't be easy. - won't be easy.
At this point...
(Brief silence falls.)
(Glancing over)
Shall we use it?
- Let's use it. - Let's use a bonus coupon.
Bo Ram should step forward.
- We'll use a bonus coupon. - We'll use a bonus coupon.
I'm sure it puts a lot of pressure on her.
(She is the savior who'll save them from the netherworld of failures.)
Well, let's do our best.
She can take seven shuttlecocks.
Take seven.
Our life expert.
Please stare at the person who should sit out.
(Chuckling)
(Coach Kwang sits out.)
Bo Young, Yeon Seok, and me.
- We'll take shuttlecock each. - Okay.
We'll take one each.
We need to succeed in it this time.
Let's go!
- Let's go! - Good luck!
This is our chance.
It'll be hard for us to complete Round Two if we fail this time.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - Let's go!
The order will be Bo Young, me, and Yeon Shik.
- Then you'll hit seven. - Will I be able to do it?
I always hope...
- Here we go. - that I'll hit the target.
Bo Young, you'll take off much pressure if you knock out one.
(Bonus try)
(If they fail this time, success will be impossible.)
I really want to succeed in it.
Ready. Set.
(Bonus try)
- I have no luck. - Just one.
For goodness' sake.
(Even Jae Seok fails to hit it.)
(Nervous)
Just one.
- It isn't like that. - But time...
- It's my turn, right? - It's your turn.
Life expert.
(It's the life expert's turn.)
(Bonus try)
One.
(She takes out 1 target in 2 tries.)
(She has 5 shuttlecocks left while 1 target remains.)
Jelly.
(Please take out one more target!)
(It got knocked out!)
(She succeeds in it by herself!)
I did it!
(Jelly's mom did it!)
(Jelly, did you see it?)
As soon as she called for Jelly...
- Jelly. - Our life expert didn't disappoint.
Our life expert didn't disappoint.
- Nice. - She didn't disappoint.
- She didn't disappoint. - How does it feel?
- No way. - Jelly helped us.
- Round Two was a success. - A success.
A robot vacuum.
(Happy)
She really is a life expert.
- She is different. - She is different.
She hit 2 targets with 3 shuttlecocks.
Seriously.
She really is a life expert.
- We'll never be able to do that. - Although...
the 8th, 9th, and 10th tries remain...
- Right. While that's the case... - Three tries remain.
But the difficulty level... Yes.
The difficulty level will increase.
- Okay. - So please think about it.
- All right. - Stop.
- They're wise. - Seriously.
- They're so wise. - They're wise.
- They're wise. - But...
- I'm a bit upset. - No.
- Why are you upset? - I'm not upset.
- They readily went, "Stop." - I...
They don't trust us to do well.
They have zero expectations.
It's understandable.
It's the first time in the history...
of Whenever Possible to clear all the targets...
and succeed in the mission.
(In Round 1, she knocked out 2 consecutive targets.)
(In Round 2)
(she knocked out both targets with Jelly's strength!)
- That has never happened. - Seriously.
- We didn't succeed in it. - We didn't succeed in it.
We didn't succeed in it.
Bo Ram succeeded in it.
If Bo Young hadn't given us...
two bonus coupons...
- This would've ended badly. - Seriously.
We would've failed.
- Bo Young helped us. - Thank goodness.
- We sincerely congratulate you. - Okay.
(The three of them succeeded in having a buffet date.)
"Gold Land."
It feels great because I've had some success today.
I'm very happy to see them receiving the presents.
I'm relieved.
- I was on the very first episode, - Exactly.
So it felt very nice to be on the last episode of Season Four.
Please invite me back sometime.
Please give a lot of attention to "Gold Land..."
that'll be revealed on April 29.
Congratulations.
Yeon Seok and I...
- Yes. - will be back...
- after a break. - Yes.
- I can't wait for the next season. - I know.
Until then, please don't forget about us...
- and stay healthy. Thank you. - That's right.
Viewers who watched Whenever Possible,
many guests who joined us,
the production crew members,
and many people who shared their spare time with us,
we sincerely thank you.
We'll return next season.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for sharing your spare time with us.)
Thank you.