My gosh.
It's warm enough to stay outdoors now.
It's spring.
- Spring has come.
- Gosh, it's spring.
So we're in Jongno.
- Changsin-dong.
This is Changsin-dong past Dongdaemun.
- Yes.
We've never opened our show from Changsin-dong before.
I haven't been in the back of Changsin-dong for a while.
Twenty dollars.
Here in Changsin-dong,
I can hear the guy shouting from the truck.
I keep hearing him trying to sell some goods.
Right. Here's another thing. I haven't seen this sign in a while.
The sign that said they were buying gold teeth.
But hearing that makes this place feel a bit homey.
- Yes, that's right.
- Right.
Back in the day, I used to wake up...
to the sound of the truck and the vendor shouting...
- when I wanted to sleep in.
- Yes. They were selling something.
They used to sell hairtails, vegetables,
- and fruits.
- Gosh.
There used to be a lot of trucks like that.
- While my journey here - While my journey here.
(Mysterious singing fills the alley after the truck passes by.)
This is Changsin-dong. Have you been here before?
- No, I've rarely been here.
- I was born here.
- Really? Here in Changsin-dong?
- Yes.
- I don't think...
- I've traveled here before.
- Right?
- I'll show you around.
- Okay.
We're starting right away.
- They're here.
- It's Jun Sang.
(Chuckling)
- Jun Sang, hello.
- Hey.
- It's been a while.
- Hello.
- Hey, Son Myeong O.
- It's been so long.
- Gun Woo.
Gun Woo.
- Jae Seok!
- Okay.
- Gangnam Yu. Let's go.
- Yes, Jun Sang.
Gosh, Jun Sang.
(You...)
(Do you know me?)
(Bang Gwi Nam, the national husband from "My Husband Got a Family")
(Lee Pung Sang, the most pitiful man from "Liver or Die")
(He always nailed his character in all of his projects.)
(He can pull off the action scenes...)
(with a physique that defies time.)
(The flawless actor with 30 years of experience)
(An all-rounder who has also dominated the musical scene)
(Actor Yu Jun Sang)
(What a coincidence.)
(He left a strong impression in "The Glory" as Son Myeong O.)
(He's the same guy.)
(There's no limit to the characters he can portray.)
(Actor Kim Gun Woo)
- Sit here.
- Okay.
It's been a decade since I last saw you, Jun Sang.
- It hasn't been a decade.
- Last time...
"Happy Together" was our last show, right?
- Has it been that long?
- "Happy Together?"
"Happy Together" was our last show.
- It's been so long then.
- On TV...
You haven't invited me to your shows this long?
- My gosh. It's so nice to see you.
- Jun Sang...
performs in musicals too.
- Right.
- So he talks like he's in one.
- Yes.
I've never met Gun Woo before.
- You haven't?
- I haven't.
- Really?
- Yes.
It must be because of the character he played, Son Myeong O.
- So he has a kind face.
- He's... Right.
- He has such a kind face.
- Right.
I've gained weight too.
- You've gained weight?
- Yes, I think so.
You look very slim.
But I gained about 4 to 5kg.
- I see.
- Did you gain weight on purpose?
A lot of people told me I looked better with some weight.
They can't easily forget...
- your character from "The Glory."
- That's why?
- Right. I think so.
- I see.
Did you recently work on a project with Gun Woo?
- Before...
- Yes.
- we talk about our project, - Okay.
Let me ask you this. Do you know this neighborhood?
- It's Changsin-dong.
- Changsin-dong.
- Right.
- Did you grow up here?
I used to live here when I was a kid.
- I see.
- I was also born here.
- This is your hometown.
- It's Changsin-dong.
- You were also born here?
- I was.
- I see.
- I lived here until fourth grade.
- You grew up here.
- Until fourth grade.
Let me tell you who else lived here.
Paik Nam June.
(His old house was renovated into a memorial hall.)
And Park Su Geun.
Kim Kwang Seok also lived here from what I know.
- He lived here?
- He did.
- Many famous writers and artists...
- Right.
- lived around this neighborhood.
- Artists. Yes.
- Most importantly, - Yes.
There was a man named Kim Sang Ok.
- Okay.
He was a Korean independence activist.
He threw a bomb at Jongno Police Station...
against the Japanese policemen.
He kept one bullet left in his gun.
"Long live Korean independence." Then he shot himself.
That's why I have huge pride...
- You have pride.
- in this neighborhood.
But this neighborhood is slowly dying.
- I've been trying...
- Yes.
To save this neighborhood by attracting attention.
- You've been trying?
- Yes.
Well, that's the thing about him. He's...
Wait, where do you live now?
Bundang.
- That's a newly developed city.
- Shouldn't a resident...
Given how much you love this neighborhood,
shouldn't you live here?
- Seriously.
- So...
- He seems to love Changsin-dong.
- But...
- But hear me out.
- It's a historical place. I get it.
- After coming here...
- At least, he could live...
- in Jongno if not Changsin-dong.
- How did they pick this place?
I was so surprised.
- You were born here.
- Right.
And you're very proud of this neighborhood.
Besides, there are so many cool places...
- in Changsin-dong.
- Yes.
I really hope this neighborhood continues on.
- You know what?
- Yes.
Things don't always go as we hope.
I hope we can preserve this neighborhood...
while renovating the buildings.
- I agree. Right.
- The buildings become so modern.
Only the guys in their 40s and 50s who are interested in real estate...
Gun Woo doesn't seem so interested.
- How old are you?
- I turned 36 this year.
- You should start paying attention.
- You're still in your 30s?
- Pardon?
- Yes.
- He looks like he's in his 30s.
Really? We're playing friends in our musical.
- What's the musical about?
- It's about...
a Korean independence activist.
Have you heard of Yuhan Corporation?
- Of course. Yu Il Han.
- Yes.
- Yu Il Han.
We adapted his life story into a musical.
- It's called "Swing Days."
- "Swing Days."
- Sang Hun is in the musical?
- He said he'd be in it too.
(In 1945 during the Japanese colonial era, )
(a secret intelligence operation for the Korean independence began.)
(Yu Il Hyeong, a key figure who participates in the operation)
(Yasuo, a Japanese officer who opposes the activists)
(Hwang Man Yong, Il Hyeong's friend and partner)
(An original musical about Dr. Yu Il Han's Napko Project...)
(during the Japanese colonial era)
I'm playing Dr. Yu Il Han.
And he's playing Colonel Yasuo who was forced to change his name.
- So you're playing the villain.
- Yes.
You guys are friends,
- but chose different paths.
- We chose different paths.
- Because of the war.
- Right.
So you're supposed to be friends?
(Getting upset)
- Should I do a leg split?
- So...
- What should I do?
- No.
Gun Woo. Have you performed in musicals before?
This is my fourth musical.
- He's been in many musicals.
- You've done many musicals.
I started performing in musicals not long ago.
This is my second musical with Jun Sang.
Once I began performing in musicals, I did one every year.
- So it's my fourth musical now.
- My gosh.
- It's your fourth one.
- Yes.
But I'm still a mu-kie. It hasn't been that long.
- A musical rookie.
- A mu-kie.
- I didn't know about that word.
Actually, Yeon Shik performed...
- in musicals too.
- I've been in musicals too.
- He performed in many musicals.
- Gosh, no. Not really.
That's impressive.
I don't think I'm a mu-kie.
- You're not.
- But I still am.
Aren't you a mu-ran?
- What...
- A musical veteran?
- Don't shorten everything.
- What?
- A mu-kie...
- That didn't sound right.
He's a musical rookie. So you're a musical veteran.
What's Jun Sang then? A mu-dad?
- A mu-dad.
- He's a mu-dad.
Anyway, Jun Sang and Gun Woo are joining us today.
Let's get started.
- Let's go.
- You know what I think?
- Jun Sang is an enthusiastic guy.
- Right.
- Here...
- If you don't want me...
to be enthusiastic, I won't be.
- No, you should be.
- Should I be?
- You should be.
- Okay.
- You're the son of Changsin. Yes.
- The son of Changsin-dong.
"Kwon Yu Bin and Kim Ji Hoon."
"My husband begins his day when the sun sets."
"I've been preparing for summer since early spring."
"We're working hard as we live out of sync with time and seasons."
"The owner of a cafe we frequent thinks we're unemployed."
"We'd like to reveal our jobs on Whenever Possible."
- But...
- The cafe owner thinks...
they're unemployed.
Do they work together?
I guess they're always together.
We have to go to Gwanghui-dong.
I guess we need some kind of transportation.
- Oh, right. There is...
- Changsin-dong...
this old lady who's been running...
- a tteokbokki stall for 50 years.
- We should go there.
We should go. Let's go.
- Since we're here...
- You want to see her. Sure.
- Tteokbokki is great too.
- Do we have time, though?
- Yes.
- We do.
- We have to be there by noon.
- Let's drop by.
- We have time.
- I'm not sure if she's open.
Yeon Seok, you're not from the Myogeumdo clan, right?
- Wait, he's not a Yoo.
- He's not.
- He's an Ahn.
- Yes, I'm an Ahn.
I know that. Right.
The Yoo clan did invite me to some kind of event.
That was a long time ago.
That's so funny.
Right, about 11 years ago,
I came to this neighborhood.
My old house...
Do you see that hill?
- Really?
- I used to live there.
Do the alleys still remind you...
- of your childhood?
- Yes, they do.
- Really?
- But my old house was gone.
So I wrote a song called "To My Birthplace."
- Really?
- I released an album too.
- He keeps releasing songs.
- "To My Birthplace."
It's over there somewhere.
- Over there?
- Yes.
Gosh, it's such a narrow street.
It's an alley in the market.
Crazy, right?
This place is amazing.
Look.
It's so fascinating that it looks exactly like the old days.
- Right.
- It's incredible, right?
- Hello.
All right. This is the alley.
("To My Birthplace" by Yu Jun Sang)
- This is the alley.
- The bread looks good too.
(The place where I grew up)
The rib restaurant here.
Sir!
Jun Sang, look for the tteokbokki stall now.
Look at the rib restaurant.
The ribs...
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm just dropping by.
- Find the tteokbokki stall.
- We're here. All right.
- Is this the place?
-Ma'am.
Ma'am, I'm here.
Hello. My gosh.
- You're open.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- You look familiar.
- Yes.
So you recognize him, but not me?
Right. He always promotes the vitamin brand.
- Why didn't you do more than that?
- My gosh, seriously.
This is Gun Woo.
- And this is Yeon Seok.
- I'm Yoo Yeon Seok.
Jun Sang is on our show today.
You look better than the last time.
- I look better?
- Yes.
I've gotten prettier now that I'm a year older.
(Chuckling)
- Look at the color.
- Gosh.
That looks so good.
Oh, my. Look at the color.
(A vibrant color)
- I want to try the fishcake broth.
- Three dollars. One serving.
No. Don't pay.
- Give us one serving, please.
- No. Just take a skewer and eat it.
- No. We'll order one serving.
- Right.
- We should have some.
- We'll try some.
You don't have to.
- We want to try it.
- I don't have to sell it to you.
- Ma'am. We want to taste some food.
Then just eat it.
- But still. Give us one serving.
- Eat it already.
- I want to try some sundae too.
- Gosh.
- The fishcakes too.
- I want to eat some food.
- No.
- Sundae too.
So...
It's not that, ma'am.
That looks good. It's old-school...
- tteokbokki.
- Seriously.
I said you didn't have to.
- Have a taste then.
- Okay.
- Try it.
- Try it. Her food is great.
(The frown of the truth)
- It's good.
- Thank you.
It's the perfect tteokbokki from the market.
You have to get it at the market.
- It's nice and bouncy.
- Yes.
(It's so good that it leaves them in awe.)
It's nice and sweet.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Gosh.
You know what?
It's so good.
It's better with the tteokbokki sauce.
Yes, you can do that.
- Let me give you a bit more.
- Gosh, no.
All right then.
The cameramen never get to have some food.
Right.
Try it. It's so good.
(He wants to introduce her tteokbokki.)
- It's good, right?
- It's so good.
(They end up having fishcakes too.)
- The tteokbokki is really good.
- Right?
- Aren't you happy we came?
- Yes.
- Ma'am, let us pay then.
- Thank you.
- No.
- Come on.
- You don't need to pay.
- We have to pay.
- You can promote my stall.
- Ma'am, take it.
- I won't take it.
- First customers must pay.
- You must take it.
First customers must pay.
My goodness. You're driving me crazy.
Ma'am, I'll come back.
- Thank you. It was so good.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Sell a lot.
Thank you. I'll watch you on TV.
- Sure.
- Thank you for the food.
I'd love to eat some more with the fritters too.
- Gosh, seriously.
- You...
You're indeed the son of Changsin.
- You know all the alleys here.
- Once our episode airs,
more people will know that you're the son of Changsin.
- The son of Changsin.
- You know?
- We have to get on Bus 105.
- Bus 105.
(Navi Yoo is checking the route.)
Do you need help?
- No, it's okay. Bus 105 seems best.
- Okay.
We have to walk for seven minutes after we get off.
- Bus 105?
- Yes, Bus 105.
- That's the bus stop.
- Yes.
- The bus is here.
- It's here?
That's the one. Bus 105.
- Where?
- The traffic light...
- Wait.
Oh, no.
- Please.
- The traffic light...
Stop.
- I hope it hits a red light.
- Please stop.
- It stopped.
- It stopped. Wait.
We just need it to turn green. Why...
- It's green.
- We're good.
- We'll make it if we run.
- Bus 105.
- We're good.
- We'll make it if we run.
Hello. Thank you.
We got on just in time.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Go ahead.
We got on just in time.
- We got on.
- That was some crazy timing.
- That was good timing.
We have to get off at Exit Eight of Dongdaemun Station.
- Dongdaemun Station. Yes.
- Exit Eight?
How many stops are we away?
We just need to go three stops.
What about your son, Dong Woo? Did he get discharged?
- Did he go back to school?
- Oh, he said...
he didn't want to go to college.
I told him to fulfill his military service. So he did.
- After his military discharge...
- He said he wanted to study now.
- So he's preparing...
- Yes. Kids want to study later on.
- Forcing them to go to college...
- Of course.
I mean, they don't want to study anything.
- The world is different now.
- My children are happy.
Their parents are stressed.
- My kids don't want to study.
- Right.
- But they're good kids.
- Of course.
Wait. Gun Woo, do you have any siblings?
I have an older sister.
- You do?
- Yes.
- Are you close to your sister?
- Yes, we're close.
- How many years are you apart?
- Really?
- A year. Yes.
- A year?
I can sort of see that.
You look like you'd be close to your sister.
Right. We resemble each other.
So she's got the short end of the stick.
- You guys resemble each other?
- Yes. We do.
She got the short end of the stick...
because they resemble each other.
(They arrive as they chat on the bus.)
- Let's get off.
- Okay.
- We have to cross there.
- There?
- Yes.
- Wait, where are we?
- Wait. Isn't this Daehak-ro?
- Let me tell you where we are.
Dongguk University is up on the hill.
- Here?
- Yes.
- If we walk that way, - Yes.
- we'll see Chungmu Arts Center.
- I see.
Over there.
What are we doing at Chungmu Arts Center?
- What?
- What's on at Chungmu Arts Center?
- "Swing Days."
- Okay.
(Promoting "Swing Days" whenever possible)
I see. This is close to DDP.
- Right. DDP is over there.
- There.
(Their first spare time is around DDP, the symbol of fashion streets.)
I didn't recognize the street for a second.
We're here.
It's the second floor of this building.
Where?
The second floor of the yellow-brick house.
Right here? Then we must enter from here.
- Is this the place?
- Let's go up.
Wait. My gosh.
- Hello.
- This is the place.
- Gosh, this place...
- Are you Yu Bin?
- That's me.
- Are you Ji Hoon?
- Yes.
- You also have a dog.
(Kwon Yu Bin, Kim Ji Hoon, Bok)
Is this a design studio?
We sell clothes...
at the Dongdaemun Wholesale Market.
(Then Whenever Guests are a married couple, selling clothes.)
At the Dongdaemun Wholesale Market.
So this is your office.
It's also our storage and meeting room.
There are so many shopping malls nearby.
- Right.
- Yes.
Where should we sit down to chat?
- Here.
- Right here.
I'll sit here.
What's your dog's name?
- Bok as in fortune.
- Bok?
- Yes.
Bok is quiet, by the way.
- Bok is so gentle.
- How beautiful.
- Right.
- What a gentle dog.
Look at Bok.
Bok is quietly sitting between you guys.
- Look at your gleaming eyes.
- Right.
Nice to meet you.
Jun Sang and Gun Woo are joining us today.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
You guys look like fashion models.
Right. They're also stylish.
- Right.
- Yes.
- You look so stylish and trendy.
- Right? Yes.
What do you guys usually do around this time of the day?
This is our day off.
It's our day off. We're off until Saturday.
And we start working on Sunday evening.
(A completely different schedule from that of office workers)
The market opens up late at night.
- Right.
- You guys rest in the morning.
- I see.
Actually, growing up, Dongdaemun was...
- It was a shopping mecca.
- Right.
(Back in the day, it used to be a shopping mecca.)
I used to shop around here when I was in college.
I would grab some tripe while shopping.
- Right.
- I'd get some tteokbokki too.
- I have many shopping memories.
And there are so many stores.
The best items from each store were different.
And at some stores, owners gave many discounts.
Bargaining for better deals was fun too.
There was an outdoor stage outside the shopping mall.
- Right.
- There was a stage, right?
I participated in the event when I was in college.
Did you dance on stage?
Yes. I participated for fun and ended up winning first place.
- Really?
- I won a prize.
- She must be a good dancer.
- What did you dance to?
- I was quite chubby back then.
- Okay.
The crowd told me to dance...
to "Tell Me" since I was cute.
But I said, "No. I'll dance to a sexy song." And I did it.
But it worked.
I even crawled on stage. So it worked.
- You did that?
- Yes.
For the first time, I won...
I can tell from her outfit.
- Right?
- She still has that cool vibe.
Thank you.
(Hesitant)
I used to work around Dongdaemun too.
Really? When?
- I...
- In the wholesale market?
Yes. I worked here when I was young.
I used to help out the merchants.
- You helped them sell clothes?
- Yes.
- You moved bags of clothes too?
My shift started at 10pm and ended at 10am the next day.
- It's not easy.
- I was a part-timer.
Before my military service,
I used to sell bags.
How was it? Were you considered a good worker?
- I'm quick with my hands and feet.
- Yes.
I got things done fast and got off work.
- I didn't get scolded.
- So...
- you finished your job?
- Yes.
(A good worker at Dongdaemun)
How's the clothing industry at Dongdaemun these days?
- Our customer base got smaller.
- Right.
We started our business when COVID-19 broke out.
- Really?
- Yes.
Everyone tried to talk us out of it.
We didn't think we would get another chance...
to run our own business if not then.
(When they began their business together)
(They began their business when everyone thought it was a bad time.)
I work during the day too.
(The wife is busy during the day as she begins working at 9am.)
(The wife is in charge of designing and holding meetings.)
I open the store at 8pm. That's when my shift begins.
I start working with another employee.
Then I grab a meal.
(He distributes clothes she designs across the country.)
I go to sleep late at night.
- Late at night?
- Yes.
(The couple works day and night with perfect teamwork.)
How long have you been running your business?
We've been running the business for about five years.
But I've been working around Dongdaemun for 14 years.
- Gosh, that's a long time.
- It's been about that long.
Then what about you?
After getting discharged from the military,
I've been working here ever since then.
- You've been working here.
- Yes.
What about you, Bok? How did you get here?
(How did you get here, Bok?)
- How many years has it been?
I think I can even interview Bok.
Bok is eight years old.
- Bok is on the older side.
- Yes.
You look younger than your age, Bok.
I brought Bok, so Bok can get some good energy.
Gosh, Bok looks so young.
- I can tell Bok is...
- Bok is sleepy.
Getting sleepy.
(Bok is trying so hard.)
There are so many people here.
(But Bok can't keep the eyes open.)
Bok must be sleepy.
Why don't you go in and take a nap?
(Pretending not to be sleepy)
How long have you been married?
It will be exactly three years...
- this May. Yes.
- Three years.
- We dated for a long time, though.
- I see.
We've been together for ten years.
- Did you meet here at Dongdaemun?
- Yes.
- While working here?
I didn't know I would end up marrying him.
Then, when you started dating him, you weren't serious...
- about him?
- He was just some guy...
who came to say hello at the store.
But he wouldn't say hello to me.
- He said hello to other workers.
- I see.
I thought, "Why is he so rude?" I seriously thought that.
The way you said it...
- Was it...
- You've got some skills.
- Right.
- So...
his face suddenly popped into my head.
Then late at night,
my co-worker gave my number...
to him without my knowledge.
That made me think if we were meant to be.
Why didn't you say hello to her? She said you were rude.
(Why didn't he say hello to her?)
- He must have liked her.
- It was...
- Like he got butterflies.
- In hindsight, I didn't say hi...
because I wanted her attention.
- To get her attention?
- Yes.
- I didn't say hi on purpose.
- In hindsight, you think so.
- Right.
- I see.
- "Is that what I wanted?"
- Right, perhaps.
I still remember this. She was working...
at the store while wearing red lipstick.
That was really cool. I mean, she looked so pretty.
"Cool?"
- I think he meant to say, "cool."
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- Like girl crush.
Girl crush.
I couldn't stop thinking about that scene.
You're together throughout the day. How's that going?
- We run our own business.
- I see.
- Right.
- He's very sensitive to sales.
Our mood is bound to fluctuate based on sales.
- Yes. But I don't let it affect me.
- Everyone's like that.
It doesn't matter how much we make together.
As long as we're together,
we can handle everything.
- Go on.
- But he thinks the opposite.
Let's say we only made 100 dollars. Then as soon as we come home,
he sighs like this. He won't even talk to me.
Let's say we sold a lot of clothes.
"Did you eat?" He'd be in a good mood.
- You know...
- He tries...
Your mood heavily depends...
- on the daily sales.
- My gosh.
- It varies a lot.
- It goes up and down.
But Bok is also a victim in this.
- Bok too?
- Yes.
When our sales are high, he does this. "Bok."
(He acts cute and gives a lot of snacks.)
You didn't have to do that.
- You didn't have to do that.
- Gosh.
(That's why Bok is hoping for strong sales.)
You must have been meant to be. You're running a business...
- together.
- Yes.
Anyway, we're here.
Like the name, Bok, we ought to share good fortune.
- We should.
- Yes.
Jun Sang is known for his enthusiasm.
- Let's go. Hey.
- Hey.
- What? It's one.
- One.
- One is good.
- It's good.
All right. Open it.
- This?
- The first one.
I'm nervous.
"Our daily outfit must also look cool."
"It will complete the outfit for the flawless look."
"Matching hats from R Brand."
Matching hats.
Matching hats from R Brand.
- This looks great on them.
- Yes, it looks great on them.
- It looks great on you.
- Yes.
(The matching hats are at stake on this mission.)
(Ping Pong with Rollers)
(They will hit the ping pong ball with a lint roller...)
(to knock the ball off the cone of yarn.)
(Round 1)
(The number of target balls, 2)
This is hard, Jun Sang.
- With this? Isn't it sticky?
- This one...
- It's not sticky.
- That's good.
So this is the stick.
This is hard. Come on.
The 4 of us complete this within 10 tries?
- Right.
- I see.
We'll split 10 balls and must do it in 30 seconds.
(They will get 10 balls and 30 seconds.)
Should I let it bounce?
- If it's over there...
- Wait.
Gosh, the direction...
- The direction...
- Come on.
The direction is off.
- Besides, the surface...
- Right.
- Yes.
- isn't flat.
- It's iffy.
- It won't go the way I want.
We have to hit it hard.
I'm usually good at this.
- The stick...
- It can shake?
We can't do it with this.
This is it.
I have to let it bounce once.
(Jae Seok tries it with a backhand push.)
This method is better.
This is better.
- Aim is better with this, right?
- It's better.
The cone of yarn... We can't hit the cone?
We can't hit the cone?
(He succeeds on his first try.)
What was that?
- I did it.
- Great.
- Jun Sang.
- Didn't I do it just now?
- Not now.
- No?
(He knocks down two balls in a row.)
Jun Sang...
- You should take three.
- He's the ace.
- Try it, Gun Woo.
- Okay.
- This is...
- You did it on your first try.
You might get hit. Are you guys going to be okay?
- Go easy.
- Will he hit it hard?
- This is...
- I'm awful at ping pong.
Try to hit the ball, at least.
- What?
- Wait.
(Gun Woo?)
You said you were quick with your hands and feet.
Wait.
- I'm not good, but I get lucky.
- He managed to hit it.
- Shouldn't this count?
- Okay.
(It's looking promising.)
This is amazing.
For our 1st try, you guys should take 3 balls.
- Yes. He and I will take 2.
- And he and I will take 2 balls.
Let's cheer.
Gather around.
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- The time limit is 30 seconds.
- Right.
Thirty seconds.
- Ready.
- What if I succeed in one go?
Ready. Set.
Here I go.
(1st try)
That was close.
(Hit slightly below)
(Second player, Jun Sang)
Here I go.
Oh, no.
It's tough when you actually try it.
Ten seconds left.
- Ten seconds.
- Hold on.
Goodness.
(Yeon Seok's 2 balls remain.)
- Game over.
- What...
(Failed due to using up all the balls)
Aren't the balls supposed to fly over?
(Making eye contact)
We failed. It's impossible when we actually try it.
Go ahead.
- Controlling your strength is...
- It doesn't feel like we tried.
- I've got it.
- Good.
(Jae Seok knocked down both balls.)
- It's around here.
- Go first.
- Go first when you've got it.
- Okay.
Try three balls.
Don't you need to practice?
No, give it a shot when you've got the hang of it.
- Let's cheer. In 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Start right away.
- Ready.
Set.
(2nd try)
That's it!
(He finished it immediately with just 2 balls!)
For real?
- I told you, didn't I?
- Right.
- See that?
- What has...
- What's up with me?
- gotten into you since last week?
- I've got goosebumps.
- Nice.
- What's up with me?
-What's up with you?
What's up with me?
That's it!
(A miracle in just 2.05 seconds)
(Messi of the actual try even today)
- Jae Seok.
- I know, right?
Jae Seok successfully made...
three hard shots in a row last week.
Two in a row.
And last week, three in a row.
(Feeling respect)
- How cool.
- Bravo.
How cool, Jae Seok.
When I said we should practice more, Jun Sang said,
"Go for it!"
- The timing was great.
- Totally.
It was amazing.
- All right.
- You've secured the matching hats.
Please decide whether to go or stop.
- No questions asked, it's a go.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
It's time to check Round Two's present.
- Two in a row...
- It was awesome.
"A fresh environment is needed in a workplace..."
"filled with dust from clothes."
- "D Brand air purifier."
- "Air purifier."
(Round 2 present: D Brand air purifier)
- Nice.
- Great.
- It's a nice one.
- The latest model.
- Gosh.
- It's the latest model.
I want it myself.
Gosh, that's...
- Come on, Gun Woo.
- My gosh.
- We must get it for them.
- Round Two present.
(Round 2)
(Target: 3 balls)
(One added target)
- Three balls.
- Three?
So that's Round Two.
You could hit 2 birds...
- with 1 stone.
- Right?
- True.
- Yes.
That's if you hit the ball.
I have a feeling we'll succeed in one go.
That surprised me.
(Successfully hit 2 birds with 1 stone)
- Good.
- I told you...
hitting 2 birds with 1 stone was possible.
Nice.
Even our guests are happy.
- We're on a roll today.
- Yes.
Right now...
(A feeling we'll succeed today)
Good. Try to find your "it" spot.
- Try it, Gun Woo.
- Gun Woo.
- Practice over here, not there.
- Okay.
(Gun Woo is still lost.)
- Gun Woo.
- Right.
Move together. Okay.
- Moving your body works.
- Nice.
I'm ready.
- Already?
- Then...
- What about me?
- You...
Just because you're doing well...
- Give me time to practice.
- Go ahead.
That hurts.
Sorry.
It's been a while since I've been treated like this.
All right, we're tight on schedule, okay?
- What...
- Go ahead.
(Putting on airs)
You won't make it today.
- Just think about our lunch menu.
- What a blow to my pride.
Good one.
We might make it to Round Three.
- Everyone is doing well, right?
- Okay.
Let's try right away.
(The go-getter caught the perfect moment.)
- Let's go.
- Do we?
- Yes, go.
- Right now?
- You should try 3 balls.
- Here I go.
Ready. Set.
(3rd try)
- Oh, no.
- A miss.
That's it.
(Hit 2 birds with 1 stone)
It's...
- Next.
- Gun Woo.
I've hit a lot.
(A success if they hit 1 more)
- Try two balls.
- Go last, Jae Seok.
Okay. Leave two balls for me.
One. No rush.
- One more.
- Move together.
Here I go.
- Jun Sang.
- Ten seconds left.
- Switch. One more, Jun Sang.
- Two left.
One is enough for me.
Seriously?
(Jun Sang finished it!)
- Let's go!
- Unbelievable!
- Goodness.
- Nice.
For real?
- We are...
- Jun Sang is...
- Nice.
- We're in good shape today.
- I've got goosebumps.
- Great.
I'm mind-blown.
(With Yeon Seok hitting 2 birds with 1 stone...)
(and Jun Sang wrapping it up, )
(they succeeded Round 2 on the 1st try!)
- We had a good strategy.
- With just three tries...
Only one ball was left.
When I had gotten the hang of it,
Jun Sang told me to go for it right away.
- I know.
- Yes, good job.
- He's the best coach.
- Yes.
Okay.
Even the air purifier has been secured.
(Secured matching hats and an air purifier)
Whether to go for Round Three or stop.
- No questions asked, it's a go.
- Go.
- Of course.
- Yes, of course.
- We...
- A chance like this...
I rarely suggest moving on to Round Three, but today is a must.
Today is really a must.
- We're on a roll, right?
- Yes.
(What's the present for Round 3?)
"A couple camping in the mountains..."
"and on the beaches in our spare time."
"Please add more aesthetics to it!"
"L Brand's smart TV."
(Round 3 present: Portable smart TV)
- Hold on a minute.
- I really want that myself.
- My gosh.
- For real?
- We've been wanting it badly.
- Round Three.
(Adding aesthetics to the couple's camping, portable smart TV)
- Unbelievable.
- You'll have your own theater.
Exactly.
(Round 3)
(The ping pong balls increase to 6.)
- How many?
- What?
(6? Did I hear correctly?)
That's too much.
- How many?
- Ten in thirty seconds?
- Sorry?
- As is.
But it's...
- Give us more time.
- It's six balls.
The difficulty shot up...
- in Round Three.
- This is a tough one.
- Jun Sang.
- Let me get the hang of it.
Right now... Not at the moment?
- Really.
- We should hit hard...
and aim to hit 2 or 3 birds with 1 stone.
- Right?
- Jae Seok...
Depending on where it drops...
Jun Sang's got it.
(Practicing until he's got the right timing)
- We've got several tries left.
- Right.
It's about time Jun Sang starts getting annoyed.
- Yes, Jun Sang is...
- Right?
- He's in the zone.
- Jun Sang is a go-getter.
He tries until he succeeds.
Oh, dear.
(Rummaging)
Don't put them in your pocket.
Have them in your hand.
(Lacks knack compared to his passion)
Go for three balls.
- Try it, Gun Woo.
- Okay.
Let's check if we can succeed with ten balls.
You haven't knocked any down, right?
What? No, it's my turn now.
(Gun Woo hasn't had much success yet.)
- You should succeed at least one.
- True.
- Hit with power.
- Power.
With power.
- It's tough.
- I have a feeling it'll hit one.
Right. I'm bad at it right now.
Gun Woo is...
- Me?
- He's not...
the athletic type.
- Gun Woo.
- I should hit like this.
(Struggling)
(Yeon Seok practices as well.)
- Good.
- He's on a roll now.
Nice.
(Hit 3 in a row)
- Let's go.
- You do three.
- Let's do it.
- Nice.
- I've got the hang of it.
- You do three. Hurry.
- Three?
- Do three.
- Hurry.
(The go-getter and Coach Yu rushes him.)
- Go. Here we go.
- Nice. Here we go.
- Ready.
- Here I go.
Set.
(4th try)
- Nice. That was close.
- Oh, no.
What?
Knock one down.
- Nice.
- Three balls.
(Hit 3 birds with 1 stone)
(What just happened?)
- Well done.
- Three balls. Go, Jun Sang.
- Jun Sang.
- Go, Jun Sang.
- Go.
- Hurry.
- We're running out of time.
- Three.
No, two.
Hold on.
- Oh, no.
- Hurry.
- Five balls left.
One.
No rush.
- Two left.
- Don't rush, Gun Woo.
You've got plenty of time.
(Gun Woo with 2 balls)
Five, four...
(Failed)
(Screaming)
We're off to a good start.
- We are.
- Right.
(Gun Woo's screaming was memorable.)
- Really.
- I knocked down three balls.
You end up screaming before you know it.
It's making me feel small.
- That was great just now.
- I agree.
- Not bad. There's hope.
- For real.
Yeon Seok should go first.
- Should I?
- Yes, go first.
Give me one more ball as the starter.
- Four balls.
- Okay.
- You do four.
I'm good with two.
- Gun Woo, do two.
- Sorry?
Do two.
I need to hit at least three balls.
- Good luck.
Here I go.
Ready. Set.
(6th try)
Why are you losing steam?
At least one, okay?
Nice.
- Four balls.
- I couldn't do my share.
(A disappointing 1 hit)
I couldn't do my share.
Good one.
- Gun Woo.
- Okay.
(4 targets left)
Let's go.
Ten seconds left.
Come on.
(Failed)
The balls.
- There are too many.
- Just how?
Earlier was our golden chance.
- It's tough.
- Controlling your strength is hard.
- How many tries do we have?
- Three.
- We have to succeed in 3 tries.
We have three tries left.
It was easy up until Round Two.
- Right away...
- The difficulty.
We were on a roll...
- in the earlier rounds.
- True.
I get it now. Rounds 1 and 2 were baits...
- so that we'd go for Round Three.
- Exactly.
"Go for Round Three."
And then, they bump up the difficulty.
Listen. It's their own strategy.
- A smart strategy.
- Round Three is...
- It's a real challenge.
- Fail,
and all the presents are gone.
- Yes.
- It's tough.
They were like freebies until Round Two...
to make us try Round Three.
One player must knock...
- many balls down.
- Hit 2 birds with 1 stone.
It's a must.
- We need a moment like that.
- True.
- We'll try.
- Go for it, Jun Sang.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Do 4, Jun Sang.
- Do 4.
- Four.
- Ready.
Should we each do two?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 8.)
(8th try)
Come on.
(Hit 1 ball)
(8th try)
- Nice.
- Good.
Go for it.
(8th try)
That's it.
- Oh, no.
- I'll go.
(Third player, Gun Woo)
- Good luck, Gun Woo.
- Good luck.
(8th try)
Just one.
Ten seconds left.
You never know.
(8th try)
It's over.
It was our best shot yet.
- It's not easy.
- Seriously.
Why do we fail?
It's tough. Once we go for it, we get nervous.
It's hit or miss.
We've got two tries left.
- It's...
- During practice...
- Exactly.
- He's Practice World Messi.
But Jae Seok's been lucky these days.
(Watching)
- If only that would happen.
- Let's do it.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
- Do 4, Jae Seok.
- No, 3.
- Three?
- Three.
- You do three.
- Okay.
- We only have two tries left.
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go.
- They do 3. We do 2.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go.
- You do three.
- One?
- I'll do one.
(9th try)
Well done.
Couldn't you have flown further?
Oh, dear.
Hold on.
Nice.
We have hope.
- Great.
- Nice.
- Well done.
- Okay.
(3 targets left)
You'll succeed.
- Come on.
- Do one more.
Ten seconds left.
That's it.
- Good. It's our golden chance.
- Two left.
Good. It's our golden chance.
- It's our golden chance.
- Two left.
(The last is ace Yeon Seok.)
(9th try)
We might make a miracle.
Five, four...
What a bummer.
(Failed)
(If only they had hit 2 more...)
What a bummer.
Really, that was close.
I'm about to lose it.
- It's just too difficult.
- Exactly.
We must hit 2 birds with 1 stone...
- at least twice.
- You're right.
Six balls is a tough one.
Why are we so bad at it?
Just go for it.
(Here it goes again.)
Seriously.
(Rolling down)
I don't even need to aim well.
The balls just go down during practice.
The balls go down during practice, but during the actual game,
- I go down.
- Exactly.
It's the mentality that goes down.
I don't even need to aim well.
- One.
- Bounce once.
(1 hit)
If only that happens, we'll succeed.
(Another hit)
You should go first.
- Go first.
- No, it's our last try.
- Then...
- Let them decide.
- He's on a roll.
- Why not?
- Please decide the order.
- Yes.
So that there's no regret.
(Starting to discuss)
Jae Seok should...
I'll make it.
Give me your paw. Let's do this.
(Before the last try, )
(the go-getter is in special training mode again.)
- Tell us your strategy.
- Yes, please.
Jae Seok gets to go four times.
- Four balls.
- Yeon Seok gets four times.
- Four.
- The rest get one ball each.
(The rest)
- I think it's a good idea.
- Wait.
(Laughing)
They desperately want us to succeed.
Don't move from your spot.
What about the order?
- First, second, - Right.
- third, fourth.
- Okay.
- I'm the last?
- You always succeed as the last.
- You're asking for Yoo One Shot.
- Yes.
- Got it.
- I have faith in you.
- Let's cheer for the last time.
- Let's cheer.
- We'll succeed.
- Yes.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- Let's go!
Call it.
- Here we go.
- The last try.
- Ready.
- Please.
Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
(Jae Seok starts with 4 balls.)
Come on.
(Last try)
Again?
- Nice.
- Only one?
- Me, right?
- Yes.
One at a time.
(Last try)
It's...
- Good.
- Nice.
(Jun Sang hit 1!)
- Good.
- Nice.
Hit them on the first go.
(Last try)
- Good.
- Ten seconds left.
(Hit 2 birds with 1 stone)
Nice.
(Last try)
(The last ping pong ball)
- Five, four, three...
- No rush.
Three, two...
(The end)
Two...
Gosh.
(Solemn)
It hit it.
It hit the ball.
It did for real.
If only I had knocked more down.
To think they'd take it back immediately.
(Scratching)
(Bok has become teary-eyed.)
It hit the ball.
- Can't you say we succeeded?
- To end in Round Two,
- True.
- we had too many tries left.
But we always fail in Round Three.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
It's okay.
(Gifting merch as an apology)
- Good luck with your business.
- Thank you.
- Really.
I hope you hit the jackpot.
- Thank you.
(Failed to liven the mood up)
I'm sorry.
Can't we have a ping pong match with the production team?
The production team is hateful, right?
Are there any must-eat places nearby?
Come on, Jae Seok.
- Still.
- We failed.
- It's to change the mood.
- But...
I attended Dongguk University.
- You'd know the area well.
- Yes.
At the back of Dongguk University.
- Let's leave it to Jun Sang.
- That's right.
- He'll be our guide.
- Yes.
- Let's go, Jun Sang.
- Okay.
- Bye.
For goodness' sake.
We'd like to give tickets...
- of the musical "Swing Days."
- Really?
- Yes, as a gift.
- Thank you.
- The theater is nearby, right?
- Yes.
- I've never watched a musical.
- Really?
I've been dying to watch one.
- Nice.
- Great.
- The theater is around the corner.
- It'll be a great date.
I feel bad for giving him one ball to hit.
- No, it's okay.
- It's been bugging me.
- No.
- That doesn't matter.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Bye, Bok.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be.
It's just...
Nothing is working out.
In our next spare time, let's suggest ending it in Round Two.
But the thing was,
- we had 8 to 9 tries left.
- Exactly.
(Too many tries to give up Round 3)
- Jun Sang.
- How disappointing.
- Let's check our next spare time.
- We should check the time first.
We can have you guide us to lunch, Jun Sang.
- Yes.
- I'm sure there are many...
good, shabby places...
- Good places?
- left behind the school.
- Let's get going, Jun Sang.
- Okay.
Why don't we head over after having lunch around here?
- Since you know the area.
- Gun Woo.
- Yes?
I don't think...
- you're the athletic type.
- Listen.
I was disappointed in myself today.
I'm not this bad.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
You're usually athletic, right?
Yes, it's just that...
I'm bad at ping pong.
(Is that so?)
- I'm good at soccer.
- Are you?
- Are you good at soccer?
- Yes.
I'm also good at running.
But I'm not so good at kicking jegi.
You said you were good at using feet, but it doesn't mean...
that you're good at everything related to feet.
I guess you're right.
Do you want to try going without a map?
- Where?
- What map?
The restaurant and stuff.
Are you guiding us there?
- Yes, I can take you there.
- Okay.
A place where there aren't that many people...
- That sounds good.
- Yes.
Now, there's Dongguk University up the hill.
- And there's the Jangchung Arena.
- That's right.
There are lots of good restaurants around here.
A lot of them are old.
But most of them are gone.
- That's true.
- They all...
- We'll cross the street here.
- Okay.
(Looking)
It's obviously an alley for good restaurants.
- This is...
- It's so...
It already smells delicious in this alley.
Wherever you go...
- All of them look good.
- Yes.
Okay, then.
What's your...
Have I come here before?
I'm looking for a shabby place.
Oh, there's bean sprout gukbap.
You don't know where you're going?
You'll just look around and pick one?
Of course.
- Is that it?
- I'm looking for one.
- But...
- You don't go there often?
I thought you were going to your favorite place.
Jun Sang!
- I should have looked it up.
- I don't...
know any good restaurants.
- Then, why...
- What are you doing?
(Flabbergasted)
- Then, why...
- We shouldn't be going this way.
All the restaurants here serve good food.
- It looks like it.
- What do you think...
about bean sprout gukbap over there?
I've been seeing that the moment I came here.
(Suggesting a restaurant that he sees)
- You went to school here, - Yes.
So I thought you knew a place.
What...
That beef bone soup is also...
It looks pretty good.
It does, doesn't it?
(He hurriedly checks out the interior.)
There's kalguksu too.
Do you guys eat kalguksu?
Do you know the place?
- This one?
- Yes.
I don't.
(Saying out loud all the food he sees)
But I feel like their kalguksu...
This is awesome. Pork Cutlet Story.
- That looks good too.
- Pork Cutlet Story?
- Jun Sang.
- That's common in a college town.
- Don't do this.
- We should...
I'm sure their pork cutlets would taste good, but...
I've never seen Jae Seok stop the guests before.
Shouldn't we at least hear them out?
I like this type of stuff.
Shouldn't we hear them out?
Yeon Seok, you know my style.
Jae Seok is okay with pretty much all restaurants.
But you can't just walk in by looking at the sign.
In this alley full of good restaurants...
I mean...
Yeon Shik, look one up.
- Gun Woo.
- Yes?
Look it up.
I'll have a word with Jun Sang.
You guys can look it up.
There are so many good restaurants.
Gosh.
(The two younger members look up restaurants.)
Don't do this, Jun Sang. I know their food is good, but...
I like his way of picking a restaurant, though.
- So do I.
- Yes.
I also liked the beef bone soup place.
(Searching hard)
Beef bone soup sounds good to me.
- Let's go, then.
- Sure.
- I'm okay with it.
- Good.
(They choose the place they saw on the way here.)
That was so funny.
I don't normally go out looking for good restaurants.
We'll trust your hunch.
That's so funny.
- There are lots of empty tables.
- Lunchtime is almost over, so...
You can go in.
Welcome.
- Hello.
What would you like, Jun Sang?
Just regular bone soup.
- I'll have pork bone soup.
- Good.
- Two.
- Three.
- Beef bone soup.
- Yes.
- Beef suyuk?
- Yes, beef suyuk.
I'll order them.
It says Mr. Huh Young Man was also here.
- Really?
- He was here on "Food Travel."
It feels good to find a nice restaurant by chance.
That's interesting.
It's been a while since I had leaf mustard kimchi.
It's good.
- Leaf mustard kimchi?
- It's very good.
(Their kimchi is already good.)
- This is nice.
- Thank you for the food.
It's so good.
(A scoop of rice with leaf mustard kimchi)
(Moaning)
- It's good, isn't it?
- Yes, it's lovely.
This leaf mustard kimchi is very good.
They are knocked down so easily when I'm practicing.
(Jae Seok also takes a bite.)
Right.
We almost finished our leaf mustard kimchi.
We're already eating rice with leaf mustard kimchi.
(Very popular)
Here's your food.
- Okay.
- That looks delicious.
Thank you.
The soup looks really good.
Try this.
(Beef bone soup with clear broth)
(Pork bone soup has milky broth.)
It's obviously a famous restaurant.
(A sip of beef bone soup)
It's...
It's good.
It is a famous restaurant.
- This is...
- It's approved by Mr. Huh.
I love it.
(Jae Seok is in love with the taste.)
The soup is...
(Exclaiming)
That's good.
- It's your favorite type, right?
- Exactly my favorite.
It's your favorite type of food.
You know what it is.
- It's so neat.
- Their pork bone soup is...
- their specialty.
- This is also good.
Right? Beef bone soup is so good.
- People would line up for this.
- I'll try the broth.
The meat pieces are so big.
Yes, they are.
- That's a lot of meat.
- It's so much.
Pork bone soup is nice and thick.
It's different from pork soup in Busan.
- It's delicious.
- Yes.
- That's awesome.
- This hits different.
Awesome, right?
It's incredible.
Beef bone soup and pork bone soup are very different.
It's the best pork bone soup I've ever had.
- Really?
- Yes.
Right?
We found this good restaurant...
just with Jun Sang's...
(It was all thanks to his hunch.)
hunch.
When we get out,
we'll film it again.
I'll act like I'm introducing you to this place as we walk in.
You can record it later.
Say, "I frequently come here."
(Anyway, Jun Sang found this unexpected restaurant.)
I would highly recommend...
this place to my friends.
- Yes.
- Right?
(They're literally gulping it down.)
(And this man enjoys it better than anybody else.)
(He drinks from the bowl.)
That's so good.
This is a genuine reaction.
I forgot about how we failed Round Three.
- It's that good?
- It's that good.
(This bone soup makes him forget about failure.)
I should pack some to go.
- Right?
- It's good.
Gun Woo, pack one home and eat it when you want.
It's on him.
- What do you say?
- Really?
- Yes. You want it?
- Thank you.
I'm sure it'll come to your mind as well.
(Nodding)
- Beef?
- Yes.
Can we pack some to go?
Yes, you can. What do you want?
We'll take beef bone soup...
- Two servings each.
- Two servings each?
Yes, please.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Jae Seok.
- It's nothing.
- Thank you.
- It's nothing, Jun Sang.
- No.
No.
(Vocalizing)
He's doing a vocal exercise.
- Do you always...
- He has to.
Has it been 30 years since you started performing?
Yes, it's a little over 30 years.
You were a publicly recruited actor.
Yes, on SBS.
That's right.
- Oh, SBS.
- He was publicly recruited by SBS.
I'm in the fifth batch.
(Impressed)
- Nam Joo is in the fourth batch.
- Oh, Kim Nam Joo.
- And there's Kim Myung Min.
- Kim Myung Min.
(6th batch, Kim Myung Min)
- Dong Il was also on SBS.
- Sung Dong Il.
They publicly recruited actors, but they stopped.
Right.
Does that mean you become an employee?
You're an employee at first.
- Like contract actors.
- Just the contract.
- They're just affiliated.
- That's right.
We got 50 dollars per appearance at the time.
Was there a monthly pay on the side?
I think the base pay was like 200 dollars.
But we got 50 dollars for 1 appearance in a show,
so we tried our best to be in it.
(The 50 dollars meant so much to them.)
I recently did a one-man musical.
It's about Apollo 11 in 1969.
("Behind the Moon," the 1-man musical, recently ended.)
I had to act out four different roles.
Goodness.
I'm leading the show by myself for an hour and a half.
And it was so fun...
doing it all by myself.
- I cried while watching it.
- Yes, he came.
He's the type to act passionately.
I was singing like 17 songs by myself, and...
- Oh, my gosh.
- Gosh.
But I wasn't even tired because it was so fun.
But to find the fun in it,
- you need a lot of practice.
- True.
He practices so much.
He memorizes all the lines on day one of practice.
- We haven't even...
- It's a read-through.
Gotten through the whole script.
But he suggested that we move around that day.
It's an original musical.
You have to make the scenes as you go...
- That's right.
- when it's an original musical.
I met Gun Woo in the elevator for the first time that day,
and I immediately went, "What's going on?"
(He remembers the day.)
You started a scene out of nowhere?
Yes.
Two fleeing Koreans snuck in.
I have to search the place.
This is a founding anniversary party hosted by the US headquarters...
for the executives of the Shanghai branch.
No uninvited guests allowed.
They are armed.
I must search the place...
for the safety of your guests.
Armed Koreans.
Here?
Oh, I'm an audience.
- I'm not a part of the play.
- It's an interactive performance.
- Is it interactive?
- Fine.
Then, will you be responsible...
for ruining this amazing party?
Sorry?
That's how it went.
He seems pretty fed up with you.
(He seems pretty fed up with Jun Sang.)
I had gotten used to it,
but it's been a while...
since I was away from him.
- I can see that happening.
- I can get used to it in a week.
(Getting used to Jun Sang)
I'm getting used to him now.
I saw him hesitate a few times.
Yes.
When Jun Sang started acting it out.
Then, I'll pay for the takeouts.
- We must decide who pays for this.
- Yes, that's a different matter.
We'll play a simple game.
(Deciding who pays)
Is there a game you usually play?
We'll have the staff...
set an alarm on a phone...
- and pass it around.
- While we're talking.
Yes, while we're talking.
You lose if it goes off in your hand.
- It's a time-bomb game.
- Exactly.
- Like a time bomb.
- Who should set it?
- Set a timer.
- You decide.
(The alarm will go off in 1 minute 36 seconds.)
Gun Woo will go first.
- I just have to ask, right?
- Yes.
- Ask and answer.
- And answer.
- Ask anything.
- It's begun.
What do you usually have for dinner?
I usually have rice, what about you?
That's not how you do it.
You have to finish asking the question.
(You must finish the question first.)
Do you have any worries these days?
Worries?
Well, I...
- I feel at ease.
- That's good.
I'm not particularly worried about anything.
I'm thinking of how I should do well in my new work.
I'm worried if "Phantom Lawyer" will do well.
Is there a drama scheduled for you?
The shoot begins in May.
You've been in musicals,
so I'd like your advice for a musical newbie.
I'd appreciate your input.
All you can do is practice hard.
You have to ask first.
- Ask first.
- Right. Practice.
Do you have any tips?
Can you ask Jun Sang a question?
- Anyway, - Yes.
I was a huge fan of "Infinite Challenge."
It's such an honor to meet you.
- Sure.
- Can I get a photo with you later?
It was handed to you. That's wild.
(Jae Seok will pay.)
- That was incredible timing.
- What was that timing?
That was amazing.
(Amazed by the perfect timing)
Sorry about that.
That's okay.
It's fine, Gun Woo.
- That was a bit...
- It was...
That was so discouraging. It just went off.
Gun Woo would have paid...
- if I had stalled him longer.
- Exactly.
I'll pay for lunch, then.
- And you'll pay for our takeouts?
- Of course.
I had delicious food at a good restaurant, so...
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Shall we leave?
- Yes.
(Jae Seok pays for their food and takeouts.)
Thank you for the food.
Did you know when you handed it over?
It was timed perfectly.
Oh, no.
It looked like you gave it to him when you felt the vibration.
A little.
There was an overlapping second.
- No one can be sure.
- Right.
He could have lost by a split second.
But the sound went off in your hand.
- Let's get going.
- Let's go.
Should I guide you to the next destination?
I did poorly in the game, after all.
Navi Kim will guide us.
Okay.
Is this it?
(Navi Kim looks up the route.)
- It's that way, right?
- Yes, it's that way.
Hello.
(They also got coffee to go.)
(While saying hi, )
(the new recruit focuses on the map.)
(The original guide enjoys the freedom.)
(Peeking)
Yeon Shik isn't holding his phone on the street for once.
- I'm...
- Thanks to Gun Woo.
Walking leisurely with milk tea in my hand.
- That's good.
- Gun Woo is...
It's fascinating how you managed to talk and check the map.
It's more chaotic than expected.
- It does get chaotic.
- Yes.
- You have to talk too.
- We go straight now.
Okay.
(Humming)
Jae Seok, nice to meet you.
- Jun Sang.
- Is that the new song?
- Your throat is in great shape.
- No.
Sing us the main number while you're warming up.
(Singing instantly)
- Hello.
Hi, kids!
- I've made up my mind - Hello.
(He gets back into character after saying hi to people.)
(But the audience next to him loses focus.)
I've met lots of musical actors,
including Yeon Seok,
and I've never seen anyone sing on the street.
He's the first one to continue singing.
Normally, someone interrupts them...
They prefer not to sing, even when we ask.
(Trust me)
(Act 2 begins in the meantime.)
(Watch me)
(The veteran musical actor joins him.)
(Act 2 ends with a grand finale.)
I have to maintain my voice in good condition.
Seok, Jae Seok!
- You constantly warm up.
- I must.
(Meanwhile, Navi Kim is distracted.)
(Solely focused on the map)
- Are we going the right way?
- Yes.
- We are.
- Now, we cross the street...
at the pedestrian signal.
(Pleased)
The light turned green.
- Great timing.
- It's green.
This is luck.
- Cross - This is the road.
- This is the road - Crosswalk.
- This is my path - Crosswalk
I apologize.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
(The 4 musical singers suddenly get embarrassed.)
Now, we go straight this way.
Straight.
This is our.
Now, to our one o'clock.
- This way?
- Yes.
- It can't be that hotel, right?
- Where?
The one we see.
- Jang Myung Hun.
- Myung Hun.
"This place used to be alive with the sound..."
"of clinking glasses..."
"and guests checking in."
Is it a hotel?
"After being fully booked for so long, it stands quiet,"
"waiting for the very last check-out."
They must be closing.
- "Will you be our final guests?"
- Oh, no.
- Maybe it's a guesthouse.
- Yes, something like that.
- Accommodation.
It's an accommodation, but we're their last guests.
It's on the fourth floor of this building.
- Here?
Yes, fourth floor here.
- This building?
- This one.
What kind of hotel is here?
- Oh, there it is.
- Really?
"Walk-in stay, 35 dollars."
This one?
- This is it.
- This is...
This is the place.
- Walk-in stay?
- It looks like...
- a pawnshop from back in the day.
- It does.
- What is this place?
- This is it.
- It's like an old inn.
- I guess...
it really is an accommodation.
- The sign...
- So, they're closing down today.
- I don't see the sign, though.
- The last...
Let's go upstairs.
- There's a mirror here.
- It's a totally different vibe.
It is.
Right?
- This is...
- Is it...
- Wait.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- There are lots of people.
- What?
- Hello.
- Good afternoon.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Mr. Jang Myung Hun?
- Yes.
Oh, there he is.
- He's our Whenever Guest.
- Good to meet you.
- Hello.
- Glad to see you.
What kind of place is this?
It's a theater.
- A theater?
- Yes.
Oh, it's a theater?
Yes, this is where we perform.
We thought it was like a hotel, but it wasn't.
It's a play set in a guesthouse.
(A play set in a guesthouse)
So, you even perform here?
- Yes.
- This is the stage,
and these are the seats.
(On one of the walls, )
(it's filled with visitors' notes.)
"I'm dying to drink that beer."
"I'm quitting drinking, and you made me crave beer."
(Pleased)
It's Almighty Yu!
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
They're doing a play set in a guesthouse.
All we have is beer.
Would you like some? Or not?
Jun Sang, do you want a beer?
No, thanks.
Is the title "Care for a Beer?"
- Yes, that's right.
- Oh, that's the title?
That's why you actually have beer.
Yes, we drink beer during the performance,
and we share it with the audience...
as we talk.
(You drink beer with the audience?)
And you clink glasses?
- Yes, we do.
- We do.
(They even clink glasses with the audience.)
- It must be interactive.
- It is.
We perform in Part One,
and in Part Two, the actors and the audience...
sit around to drink beer and talk.
(They get to watch a play and drink beer.)
That's amazing.
How long have you been performing?
This play started in 2014,
- It's been 13 years.
- so it's been 13 years.
Just this one play?
- It's been going on for a while.
- Yes.
At first, we did it in a greenhouse.
Every two years, when we're selected for a government project...
or we secure funding, we performed.
(At a guesthouse in Jeju in 2018)
(They've performed in various places.)
Even small mistakes will be...
so noticeable in such a small theater.
Have you ever made any mistakes?
- Even recently.
- So many mistakes.
- There was one recently.
- What was the mistake?
The door got stuck once.
- When you had to enter?
- Yes, it got locked.
How did you solve it?
We enter and exit through that door,
and the doorknob broke.
- Oh, it broke.
- Oh, no.
We were trying to come in, but we couldn't.
We had to stop the play...
and apologize to the audience.
Did you stop the play entirely?
- Yes.
- Because you couldn't open it?
The audience stepped forward and tried to open it.
It's truly interactive.
- Now, that's an interactive play.
- Yes.
But you wrote that it was the final check-out.
Is it because the play is set in a guesthouse?
Yes, there's that, and our play is ending soon.
- Oh, it is.
- Yes.
We're actually checking out of this place.
Did you rent this place for the play?
- Yes, it's an open-run production.
- Yes.
As the audience numbers dropped,
we've decided to wrap up the production.
- March will be the final month.
- I see.
You must be sad.
(Tae Yang must be sadder as the director.)
We would continue if the play were successful.
But I believe this is the end this time.
This is it.
I think it's a beloved play, though.
I read one of the notes,
and it said, "I rewatched it in eight years,"
"and it's still good."
- Some of them even come back.
- Yes.
It's literally packed.
- The audience wrote them.
- Yes.
(The notes fill a whole wall.)
("Care for a Beer?" was deeply loved.)
You must have a performance tonight.
How many are you expecting tonight?
Today, we're having 11 people.
With the 4 of you, it will be 15.
You're really good.
- She's good.
- Yes.
If you include the staff members as well...
- Right. If everyone comes...
- There will be about 30 people.
Will it be a full house then?
We'll love that.
- You'll love that?
- Yes, we'll love that.
(The audience's ardent enthusiasm...)
(and the actors' great performance shined here.)
(With the memories in their hearts, )
(the play will check out.)
(But with the passion and effort for the theater...)
(and the memories that've made together, )
(Whenever Guests will move on to the next chapter.)
Since we're here...
Your performance will be over soon,
- so it'll be nice to wrap up...
- Yes.
- on a happy note.
- Let's do it on a happy note.
Let's begin.
- Bonus tries.
- Gun Woo.
- I need to get two, right?
- That'll be the best.
- Please.
- Two is the best one.
Two.
(His goal is number 2!)
(They get 1 bonus coupon.)
- That's good.
- Well done.
- Let's check the Round One prize.
- Okay.
"After every play, we have a get-together."
"We want to order food without checking the price."
Three hundred dollars for a get-together.
(Round 1 prize, 300 dollars for a get-together)
It's the perfect prize for us.
- Nice.
- It's cash.
Okay. Let's have a get-together today.
So that you can have a get-together anywhere,
- we prepared 300 dollars in cash.
- We really want to give it to them.
- Right?
- Three hundred dollars. Yes.
- Yes.
- What's the game?
(A mission for 300 dollars for a get-together)
(Ddakjichigi)
(Round 1, Take turns slapping the ddakjis...)
(and flip over 2 out of 4 ddakjis.)
Ddakjichigi.
- Ddakjichigi.
- You're good at this, right?
We played this game when Ji Jin Hee visited.
But we failed that mission in the end.
You're right.
(In Season 3, they played the game with Seok Jin and Jin Hee.)
(The well-known king of ddakji was confident.)
Let's succeed in it.
(The king of ddakji showed his skills, )
(but his colleagues...)
(continued to fail.)
(They failed in the end.)
(It's a painful memory for the king of ddakji.)
Jae Seok is the king of ddakji.
- Really?
- Yes.
But I won't be doing this alone.
I've never done this.
(Worried)
(The go-getter begins to practice right away.)
Two out of four?
- This is...
- It's a bit difficult.
Jun Sang, hit the center.
(He succeeds in it in one go.)
The center. Try it, Gun Woo.
Hit the center.
(Hit the center?)
The center.
(Gun Woo succeeds in flipping it over.)
- Okay.
- There you go.
You're good at it.
We're set.
- I think we'll be able to do this.
- Yes.
Let's give it a go.
- Let's do a cheer together.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's do a cheer together.
- Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- Two out of four.
- Yes.
Two out of four.
- Here we go!
- The king of ddakji will go first.
- This is pretty doable.
I'll go first. The ddakjis shouldn't spin too much.
(They can't wait to see the king of ddakji's performance.)
(He flips it at once!)
- All right.
- He's the king of ddakji.
- Am I next?
- Yes.
(Gun Woo is next.)
(Don't forget to hit the center!)
What? Gosh, that's...
(Oh, no!)
(Clapping belatedly)
(No groaning)
(Sad)
All right.
(The go-getter is next.)
(1st try, Jun Sang)
(It spins and lands on the same side.)
(1st try, Jun Sang: Failed)
(This is bad.)
It's hard to keep it from doing a full turn.
- It shouldn't do a full turn.
- But if you hit it gently...
If you hit it gently, it won't flip over.
- I'll just flip it over.
- Just flip it over.
Hit it hard. Hit the center.
I'm not very good at this game.
(If Yeon Seok flips it over, they'll succeed in Round 1.)
Good luck.
I didn't play with ddakji when I was little.
(He babbles due to nervousness.)
(Failed)
I didn't play with ddakji when I was little.
(Giggling)
- It's okay.
- Ddakji...
- Good luck.
- It's okay.
When I practiced earlier...
You were too far.
- You need to get near.
- Get near.
- He's good at twisting his wrist.
- I didn't play with ddakji...
You succeeded in it.
Gosh, this is...
- Let's play.
- Are you ready?
The king of ddakji will go last.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Two.
- I won't go too far.
- Hit the center.
- The center.
- I'll hit the center.
- I'll hit the core.
- Exactly.
The core.
(2nd try, Yeon Seok: Failed)
The center.
- The center.
- Yes!
(2nd try, Jun Sang)
I did it!
- I did it! Let's go! Yes!
- Gun Woo, finish it.
(Thanks to Jun Sang, )
(success is near.)
- Let's go! Yes!
- Gun Woo, finish it.
The center.
Just finish it.
(It'll be a success if they flip over 1 more ddakji.)
(I'll go near and hit the center!)
(Gun Woo's perfect finish!)
(The ddakji coach cheers.)
- Well done.
- We did it.
Well done.
(We'll have a get-together today.)
- Round one was a success.
- A success.
(Round 1 was a success.)
That was great.
- That was great. Okay.
- Thank you.
- We get to Round Two quickly today.
- I know.
- We should go for Round 2.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
- Okay. We should go for it.
- Many tries remain.
- We should go for it.
- That's right.
- The Round Two prize will be nicer.
"To celebrate the last performance,"
"we want to go on a trip together like we did in the past."
Five round-trip plane tickets to Jeju Island.
(Round 2 prize, 5 round-trip plane tickets to Jeju Island)
Let's go!
(His jaw drops.)
For all five of them?
(Check into Jeju Island!)
Jeju Island.
What? For all five of them?
Use 300 dollars for a get-together...
- and go to Jeju Island.
- I got goosebumps.
- Round Three...
- The prizes are on another level.
What's the mission?
(Round 2)
(Flip all 5 ddakjis.)
(But it'll proceed as a loyalty game.)
- What?
- A loyalty game?
(A loyalty game for ddakjichigi?)
So the one who has flipped it...
- can keep going.
- That's right.
- That's how it is.
- He might finish it alone.
Okay.
So flip over as many ddakjis as you can.
- We need to flip over all five.
- Yes.
(They'll have better chances if the first one flips many.)
(Oh, no.)
Almighty Yu!
- We need to flip over all of them.
- It'll be hard.
It's very hard to flip over multiple ddakjis in a row.
Hit the center, Yeon Seok.
- The center.
- I'm practicing.
Hit it with this side.
Not the flat side, but the bulging side.
- Do I hit it with this side?
- Yes.
- I learned it earlier.
- Do I hit it with this side?
- Is there a difference?
- Hit it with this side.
(Grinning)
Hit it with this side.
Not the flat side, but the bulging side.
(Flipping over)
(The go-getter takes the tip quietly.)
Hit it with this side.
- Let's give it a go.
- Let's do it.
- Let's succeed in Round Two.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- I'll go first.
- That sounds good.
(The king of ddakji goes first.)
The king of ddakji, please show us!
(The king of ddakji, please show us!)
I'll flip over two at the very least.
(We believe in you!)
Today's king of ddakji.
The king of ddakji!
(3rd try, Jae Seok: Failed)
(The king of ddakji they believed in made a mistake.)
The king of ddakji!
- It's okay.
- I'll give it a go.
Oh, no!
- For goodness' sake!
- He hit it well.
- Gun Woo, you can do it.
- Okay.
(Now, the remaining 2 need to flip over 5 ddakjis.)
- The center.
Hit the center.
(I'll hit the center like the last time!)
(What?)
Hold on.
(He hit the floor.)
That's funny.
Hold on.
I'm sorry. This is...
How did I hit the floor?
It's because the floor is shaped like ddakji.
- The floor...
- Yes.
"It's because the floor is shaped like ddakji."
(Ddakji-shaped floor)
(A strange consolation)
- Gun Woo.
- Still...
- I'm sorry.
- Still, you never know.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Give it a go.
The king of ddakji, you're too much.
- Yoo Yeon Seok!
- Stop it.
Stop it. There's no way it'll work.
There's no way I'll flip over five.
- You never know.
You might create a miracle.
That's right. I might flip over all five.
- Just hit the center. Don't worry.
- Okay.
- I'll just hit the center.
- In any case...
Show us a miracle.
That's good.
(He takes care of one!)
- The second one.
- I'll continue on with this energy!
That's good.
(Cheering)
All right. Let's go.
Okay. Let's do this!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
Let's see who...
Oh, no.
(Failed)
- Still...
- It was cool.
(Still, Yeon Seok flipped over 2 by himself.)
It was cool.
Maybe I should practice some more.
- Seriously.
- Maybe I need to use this.
- What?
- I should use this from now on.
That's good, Jun Sang.
Let's begin right away. Here we go!
- All right.
- Here we go!
- You're first.
- Okay. Let's begin.
- Hold on. Say, "Here we go!"
- Here we go!
He's passionate.
(His passion explodes.)
Here we go! I want to begin!
- Here we go!
- Jun Sang, do it with passion.
(Jun Sang, do it with passion!)
Okay!
(The go-getter fails.)
For goodness' sake!
(He only had passion.)
If you hadn't stopped me, I would've succeeded in it.
- Jun Sang can't go first.
- I can't do this.
- You know,
the staff members were like, "For goodness' sake."
(Many people sighed.)
Jun Sang can't go first.
(5th try, Jun Sang: Failed)
- Yoo Yeon Seok!
- For goodness' sake.
- Here we go!
It's your turn. Go.
Just hit the center.
- There you go.
- Okay. We got this.
- We got this. Let's go.
- That's good.
- The center.
- I'm the king of ddakji today.
(5th try, Yeon Seok: 1)
(5th try, Yeon Seok: 2)
- I'm the king of ddakji.
- Let's go.
- Get the other two.
- Yes!
(The prince of ddakji has been born.)
You got this.
(The 1st king is proud.)
- You got this.
- My goodness.
(They witness the miracle of the prince of ddakji.)
- He doesn't disappoint.
- He did it.
That's good.
(He can't believe his impressive performance.)
- He's cool.
- We got this.
We'll succeed in Round Two.
I'm the king of ddakji.
- It's okay.
- I'll go next.
- Okay.
- Only 2 remain. Come on.
- Only 2 remain.
- I'll go next.
- Let's go.
(2 people and 2 ddakjis remain.)
Shall I hold it like this? I'll hold it like this.
(He grabs the ddakji carefully.)
- Please.
Let's go, Gun Woo.
Let's show them.
- I haven't gone yet either.
- Okay.
Hit the center.
(I'll hit the center!)
Please hit it.
Hit the center.
We got this.
(Gun Woo succeeded in it too!)
That's good.
- Let's go. Finish it.
- Finish it.
(If they flip over 1 more ddakji, they'll succeed in Round 2.)
(Please!)
(It didn't get flipped over!)
- The king of ddakji.
- Gosh, this is...
This puts me under pressure.
Hey, this puts me under pressure.
- Hit the center.
- Do it as you always have.
- You're the king of ddakji.
- I'll do it as I always have.
- Seriously.
- If I fail...
Didn't we do this...
- when Ji Jin Hee visited?
- Exactly.
- The king of ddakji.
- Okay.
(We can't repeat the failure of the last time.)
Shall I hit it hard?
- Hit it hard.
- That'll be better, right?
- Hit the center.
- I'll hit the center.
The center.
(Only 1 ddakji remains.)
Let's go.
(We're in your care, king of ddakji!)
(Failed)
For goodness' sake!
(The fifth try fails.)
Come on! For goodness' sake!
(Screaming)
(Solemn)
(And fury)
For goodness' sake!
I'm so annoyed!
Firstly...
- Let's have a bonus try.
- A bonus try.
A bonus try.
- Good luck.
- Myung Hun, come on in.
Please take the ddakji from one member.
- Please replace me. I'm in a slump.
- No.
- No, it's up to him.
- But...
Please take the ddakji from 1 of the 4 members.
(He chooses Jun Sang.)
(Jun Sang misses it since he's busy practicing.)
- He's practicing diligently.
- Jun Sang.
He wants you to take a break.
(The go-getter is out.)
Give your ddakji to Myung Hun.
- All right.
- Gosh, Jun Sang.
- Gosh, Jun Sang. This is so funny.
- This is so funny.
I survived.
- Go ahead and practice, Myung Hun.
- Okay.
(Success)
- Good.
- It's hard.
There you go.
- There you go. Let's go.
- He hits it hard.
- Let's begin right away.
- Begin right away.
- No, let's begin.
- Go.
- Here we go!
- Go!
You can do it.
- You got this!
- Like what you did earlier.
- Do it as you have earlier.
- Do it as you have practiced.
(Bonus try, Myung Hun: 1)
That's good.
- Come on!
- It was too weak.
It's okay.
(Still, Myung Hun did his share.)
- I'll go next.
- Go ahead.
(Let's succeed in it this time!)
Nice.
(Bonus try, Jae Seok: 1)
- Gosh.
- Gun Woo, go ahead.
Gun Woo.
- Gun Woo, go.
(Bonus try, Gun Woo: 1)
(He gets better each time.)
(2 ddakjis remain.)
- Let's do 1 more.
- Just 1 more.
Just one more.
That's good.
You can flip over two.
(The 2 remaining ddakjis fall into Yeon Seok's hands.)
I think you'll succeed in it.
- Just 2.
- Just 2. Let's go.
I did it earlier.
- I flipped over three.
- Let's succeed in the bonus try.
- I'm the king of ddakji today.
- Good luck.
I'm the king of ddakji today.
I'm the king of ddakji.
(The bonus try failed.)
It's okay.
- It's okay.
- The 7th, 8th, 9th, and 10th tries.
- If we succeed in it this time...
- Yes.
It's harder than I imagined.
Now...
- You know, - I'm so annoyed.
Instead of hoping for Round Three...
Seriously.
(His success rate is 100 percent during practice.)
He's Messi during practice.
- He's perfect during practice.
- I'm so annoyed.
Seriously.
It gets flipped over even when I hit it carelessly.
Then I'll go first.
- Okay.
- I'll go first.
Why don't you ask Jun Sang when he'll go?
I'll enter as I see fit.
Just go ahead and start.
- He'll enter as he sees fit.
- Okay.
- Enter when you get the feel.
- When you get the feel.
- Okay.
Okay. That's good.
Jun Sang is so funny.
When Jun Sang fails, he goes...
(Copying the devastated Jun Sang)
(The pose of devastation)
- Let's do a cheer.
- Let's go.
- Seriously.
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- Let's go!
- I'll go 1st.
- Okay. Go 1st.
- We'll succeed in it this time.
- Let's do this.
We'll succeed in it no matter what.
(The king of ddakji's pride is on the line!)
- We'll succeed in it this time.
- All right.
We'll succeed in it no matter what.
- We'll succeed in it.
- Come on.
(7th try, Jae Seok: 1)
This is driving me crazy.
(7th try, Gun Woo)
(The marksman of the center goes next.)
We'll succeed in it no matter what. What? Hold on.
(Is it my turn?)
Jun Sang, is this the time?
Jun Sang, this is the time.
(He makes the pose of devastation again.)
(He loses his willpower.)
- Jun Sang.
- You know, Jun Sang is funny.
(His skills don't match his passion.)
- I lost my energy.
- Seriously.
Watching Jun Sang makes me lose so much energy.
We need to do this. We really need to do this.
- All right.
- Come on.
It'll be a good experience.
- The 8th, 9th, and 10th tries.
- I can do it.
I flipped over three earlier.
- Let's succeed in Round Two.
- I think I can do this.
(Yeon Seok needs to flip over 4 for success.)
I feel like you'll succeed in it.
I can do it.
- Nice.
- All right. Let's go.
Seriously.
- I'm the king of ddakji today.
- Good luck.
I'm the king of ddakji today.
- You never know.
- Good luck.
(7th try, Yeon Seok: 1)
(He flips over another one!)
- Yes!
- That's good.
Let's flip over two more.
(2 ddakjis remain.)
- I got this.
- Let's flip over two more.
- You got this.
- This is my day.
- This is your day.
- That's right.
It's today.
You'll flip it over.
- This ddakji...
- This ddakji... Hold on.
- Hold on.
- This one.
- This ddakji is strange.
- It's a bit off.
I think someone stepped on it.
Seriously.
Two tries remain. We need to succeed in Round Two.
It may look like a simple task,
but flipping over all of them is a feat.
- It's difficult.
- Statistically, it's difficult.
If you hit it too hard, the ddakji spins many times.
Jun Sang, are you okay?
(The go-getter wilts.)
I think Jun Sang will be sick for a few days.
Jun Sang, go first.
- Here we go.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Jun Sang, let's go.
This is the ninth try. Let's go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
(Jun Sang, you can do it!)
(9th try, Jun Sang)
There you go!
You got this.
Yes!
(He succeeds in it 2 times in a row!)
(The go-getter has awakened!)
(9th try, Jun Sang: 2)
(9th try, Jun Sang: 3)
(He flipped over 3 by himself!)
We got this.
(Just 2 more!)
(9th try, Jun Sang: 3)
(It doesn't flip over!)
- We got this.
- Okay.
- Yu Jun Sang!
- All right! Let's go.
- We got this.
(He begins to aim for the center.)
(9th try, Gun Woo)
Let's go.
(Gun Woo takes care of one!)
We got this.
- We got this.
- Finish it.
It'll be a good experience.
(Only one ddakji remains.)
- Finish it.
It'll be a good experience.
We did it!
(Gun Woo finished it!)
(Two of them succeeded in flipping over five ddakjis.)
(They did it.)
They did it.
- Kim Gun Woo!
- Thank you.
- We did it. Okay.
- We did it.
- Thank you.
- Round two was a success.
- A success.
It was perfect.
We have one try left.
Decide whether to keep going or stop.
No, don't decide to keep going.
You have to stop.
- You never know!
- No!
- They might succeed in it!
- Choose well.
- Don't do that!
- Come here.
It's up to them to decide.
- No!
- Come here, Jun Sang.
I'll give you the last prize.
- No!
- Shall we keep going?
- Will you keep going or stop?
Stop!
They can do it!
We can't! No!
No!
It was like a scene from a musical.
Whether to keep going or stop...
- is entirely up to you.
- Yes.
- Okay.
All right. In that case...
- All right.
- Hold on.
We can't do it!
- We can't do it.
- We can't!
Only one try remains.
Will you advance to Round 3? In 1, 2, 3.
(Please stop!)
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Stop.
Okay.
That was the right thing to do.
- Well done.
- Okay.
Great job.
(They get 300 dollars and plane tickets to Jeju Island!)
Thank you.
Jun Sang, you pulled through at the end.
Gun Woo.
- He hit ddakjis in fury.
- It was great.
Knowing the hardships of people in the theater scene,
I wanted to succeed in the mission no matter what.
- Thank goodness.
- I'm glad...
- you contributed in the end.
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- I agree.
I almost went home without any final comments.
- Thank goodness.
- I agree.
- I had so much fun.
- Right?
Yes. I failed to make any contribution to the first game.
Earlier, I was like Jun Sang.
(During the first spare time, Gun Woo was in the Jun Sang mode.)
So I wanted to do this well.
- You did very well.
- I did my share. Yes.
- It's hard to finish it.
- That's right.
- It's hard.
- I'll invite them...
to my musical.
- That sounds good.
- Thank you.
Let's talk about it after the shoot.
That sounds good.
We sincerely thank everyone who has joined us today.
- Thank you.
(On a spring day, )
(four men in yellow appear.)
(The man who is in charge of being strange, Park Hae Soo)
(The man who is in charge of cheering, Lee Hee Jun)
(We're always together.)
(I followed him around.)
(When the food is tasty, they exchange a look.)
(When one jokes around, the other one copies it.)
(The two middle-aged men have the perfect chemistry.)
(Today will be perfect if we can give the prizes!)
(They're ready to give the prizes.)
(Come on!)
(Is it okay to get angry on TV?)
(Can't we hurl it haphazardly?)
(Hae Soo isn't so nice.)
(Will their chemistry suffer a crisis?)
(Jae Seok, stop it!)
(Their chemistry malfunctions.)
(They fail to crumble here!)
(Here comes the uncle!)
(They only have each other to trust.)
(Will spring come to the four men?)
(Whenever Possible)