♪After a sleep, love's progressing
at top speed.♪
♪Beyond imagination.
One climax after another.♪
♪I could not believe my eyes.♪
♪After a sleep, love's progressing
at top speed.♪
♪Shall we love each other or not?♪
♪If magic really exists,♪
♪where was the Glass Slipper dropped?♪
♪Was it intentional or not?♪
♪We fell in love overnight.♪
♪No preludes. Too quick and too unexpected.♪
♪It's the most exciting subject.♪
♪We're still young.♪
♪Some setbacks are no big deal.♪
♪At times we lose our rhythm♪
♪but we'll know the beat of love better.♪
♪He's nice in fits and starts.♪
♪You're expectant
and also afraid of being hurt.♪
♪So hard to read his mind.♪
♪After a sleep, love's progressing
at top speed.♪
♪Beyond imagination.
One climax after another.♪
♪I could not believe my eyes.♪
♪After a sleep, love's progressing
at top speed.♪
♪Shall we love each other or not?♪
=You Are My Destiny=
(Episode 25)
(Ximi's notebook)
Hi.
I'm Ximi.
I'll make my debut soon.
I'm a lively, cheery and curious baby.
Though I'm still in Mom's belly,
I can't wait to see the outside world.
Due to the critical nature of the situation,
the enthusiastic Uncle Dylan
went to see the doctor with us.
Hi, Ximi.
Thanks to your father,
I became your Snail mother.
Your father thinks he's handsome.
Let's call him Father Cricket.
(Cricket sounds like handsome Xiyi in Chinese)
After you learn how to speak,
you'll call him that.
You've finally stopped being naughty.
Every time I listened to music
with your great-grandmother
and molded clay,
you behaved well.
Your great-grandmother said
you inherited her and my artistic senses.
I hope
you'll be a child
who loves art and music.
So I can draw and mold clay
with you.
But
if I fall asleep at a concert again,
you'll need to wake me up.
I was so careless.
I didn't have enough rest
because I was too absorbed in work.
I passed out on the first day
of your father's business trip.
The sight of your father
rushing back regardless of the consequences
touched me deeply.
But I blamed myself for
not taking care of you well
and messed up your father's itinerary.
Fortunately,
it was a false alarm.
Hearing your little heart
beat steadily,
your father and I felt happy.
To welcome you into this world,
we learned how to take care of you.
We're becoming more like a family.
We look forward to you
entering this world as a healthy baby.
However,
I can't watch you grow up.
But I hope you'll know
your mother loves you dearly
and your father
also loves you dearly.
How is Jiaxin?
What's the situation? Is she okay?
Didn't you go to the hospital?
How come you can't answer my questions?
Her cousin was guarding her ward.
Nobody could enter the ward.
Even Xiyi couldn't enter the ward,
not to mention me.
The child is gone,
but she should be fine.
She'll be discharged soon.
I asked Mr. Shen.
Wang Xiyi added the supplementary terms
to protect Jiaxin's rights.
I don't understand why things
turned out this way.
I'm Jiaxin's best friend
and a lawyer.
I had no idea
when she signed the divorce agreement.
I'm really incompetent.
You can explain to them for Mr. Yi.
Entrepreneurs like them
tend to notarize their properties
before getting married.
You're experienced and well-informed.
Surely you know.
Besides, they got married in a hurry.
That's why they signed the divorce agreement.
The supplementary terms were added later
to protect Jiaxin's rights.
It proves he has grown fond of her.
I can't talk to her.
She just lost her child.
This is the most painful moment in her life.
You want me to remind her and her family
of the car accident that was caused
by her overreaction on the road?
It's not that I don't want to
explain for Wang Xiyi.
You just shouldn't tell her
that even if you had the chance.
Ximi.
I've known about your situation.
I dreamed of Ximi.
Ximi.
He was so young.
Protecting him should be my priority.
But as his mother,
I failed to keep him safe.
It's all my fault.
I used to get through hard times like this
by crying
and sleeping.
Everything would be better after that.
But now,
whenever I close my eyes,
Ximi occupies my mind.
My child.
But I can't tell my mother.
If she saw me like this,
she would feel sadder than me.
Why are you here too?
Right after Xiyi heard you left,
he rushed off to look for you.
Before I could finish my words,
he unintentionally pushed me.
Now I can't have a baby for real.
How can it be?
You lost your child.
I lost the right to have a child.
Jiaxin,
I understand your pain.
I'm sorry.
If not for me...
I don't blame you.
I also don't mean to blame Xiyi.
Jiaxin,
I'll leave Xiyi to you from now on.
Please take care of him for me.
No.
I can't face him calmly now.
Please
take this back.
I think you need this more than I do.
If we didn't know each other
under these circumstances,
maybe we could have been friends.
Anna,
if I didn't
come between...
There's no "if"
in this world.
Now I have
no chance whatsoever.
Why didn't you answer my call?
Where are you?
If you saw my WeChat message,
please call me back, okay?
Call me anytime.
I've tidied up the baby's room.
It's a man's job to assemble
the little rocking horse.
It has been assembled.
Jiaxin,
I miss you so much.
I'm sorry
for letting you suffer.
After you get discharged from the hospital,
I'll take you home, okay?
Let's start over.
Okay?
(Delete)
(Delete contact "Wang Xiyi"
and the chat history with that contact)
(Jiaxin has enabled Friend Confirmation.
[Send a friend request] to chat.)
Jiaxin.
You are leaving me, aren't you?
You won't forgive me, will you?
Why did I call you?
Why did I chase you?
I shouldn't have followed
the lawyer's advice.
I should have torn the divorce agreement.
I don't want a divorce.
Jiaxin.
I really want what's best for you.
I just want you to have
something to live off.
I don't want a divorce.
Now I have lost both of you.
Ximi.
I'm sorry.
I have lost you.
I have lost your mom as well.
Tell me.
Do you hate me?
Do you hate me? I hate myself.
It's all my fault.
Your self-torture
distresses me.
You think this will make
Jiaxin and Ximi forgive you?
How long are you going to wallow in despair?
Look what Jiaxin has turned into.
Ximi is gone.
Don't I feel heartbroken and sad?
But I'm still here to lift your spirits.
If you keep doing this,
Jiaxin may forgive you,
but will your mother-in-law
still trust you with her daughter?
When your father passed away,
I endured the pain of losing my son.
Faced with the covetous shareholders,
I ground my teeth
and held the company together.
When Xiuling and her ex-husband
sucked the company dry,
I ground my teeth again
and helped the company regain a foothold.
This time,
I really want to bear your burden.
But I'm old.
Do you understand?
Zhengren is inexperienced.
Rebuild the southwestern factory.
Handle the claims of your injured employees.
Check the inventories of other factories.
Distribute the goods.
Nobody except you
can do these things.
Sometimes it's good to be busy.
You'll get to think
things over,
get over the pain,
and care for the people you should care for.
I'll tell Xiuling to visit Jiaxin
after she gets discharged.
Both of you
need to endure this experience.
Calm your nerves.
Leave Jiaxin alone
for a few days.
You should take the time to think.
Don't disturb her.
You're back.
Why are you here?
You and Jiaxin didn't live here.
I heard that Jiaxin was coming home.
So I rushed here to pack my stuff.
I just made rice gruel.
Here. Have it while it's still warm.
Great.
Jiaxin, come on.
I don't want to eat.
Why? Sit down and have some food.
Mom.
You didn't have any appetite
at the hospital.
You relied on saline to survive.
Now you're home, grab a few bites at least.
Sit down.
I really have no appetite.
You...
Look at you. You've become scrawny.
Do you expect me to watch you
avoid foods and drinks?
Huh?
My daughter isn't what she used to be.
What have I done wrong
to incur such punishment from heaven?
Jiaxin,
your mother has been busy
looking after you these days.
Don't let her worry about you.
You have no appetite?
I'll cook some more dishes for you.
I'm sleepy.
I want to sleep.
I'll eat after I wake up, okay?
You think I don't know what you did?
During your stay at the hospital,
you sneaked out of your ward every night.
You stood outside the nurseries
and watched the newborn babies,
shedding tears.
Mom.
I just can't control myself.
I've been trying not
to think about Ximi.
But I lost sleep every night at the hospital.
Every time I closed my eyes,
I heard the baby's cry.
Mom, I really don't know what to do.
Don't care about other people's opinions.
I have always been proud of you.
But I always make you sad.
That's because you're capable.
Other people can't make me sad
even if they want to.
Mom.
Cry on my shoulder.
Cry if you want.
It'll make you feel better.
Mom.
Things will be fine after a cry.
The fastest way is to deliver the goods
from the Guiyang factory.
We must send the required amount
of goods from Chengdu to Europe.
Mr. Yi,
allow me to remind you.
Even if we got the goods ready,
we wouldn't have the time to load
the last train of China Railway Express.
If land transportation doesn't work,
we can transport the goods by air.
Mr. Wang,
do you know how many times higher
the cost of air transportation is
than that of land transportation?
If we transported
a ton of goods by air
and sold them out,
we'd still lose money.
I know.
But we are new
to the European market.
Delaying the arrival of the goods
means breaking the contract and promise.
Money couldn't buy back
our damaged reputation.
Right, brother?
Yes.
Zhengren is right.
Let's do this.
Coffee.
Let's take five.
Can't you see his look?
Why did you pour coffee into that mug?
Where is your workplace sensitivity?
But you told me
Mr. Yi liked that mug
and I should fill that mug with
whatever he wanted to drink.
I said that a long time ago.
Circumstances have changed, my friend.
Never mind. Just take it away.
(Cheng Jie Group)
Jiaxin,
I know you're mad.
You refused to meet me.
You refused to listen to me.
It's okay.
But send me a message at least.
Let me know you're doing well.
Okay?
It contains so much water.
What is that?
A shrimp.
Throw it away. Throw it away.
You've gone too far.
This place looks so beautiful.
What made you come to the island
and visit me today?
Well,
I was going to ask for a leave,
but my leave letter got confiscated
right after I submitted it.
Mr. Shen was worried about you.
He said there was no need to ask for a leave.
He just gave me a day off,
telling me to come here and check on you.
Thank him for me after you get back.
Tell him I'm fine
and don't worry about me.
Yeah.
Jiaxin.
I know
you don't want to see Wang Xiyi right now.
But I think
you should try to sit down
and talk things out with him.
Mr. Shen said
the supplementary agreement
he gave you that day...
Don't mention that to me again.
I don't want to hear anything about him.
Don't mention him to me again.
It's really getting cold.
Come on.
You should go back.
Let's go.
Dylan.
Here you are.
Your mother went to your cousin's home.
She told me to wait here for you.
How can I help you?
I'm leaving Shanghai.
A few days ago, I went to the Wang family
and took back the clay doll
Master Zhongshan Long had given you.
I met Grandma.
Grandma was worried about you.
But she didn't want to disturb you.
So she wrote a letter
and asked me to give it to you.
Jiaxin,
how are you doing?
Recently,
the thought of visiting you
has occurred to me repeatedly.
But I feared my presence would sadden you.
In the end, I decided
to write this letter.
This is to express my concern,
tell you I miss you,
apologize to you
and thank you.
I spent too much time
managing the company in the past.
I looked glorious,
but I lost kinship.
After I handed the company over to Xiyi,
I could only stay in the mansion alone.
It is a cold house.
Fortunately, you came to our house.
Your warmth and kindness
changed my family little by little.
Because of you, I was able to enjoy
my family's companionship.
I hope you and Xiyi
will live happily ever after.
But I'm not a selfish person.
I consider you my granddaughter.
Therefore I'm telling you this.
Forgive Xiyi or not,
don't blame yourself.
Don't be trapped
in the pain of losing Ximi.
I lost my child once.
I understand
the unforgettable pain.
No matter what your decision is,
I fully support you.
Good girl,
remember
that the Wang family
will always be open to you.
Hope you'll stay
safe,
cheery,
and happy in the days to come.
Love, Grandma Zhenzhu.
Here.
Do you plan
to return to the Wang family?
The trust has been destroyed.
There is no second chance.
I don't want to see him.
Then
will you leave?
Leave?
Where can I go?
Someplace
without him.
Here are some drugs.
Take these drugs along.
God knows how long
you'll be gone.
You'll be living in an unfamiliar country.
It'll be difficult to see a doctor
or take drugs there.
Besides, foreign people's physiques
are different from Chinese people's.
The more I consider it, the more I worry.
You need to take these drugs.
Look at your skin. You haven't
recovered from your allergy yet.
Yeah.
Nobody will apply medicine
for you in another country.
You need to take care of yourself.
Yeah.
If I make a mistake out there,
nobody will get to punish me.
Oh, you naughty girl.
I'll whip your ass right now.
Mom.
After I leave,
will you be okay living alone?
Don't worry about me.
I'm able-bodied.
What could possibly happen to me?
It's how I've been living all this time.
You were in Shanghai
and I was in Huaniao Island.
We didn't see each other normally.
We just met up
once a month.
We didn't call each other.
We occasionally called each other, right?
Don't take me as an excuse.
Do what you should do.
Alright?
You won't miss me?
I won't.
Go.
Leave this place and go somewhere,
free from your past and concerns.
Start over your life.
I will
wait for you.
I will wait for my daughter
to become independent
and beautiful
and come home happily.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you...
Stop saying sorry.
I hate hearing that from you.
You haven't done anything wrong to anyone.
From now on, I only want to hear
about your new life,
your new friends
and the interesting things you've done.
Come back to me soon
as a healthy and happy person.
Okay?
Yeah.
♪Those mistakes I made in my life,♪
♪I take them well.♪
♪You don't know a good thing♪
♪till it's gone.♪
♪When you fall in love with someone,♪
♪you start to hope
that love will be everlasting.♪
♪In the great wilderness of the world,
I can only see you.♪
♪I want to give all my love to you.♪
♪Can you summon♪
♪love?♪
♪What would you do♪
♪for love?♪
♪Don't say "I love you" yet.♪
♪Don't fall in love with me yet.♪
♪Fairytale should have
an impressive beginning♪
♪regardless of its ending.♪
♪There is an understanding between us♪
♪that you will finally find me.♪
♪You are the only one
who understands why I keep waiting.♪
♪I will not run away from it,
because you are my destiny.♪
♪I'm looking for you.♪
♪I'm waiting for you.♪
♪I'm loving with you.♪