♪Can you feel my love?♪
♪I want to be your moon,♪
♪turning your sorrow into fairytale.♪
♪Do you want my love?♪
♪I want to kiss you under the moon,♪
♪feeling the onrushing strong tide.♪
♪My soul sings for you.♪
♪My heart misses a beat for you.♪
♪Let's fill up the world with our love.♪
♪Let's be the happiest couple in the world.♪
♪Love is so divine that we lose our mind.♪
♪Love is so strong
that it's gonna last a lifetime.♪
♪The moment I fall in love with you,♪
♪I want to date you♪
♪under the ancient mysterious moon,♪
♪letting the universe be the witness♪
♪of our eternal love.♪
♪I want to kiss you♪
♪under the starlit summer night,♪
♪letting our eternal love♪
♪become a shining legend.♪
♪Under the moon.♪
=You Are My Destiny=
(Episode 10)
Chen Jiaxin.
Who am I?
Wang Xiyi.
And?
The General Manager of Cheng Jie Group.
I'm your husband!
Whoever treats you like this
is giving me a difficult time.
But if you don't even care
about those rumors,
what would people think of me?
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
Would you be strong for me?
Would you be more considerate for my sake?
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
(Flowery Island)
Watch out.
Gentlemen, please wait.
We still have a warm-up performance.
Just a moment. It'll be over soon.
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
Oh, no! Jiaxin is very timid.
She'll screw it up onstage!
What is Wang Xiyi doing?
You can do it!
Did she really cheat the Chairwoman?
Will we lose our job
because of her?
I hope not!
Why is she here?
Bro, you've got to stand up for us!
I...
I really like grandma Zhenzhu.
She treats me
very well.
I'd never do anything to hurt her.
So, I would never fool around
with some man
to make her angry.
It's not true.
The rumor you are spreading
is not true.
So who should we trust?
Right! What is the truth?
-Who should we trust?
-Will you explain?
Who is telling the truth?
Who on earth should we trust?
That's right. Who should we trust?
Who should we trust?
Yeah.
Trust me!
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
Because I'm the General Manager
of Cheng Jie Group!
And I'm the one who secured you a job!
Chen Jiaxin cares about all of you,
that's why I chose to work with Haifei Group.
He claimed that he don't want any attention
and let the one who wants it to have it?
Mr. Yi,
just hand over your factory.
What's wrong?
Roushui.
What's the matter?
Let's cut the ribbon first.
Now, dear reporters,
please take a picture for Mr. Yi and me.
You, get out of here.
I'm sorry. So sorry.
Sorry?
Who are you? Do you know what it is?
It's a ribbon-cutting ceremony.
How is this related to you? Why are you here?
Stop it.
Have some respect, please.
She's my employee.
Whose?
Mine.
She works for me, the General Manager
of Cheng Jie Group.
In our company, regardless of the position,
everybody deserves to be respected.
If you are rude to my employee,
then it's my job to remind you
to apologize to her for your rude behavior.
Are you kidding?
You're asking me to apologize to her instead
of asking her to apologize to me?
Wang Xiyi,
do you know how to do business?
Wait. Wait.
It's a misunderstanding.
Mr. Zhou, don't be angry.
Let me apologize to you.
Just take it out on me.
After all, harmony brings wealth in business.
We've just reached an agreement,
so don't make it fall apart
for such a small thing.
Right?
Jiaxin. Jiaxin.
Calm down and be nice.
We'll be jobless
if we lose the contract.
Sorry.
Have you ever helped?
Enough.
Stop fighting.
Mr. Yi,
you still can't see right
and wrong clearly, right?
I'm good-tempered,
but I still have my bottom line.
Brother, it's not the time to
be partial to our people.
I won't allow it no matter
who gets insulted here.
So you are saying it's nonnegotiable?
Then the deal is off.
Let's just terminate the contract.
Terminate it.
Mr. Zhou. Sorry. Sorry.
It's my fault.
Please forgive me.
Mr. Zhou,
since you've make up your mind,
I'll tell you my real thoughts.
I've tried
your shampoo.
I really dislike that smell.
Unlike you,
I will never do the things
I don't like.
And I will never throw
my dignity away for money.
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
And now,
as the General Manager of Cheng Jie Group,
I announce that I'll end
the contract with him.
Huaniao Island Factory
will stop all the production immediately.
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
♪I want to date you♪
♪under the ancient mysterious moon,♪
♪letting the universe be the witness♪
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony; Heritage & Haifei)
♪of our eternal love.♪
♪I want to kiss you♪
♪under the starlit summer night,♪
♪letting our eternal love♪
♪become a shining legend.♪
♪Under the moon.♪
♪I need you, baby.♪
(Joint Ribbon-cutting Ceremony
Heritage & Haifei)
(Three Things Mothers-to-be Worry about)
Well...
About the ribbon-cutting today...
Just mind your own matters.
Don't waste time on other things.
Oh.
Go take a shower and go to bed early.
Okay.
(Pregnant Woman's Classes
July schedule)
What a hopeless journey ahead!
I've been busy all day at work,
yet I still need to work while I'm home.
I already feel quite stressful.
I can't take any more
negative energy from you.
Don't be angry.
It's a disaster to us,
but it's a good news to you.
Your company
will make big money very soon! Very soon!
Why?
Because...
If the situation remains the same,
in the near future,
our company will need
a great number of lawyers
to deal with litigation
and bankruptcy liquidation.
What happened to your company?
What happened?
Our company is already
going through a hard time,
and now our partnership
with Haifei Group is over.
So, Mr. Yi will place
all his hope
on Heritage series products,
which, as you know,
have been suffering sales decline
for a long time.
That's why I said
"what a hopeless journey ahead".
(Heritage Soap Factory)
Go ahead. You go ahead.
You go.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Wang. Well...
The contract has been terminated.
And the Chairwoman is
admitted in the hospital.
Will anything happen
to the factory?
Yeah.
Will we be fired,
and then the factory be changed
into an automated one?
Yeah.
Please don't sigh anymore.
We need you to guide us a way out.
That's right, Mr. Wang.
You are the only one we can count on now.
Right. Please help us.
What can I do?
My brother is the General Manager.
He's already announced
to shut down the factory.
So the group won't provide
any resources to us.
Even though I want to help,
there's nothing I can do.
It's all because of Chen Jiaxin.
She looks pretty and nice,
but actually she's quite sly.
She's changed.
Exactly.
She's made a big trouble
on such an important ribbon-cutting ceremony.
Apparently, she and that Mr. Yi came
to screw us over and try to fire all of us.
She is such an ungrateful traitor!
Aunt, I'm back from shopping.
Really?
Where's the rice?
Mr. Li said
because of Jiaxin,
his son was unemployed,
so he wouldn't deliver the rice to us.
He is so heartless!
I always shop in his store.
Can't believe he would do this to me!
Aunt,
how about closing the noodle stall
for a couple of days?
Just take a few days off.
Whatever you wanna eat, I'll cook for you.
Please don't listen to the gossip.
What has Jiaxin done wrong?
Those women gossip every day
instead of working.
I need to talk to them.
Aunt. Aunt.
Calm down.
Jiaxin was worried that
you'd argue with people,
so she asked me
to keep you from leaving home.
You see. She's pregnant,
and I'm also going to give to birth.
So don't let her worry,
and don't make it difficult to me, okay?
Aunt, here's your rice!
Thank you!
Don't mention it. We are family.
Where's Jiaxin? She's back to Shanghai?
I just knew you wouldn't
help me for no reason.
Why are you looking for her?
It's about...
the factory.
The deal between Mr. Yi and Mr. Zhou is off.
We just hope that Jiaxin
can apologize to Mr. Zhou,
so that Mr. Wang may save the deal.
So, now that you need Jiaxin,
she becomes your only hope?
You've forgotten how you
gossiped about her before?
Aunt, I didn't lie though.
You could totally tell from
what Mr. Wang said
that Jiaxin was the one who
made the Chairwoman furious.
What's wrong with you?
I thought you were here to comfort my aunt,
but it turns out you came to piss her off.
Quiet down!
Quiet down?
Just get out of here!
Stop annoying us.
Aunt, how about...
Didn't you hear what your wife said?
Get out, now!
Go away. Leave here.
Leave. Get out.
Alright.
You are angry. I can't handle you guys.
I'll just leave.
He drove me crazy!
Aunt, don't mind his words.
Don't be angry with him.
Calm down.
It's just a pregnancy checkup.
You don't have to go with me.
I can go by myself.
I know you are busy.
Let me ask you.
That Doctor Hao won't be
Wang Xiyi's spokesman,
so he won't accompany you
to the checkup either?
I'm not that close to him.
I'd better keep a distance from him.
I don't want to rely on him too much.
Makes sense.
You know what?
Anson told me
that Wang Xiyi had a lot of trouble at work.
He's been trying so hard
to save the Heritage series,
but got no luck yet.
The Heritage series is the glory
and lifeblood of Wang Xiyi's family.
Though he never admits defeat,
I'm not surprised
that he's been terribly busy.
Come on, Jiaxin,
don't worry about him too much.
How about this?
You can come to my firm after checkup.
I have over 200 cases...
No.
I'll go home and be with my grandma.
What are you doing?
Chen Jiaxin!
You've finally made progress!
You always said "yes" before
no matter who asked you for help.
But now you've finally known
how to say "no" to people.
Sorry.
Then I...
It is a compliment, my dear!
Why are you apologizing again?
It's my great pleasure to be the first one
who's rejected by you on earth.
Are you crazy?
My phone.
It's my sister.
Hello? Sister.
Left home?
Arrived in Shanghai already?
Let's put it aside that
the ribbon-cutting thing
has become the butt of the joke
to the whole industry.
There's no way to hide the fact
that the Chairwoman is hospitalized.
And the most important thing is
that Haifei Group has sent
us a letter of demand.
Do you think we should call Mr. Shen over?
The shareholders are not happy about this.
How are things going in Europe?
The same as before.
But some told me
that there was a proposal about
changing the General Manager
would be reviewed on the
Interim Board Meeting in two days.
Just let it be. Are the guests here already?
Yes. They are waiting for you.
Okay.
(Chen Jiaxin's Pregnancy Checkup
Remind 10 minutes later)
What's wrong?
Let's go.
Brother, you are here!
I heard that Mr. Chen and Mr. Xie were here.
I haven't seen them for a long time.
So I came by to say hi.
Sit here, brother.
Zhengren is quite outstanding!
This is so-called "the new generation
will invariably surpass the old."
He's successfully
made a deal with Haifei after he came back.
He's capable, enthusiastic and resourceful.
Xiyi,
you should give him
more opportunities to grow
and trust his potential.
That's right.
Our company needs new talents like him.
Always sticking
to the old ways will only hold us back.
Thank you, I'm so flattered.
Brother,
since we have two Directors here,
I wanna say again
that I hope you can consider
about our cooperation with Haifei.
Do you think you know Haifei better than me?
As far as I know,
Zhou Zhan is actively purchasing
our shares right now.
I seriously suspect that he's going
to seize the decision-making power
of Cheng Jie
so that he can eventually
acquire our company.
You think too much.
I'm not like you.
I only want to solve the problem.
"Automated Production Plan"?
Isn't it a plan drafted long time ago?
We have only two solutions now.
One,
you need to apologize to Zhou Zhan
so that we can continue to work with Haifei.
The other,
we may come back to life
if we downsize the factory as planned.
This is how you'll treat
the island people who've been supporting you?
I guess you two
must agree with Zhengren.
Why don't you let Zhengren
deal with the downsizing?
It's a good opportunity for him
to practice his business skills.
What if I don't take either option?
Xiyi,
we are talking to you as your elders.
If you don't respect our decision,
we will also exercise our
due authority tomorrow
on the Board Meeting.
You are not in charge here.
Mr. Chen! Mr. Xie!
Brother, you...
Well.
The "Automated Production Plan"
has been drafted long time ago, right?
Why did you reject it suddenly
just for Chen Jiaxin?
I didn't do it for Chen Jiaxin.
Grandma once promised the island people
that they wouldn't get fired.
So how can I do things
that will undermine grandma's reputation?
Alright, then let's not talk about Jiaxin.
But what should we do now?
We've just offended Zhou Zhan,
and now we've even offended
Mr. Chen and Mr. Xie,
who used to support us the most.
So what are we gonna do
on tomorrow's Board Meeting?
How come you are so absent-minded today?
Let me think about it.
Where are you going?
We still have an appointment with the bank!
Hey!
I've rescheduled your meeting
with Mr. Xu of the bank.
Okay.
You really
would rather mortgage the company's assets
than downsizing or apologizing to Zhou Zhan?
Let's talk to the bank first.
I must be crazy.
I leave all the things behind
and come to find Chen Jiaxin.
What... What brought you here?
You've done your checkup?
Yes.
Jiaxin!
Sister.
I walked all the way here. So hot.
Thank you for coming!
Mr. Yi?
You came with Jiaxin for the checkup?
Yes!
I just knew it!
People don't have a chance to
see how close you are.
That's why they always gossip.
I can't stand my husband doing that.
So I left home.
Mr. Yi,
would you like
to go shopping with Jiaxin and me?
He still has work to do.
I happen to be free this afternoon.
I'll accompany you then.
That's great.
I'll max out Jia Tiancai's credit card.
Let's go.
This store is so amazing.
You guys suit yourselves.
I'll go take a look now.
Is it boring to go shopping with us?
I hope we are not disturbing your work.
Actually, I wasn't that nice to you.
I used you and Ximi to approach Doctor Hao.
And you didn't tell anybody.
So, we are even now.
Well,
I think you were nice to me.
You even stood up for me yesterday
on the signing ceremony.
To be frank,
you don't have to think of me first
when you do things.
About Doctor Hao,
I actually over-reacted.
I will often
remind myself in the future.
Please forgive me.
You didn't go to the hospital
for my checkup, right?
No.
You wanted to persuade Doctor Hao?
He's the only one who can help
with the revival of the Heritage series.
Xiyi!
Will you come help me?
I don't know which size to choose.
Would you try this for me?
See, should I choose
size M or L? Help me.
The Heritage series is the glory
and lifeblood of Wang Xiyi's family.
Though he never admits defeat,
I'm not surprised
that he's been terribly busy.
Jiaxin.
Would you come and help me?
Okay.
I feel so awesome.
Each time I swiped the card, I felt like
I just slapped hard in Jia Tiancai's face!
His face
must have been swollen by now!
Even so,
you've bought all the things for him.
Is that also a slap in his face?
You don't understand.
If I really drive him away,
what am I supposed to do with my baby?
When you two
fight a few more times, you'll understand
my mixed feelings.
Come on, I'll take you guys out for a meal.
What's going on?
What happened?
No response?
Try again! Don't be panic.
We are stuck in here.
What should we do?
Calm down, sister!
Sir, how may I help you?
Hi,
we are stuck in the elevator.
Sorry.
I'll contact the repairman now.
Sir, don't be panic.
Please press the button of each floor
in case the elevator drops suddenly. Okay?
I've done it.
Of course, I'm worried!
If anything happens,
the three of us and two unborn babies
will all be killed!
I don't... I don't want to die in here.
We'll be fine!
Calm down for your baby's sake.
It hurts!
What's wrong?
Sister, don't scare me!
Maybe it's contraction!
Have you experienced
this type of pain before?
No.
My waist has been sore the whole day.
That should be the sign of contraction.
Sister, hold on!
Sister, take it easy!
Sit here.
Sit here, easy.
Stretch out your legs.
Jiaxin,
check her cervix.
Sister, you'll be fine.
Hello?
Will you be quicker?
Here's a pregnant woman in labor!
Please wait a moment!
The repairman is already on his way!
No signal!
By the way,
would you please dial
a doctor's number for me?
The number is...
18625599688.
It so hurts!
I can't stand it anymore!
Sister!
Here, hold on to my hand. Don't be panic.
I don't want to give birth anymore!
I don't want to!
Calm down!
Jiaxin, how's her cervix?
It has dilated.
About...
How wide is it?
About
four-fingers wide.
Four.
It's Doctor Hao.
Doctor Hao, it's Wang Xiyi.
I've made myself very clear.
Please don't bother me anymore!
I'm not calling for the spokesman.
We are stuck in the elevator!
Jiaxin's cousin is in labor.
Tell me, what's her condition?
Her contractions occur every two minutes.
Each contraction lasts for about one minute.
Her dilation of cervix is
about four fingers now.
So it's still in phase one.
However,
it doesn't mean there's no danger.
Tell me,
do you have anything contains alcohol,
and is there anything can cut umbilical cord?
I have alcohol pads and a small scissors!
Good!
Since we don't know
when the rescue team will arrive,
use the alcohol pad
to clean the scissors first,
just in case.
Okay, I'm on it!
Do you know how to do Lamaze breath?
Lamaze?
Doctor Hao, I know!
Okay, then keep doing it
till the rescue team is there.
Alright, got it!
Sister!
It's so painful!
I can't stand it!
Sister!
Sister, calm down!
Listen, look at me.
Jiaxin and I are here.
Nothing will happen to you!
Okay?
You'll be fine!
Sister, listen to me.
Your contractions
will occur more often
and the pain will be more intense.
But trust me, it's all normal.
You are fine!
Follow my lead, okay?
Now,
take a deep breathe. Inhale.
Deep breathe. Inhale through the nose.
Inhale.
A deep one.
Okay, now, exhale.
Like blow the candles.
Exhale.
Now, inhale.
Inhale.
Inhale hard.
Alright, exhale.
Like blow the candles. Face to Jiaxin.
Exhale.
Very good.
Let's do it again.
Inhale.
Blow the candles. Exhale.
How do you feel? Better?
Yes, a little.
You can make it.
I'm sorry, my baby.
I was lying when I said
I didn't want to give birth.
For you,
I can take any kind of pain.
Jiaxin,
Hurry!
Hurry up. Hurry.
Take it easy.
This guy
is quite impressive
when dealing with emergency.
Smells so good.
Instant noodles.
I'm starving.
Hey.
Wanna eat it?
Yes.
It'll cost you 100 yuan.
I don't have cash.
I'll add you to my WeChat later
and transfer the money to you.
Hot! Hot!
Xiyi.
You were so amazing.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't even know what to do.
It was all thanks to Doctor Hao's book.
Jiaxin.
Thank you!
Huh?
I want to thank you.
I had no idea
pregnancy would cause discomforts,
and giving birth could be so dangerous.
Thank you for keeping Ximi.
When you are in labor,
I promise I'll be by your side.
Okay.
The baby is born!
You little monster!
Why did you have to come out
while your dad wasn't around?
In this case, how can he know
how much pain I've suffered?
Your husband was worried sick.
He even cried on the bus when he heard
the baby was born.
Let Xiyi hold the baby.
He's done me a big favor!
Careful.
His nose looks
just like his mother's.
So interesting.
Will my baby
look like me?
Eyes?
Nose?
Mouth?
Maybe mouth!
Will the baby inherit his mom's personality?
Better not.
But it's also not a good thing
if the baby inherits my temper.
Grandma.
If I were to be replaced
after the Board Meeting,
it'd be even harder for me
to protect the Heritage series.
Will you blame me then?
What are you doing here?
You'll face a tough war today
on the Board Meeting.
And it's highly possible
that you'd be defeated.
That way, I'd also lose my job,
and become unemployed together with you.
So,
I wanted to pay the Chairwoman
a visit while I'm still
one of the employees of Cheng Jie Group.
No worry.
I will write you a recommendation letter.
Forget it.
I'm very picky. I won't just
work for anybody.
So,
please hang in there!
Who sent me a message now?
It's an Email from the Europe!
I'll forward it to you right now.
Forward it to you.
"To Cheng Jie Group"
"Congratulations on passing PIF certification"
The company has injected a lot of money
to protect our market.
Even so,
the stock price is still sinking.
Since the Chairwoman is in the hospital,
I don't want to give Wang Xiyi a hard time,
but the company has become like this,
so he's not qualified anymore
to be the Mr. Yi.
Dear directors, you are right.
As the Mr. Yi of Cheng Jie,
he should apologize to Zhou Zhan
and sign the contract with him.
I will never apologize to him!
Let me show you something.
This is the PIF Authorization Report
sent from France government just now.
PIF
is authorization of Cosmetics Europe.
To obtain this authorization,
experimental report on effectiveness
and safety will be required.
The packing material
and the substances of essence
will go through strict inspection,
even the testing by a toxicologist.
We've spent three years
and finally got the authorization
for Heritage series.
So what?
The problem at hand
is that Haifei has stopped
the partnership with us.
Our stock price is declining
and the market is unstable.
Don't shift the focus.
You've studied overseas,
yet you don't even know what PIF is.
I seriously doubt your
academic qualifications!
Of course, I know.
Since you know,
then I'll ask you not to shift the focus!
Dear directors,
with this authorization,
we'll become the very first domestic company
that can sell its products
through the major supply channels in Europe.
Chinese products will from now on
be sold in overseas markets.
Cheng Jie is making history!
Alright, guys,
we still need to talk about
replacing the General Manager.
Everybody, listen to me.
Since Heritage soap was first
put on the market 20 years ago,
we've been rejected by the European market
for several times.
And now, Mr. Yi has finally made this happen.
Why should we replace him?
But his recklessness
made our stock price suffer.
With such an inconsiderate leader,
how can the customers
trust our products?
Even with the PIF Authorization,
they still wouldn't let you go.
Seems like they won't change their minds.
What should we do?
Doctor Hao?
Director Xie.
What brought you here?
Gentlemen,
I'm here today as
Advisor to the World Health Organization.
I've accepted Mr. Wang's invitation,
and I'm willing to represent
the Heritage series.
Wish us a successful cooperation.
Thank you, Doctor Hao.
To be honest,
rarely do I meet a leader
as passionate and determined as Mr. Wang.
So,
I would say I have faith
in the Heritage series
because I trust Wang Xiyi.
With Doctor Hao as the spokesman,
I would like to give Mr. Yi another chance!
What about you guys?
No worry. Your husband is safe now!
Next time, unless you are in labor,
I won't forgive you
if something like today's
accident happens again.
Doctor Hao, thank you.
Doctor Hao.
Thank you.
But why did you
suddenly decide to represent
the Heritage series?
You should
ask Jiaxin this question.
(Parent-child Classroom)
(Ninety-nine Things Fathers-to-be Must Know)
I've bought
the textbook for you.
You'll take the class together with me?
From now on, I'll try my best
to take every class with you
and accompany you to
the rest of your checkups.
Why?
Because you've helped me invite Doctor Hao.
So it's only fair that I take class with you.
Oh.
Let's get ready.
(Ninety-nine Things Fathers-to-be Must Know)
Because I can't let the mother of my child
go through this
and face everything alone.
Mr. Yi.
Good news! Mr. Yi!
Good news!
I told you...
Listen to me, Mr. Yi.
We are so in luck.
Look at this!
Take a look. You know what?
Based on the news report,
the content of plasticizer
in Haifei's products exceeds the standard.
Meanwhile,
all the products on the market
that copied theirs
misused dioxane and estrogen.
All the disqualified daily chemical products
have been taken off the market.
As a result, the market is
so out of stock now.
On the other hand, due to the PIF
we've just obtained,
all the supplier channels are trying
to order our products!
I've told you,
chance favors only the prepared mind.
According to the regulations of
the State Food and Drug Administration,
Haifei's products have all
been taken off the market
due to use of plasticizer,
which has severely impacted
almost all the suppliers
that worked with Haifei.
The safety issue of daily chemical products
has once again aroused
the attention of consumers.
After interviewing the consumers,
reporter has found
that when choosing daily chemical products,
people prefer high-quality
and safe Chinese products.
They also become more rational
towards advertising marketing.
Please stay tuned.
I thought working with Zhou Zhan
might open another path for us.
It turns out
it was dead-end.
The Heritage series, however,
rose from the ashes,
and became more and more popular.
The most unexpected thing is
that Jiaxin actually saved us
by stopping us from working with Zhou Zhan.
Whether it's medicine or tea,
timing is important when making them.
At my age,
I can't taste nothing anymore
but medicine and tea.
Didn't understand?
When you are my age,
you will.
Master,
I'm afraid I won't be able
to reach your spiritual level
even when I'm your age.
Spiritual level?
What spiritual level?
There are so many temptations
in this world.
Speaking of tea,
I think I've tasted all the top tea.
But, Master Zhongshan Long,
you only drink one type
of tea for several decades.
I don't think I can ever
have this kind of focus.
I picked this tea
together with her back then.
I guess what you are enjoying is not the tea,
but your memory.
Maybe.
How is she doing?
Grandma.
Heritage series is safe,
and has become very popular.
Really?
Really.
I've been applying for PIF for three years.
And now we've finally got it.
Doctor Hao also agreed to
represent the Heritage series.
Our products have been sold out.
That's great, Xiyi. You are so amazing.
Grandma!
Did you hear me?
We've succeeded!
What are you doing?
My mom has told me,
no matter it's the happiest
or saddest time,
you need to hug someone.
Otherwise,
happiness will become sadness,
and sadness will become worse.
♪Those mistakes I made in my life,♪
♪I take them well.♪
♪You don't know a good thing♪
♪till it's gone.♪
♪When you fall in love with someone,♪
♪you start to hope
that love will be everlasting.♪
♪In the great wilderness of the world,
I can only see you.♪
♪I want to give all my love to you.♪
♪Can you summon♪
♪love?♪
♪What would you do♪
♪for love?♪
♪Don't say "I love you" yet.♪
♪Don't fall in love with me yet.♪
♪Fairytale should have
an impressive beginning♪
♪regardless of its ending.♪
♪There is an understanding between us♪
♪that you will finally find me.♪
♪You are the only one
who understands why I keep waiting.♪
♪I will not run away from it,
because you are my destiny.♪
♪I'm looking for you.♪
♪I'm waiting for you.♪
♪I'm deeply in love with you.♪