This is new.
Yes, ETA 20 minutes, donor is in good condition, hello.
Hello.
The documents are fine, the donor committed suicide, oh, why would this happen when you are young.
Where is the wrong answer in my words?
Gone, wrong, wrong, here it comes, hello, the status seems to be taken off now.
What? It's a tattoo.
Arguing is still quarreling.
Where.
I saw it. I saw it somewhere too. I think I saw it in a 40,000-year history book somewhere. Murning is someone's love, someone's.
Missing donors.
Today the flower of love is abandoned on this land.
Ah, it's an iron plate. No, what body is an iron plate? It's made of a few knives. It's a super power or something. It scared me. What's wrong, mouse.
Yes, come out.
I like you, go out.
It really doesn’t hurt, right?
in.
I said this several times because it hurt.
2 days.
If not, it would be Obyte.
I should have been drooling over this, but the pilot version entered the hearts of others and gained a firm foothold once it arrived here.
This is very embarrassing.
As long as it doesn't hurt.
Isn’t it?
All right.
It would be nice if it didn't hurt, but it might not, so.
That's why I was discharged from the hospital.
Mom, if it doesn't hurt.
Of course, Mom.
What is this, a tattoo.
No, I think it was a side effect of the surgery or just bad friends in the hospital.
You are not in a relationship, don't get angry just because of where your girlfriend is. Eat slowly, your heart rate is over 90.
Like this.
In fact, I don’t even have enough money to pay for it now.
Why don’t you have money? Just tell me what you want to do or buy.
Want to do.
I have a thing.
Just tell me, do you want to try Taekwondo again?
You can't just talk about Taekwondo without practicing it. It's absolutely not possible. It's very dangerous.
The doctor said you can run properly.
Ah, what does the doctor know.
If dad didn't know, the heart wouldn't come.
If you want to do it when you do it, you can go to that university and do Pilates or something like that.
Dad, the thought of your heart stopping during the game makes me feel sad. You even move your clothes and mushrooms when you sleep. Now mom is also going to eat the heart's meal, and your grandpa is also going to learn the words of the cross.
You should do it, come out, my dad.
How can there be someone as beautiful as you in the world?
Yes, gods.
So we have made batteries for all kinds of organs. This is the next one. This time it is the pancreas. Anyway, fortunately, it seems that my father is going to pass away this time. Anyway, you have been revived.
before.
I'll give you everything, not to mention the price.
You grill the meat.
Go out into the world in rhythm.
Father.
Can't.
You know what it is, WTF absolutely.
No, it's not like that.
It’s time for physical education class.
I've seen it happen if my heart rate goes up.
No, it wasn't me who steamed them, but the shoes.
Why are you so casual, really, always?
In this case, this can be thrown away directly.
Today is designated driver day at my dad’s place, so I went in first, bought some sturdy shoes in that color, and spent money and food healthily with my friends, and that’s all for today.
Where is that friend.
Okay, it's hard work, Jin Pil did fat today, so he is doing the Taekwondo style with fifty reverse kicks, ouch.
If not, why is the monthly rent of 100,000 won empty? Let me explain.
Don't I want to give it to you? Don't make me do it. If a savage kicks a child like that, does that mean you want to fight or date? Yes, sister. When you are old, the 20540° rotation axis is also shaking. Go to sleep and come out to have a look. This is all for your own good. Put your center of gravity in the right place and determine your goal.
Recently you.
Why ask me.
What's going on.
Dad, there’s a growing guy coming to our dojo.
Sorry, caught me.
What is the answer? Winning or losing is more important.
uh-huh.
Greasy food is not good for the pancreas.
Isn’t it very prosperous?
Xiaona, why has dad been sick and suffered so much during this period?
sorry.
Father sightseeing is now cordially blessed and father buys a solid flavor.
People are amazing.
Respirator.
Even lying in a coma, this ear heard clearly all the things I should not have said when my father was alive, ouch.
Didn't you hear it all, oh my god, I mean all the sons of bitches in the world, me.
Judging from the car, from the engine to the parts, it has become a sports car.
This video is shared by Weibo: Tacit0924 URL: https://link3.cc/tacit0924
Me too, I'm afraid I won't do it.
So, I think it's the donor's special physique.
Isn't it, he said he has the donation code superpower.
It’s not okay for children to learn Taekwondo. Why do they always have to wear uniforms? Uniforms.
I wear it because it’s comfortable. I wear it because it’s comfortable. The doctor said my heart is in good condition.
As long as there is, Taekwondo is definitely not a good idea, don't run, be gentle.
Walk lightly.
Uncle has been walking around our gym since the beginning of last week, it's Barbary Stock's love, all three of them.
This is a crime.
Selling this?
Heart, three long three or four, it seems like a diagnosis needs to be issued, female.
The student grabbed it slightly and took it.
They all spoke in the tone of the female high school students in the second grade.
What’s wrong with you?
Because I grew up in my grandfather's hands when I was learning to speak.
You don't know how capable you are yet, do you?
No, I thought it was the growth plates fiery open.
Do you think this is a conversion station?
Mom knows.
Mom is not here.
Is dad here?
I have a father.
If you knew this fact, you would cry for three days and two nights and faint, but I won’t. I will.
It is absolutely not allowed to be said in our school.
You did a great job, it turns out super powers are secretly known, here is the formula.
So the uncle’s secret superpower is ugly.
But who is the donor and how could he have such ability?
Don't you know you can make six chess pieces now?
Heart, sun, cornea, heart, liver, pancreas, duck, horse and four people if you find the remaining transplant recipients.
Would there be any clues?
How to find it will be held at Seoyang Park on the 10th. There are hundreds of contestants participating in the annual non-citizen temperature dialogue with family members nationwide, and Hwang Jae-won announced that he officially participated in the competition.
Hi talk to power.
Can't channel, even the cookies stationed there have become.
Aunt is real.
What are you doing there.
Are you like this?
I really need a pair of shoes.
Have you looked for it?
Ouch.
No, no?
Take it, oops.
Could you please look for that one?
This guy spends 10,000 yuan on his phone every day. I guess he has no friends.
Why is it necessary?
Please eat one of these.
no.
Just eat it, I had a kidney transplant and became very healthy, thank you very much, so give your gut.
fine thanks.
Is there anything, maybe Zhang.
If it's bad, this is what the prebiotics and probiotics do together, sweeping the tummy clean of vitamins.
The one from Vegetable Auntie.
Arms, arms.
Even if you sell it the wrong way.
What's wrong with your arm?
Is there any apple flavor?
Ah, but if I eat too much of this, I'll have a stomachache. And our food, including salad, would be cheaper if the salad was delivered regularly.
Let me show you here, oh, why.
After my heart surgery, I can pray well now and my strength has become so great. This uncle underwent a transplant.
show me.
The child's younger brother.
What is the ability of auntie?
Ah, I didn't, I had surgery.
Nothing has changed, I just.
Although I'm not sure, people say that my skin has improved and I've become more beautiful. Really, what's so good about me?
real.
Do you have a super power to become beautiful?
Being pretty is also a superpower these days.
It has come to this point.
No, no, no.
Recently I pretended to buy Yakult and asked for a lot of numbers, which are men’s first loves.
I remember now.
I've said no, please take your time.
Auntie also has tattoos, and having tattoos means having super powers, that’s the formula, but you may not have discovered it yet.
This uncle is Dr. Chuck, a person with super powers, but you don’t know.
Originally, if people with special abilities gather together, unknown abilities will come out. If you find the remaining ones, you will discover them yourself.
How to find the rest.
In the third year of Jindeok Middle School, Do Kyung-soo, who completed a heart transplant, married Do Kyung-soo, the future hope of the five-time champion of the elementary school Taekwondo class.
Is it bulletproof?
If Jin Shan also had a kidney transplant in 1975, Rabbit is unmarried, and there is still first love on her face, what?
Park Ji-sung attended the meeting.
Profession?
Who are you?
My name is Huang Jidong. During the maneuver, I also received Huang Jidong's cornea.
Mr. Mobile said how we found it.
Ah, everyone has a tattoo, right? If it comes within a radius of a few kilometers, it will glow, but this.
Because only I can see it, eventually.
It can't be explained.
So uncle just now.
One is different from the electromagnetic wave WIFI.
is that so?
Another drink for 500.
Great, Mr. Mobile is our superpowered captain, and the captain is still looking for someone else.
It is a military regime.
No, within a few meters.
Doesn’t it say that you have to be there to see it? I wonder where it is.
That's just like before, hacker in that movie.
It looks like a dictatorship if civilian audits are discovered.
Violation of the Privacy Protection Act, violation of the Information and Communications Act, and leakage of personal information.
You don't know that even reputational damage will follow.
No, you were the one who said you wanted to find it first.
The method is not just because it is good and because it is busy.
Yeah, you don't have a job.
Who said what China is.
The writer is the script.
I can't use it.
Look at Heroes, it's over next week, you like Heroes, then you know the community there.
Return to where we are.
I heard that you became a hero. It turns out that we like each other very much. There are many indigenous foreign language high schools among us. Please do me a favor.
It turns out to be a poem. No wonder it asked us to stop talking.
It is close to plain language. What year were you born? I was born in 1987. What is the fast belt of Apple's clothes? Isn't it soup? What is the basis of curvature? According to.
The argument to be faced is that if new life is received from a body on a truly good day.
Like family now.
Decided to print more uncle stickers.
Didn't you do it?
Hi Yolanta, what's your show this time?
Zhu She took the liver and gallbladder of the poor souls and filled it with it.
It’s very expensive now.
Sometimes, when that happens, I will go to other places to ask. You know, there are many cults in South Korea.
You are so annoying, get out.
Yes, I have.
Yansheng Yongchun carefully congratulated the gods of heaven and earth and resurrected Jerry.
Congratulations, God of the World.
A busy man has arrived.
God, why would it be pitiful to do it?
Can making a movie save more lives?
Learn carefully.
How did my chance come about? I heard about it.
I injured my ears when I was a child, so I can't hear clearly.
No, no, my ears can hear it clearly.
How much money would it cost if my daughter handed over the foundation to me?
But I will not hand over the pharmaceutical company to you. I am very proud of it. This is the business my father has been doing since the beginning. I am not a filial daughter. This is Bingjun.
There has been no filial sons and daughters in our family from generation to generation, and our blood is greedy.
I called 45 Shinto head allowances, I'll call you fifty, tell Owl.
Don't flip over because you're injured and you hit the wrong way when doing the Zhaler show at Jeongseon Market.
With.
\550,000 so.
I beat you like a dog, including your pants. You know you took a lot of medicine that day.
Follow the decimal places of the big brother.
It seems that both shit and geography think he is a real god.
Don't talk about Shiva. In order to build this Lezang line, he said the same thing. If you were asked to say that, you would have cleaned up a meal.
I think he is.
There are five minutes left for lunch.
Five minutes ago each.
Only when the position is correct can we work at the right time, and the right time can protect our safety. Please use it safely. There are 3 minutes left. Users cannot force the time to work. Now you see that this violates the Labor Standards Act. Mr. Li Xiuxun knows the law so well. When he was a judge and prosecutor, why did he do such a thing here? Don't discriminate me because I am a contract worker. Even if I am not a contract worker, even if I am the president, as long as I abide by the rest time, I will abide by the working hours. This is my practice. The one who does not abide by what should be abided is this consortium. Is it the year of revival or something? Let me set a date and add work on empty days. There are insufficient safety equipment. If this goes on and an accident occurs, will the team leader save you? The leader can't even save you, and he sent you to hell. Rolling around, you dare to look at the birdman in your mouth.
It's like this, no, change that one.
Let me do it.
I've said it several times, and he really answered the phone.
Hahaha.
OMG.
people.
When will you come?
oh.
Because I saw it.
Why collect people’s words?
It’s not that I don’t believe it.
This is the true use of medicine, countless times, let me do it.
As he was doing it, Dao Bo became excited.
If the people secrete, there is no door, it is very clear.
Why don’t you just kick the dog instead of catching it when you get up?
Mr. Huang Xinling captured the scene very well. There was not a single person with gray hair. Was the person who endured him at that time a special committee member?
Special physique, yes.
There should be people who have received comments.
Ah, it seems that it is pollen flying, let’s stop here.
Just do it, now that you have done it.
You don't go anywhere on weekends and you don't have any friends.
I have no friends.
But I.
I will only love you.
Not me.
That was also the case. I took a year off due to illness, so I had no friends.
You know, when it hurts, it doesn’t hurt, but when it doesn’t hurt, you’re afraid of the pain.
Kiss ancient songs.
It turns out that super-powered people are lonely friends.
mmm hmm.
Did you know that?
What you think it is, is what it is.
The villains are in the same superpowered group.
Then attack other super-powered people.
Why should I have all the super powers by myself?
So we have to find the villain first. Before our abilities were taken away, that’s how we were. People with super powers make friends with people with super powers, and rich people get along with rich people.
Uncle, why don't you try it?
Uncle, if you are caught by dad, just tell me, because I will give you everything in our team.
But what about this villain?
Let’s find out.
You can tell at one glance, you can tell at one glance.
This kid is a villain, even though he is not, but he knew it and ate two chicken wings.
Junshan, I found it, I found it, what my superpower is, look.
Du Gu.
Do I have no super powers? Why am I the only one with a tattoo that's round like plankton?
Why did the aunt go to Churong Station?
The superpower you want.
If you have, you can save people, just like a hero.
Just having super powers doesn't make you a hero.
Why?
Experience value positivity.
There are scoring lines based on the number of people saved and the degree of self-sacrifice, and there are heroes and so on.
I don't really like the score line.
It's fruit, child, what is he, not coming?
Well, that amazing hacker.
He said he found it, but he didn't know. When I came to ask him, he said that he had a stomachache because he ate too much.
Even if they show up, it’s very late and they’re very young, so they can leave their message via text message.
I will return your money.
Damn it, how could Percy appear 11 times in the same position for a week in a row? It seems like the machine is broken. What should I do? Take off my glasses.
This one seems broken.
Not knowing.
I just sit here and say is this the sound that is compensated? See this finger this this this is splashing out, so the exploding curtain you are what Pikachu ah static electricity.
I didn't make Pikachu.
No, this is an offer, oops, it's totally Oufei color, you should contact our big brother Longku, because the text message happened to be sent now.
I gotta push that one.
Although there were five stops, where did they go?
That middle school student can’t come in, alas.
Isn’t this an Internet cafe?
I was originally a high school student.
It’s me, who took a year off and became a high school student.
To go out, not to the Internet cafe, auntie, I have a stomachache if I don’t eat yogurt.
I'm not here to sell Yakult, I want to take that young man with me.
So this young man is not a young man who can just take it away, he opened a store on this young man, there is no Jewish law, have I been raised, that toilet paper.
No.
Far away, not friends.
Uncle, let that uncle go, my father is a Taekwondo coach.
My father is a criminal with a criminal record. You didn't listen to anything I said just now. This uncle just made a mess of the store. This uncle can only suffer losses. He should be a person, not a friend, but he has no friends. He should be severely punished and cannot be used.
Because we were going to eat spare ribs and we were scolded. If you want to start a new life, come here, otherwise leave.
I go my own way.
Come on, just let me go and I'll do you a service, gentlemen.
I said a word, which was understood by the way, but I had bowel problems.
Beef brisket pork chop.
Went in, about 10 minutes?
Okay, how come there are four people?
Are all of you here?
It took exactly 4 minutes and 28 seconds.
Please tell dad for me.
Now let’s go beyond what.
in.
Go ahead.
brother.
fine.
I eat well, unlimited.
The defendant is in a good position because of you. The dog suffered, but it didn't count. After a long time, people knew that it was you who counted the consequences. You are using a plain language, which is similar to a respectful title.
Look at the Shaoz, friends at Chorong Station.
What did my friend say about this person? Do we have to stay together forever?
Then you have the ability to hack in and find it, because you can't, don't you?
Because it is illegal, so I don't do it, so why do you, a law-abiding gentleman, plagiarize other people's scripts? Are you blackmailing me?
That's how it's done.
I took a look at it because it was so neatly organized.
Wait a minute, today and selling a script was also thanks to my friends, so there are no friends.
Wow.
The world of children has been sued several times by famous malicious commenters. Without even watching it, the movie rating Terra is not a vicious guy. Do you know that your coin is now cut in half? There are 80,000 left.
You have to sweat to make money.
Isn't it pitiful that this guy who justly became the value of a coin in someone else's murder case? If it were me, I would commit suicide.
Did you say that?
There are things I want to say, but there are things I can’t say, and the answer is suicide.
Let's go.
Zhishengxi
I can’t bear it any longer.
Really, what happened between us? Didn’t we agree to report it? Hey, this is nothing.
I played it out of pity, I thought you really became my friend, hey, come here.
It's called a wedding, if that's what you really want, let's meet now.
Why didn’t you answer the phone? Where did you go? What happened?
Who are you with?
Are you with your friends?
I have no friends.
What a person has done up to this time.
Who are the friends, give me the number, no friends, you know what's going on, I am a resident doctor, all in the hospital, until Yinghan City, I took them all off, I tore off all the Yuhan City, and I am also a child of achievement now when I play with friends.
real.
I am a friend.
No, no friends, no one, I just want to accept that I don’t need to exist in the future, that’s it.
He did.
The wine died just like that at that moment.
I knew it was you.
Why did I die? The real tree heard it at the moment, not because my heart hurt, but because my father seemed to be stopping. I am a dog, why should I be a lucky charm.
I had a fight and was so depressed that I didn't tell anyone in advance.
It’s over, it’s over, it’s over, don’t run anymore, you will slip.
Have a cup of tea before you go.
Now don't take that stuff anymore.
sorry.
I heard you had a kidney transplant, and it seems like everything is healed, and your face has gotten better.
The skin has improved.
You see, the Master’s wife looks like a young girl.
You took two lives, that's great.
You deserve to lose, don't you.
If you do something wrong, spend the rest of your life doing good things. Your husband's clone can't do that, so you saved many people, auntie.
Don't live, hope you can commit suicide again, hope you don't fail this time, you must succeed.
I was so angry for no reason that I almost died.
Don’t start a fire and let people like my husband die.
I hope the ajumma dies.
Let's do it.
What did you research?
In order to develop new drugs, Dean Song has three years left before retirement.
Three years and four months.
After retirement, will the grandchildren go to poop?
Because of your weak health, Vice President, do you want to do it?
Yes.
It is time for our country to win the Nobel Prize in Music.
So what to do.
What do you think will happen.
Why are you here.
Really no one will watch it.
Stop looking, auntie.
This is the focus of the villain, the uncle is the villain.
You've found it, don't look for it anymore, now.
Oh, this uncle is not evil, he is a little bit.
Not that Holman-style guy, that's me.
I am a villain.
You will only know the pain if you have experienced it.
If the body is twisted, the mind will also be twisted.
Well, I don’t want to see those self-righteous guys hiding behind those guys who don’t want to be seen and cursing at others. I also don’t want to see those guys who are capable and have nothing being bullied.
This is the formula, but doesn’t the uncle have super powers?
We should use this kind of thing to look at it. If the baby is born, it will be like that child, and it will be born very well. What kind of superpower is this? Do you have this ability?
It is 100000000.
This is who I am, so I live this way.
I didn't plagiarize the script. We were supposed to write it together. But I wrote it somewhere else.
The uncle really played with me because I felt sorry for him.
That sentence was cancelled, and I went to say sorry to Fairy Aunt.
Do it, go there, uncle does it himself.
There. There.
He said he found a simple one.
Actual blind man now.
These people are not our believers. They are in a safe paradise and will do all this before the day of revival. When I was there, there was no Lord. I had just reached the 50th floor and the 60th floor. It was completely the best. Refresh Dad said it himself. So what stable equipment is needed in the place where Refresh Dad observes? It’s because there is no trust, so there are many people who are afraid. It’s not like that.
Let’s eat. The district chief has 15 minutes left. It’s lunch time.
Let’s eat something first, we are not robots at all.
How can this robot eat only one day today? Come on, finally one ramen fell today.
Check it out when you come.
Get me a cup of noodles, got it.
Oh, if you don't come, don't you want to know how to work? What's the point of coming? You'll lose all your oxygen. You don't have any ideas and no ability. You'll be crooked.
Sorry, I have to go first. Come back after we meet.
What's wrong? Look for Auntie's super powers.
I'm sorry, you didn't miss it very much.
I am not qualified to be a complete student. There is no such thing as that.
Didn't we decide to find super powers together and become heroes?
Mr. Zhuzi, I have seen it too, right?
I'm not unqualified.
I didn't look that closely.
This is a precious ability, please use it well. I owe you a lot of favors during this period.
Me too, I don’t do it.
Damn it, I ate it.
A world where even living is difficult.
What super hairstyle? I’m here too. What can I do? The chat group that was disbanded today also exploded.
I was nervous because nothing was happening.
Stop it, I'm doing it, I can't hear any sound, go in, quickly.
It used to be no big deal.
If the regional head sticks to his post, it seems that the regional head over there will become a teacher. Go out, two periods.
Use two lines slowly, slowly, slowly.
Where is this.
That's right.
A year has passed.
Yes.
But I just came here, no.
I have no idea.
But no, inside.
There are people there, too, in the valley.
If not, it can't be opened.
Wait, ah, open, got it, open.
At that time.
sorry.
There's no such thing as a water mirror here, because the smoke makes it impossible to see?
Hey, turn this song off.
Mr. Mobile.
Be a child.
Oh, the car is coming.
I'll wait for you.
After you come in.
What do you say? Let me in and I'll give you the directions if you have one.
Either go in or don't.
Open the door, run over to open the door for you, ask you to show the way, you show the way, what else can I do, I don’t ask you to do anything, it’s like this.
Don't point fingers, don't point fingers, point fingers, point fingers at who is doing what, where is doing what, what should be done.
I mean don't point fingers, don't dictate.
Don't point fingers, boys, as soon as they look at each other, they will snap and put the buds in, soldiers.
No, these assholes come sit down and come in.
Uncle's way.
Please tell me.
Put a little bit on the left, no, right, go straight.
straight.
Yeah, there.
Today's center.
Come to Li Sugen's house and cheer up.
OMG.
Uncle.
What water faster?
What are you doing?
Don't just stand there, even if you don't know.
Listen to the sound.
Aunt.
What?
Where is the pillar.
Where am I going, no, if you're going to get me some water, you're going to ask me where I am, do you know where I am?
Wearing a water purifier, what a superhero.
What to do, catcher.
In that case, uncle.
Did you go out and see what it was?
Just like the water purifier bus, I'll go with Honey.
The child is now caught outside here, please, I somehow.
Ah, go to hell, thank you.
Just walk another 10 meters.
This is where construction happens, like a gas mask.
No, sorry.
But I just saw there are a lot of tank-like things here, like oxygen tanks.
Nothing, here it comes, canister.
Not you.
here.
no.
Put your head on my shoulder.
Squeeze me.
I'm.
Too tight, too tight
that.
You love me too.
Your lips come next.
To my dear.
My name is Xu Ruoshan. I received a liver transplant. Existing underlying diseases can be cured or not. I can cure fractures, bruises, and chronic fatigue in the shoulders caused by simple accidents.
A must when needed.
Please tell me.
Ah, the uncles are designated drivers, and so is my dad.
Just now, I saw that the teacher seemed to have taken away something that someone else had just damaged.
That's okay, I just need a glass of water.
It doesn't matter, people like teachers are really heroes, aren't they.
applaud.
Ma’am, I think you are a true hero and I sincerely thank you for saving my life.
I don't know what you are talking about. Stop crying, auntie. You scolded that bastard, why are you crying? It's inappropriate, and it makes you even more scared.
Ah, actually I used to.
Because of depression, I was controlled by anger, took medicine, had surgery, became healthy, and am really much better now.
Green baths are a superpower.
I thought it was his younger brother.
I forgot what happened just now. We have to name them one by one. What names should we give to the hair? Also, why is it that when we watch foreign movies, the heroes all have the same name, something like "The Distance of Man".
Now that I am very strong, how about saving people?
It's called begging, you don't mind, do you?
In English, Uncle Nine Nine Girl is an oxygen tank, so he is a tank boy.
Tank boy, but what are you going to do?
Ah, I was originally Hulash’s agent, so I wanted to be Hulash’s, but is Jiehang a bit like that?
No, but Mr. Hurry likes the mouth of Hurrish Street better than Mr. Hurry's woman.
Yeah, if you don't call me.
Because I can, the teacher's name is.
Since he is the grandson of a weak man, he can just be the weak hand.
Hands are medicine hands.
Mr. Zhuzi's name is Zhuzi, so he is a Bluetooth person.
That wifi one.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, Chinese is not the focus of your study.
My father said to stay healthy. Ugh.
Well, I actually thought about that name, but because I changed the person and added strength, I missed it.
They all speak English.
Because we did it, there was also a sense of unity.
Very good, that’s neat, right? We have already chosen the names for today, and the atmosphere is like this too. Bruzmann fits the mood of today.
The music prompts are amazing.
But uncle, this one is really amazing, just watch it once, the action.
Do it again.
yes.
where have you been.
Meeting friends.
If you don't have any friends.
I have a friend, help me, you.
What power.
Wait a moment.
Because it's Darcy.
Get out of the way.
See, if you have a dad, just do it.
It's still usable.
Because it can be used.
Leave everything to Dad. Dad, even if you become a pauper, as long as you call Dad, he will appear like a hero and help you solve everything. If you have a cold and your heart is not in good condition, tomorrow is the day to go to the hospital, so go back early.
us.
The new neurological language.
I wish all patients good health and a speedy recovery.
No matter what time it is, focus on watching whatever movie you want now.
Yes, I have.
sorry.
Use A for the next elevator.
Related.
Through the procedure.
A life of fighting against illness.
The church burned down.
Which department is it?
Yongshengying Village New Xinjiang Adult World God War Stage Director Facility No. 7000000000000 Xu Ruoxian.
The explosion shortly before Guangrong's death must have frightened him.
No injuries, nothing's wrong.
Thank you for your trust.
You should thank me, yes.
I will try harder to believe in you.
The new god of eternal life and eternal spring.
Coming.
Door god, this one.
Door god, no, last time, fortunately it was organ ritual.
received.
I received Khan.
Has anything changed since I had my transplant? Surgery.
I don’t know if I’m better now. I’ve become healthier and not as tired anymore.
Not that, not like that, but somewhere special.
Uh, I'm not sure.
I heard you looked younger.
Getting younger, nothing to go to, name.
I have no idea.
I am Xu Ruoxian.
Weakness Line Seven Operation The body is managed very well.
Let's watch it again.
Who is where.
Nurse.
Are you preparing for the exam?
No, I just do it for fun.
I am watching.
Ah, great, this proxy driver, sorry, what should I do?
Suddenly we meet in a place like this, okay, do you want to change buses, oh, sorry, where is the headquarters of Refresh Pharmaceutical, I work next to Refresh Pharmaceutical, I am familiar with the road, ah, great, then I'll leave it to you safely, I have gum, gum.
Don't start.
Ah, yes, first of all, we need to do a tissue examination, but if the dose exceeds the lethal dose, we can’t use anesthesia because she is a mistress. Ah, we also have Zhao Shixin storing 70000000000000, which is a bit fake.
Ah, longevity yourself, where, where, where, should go home, yes, ah, but, in a book-ending card urine, is the core library, where the request is done very well.
That one missed, that's it.
Little we are popular little worldly wisdom little worldly wisdom little worldly wisdom.
The Stray family.
If not, let him pass out.
Let me do something.
you.
Wait a moment.
Yongshengying Village is renewed in the river.
You are very interesting.
You planned it.
Long time no see.
Xu Ruochun.
Operation seven doesn’t matter, it doesn’t matter, who said that.
Dean Song has six.
Look.
The liver has a bit.
If you keep it, it will grow again, right?
Yes, that's right.
Handsome all his life.
Shichen Gann has become real wealth, an image within me.
Well.
pigment.
Sorry if it's the same elusiveness.
That's OK.
Have surgery.
bring it on.
Zhao Shiqing is your boss.
Meditation therapy.
When you are in deep trouble.
Catch him back.
Just gently and gently.
Auntie is here.
I'm leaving.
Oops, high.
Thanks.
Wow.
There is delicious food.
Yes, yes, yes, you must be lonely, I'm from the Free Creatures team.
What's wrong, what's wrong?
It's okay, it's okay, hey, hey, I don't like that, who are you? Go with your pet.
Here you go, leaving right away, daughter.
Keep going to the end, keep going to the end.
Ah, waist, waist.
Ah, I can't do warm-up exercises, yesterday it was really, ah, light.
Take off.
oh.
One more day.
Wow.
Come on, watch it all in one go.
Yeah 540.
Did you call me more?
Mom must have finished eating all her kimchi. I’ll get you an empty bucket now.
Aren't you in the same position as dad?
If you need anything, please bring me some water.
Wow, haha.
I just said, you have arrested the wrong person, sir, just let me out first.
This is George H.W. Bush.
Could Dad have come earlier?
No need for a position, just a few simple Nobel Prizes will do.
Your dance is written wrong, you deserve to be beaten by the old man, who will live longer.
Same, please confirm.
Who are you?
Where is it, come now.
Who are you, brat.
It's a magic trick. Why can't you recognize your dad? Did your dad say he was a handsome man when he was young?
Um.
Be careful with the stairs, we will go up slowly, go this way too.
I don't know where my clone is.
Father.
Only with me can one become a god.
Aren't you afraid? If there really is a God, what kind of punishment do you want to receive?
Do you go to church here.
Dad will forgive you.
I know I can't do it, so I don't want to be a god.
Ah, the head is fine, right down there.
I hid myself.
Director Zhao, long time no see. Who are you? I clearly know why this is happening.
I have no idea.
Be gentle, the boss will serve you seriously.
Hey, she.
Oh my god huh?
That's too much.
oops.
What, you, did it? Didn’t you come here with me, brother?
This video is shared by Weibo: Tacit0924 URL: https://link3.cc/tacit0924
He got Iktau Mactau.
You absolutely, absolutely can't, you absolutely, absolutely can't, your eyes really absolutely can't heal me.
Go ahead, so that mom will be really serious.
Isn't the cornea also very fast?
The rest of the children came along.
Do it, why is there one more person, it is better to leave time safely, how much money.
I guess so.
Boy, this is it.
You have to cooperate. Dogs in a weak state will also make a lot of noise when they sleep. How painful that must be.
I think.
No, no matter what it is, no, I have to go, no, no, absolutely not this time, no.
I thought your father didn't know that he was like this.
When did the parents first know?
As long as you smell the scent of Tashi's little butt, you know what's wrong with him. This is what parents are like. You said you have been living in a hospital for three years?
Pro 9° nailing.
We met, so the body is a little bit.
Because it was me, I made a friend, but that friend.
Those things are just that.
Because there is nothing to read.
Wear shoes every day, even if they are real.
Hundreds of miles.
about.
Come in.
Air conditioning our daughter chestnut is also a bit like our daughter why to learn Taekwondo, but said so, because don't want to eat, so don't want to eat, so a group of people.
So your own body.
You beat it until it's a mess, but in the end, it's actually torn down.
Now dead.
My friends were caught by the blood rashes.
We have a relationship that's completely like family, so I...
We have to rescue him.
Can.
Hiding tightly behind Dad.
That's it.
Last time just like the sword, the numbers for the guys in suits were just ages, eh.
Do you want to listen to other songs?
Dad said that even now, he gets excited when he hears this song. He won the championship with this song, didn’t he? I immediately remembered what Dad’s nickname was, Taekwondo V, Taekwondo V, the Li Ge who is united by justice.
Why, why yoga.
No, cheer up, auntie.
Why is this place.
Kidnap us.
I think I've been cheated, let me get out first.
Where are the restrooms.
No, it's not.
Are you okay, kid?
It's very interesting and amazing, I've never seen it with your eyes using wifi.
Maybe because it was only one side, the bocas were a bit back and forth.
Sorry, I woke up suddenly and rushed over.
That friend had a cornea left behind and was feeling a little uncomfortable. Could he have seen these as well?
Will do this too.
The damage caused during the removal process is severe and it is impossible to recover using modern medicine.
Yeah, that's it.
Hmm.
It's me. If you miss it, please help me fix it. Oh, it can really be fixed. The battery is dead.
Drinking water can help you recover.
Drink some water and help me fix it. Didn’t I get you some water last time?
You know, sold.
How to do it.
There are two philosophies in life.
OK.
The god of eternal life and eternal spring, Jiangling II.
Saints present.
Welcome all the careful people. Now, according to his words and his promise, he has returned with a new body that will never die to save us from falling into the fire of hell. Looking at the unbelievers, among the kings who have descended in the body, among the kings of poets, we three, Xu Yingchun, let's shout together handsomely.
I see.
There are two, I don't know.
The rest of my life will be filled with new thoughts in the spring, and eternal destruction and transcendence will also be me. On the promised day, I will return in a young body in front of you. Those who believe in me and serve me will become my 100 cities.
ah.
Um.
Yongsheng Yongchun Xinjiang adults.
Bourguignes.
color.
I will break the rocks of the promised day, showing strength, trust in me, those who serve me, my Merthon.
put up.
this.
The person to be.
Jin Jingchun's latest arrival eliminates all diseases and awakens the lion.
Attach the carrots.
And then died.
If the ruler is saved.
Ah, why are there so many entrances?
Are the artists here?
Right
It scared me.
I'm going to be scared.
in.
Don't run.
yes.
Director Lian Sheng has become a complete god in the latest room, and is back, full of praise for the petals.
You know.
So you are a complete kid.
Brother, who are you?
You are so handsome, Park Jong-min, oh, this is Barcelona's hero, I used to fight when I was a kid, nice to meet you.
I am.
oh.
Ah.
Oh my god, didn't you see it.
How do you homeschool your kids, for adults.
I'm sorry for kicking you, but it's like this for me now, you're a while, always telling adults that you're this guy's way, and the same goes for the dad at home.
No, not at home, of course my father was born in nineteen hundred and five.
My brothers are my friends.
They took it away.
Actually, it was my daughter who said it. She modified it a bit here. Anyway, that’s it. Let’s go to bed. Now that we have introduced our respective families, let’s get to the point. Finished primary school, let me write about your heart.
Is the kid crazy?
It doesn't matter who it is.
I'll go pick you up even if you don't tell me.
I wanted to cover it up, it came out very well, but how did it come out?
It looks like dad.
Hello, hello.
This is the last farewell, no greetings.
Only if you reach this level can you be called a girl, here she is a tomboy.
How much you have done.
That’s great. I feel at ease having such an outstanding daughter.
No children, so no railways, very weak, very worried, how could the Tank Girl have children.
Presigen.
Jin Shannv.
seed.
Let me say something too.
Who are you? I am Yongsheng Yongchun Xin Xinjiang for me.
The brother looks like a villain and has tattoos.
But why is that person the older brother and I am the uncle?
Aren’t you very handsome?
Ah, it's here, uncle.
Like a star who needs to be taken care of.
Person B is speaking, but not politely.
Grab the rope and take out the rope, where Mr. Mobile and Mr. Weak Line are.
Did I eat?
Don't make me do it too much, wait a minute.
Not dead yet.
Google, here we go again, here we go.
Park Ji-sung's useless style.
Your occupation is.
He can't be dead.
But what was just said.
It turns out that before writing the ultimate move, light up the herbivorous first.
That's politeness.
The hour hand is too dirty and can’t survive. What did you just say?
Did you do it?
What is Mera?
Haha.
What do you mean, guys?
Winter insect.
Let's see, we.
Kim Sun Nyeo is here.
Hey, there is a way.
Our Jin Shannv 10000.
It would be so troublesome if you were on my side.
You don't have to do it.
Please help me just once.
Their abilities transfer to me.
That's not 1°.
Lost the ability after transfer.
Then I will keep sucking your blood.
Don’t do it, it’s very clean.
No, just.
Yakult.
Let me buy you a company.
My eyes.
do the laundry.
Really love yourself, cornea focused.
Eternal and eternal new God, may you become the true sacrifice and live forever in me.
My life.
There are two kinds of burdens in one’s heart that cannot be achieved.
That one is young.
What is one?
Only by asking can you get on with the big things.
One should probably take some pictures.
Whether you see it or not, you need a visible God. I want to become a God and make mankind a plateau. Isn’t that what you want to say? Now, it seems like I have attended some cult school somewhere. If I write such lines recently, I will be attacked by terrorist attacks in the ratings.
You have a great talent for capturing people's feelings. He is famous in this village.
If the person who left the message is malicious, I will replace him.
Dad: Yes, weak and kind.
Are they all fake?
Is everything you showed me fake?
Brother, abandoned my family, and all night, it was my property that Tel drove.
The large pillar color presented.
Have you all been deceived and done useless things?
So seriously.
If you want to see God, give me those humble bodies, my eyes, and my age.
Your mouth.
It’s coming out. It’s coming out.
This needs to be dyed.
I think it should be possible.
What is it? If you open this here, it will open, and then you will see that I have grown up.
What to do, but don't believe it.
Are you going to kill everyone up there?
Would you kill everyone who believed in you?
Albumin can be redone, my concept is death.
It’s God.
These Japanese guys.
That's right.
Eternal life in Yongchun New Xinjiang, may you become a part of me and enjoy eternal life.
Kim Sunnyeo, hurry up.
Leave it to me.
Otherwise, give all of you to me.
And, yeah, shoot the eyes, that's your style.
Go search for me.
Fucking Rome.
Uncle, how do I do that?
Turn it off.
I'm not sure.
What should I do then.
I need to use that symmetry thing to scatter, but I'm not a techie right now, so sorry.
for me.
Tell me something.
What should I do?
I don’t know either, I’ll have to wait and see.
If successful, we are the same age. If successful, we are the older brother.
Well, we.
Hey, bring Dyson's tattoo, now bro.
And Aishi.
Hey, stop talking and catch him.
Give it to me first, what?
Discovered.
Why do you want to win? If it's mine, let me die.
Should be dead, someone like me saying that?
I do this, I don’t do this.
The sound that followed.
Becoming so stubborn.
I fell down, and there were our seniors in the women's alley.
It's at my house.
Sorry, Dad is a girl dad again.
Don't you have a kid who is still wet behind the ears?
Ali am sunny.
Your test.
I don't want to give it a try.
I want to be a nurse.
Hey sir.
Come with me, I'll get the ticket, oops.
What to do, Yakult.
Both.
It must be broken, ah, me.
In order to deliver takeout at night, and that Vietnamese meal started to lose weight, and I had to order darts.
But what to do if you do it.
Is this the parking lot?
Bluesman.
Not Bluetooth Man.
So ours is there too, listen to a song while I wait.
I can't tell you, no, I'll hit it, you put that one, I don't like it, you know what it is, ah, now.
Badrin.
Honey, can I get this done in a minute?
If you come out of the convenience store while walking, I will drink mineral water to fix it for you.
Put your car keys there, put your car keys there.
How can we call each other by our names when we are learning to drive?
I'm gonna lose, I gave them that, no, to each their own.
Although we have a name, we don’t have a group name. If you watch foreign movies, when people with super powers get together, the first name they give is Kidman.
Sister, get up, that's it.
Then say it in English, in Korean.
Sister, you can choose the name yourself. Actually, I can come up with a better name.
No, let me build it, because it will be hard if it falls.
Please charge.
I like this friendly feeling, like a greeting.
It's just right now.
A name flashed by.
Ah, because there are five of us, so five people say hello.
If you do it in English, I know that, I know what it is, uncle like this.
You try it.
We can go for a walk together.
We just want a badge.
All that is said, let me give Orecca the love we're giving our family to our home.
All my sisters were with me.
Being alive is a joy and we will only share all the deals this world has to offer and I hope my hands are on our future goals and we know we won't give you our golden rule of what you will do, what you will not do and what you will not do, it's ours.
I'm going to put a hole in your knee.
Now you will only see me.