[Destiny]
[Episode 4]
Geez.
Getting up so early to exercise.
I didn't get enough sleep
and eat breakfast.
What's wrong, Director Song?
You woke up on the wrong side of the bed.
Why not run for a bit to calm down?
Please don't interfere with my work.
I'm going to take a shower first.
I'll treat you to breakfast later.
You’ve got a little conscience.
♪ Your pupils reflect the fiery, lively scene ♪
Like this?
♪ Dispelling my unease ♪
♪ Suddenly, you appear and I tightly hold that beam of light ♪
Forget it.
♪ You're covered in light ♪
♪ Melting away every inch of my pain ♪
This is better.
Song.
Mr. Cui, why are you here?
Director Ouyang takes this very seriously.
He said you're new
and asked me to guide you.
Artists are always late,
not following the schedule.
Never mind, I'll wait with you.
No, Mr. Cui.
I've already filmed.
See.
Your camera position is not right.
Come on.
If you want to make a man look imposing,
you need to lower your camera.
Like this, Mr. Cui?
Lift it up a bit.
Like this?
Let me
help you.
Like this.
Mr. Cui...
Is it better now?
Mr. Cui, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
See.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
I-It's a misunderstanding.
I'm Cui Yongzhi, the Editor-in-Chief of Ripple.
I was helping her adjust the camera position.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Song, explain!
He's our Editor-in-Chief, Cui Yongzhi.
Editor-in-Chief.
I thought some pervert had shown up here,
touching her in broad daylight.
I-It was just
for the documentary's sake.
I was teaching her how to
adjust the camera more professionally.
More professionally?
Isn't this my documentary?
Shouldn't I be the one deciding on the camera position?
Besides, the contract clearly states
that to protect my privacy,
only one filming crew member
is allowed to follow me.
Right.
Then I'll leave.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Song, keep it up.
I'm leaving.
Keep up?
Who needs your concern?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Don't just stand there, let's have breakfast.
How can a girl be so careless?
How was I supposed to know
he was that kind of person?
I'm just here to work.
No matter what you do in the future,
you need to protect yourself first.
You should bravely resist such workplace harassment.
I didn't notice before...
What didn't you notice?
You're quite harsh with me,
but so soft on others.
This kind of person only pushes his luck
and picks on the easy targets.
If you tolerate him once,
they'll keep challenging your boundaries.
I see.
I'll be careful next time.
Next time?
There shouldn't be a next time.
I was just saying.
Never mind, it’s no use talking to you about it.
Look how skinny you are.
Go work out first.
I’ll teach you some self-defense moves.
Stay calm when facing problems.
Especially for someone like you,
who's at a disadvantage in size and strength.
Don’t try to compete in strength.
Then what should I compete in?
What do you think?
How would I know?
Technique.
Technique?
Come, hit me.
Throw a punch.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Today I'll teach you a shoulder throw.
Let's break down the moves.
Put up your fists.
If the opponent raises one hand in front of you.
Hit me.
Start with a block,
then turn your hand around to grab his arm.
Step in close to his body.
Tuck your hand
into his armpit.
This makes it easier to exert strength.
Turn around and retract your leg.
Use your hips to push against his abdomen.
Then,
turn firmly towards your waist.
Okay?
Okay.
Alright, try it.
Here I come.
Right.
Step in.
You're too far from me.
Your foot needs to be closer to me.
This way, it's easier for your hips
to lift me up.
T-Turn your body.
Harder.
Three, two, one, go!
Can you do it?
Use all your strength!
What do you mean?
I mean the strength of all your ancestors.
You brat!
Come on, three, two, one, go!
♪ Waiting for the next shooting star to fall ♪
♪ To fulfill the promise we made ♪
♪ Never to part again ♪
♪ I'll never ♪
♪ Worrying about safety distances ♪
♪ Lying in your arms ♪
♪ Giving me all the courage I need ♪
Tell me.
Was he really taking advantage of me?
Who's advantage?
Are you even listening to me?
I'm talking about Chu Xingyan.
What happened?
He took me to practice self-defense today.
I was falling apart.
You were falling apart?
It's not what you're thinking.
I mean.
He was tossing me around like a sandbag,
just like Hulk tossing Loki.
Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.
Think about it.
He tossed you around like that.
Doesn’t that just mean
he wanted to have some physical contact with you?
Looks like he’s interested in you.
Stop it.
It’s all
just acting.
Let me foretell it for you.
The front means you get lucky.
The back means you don't.
Look.
You get lucky!
Chu Xingyan and me?
He's a superstar.
Who am I?
You’re not lacking arms or legs.
The way he’s been acting around you
means he likes you.
I don't want to be just another fish in his pond.
You can live in many ponds too.
He has his fishes.
You have your ponds.
You were saying
he’s gentle, thoughtful,
and knows how to care for people.
Except for occasional disappearance,
and the fact that
he won’t go public with his relationship.
He seems flawless.
Imagine.
Dating a handsome guy like him.
So cool.
Remember. You have one more friend
means you have one more direction.
You have one more boyfriend
means you get one more home.
I don’t want to date right now.
I just want to finish my work smoothly.
These two matters do not conflict.
You get to date
and the company pays for it.
Such a good thing.
I couldn't even have an opportunity.
No way.
I can’t make
the same mistake again.
He’s not the right person for me.
Remember.
What a hassle.
Don't be nervous.
They're looking towards the door.
They shouldn't be waiting for you.
So many reporters.
It's probably another superstar.
Let's go back.
Lin Haohao is here.
Lin Haohao, look this way.
Over here, Lin Haohao.
Lin Haohao is here.
Look over here.
Look at the camera, Lin Haohao.
Look this way.
Lin Haohao, look at the camera.
Haohao.
Are you here in Anzhou to film a new drama?
You’ve been nominated
for Best Actress at the Golden Sheep Awards.
Do you have anything to say?
Sorry.
We are not accepting any interviews at the moment.
Please stay tuned for official updates.
Thank you.
Chu Xingyan!
They haven’t appeared on the same stage for 3 years.
Could it be that
they're collaborating on a new drama?
Say something, Chu Xingyan.
Chu Xingyan, say a few words to us.
Tell us a bit more!
Are you and Lin Haohao getting back together?
Chu Xingyan!