Are you waiting for her?
Jiao Jing.
Zhu Yihai.
You fell for it after all.
It's over.
We left Director Ge behind.
Who is it? I'm busy!
Enough.
Ge Zhendong is already on his way.
You're useless now.
Keep an eye on him.
What are you doing here?
Sun Qian.
Don't just stand there. Tie them up!
Do you even know how?
Tie the two of them together.
Got it?
Hurry up!
Listen up.
This is a huge deal.
None of you better drop the ball.
Secretary Yu, it'll be done soon.
Within the hour,
Aimin Street will be yours.
Come on, now.
This Ledger is Long Xiao's lifeline.
Of course I'd keep it on me.
Good.
Boss Long.
What is it?
Zhu Yihai's got someone in the club.
I caught her.
Fine, got it.
Boss Long, shouldn't you go question her?
Step outside for now.
Boss Long.
One moment.
I've got something here
to take care of.
Are you lecturing me?
Boss Long.
Director Ge is here.
Everyone, get out here!
Brother Hai, Brother Hai.
I've got a knife on me.
Take it.
All of you, line up out here!
Move it!
What kind of game
is he playing now?
Boss Long.
Zhu Yihai's lackey, Xiong Dali.
I know him.
Security Chief, Dao Balian.
I know him well.
They got in my way of dealing with Ge Zhendong.
So I'll deal with them.
Brought them here today
for you to handle, Boss Long.
So, Ge Zhendong.
Excellent.
Wonderful.
Jiao Jing, you bitch!
Lied to Brother Hai again!
Let me go, I'll kill you!
Xiong Dali, oh Xiong Dali.
How is it that even now,
you haven't learned a damn thing?
You stay put.
Find somewhere safe.
So Long Xiao really is making a run for it.
Boss Long.
I was just doing my job.
Please, spare me.
Just let me go, yeah?
Xiong Dali, look, what a great attitude.
Right?
Learn a thing or two from him.
Director Ge.
Bringing you in like this,
you don't mind, do you?
I, Long Xiao,
am a businessman too.
I don't want to get rough unless I have to.
But please don't push me.
Alright?
Let's sign this agreement today.
How about it?
Where's the agreement?
Long Xiao is desperate to get out of here now
because his bosses only gave him two days
to handle the Aimin Street situation.
I don't think we can just sit and wait to die.
But Long Xiao has too many men.
Zhu Yihai, do you have a plan?
To take down Long Xiao and his backers together,
we have to find proof of their collusion.
Here.
Director Ge.
I've got the agreement ready.
Let's settle this today.
Come on.
Xie Fan.
What kind of game are you playing?
Long Xiao, where've you hidden Huilian?
Long Xiao.
Didn't see this coming, huh?
Even you can get outsmarted one day.
Boss Long.
Surprised, aren't you?
I told Long Xiao where you were hiding,
so you could prepare in advance
and wipe out most of his men.
Jiao Jing.
Let's do it this way.
Who are you?
I'm here for the agreement.
What agreement?
Who are you?
Xie Fan.
Long time no see.
Li Erhu.
Oh, that's right.
Little Fan.
You really messed up Dongxing Factory back then.
Now you're in my hands.
You? A hitman? At your level?
Exactly.
Lili, come take a picture.
Lili.
This is Dao Balian's first time catching a bad guy.
A once in a lifetime moment.
Come on, come on.
One more.
All your dirty deals and plans with Secretary Yu,
I know everything.
In your plans,
I was never part of them, was I?
Zhu Yihai.
You actually betrayed me for Zhu Yihai?
Without me,
you'd still be a bar hostess.
Yes.
You pulled me out of one abyss,
but dragged me into another.
For six years,
for your so-called business,
how many unspeakable things have I done?
I hoped you could trust me,
treat me like family.
But you didn't.
Secretary Yu.
It's falling apart.
Liu Tianqi's been caught.
They'll trace it back to me soon.
What do you mean?
I'm pulling out.
You've made this big a mess,
and you think you can just walk away?
Of course, I don't have to leave.
Worst case, I do time.
But our Ledger from all these years,
aren't you worried about that?
I'll say it again.
Aimin Street is the future
entertainment hub of all Night City.
I know, I promise I'll get it.
What guarantee can you give?
Secretary Yu.
She's Zhu Yihai's woman.
With her in hand,
I guarantee I'll take Aimin Street.
Wrap things up within two days,
and I'll get you out of Night City.
Don't worry.
I won't leave any loose ends.
Everyone involved,
I'll take care of every last one.
Come in.
Oh, you came just in time.
Help me pack my bags, quick.
I have to leave town.
Mm.
Then let me go with you.
Oh, come on.
It's just a business trip.
I'll be back soon.
Huh?
Really?
Really.
I'll be back in a couple of days.
So in the end, you don't want to take me.
Why?
Why won't you?
If you really think
all of this is some kind of favor,
then let me tell you this.
Every single second I've spent with you,
I've wished you were dead.
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
Jiao Jing!