Ji Sung
Kim Min Jung
Jin Young
Park Gyu Young
NO JUSTICE
The Devil Judge
This work is set in virtual dystopia (imaginary society with great injustice) set in Korea, All characters, organizations and events are fiction.
Why did the cops arrest Yo Han?
What on earth is happening?
Why can't you answer? What's on earth going on?
Don't tell me that... Yo Han really did it?
The church...
Did Yo Han kill my parents?
No, he didn't, Elijah. That's not it.
It's all my fault.
I got tricked like an idiot by those people
and reported Yo Han to the police for killing Su Hyeon.
What?
I will set it right, no matter what it takes.
I will make sure to bring Yo Han back.
Even if it costs me my life.
Why—
Why did you do that?
Why... Why did you do that?
I'm sorry, Elijah.
Why did you do that?
Ajumeoni...
continue to stay with Elijah. Please do me that favor.
What about you, Young Master Ga On?
[Episode 16]
What's this, coming to see me so late at night?
So according to what you say,
Judge Kang Yo Han is not connected at all to Yun Su Hyeon's death.
All this was done by the Social Responsibility Foundation Chairwoman Jeong Seon Ah?
Yes.
I heard what you had to say.
It's indeed an interesting story,
but, as you know, we need sufficient evidence in order to make a move.
Wait a minute.
I'm the one who falsely accused Kang Yo Han.
Ah, yes.
You're saying you made a false accusation?
That's right.
I falsely accused him with malicious intent.
I saw him using public opinion to cover up the case of his trial manipulation,
so I thought we should catch him using any means.
That's why I manipulated the evidence and falsely accused him.
Please arrest me.
Hold on, Mr. Judge.
Don't get so worked up.
First, go back to your place and have a good rest.
Think about it a bit more, all right?
Why do you keep being like this, now that it's all over anyway?
It seems you've already received some orders from higher-ups.
If you keep doing this, I may have to report you for neglecting your duty.
And I'll reveal this to the media.
Do as you please.
By the way, you know that a national state of emergency has been declared, right?
If the media broadcasts anything without the government's permission,
they'll be in violation of the emergency decree.
Please search carefully for a media outlet
that is crazy enough to broadcast it.
Kang Yo Han!
It's Kang Yo Han!
I missed you. And here you are, bastard.
You won't be able to get out of here. Why? Because I'll kill you.
I will kill you!
This place is going to be your grave.
Shocking news.
Live Court Judge Kang Yo Han was arrested last night
on charge of abetting a murder and is currently in custody at the Jungbu Detention Center.
The investigation has revealed that the victim in Judge Kang Yo Han's case is
Lieutenant Yun Su Hyeon of the Metropolitan Investigation Unit (MIU).
I can't believe it!
Judge Kang Yo Han who was arrested without warrant
had been receiving a lot of love from the citizens of the nation while operating the Live Court.
As a result, Judge Kang Yo Han's charge of abetting a murder i
s expected to lead to public outrage.
You were the one who put Kang Yo Han in charge of the Live Court Show, Chief Justice.
Someone who manipulated trials and abetted a murder.
My goodness, Supreme Court Justice Min, how could I have known that?
Besides, it wasn't my idea to put him in charge—
Are you going to avoid responsibility too now?
Look here, Justice Min.
Stop bringing shame to the Judiciary
You're here.
Didn't you say you'd resign from the supreme court justice's position?
Someone has to clean up this mess.
I'm not the type to avoid taking responsibility.
How much more shameless are you going to become?
You really had Su Hyeon
killed? Just to entrap Kang Yo Han?!
And you call yourself a human being?!
I didn't know that Su Hyeon would die.
I didn't think Chairwoman Jeong Seon Ah would go that far.
1, 2, 3.
[Professor Min Jeong Ho]
You want me to be a justice of the Supreme Court?
I know well that you are not the sort of person who cares about official posts.
But we need people like you at times like this, Professor.
A president like Heo Jung Se does politics.
And a judge like Kang Yo Han conducts trials.
They are all the same bastards.
They're all con artists who incite the public.
That Live Court Show they're planning to run seems very dangerous.
They're turning the court system into a mere busking show on the street.
Though I'm simply assisting Master Seo,
I think that we have to block this move, no matter what.
Can't we quietly accomplish something while doing our parts?
Me at the Foundation, and you at the Supreme Court?
You're quite a brave woman.
Well, someone has to do it.
When you become a Supreme Court justice, the first thing you need to do
is to put someone near Kang Yo Han to keep an eye on him.
Keep an eye on him?
- Professor.
- Hey.
I'm sorry, Supreme Court Justice.
Are you ordering me to play the role of Judas Iscariot?
Someone needs to be there.
Someone has to be vigilant and keep his eyes wide open even in this insane wind.
It's a request.
In this world,
there's no easy way to bring justice.
I just wanted to stop Kang Yo Han
from destroying the world.
Kang Yo Han's supporters are terrorising me,
and revealing my family's personal information online.
I can't hold back anymore.
I will do whatever it takes
to drag Kang Yo Han down.
Did you kill Su Hyeon?
We never talked about such a thing!
Su Hyeon was like a daughter to me.
Then, what? Are you going to quit everything now that we have come this far?
I remember you saying you wanted to stop Kang Yo Han at all costs.
"Whatever it takes"
It's not something that can undone, anyway.
We have only one more step left.
Don't you want to leave you mark in history as
the great chief justice who would took charge and ended a time of chaos?
Don't you?
Supreme Court Chief Justice.
Someone had to become a monster to stop Kang Yo Han.
You can spit at me all you want.
Because, at the end of the day, it is history that will evaluate me.
You dirty hypocrite.
Tell security to come in.
How could you do this? How could you kill Su Hyeon?
How could you do that to Su Hyeon?! How could you kill Su Hyeon?!
Tell me. Tell me, Min Jeong Ho!
Tell me, Supreme Court Justice!
Tell me!
Let go of me. Let me go! Min Jeong Ho!
Say it! Say it!
Tell me, how you could do that?!
Min Jeong Ho!
Judge Kim, what was that on the news?
That's not true, uh? Judge Kang didn't do it, right?
No, he didn't. The foundation set up a trap.
That's what I thought.
What do I need to do? I will help.
We have to save our chief.
Wow! Look at whom we have here.
People said you'll run into your worst enemy at the worst place and time.
Do you know how hard it's been for me because of you?
- Has the part with the prison warden been resolved?
- Yes.
I've frightened him properly, so he'll do what he's told.
Is that what the Minister of Justice ordered?
[Nam Si Wu, Warden of Southern Gyeonggi Prison]
It is true, that it was Minister Cha Gyeong Hui's orders.
[Do Yeong Chun was replaced at the instruction of Minister Cha Gyeong Hui.]
Is it true that you were bribed or threatened?
I apologize. I couldn't withstand the minister's threats.
I was demoted and kicked out to here, because of you.
Isn't it a good thing that you're here to take full charge of a suspect of a major case?
How dare you be so arrogant?
Hey, you jerk. Do you think you're still a judge?
You're a rat in my hands now, don't you know?!
Oh my!
Our chairwoman is really amazing.
When you did you turn Min Jeong Ho over to our side?
- You're the best! You're the best!
- You're the best.
Ah, this one ... Yes.
All right. Our Chairwoman Jeong—
Sit.
Chairwoman Jeong is certainly an excellent storyteller.
You know how Jesus loved Judas the most among his disciples
and then Judas stabbed him in the back later and totally betrayed him?
I bet Kang Yo Han
is going crazy in jail right now.
Abetting murder of a cop! Wow!
Kang Yo Han is definitely out of the picture now.
I wonder if Kang Yo Han even needs to go to trial.
What are you talking about?
Since Kang Yo Han's off the stage,
if he disappears quietly and quickly, wouldn't everyone be so happy?
This is what I've been thinking about.
Our president thinks too much.
They say if you think of trivial things, the day you die is not far away.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you'll take good care of it, I'm sorry.
I'm going to ... I'm need to go to the bathroom.
Stop right there!
Why are you doing this to someone
who knows what they're doing?!
That's right!
Our Chairwoman Jeong is no ordinary woman.
Ajeossi Heo Jung Se also adapts quickly.
He changed completely as soon as his role changed.
That's right.
But ...
it's too overtly fast.
What do you mean?
Not to mention, those money-hungry old men
are actually being careful around Heo Jung Se, who's practically useless?
I might've been underestimating Heo Jung Se.
Find out. There is definitely something going on there.
Heo Jung Se, that man,
was obsessed with increasing the number of people who were forcefully removed.
Check out the shelters in the Dream Village.
See if there are any missing people or not,
if they are being taken away somewhere else or not.
Thank you for supporting my husband's plan this time.
The weekend farm?
You all did a great job convincing your husbands.
It was a very close call.
Don't worry about it. To be honest, we support anything that makes us money.
While we're on the subject, do you ladies want to visit the weekend farm?
It sounds good. I am curious to see...
whether our crops are growing well.
All right, I'll set it up.
Even if you got tricked, how could you frame Judge Kang for murder?
I know I'm being shameless, but please help me out just this once.
I need to save Chief Kang, but I can't do it without your help.
I'm not sure.
I don't know if we can continue to trust you.
There's no time.
Do you think those people will leave him alone until the trial?
We don't know what they might do to him.
The only way is to expose something big and render them helpless.
If the public's attention falls on them, then they won't be able to do anything for a while.
Wait a minute. What do you mean by something big?
Inside the Dream village.
It must be dismal like an internment camp. We need to expose that.
That's impossible.
Military men guard the place.
I'll go alone.
Where is the place that has the tightest security?
That place is the one they want to hide most.
Then that would be the Dream Village Medical Center,
but even if you somehow manage to get in, there's no way you can get out of there.
Will you still go?
Yes. You just have to get me in.
All right. Let's say you get lucky enough to get out of there after filming something
but you have no way to reveal it.
Journalists and the media are being careful around the government.
Video platforms and social media have all been shut down.
Now, this country
is no longer a free nation.
About that...
I have an idea.
What's your idea?
Please get me one thing.
Elijah.
There is something I really wanted to tell you.
Not so long ago, I met with the person who used to work at the church.
The electrical wiring was just so old
that a fire erupted from the power distribution board.
A simple accident that was no one's fault.
But Yo Han made you suspect him on purpose.
You said that once you could walk, you'd kill me first.
Do one thing at a time, step by step, hmm?
He made a donation cancellation certificate on purpose just for you to see it,
and kept telling you things to make you irritated.
I don't care about a guy I've already killed
if I actually killed him.
Because you struggled with losing your parents.
You didn't eat or sleep, and you got thinner every day.
So Yo Han wished that at least the strength of hating him could make you live.
But Elijah, even if you misunderstood him
that's not your fault.
Yo Han did it himself because he wanted to.
You are not to be blamed, Elijah.
Thus, if you see him again, be good to him.
Yo Han will come back to your side for sure.
It won't take long, I promise.
So at least eat a little.
What if you are sick when he comes back?
Yo Han!
You're already on death row, so you can be executed at any time, if that's what you want.
Please spare me.
That's all the strength of your voice?
Please save me. Save me!
Run away now. Hurry.
Stop there!
Dream Village Food
Phase 3 clinical trial in progress
Restricted Area
Just hold it in a little more.
More, more.
It's done.
Ah, my headache!
Han So Yeon, what happened to you?
It's me, Kim Ga On.
Judge Kim, how did you manage to come here?
Don't worry now.
The president is coming in!
The president is here!
I'll be right back. Just a moment.
Our chosen medical staff.
You really worked hard.
As requested by the EU, we're clinically testing the new vaccine.
The subjects are now 3620 people overall.
Out of those subjects, 182 have passed away due to side effects.
182 people? That's not bad.
Share the results with the client and report any countries behind on their payment to me.
Oh, and we've gotten new requests from several other countries, including Russia and Japan,
so I think we need to expand our farm in a hurry.
Since many countries are competing to develop a vaccine first,
the demand for clinical trials is extremely high right now, Mr. President.
Wow, if Seoul residents aren't enough,
then we may need to bring in people from Busan, Daegu, and even Gwangju!
Even though our country doesn't produce a drop of oil, we can still make a living with our human resources.
As I've always said, people are the most precious things.
I've been telling you this so many times, right?
Look around, all of this, everything here is money.
Do you know how much each person is worth in clinical trials?
It's no joke.
Not to mention, when they die, we can harvest all their functioning organs.
Even their hair, blood, and all the byproducts...
We collect them all and export them. Nothing—
Nothing goes to waste.
Mr. President, you're quite the businessman!
But you've been pretending you weren't the whole time.
Were you going to hog all the profits to yourself? You were so mean.
I was waiting for the right moment to share it with you.
But does Jeong Seon Ah have to be a part of it too?
I'm not saying we should leave her out though.
We would have bigger shares, it's not a bad thing.
Besides, she's not that useful anymore anyway.
Both Cha Gyeong Hui and her, ugh, I hate aggressive women.
She's too uselessly smart...for a lowly maid.
Right? Now's our opportunity to cut her off.
Oh, and send someone to the prison to take care of Kang Yo Han cleanly before he causes any trouble.
Yes, Mr. President!
Why are you being like this?
Do you like it?
- Let's go together.
- We should go too.
Miss So Yeon, let's get out of here.
What are you doing?
I've been ordered to check her vitals.
All right.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Don't be too nervous, Judge.
Honestly, I've been waiting for someone to come help, and I'm not the only one.
We've been all confined here and our phones have been taken away.
There are even sane people in here.
Does it make sense? How can the country do such a thing to its citizens?
This person is dead. The organs have been harvested and we're on our way to the incinerator.
We will help you.
Since we will get you two out of here, please be sure to let the world know
what's happening in here.
Yes, I will do so.
Are you all right, miss So Yeon?
Yes, Judge Kim? Are you all right?
Yes.
I saved Han So Yeon. We got lucky.
Did you get what I asked for?
Is there really no other way?
How about looking for a reporter who is brave enough to report this...?
That's a long shot. We don't have time for that.
All right.
Phase 3 clinical trial in progress | sector 120-27
You look so pretty. How old are you?
I'm 18 years old.
What did I do...
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry, really.
Sorry...
Judge Kim. Did you figure out a way?
I have a request for you, Judge Oh.
Just tell me. I'll do anything.
Tomorrow is Supreme Court Chief Justice Min Jeong Ho's inauguration.
That's all I need to do, really?
Yes, I'll ask you this one thing.
All right, but what do you plan to do at his inauguration?
[From Judge Jeong In Seok: We've got a big problem Judge Oh. Turn on the TV quickly.]
Judge Kang who had been arrested for murder is dead.
[Judge Kang Yo Han stabbed to death by an unidentified assailant at the detention center]
Judge Kang Yo Han was held in custody at Jungbu Detention Center
where it seems he was stabbed by an unknown assailant.
Judge Kang Yo Han was the first judge in Korea to...
[Judge Kang Yo Han stabbed to death by an unidentified assailant at the detention center]
Eonni.
It's okay.
I was going to end him with my hands anyway.
It's for the best.
It's really the end now.
"The End" shows up boldly on the screen,
and the ending credits roll up.
Then, finally, the lights come back on.
And the audience claps and leaves.
I guess Kang Yo Han had grown on me a bit.
I think I'll miss him a little, Mr. President.
Should we host a memorial for him every year?
Okay, then we'll stick a candle and an incense stick into a cake,
and lay out the meat pancakes and japchae(Noodle dish with vegetables and meat...
Is there something you need to think seriously about? Or any worry?
Pardon?
No way.
I was just... thinking about how much we went through because of him.
It was painfully irritating.
It's was definitely irritating and sickening.
We should say bye-bye to him now.
So I was thinking...
What do you think about hosting something small and meaningful?
Like what?
Something to commemorate Kang Yo Han and celebrate us, how's that?
And Supreme Court Chief Justice Min Jeong Ho will be inaugurated tomorrow too.
So?
Now you'll be able to reign forever.
We should celebrate with all the core members of the Foundation.
In the courtroom where that bastard Kang Yo Han held trials
and dared to challenge you.
What's up with you, Chairman Min? Is it your time to die? Why are you acting out of character?
That's not bad, that's not bad, that's not bad.
Ah, call Jeong Seon Ah and make sure she'll be there.
Even when I sleep, I wake up with my heart pounding.
I really understand you two, but her I really ...
How dare she ...
Why don't we end her as well at one shot, right there in the courtroom
where her lover played court games?
Chairwoman Jeong Seon Ah.
Now that it's all over, we should all make a toast.
It's your era now, Chairwoman Jeong!
It's about time we get a female president!
Fine, then. See you at the Supreme Court.
All right.
Jae Hui.
Yes, Eonni?
Get me a pistol.
A cute one that will fit in my purse.
Why this?
I.. think I'll become the president.
I have to protect myself now.
You worked hard, all this time.
These chaotic times are now over.
[Press conference marking Chief Justice Min Jeong Ho's inauguration.]
This is the time to straighten justice, that has fallen apart.
I will become the Chief Justice of the Supreme Court,
who will gradually build up the collapsed judiciary system,
step by step from its foundation.
Thank you.
Chief Justice, may I ask why you called a press conference separately
without an official inauguration event?
We're in a national state of emergency, aren't we?
I believe this is not the time to prioritize my personal honor.
Please understand. Thank you.
- Way to go!
- What's your next plan?
Supreme Court Chief Justice!
Congratulations.
Thank you Judge Oh.
While you were talking to the press just before,
Chairwoman Jeong Seon Ah asked to meet with you privately.
She asked me to deliver the message.
- Really?
- She said she'd wait in your old office,
since it's empty.
All right.
Judge Kim, I delivered him the message as you asked.
Thank you Judge Oh.
Get out of the building now.
Out of the building? Why?
I will tell you later. Please listen to what I am saying right now.
All right.
Wow, now that I'm actually here, I can see that the interior is completely custom made.
I am devouring this view.
Everything seems to be beneath me from here.
This is the reason why Kang Yo Han
was so cocky and arrogant.
Chairmwoman Jeong. You just sitting there,
you have an aura almost like a halo behind you.
- It's shining.
- She's right. She's right.
Whenever there's an important event for the foundation, let's do it here, Chairwoman.
Without a doubt the stage production is different because the ladies are high-class.
- Of course, it's our specialty.
- You don't know anything.
Honey!
Let's drink to the end.
Ah, really.
Ga On! Ga On! Why are you doing this? Ga On.
Ga On!
Let's go together, Professor.
There's no media outlet with a conscience, that will report the truth.
Still, it would be different if it were some exciting news that could make money.
Like the new chief justice, who blew himself up with his student,
on his inauguration day.
When the bomb explodes
an email in my name will go out at once to all the major media outlets.
It's an email about the reality of the Dream Village business.
They won't be able to ignore it this time.
Think of this
as atonement for ... Su Hyeon.
That is if you still have some conscience left.
No, Ga On.
Am I a bit late?
It took time as I was coming back from hell.
Chief.
You were alive. It's such a relief!
What happened?
You're a rat in my hands now, get it?!
But Warden,
how was the weather in the Bahamas?
What are you talking about right now?
You've been committing all sorts of crimes over the last 30 years,
and have tenaciously saved up 12 billion won.
You put it all into your secret Bahamas bank account,
during your vacation there last summer.
How do you know about that?
Sit down.
I said sit down.
Do you think it's sheer coincidence that you have come this far without being fired?
You are my insurance
that I have prepared for emergencies.
Go check it.
That money isn't there anymore.
Please save me, Judge Kang.
That money is my life. What do you want?
What do I have to do?
- Your specialty.
- Excuse me?
Switching prisoners.
But you're too well known. There's no way we won't be caught.
Who said anything about going undetected forever?
Only for 24 hours,
Just endure it for exactly 24 hours.
And I will give you your money back.
Really?
♫ My thoughts are covered in the scent ♫
♫  I try to find a water source, a river or an ocean gold.  ♫
♫ Who might help me with what I seek  ♫
♫  Can't believe it's so hard to think of a way out, out it seems ♫
♫ I pour my tears in the glass, water my plants ♫
♫ And drink the rest (And drink the rest) ♫
♫ From drought to flood, so obscene ♫
♫  That's my very own inner evergreen
(That's my very own inner evergreen) ♫
♫ There's still a drought in my mind
My thoughts are drowning me all right ♫
♫ Completely blind (Completely blind) ♫
♫  It is that drains my mind,
whatever makes me write these rhymes  ♫
You've done something cute, Warden.
No. It wasn't me.
The guy from the Blue ... Blue House did it.
Well, this wasn't a part of the plan, but it worked out for the best.
You've got a dead body to replace me, right?
Yes, sir.
Are you saying that you had a plan?
To get out of there on your own?
No way.
I'm sorry, Judge Ga On.
Lawyer Go.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
I wasn't sure we could trust you completely.
You got out with the help of the guy who had replaced Do Yeong Chun.
Then, did you really give back the money?
I gave it back,
with love rather than money.
Warden's Office
♫ If you can hide, hurry and avoid me. ♫
♫ Rockin' rockin' rockin' rockin' like a fire fire ♫
♫ Gotta burn it all the pain ♫
[From Hanil Senior Center: Thank you for your donation.]
[From Korean Animal Shelter: Thank you for your support.]
[Center for Abused Children: Thank you for your great love.]
[Hope Orphanage: Thank you for your donation.]
Kang Yo Han, you bastard!
What are you going to do?
He has to pay for his crimes.
The cost of a life is a life.
As for this man, Min Jeong Ho,
please let me handle him myself.
♫ Fire fire  ♫
♫ You can't hide away from me ♫
♫ Break me if you want. Hey what you gonna do? ♫
- Cheers!
It's too high!
It's always fun.
What's going on?
What is this?
Is there an event today?
Who prepared this?
It's weird.
It's not me.
Hello everyone.
To Kang Yo Han, who is in heaven!
The atmosphere is nice.
Now that we're all in one place and seeing each other face to face,
it feels new.
I'm pleased to see you too Kang Yo Han!
Thank you for the hearts, Chairman Park.
What... What?
So, you are alive.
This is live right now, isn't it?
He's dead.
What kind of prank is this?
I'm hurt you think it's a joke.
It's a sacred trial.
A trial? What did he say?
You've blocked all the newspapers, broadcasts, and the internet,
but you've missed one thing.
Wait a minute...
DIKE app?
Bingo!
I'm going to start the live broadcast now.
Citizens of the nation
everyone's last live trial is starting now.
[The Live Court Show. The last live court begins!]
The Live Court Show
I will introduce today's cast first.
Saram Media chairman Park Du Man,
Saram Media finance director Pi Hyang Mi,
Minbo Group director Kim Sang Suk,
Minbo Group chairman Min Yong Sik,
First Lady of Korea Do Yeon Jeong,
President of Korea Heo Jung Se.
Why also me...
These are the people who run the country.
- Honey!
- Why aren't I getting service?
Honey. Honey, what happened?
I'm not getting service.
This is terrorism against the head of state! It's a crime!
Yes, that's right it's a crime. I'm a criminal.
But what about you all?
Aren't you all criminals? Mr. President?
[Footage captured Inside the Dream Village]
DIKE app
100,175 viewers
Footage captured inside the Dream Village.
Dear citizens.
This is the reality of the Dream Village business.
You guys were doing that dirty crap behind my back, weren't you?
You knew about it?
- You crazy—
- Isn't this horrible?
They're taking people away with the excuse of a virus that doesn't even exist,
and selling them as the subjects of human experiments.
This is an idea that only a creative nutcase can think of.
- It's fabricated.
- I respect you, Mr. President.
Falling for a scheme— Wait—
Dear citizens, whom I love and respect!
This video was all fabricated!
This is an anti-national move to overthrow the current government!
- As I've always said,
- What?!
people are the most precious thing, right?
Look around, all of this, everything here is money.
Do you know how much each person is worth in clinical trials?
It's no joke.
Not to mention, when they die, we can harvest all their functioning organs.
Even their hair, blood, and all the byproducts...
We collect them all and export them.
Nothing goes to waste.
I didn't know ...
As expected, you look good on screen, since you were an actor.
These are the people who died at the hands of Jeong Seon Ah, the chairwoman of the Social Responsibility Foundation.
Because of her ambitions.
And to attack me,
she killed innocent people.
Also, Chief Justice Min Jeong Ho, who took office today,
is a hypocrite,
591,897 viewers
Min Jeong Ho, the current Chief Justice of the Supreme Court.
who has been playing the role of Jeong Seon Ah's informant.
Min Jeong Ho betrayed Lieutenant Yun Su Hyeon, who was like a daughter to him,
and worked with Jeong Seon Ah, who had Lieutenant Yun killed.
Isn't that really alarming?
Go and ...
live in hell for the rest of your life.
Your name will go down in history.
Just as you wished.
Dear citizens, are they guilty?
[Guilty]
[Your vote is done.]
National Voting Status
936,648
Guilty 99%
Innocent 1%
No!
I'm innocent. I'm innocent.
In that case, we need a proper punishment.
What is that? What is that?
Is that in here now? That?
What is that, honey? What's going on?
The moment any of you try to get out of here,
this bomb explodes.
What do we do?
- Check it out.
- Honey, what do we do?
Honey.
It's really there!
Citizens, please form the judgment yourself.
Our president won ten million votes in the presidential election.
The moment that the number of clicks on the DIKE app reaches that number,
you'll be able to see a magnificent firework display.
Celebrating the victory of democracy.
I will be going now.
Where do you mean, Judge?
To the stage.
Facing the judge's bench, the door on the left...
- Kang Yo Han, that bastard.
- Honey. Honey.
- It doesn't open? It d-doesn't open? It doesn't open?
- It doesn't open.
Damn it!
Oh my! Oh my! Oh my. Oh my.
- Kang Yo Han!
- Oh my!
One more step and I will blow this place up right now.
Dear citizens.
The video of the Dream Village hospital I showed you earlier
was taken by Judge Kim Ga On, at the risk of his own life.
After all this is over,
Judge Kim will make a statement on all the facts.
These villains will go to hell with me.
No!
Judge, you have to save my life.
Didn't I do everything you told me to do?
Didn't I bring them all here?!
- Hello?
- It's been a while, Chairman Min.
You — How did you ... ?
We don't have time, so listen to me carefully.
There's something you have to do for me.
At Min Jeong Ho's inauguration, make all the foundation members gather at the live court.
What did you say? What kind of crazy shit are you —
If you don't, you will be done for.
I have evidence that you tampered with the foundations' slush fund to prevent Minbo Group's bankruptcy.
Don't lie to me!
If you don't believe me, open your desk drawer. I put a copy in there.
You daringly stole their money.
Save me. If that's revealed, I'll be dead.
If you want to live, do as I tell you right now.
You son of a b*tch.
Hey, you crazy bastard!
Get off me!
How dare you... ? Should I kill you?
You crazy clown bastard.
Save me. You have to save me!
Wow. All right.
I will give you a chance because you made a deal with me.
- It's open. The door is open.
- Oh, the door opened.
Isn't this situation ...
feel a bit familiar to you?
Just like in the catholic church, ten years ago.
Run for it. Only one person on a first come first served basis.
Only one person on a first come first served basis.
No!
Yo Han ...
Hyung.
Wait a minute. Wait a ... Wait a ...Wait a minute!
Be quiet! Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Kang Yo Han. Wait a minute.
Make ... a deal with me.
Be quiet! Attention!
Kang Yo Han!
All you have to do is save me, really.
I'm the commander-in-chief of the military. We can do a win-win situation.
These guys are just businessmen and women.
I'm different from them.
Without me, what would happen to the country?
I'm the Republic of Korea. I'm an artist and a leader.
Please just save me this once.
This country ... please! I'm the king!
Please, I'm the king! I'm ... I'm the king! I'm the king! I'm the king! I'm the king— !
♫ I can't breathe, I can't breathe ♫
♫ Get me out of this darkness ♫
That bastard is annoyingly loud.
♫ which has lost its light ♫
♫ I can't breathe ♫
♫ I cannot stop it anymore, it swallows me whole  ♫
♫  Save me from myself  ♫
♫ Am I lost in ♫
- Shoot him! Shoot him! Shoot him!
- Shoot him!
♫ a dense fog? ♫
- Please shoot him.  - Shoot. I told you to shoot. Shoot.
Shoot him.
♫ but I can't see ahead ♫
Is it the two of us, in the end?
Come with me, Seon Ah.
♫ No matter how much I shout to reach out and save me ♫
♫ I can't breathe, I can't breathe ♫
♫ I'm suffocating
Save me from this pain
I can't breathe ♫
♫ Save me from this pain ♫
♫  I can't breathe ♫
Goodbye, Young Master.
♫ I can't breathe ♫
♫ I cannot stop it anymore, it swallows me whole  ♫
♫ Save me from myself  ♫
Damn it, this is bullshit.
It's okay, Seon Ah. It's okay.
Do you know?
I really loved you, Young Master.
Judge Kim.
- Judge Kim!
- Judge Kim, save me.
- Please save me.  - Judge Kim.
- Please.  - Please save me.
I was wrong.
Chief ...
Don't move.
What are you doing here?
You can't do this.
Are you going to leave Elijah alone?
And die together with all those scumbags?
It can't be helped.
After the performance is over, the actor has to disappear.
I will go with you.
You will be the hero.
For the devil ... I'm enough.
Chief! Chief! Chief!
Chief! Chief!
- Chief!
- It's dangerous!
Kang Yo Han!
- Judge ... !
- I was wrong.
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Kang Yo Han!
Judge Kim, are you all right?
The ambulance is here.
Let's go. Can you get up?
Elijah?
How about this?
Are you all right?
You really thought I'd topple it, didn't you?
Secure an emergency exit passage. Check the amount of time you need. Time required to detonate?
Caution when changing location. 1. Concentrate on dangerous columns. 2. Disguise 3. Distance check required.
The focused areas will easily collapse.
After the performance, the magician must disappear.
I'm done taking care of things.
Now you have work you must do.
Ajumeoni.
Young Master Yo Han has come.
What happened? What about Elijah?
That was ...
Young Master!
You're alive!
Were you worried, Nanny?
Why wouldn't I be?
Nanny. You're fired, starting today.
Excuse me?
Leave this house and live freely now.
There won't be anyone living in this house anymore.
What do you mean by that?
Huh? Young Master ...
Elijah is in her room, right?
Yes.
Y-Young Master ...
Elijah.
Yo Han ...
Are you out of jail now?
Is everything okay?
Yes.
You don't have to worry. It's all right.
We're going to go to a safe place now.
A safe place?
Should I show you where it is?
It's a rehabilitation hospital in Switzerland.
I've been continuously donating to them,
to find a way to get you to walk.
Shall we go there?
Just the two of us?
Yo Han ...
Ah, he is alive!
That's a relief.
But I think I will be even more busier.
What do you mean?
The young master set up a health food shopping mall for me.
He said it is severance pay.
He told me to sell healthy and tasteless things as much as I want.
Is that a curse or what?
- You're really going back to your hometown?
- Yes.
Isn't it too unfair to show this charm only in Seoul?
One month later.
- That's true.
- I signed up to volunteer at the juvenile case department.
I'm going to scold the young people who messed up and help them too.
Because I think I can do it well.
You will do well, as always.
You've done a great job.
You as well, Judge Kim.
Call me if you ever come to the area.
Public hearing on judicial reform to overcome the Kang Yo Han incident.
Our new ruling party will never repeat the mistakes of the Heo Jung Se administration.
We have prepared this hearing today to correct the true rule of law..
Let's give a round of applause to Judge Kim Ga On, our national hero.
Judge Kim, what great ideas do you have to prevent disgraceful incidents,
similar to Kang Yo Han's, from happening again?
Is it disgraceful?
Kang Yo Han may not be a hero, but he is also not a criminal.
Do you think people were crazy about Kang Yo Han
because they are just stupid and easy to be swayed?
As expected, he's young, so he's very energetic.
I think you're saying we should look for the root cause.
But is that something that could be done soon?
The order is to come up with some impactful measures
and try to resolve the public sentiment first.
That's right, Assemblyman.
Our prosecution office is considering transferring the authority to select judges
to the Ministry of Justice, so that we can strengthen the process of selecting judges
and filter out risk factors like Kang Yo Han—
What kind of nonsense is that?
That is a violation of judicial independence.
Assemblyman, rather than that, it would be better to bring in Judge Kim Ga On,
who is popular with the citizens, as the presiding judge to form a new live court —
At a time like this ...
Excuse me?
Shouldn't we do our job first?
I apologize.
I dared to say something arrogant in front of the great seniors.
Please forgive me.
We are all people who do the work entrusted to us by the sovereign citizens.
Shouldn't we make sure that there are no people who suffer unfair treatment, that there are no people who shed tears of agony,
and that those who made them shed those tears, fairly pay for their crimes?
Isn't that our job?
This is the reason I became a judge.
If we don't do our job, someone will suffer.
That suffering is what creates a monster.
There is a reason why people get angry.
What you said is great.
Young people should have that determination.
I respect you.
I have thoroughly listened to what Judge Kim has said.
Now, how about discussing practical measures, Assemblyman?
Let's do that. You mentioned the process of selecting judges earlier, the two of you talk more ...
Still, a little more ...
It's the same.
Nothing has changed.
What should I do now,
to help create a world that doesn't need Yo Han?
Do well
or I will be back.
Chief!
Kang Yo Han!
Channel Manager: cgwm808
Segmenters: SignsofSerendipity (Chief), henrri_11, baepsae29, valneijr, ma_xt_26, silentabyss203_410, janiedy, _quisiera1990,
Korean-English subbers: nomi637, roymon, emilyazel, cgwm808,
Korean-English subbers cont/d: kimlunique, euib_ , allie_sun, choitrio, _nyonge, tenshi2408, bluewind,
Translation editors: rmsunako_557, awesomeharry, gothye7
Chief English Editors: cgwm808, irmar
♫ I stay up all night ♫
♫ I think about your eyes ♫
♫ And when the light of dawn shines ♫
♫ I shake off the gloom. ♫
♫ You said I'll live in the sunlight,  ♫
♫ in the sunlight, in the sunlight ♫
♫ You said I'll live in the moonlight, ♫
♫ in the moonlight,  ♫
♫ in the moonlight ♫
Thank you for watching The Devil Judge with us!