[Be On Cloud]
[iQIYI]
[All the comments by the participants in this program are their personal opinions, which do not represent the stance of iQIYI]
[Present]
[Previously]
All 4 pairs of you
are going to perform in the final stage,
which is very challenging.
Because the production team and I
want you to choose a scene from KinnPorsche.
And you can reinterpret it
in your own way.
Redesign new locations. Reinterpret the new background.
Wearing clothes and doing hair, and so on.
And most importantly,
only 3 pairs
will perform live on stage.
And only the winning pair
will get to be
in the next series with Be On Cloud.
Choosing their own partners
was 100% random.
No intervention or recommendation from us at all.
We are also excited about
who will choose whom and how?
But in the end, the result is what we thought they would choose.
We've been watching and thinking they will choose each other
[The Hidden Character]
[iQIYI Original]
[Workshop Day]
The final stage is so close.
So we have to practice the scene together.
And prepare for a workshop with Teacher Ning.
Understand and interpret the characters.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
So you’re confirmed to use this scene?
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
-Yes.
-Okay.
Now let's see how you're interpreting it.
Today, I'm only asking them
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
and let them introduce how they will present some ideas
Try to make it as specific as possible,
so I have them print some pictures.
Let them pick 15 pieces of personal belongings for their characters
to see what they are.
And let them explain.
what would happen and how it will be in the scene.
and how it will be in the scene.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
There'll be pictures of the characters or other actors
that they think are similar to their version.
I'd like to ask what you've learned.
Since you started meeting each other,
with all the seniors
commenting, practicing,
and playing games,
and up to this point,
what did you learn?
I am absolutely certain
that I am very happy.
As for the changes,
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
I think I've made progress.
-I'm hungry, bro.
-There's chicken soup.
Love you, XOXO is only for you.
Uhhhhhh.
I am more mature.
I love myself more
and am more confident.
Since I got into this show,
I've been through 3 Chapters.
The first Chapter
is The Hidden Story
that we had to show our naturalness
and be ourselves.
Talking about our personal stories
so everyone will know more about us.
Hello, I'm JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat.
Back when I was in school,
almost every afternoon for 2 to 3 years,
I always put up with one person
I loved studying. I went to ask the lady in the restaurant, ”Auntie, do you have crispy pork?“
-She said no. It's sold out.
-You're exaggerating it!
OK. Go on, go on.
-You know I'd been waiting this dish for 2 years!
Everyday she said it's sold out.
I waited everyday. And there was none.
When I used my crispy pork joke,
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
I actually saw other people lie too.
So I was like…
OK, I had to say something too.
And I suddenly felt hungry.
So I said it out
quite seriously.
This person used physical violence with his dad.
His own father.
Because he comes from a home with domestic violence.
I honestly had no interest in this field.
Because I kinda had a family problem.
My family has their own business.
But I don't wanna get involved.
So I was trying to find a way to get myself out as soon as possible.
And some people recommended me to try this
and I consulted with some friends.
Everyone said I should try it.
When I started to have auditions,
some people say
try this one.
That's how
I found this show
and applied.
There is something in ep. 3 of Chapter 1
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
that I talked about myself.
First of all, I'm sorry for what I did.
I feel guilty and want to apologize
I'm sorry dad for for what I did.
I said I did it
because I love him.
But I just lost control. I'm really sorry.
I actually didn't want to do that.
But under the circumstances, I had to protect myself.
So I went emotional on many things.
A lot of things.
That story taught me
that I could talk to anyone.
And there's nothing in between.  Talk directly and openly.
Be honest and understand each other without any misunderstandings.
When I first came,
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
I need to change my partner.
To be able to pair with Jet,
I felt so happy
because he's experienced.
He's been telling and teaching me what to do.
Because the scene I had to perform was a kissing scene.
But he told me,
‘You don't have worry about anything,
kissing or not kissing.
Just believe
in the character, and what he wants."
When it was the real performance,
I felt like the body moved on its own.
Like I was in the scene and I was that character.
So I just let the feelings flow.
I'm in love,
but it became a threat.
We're a couple,
but I'm hiding in the corner.
Every wall
You'll protect me
without me asking
In the past, each chapter was different.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
It's not like this one.
The first one was about The Hidden Story.
Yes. I forgot my mom's birthday.
And everyone might have seen it.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
My mom struck me. I was stunned.
I forgot about my mom's birthday. I'm sorry!
What happened, baby?
I'm fine, Mom.
I thought you called about my birthday yesterday.
Hahaha.
I still
don't like
saying goodbyes, like I said before.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
Like...
It felt like...
something was missing.
There are 11 in THC, and 12 including Ta.
When knowing someone has to go,
I was really down.
I don't like it, I don't like this at all.
I don't like leaving.
It's not a very big deal,
but I felt like our intimacies will have fallen away.
I recommend you to audition for The Star.
I want this country to know Kinn The Star,
born to kill Bird.
Searching for the star?
Okay! Cut!
JJ chose Fuaiz, when they got together.
They are the most interesting pair in my opinion.
[Mile]
Among these 4 pairs,
I like them the most.
When they were standing there for the interviews.
I was like, Hey...
There's something about their appearances and what they both learned.
I wanted to see them.
Because one's natural and the other is not.
When they get together, it makes you interested.
It's hard to explain.
[Mile]
The strength of these two is they chose the right partner.
OK, so which scene did you pick for the final stage?
Still the dating scene at a café.
Come, 1, 2, 3.
Hey! What you’re doing, Kinn?
Kinn!
There're people here.
It's okay. C'mon!
We're not at home.
I got feedback that we might play it safe.
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
For those who have to perform, for me to do it, it's not easy.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
We should make the audience blush
like when we saw Apo and Mile.
It's not easy.
When I was watching this scene, I felt shy and it made me blush.
But what we should do
to make the audience blush too.
-And…
-And Apo will be like…
It might look like it's easy but it's actually hard.
-Okay. That's how Apo sees it.
-Yes.
-Okay.
JJ and Fuaiz had made a lot of progress and received many praises.
[Apo Nattawin Wattanagitiphat]
I think it makes them too proud
or too confident
It made them think that they could do it whatever they choose.
So they insisted on doing that.
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
In the end, we chose to stick with the same scene.
It's a very challenging scene.
I wanna try it.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
I talked with JJ
that we wanna try it.
So we have to redesign it all over.
The stage, the lighting, the props,
the blocking, everything. It's very challenging.
-Okay. Let's do some exercise. Kill Bill. Fencing.
-Kill Bill.
Yes.
This is very simple. Just imagine that you are enemies.
I chose this swordplay exercise,
[Ning]
[Acting coach]
because this exercise is used with the actors who still block themselves in feelings.
[Workshop：They must imagine that they are enemies by fencing.]
And it's an exercise with physical lead.
A body leading.
When you're using the body and believe in that situation,
whatever holds you back, the hesitation,
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
[Ning]
[Acting Coach]
uncertainty that is not good enough,
or your concern about your image, they will all be gone.
[Ning]
[Acting Coach]
Because of tiredness.
Okay. Breath. Relax for a moment.
When Fuaiz had to dodge
and I had to slash him,
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
I imagined he was
my best friend who killed my lover,
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
so I wanted to kill him.
When changing to be the person who dodges
and Fuaiz slashing at me,
I imagined that I didn't kill his lover
and he just misunderstood.
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
I was trying to dodge.
And sometimes I lost focus.
I got out of step and hurt my hand,
but I tried to pull myself back to the script.
Okay.
OK! Let's talk about it.
They both finally did it well.
I hope they will discover something from this exercise.
[Ning]
[Acting Coach]
How do you feel right now?
Still exhausted.
Okay.
-It seems like what's inside is still not fully expressed.
-Ah.
I feel like there are some emotions remaining.
I just tried to kill someone.
And the emotions are still here,
because
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
I'm still catching my breath.
Both the breathing and emotions are still there.
Then let's try to shout.
Find your space and shout as hard as you can.
After shouting, I felt some Wink!
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
Wink like whatever remains has gone.
Like something blocking my eyes was broken down and gone.
Okay. I think you did well.
Thank you.
Okay. So go prepare some clothes.
-I'm gonna let you wash up, get changed, and come back.
-Thank you.
Okay.
Go have some rest.
After the exercise, I feel more open,
more calm and relieved.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
I shout when I want to calm down.
It was just the feeling that I wanted to let it out.
-Hello.
-Hello again.
You're still alive.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Now, let's try the scene you picked.
The challenge is to try to interpret it differently.
In your version,
the dialogue depends on who you will be, Kinn or Porsche.
How will it be?
Who is Kinn and who is Porsche?
-I'm Kinn.
-I'm Porsche.
Okay.
I'm interpreting the character as...
The story line is completely new.
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
Porsche in Fuaiz’s way…
is actually not different from the original.
Being a mafia’s son,
from a rich family.
What if I want you to try
to find the way back to the same dialogue.
From beginning until the end.
You might need to guess
what happened to the kid of the main family.
I think what is different is the background of the characters.
But
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
what the characters want is exactly the same.
Kinn still wants a lover and still wants to take care of someone.
Because his dad is sick and he is an only child.
And his mom passed away when he was young.
And Porsche,
he doesn't wanna be a mafia, but to be independent.
Okay. Now this is the last one I want you to do.
I want you to sit cross-legged and face each other.
Try not to do much. You don't have to talk.
[Ning]
[Acting Coach]
Just sending feelings by looking at each other.
And really be there.
[Ning]
[Acting Coach]
So try holding hands.
You don't need to do much but look at each other.
Send feelings to each other.
Try to believe this person in front of you is someone you really love
and you've been through a lot with.
No matter how many obstacles there may be,
you really want to
spend your time together.
And really want to be with each other.
Teacher Ning had us holding hands and
imagining the person in front of us is our lover.
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat IG:jjaypf]
Someone we wanted to be with.
Someone like a soul-mate.
Thank you so much
for being by my side.
I think I feel the feeling of the characters conveying.
When we believe in it all,
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
including the relationship between Kinn and Porsche in the past,
I felt like I have a lover sitting in front of me.
But in the past, I didn't really believe in it.
And when I believed in it, it worked and it got easier.
So I just said what I felt.
I don't want anything else in my life but you.
I'm happy as long as I have you.
No matter what my life will be,
I love you.
Thanks for being with me.
Stay with me forever.
I will always be by your side.
Don't leave me.
I'm not gonna leave you.
Do you believe we're in love?
I do!
[Fuaiz]
[Thanawat Shinawat]
[IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
I believe we are, because
what JJ said was all expressed through his eyes.
That he wanted to be with me. He's in love with me.
When I heard it,
I was like I love you too! I'm not gonna leave you.
I confessed my love while comforting him.
I just said what I felt.
I love you. I wanna be with you.
I'm happy to be with you.
I wanna be with you forever.
[JJ ]
[Patiphan Fueangfunuwat]
[IG:jjaypf]
It speaks out on its own without thinking. Like it was from my heart.
No one forced us to do anything, we just listened.
Really listening. Because it's right there.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
When you listen, you'll feel something and say it back.
It shows more honest communication.
This is the purpose of this exercise.
What you have to prove is…
ur…
how something that has nothing is challenging you.
And what's special about it.
If it was true, it's definitely special.
Actually, I think this is quite hard.
Right? Because
it's not an action scene or there's a big conflict.
-But try to do your homework.
-Yes.
What I detected is some hesitation,
like what should I do?
Thank you.
Okay.
Keep fighting!
-Thank you.
-Yes.
I feel like
there's too little conflict.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
Porsche in the original
has his reason to be in the main family.
And Kinn also has a reason to take him in as his sidekick.
But when they are both mafia's sons,
at the moment they are dating,
they didn't know their
families are in conflict with each other
so there's nothing between them.
So I recommended them to... I have to go along and respect their idea.
I'll give them some feedback later.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
[3 Days Later]
[Fuaiz]
[Thanawat Shinawat]
[IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
So we decided to change.
Because they said that much.
We wanted to challenge ourselves more.
[Production Meeting]
The seniors and the teacher worried about the scene.
[JJ ]
[Patiphan Fueangfunuwat]
[IG:jjaypf]
[Fuaiz]
[Thanawat Shinawat]
[IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
A lot of them think we're playing too safely.
It doesn't look interesting.
So we changed to the fighting scene of Vegas and Pete.
[JJ ]
[Patiphan Fueangfunuwat]
[IG:jjaypf]
If you don't kill me today,
I'll do it myself!
Let me go!
Pete!
I'm sorry. Okay?
I'm sorry!
I'm Pete in this scene.
Gotta say that I'm Pete because
[Fuaiz]
[Thanawat Shinawat]
[IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
I want to try it again.
Because
when I was pairing with Ta, I got low points.
The lowest one. I got only 2 coins.
So I feel like I wanna give it a try again.
I want to spend more time with it again.
[JJ ]
[Patiphan Fueangfunuwat]
[IG:jjaypf]
I think this scene will use a lot of potential.
We have to work hard on it.
Here are the references we want.
Chain and pole strap.
[Production Meeting]
But I don't know how to find it,
so I got a saline pole.
And wristbands.
It's like our project got demolished.
We had to start it over again.
[Fuaiz]
[Thanawat Shinawat]
[IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
We had to talk about the stage.
How we interpret the characters.
Everything. And we have to do it again.
We gotta talk about
how we're gonna perform, what they feel in this scene,
what they will say, and why they feel like that.
We have to spend more time on it.
A lot more.
We have to focus on acting.
Acting is hard.
-Gotta get into details.
Gonna have a workshop with Teacher Ning too.
-Yes.
For the costume, we wanted to change Vegas
to a university student that Pete has at home.
Don’t have to change much. Just add a little
to make him look like a student.
Like a gaming room?
-I don't know.
-Playing games.
-You're a student, you can ask yourself.
-I graduated.
But how was it before?
Just live and sleep day by day. Thank you.
What they have to focus on is to try to do something new.
[Apo]
Try to do something you think you can't.
I think we humans have fighters in us.
If they could pull this back,
the overconfidence will be gone.
And they can go beyond.
Dear viewers, you can participate in a live voting
in The Hidden Character Final Episode.
[Vote]
[Fully Prepared]
[The Hidden Character]
[Final Episode]
[Live Show]
The couple with the highest combined votes
Will become the presenters of Luvys' Serum.
[First couple presenter
Luvys' Serum
Love Your Skin]
And receive leading roles in the next series of Be on Cloud
With a cash prize of 500,000 baht.
[Receive leading roles in the next series of Be on Cloud]
[Cash prize of 500,000 baht]
Additionally, they will also travel to Japan for a fashion shoot
and have an interview with Awesome Magazine.
Voting for episode 11 will begin
at 21:15 on July 1st.
[Voting for episode 11]
[Begin at at 21:15 on July 1st, 2023]
[Until the last pair finishes their performance]
And will close at the end of the final show.
The total votes received by each contestant
will be combined with their own partner.
[The total votes received by each contestant]
[Will be combined with their own partner]
And count the total score.
The couple with the highest overall score will be the winners.
[The couple with the highest overall score will be the winners]
You can vote through two channels as follows:
Channel 1:
[Vote through two channels:]
[Channel 1:]
WWW.THCBOC.COM
[WWW.THCBOC.COM]
Step 1: Go to WWW.THCBOC.COM
[Step 1: Go to WWW.THCBOC.COM]
Step 2: Log in to your account. Navigate to the homepage.
[Log in to your account. Navigate to the homepage]
Step 3: Select the profile of the contestant you want to vote for.
[Select the profile of the contestant you want to vote for]
Step 4: Choose the number of votes you want to cast.
With the following details:
[Choose the number of votes you want to cast]
4 votes: Service rate 20 Baht.
12 votes: Service rate 49 Baht.
[4 votes: Service rate 20 Baht]
[12 votes: Service rate 49 Baht]
25 votes: Service rate 99 Baht.
[25 votes: Service rate 99 Baht]
80 votes: Service rate 299 Baht.
[80 votes: Service rate 299 Baht]
100 votes: Service rate 349 Baht.
[100 votes: Service rate 349 Baht]
Step 5: Select the payment method.
The available payment methods for voting through the website are as follows:
[The available payment methods for voting through the website]
Credit or Debit Card, Thai QR
Alipay, and WeChat.
[Credit or Debit Card, Thai QR
Alipay, and WeChat]
After completing the transaction,
the system will notify with the message "Vote Successful" through the website.
[Vote Successful]
Channel 2: Voting via SMS.
[Channel 2: Voting via SMS
Dial 4141666
followed by the contestant's code and press call]
[4141666]
Dial 4141666, followed by the contestant's code and press call.
6 Baht per vote for all networks.
[6 Baht per vote for all networks]
As for Big Vote. Dial 4141069, followed by the contestant's code and press call.
69 Baht per vote for all networks.
[As for Big Vote(12 points), dial 4141069,
followed by the contestant's code and press call]
[69 Baht per vote for all networks]
Mio and Bump. They've got a good chemistry.
[Mile]
Very good. Probably because of their common interest
which is music.
[Mile]
In actual work, it’s a good thing.
It will make them
want to work together. Even if it's not about work,
they will still keep each other company. And that's a good thing.
I have to admit about this.
[Pond Krisda]
[Founder and CEO of BOC]
Mio has disappointed me greatly.
I still hope that
his changes this time will truly make a difference.
That he will have more discipline
to use his ability properly.
I don't know what I'm doing.
How could life get better when I can't even do this?
It's not fair for everyone. I got them in trouble.
I don't have any excuses. I was really wrong in the past.
I made the same mistakes again and again.
Pond…
If looking back to Chapter 1, Pond has said,
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
I have something good.
But the only thing I lack is discipline.
He said it since then.
I felt very guilty after talking to him.
He has constantly reminded me.
Yet I still managed to disappoint him.
Bump as well.
If we go back and watch the tapes,
Bump didn't even talk.
[Audition Day]
Hello.
I'm Pawat Akkradetsakul,
and my nickname is Bump.
I am now 19 years old.
Yes.
He didn't talk to anyone. He said he didn't want to.
He was afraid people wouldn't like him. It was his flaw.
Now, he's talkative and he is very protective of his friend.
They are really protective of each another.
Whether it's Mio or Bump shooting,
[Pond Krisda]
[Founder and CEO of BOC]
they will encourage each other.
May I say something?
Sure.
Well, yesterday at the workshop
It was just like what Pond said.
That Mio seemed uninterested in acting.
When the teacher was talking,
I could see that he made an effort and improved rapidly.
nothing and couldn't remember the scripts,
or didn’t bother at all,
he could actually do it.
-This is my viewpoint that others might not see.
-I see this too. Thank you so much, Bump.
- Hello, Teacher.
-Hello.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
It looks like you've got some characters.
-Annoying as usual.
-Oh.
Let's start from a recap before getting to the scene you picked.
Since the first day you met until now, how's it been?
Good. I felt like being here is a story of my life I wouldn't forget.
Hello, I'm Athens Werapatanakul
and my nickname is Mio.
[Audition Day]
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
It's almost over.
I got used to the show and things like this.
[Audition Day]
It feels like it has become a routine.
Back then, it was
Copper’s story about the missing tooth.
This person got his tooth pulled out just to get attention from the one he liked.
And I was like,
Hey, I used to have a missing tooth photo.
So I went through it and, Hey, check this out, a missing tooth.
I thought everyone would be fooled.
Because I had this proofed others didn't.
Back then, I wasn't really good at playing the game. So it didn't go smoothly.
If I was smooth and my picture was very clear,
I would have scored a lot of points.
Yes.
It was a crush when we were young.
At that time,
there was a good song
with a good meaning.
So I sent it to her.
The song was Jung-See-Man-Tong-Torn.
I just talked nonsense.
I thought it should be related to pulling teeth.
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
What should I talk about?
“Jung See is going to pull. Pull the teeth.
I was like, Hey, I'm gonna send this song to the person I liked.
To have a tooth pulled out. I have no idea.
It was so random.
When I worked with Mio for the first time,
he seemed uninterested.
And he wasn't really committed to it.
Um. To be frank, I don’t feel like working with you, Mio.
I told him to study the scripts, but he didn't.
Being late. Not doing homework.
Ask anybody here.
How serious I am about this.
Mio didn't seem to care about anything.
And we saw his progress.
[Apo]
Struggling to make progress, so the seniors had to remind him.
Until he got better. He started to improve.
As for Bump,
he is on and off.
Sometimes he's natural, and other times he's not.
It seems like he can sometimes control his focus.
And the other times he can't.
So it becomes somewhat unstable.
But if he's with Mio, they might make a good pair.
[Apo]
Tell me which scene you picked and who is whom.
[Asst. Prof. Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Acting coach of the movie ManSuang]
At first, Bump and I picked the scene that
was really about music
and we believed we could do it.
And when we went to  present to all our teachers,
-They said they didn't buy it.
-Teacher Apo.
-He should have known that we understood those characters.
-Yes.
But the new scene we picked was
Kinn and Porsche falling off a cliff.
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
So tell me how you are adapting it.
-Ah, good shot!
-A great shot.
-This is a highlight.
Say it.
-In this series, Kinn is the mafia. Porsche is the bodyguard.
-Right.
But I saw in their positions, what we really wanted.
It...
could transform into high school students.
Becoming students from the 90's. If we're talking about something Mio and I are into.
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
That would probably be the high school years, a time filled with nostalgia.
I like something from the 90's,
I thin it's very attractive.
So, in this situation, it usually takes place in school, school, classroom or the wood.
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
Based on the original,
Mio is portrayed as a rebel.
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
He will fight everyone single-handed.
But I like cute little things.
I like watching anime just like what kids do.
But I like Mio. As I mentioned before, if we had an argument or something, I would get upset.
-OK? -How is it?
-We have changed our clothes... -OK.
to fit in with the characters.
Alright, let me see when will you get into character.
I believe you are now starting to feel the vibes of the characters.
-Ah, okay, let's do some practice.
-OK.
There are lines like "Come here" and "No." Who's gonna say "Come here" first?
-Me. I'll say "Come here."
-I'll say "No."
"Come here" and "No."
We gotta express our feelings through "Come here" and "No," these two lines.
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
We cannot say other lines or expand on them.
We need to express emotions through words.
It's an exercise that I really like because it's very simple.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
It's just like that, you can make actors to see...
Hey, actually a certain scene can happen
as long as we add some requirements and obstacles
to create a struggle between them. Then a scene is created.
At first, Bump said "Come here" first and I said "No".
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
[Rehearsal]
[Two people need to express emotions through "come over" and "no"]
-Come here. -No.
OK. Pause.
If you've been using this method to call him and he still hasn't come,
do you still want to continue using this method to call him?
At first, I thought it was very simple. Just say "come here" and "no".
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
At first, we didn't seem to be in sync.
It's like, I didn't get the vibe.
-Come here. -No.
-Come here. Come here. -No.
- Come here!
- No!
Come here.
No.
Come here!
-No.
-Come here.
Come here.
No.
-Come here.
-No.
-Alright, time's up.
You did better than the first time.
It felt genuine.
That was why Teacher Ning said it was good. She liked it.
[Bump]
[Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
-Hey, come here. -No.
What I really felt, it was just some sayings. I didn't feel anything.
But Teacher Ning taught me to really imagine.
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
And really see the image clearly.
Come here.
-No.
-Come here.
No.
Time's up.
I really feel like I want him to come over.
[Mio]
[Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
Because I imagined my best friend was about to jump off the bridge. At first I tossed and turned.
I was imagining myself walking on Rama 8 Bridge, with cars passing by as I stroll along the bridge.
Then I see my friend about to jump off the bridge and I say, "Come here."
Don't jump. My mouth says "come over", but my heart screams "don't jump, come over".
I really want him to come over at the moment.
Come here.
OK. Very good.
Thank you,
Let’s have a short break for 5 minutes, and we'll do another exercise.
The most important thing is that we must truly believe that we are there, doing that thing.
If we don't believe it, the audience will definitely not believe it and it will seem fake.
[Mio Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
This exercise made me realize
[Bump Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
what the character needs,
and what happened during the event.
If we believe, everything will make sense.
-Guys.
-Pay attention to teacher's words.
Looking forward to seeing them
[Apo]
being confident.
Because every time the countdown starts at 5 4 3 2 1... they would be like worrying about making mistakes.
Their advantage lies in their strong chemistry,
which means they can choose any scene and do whatever they want.
Just hold hands and praise through fear, then they can unleash their abilities.
I believe they can do better than what we have seen every week before.
[Apo]
Now the teacher wants you to improvise
OK.
Do you still remember the exercise where I asked you to write something
and draw lots?
For that one, I chose to have them improvise in the classroom and create a scenario.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
I think we need to confirm
whether they can fall in love with each other,
because they seem like very good friends.
It becomes even more challenging to speak the words in the drawn content.
Ning asked us to write our own lines for the play. As soon as the practice started, I went up to talk to him
[Training]
[Two people need to improvise. The scene must include the lines drawn from the lottery]
[The lines for drawing lots are written by the two people themselves]
What are you doing, bro.
Do you know? Someone told me that
we don't have to do homework anymore.
-Stop, Porsche.
-It's almost my birthday
Wanna see Nemo. Oho! TaLaLa.
[Bump as Porsche.]
[“Wanna see Nemo, Oho! TaLaLa”]
What are you writing?
You can stop writing. There's nothing.
-Do you know what I like?
-What?
-If you guess it right,
I'll go with you.
For real? You said it yourself.
Hmm, Nemo. You like fish,
you like marine animals.
- Guess you like eating mackerel.
-Nope.
-But Nemo was right. -Really?
-But there's more.
-Really? What's wrong with Nemo?
You know what?
Nemo, oho! Right?
-No. -Really?
Nemo, Oho! TaLaLa.
Seriously! What is it?
It's Nemo.
No kidding.
I just named it Oho! TaLaLa.
Seriously?
You don't have to write.
Cut, Kinn.
[Mio as Kinn]
[“Kinnhehezaza55.com”]
In the scenario that Teacher Ning described,
[Mio Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
tomorrow is my birthday
and Bump is angry with me
because I don't usually talk to him
[Mio Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
when I'm hanging out with friends.
Okay, let's go to the mall, the newly opened one.
Weren't you supposed to go with your friend?
But this mall has games,
you need to register with your email first.
I have registered for you using the same name as mine.
It's porscheeieizaza55+, but mine is kinneiei55zaza+. Do you wanna go?
- No, I’ll stay here.
- but I signed up for you.
-I'm not going, whatever you say.
Stop, Porsche.
Tonight the moonlight is soft and bright, it reminds me of you when I see it.
[Bump as Porsche]
[Tonight the moonlight is soft and bright, it reminds me of you when I see it]
I also want to be with you, but they always ask me to go out together and I don't want to.
-Porsche.
-Where do you go
-Porsche, my bro.
-every night for fun?
I also wish
that you could go out with me at night.
Tonight the moonlight is soft and bright... it reminds me of you when I see it]
But you definitely won't choose me, you must be going out with your group of friends that you love so much.
You miss me? Let's go out together then. Since you said it like that, we must go.
I have a request. Maybe I also have something to show you.
Do you want to tell your friends that you're going to hang out with me?
I want to hang out with Porsche.
Aren't you afraid that your friend will get angry?
-If they're angry, then you should come with me. -Let them be.
I'm not afraid.
They're so weak.
-Really? -Yeah.
-Are you sure? -Sure.
Are you looking at me like that because you're trying to start something or because you're interested in me?
-Screw you. -Hahaha, let's go.
Don't study, let's go play together.
We were asked to play a certain character with a specific personality.
I think Teacher Ning wants us to try and see if we can do it.
[Bump Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
I feel that you are more relaxed than before,
and it is evident that you trust each other,
This makes it easier to get into the scenario.
If you can focus and spend some more time immersing yourselves, I think it will be OK.
Regarding this scene, I would like to remind you
Although the age has been reduced to student years,
the dramatic conflicts of the characters cannot be diminished.
Try to take a look and see what elements are similar to those in the original "KinnPorsche."
In order to maintain the intensity of this scene, we will review the rest during our rehearsals.
But I've seen your progress.
-OK. Well done. -Thanks.
Well,
keep going.
Ning assigned us homework to find more dramatic conflicts between our characters.
[Bump Pawat Akkradetsakul]
[IG:bump_pawat]
It's quite challenging. Ask us to use a new perspective to understand the character,
as everyone has already understood it in that way.
I have also...I have already redesigned the characters.
This is also the homework we need to discuss when we go back. How can we further develop and extend it here?
[Mio Athens Werapatanakul]
[IG:athenswerapat]
I can see another kind of chemical reaction between them. One is able to convey emotions, he will listen and be submissive to the other.
The other one is even more aggressive,
so it's OK when they're together.
Actually, the so-called "BL drama" is just a mutual affection between friends.
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
If you think about it this way, then the chemical reaction between them is very good.
They both try their best
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
to support each other and have a very harmonious conversation.
It's very rare.
-Right, right.
-Like this?
-Right, don't block me.
I'm Thai.
You can take a look at our progress from the first episode
and please continue to follow us in the future.
You can also follow us on Bear and Hug.
Not again.
You can follow us on the Be On Cloud channel.
Dang.
-Hello.
-Hi, teacher.
-How are you feeling?
A... little nervous.
What's going on? How nervous are you?
It's like, wow, quite a big show. Kinda stressed out, stressed but enjoyed.
Oh, let's recap what has happened until today
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
how has it been? What have you learned? What have you discovered about yourself?
Well, since the beginning, from the first episode until today.
I feel like I've gotten to know myself better. I've learned what I like and what I don't like.
And I'm constantly working on improving myself, hoping that one day it will be better than this.
Since I started this recap of myself.
I went back and looked at my story to see who I used to be.
[Audition Day]
Then I go back to watch old shows, sitting and having a conversation with myself. I tried reviewing and writing down the traits I don't like about myself.
After writing down the traits I dislike, I talked to myself,
questioning why sometimes I became someone I'm not.
In the first episode, I was too focused on winning, to the point where my brain commanded me, what it's called? It's like...
[New Chunnawan Mandee]
[IG:nnewchun]
I did something to let the others know I was panicking.
Hoping they would pay attention to me and maybe choose me.
Hey, listen to me! Listen to me!
What do we gain from playing by ourselves? If we give the wrong answers, we don't score any points.
It's better we tell the truth.
If anyone has been watching them since day one,
[Apo]
I think they would probably be able to advise or teach the audience.
Because I believe that many audience
have this personality as well.
It's like, we read something from social media and start craving for success,
and think "I must succeed, I must succeed."
To the point where humans believe they must be successful.
Well, at fist I hoped for nothing but victory,
[New Chunnawan Mandee]
[IG:nnewchun]
until I forgot about the joy along the way.
Because in reality, there's a little corner
[Apo]
pf a group of people who simply growing vegetables.
Waking up just to sell vegetables for 5 or 10 baht, and that's enough.
That is success.
Since I got in and got to know more friends, got to know the production team.
They're so lovely.
[New Chunnawan Mandee]
[IG:nnewchun]
There was so much joy in the process
that I only realized it after experiencing it. I feel
that participating in this program is really worth it.
How about you, Jet?
Well, it has...
allowed me to learn new perspectives.
Then, I became more confident in being myself.
Since
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit]
[IG:jet_bundit]
Since coming to this program, from the first episode until now,
[Audition Day]
I feel that I have grown a lot
and gained many new perspectives and inspirations.
I...
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit]
[IG:jet_bundit]
I seem to understand my own shortcomings now.
I messed up at the first episode, didn't I?
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit]
[IG:jet_bundit]
I lied and said I joined the Boy Scouts when I was in my first year of high school.
The most serious encounter I've had was
when camping,
someone took my things and hid them.
What kind of camping?
Boy Scout.
It's the kind of Boy Scout camping where you stay overnight.
What grade were you in?
Grade 10.
-Oh, Grade 9. -I got you!
-There's no boy scout camp in Grade 10! -It's Grade 9!
I was exposed. It's over.
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit]
[IG:jet_bundit]
Chapter 2. We got outside.
We went to the beach, I was really happy, because I haven't been to the beach for a while.
And when I went, I felt...
ah! So refreshing!
I got a lot of motivation to work.
When I was about to win, I got pranked by Job again.
Okay, I'll roll the dice
to decide what to do.
Did they get the card again?
Why us, bro?
Once you get the card, the whole game is over.
First of all, I would like to know which play you have chosen and how you interpreted it.
We chose the scene where Kinn delivers gun to Porsche.
I have something to give you.
My favorite gun.
Every time there is an important action,
I will bring it with me.
You need to return it to me after you finish using it.
The gun
and yourself.
We have to admit that the scene they have chosen is very challenging.
[Apo]
However, from the beginning until now, I have hardly seen any progress from them.
You can tell that they are serious, but that kind of seriousness
is like an unaligned knob. They are trying hard to find it,
but
haven't found it yet.
Why do you like this scene?
我个人觉得
-Personally, I think this scene has a lot of complex emotions and is a very important one, right, bro? -Yes.
It's an important scene of the series "KinnPorsche".
Kinn must have a great deal of trust in Porsche to entrust such an important gun to him. It seems that Kinn really loves Porsche.
Similarly, this scene will also have some moments of genuine expression that burst forth.
[Mile]
The dialogue between Kinn and Porsche in this scene
involves some teasing behavior that is typical of people who have feelings for each other.
-Right.
-Yes.
And which role do you each of you choose to play?
-I play Kinn.
-You're Kinn. -New will play Porsche.
We will change the location of this scene from the secondary family house
to somewhere else you know? A safe house or a vacation home.
At an out-of-town location by the seaside, this scene is very important. So if it could take place at a spot we like,
it's supposed to feel good.
So,
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
they changed the setting to
a safe house by the seaside. This is the part that they adjusted.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
For their specific needs,
this is a talisman used to bless
oneself. After all, they are part of the Thai mafia.
OK, from this perspective, you think Kinn would believe in these things.
Yes.
Then let them establish a character with their own style.
As for their appearance, try to see how they can blend in with the characters.
When the characters are integrated into their appearance,
temperament and gaze, perhaps some thought patterns or
perspectives can be found that allow them
to break away from the images they saw in the original play.
OK, good.
Let's slowly accumulate the points we discover. Let's not
judge whether they are right or wrong, but constantly explore.
The next step, I want to conduct character interviews.
If they don't have a script to follow, they need to speak for themselves.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
They need to think for themselves and answer for themselves. See if they can do it or not, and adjust accordingly.
[Training]
[Two people are interviewed as the characters they have chosen to portray]
Kinn, how do you feel right now?
How's your life now?
If I have to be honest,
[Jet as Kinn]
the pressure is quite high.
Can you talk about what you do every day?
There isn't much going on.
Wake up.
Take a shower.
Have a cup of coffee.
Read a book.
Attend meetings.
Occasionally, I will go out to discuss business matters.
So tell me about Tawan.
Tawan.
Who is it?
I don't really know him or anything.
I'm not very good at
remembering names.
But if I remember correctly,
it seems like he may have been killed or something.
Yes, actually that's what I was thinking.
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit]
[IG:jet_bundit]
Because if it really follows the series, Tawan would still be alive,
he's not killed by Kinn.
What I answered back then was that..
I thought Kinn in my thoughts had taken care of it, had shot him.
[Training]
[Two people are interviewed as the characters they have chosen to portray]
Porsche, how do you feel about getting out of the woods?
I feel like Kinn is very important to me.
[New as Porsche]
Because he helped me while I was in the woods. And he blocked a bullet for me.
Do you feel that your perspective towards him have changed?
It's changed a lot. I didn't expect Kinn to protect me like this.
Can we say he is your boyfriend now?
[Jet as Kinn]
My significant other would be better.
Now your feelings towards Kinn have changed.
You...
what are you going to do with yourself?
Now I'm still not sure.
Is it love or just a momentary infatuation? Infatuation or love?
[New as Porsche]
What made me feel
a change towards Kinn was that he was willing to take a bullet for me.
In that moment,
I truly felt like he was willing to die for me.
But I've also thought carefully about whether he really loves me
or if it's just an act because he's not sure how I feel about him yet.
Well, at this point we also need to further understand the roles.
[New Chunnawan Mandee]
[IG:nnewchun]
Must have a better understanding of the role and do more homework.
[Apo]
The first step is for him to find himself.
He must ask himself
what he likes and what his first smile in life was like.
Or, when he confessed his feelings to someone for the first time, what kind of feeling did he have before saying it out loud?
However, he may have missed an important turning point that made the relationship between two people different from before.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
Like, Porsche used to be drugged and had a relationship with Kinn.
He suddenly forgot about this incident, which caused him
to struggle.
Because of this perspective, the attitudes of the two people towards each other changed, and they began to feel uncertain about their own feelings.
There was also the experience of working together in the forest, and he began to see the sincerity and authenticity of the other person,
which slowly developed into a romantic relationship.
In our real life, it is also the same.
We cannot always know what that feeling is.
Sometimes we cannot perceive the feeling of that moment,
perhaps because we do not have enough connections to that feeling.
perhaps, we accidentally overheard.
After training with Teacher Ning, I feel like I have a better understanding of Porsche.
[New Chunnawan Mandee
IG:nnewchun]
With this improved understanding, I am now able to more freely establish the characteristics of Porsche.
My favorite thing is
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit
IG:jet_bundit]
to act.
Helping these two people cooperate just right,
neither too much nor too little,
because both of them are very dedicated.
After they worked hard on it,
[Apo]
they forgot to
think about what the role needed and even what they themselves needed.
It seems they have thought further ahead.
I want to obtain it, but I forgot why I am here.
Audience can participate in real-time voting for the live performance of "The Hidden Character Final Episode".
[Participate in voting]
[Real-time voting]
[The Hidden Character Final Episode]
[Live Show]
The pair with the highest total number of votes can become Luvys' first brand ambassador.
[Luvys' first brand ambassador]
play a role in the sequel of Be On Cloud, and receive a cash reward of 500,000 Thai baht.
[Play a role in the Be On Cloud's]
[Upcoming drama]
[Cash reward
500,000 Thai biaht]
[Fashion photo]
In addition, there will also be opportunities to go to Japan for fashion photo shoots and interviews.
Voting starts at 9:15 PM on July 1st, 2023. THC Episode 11.
[Voting starts at 9:15 PM on July 1st, 2023. EP11]
[Start Voting]
[Until the end of the last group's performance]
After the final performance of the last pair, the voting will be closed,
and each contestant's total votes will be added to their team's votes.
[All votes of the contestants]
[Will be combined with those of their team members]
The pair with the highest number of votes will be the winner.
[The group with the most votes will be the winner]
There are two channels available for voting as follows:
The first channel is to vote through the website WWW.THCBOC.COM.
[Two channels for voting and viewing details]
[Down below]
[First Channel]
[Voting through the website: WWW.THCBOC.COM]
The steps for online voting are as follows. First, go to WWW.THCBOC.COM.
[1.Go to "WWW.THCBOC.COM"]
Second, log in to the system and click on the homepage.
[2. Log in the system and click on homepage]
Third, select the contestant's avatar that you want to vote for.
[3. Select the contestant's avatar that you want to vote for]
Four, choose the number of votes to cast.
[4. Select the number of votes to cast]
4 voting tickets with a service fee of 20 Thai baht.
[4 voting tickets with a service fee of 20 Thai baht]
[12 voting tickets, service fee of 49 Thai baht]
25 voting tickets, service fee of 99 Thai baht.
[25 voting tickets, service fee of 99 Thai baht]
80 voting tickets, service fee of 299 Thai baht.
[80 voting tickets, service fee of 299 Thai baht]
100 voting tickets, service fee of 349 Thai baht.
[100 voting tickets, service fee of 349 Thai baht]
Five, choose a payment method
The following are the payment methods available for online voting:
[Payment methods available for online voting]
Credit card or debit card, ThaiQR, Alipay, and WeChat Pay.
[Voting through the website WWW.THCBOC.COM]
After completing the transaction, the webpage system will display a message indicating that your vote has been successfully submitted.
[Vote Succeed]
The second channel is through SMS voting.
[Second channel: Voting through SMS]
[Click 4141666]
[Big Vote Click 4141069
Followed by the contestant's number]
[Then click to make a phone call
Every operator charges 69 baht per call]
Dial 4141666.
Followed by the contestant's number
and press call. 6 Baht per vote for all networks.
[Service Fee: 6 Baht per vote for all networks]
As for Big Vote. Dial 4141069, followed by the contestant's code
and press call. 69 Baht per vote for all networks.
[Big Vote 12 points]
Today, I attended a workshop with Teacher Ning. I partner up with Ta. So we came together.
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
When I saw them today. It was surprising.
[Apo]
He is someone I don't think
I can naturally connect with at this level right now,
but has become a person worth beholding.
Today we will have a training session,
and there may be some acting involved. But before we begin, I would like everyone to reflect on themselves.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
From the very first day you stepped in.
Since the first day I got in, my first mindset was about wanting to win.
I wanted to win.
Absolute win!
From the first and second chapters, I had the idea of wanting to win over everyone.
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
I must get first place.
Have your mom said the word 'love'
as much as possible.
Every night before bed, what do we say?
[Say "Love you"]
-[Love you. Love you. Love you xN]
-Let's continue.
And the winners are Copper and Lotte.
The second group won 6 gold coins.
Copper is a person who is very meticulous, serious
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
and plans everything carefully.
And the last one,
8 coins.
Copper.
As soon as I announced that I had won 8 gold medals just like before,
[Copper]
I believe many people were feeling inside,
"Doesn't Copper help anyone?"
I feel that when we play a game,
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
I have to go all out with it.
From my viewpoint, he's been winning all along
[Apo]
in everything that he did
He doesn't wanna lose.
He wouldn't do anything
that would make others feel bad,
so in the end he became known as a polite person.
But when I reached the third chapter "Performance"
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
it seemed to change my mindset and made me want to enjoy it more.
Instead of wanting to win, I wanted everyone to enjoy my performance.
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
So, how do you feel, Ta? You're already in KinnPorsche.
And you have to join this game.
Let me tell you, it's tiring.
I told you, it was a long way.
Honestly, if anyone has seen Ta all along,
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
you'll get that Ta has become younger.
It's not about his look.
It's about the boyhood he's supposed to have. Because he's been with the seniors a lot.
He's been with adults a lot, that he forgot he was actually 23.
Sometimes
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
when we're with someone older,
Certain traits rub off on us.
But as time goes on, I started to take in. The old beliefs I used to have, started disappearing.
Until now, I feel like I'm more like a kid.
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
If we were to interpret
KinnPorsche to make it become closer to us.
Well, do we have to talk about the scene too?
OK.
We chose a
quite happy scene.
The viewers will probably enjoy and be happy.
From what I've seen. I think it's a memorable scene. A scene with "Eating hotpot"
Let's cheers.
Cheers! Cheers!
Fill up my beer.
Don't you have hands?
It's a very lovely scene, a scene that deepens mutual understanding. However, everyone has their own thoughts.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
Why did you come?
Do you still need to ask?
I'm here to take you home.
If you want to have a good conversation with him,
you must stay calm.
If it were before, I would have spoken like that.
But now I know
you are on vacation.
This is a very lovely scene.
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
But cute doesn't mean it's simple to portray.
It's not easy to act out a scene where one person is unhappy
and the other one tries to make up but still puts on airs.
-KinnPorsche is about the mafia.
-Yes.
So we thought it was the year 1956,
-Thugs rule the city.
-Yes, yes.
I mean,
Copper and Ta,
they adjusted their performances to fit in the era, around 2499.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
This drama is quite close to myself.
I know it's very close to me.
How should I put it?
My grandfather used to run a gray business.
Oh, this story is interesting.
It was during that time,
-around 1956. The city got ruled.
-OK.
And my grandfather kept doing it until he was 27.
At that time my mom was born. He brought my mom to Bangkok.
Well, my grandfather was shot in a hotel bathroom.
And his mouth...
What I heard was that my mother was 6 years old at the time,
and she didn't know anything. She only knew that
when they returned
to Chanthaburi province, she learned that her father had been shot.
However, they have a strong inspiration,
such as the source of Copper's idea. He said his grandfather
really had similar characteristics to the "KinnPorsche" during that era.
He has a convincing photo album, hoping that it's a good start.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
The danger of changing eras is
whether they can achieve that level,
and whether they truly understand the inner world of people from that era.
Okay, this training is called "Dance the song of your life".
I want you to try to explore
different periods of your lives.
The reason I chose this exercise "Dance the song of your life"
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
is to play the music and let them immerse in different moments of their lives. From childhood to old age.
It's an exercise
designed to help actors who may not yet understand their own emotions.
That's it. Relax and breathe.
Now, I want you to imagine about the time when you were 1-3 years old.
I think this training might help...
in terms of self-awareness and
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
guide our body
into the authentic emotions of that moment.
Ta, let go of your body. Don't walk, just move around, Ta.
If you feel frustrated, release it. Ta
It's like
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
there were many other emotions,
that I didn't wanna show to others.
Like negative emotions that I didn't wanna show it off.
-Ta, shout it out loud. -Ah!
-Again!
-Ah!
Probably because Ta couldn't express the emotions. He seemed stiff while dancing.
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
Well, this is their first time attempting this, but they managed to do it.
We'll use this exercise with them repeatedly in the future. to see if
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
they become more receptive.
How was it with you, Ta?
I feel...
-When you said, it's like we have express it out. At first I was walking, but did I feel it? I did. -OK.
-I felt it. But maybe I couldn't express it through dancing. -Well.
-But, it felt... -You felt it.
It's like he felt it, but
he didn't know how to use his body,
like the body and internal emotions hasn't been connected yet.
Actually, at the beginning, you asked us to close our eyes and imagine when we were born.
-When we just opened our eyes, we didn't feel much and thought that we couldn't hear very well. -OK.
So I was forcing it.
What happened in the mind?
I feel like I'm forcing myself,
telling myself that I should feel this way
and make these gestures.
I admit that I was also restrained at the beginning,
and I thought a lot. If I dance like this, will it look good to others?
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
Is it okay for others if I dance like this?
When I was in elementary school,
it was the worst time of my life.
It was when I was bullied every day.
At that time, I was small in stature and shy.
I also used to love to cry back then.
Does "love to cry" mean crying often at that time?
Back then, I cried every day. Perhaps it was also because I had difficulty expressing my emotions.
Because my parents have high expectations of me every day. They wanted make me say that
a man should be strong and resilient,
never cry, and be a leader.
-Did you have to say these out loud?
-Yes, I had to say it out loud, every day and night.
Working with actors, I often witnessed the things that happened to Copper.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
Especially male actors, because sometimes
they are taught to be strong
and not show their vulnerability, as well as trying not to be sensitive to their emotions.
They have been telling themselves this for many years, which resulted in
them being unable to connect with their inner feelings after becoming an actor.
Sometimes, he accumulates a lot of stress
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
and it takes quite some time to slowly eliminate it.
I have seen the progress of both of you and I feel that I have touched upon
the key points of being an actor and a human being,
which means we should accept our vulnerabilities.
Actually, when it comes to this topic, I will use everything that Teacher Ning mentioned.
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
I think I understand
my emotions and am aware of them. At that time, I can feel what is happening inside me.
How I react to other people's words.
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
I think they can achieve it
by weakening the framework
and understanding their emotional barriers without piling them up in their hearts.
By helping with sincerity, they will gain a better understanding of themselves.
[Assistant Professor Dr. Bhanbhassa Dhubthien]
[Director and Acting Coach of Man Suang]
Every little brother must rehearse to the best of their ability, not knowing their fate, and whether they will be able to perform in the end.
[Mile]
Voting Rules.
Choose the last three pairs to take the stage. One pair will be eliminated.
Where do the scores come from? They come from the company.
Choose
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
who should continue
to walk towards the real stage.
If I can only choose one group to bear the burden, it would be very burdensome.
Because everyone seems to have a bright future.
They're very promising, compared to myself.
Compared to when I was their age, they are making progress very quickly.
I believe every voter considers the big picture
and how much they want to support this person.
[Apo]
The reason for letting everyone make a decision is fairness. If today,
he feels that he can make a decision,
it means that he can choose. Then he has the power to choose who he likes.
I also hope to see many people helping with the auditions and making decisions, so that I can get
the best actors to perform in this drama.
Please come and watch. I believe
[Fuaiz Thanawat Shinawat
IG:fuaiz_thanawat]
in the grand performance,
and I am sure that everyone will enjoy it very much.
[Bump Pawat Akkradetsakul
IG:bump_pawat]
Sincerely invite everyone to watch it, I can say that every performance in each group
[Copper Phuriwat Chotiratanasak
IG:copper_phrt16]
is definitely incredible. Everyone will surely enjoy it.
I have put a lot of effort into my performance and done a lot of preparation.
I would like to invite everyone to come and see it.
[JJ Patiphan Fueangfunuwat
IG:jjaypf]
I believe this is a performance that everyone will definitely enjoy and laugh along with.
[Ta Nankhun Phakphatphonphop
IG:ta_nannakun]
I can say that the eight of us put a lot of effort into preparing for this performance.
[New Chunnawan Mandee
IG:nnewchun]
I hope you can see exciting new things on this stage.
[Mio Athens Werapatanakul
IG:athenswerapat]
There's a little surprise in here.
[Jet Chatsadakorn Bundit
IG:jet_bundit]
Fans and friends should find it interesting and thrilling,
[Pond Krisda]
[Be On Cloud Founder CEO]
giving these boys the opportunity to have a sense of participation with wonderful memories.
[Apo]
I want everyone
to give these young boys confidence,
just like the day when you gave me confidence.
If people come to see them, they will see their charm.
[Mile]
because they are very serious about
creating happiness for the audience and sharing good things.
If you're free, please come and watch it.
[The Hidden Character]