=Will Love in Spring=
(Adapted from the original work
"Lover" by She Mu Si)
=Episode 7=
Jie, you are back.
Jie?
You are back.
We met in Yanggou Village before.
My surname is Yang.
I'm Mr. He's comrade.
I took the liberty
to set up the funeral hall
with the funeral parlor staff.
Please forgive me
if I overlook something.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
Where is my mom?
She has been with He.
She is probably in the embalming room.
I'll take a look at the funeral hall.
Let me know
if you need me to do anything.
All right.
Ms. Liao.
Do you want some water?
I... I'm not thirsty.
No, thanks.
Mr. He's 3-dimension
facial reconstruction
takes some time.
You can look at the details
to feel more assured.
I'm sorry
to butt in everything.
Not at all.
This is just what we should do.
Take your time.
No rush.
All right.
Are these made
for those who died in accidents?
Yes.
3D printing helps
conceal all disfigured parts
as possible in the shortest time,
especially in cases like Mr. He.
Manual restoration
is rather difficult.
Can you understand this?
After the mold is done
and placed on the deceased,
we will proceed with facial makeup
and detail restoration.
This allows the family
to see a familiar face
when they say goodbye.
This technology
is more advanced
than over ten years ago.
My first husband
died in a car accident.
I'm sorry for your loss.
My husband
was pretty meticulous.
Please...
Please take care of him.
Don't worry.
I will.
(Great Virtue Endures)
(Return to the earth fulfilled,
bless the descendants abundantly.)
Jie,
there is a condolence money desk
and registration desk.
He was a people person.
There must be a lot of guests.
If you don't have
any special requests,
I will handle it.
I'm fine with it.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
Don't be so courteous with me.
Besides, you'll...
Jie.
Niaoniao.
Jie,
I lost my dad too?
Jie.
Mr. Yang,
if you have any instructions
for us three,
please tell us.
Tomorrow,
we will send He off properly.
Someone has to go home
to issue an obituary.
Zhuang Yan will do this.
According to our local tradition,
it has to be done by the son.
Zhuang Yan will do it.
But I'm not Mr. He's biological son.
Maybe Niaoniao could do this.
Niaoniao is too young.
Some of the procedures
are too difficult for her to manage.
But I...
I'm afraid
my identity isn't suitable.
If Mr. He is upset...
Have you forgotten
how Mr. He treated you?
He won't be upset
if you send him off.
He will issue the obituary
as the eldest son.
All right.
Let's split
and proceed.
Mr. Yang,
don't worry about the money.
I will give Mr. He
the most dignified funeral.
Okay.
Let's go.
Zhuang Yan,
take Niaoniao home
and do what Mr. Yang said.
Come back here afterward.
We are going to keep vigil for Mr. He.
Mr. He,
I'm now going
to trim your fingernails.
It trims off
your worries and doubts
as well as
your mundane troubles.
Mr. He,
please move on peacefully.
My condolences.
Thank you.
Jie, please stay.
Just tell me if you need anything.
Thank you.
Take care.
I'm leaving.
Please take care, girl.
Having you all and your mom
is my luck.
(Registration)
Please put the shoes on
for the deceased.
He, I'm putting shoes on you.
Mr. He,
if I really get recognized
by the town this time,
I'll give you
an appreciation pennant.
Sure.
That's right.
Mr. He,
I promised I would give you
an appreciation pennant
if the town government honors me.
I had Niaoniao order this.
I planned...
I planned to hold a grand celebration
during the New Year
and give it to you.
It seems I can only give it to you now.
(Honor Mr. He Zhangyue the title
of "The Great Man of the House")
Mr. He,
without you,
how will the family carry on?
You are not made of iron.
Get some rest.
Chen Maidong,
I have never once
called him "dad".
He won't blame you.
You don't understand.
You don't.
Mr. He is gone.
He is gone.
Don't cry here.
You will your siblings up.
Dad.
Chen Maidong,
do I really bring bad luck?
Don't say silly things.
I had already lost my dad,
so I cherished Mr. He very much.
I wouldn't dare to call him dad.
Still,
he has left.
My mom and I think
it's our fault.
Sometimes, the good die young
because Heaven thinks
they are too tired
and gives them an early rest.
I can't understand.
I really can't.
No one is born already knowing it.
I have been in this industry
for a long time.
(It was only a few months ago)
(that I realized something)
(through a boy.)
(That the people closest to us)
(will one day leave us.)
For example, my grandma.
Zhuang Jie,
parting with our closest ones
may be a signal from Heaven
to remind us
that after the most reliable barrier disappears,
it will be our turn sooner or later.
Life has its limits.
That's why we should strive hard to live,
create, and love.
If life carries on forever,
it would be quite boring, actually.
But why me again?
Why does it always have to be me?
I'm sorry.
I can't answer that.
Chen Maidong,
have you ever
lost someone in your life?
When I was 17,
my best friend
died right before me.
His name was Song Ran.
When he died,
he was also 17.
(Before Song Ran died,)
(he called me.)
(But I missed it.)
(To be honest, I was just lazing around.)
(I was playing video games
at the cyber cafe.)
(Song Ran)
(had never been in a fight before.)
(That was the first time.)
(So,)
even now,
I still blame myself
for his death.
You are saying silly things too.
No, I'm serious.
Every day since Song Ran's passing,
I have wondered
why it had to be my friend
and why I had to witness that scene.
If people die at last,
what is the purpose of living?
Do you have an answer now?
Someone
gave me the answer.
All right.
Your feet are clean.
You are clean too.
Stop messing around.
Those who are meant to leave
will eventually leave.
You can't keep them.
Those who are meant to leave
will eventually leave.
We can't keep them.
So,
you decided
to enter the funeral industry
because of this man?
Yes.
He told me
death always happens suddenly.
Being upset is useless.
Someone
has to do something.
If so,
is he your master?
I have learned various professional skills
from many experts.
But only he
is my master.
(Vocational Skills Level Certificate)
(Vocational Skill Level Certificate)
(Name: Chen Maidong
Profession: Embalmer)
What is your master doing now?
He must be retired.
Well.
He is gone.
He had bad habits
and no one was around
to take care of him.
He called me at the weekend
and proudly promised
to take me to go hiking
when I return to Nanping
during the New Year.
The next day,
he passed away.
(Beijing)
(At the age of 17,)
(Master sent Song Ran off.)
(At the age of 27,)
(I left Beijing for Nanping)
(and sent him off myself.)
(Because of Song Ran,)
(I refuse to forget about death.)
(Because of Master,)
(I learned to help more people)
(to leave this world with dignity.)
Zhuang Jie,
losing
is a way of teaching us
to slowly accept.
I know you are suffering.
But you will get through the pain.
Like you?
Yes, with me.
(Being mortal,
we can only lessen our grief.)
Those who are meant to leave
will eventually leave.
We can't keep them.
Being mortal,
we can only lessen our grief.
(Pardon us if we fail to inform you.
The He family is in mourning.)
♪I want to pretend
that it doesn't matter♪
♪Someone in my body♪
♪Is fighting against me♪
♪Refusing to be a puppet of prejudice♪
♪Bearing it silently♪
♪Everyone has their
bitter and anxious times♪
♪Enduring the pain without a word♪
♪Waiting for the wound to heal♪
♪Take it over with another smile♪
♪Heartbreaking moments♪
♪Unwilling to show weakness
before difficulties♪
♪I care about the journey more
than the destination♪
♪The best self♪
♪Is often confusing♪
♪And hard to figure out♪
♪The best self♪
♪Is often confusing♪
♪And hard to figure out♪