[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
[Episode 2]
I want to go back.
His Majesty appointed you to join the verbal struggle.
All the land belongs to His Majesty.
You won't be able to escape.
You will save me, right?
It's okay
to save you.
Really?
As long as I can go back alive,
I'll ask the author to add more scenes for you,
like giving many beauties and much wealth to you.
You'll be the treasure of the world.
What nonsense are you talking about?
That's not important.
How are you going to save me?
It will pay
my reputation.
Then, it's not appropriate. Forget it.
Mr. Wen,
you have profound learning
and are kind.
I'm weak, pitiful, lonely, and helpless.
You won't
stand by, right?
You take the initiative to
ask for my help.
I heard you're looking for an ancient painting, right?
Yes. Will you help me look for it?
Yes.
I can kill two birds with one stone.
As long as you come with me to study in the academy,
and do whatever I want you to do,
I'll sacrifice my reputation to play a loving couple with you.
Then, we can keep your illiteracy a secret
and keep you safe.
At the same time,
I'll try to help you look for the painting.
Good.
As long as I can ride your coattails,
others won't suspect that I'm illiterate.
Then, I'll be safe.
Okay.
I
have written down our words on the agreement.
If there is no objection,
we will take it as the written pledge
and never betray it.
Wait, you prepared
it beforehand, huh?
He needs my help
but it seemed like I was begging him.
What a cunning man!
He set a trap for me.
Find the painting for me.
[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
I have never seen this painting.
So strange.
It's
totally different.
But its outline is about like this.
Remember the aspect astrology.
It's a busy road.
It's lovely.
My lady.
Young Madam is curious about everything.
Would you like a sugar painting?
I...
Mr. Wen is here.
Is this Mrs. Wen,
the World's Greatest Talented Woman?
Sorry. I didn't recognize you, Mrs. Wen.
What do you want? I'll give it to you for free.
I want this one.
Okay, I'll make it for you right away.
Does everyone know him?
Feng State has always been thinking highly of scholars rather than warriors.
Young Master is the World's Greatest Scholar.
Everyone respects him.
Mrs. Wen, your sugar painting is ready.
Catch the thief!
Stop! Stop!
Freeze!
Go!
Did you see that man?
Yes.
He was caught
and will be punished severely
because he was found
to be illiterate.
Don't be afraid.
I will protect you.
Go away. Warriors are not welcome.
Go away!
What are you doing?
Go away.
Please come in, gentlemen.
What did they drive them away?
Do they think warriors are not respectable?
That's because
some scholars have booked the whole place.
Why are people divided into different classes?
Why a talented person is superior?
Isn't his life
supported by ordinary people?
Besides, we need warriors to protect our country.
If there is an attack from outside,
can we defeat enemies by reciting poems?
Everyone is born equal, and there must be a use for their talent.
That makes sense.
It's going to rain.
Jiaobai.
Yes.
Come with me to buy umbrellas.
Okay.
My lady, let's go.
Miss, take a look.
Sir, do you have
rare
and precious ancient paintings?
Are you one of those who are looking for the treasure of Feng State?
Give up as soon as possible.
The saying that whoever gets the treasure will rule the world
is just a rumor.
What treasure?
I just want to buy ancient paintings.
Paintings?
I have all kinds of paintings.
Pick whatever you want.
Du Yaqin is elegant
and attractive.
It turns out that there's an ancient fan culture.
She is a celebrity of the ancient times.
Who is Du Yaqin?
She is the daughter of Vice Censor-in-Chief Du.
She is
from a noble family.
She is charming
and talented.
She's named as the World's Second Talented Woman.
The second.
The World's Second Talented Woman?
I read it in the comic prologue.
She was defeated by Cheng Manyi.
Du Yaqin is elegant
and attractive.
Miss Manyi.
Didn't Wen go with you?
He...
He has something to do.
I used to call him Wen.
I blurted it out just now.
Do you mind it?
No.
Great.
After, we had a relationship
but we were fated to be apart.
Sorry, I said something wrong again.
Don't get me wrong.
Never mind.
Manyi, what is this painting?
Please lend it to me.
Give it back.
Let me see it.
How dare you treat Fairy Yaqin so rude?
You...
You must have had the evil intention out of jealousy.
We'll seek justice for Fairy Yaqin.
What does this have to do with My Lady?
It was Du Yaqin who provoked
us.
Wen,
please don't blame Miss Manyi.
I believe
she didn't mean to hurt me.
A talented bitch.
She is so insidious
that she set me up with several words.
Honey,
are you scared?
First,
it has nothing to do with my wife.
Why will I blame her?
I hope you can stand firm
or stay away from her.
Don't hurt her again.
Second,
don't call her that anymore.
She is two years
younger than you.
Wen.
Don't call me like that.
I only have a sister,
who is called
Wen Chenwei.
We only have a teacher-student relationship.
Please call me Mr. Wen.
Let's go, Honey.
As your mentor,
I advise you
to stop playing tricks.
I witnessed your tricks
in the Talented Woman Competition.
You need to be more honest.
Stop.
I didn't expect you to be an expert in recognizing bitches.
Good for you.
Hello, Mr. Wen and Mrs. Wen.
What is
an expert in recognizing bitches?
I can't explain it to you for the time being.
Have you found anything about the ancient painting?
Hello, Mr. Wen and Mrs. Wen.
[Tea Tasting Party]
No.
You're Chenyi, the top professor
of the top academy
and the top collector of Feng State.
You can't even find an ancient painting, huh?
The contract is settled.
You and I are under one umbrella.
Even if there's a storm ahead,
I'll keep my promise.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Even if Wen Chenyi tries to rape me,
I can teach him a lesson.
Although we are a fake couple,
we have to sleep together.
But don't worry.
I won't touch you.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not scared.
Then, what do you mean by doing so?
Are you going to murder your husband?
It's for peeling fruits.
The bed is mine.
Look at you.
Why did you waste your time
in using these boring tricks,
and even hurt yourself to gain my confidence?
Don't move.
It hurts.
You can sleep on the bed.
I'll sleep on the couch.
Be gentle.
It hurts.
[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
Sister.
Wen Chenyi, what are you doing?
Do you want to trick me again?
Yi just wants to play with you
because I think you are cute.
Why did you kick me?
Yi, Sister?
Don't you know me?
It's my first time to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Wen Chenyi,
you're a good actor.
I'd like to see
how long you can keep playing.
I will give him a lie-detection test,
a professional method.
Boy,
come here.
Turn around.
Boy, how old are you?
Nine year old.
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm Wen Chenyi.
You are...
You're a cute fairy.
His heartbeat is normal.
Is he not lying?
Does he have schizophrenia?
Sister.
You put your hand on my chest.
Do you want to play a game with me?
Cheng Manyi,
he is just a kid.
Boy,
you're so cute.
I have something to do.
Okay.
Young Madam,
you finally found out Young Master's secret.
Please take the burden from now on.
I won't bother you.
Goodbye, Young Madam.
Why did I run into all kinds of weird things?
Sister,
have an apple.
Every time I get sick,
my parents give me sweet food.
Then, I won't feel bitter.
If you're in a bad mood,
eat this apple. It's sweet.
I'm afraid that you have to
take the burden of taking care of him.
In the future,
you may find our Young Master will have strange actions,
like he's transformed.
Yes, transformation.
Wen Chenyi is ill.
What a pity.
What do you want to play?
I'll play with you.
Okay.
Let's go.
♫The candle is burning out, the dawn is breaking♫
♫The moon knows my thoughts♫
♫Life is so long, I hope to spend♫
♫The rest of my life with you♫
♫It's a long way to go♫
♫May I have a lifelong partner♫
♫Let me be your lover♫
♫Hope you can get to know my love♫
♫Wait for the arrangement of fate♫
♫Let us be together♫
♫It's a long way to go♫
♫I want to be with you forever♫
♫In halcyon days♫
♫I can hug you♫
♫And give you a happy life♫
I won, Sister.
♫Let's hold hands and grow old together♫
One more round.
♫Let that story be sloppy♫
I won again.
♫It's worth the love♫
A 9-year-old kid is
♫It's good that it's you♫
smarter than me.
Is it normal?
♫It's okay to be a little late♫
Wen Chenyi, are you pretending?
Moonlight shines,
baby,
listen to this song.
You put your hand on my chest.
Sister, look.
Did I have a seizure last night?
Yi, don't be afraid.
I am here.
If she talks about this,
I will be embarrassed.
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Are you getting worse?
Let me check on you.
I'm not sick.
Don't talk nonsense.
Don't be late
for school tomorrow.
You're Wen Chenyi now.
I took care of him all night.
But he didn't even say "thank you."
He's ungrateful.
Young Master, you've recovered.
Young Madam is indeed virtuous.
Master and Madam picked the right girl.
Have you read all the ancient books I gave you?
Have you memorized
all the poems?
I think
it's time to check your studies.
Jiaobai, huh?
Young Mater,
I said nothing. I...
[Wen's Mansion]
Why is there a chicken?
My lady, you're awake.
Who did this?
Young Master.
Where is he? I will beat him.
You have to wait for Young Master
to come back from the academy.
By the way, My lady,
today is the first day of the academy.
Oh no.
I forgot about this.
Wen Chenyi will kill me.
My lady,
wait for me. I'll go with you.
No need.
Luckily, I'm prepared.
Hurry up, Dongqing, tell me
where is the academy?
Go out and turn right.
[Wen's Mansion]
It's time to show my real skills.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
There's no taxi.
It's really a hard time.
Assassin!
Stop!
How dare you! Surrender now!
Miss,
the way you attract me is so unique.
I like it very much.
It's a misunderstanding.
I'm just a passerby.
Bye.
Miss, where do you want to go?
His clothes
looks exactly like mine.
Is
he also a student of the World's Greatest Academy?
I know who you are.
I'm a student of the World's Best Academy.
A student from the World's Greatest Academy.
Why are you laughing?
Am I wrong?
Yes.
Do you know who I am?
Who are you?
I'm your teacher's wife.
You're so funny.
I'm serious.
I'm Wen Chenyi's wife.
Mr. Wen's wife?
But I heard that
Mr. Wen married
an intelligent, virtuous, and talented woman.
What you did just now
is totally different from a talented woman.
I was
testing a new means of transportation.
And then?
If Mr. Wen finds out that
you reject to let me off, and I'm late because of you,
I'll let you fail the exam at the end of the year.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you'll be in big trouble.
Ask your men to move their swords away.
I'm going to the academy.
You're so funny.
Initially, I wanted to give you a ride.
But if you insist on going alone,
then go ahead.
Leave now.
Yes.
In that case,
I'll give you a chance.
Let's go now.
[World's Greatest Academy]
He is coming.
Who?
So handsome.
He's Helen of Troy.
Mr. Wen.
You changed your uniforms without permission.
Copy the rules ten times.
I wrote a poem.
Mr. Wen, please read it.
The autumn rain goes on and on.
Cicadas are constantly singing.
I want to express my love.
No good.
You didn't even learn the rhyme
let alone the artistic conception.
Mr. Wen.
Mr. Wen is married.
Why didn't you
come to the academy with Cheng Manyi?
My wife
is not feeling well.
So...
She is coming.
Is that Cheng Manyi's carriage?
Another Helen of Troy.
Welcome.
Okay.
I know I'm extraordinary today,
but please
do not stare at me.
Goddess.
You are incredibly talented.
You are Cheng Manyi, an outstanding woman.
Why did Mrs. Wen and the Fifth Prince
come in the same carriage?
They just got married.
But now Cheng Manyi is flirting with another man.
Mr. Wen
is really unlucky.
Manyi is carefree
and doesn't care about trifles.
How can you make wild guesses?
That's right, guys.
Don't misunderstand that
the Fifth Prince and Cheng Manyi
are too intimate.
Cheng Manyi is married to Mr. Wen.
If you keep spreading gossip, it will damage their reputation.
You...
What a tragedy!
This couple is not harmonious.
What a sin!
Forget it. I'll help you
in case you want to break the contract.
I'm going all out.
Honey,
did you forget that
last night,
we talked about the philosophy of life, poetry, and so on.
You promised that
you would never go apart from me
till the doomsday.
Why didn't you wake me up in the morning?
I almost got late.
You were tired last night.
I wanted you to sleep more.
But why were you in the same carriage with the Fifth Prince?
Fifth Prince? Who?
He is the Fifth Prince, Feng Qiwu.
What's wrong with having a ride with a classmate?
Du Yaqin,
why did you have such a
dirty thought?
What?
What are you talking about?
You just got off the carriage
but you pretended not to know Feng Qiwu.
Is your love for Mr. Wen
true?
None of your business.
Mr. Wen,
you've only known each other for a few days.
I'm just worried that you were cheated.
A few days?
Actually, we've been in love for a long time.
I still remember that years ago,
when we met by the Dafeng Lake,
he fell in love with me at first sight.
Then, he pursued me for months
before I agreed to be with him.
But there was a "green tea",
who
showed up to ruin our relationship.
How could "green tea" harm people?
It
describes someone
that looks fresh, like green tea
but actually,
she's a bitch.
Anyway,
I was so smart
that I revealed her evil mind
hidden under her innocent appearance.
Then,
we got married.
The end.
You're indeed extraordinary.
Your sentences are novel.
What a romantic story.
I think
you just made
this ridiculous story up.
My brother and Manyi are deeply in love.
They are a good match.
Stop slandering them.
Chenwei,
I'm just worried about the Wen family.
Why are you so aggressive?
Thank you for
alienating my brother and sister-in-law.
I...
I didn't.
Yaqin is kind-hearted.
After all, we are classmates.
Enough.
I guess I have to use my ultimate skill.
Or I can't end it.
I can make up stories.
But can I make this up?