[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
[Episode 6]
Guys, move!
Yes.
Cheng Manyi!
Like this.
Arms outstretched.
No good.
Put your hands on your hip.
To the left.
To the right.
No good.
The other side.
Turn around.
Turn. Faster.
I really...
Today, Young Madam
suddenly asked me about your birthday.
I wonder what she wants.
She went through so much trouble
and played tricks.
Turns out she's preparing a birthday gift for me.
I'll pretend that I don't know
so that her effort won't be in vain.
The best color is dark green,
which is elegant and luxurious.
The bamboo pattern
shows the dignity
and character of a scholar.
And the blue shirt style works well.
Honey,
what do you think?
Very good.
Boss, make it his size.
Make the design as he mentioned as soon as possible.
Okay.
[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
Manyi. Look.
This robe should only be in heaven.
You can't see it many times in the mortal world.
It turns out that it was only my wishful thinking.
It looks better than the ones made in the palace.
I did it for others' benefit.
Manyi.
You have extraordinary taste.
Look. Isn't it beautiful?
Is it beautiful?
Today, we're going to learn "Discourse on Politics."
Why do you have this robe?
What?
This robe?
I saw you and Mr. Wen
went to the garment-making shop.
I found the fabric you chose was very good.
So, I bought the same one at a high price.
Look.
I hope that you can…
Do I look good?
You're so annoying.
you can…
Doesn't it look good with this piece?
Does it look good?
You're so annoying.
Put it down.
Manyi. You have good taste.
Help me with my shopping in the future.
The academy is the place to learn knowledge
and get enlightened.
Our clothes shouldn't be too luxurious.
For one thing, you won't fit in;
for another, it will encourage a sense of competition.
I hope the student to my left
can change his robe.
Mr. Wen is talking to you.
To me?
Mr. Wen is right.
I'll change it now.
Focus on your class.
[Sorry]
Since you don't want to study
or make progress,
our contract will be canceled.
I'm sorry, okay?
You look handsome.
You're upright and kind.
I can't even praise you for your kindness.
It's said that no one is perfect.
Nonsense!
You're an exception!
You won't make things difficult for me,
a poor and helpless girl, will you?
That contract...
It is still valid.
I was just being angry.
A gentleman never goes back on his word.
Manyi.
Why are you here?
What a coincidence. You also want to climb over the wall?
We don't have to attend the elective course this afternoon.
Right?
I agree with you.
I always wanted to skip the elective course.
Manyi.
More.
Stand still.
Up, up, up.
Okay?
Yes.
Manyi. You've left?
What about me?
Manyi!
Young Master, bad news!
Why are you so nervous?
I saw Young Madam
going shopping with the Fifth Prince.
They were even chatting and laughing.
Whether she'll cheat on you
depends on this.
This is a serious matter.
I dare not neglect it.
Young Master, you must be strong.
Hang in there.
Let's go. I'll get changed and take me there.
Let's go.
Take a look.
This is not bad.
It looks good.
Young Master.
Take a look.
Didn't Young Madam make that robe for you?
Why is the Fifth Prince wearing it?
That's because
I really don't like that robe.
Young Madam insisted on giving it to me,
but I still refused her.
But she thought it'd be a waste,
so she sold it to the Fifth Prince.
I knew it.
Young Madam can't spend your money
and bring you to buy clothes for others.
Young Master, are you going to change?
It's raining heavily.
Let's go back first.
No.
Keep following them.
I want to see
what outrageous things they're going to do.
Let's go.
Young Master.
They went into an out-of-the-way alley.
Young Master, hang in there.
Don't lose your manners.
That's right. Let's go.
Let's go.
It's intolerable.
Young Master, at this point,
seeing is believing.
They are doing nothing.
How is the carriage?
Not bad.
It's quite solid.
It's not a problem to carry five or six people.
Ordinary people can't
afford this kind of carriage.
But in the capital,
the noble lords
and wealthy landlords
all have carriages.
We can get them all.
Okay.
Okay?
As long as there are enough carriages,
we won't worry about having no business.
Look.
The Feng State is peaceful and prosperous.
Clothing, food, and shelter are all provided for the common people.
The only thing they lack is convenient transportation.
People can't afford a carriage,
but they can afford the fare of riding one.
As long as we can seize the market share,
we can solve most students' commuting problems
and can also make use of idle carriages.
It's a very profitable business.
Great, Manyi.
Thank you.
We played a trick on Vice Censor-in-Chief Du,
and he really went to tell my father.
My father docked my salary for three months.
I'm really poor now.
Fortunately, you developed the Yuber service
so that I can earn some pocket money.
Or else, what should I do?
Don't mention it.
We are brothers.
Let's make money together.
Okay. Let's make money together.
Wang Fugui, six carriages.
Next.
Chen Youcai, three carriages.
Li Yongsheng, one.
How many?
Three, three.
Your idle carts
would be considered as your investment.
You'll be rewarded.
We now have the carriages.
The rest is publicity.
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Dear carter friends,
sorry I'm late.
Are you still worried about having to get up early and return home late?
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
Are you still angry about your employer's pay deduction?
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Are you still worried about not having enough money to get married?
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
Come to work for me.
The more passengers you take on,
the more you earn.
♫My good luck is here♫
You will also have a salary.
Anyone wants to join us?
♫Is this the grand prize or the first prize?♫
Yes!
Tomorrow, I'll make everyone in the capital
♫Like the wildflowers which I can pick at will♫
know about our Yuber service.
♫Don't be shy, it's all for you♫
Manyi has said
you can enjoy a discount if you take a ride on the first day
or have a monthly plan!
♫Your good luck is also my good luck♫
Off you go!
Yes!
♫We're a perfect match till the end of time♫
[Yuber]
♫The love I had in my previous life and the debt I haven't paid back in this life♫
♫If we happen to fall in love, it's not bad♫
I hereby announce
Yuber is open officially.
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Our slogan is
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
"You can go anywhere with Yuber"!
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
We started the business in the morning
and failed in the afternoon.
Life…
is like a joke.
Isn't our discount enough?
Any more discounts, and we might as well make it free!
That's right.
In my opinion,
people don't accept new things like this.
I know.
How about I ask my father
to give a decree
that all the citizens must
use our Yuber service when they go out?
That way, we'll be like bandits.
Besides, you have to rely on your father for everything.
Don't you want to do something big by yourself?
Indeed.
Thank you, Manyi.
You're the first person
to tell me this.
Trust me. I'll do my best.
Come on, get up.
Come on!
Why should I encourage him to start a business?
He is a prince.
He has a throne to inherit.
I'm the one who needs to work hard.
[World's Greatest Academy]
What carriage is this?
I've never seen it before.
Honey!
Excuse me.
Honey, I'm here to pick you up.
Look, this is the carriage I prepared for you.
Do you like it?
I really like your choice.
But the academy is a quiet place.
Don't make such a big fuss anymore.
Yes.
Please.
Considering
you still have me in your heart,
all the things that happened before,
I won't hold against you anymore.
Master, let's go.
[World's Greatest Academy]
Why is the carriage parked here, Manyi?
What are you doing?
Honey, I'm sorry.
[You can go anywhere with Yuber]
Yuber's grand opening special promotion!
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Today, we will select several lucky people
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
from the users who sign up for a prepaid card.
And they get to travel with Scholar Wen in a luxury carriage.
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
Cheng Manyi, you…
Girls who are yearning for love
and dear colleagues who admire Scholar Wen,
♫My good luck is here♫
you're just one prepaid card away
from your dream.
♫Is this the grand prize or the first prize?♫
You can't miss the opportunity.
It will never come again.
What are you waiting for?
Give me ten more cards.
♫Like the wildflowers which I can pick at will♫
We don't have that many.
♫Don't be shy, it's all for you♫
What should we do?
The amount is limited.
Hurry up, go!
♫Your good luck is also my good luck♫
Slow down
Yuber!
Where are you going?
♫We're a perfect match till the end of time♫
Yuber!
Wait.
♫The love I had in my previous life and the debt I haven't paid back in this life♫
The first lucky person has appeared!
♫If we happen to fall in love, it's not bad♫
Congratulations.
Hurry up and buy it.
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Here you are.
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
There's not much left.
Hurry up and buy it.
Yuber!
♫A stroke of romance fell from the heavens♫
Sir, where are you going?
Whoa.
♫Pretty girl and handsome guy♫
Scholar Wen.
You're really good, Honey.
You actually used me as a living signboard to attract customers.
You're really a business genius.
Honey, don't be angry.
I just borrowed your body.
Besides, we are a couple.
The money I earn is yours, too.
All right, your mission is done.
You can go home now.
[A Talented Girl Grows Up]
Young Master, today's profit is 850 taels.
So much?
Manyi, if it weren't for you,
our business would have failed.
Today's profit...
No way.
Even brothers need to keep accounts clear.
Besides, I just brought up an idea.
You invested money and contributed efforts.
You should take the larger part of it.
You worked very hard. Take it.
You take it.
Okay, I'll take ten taels.
You can keep the rest
for me.
Okay, I'll keep it.
I'll listen to you.
It's gonna rain. I'm leaving.
Manyi.
I have something to do later.
I can't see you off.
Liu, see Manyi off.
This way, please.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Miss Cheng, if you want to play,
go by yourself.
I won't accompany you.
Are you going or not?
No.
I know you've had a lot of grievances with me recently,
but I have my reason.
Reason?
Is it because I'm too strict with you
or because I couldn't play around with you?
So…
My reason is you.
Me?
Do you want to know why?
♫Happy birthday to you♫
♫I wish you the same happiness♫
♫Every year and every day♫
♫Congratulations♫
Wen Chenyi, happy birthday.
You prepared this for me?
Do you like it?
I made you kneel in the ancestral hall
and got a cough.
I feel bad about it.
Mother told me
you had never celebrated your birthday.
So, I thought I could
celebrate your birthday for the first time as compensation.
I wanted to make you a robe,
but...
Isn't the robe
for the Fifth Prince?
The fabric you chose was very good.
So, I bought the same one at a high price.
I couldn't give it to you because he has the same one.
It is still in my room.
So I used Yuber to raise money
to prepare these for you.
Look at this.
Wei said
Vice Censor-in-Chief Du is the worst to the Wen family.
So, I specially made this.
If he makes you angry,
you can hit him.
Vice Censor-in-Chief Du.
-Hit him!
Beat him to vent your anger.
Indeed. It's all him!
What about these?
These? Aren't you weak?
These are for you to exercise.
When I'm gone one day,
if you are in danger,
you can at least run away.
I'll teach you how to use them.
Wait.
Why would you be gone?
I...
I have to go to the toilet and go shopping.
Don't think too much.
Come here.
Let me teach you how to make a wish first.
Later,
put your hands together like me.
Close your eyes and make a wish.
And then, blow out the candles.
This way, your wish will come true.
This custom is unique.
Try it.
Happy birthday!
Thank you, Manyi.
You're welcome.
Now, start enjoying your birthday party.
These are all raw.
How can we eat those?
Here.
Thank you.
That's called a skewer.
You don't need chopsticks.
Skewer?
You have to
take one
and eat like this.
That's what makes you feel good.
Delicious.
I misunderstood you before.
I thought you just wanted to have fun,
and I punished you on purpose.
Actually, I...
Then, apologize with wine.
Fine.
It was all my fault.
Please forgive me, Heroin Cheng.
Hurry.
Okay.
Eat more.
Cheers.
Delicious.
Who is it?
Thief! Don't run!
Tell me who you are. What are you doing here?
Manyi!
Stop!
Don't chase a desperate enemy!
In case there's an ambush.
What is that thief doing here in the middle of the night?
Stealing?
Poisoning?
Murder?
You still have the mood to drink tea?
Are you really not worried at all?
I'm used to it.
What do you mean?
The Wen family was often visited by intruders at night.
Their purpose is
to steal the seal of the academy.
So, the mastermind
has been targeting the Wen family and the academy
in order to
get the seal?
Normally, according to the dramas,
this seal must be a treasure
with a big secret hidden in it.
It's my fault.
I failed to find the seal.
Please spare my life, My Lord!
Father, please calm down.
In my opinion,
we should start with Cheng Manyi.
What do you mean?
Tomorrow is Double Seventh Day.
According to the tradition of the Feng State,
Mr. Wen
will write the dedication on the Double Seventh Lantern Festival
and stamp it.
In that case,
tomorrow is a good chance to take action.
We can use Cheng Manyi
to distract them
and take the chance to get the seal
so that we can report to the noble one.
Then, the World's Greatest Academy...
And Mr. Wen…
Will all belong to
the Du family.
[Wen's Mansion]
What are you doing?
I specially prepared these for you.
Do you like delicacies
antiques,
or my…
recent homework.
Just say what you want.
You're scaring me.
Let's go.
I haven't been late or going home early recently.
I wrote so much that I even have calluses on my hands.
Aren't your calluses on your hand
from practicing martial arts??
That's not important.
What matters is
Dongqing said it's a kind of festival today.
Can you give me a day off?
Balancing work and rest is the key to success, right?
Wen Iceberg!
It's useless to beg you.
Why don't you get changed?
Today is Double Seventh Day, the most fun festival in the Feng State。
I've already prepared a plan for you to have fun.
You'll miss it if you're late.
Dongqing, bring me the uniform!
Magpies gather in the sky,
and people meet each other in the mortal world.
Every year at the Double Seventh Festival,
the male students will air their scriptures
to pray to be uncorrupted.
As for female students, they will make Qiao cake
and pray to Lady Qiao
for their wishes to be granted.
On the night of the festival,
people who are in love
will date at the Double Seventh Festival
for good luck.
That is the custom of the Double Seventh Day.
What is this?
This is Qiao cake I mentioned.
Qiao cake?
Smells good.
It's fun to experience the traditional customs,
but I didn't prepare anything.
Jiaobai.
Coming.
Be careful.
This… Is it for me?
Young Madam, be careful.
No ordinary person can carry this Qiao cake.
Mr. Wen knows you so well.
He especially had this made for you
the night before yesterday.
Not bad.
You're always reliable at critical moments.
But is Lady Qiao really so effective?
If you pray sincerely,
your wishes will be granted.
Does Young Madam want to pray
for a happy marriage with you, Young Master?
Lady Qiao,
I don't ask a happy marriage from you,
but please make me rich overnight!
Coming true!
It's coming true!
What was I hoping for?
Pay attention to stitches, cutting, and color coordination.
The Qiao Dress decides whether you can
amaze everyone present
at the Double Seventh Lantern Festival
and find your Mr. Right.
Forget it. Nothing is difficult in the world
as long as you give up.
Manyi, don't be discouraged.
A person with both talent and beauty
needs no adornment from clothing.
That makes sense.
The graceful beauty stands tall, herself being a match to a group.
Unparalleled in elegance — Du Yaqin.
She wears a robe of radiant clouds,
with an emerald adornment between her brows.
That's what you'd expect from Du Yaqin, the Feng State's No. 1 Beauty.
Is this the Qiao Dress you made
for the Double Seventh Lantern Festival?
It suits you well.
Don't jump to conclusions yet.
This is just the beginning.
Just wait, and you'll be amazed.
I'll wait and see.
Manyi.
Do you have any idea?
No.
I was just bluffing.
But I can't lose in terms of momentum.
But what should we do?
Why don't I give my Qiao Dress
to you?
You look better in this dress.
It's time to improve Feng State's aesthetics.