Mom, will our town really be
- turned into a lake?
- Yes.
They said they have no choice because of the dam construction.
If they make the dam, the whole town will be submerged up to where that mountain is.
Then, is our house also going to disappear as well?
It won't disappear. It's just going to remain inside the lake,
though we won't be able to go there.
I see.
We could go there in a submarine!
Oh, yes we could!
When I go to Seoul, I want to learn how to swim.
- Really?
- Yeah, I want to learn with you.
That's great. Then let's go take a picture.
- Okay.
- Great.
Since it's the last day before the move, let's quickly take a picture and then go. The movers are probably waiting for us.
- One, two, three. Kimchi!
- Kimchi!
Excuse me, are you okay?
Hey, please come to your senses!
- You, you...
- Ah!
Did you follow me all the way here to get your revenge?
What revenge? I didn't know, I really didn't know! I thought you were raising your hand since you put up your arm
How did you know that I can't swim? Did you do a background check on me? Huh?!
Background check? Why would I do such a thing? No!
How can you try to kill someone just because of a contract? Murderer!
- I'm telling you it's just a misunderstanding!
- What misunderstanding?
Hey, wait!
Excuse me! This woman... just...
pushed me into the river...
- Are you alright?
- Yes! We are alright!
Don't come near me! Don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't do it!
Stop right there! Dear god.
Why?
Let's go to the police station.
- The police station?
- We have to ask you some questions.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
And you there, you come with us, too.
You can write on this.
That bastard, with another woman...
went into a motel.
I hope that he'll be alright...
Yeah, it's better if you keep sleeping.
Where am I?
At the police station.
That was a good idea. Now go and turn yourself in.
What do you mean turn myself in? It really wasn't intentional.
It's the end for you now. Do you know how big of a crime murder is? Hmm?
W-w-why? Why are you crying? You didn't do anything good.
I'm not crying because I did something good. I was so worried that you were actually dead.
To be honest, the woman over there was betrayed by a jerk.
After being hurt by that guy, she jumped into the Han River.
He said he would only go to hotels with her, but he apparently has been going to motels with other women.
Oh, so that's what happened?
It's so unfair! They were hanging out together.
I agree. Men are pigs.
Hello, sir, are you awake now?
Don't you think you should go to a hospital?
No, it looks like I'm fine.
Then, could you two come here as well? I have some quick questions.
Yes.
You're... a diving coach?
Does it make sense that a diving coach wants to die by drowning in a river? Are you joking?
I'm sorry.
And you almost killed this man right here.
I was in hurry.
If you were in such hurry, you could have gone in yourself.
You're a diving athlete yourself.
I'm so sorry.
- She didn't do anything wrong. I'm the one who should be punished—
- Back off, Ahjumma.
I am not an ahjumma.
What would you like to do? Do you want to press charges?
If not, would you like to go for a settlement?
I'll consider it if you promise not to show up in front of me ever again.
Yes, I will. You'll never see me again.
To be honest, we don't really have a reason to ever see each other again, right?
Yes, it's fine then.
Then, I will take it as you have come to an agreement and I will allow you two to go.
Excuse me.
Is the woman who tried to commit suicide by jumping into Han River okay?
It turned out that she's a diving coach.
But... are you a witness?
No, I am...
I forgot where I was going to.
You still have to pay the fine
for dumping trash in the Han River.
Thank you!
Give it to me, I'll pay for it.
Why would you?
I'm responsible for all this. I forced you to sign up and everything.
I'm stupid for sleeping with that jerk.
Give me.
No, I said that I'll pay.
It's not your fault.
The entertainment newspaper, This Touch revealed a paparazzi photo of
Congressman Kang Jung Do from the Shin Nara party and the singer, Ms. R.
Congressman Kang has been buying and reselling artworks
using Ms. R's name at an art gallery owned by his son.
Father's caused trouble again.
This is annoying.
Don't be so stubborn. I'll pay. It makes sense that way.
Okay, I'll pay for your meal then.
Let's go eat something.
He left. I didn't get a chance to thank him.
Are we allowed to leave now?
- Are you still here?
- We're leaving right now.
Thank you. Bye.
Yeouido is in shock because of this scandal
involving a potential presidential candidate and a female singer.
Congressman Kang also has been criticized for his inappropriate behavior...
He's not even breaking a sweat yet and he's already causing problems.
That old man still has his old, bad habits.
- Do you know him?
- I don't know him!
How would he know a well-known congressman like him?
Aigoo! How embarrassing.
A congressman should know better than to cheat and then get caught.
He is really handsome, though.
He's probably popular among women.
Don't you think so?
Excuse me, we'll order more!
We'd like another soybean stew and a bowl of rice.
Okay!
He clearly thought of me as a joke.
I didn't even know and I gave him my body and my heart.
What's so good about him anyway?
I'm such an idiot.
I shouldn't have thought it was possible to find love at my age.
That bastard, seriously...
Don't worry! I'll find him and destroy him.
- I'll slap him as hard as I can—
- Don't.
What do you want me to do, then?
Should I write all about him on Agoura so it'll destroy his life?
I said don't.
I still...
like him!
- Yes, Team Leader?
- Where are you right now!?
Please calm down!
Is everything okay?
Where is it?!
Let's hurry up!
Yeah, what's going on?
Until when are you going to do this to us?
I don't know what to do.
What's going on?
I asked you when she's coming.
- Team Leader!
- Jung Eum!
Yoo Jung Eum?
- Why are you doing this!?
- Why am I doing this?
Say something!
Hey! Stop it!
Jung Eum!
♫ Dirty hair ♫
This is the worst day in all my twenty years of
experience as a matchmaker.
Let's die together today.
No.
You'll die on your own.
I'll kill you, Yoo Jung Eum!
Get out of my face for now.
Did you know about Congressman Kang's adultery?
Did you really not know?
Since when was he setting up his slush fund?
In order to be faithful to the subject,
I paint my subjects to look nothing like them.
Oh, Elvis.
A strange feeling.
That's interesting.
Do you know what's really interesting?
People recognize the person immediately
even though it's been exaggerated so much.
Some say that it can't get more faithful than that.
Even if you try to exaggerate the relationship as if its love,
people will recognize that it's adultery.
Ah! You must be the second oldest son.
The one who resembles you.
But I don't think this is adultery like you think.
I really respect your father.
Unfortunately,
I think that love needs to be tested.
Excuse me.
Hey. Son.
Hey!
This is the only door you can use to avoid the reporters.
But you'll have to overcome it with the power of love.
Mr. Congressman!
I'll call you.
Darling!
- Do you have ramen?
- No.
We have rice, though.
Don't you have any kimchi?
You should have a sense of shame.
How do you think Eun Rim is doing?
Are you scared, or are you really worried about her?
Both.
Then you should stop now. It's about time you stopped.
Love is not something you do.
It's something you fall into.
That's because you tend to fall in love so easily.
Did you know?
You're supposed to become fearless from lack of judgment when you fall in love.
I don't thinkthat you're completely in love
considering that you're still scared of Mom.
You must be a coward for not falling in love, then.
If that's not true,
then stop acting like a coward and try to find someone.
Stop obsessing over toys like a kid.
This is a present for you.
Have you been waiting for me here this whole time?
No, I was waiting for the toy.
Haven't you read the article about how investment in toys make more profit, even than investments in the stock market?
There are more and more adults who feel nostalgic about their childhoods
and their memories are fading.
The price has no choice but to keep increasing.
It's a world where you can make money from nostalgia these days, Father.
I'm the owner of Kang Jung Do.
Did you think that I didn't know about this?
Adultery isn't a crime anymore.
It doesn't end until I decide to get a divorce.
Don't waste your time on this kind of stuff
and focus on what you promised.
My husband is the one
who'll end up being elected, anyway.
Eun Rim, I'll just resign.
Shut up!
That's hot liquid, Eun Rim.
Resign? Don't even think about it!
You betrayed your wife and got caught with adultery, and now you suddenly develop a conscience?
Couldn't you use your great conscience on me!?
Kang Jung Do, listen to me carefully.
I didn't support you in becoming a congressman because you're a good husband.
It's because I thought that you had the potential to be a good politician.
I don't expect a lot from you.
I'm the head of this family anyway.
I'm going to protect my family
so you justdo what you're good at.
Prove that you're valuable
to your kids, daughter-in-law, and grandchildren.
Choon Nam.
Forget you.
Hoon Nam, you'd better be careful.
If you ever embarrass yourself,
I'm going to send you off
to a temple on Jiri Mountain with shaved heads.
The same goes for Yook Ryong. Watch him carefully, too.
Yes.
Thankfully, I was able to
give the eight of them refunds for their memberships without paying a penalty.
What about that guy, Yook Ryong or Jab Ryong or whoever he is?
There's nothing we can do, since he already canceled his account.
He just took all of our women and then left?
What a bastard.
In that case, don't you think we should at least sue him?
- The victims are against it.
- Why?
They apparently loved him.
That's why they agreed to settle and get their money back and stay quiet.
Are they crazy or something?
- Yoo Jung Eum.
- Yes?
You have things to settle with me.
This is the list of the "Zero Members."
By Zero Members, you mean
the legendary clients who never got a date with anyone? The absolute Undateables?
I'll give you three months. Take care of all of them.
Three months? Are you kidding?
Do you think this is a joke? My seniors think I should fire you.
I barely convinced them not to when they told me to blame you for the accident.
No! Why are you doing this to me,
when all of this is that Yook Ryoung guy's fault?
Of course, I'm responsible for not being careful enough.
But if we let this slide, he's going to create more and more victims.
Don't you think it's right to officially sue him?
Are you trying to close our business? Wasn't it enough to make us lose eight members!?
Do you think our other members will be okay with it when rumors of this go around?
I don't care if you kill him or keep him alive, deal with it on your personal time!
You've got to give me and the company a break!
- Team Leader!
- You either resign or take care of the Zero Members.
I can't do this anymore.
- What?
- Do you think love can justify everything?
Do you think it's acceptable to do all kinds of horrible stuff if it's in the name of love?
I cannot forgive a person who had an affair!
I can't accept this!
Who does she think she is to talk about love in front of me?
You came.
What are you still doing out here?
I can't go back because of the reporters.
But, Hyung, are there people who can really die for love?
- There are.
- There are?
Male bees have genitals inside of their bodies
- so if they mate with the queen bee, their stomachs explode.
- Jeez.
But we're not bees. We're humans. So in the human world,
the odds are much higher that you'll
get stung by the queen bee while trying to do this and that.
Don't visit the flowers too often.
The queen bee is getting ready to sting you with her poison.
The reporters probably haven't left yet.
Is love a scam?
I'd rather quit.
English? Fine, I can take classes.
I'll start by writing a personal statement.
Hello, I am Yoo Jung Eum.
I used to be a professional diving athlete,
and I have also worked as an exercise and life coach at a cultural center.
But due to lack of students, the classes got canceled.
And I've been doing various part-time jobs...
No, this isn't it.
You'd better start paying the rent for the room before I re-paper the walls and let the real estate agency take over.
Enough is enough!
Exploitive employers!
I'll kill all of you!
Attack, attack!
You are all dead!
Look at what we have here. Good, good.
Die, just die!
Come on, come on!
Attack, attack, attack!
Reverse turning kick!
What is it?
I'll do it.
You'd better.
What? She just hung up? Oh, I should just...!
That's right. I will meet with her and let them know clearly
what the reality is for them, what their ranking is like,
why they are the Zero Members.
Hello, do you know where Na Ga Yong is?
Here he is.
I'm Na Ga Yong.
Hello, I'm Yoo Jung Eum from Geum Sang Chum Hwa. We talked on the phone earlier.
Hello, let's talk on the way.
I suddenly have to go on a business trip, so I need to go to the airport.
Since you're busy, I will try to explain things to you quickly.
The reason why I wanted to see you today is—
Please excuse me.
I'm sorry, it was a Chinese client. They wanted to know when I'm arriving.
It's okay.
The reason why I visited you today is—
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, it was a Thai client. There was a misunderstanding with the orders.
I'll have to go there myself. My subordinates can't seem to figure things out.
Oh, that's a shame. I will help you.
Taxi!
I'm sorry, it won't be possible to talk today, I have to leave right now.
Then, when do you get back from your trip? When can I see you?
I'll be back tomorrow night and leave again the next morning.
If it's something urgent, do you want to come to the airport with me?
Excuse me, could you give me a call later?
Yes, sir, I am leaving now.
Did you wait for a long time?
I made it myself, please give it a try.
Thank you.
It is so delicious!
You're very beautiful and have great qualifications.
I feel like you'd be very popular among men.
Please excuse me, a customer—
No problem, take care of the customer first.
She looks okay.
Here.
Oh, yes.
What happened?
The thing is, I have facial blindness.
Am I also able to fall in love?
Of course you... can...?
Really?
If you watch the movie  50 First Dates ...
The woman only has long-term memory,
but she found someone who she loves and they got married and lived happily.
Thank you for your hard work.
See you next time.
See you later.
My name is Kang Dol Jin.
Hello, I'm Yoo Jung Eum from Geum Sang Chum Hwa.
But... your blood make-up looks so real.
This is real blood.
Are you alright?
Of course, this is my work and my dream.
Women dislike these types of things, dont they?
I'm certain that
there'll be a woman who can understand your dream.
No, I'm sure of it!