Hold on.
What do you mean Soo Ji is at your place?
You're also at Jung Eum's place, too.
I've been renting a room at her place for a long time.
She's also someone I've known for a long time.
Even if you've known her for a long time, you don't let just anyone stay at your house.
Even a friend renting a room isn't this nosy.
Kang Hoon Nam.
Let's...
break up.
I'll be leaving first.
Jung Eum.
- Why are you doing this?
- Isn't this a bet?
Isn't dating me a bet?
You came to my house to seduce me.
Is it true?
Am I right?
It is true.
So...
that's why you asked me out.
You've seduced me,
so is dumping me what's left?
Jung Eum, that's not it—
I didn't know.
I...
I... I really liked you.
- It was a good meal.
- I brought you here, so it's my treat.
I thought you'd chase after them right away.
I think it should be a conversation between the two of them.
I felt like this before, but you're a cool person.
I felt it before, but you know how to read a person.
Reading a person...
Someone I know needs that ability, too.
You're a cool and nice guy, but
even after you hear this, will you stay a nice guy?
It was a bet.
Those two that just walked out... everything from going out to breaking up,
it was all a bet Hoon Nam had made with his cousin.
Really? I decided to go out with Jung Eum yesterday.
Jung Eum is more innocent than she looks. She's also gullible.
That's something you should say to a person who is determined to deceive her.
I'm sorry.
Was this really
just a bet?
Tell me that it's not. Please, just tell me that it's not.
I'll fall for it. Just lie to me, okay?
You want to make a bet? I'll seduce her and then break up with her.
I'll give you a blank contract.
A blank contract?
It was a bet.
I've done wrong.
Jung Eum, but what happened was—
I told you to enjoy your thrills somewhere else, right?
I told you that she's gullible and cries easily. I told you to leave this innocent girl alone.
Don't ever
appear in front of Jung Eum again.
Joon Soo.
Joon Soo!
Let's go.
♫  Even if I try to hide it  ♫
♫  It shows   ♫
♫  I can't hide my heart  ♫
♫  Am I the only one in love?  ♫
♫  Truthfully, I'm afraid you aren't  ♫
♫  Why did I realize only now?  ♫
♫  I really believed that I wasn't  ♫
♫  I thought I wouldn't ever say I'm in love  ♫
♫  I was confident, but why am I like this  ♫
♫  A day flies by when I think of you  ♫
♫  I can't make any excuses  ♫
♫  I always miss you  ♫
♫  I can't do anything anymore  ♫
♫  Without you  ♫
♫  Those words I've never said  ♫
♫  The words I can't say without you  ♫
♫  I love you more than me  ♫
♫  With what words should I love you more  ♫
♫  I can't express it more, a fool like me  ♫
♫  Since it's the first time, I'm clumsy and awkward  ♫
♫  Nothing else has meaning to me  ♫
♫  If not you  ♫
I won't avoid this by saying that I'm sorry.
The start was wrong, but my final destination is you.
I'm going back to the starting line,
but I'll be sure to come back and the promise I made to see the plums...
I'll keep that promise for sure.
Will you be late today?
I'm not sure, I have to see. Why?
Just asking. Let's eat something delicious.
I'm leaving.
Don't be hurt.
♫  Sunny, yesterday my life was filled with rain  ♫
You came?
♫  Sunny, thank you for the sunshine bouquet   ♫
A blank contract...
But, President, this...
Wasn't this a bet you were winning?
I lost.
You're dead if you use this recklessly. Be sure to get my approval beforehand.
Why did he give it to me if he wants me to get his approval?
Does he like her?
Yes, I know. Yes. Yes, yes...
But, CEO...
Yoo Jung Eum is an employee that has been with us through all of our hardships at this company.
The time limit you promised hasn't even passed yet
What about monitoring her for a little longer?
She works herself to the ground trying to figure out the Zero Members—
I don't want to be a team leader who can't even take care of an employee who's been working hard for this company.
I will take responsibility for her.
Oh, god! You surprised me.
It's because of me, right?
Oh! Of course not.
It's not because of you.
I heard everything.
How many do you need?
The Zero Members... how many of them do I need to take care of
so that you don't have to take responsibility in my place?
Oh Doo Ri is the most important case, right?
Hey.
Don't get stressed, okay?
It's over once we quit.
I want to rest now, too.
What do you mean rest? Huh? You said you had to make money.
I'll take care of it.
Just endure a little longer.
Well, I'll make sure the Zero Members get resolved any way I can.
And I'll find Kim So Eul and make Oh Doo Ri's case work out.
Even if we have to quit, we should be able to quit with our heads up confidently.
That leopard patterned jacket... you should be able to throw it down confidently.
I'll make sure they work out. I will.
Oh, Jo Seok, where are you right now?
Ulleungdo?
You lost him again?
Okay, call me when you find him.
Okay.
Cracorn, did you get to work okay? What should we do about Na Ga Young?
- Yook Ryong!
-  Yes?
Yes, CEO.
Come, sit here.
Did you find Kim So Eul?
Well, not yet...
I want to see him so can you please hurry and find him?
Kim So Eul?
Yes.
I'm going crazy because I want to see him.
Hurry and find him.
Happy birthday... to you...
♪  Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you  ♪
- Oppa, what are you doing?
- Why don't you come?
Oppa, let's go see the performance. Let's go.
- Wait.
- Who's this ahjumma?
Yang Sun Hee...
What's with you?
Leave tonight free. There's something important I want to say.
What important thing does she want to say?
The girls took the time to pick out a pretty one for me.
I won't even have a reason to wear it.
Okay.
Let me be the one to start and end it.
Am I disturbing you?
What brings you here?
Can we drink a cup of coffee?
I heard that you left that house.
- Who told you that?
- Is it important who told me?
It's important that you left.
I'll be returning.
Don't do that, I went home.
You can come here.
I saw your note.
How does it feel to be dumped for the first time in your life?
This must be your first time ever.
This is just a period of time for us to think.
The longer that period of time for thinking becomes,
the bigger the empty space becomes.
Some couples become stronger when that period of time is longer.
For example, what kind of a couple?
That couple... they seemed pretty strong.
Don't you ever appear in front of Jung Eum again!
Let's go.
Why drag him into this to complicate things?
It's not like you.
Is this some kind of a line from an old drama?
Anyway, I changed my personality to something that isn't me.
My dad... is sick.
Severely?
I think so.
I was nervous because my dad was so quiet for a while.
I went home and saw that he was really sick and I didn't know about it.
When I saw my dad, who used to be angry all the time, just lying down,
I felt really bad.
But he grabbed my hand
and said that he's accomplished everything
except for one thing.
That's right, you still have to get married.
So, I've decided to.
That's great.
But if I'm getting married, I want to marry someone who I want.
Let's get married.
Me?
Yes.
It's tough to find someone who matches my background, looks, and level.
How about matching in feelings? There's a huge difference there.
That difference, we can lessen it.
When all other conditions match,
it's too soon to give up just because one of them doesn't align.
Stop messing around.
I'm being serious.
Uh, President...
I have something important to report to you.
I'll end it here for today.
I think I've declared war officially.
Don't take it any further tomorrow. I'll ignore your declaration of war.
I'm fine, as long as you heard me.
See you tomorrow.
What?
Can I be off...?
Did you ever go home with my permission before?
What I want to report to you is...
Whoa...
Actually, I really wanted to come here at least once.
♫  How you would think  ♫
With you.
Like this.
Of course.
Noona, let's do whatever you want today. Everything.
Okay. Let's do that.
Catch me if you can!
Hey!
You'll fall down!
Seriously!
♫  Because I had to find you  ♫
Are you okay? Does it hurt a lot?
You should be careful!
Oh, seriously!
What are you doing? Stop playing around.
Such a rascal...
Here.
Thanks.
I'll take a photo.
What the heck?
♫  To make you incomparably happy  ♫
♫  I have to protect you like that  ♫
♫  I thought I was protecting you  ♫
♫  I was young then  ♫
♫  That you were the one protecting me  ♫
♫  I understand now that it was because of you  ♫
Oh? Why are you getting out?
Not tonight.
When we were having fun at the gallery...
I don't know how President found out—
Thanks for everything until now.
It's been exactly a month for us.
Now...
let's end it.
I don't have to be too cautious anymore.
I can meet Kyung Seon and Sun Ah...
What's wrong with me?
Real-time tip...
No one can. Right...
No one can resist cuteness, indeed.
Where did you get that karaoke machine?
That? Your father.
I guess he's doing a lot of stuff with elders at the city hall because it's election season.
He rented it awhile ago, but he said there's more time on the rental and brought it here.
Are you okay?
Did Jook go somewhere?
I was cleaning and noticed that his things were gone.
Ah, he went on a business trip.  A long-term business trip.
I guess you didn't hear about that.
So, he took all his things.
You got his rent, right?
Yeah, he's tidy with things like that.
That's good, then.
Father, should we sing another song?
Again? It's okay.
Jung Eum, sing a song.
Sing another song? No...
Hey, that's a rental. We have to get our money's worth. Sing a song.
Really? If so, I'll have to sing another one.
Oh... Yoo Jung Eum's go-to song.
I've been in love.
That son of a b*tch.