[This work is based on historical events,]
[but all depiction of details of their lives and motives are fictional.]
I alone decide your fate.
Everything you own…
belongs to me.
I decide whether you live
or whether you die.
Never…
forget that.
[Episode 8]
Where on earth can His Highness be…
You go check Juhamnu Pavilion and you go check Gyeongindang Pavilion.
Yes, Sir.
The doctor visits the King far too often…
Is there anything besides the medicine for a stomachache?
We are looking for ginseng and high-quality Poria mushrooms.
Poria mushrooms...
Still, could he really…
The head guardsman is on board.
Anyhow, I'd better head back.
Sir Preceptor.
The person who just left was that His Majesty's royal doctor?
Yes, that's right.
It would have made a fuss if he had been seen by others.
Thank goodness it is you, Sir.
What is this?
The Crown Prince ordered that the doctor should not be approached.
His orders cannot be ignored.
Please remember that.
I plan to bring the doctor
to the next meeting.
Sir Preceptor!
So let's wait and see…
whether His HIghness forgives me…
or not…
- I will do the rest.
- Then I will be back.
Okay.
My lady…
Where is Young Hee?
She went to the sewing room for an errand.
So I'll have to go alone…
If it's okay, I'll come with you.
I don't want to trouble you.
It'll be too difficult to go alone.
My lady, shall I just deliver it myself?
No… I have to personally
give it to His Highness the Crown Prince.
It is difficult for anyone other than his quarter maids to see him.
Come now… He will make time for this old lady.
I was Crown Prince Sado's…
(T/N: Yi San's deceased father)
nursemaid.
How difficult it must have been for you to come all this way.
I wonder… what are you trying to deliver?
I need to speak to you privately.
This evening, please come to my chamber.
Yes, my lady.
Off you go then.
What is this all about?
I said the doctor was not to be approached.
Then I should be punished for disregarding your orders.
However, please listen to what the doctor has to say.
Many people have begun to notice.
Your Highness needs to know as well.
Preceptor Hong deceived me!
I thought it was you who called me here, Your Highness.
That is why I came.
Please spare me, Your Highness!
I will never reveal what happened here!
Sir Preceptor is my man.
Because one of my own called you here,
I will guarantee your safety.
Tell me now…
What was the reason he disobeyed my orders
and called you here?
[Ingredients for herbal medicine, Chungmaetang]
The doctors of the royal medical office
prescribed Chungmaetang to His Majesty.
(T/N: Medicine to treat dementia)
So His Majesty…
has dementia.
Did you ask me to come, my lady?
I didn't plan to do it this soon.
But
I feel a sense of foreboding.
If we don't hurry, we may miss our chance.
I have always trusted my intuition.
We have to look after His Highness the Crown Prince.
Whether he'll become like the late Crown Prince Sado…
(T/N: Yi San's father)
whether that scary incident of the year of the horse will repeat…
(T/N: Crown Prince Sado was executed then)
I have to know.
For the 700 court ladies I direct,
for all of us,
would you please go and do this?
Won't you become His Highness's concubine
and act as my eyes and ears?
I beg this of you.
There's no need to scheme.
We only need to trust in the Crown Prince.
I believe in His Highness. He will become a wise king.
He will never become like his late father.
Now that I have heard your thoughts,
you may go.
- Leave no corner unsearched!
- Yes, my lady.
You wench, stop right there!
No, you can't!
What's going on?
My lady.
Is this yours?
I asked if it's yours.
[Yeo Beom: Book of female norms]
It's mine, my lady.
- Take her.
- Yes, my lady.
Deok Im!
My lady, it's just one book.
Is it a forbidden folk tale novel?
I'll make sure Deok Im understands…
Do you know what this book is?
This book is "Yeo Beom."
(Book of female norms)
It was once in the possession of the late Her Royal Highness Yeongbin!
Pardon?
My lady, the disciplinary court lady has gone.
And did she find something suitably horrible?
The late Yeongbin's book?
[Yeo Beom: Book of Female Norms]
[Table of Contents]
Try Yeongbin's seal.
Yes, Your Highness.
So it is truly the late Yeongbin's book after all.
So it's true that you stole one of the possessions of the late concubine.
This is a misunderstanding, Your Highness. I did not steal it.
Court Lady Seo.
Yes, Your Highness.
What is the punishment for stealing royal properties?
According to the legal codes of Joseon,
anyone who steals royal possessions…
is to be punished by beheading.
Sung Deok Im.
Yes, Your Highness.
This is quite a difficult situation.
You haven't even the slightest acquaintance with the late Yeongbin.
And yet you carry one of her things.
What am I to make of this?
I can explain, Your Highness. Please give me a chance to do so.
All right, then do so.
It happened in the year that Lady Yeongbin died.
So the business with the doctor… Did nothing come of it?
Being forgiven so easily… Is that strange to you?
The Crown Prince is not one to forgive lightly.
If a subordinate disregards an order, he always gives punishment. However…
you were quite the exception.
I'm excessively favored then.
Are you jealous?
It's not jealousy, you…
One must be punished to absolve impropriety.
It's the only way to prevent future improprieties, and…
if I were you, I'd request one hundred lashes at least.
That's what a man does, isn't it?
My affairs… are my business alone.
You…
Sir Preceptor! Sir Preceptor!
Maiden, you are...
Do you remember me, Sir?
Of course. What brings you here, Maiden Kim?
So you remember me, Sir… At the well, I—
Sir, we come to beg for your help.
Could you please to tell His Highness the Crown Prince
that handmaid, Sung Deok Im, was dragged off to the Queen's palace?
She's being interrogated by the Queen.
- Interrogated?
- Maiden Sung?
Yes, Sir.
So you are saying everything you told me is the truth.
I swear to you, Your Highness.
Do you have any proof or someone
to corroborate it?
Do you?
I do not, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
the Crown Prince requests an audience.
What shall I say?
Send him in.
Your Highness.
Were you so worried that I would hurt a member of your staff
that you ran all the way here?
That is impossible.
I was simply sorry
that one of my maids had worried you.
Do you know what she's done?
I heard she had one of late Lady Yeongbin's things.
She tells me that it was His Majesty who gave it to her.
She says she met him
when she was an apprentice maid.
What shall we do?
Is it appropriate
to trust her tale
without any evidence?
His Majesty cared so much for the late Lady Yeongbin…
Would he really
have given her possession away to a mere apprentice maid?
It's…
difficult to believe.
Even your master cannot believe it.
As there are no witnesses nor evidence,
it's a very tricky situation.
The exalted King of this land
gave the late Lady Yeongbin's property to me long ago
when I was an apprentice maid.
Even to my ears, it sounds ridiculous,
so I understand why my master would not believe it.
But I proclaim it the truth a hundred times over.
I did not steal the late Lady Yeongbin's book.
I earned the book
so that book is mine.
I beg you pardon, but
it is inappropriate to say that there is no witness.
As it was His Majesty who gave me the book,
he is the only witness I can call.
I beg you, Your Highness.
Please…
please do not fault me for what I have not done, Your Highness.
We do not dare to ask His Majesty,
the supreme king, to offer himself as a witness for a mere maid, but...
You are a maid of the Crown Prince's Palace.
If your master begs me, then...
Your Highness, if His Majesty
cannot recall old memories,
what happens then?
According to the law,
those who steal royal possessions
are sentenced to death.
Then...
I beg you...
as Maiden Sung has contributed a lot as a maid of my court,
please treat her leniently,
and simply exile her from the palace.
Do you mean it?
How could we possibly
bring such lowly business to the King?
As it stands,
it's difficult to prove
that she stole it,
so executing her is too much.
Exile
will be sufficient.
It would be best to simply
resolve this quickly.
Will you accept this punishment?
Your Highness,
you are the mother
of everyone in this land Joseon.
Therefore,
as a child would beg for her mother's mercy,
please...
Please allow me an audience with His Majesty,
so I may ask one question.
I did not steal it.
If I am exiled for a crime I did not commit,
there will be no greater shame for me as a palace maid.
Please…
give me one chance, Your Highness.
The Crown Prince is your master.
The Crown Prince won't give you a chance to prove you innocent.
If I should give you a chance...
that wouldn't be a bad idea.
So bitter.
I don't remember that,
so all of you go now.
Your Majesty, her life depends on your answer.
Please, try once more to remember.
How can you ask me to remember something from so long ago?
I may very well have given the book.
That would have been
a very special day for a little child.
But for me,
it would have been nothing at all.
How do I remember something so unmemorable?
It's not like you,
asking something
so trivial of me.
Long ago,
this maid transcribed a book and gave it to you, Your Majesty.
I remember how happy you were that day…
and so I hoped to give her a chance.
Did that maid
give me a book?
What book?
A book, you say?
What sort of book?
Oh, my head,
I have a headache.
Well, come on now.
Punish her
as the law requires.
As it seems you don't want to sentence her to death,
I'll choose her punishment.
That maid
will have her heels cut
and be exiled from the palace.
Now, all of you go.
Please wait a moment, Your Majesty.
If we maim her and send her away from the palace,
she's no better than dead, Your Majesty.
Therefore, someone's fate
is dependent on you.
Your Majesty, you have always
given me lessons.
"As the King of Joseon,"
"you hold in your hands the absolute power over life and death."
"As your subjects were bestowed by heaven,"
"if we do not treat each life as uniquely valuable,"
"we are not qualified"
"to lead them."
I humbly request
that you allow
your subject
a bit more of your time, Your Majesty.
If I cannot protect my heaven-sent subject
just because I cannot recall the incident,
I'm unfit to lead the country, eh?
Come here.
Tell me what happened.
Very thoroughly.
Who knows?
I might be able to remember.
Do you suppose
you can
summon my forgotten memories?
First, please accept
my apology, Your Majesty.
Apology?
It will certainly be a painful memory.
So I ask forgiveness now
before I remind you of that, Your Majesty.
All right.
May we light the incense?
It was when Lady Yeongbin
passed away in the year of the monkey.
When I was a little apprentice maid,
the Head Court Lady ordered me
to go pay final respects to the lady Yeongbin.
In the gardens,
there was a line of lanterns.
I followed those lanterns
until I found Lady Yeongbin's funeral chamber.
If you follow the lights,
you can go to Lady Yeongbin.
Inside the hall
on that dark night,
yellow candles danced and flickered.
The room was full of incense.
Outside the hall, the air was exceedingly hot and humid,
but inside it was eerily cold.
The icy chamber where the lady lay
seemed to surround her in a protective embrace.
It was there
I saw Your Majesty.
Your Majesty saw me there
and said these words.
You look like Princess Hwa Pyeong when she was little.
Your Majesty then honored me
by telling me of Lady Yeongbin.
She used to be beautiful
in her younger days.
She was a court lady, like you.
The ends of her sleeves were very red
Every time I saw them,
my heart ached so much.
"Even ice"
"can't be colder than my heart."
Even ice
can't be colder than my heart.
I have really lost her.
Now…
she won't ever come back.
The image of Your Majesty crying as you uttered those words
is still fresh in my mind.
Afterward…
Your Majesty bestowed upon me a book of Lady Yeongbin's.
Here, take it.
It's a book
[Yeo Beom: Book on Female Norms]
Lady Yeongbin wrote herself.
You unbelievable rascal!
To save your life
you got me crying, didn't you?
I apologize, Your Majesty.
Do you perhaps remember that day, Your Majesty?
I don't!
You will be maimed and sent away!
Do you know…
why I gave you
Lady Yeongbin's book?
Do you not remember?
I do not, Your Majesty.
You said…
you wanted to become a maid with great handwriting.
That's why I gave it to you.
Lady Yeongbin had beautiful penmanship.
Still…
it was good giving it to you.
Sung Deok Im.
You…
have excellent handwriting.
You favor me, Your Majesty.
You have great handwriting.
The life of a palace maid
isn't easy.
It's not easy
to be a prince, either.
Take it.
It's yours.
[Yeo Beom: Book on Female Norms]
The night you went to Lady Yeongbin's funeral chamber...
you… weren't alone, were you?
Is it true?
How does Your Highness know—
Yes.
Prince.
Your Highness.
You've had a rough day.
Go back to the prince's palace.
Yes, Your Highness.
Are you still looking at that?
It's so pretty!
Please tell the maiden how thankful I am.
Is it that great?
Yes, it is.
It's not special.
It's really nothing.
It's what was left behind
after making the royal clothes.
The lowly palace maids might be satisfied with that kind of thing,
but you can't do the same.
Brother, why do you look at the sky like that?
Because I wonder…
when this tiresome night will end.
In your brother's heart…
there is a sun that is as bright as fire.
I wish that the sun would rise from the east,
with all my heart, you know.
Only then will…
the people of the world know my name.
Your dreams will come true, Brother.
I believe in you.
You said you liked the palace, right?
I did.
That's enough then.
Your Majesty.
So you're all here.
Though we might hate it,
there are times we must follow the will of heaven.
Do you remember the actions
I was forced to take in the year of the horse?
(T/N: Crown Prince Sado was executed)
I did it all
for my subjects in Joseon.
Those who needed to disappear were made to disappear,
while those who needed to be deposed were deposed.
Even if that meant
removing me!
When I thought of those capable of
devote their lives in protecting the Crown Prince,
you were the ones that came to mind.
I earnestly ask
that in the times to come,
all of you will do
the difficult things needed without giving up!
Will the time finally draw near?
The night you went to Lady Yeongbin's funeral chamber…
you weren't alone were you?
How did he know?
What is this?
Are you guys sleeping here tonight?
I knew it. You haven't even laid out the comforter yet.
You should get some rest.
Did you come because you were worried about me?
Are you laughing? You almost died today!
Yes, we were really worried.
Sleeping together like this...
it is like we are back to the good old apprentice days, isn't it?
Should I tell you guys an old story?
What's up, Young Hee? You're not one to tell stories.
A long time ago, I heard a story from Court Lady Park…
She told me to never tell anyone else, but…
I really want to tell you guys.
A long, long, very long time ago,
there were celestial fairies who lived on the moon.
The name of their moon palace was…
Gwanghan Palace.
The fairies, they lived there happily,
without any worries at all.
One day, the fairies looked down from the above,
and there they saw a magnificent king ruling a kingdom.
The fairies wanted to serve the king,
so they all came down from the moon and became palace maids.
The king was very happy
and promised to always treat them well.
During the great reign of peace, that promise was well kept.
The fairies lived happily.
But then one day, war arose out of nowhere.
The king abandoned the palace and fled.
The king threw off his royal robe,
abandoned his subjects,
and abandoned the fairies, too.
Taking only strong men,
who could protect him, he went far away.
And then? The king never returned?
He did return.
So the fairies lived happily again?
The king returned
and berated the fairies.
He said that they, his women, had lost their chastity,
and he chased them away.
New fairies can always come down from the moon, he said.
He chased the old fairies away,
saying he'd only be satisfied with new young fairies.
That's unforgivable! That king!
I'd rip him apart.
Hey! What if someone hears you and misunderstands?
But what happened to the moon fairies is too sad!
It's just a story.
It's just a story, right?
So?
And then what happened?
He chased all the fairies away
until he was left alone in the palace.
It was only then that the king realized
how much he needed the fairies.
Without them, he could no longer function as a king.
The king's food, clothing, and even his bed…
It all required the fairies.
Without them, no king is a king.
So the king ordered the old fairies
to return to the palace and resume their work.
So the old fairies worked as they always had
and taught the young fairies about their responsibilities.
The king was satisfied, believing everything had been resolved,
but the fairies, they didn't just forget about what happened.
They gathered the young fairies and taught them the following.
"Never believe the king."
Never believe the king.
The only ones we can trust are ourselves.
All we have are ourselves.
Don't you ever forget
this burned robe,
or the king that abandoned us.
Whatever the means,
we must always remember
to trust ourselves.
Yes, my lady.
The two of you will work in the royal kitchen at His Majesty's palace from tomorrow.
We welcome you to our group.
There's only one person left.
Bring her here.
Court Lady Seo.
M-My lady.
You know where we are, yes?
You lived your whole life in the palace.
You have at least heard rumors, have you not?
No, I don't know…
Where am I?
Oh no, oh no…
I must be dreaming now…
My body is weak these days so I've had terrible dreams.
Yes, I'm sure it is a nightmare.
If we wrap you up again and beat you with rods,
will it wake you from this dream?
It's always the same with you.
Pretending to be silly, pretending to be useless,
pretending not to know, when you really do.
You've lived a long time that way.
I suddenly had a thought…
If I'd gotten you under control sooner,
might it have been easier to take control of your student, too?
Are you… talking about Deok Im?
Just her?
It would have been easier to plant people I need in the Crown Prince's Palace.
Am I wrong?
Bring it here.
Make your mark.
We welcome you to our Fairy Palace.
I look forward to seeing your students among us.
However dull you might truly be,
you now understand what you're to do, yes?
How unfair it is.
You were always ready to stab me in the back,
but because you're a court lady, and for that reason alone,
I can't take your life.
Why are you interfering with my plan?
To protect our court ladies, I have to appoint a wise king.
You're a court lady.
How can you ignore my struggles and act against me?
The Crown Prince is Prince Sado's son.
How dare you protect a criminal's son?
The one who drove the late Prince into lunacy…
was it not you yourself?
You drove father and son apart.
You made His Majesty
loathe his own son.
With everyone saying he was insane,
it drove him into madness.
What happened in the year of the horse,
was it not all your doing?
You wretched witch, you lash out at the leader of the Fairy Palace?
But I know…
why you hated the late Prince so much.
Because he was the sole son of Lady Yeongbin.
The King is the son of a lowly maid.
You chose the worthless, insignificant prince.
The King must have promised…
to make you his wife.
Shut up.
But then as soon as His Majesty succeeded to the throne,
he then chose Lady Yeongbin.
Your closest friend, Lady Yeongbin…
You are quite something!
And now, haven't you gotten your revenge?
You killed
the child of His Majesty
and Lady Yeongbin.
Shut up.
I told you to shut up.
You don't have what it takes to be one of us.
However many times we give, however many chances, you don't change.
The day I became the leader of the Fairy Palace,
I vowed to protect the ladies of the court.
I don't want to break that vow just because of you.
The pride and dignity I take
in protecting my court ladies,
I'd rather not lose them over you.
And so even now, I am forced to save you.
Save her life only.
Why did she go to the Crown Prince's Palace with those tottering legs?
I'm talking about Court Lady Park.
What was she so determined to give His Highness the Crown Prince?
I think there was some kind of clothing inside.
It must have been a winter hat.
A winter hat?
It's a small winter hat, something a baby prince would wear.
But she could just ask someone to run the errand for her.
Why did she want to give it to him directly?
And then why did the Head Court Lady take it?
Your Majesty,
I speak only for our Joseon kingdom and our government.
The Crown Prince…
has no need to understand the complex factionalism of the court.
He has no need to consider the best appointees for the government.
He has no need to know the inner workings of the royal court.
I beg you to revoke the order appointing him regent.
We beg you, Your Majesty.
Will their cries change anything?
Our great undertaking has already been decided.
We'll have to be careful.
You have rejected appeals to act as regent twice.
It's sufficient.
Now is the time to step forward, Your Highness.
Vice Minister.
Yes, Your Highness.
You will see that the Left State Councillor resigns his post.
Please appeal to His Majesty.
Ask him to punish those who tried to harm and conspire against me, the heir to the throne.
Do not budge an inch.
There will be great resistance, Your Highness.
It's their choice to make
whether they will live in my Joseon
or die in it.
But no forced executions by poison.
On the day that I ascend the throne,
I'll personally give the Left State Councillor poison.
Mother!
Do you think your son is already king?
Mother.
Even if your son becomes king…
you'll never become Queen Dowager.
You'll always be simply the wife of a dead prince,
so don't be arrogant.
You should escort your mother away.
Let's leave now, Mother.
Who are you listening to right now?
I'm your mother.
Hyebin.
The King is still fit to rule, but now he needs a regent?
Does that make sense?
Go now and persuade your son.
He'll surely listen to the mother who gave birth to him.
Go, quickly!
As the Princess has said,
I cannot become the Queen Dowager,
forever…
I'll forever be simply a consort.
But my son…
he's been trying hard to respect the mother who bore him.
He said he would someday give me a palace name.
He's already decided on my palace name and title.
"Her Highness of Hyegyeong Palace."
And so,
that's what people will soon call me.
And you, Princess, do you know what others will call you?
When the Crown Prince becomes king, you will lose your title.
No longer a princess, you'll be demoted to a simple commoner.
Your dead husband was a member of the Jeong clan.
So you'll be the Wife of Jeong,
or Mrs. Jeong, I suppose.
You bitch, how dare you!
Mother!
Let go of me!
- Princess Hyebin, please leave.
- Take your hands off me.
Let go! Hyebin!
Mother…
This is my room. Am I the one who should go?
Princess Hyebin, please!
Hyebin!
Let go of me!
I won't let this stand.
Mother. Mother…
You saw it, right?
You saw how much Hyebin hates me.
She won't let the past go.
Does she think I killed her husband?
Why does she hate me?
Is she saying I wanted to hurt my own brother or what?
My brother had gone insane...
What else could I have done when he killed so many people!
[Fight against them.]
That day in the King's chamber, if Your Highness hadn't stepped in,
I would have been maimed and exiled.
The great favor shown to me by Your Highness…
I'll take the gratitude to my grave… No, I'll die grateful…
"Eternally grateful" sounds better…
Ah, yes…
That day… I misunderstood Your Highness.
I hadn't stolen anything,
but when Your Highness didn't believe me, I felt angry and disappointed.
But… now I understand why you did what you did.
At His Majesty's chamber that day, I was happy that you stood up for me, and
protected me, Your Highness.
On the day Lady Yeongbin passed away,
didn't you perhaps meet a little playmate of the Crown Prince?
Your Highness, how do you know that?
Yes, that day I met a playmate of the Crown Prince around my age.
Hey, you!
Hey, you. Do you maybe know the way to Lady Yeongbin's residence?
We went to her funeral chamber together, where the boy broke down.
I still remember the way he cried over her.
And do you still remember
that boy's name?
His name was…
Lady Yeongbin, it's me.
San is here.
San…
My name…
is San.
Crying too much is bad for you.
So it was you.
The civil service exam?
I don't take such an exam.
So it was you, Your Highness.
♫ Stay by my side and make flowers bloom ♫
♫ I only need that one, you only need one ♫
♫ Every day ♫
[The Red Sleeve]
~ Preview ~
Leave in a dignified outfit as a king would do.
So the Crown Prince is planning to visit the tombs, far away, where the king cannot reach him.
This is a gunpowder pouch from the Crown Prince's Palace.
It's soaked. We can't use it now.
"Our enemies have emerged, fight against them."
Everyone protect His Highness!
Please hurry, my lady. We'll have to run now.
♫ Stay by my side and make flowers bloom ♫