I'm so pissed off!
Oh my.
What's the matter?
Young Prince.
Things aren't going well, are they?
Eunuch, don't worry.
I just don't believe it.
I refuse to believe
they'd just watch the Prince of Chen die.
Young Prince...
Although
the Crown Prince promised
to hand the throne to you,
but what if
he changes his mind back at the palace
and turns on you?
What then?
Eunuch, are you saying
my Royal Brother
might go back on his word?
Oh my.
Well...
This Eunuch didn't say that.
This old servant knows the Crown Prince,
and he probably wouldn't.
But the world is unpredictable.
What if he does?
What?
Still, I can't just watch my Royal Brother die!
Heh heh heh.
Young Prince,
calm yourself.
Since this old servant agreed to help the Twenty-Eighth Prince,
naturally I have a foolproof plan.
Heh heh.
Thank you for your kindness, Eunuch.
But I wonder,
what is this plan of yours?
Of course, it's to ensure our Twenty-Eighth Prince
takes the throne legitimately.
Prince of Chen,
are you alright?
It's just at my neck.
I can hold on a while longer.
Liu Heng is coming over.
Maybe I should just agree for now.
I don't want Royal Brother buried alive.
You can't.
You absolutely cannot.
Guards!
Untie Qi Zhi.
Huh?
Liu Heng,
you captured us.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Oh.
Because I suddenly felt
making you watch Royal Brother die
would be a bit cruel.
How about it?
I'm being good to you, right?
Little Twenty-Eight,
I've made up my mind.
Since you want the throne so badly,
I'll hand it over to you.
Really?
Bring the brush and ink!
Oh my.
If only you'd been this decisive earlier.
You wasted so much of everyone's time.
Wait.
I'll write it for him.
Hmm.
Let's get one thing straight.
The moment you get the decree,
you must release Royal Brother.
No problem.
And Huahua.
And me.
Oh, let me tell you,
I never really wanted to kill any of you.
So,
as long as you come quietly to the capital with me,
I guarantee
you'll all be safe and sound.
By the Mandate of Heaven,
a decree from the Crown Prince.
After this Crown Prince was forcibly named
heir to the throne by the late Emperor,
the throne...
Fearing my talents can't rule the realm,
and the people would suffer,
I cannot sleep at night,
nor rest by day.
Fortunately, my Twenty-Eighth brother, Prince Kang Liu Heng,
excels in both letters and arms, a genius of governance.
Are you satisfied now?
Hurry up and release us.
No, no.
Sign it, sign it!
Heh heh.
Guards!
Release them.
Ah!
Don't move!
Oh no!
Ah!
Stop yelling!
P-p-put the swords down!
All of you, put them down!
Drop them!
A-and release the Prince of Chen too!
Let him go!
Hurry!
Faster!
Let's talk this out calmly.
Go, quickly!
Hurry up!
Don't move!
Stay back!
Don't come any closer!
One more move...
Move again and...
Don't move!
Stay back!
Don't come over!
Come closer and I'll...
Put that thing down before you talk.
Put that thing down before you talk!
Ah!
That Ouyang Yan...
She's gone way too far!
One day I'll settle the score with her.
Young Prince, nice acting.
Ah!
Those guys...
They actually think they escaped on their own.
Hmph.
They still think they rescued the older brother.
Eunuch Gao,
your Deceitful Switch trick
was absolutely brilliant!
Ah,
from now on,
I'll be relying on you, Eunuch.
Mm.
Of course.
Alright then,
since things have come to this,
I'll just
take the real Prince of Chen
back to the palace.
Ah?
Hey, hey, hey!
No, no, no.
Eunuch Gao.
Hmm?
The journey back to the capital is long.
It'd be inconvenient for you to bring him along.
It's fine.
Nothing inconvenient about it.
Besides,
how could I
trouble you, Young Prince, over him?
Hmm.
Ha ha ha!
No trouble at all!
Eunuch Gao,
just consider it
me easing your burden.
What's this?
By the look on your face,
are you displeased?
Or perhaps
you don't trust This Prince?
Of course not!
Am I displeased?
Hey, hey, hey.
Not at all.
I'm not displeased.
How could I be displeased?
Young Prince, you misunderstand.
Alright.
Then I'll trouble you, Young Prince.
Ah.
I take my leave.
Take care, Eunuch.
Oh my!
Hmph!
Phew.
We finally got away.
That really scared me back there.
That Liu Heng.
I'll beat him up every time I see him.
Enough, you've tormented him plenty.
Everyone,
are you all okay?
Royal Brother, are you alright?
Ah...
I'm so hungry.
Oh right.
Huahua hasn't eaten yet.
Tch.
The rest of us are starving,
but Huahua never misses a meal.
Hehe.
Huahua.
Ah.
Don't be like that.
The Prince of Chen isn't that kind of person.
I don't care what kind of person he is.
But since he won't save Huahua,
then I'll go myself.
Hey!
You don't know any martial arts.
Going there is basically suicide.
Then I'll die together with Huahua.
Then I'll go with you.
No.
Why not?
Don't we always take things on together?
You're about to become the Empress.
I shouldn't drag you into fights.
I...
Hmm?
Liu Heng?
Where?
Huh?
Hey.
It really does look like him.
Let's go check.
Who's there?
Eunuch Gao.
Young Prince.
What brings the Young Prince here?
Didn't this old servant tell Young Prince
to wait for news in Kangcheng?
The Coronation Ceremony is just days away.
This Prince simply couldn't rest easy.
What's there to worry about?
Could it be
the Young Prince still doesn't trust this old servant?
Come on.
When have I ever doubted you, Eunuch Gao?
Hmm.
I just can't help worrying the Prince of Chen
might go back on his word.
Oh my.
There's nothing to worry about.
Young Prince,
you just put your mind
completely at ease.
He's just a transitional figure.
A few days after he takes the throne,
I'll find some excuse
to have him pass the throne to you legitimately.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Eunuch.
But will the Prince of Chen
really step down obediently?
The Young Prince needn't trouble himself with that.
Just leave it to this old servant.
Hahaha.
Young Prince,
in this old servant's heart,
only you
are the one true choice for the throne.
Eunuch.
Well, since that's the case,
for the next few days,
this Prince will stay at the palace.
It'll be easier to keep in touch with you.
That's not quite convenient,
Your Highness.
There are many Imperial concubines here.
If you move in just like that,
others will start suspecting you, Your Highness.
Never mind.
Let them suspect.
Then this Prince
will take his leave first.
Safe travels, Your Highness.
What on earth goes on in that head of his?
Ugh.
Who are you people?
What are you doing with that blade?
Ask the King of Hell after you're dead.
Where's Huahua?
What Huahua?
I'm not telling you.
Wait, isn't this...
He's trying to kill me!
You know him?
I saw him before at Eunuch Gao's place.
Why is he trying to kill you?
He's literally trying to kill you,
and you're still keeping his secret?
Have you ever heard the saying?
Enemies and friends are only a step apart.
Just like love and hate,
separated by the thinnest line.
Nope.
Have you ever heard this saying?
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
Enough.
Stop preaching.
Eunuch.
Go.
We've crossed the river,
so it's time to burn the bridge.
Yes.
Guards!
Go tear down the bridge south of the city.
The Prince of Chen is with me.
And that chicken is with Eunuch Gao.
Royal Brother!
Liu Heng!
Let go, let go, let go!
We're on the same side now.
What do you mean?
Come on, let go!
Here's the plan.
We'll stay here to figure out a strategy.
You go and inform the Crown Prince.
You wouldn't be much help here anyway.
Oh.
Hey.
Why don't you keep Huahua by your side too?
I'm scared!
Fine, hit me, hit me, hit me.
Just don't kill me.
Go on, hit me.
Your Highness, Crown Prince.
Princess Ouyang Yan of Yan Kingdom is here.
Ouyang Yan?
Show her in at once.
Crown Prince!
This is bad!
Eunuch Gao,
Eunuch Gao, he...
Greetings, Princess.
Teacher is one of us.
Speak freely.
I'm back!
You're back.
Mm.
Have you come up with a plan?
Nothing yet.
Eunuch Gao is a veteran of the previous court.
He's high in rank and powerful.
And we don't have any solid evidence.
Just our word against his,
it'll be hard to bring him down.
That's right.
Plus, Eunuch Gao is plotting rebellion,
and he's built quite a network at court.
If we confront him head-on,
we'll definitely lose badly.
So what do we do now?
The Grand Secretary told us to relay a message.
Mm?
Teacher.
Mm.
He said...
Uh...
Something about giving people their, uh, own way back.
Teacher truly lives up to his name.
A brilliant taste of their own medicine!
Yes, yes, yes.
That's the one.
What are you all talking about?
It's simple.
Since he swapped the older brother for the younger,
we'll do the same thing right back.
Swap the older brother back for the younger.
Once he takes the throne,
bringing down Eunuch Gao
will be as easy as flipping a hand.
Exactly.
Once you've brought down Eunuch Gao,
you can make me Emperor.
Perfect!
That's not part of our plan.
Thank you.
Eunuch.
The men sent to kill Liu Heng haven't returned.
Could I have underestimated him?
Eunuch.
The Crown Prince
is waiting for you to taste his food.
I know, I know.
Your Highness.
Princess Ouyang Yan of Yan Kingdom
invites you over for a game of Go.
She knows how to play?
Hmph.
The Princess also said
that her brother
brought you a Go manual from Yan Kingdom.
She's sure Your Highness will like it.
Your Highness.
This old servant has arrived.
You may withdraw for now.
Yes.
Oh.
The Book of Songs?
Since when, Your Highness,
have you taken such interest in copying it?
I've been restless and irritable lately.
Copying the Book of Songs
helps with self-cultivation.
Ah.
The Book of Songs is fine, of course,
but Your Highness has Your precious body.
Staying up so late
could ruin your health. What then?
In just a few more days,
I won't have Your precious body anymore.
Even you, Eunuch Gao,
will be serving someone else.
Isn't that right?
Your Highness,
this old servant watched you grow up.
In this old servant's heart,
you will always be the Crown Prince.
Well, in that case,
keep me company and copy more sutras.
Done.
Ugh.
One just left and another shows up.
I have to say,
why do you have to hide him with me?
The most dangerous place
is the safest place.
Have you forgotten
how they treated you?
We hand him over to you
and you're still not happy?
I'm not happy.
Not happy, not happy, not happy!
I'm extremely unhappy.
You two, listen,
you won't let me be emperor,
yet keep asking me to help you.
You've got some nerve!
You'll help whether you want to or not.
Hmph.
In the morning,
you had bird's nest porridge.
At noon,
you had a whole-fish banquet.
At night, you said you'd study the Go manual,
so you had no appetite for dinner.
You only ate a little bit of pastry.
Lord Liu sent you a Jade ruyi.
You absolutely loved it at the time
and said one line:
"I hope this Jade ruyi
truly brings me what I wish."
When you said that,
Eunuch Gao was present.
Memorize it cold!
After that,
you went to the Imperial Garden
and praised a palace lantern
to no end.
Eunuch Gao was present.
Remember, it's a palace lantern.
Hey,
you're throwing so much at me at once,
how can I possibly remember?
You have to, even if you can't.
I went through a lot
to drag this out of your brother.
One wrong word
and the whole thing falls apart.
You memorize Go manuals so well,
but can't remember this?
Keep going.
On the way, a little eunuch
bumped into you while walking.
Eunuch Gao gave him thirty lashes.
Note, it's thirty,
not 28, not 29,
it's 30!
Eunuch Gao has arrived!
Eunuch Gao is here.
Why is Eunuch Gao here?
I need to hide.
Hide!
No good, can't hide here.
Oh, behind there!
Too small!
I'm done for, done for!
Hey, wait a minute.
I don't need to hide.
I don't know anything.
I thought you were...
Where's Liu Xiaoyao?
I'm here to see Liu Xiaoyao.
To see Liu Xiaoyao
about the pre-coronation details.
Mm, come, come, come.
Prince of Chen,
Shall we serve Daughter's Red at the pre-coronation banquet?
Your Highness.
Qi...
Special Envoy Qi, you're here too.
Eunuch Gao.
Your Highness.
Yesterday, this old servant saw Your Highness
took a particular interest in an incense burner.
So I had someone steal it for you.
Bring it in for His Highness.
An incense burner?
Oh my.
Some people really
know how to read the situation.
Right, Xiang...
Right, Prince of Chen?
It's a token of this old servant's regard for Your Highness.
Hahaha.
Oh dear.
It seems Eunuch Gao
is getting on in years.
That mind of yours,
your memory isn't what it used to be.
As I recall,
what I clearly said yesterday was
I had my eye on a palace lantern.
So why did you bring me an incense burner?
Huh?
Ah!
Oh no.
Your Highness.
This old servant is getting old.
When you get on in years,
it's easy to slip.
So,
the elderly must wear proper shoes.
They must be breathable,
to prevent falls.
What are you doing?
And memory tends to fail.
Heh heh heh.
Your Highness.
This old servant remembered wrong.
A palace lantern.
This old servant will go
fetch a palace lantern for you right away.
This old servant takes his leave.
Mm.
An incense burner.
Good thing I came prepared, right?
Hey,
He didn't catch on, did he?
How could he possibly catch on?
Hey,
Carry on.
Last night, you went to the brothel.
This is bizarre.
This guy here is the older brother.
Just watch me drag his little brother out.
Eunuch,
going that far.
That damn bookworm.
Didn't we agree on A taste of their own medicine?
Fine then.
I'll use your own tactics, Qi Zhi,
and turn them right back on you.
When you come back and see him here,
let's see if you're surprised,
or shocked.
Ugh.
These eyebrows are so hard to draw.
Brother.
Yan'er.
I have to return to the Yan Kingdom.
Right now?
You're not staying for my wedding?
Father just received an urgent letter from Daliang.
Dubian Kingdom fully invaded Yan Kingdom.
Generals Zhang and Shangguan have both fallen.
Father's illness has grown much worse.
I must head back at once.
I'll go back with you.
No.
You must stay.
You must become Empress of Daliang.
Only then can you bring Daliang's troops
to save our people of Yan Kingdom from this misery.
But I don't want to be Empress.
Brother.
Just let me go back with you.
Ouyang Yan,
Do you realize
that every citizen of Yan Kingdom right now,
their hope
rests entirely on you?
Remember,
Until you become Empress,
don't breathe a word of this to anyone.
I understand.
Don't worry.
Goodness.
I've been busy with Prince of Chen all day.
Why summon me this late?
No reason.
Just want to chat with you.
Is that not allowed?
Didn't you say it was important?
This Princess wishing to chat with you,
Isn't that important enough?
Fine, fine, fine.
Oh my.
The noble Princess of Yan Kingdom
willing to chat with a chicken farmer.
What an honor of three lifetimes.
Let's chat.
Hey.
Didn't you say we'd chat?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Oh.
This humble commoner isn't worthy to chat.
Honestly, I rather envy this humble commoner.
At least you can do whatever
you want to do.
Oh please.
Back when I was studying as a kid,
I was too poor to even afford paper.
Then I finally passed the imperial exam,
and they made me raise chickens.
Envy this humble commoner?
That's only because you're not this humble commoner.
If you really became this humble commoner,
you wouldn't have time to cry.
If I really weren't a princess,
then I could...
Never mind.
Tomorrow,
you'll attend the Coronation Ceremony pre-feast.
Get some rest early.
I'll be going now.
Qi Zhi.
Yes?
Thank you.
Tomorrow
will be my Coronation Ceremony.
According to tradition,
I've invited My lords here today
to enjoy the Azure Dragon Dance together.
My lords
are all meritorious servants of Daliang.
I hope My lords will continue to support me,
and build a golden age for Daliang.
Bring the wine.
Eunuch, it's ready.
Come.
My lords,
A toast to the Emperor.
The wine is poisoned.
Come!
Somebody!
Summon the Imperial Physician!
What's the point of summoning the Imperial Physician?
Oh, Your Highness.
No one can help now.
Everyone,
my apologies.
You've all been poisoned by my Bloodbane Pill.
So,
no one is leaving here alive today.
Eunuch Gao,
how could you poison me too?
Give me the antidote, quick!
Shut up!
Xiaoyao,
quit playing the carefree act with me.
Qi Zhi!
Give Huahua back to me!
Oh my,
Special Envoy Qi,
what a deep bond between man and chicken.
Deliver the flower.
Sorry about that,
Special Envoy Qi.
I stewed your dear Huahua.
But tell you what,
before you die, I'll let you
have a taste of chicken.
Please.
You killed Huahua!
I'll fight you to the death!
Don't move!
The more you move,
the faster the poison spreads.
Let go of me!
I'll fight him to the death!
Qi Zhi!
He's dead.
Eunuch Gao,
I grew up by your side since childhood.
I never imagined
you could truly be this vicious.
Qi Zhi!
Crown Prince,
this old servant can't bear to part with you.
Even if you kill us all,
without a puppet to control,
you're still just a lowly servant dog.
We'll see about that.
Hurry!
Don't move!
Come.
This way, please.
This man
is in your hands now.
What I can't have,
none of you will get either.
Why am I here?
I have to thank
that fool Liu Heng.
Who are you calling a fool?
Let me tell you all,
as for you lot,
you drank my Jiu Jiu San Lu Fatal Powder.
After drinking that cup of wine,
day one, your stomach aches for one incense stick.
Day two, two incense sticks of pain.
Take a guess,
what happens on day three?
Three incense sticks of pain, of course!
By then,
when you really can't take it anymore,
you'll beg me to be Emperor.
Let me tell you,
the antidote is right here on me.
If you want to live...
Shut your mouth!
Why are you everywhere I go?
What nonsense are you spouting?
You think you poisoned them?
They were poisoned by this eunuch!
See that?
One's already dead.
Qi Zhi!
Are you okay, Qi Zhi?
Hey,
I just,
forgot to mention this.
I spilled that earlier bowl of wine.
The cup in front of you now,
I swapped it out.
So that means,
the poison in you,
I just put there myself.
It's my poison you're hit with.
Hey!
If you want to live,
you'll all do as I say.
An incense stick passed already?
Stop right there!
Give me the antidote!
No.
Give it!
Okay, okay, here, here, here!
Take it.
Just you wait!
You dared kill Qi Zhi's Huahua!
Today, this princess will kill you!
Get him!
Don't move!
Wait, that's not right.
Didn't I already banish you from the palace?
Eunuch Gao,
I knew something was off about you long ago.
So...
General Li never left the capital at all.
Seize them all!
Nobody come any closer!
Crown Prince, watch out!
You, Li!
Tell your men to leave, now!
Or else...
I'll kill the Crown Prince!
You think you can still walk out of this palace?
Release the Crown Prince now!
You...
As long as you let me out of this palace,
I'll definitely release the Crown Prince.
You're delusional.
The ambush you set up in the palace,
I've already taken care of all of it.
You don't have a single man left to command.
Even if I let you walk out that door,
hundreds of archers wait outside for you.
Stay back!
The throne, in the end,
is just a passing cloud.
As long as you turn back now,
I'm willing to let you off.
I'll let you leave the capital,
let you retire to your hometown. How's that?
Crown Prince,
do you truly mean what you said?
Don't you know me by now?
Would I really lie to you?
Oh, my dear Crown Prince...
Actually, this old servant...
Crown Prince!
You old scoundrel!
Where do you think you're going?
Crown Prince!
Qi Zhi!
Crown Prince, wake up!
Crown Prince!
I won.
Crown Prince, what's wrong?
Crown Prince!
Old Li tried to kill me.
You absolutely can't die!
Stop!
Crown Prince!
Do you really mean to spare his life?
Just spare his life.
After all,
he doesn't have many years left anyway.
Chicken farmer,
I'm sorry.
I got your Huahua killed.
Right.
So you have to live.
You have to live to pay me back for Huahua, right?
Crown Prince!
Crown Prince, just hold on a bit longer.
The Imperial Physician will be here soon.
Oh, right.
In my study,
there's an unfinished comic book.
Right.
Ouyang Yan,
you have to remember.
I'm sorry.
I can't stay with you till the end.
Hey...
Crown Prince!
Are you really leaving?
The palace is in chaos right now.
No one cares about Yan Kingdom's affairs.
Let alone
sending troops to help.
Yan Kingdom is in a war crisis.
I have to go.
But what good will it do if you go back alone?
I'm the princess of Yan Kingdom.
I must go back.
What if you weren't the princess?
Unfortunately, there's no "what if."
I'm leaving.
Farewell.