All men must die, some deaths weigh more than others.
But I never imagined
that I'd lose my head
over a "useless prince who won't be emperor."
Hmm.
You there.
Before you die,
do you have any last words?
I have one thing to say.
Got it, behead him.
Roger, beheading him.
Off with his head!
Hey, hey, hey!
I haven't even spoken yet!
I still...
This, this...
This doesn't count!
Presenting!
Ouyang Yan of Dayan...
and Ouyang Que, for an audience!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You two,
please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
My dear ministers,
our Daliang Kingdom
has long been friendly with the Dayan Kingdom.
Today, on my son's birthday,
I hereby announce
that from this day forward,
the Dayan Kingdom and Daliang Kingdom shall form a marriage alliance,
united forever.
Wise is our Emperor!
Your Majesty,
my father has fallen ill and cannot attend.
So I shall present my sister in his stead.
I hope Your Majesty
and the Crown Prince will forgive us.
My sister is rather unruly.
From now on,
I ask Your Highness to please bear with her.
Not at all, not at all.
Please, take your seats.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
My son,
shouldn't we pick an auspicious day soon
so all the people of the realm can celebrate
this happy occasion with you?
Father,
your child does not wish to marry.
Doesn't wish to marry?
Throughout the ages,
one must build a family and rule the state
before pacifying the world.
As the Crown Prince,
if you don't marry,
how will you produce an heir
to inherit the throne?
Father,
your child stayed awake thinking all night,
and must tell you the truth.
The truth?
What truth?
Father,
what is the real reason?
Tell your father.
I'm actually
quite an open-minded man.
Your child...
Your child simply doesn't want to be Emperor.
Doesn't want to be Emperor?!
In all the world,
is there a Crown Prince who doesn't want the throne?
Father,
because your child has other dreams.
Hahahaha!
You little brat,
I think you've
lost your mind!
Guards!
Bring out all that ridiculous junk of his
and haul it in here!
Out of my way!
These are works by famous comic artists.
Don't slander them, all right?
I told you long ago
to burn all these things around him.
Why are they still here?
What's the matter with you?
Who's attending the Crown Prince?
Bring them here!
Kneel!
You two,
do you know your crime?
Take them away!
Father,
this has nothing to do with them.
It's your child.
Your child is truly lacking in talent.
I can't understand the Confucian classics,
nor can I learn the way of governing.
Only these comics
can relieve a bit of my worries.
I beg you, Father,
spare your child.
Don't make your child inherit the throne.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Huh?
What Crown Prince doesn't want to be Emperor?
Father,
then your child wants to be the first.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Why are you here?
The Crown Prince's Enthronement ceremony is near.
Eunuch Gao ordered
to slaughter this Western speckled hen
for the Crown Prince,
to nourish his body.
Hey!
Didn't we already agree?
We must wait until Huahua is fully grown
to get its maximum nutritional value.
Bullshit!
We've already checked.
That was all nonsense you made up.
This chicken
should've been killed long ago!
Hey!
You can't!
You can't take my chicken!
Let go of me!
Let go!
I won't!
With two more keepers like you in the palace,
will we ever get to eat chicken?
No!
The chicken I'm protecting is named Huahua.
It was born under my watch.
And I
am just a chicken keeper.
But in the palace,
even someone like me was given a title:
Royal Chicken Keeper.
You've finally hatched.
From now on, we only have each other.
I'll protect you.
I raised Huahua with my own hands.
It's my only family.
It snuggles in my bed to keep me warm.
No one else has ever treated me this way.
Every day it's with me,
I sleep soundly.
The Crown Prince has escaped!
Oh no!
Huahua,
our chance has come!
Once we leave the palace,
we'll be free.
Hey!
My Huahua! My comics!
Move your foot, you're stepping on my book!
Sorry, sorry!
Don't get me wrong.
This wasn't love at first sight.
I have a certain ability.
I was born able to see things I'd rather not.
Just let your child go.
Fine!
If you dare take one step out of this palace gate,
I'll strip you of the Crown Prince title forever!
You'll live as a commoner for life!
Father.
Is it really that simple?
Father,
please forgive your unfilial child.
Hey!
Crown Prince!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
What's wrong, Your Majesty?
You're the Crown Prince.
You're escaping?
You're a guard, aren't you?
I'm the Royal Chicken Keeper.
I'm escaping too.
Wonderful!
Then let's run together.
Crown Prince, please spare me!
On my own, I'd have a slim chance.
You've already failed 101 times.
No way.
You must cover for me.
Or I'll execute your entire clan, believe it!
You're scaring me to death!
You're not even going to be Emperor.
You've no right to execute my clan.
Not bad, chicken keeper.
You're quite cultured.
I am an imperial scholar.
I was being sarcastic.
You all, go that way!
Don't miss a single corner!
Search thoroughly!
He was just here.
Huahua,
I'll definitely protect you.
That's strange.
You!
Go that way!
All of you, go that way!
Chicken keeper!
You've doomed me!
Hey!
Crown Prince!
Halt!
Huahua,
from now on, we...
Halt!
Who goes there?
I'm Qi Zhi, the Royal Chicken Keeper.
You're just a chicken keeper.
What are you doing at the Crown Prince's hall?
Get out of here, now.
Huahua!
I won't give up on you!
What are you doing?
Let go!
You actually like wearing women's undergarments?
That's nonsense!
Guards!
Seize him!
Embroidered with mandarin ducks.
Heh heh.
How did you know?
You were just thinking all about yesterday.
Want me to share more details?
Shhh!
You're ruthless.
Speak.
What do you want?
I want to see the Crown Prince.
You'd better give up that idea.
I'm not going to take the throne.
It's you!
Where's Huahua?
Where are my comics?
They're all right here.
Chicken for books, fair trade.
The chicken isn't here.
Did you stew it?
I didn't stew it.
I hid it away.
You're lying!
I'm not.
Help me escape.
And I'll return Huahua to you, deal?
Hey.
How do we escape?
First, let me check my comics.
The books are all there, every last one.
Just tell me how to escape.
You and I...
swap clothes.
Once I've escaped,
then you escape.
Crown Prince.
You've used this method before.
Over thirty eunuchs have been flogged because of it.
Can you please come to your senses?
This time it'll definitely work.
Since Father's passing,
the palace security isn't what it used to be.
Read my lips.
No way.
Fine.
Then get ready to drink chicken soup.
Swap!
The young Prince has arrived!
Father!
Your child has arrived too late!
Twenty-Eighth Prince,
please accept my condolences.
By the late Emperor's decree,
before the Crown Prince ascends the throne,
I shall handle all court affairs in his stead.
I ask all of you, my lords,
for your full cooperation.
Prince.
If the Prince wishes to speak, just speak.
Why have musicians play while you do?
Having your own background music...
Never mind, let's not get into it.
Back to the matter at hand.
Father has ordered me to govern in his place.
What do all of you lords think of that?
Hey.
Under the cover of night,
this is the perfect chance to seduce the Crown Prince.
Once I'm carrying the Imperial heir,
I'll be made Empress.
Father,
the revival of our Dayan Kingdom
is right around the corner.
I'm off then.
Ah!
Your Highness!
I'm a fan of your comics.
I know you love drawing comics.
I...
I'll be your model.
Wherever you want to draw,
draw away.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'll be straight with you, my lady.
The Crown Prince has fled.
He's gone!
Hahahaha!
You're so funny.
Isn't that laugh a bit too hearty?
Your Highness,
no need to be shy.
The night is long,
so why not...
on this last night before your enthronement,
let me keep you company.
Help!
Hey!
Your strength is ridiculous!
I love men like you.
The kind this Princess
can never fail to get.
Help! She's molesting me!
I...
The Crown Prince has run away!
What?
You're not the Crown Prince?
I told you I'm not the Crown Prince.
How dare you molest me!
Ah!
Pervert!
Who are you people?
And who are you?
You don't even recognize me?
Hey!
Why are you wearing the Crown Prince's clothes?
So, you dare impersonate the Crown Prince!
I'm just passing through.
You two carry on.
Wait!
I am the Princess of the Dayan Kingdom.
What are you trying to do?
You're the Princess of the Dayan Kingdom?
And I'm a Prince of the Daliang Kingdom!
Hey!
The two of you,
sneaking into the Crown Prince's chambers at night,
what are you up to?
Guards!
Seize them!
Yes, sir!
After them, hurry!
It's a misunderstanding!
Before you die,
do you have any last words?
I have one thing to say.
Hmm?
Got it.
Behead him!
Hey, hey, hey!
I haven't even spoken yet!
I still...
This, this...
This doesn't count!
How dare you!
You dare raid the execution ground?
How can you raid the execution ground without even shouting "Stay the blade"?
I don't know your Daliang customs.
But this man, today...
you cannot kill.
On what grounds?
On the grounds...
that I'm a Princess of the Dayan Kingdom.
that I have diplomatic immunity.
And on the grounds...
that this Princess wants to save him.
How about that?
Princess Ouyang,
even with diplomatic immunity,
you can't run wild in our Daliang Kingdom.
Guards!
Behead the prisoner, Qi Zhi!
Hey!
Don't save me anymore.
I won't let you become my Empress.
Just go, quickly!
I'm not here to save you.
How dare you molest me!
If you must die,
you'll die by my hand!
Me, molest you?
Hey!
Condemning a random chicken keeper in the palace,
what kind of skill is that?
You Daliang folks just bully honest people.
She actually has a point.
But that's exactly what we're doing.
So what?
Bite me!
Seize her!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and behead the prisoner!
Who dares to touch him?
Crown Prince!
Eunuch Gao,
announce the decree.
I've returned to take the throne.
Really, Your Highness?
Your Majesty!
Long live the Emperor!
Long live!
Summon...
the Royal Chicken Keeper,
Qi Zhi, for an audience!
Your servant, Qi Zhi,
greets Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Chicken keeper,
I know.
You're an imperial scholar,
deeply learned,
yet you've been raising palace chickens.
That's truly a waste of your talents.
I summoned you here today
because I hope
you can shoulder a great responsibility for the court.
Your Majesty,
I have always held
the vision of a wise ruler and able minister.
Now that I have Your Majesty's favor,
I shall surely
devote myself entirely,
until my dying breath.
Excellent.
I hereby decree:
Qi Zhi is appointed
as Secret Imperial Commissioner,
to find for me
a suitable heir to the throne,
and within three months.
I
shall abdicate at once.
All state affairs
shall be handled by the cabinet.
What?!
Huahua!
You snuck Huahua out!
I'm coming with you.
What?
You
want to find the heir to the throne.
I
want to be Empress.
I don't care who becomes Emperor.
Whoever inherits the throne
has to marry me
and make me his Empress.
So I'm going with you.
Save your breath.
With your personality,
even after we find the Prince,
nobody would want to marry you.
Oh.
Really?
"One Hundred Ways to Cook Chicken."
Four ounces of chicken,
wash clean, add salt,
and a pinch of sugar.
Fine, you win.
Let's go together.
Want it back, huh?
Once I become Empress,
I'll naturally give it back.
Hey!
Huahua!
Trying to find other heirs?
In your dreams.
When that time comes,
they'll all become stepping stones on my path to success.