HE DESERVES TO DIE, SO KILL HIM
I KILLED HIM LIKE YOU SAID
BECAUSE HE DESERVED IT
KILL HIM!
SAVE HIM?
OVERLY SUSPICIOUS
EVIDENCE, HIKIKOMORI
I DO AS I PLEASE?
MY GOSH!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
CURIOUS?
THEY ALL DIED!
A HUSBAND-KILLER?
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE
SOMETHING IS FISHY
MUST WE ALL LIVE?
WE MUST
A NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN INSPECTOR
Maybe you'll talk to me
When will it be?
You will turn around to look
With a startled expression
Time keeps passing by
You should be almost home
Why won't you turn around?
Must you make me worry so?
I wish I could talk to you
I wish I could hold your hand
Just a little more
I wish you'd walk a little slower for once
KO DAM, A HUMBLE MAN FROM HEAD TO TOE
What the…
This is delicious.
EPISODE 7
Yes, hello.
-Hello, sir.
-You're doing a great job.
-Thank you.
Let's get going.
The security is laxer than we expected.
What if a huge truck crashed into him now?
What?
No way.
He's untouchable.
Hello, sir!
Hello.
I'm sorry about the noise when
you've kindly let us use the road here.
Don't mention it. It's for a good cause.
Those dogs can bark as much as they want.
Have fun on your walk, guys!
How are you going to kill him?
It won't matter how long we watch him.
It looks like he's tightly guarded.
Give it here.
How will she kill him
when he stays hidden like that?
Take a look.
Maybe he'll come out
when a war breaks out.
Kim Su-yong will be back in a week.
Will a war break out during that time?
Will you be drafted too, Santa?
CREATING THE FUTURE WITH KD PEACE LAB
That's it.
Joan of Arc will march out to war.
SEPTEMBER 14, 2 P.M.
KD PEACE LAB CONVENTION CENTER
-My gosh!
-That's amazing!
-It's cool, right?
-It's amazing!
Don't you think so?
All right. There it goes!
There it goes!
My goodness. Look at it go!
There!
Ko Dam…
There seems to be no reason
for her to kill him though.
Things are not always as they seem.
There will be a showcase demonstrating
a robot made by Ko Dam's company.
He'll announce
his candidacy for mayor there.
Is that so?
He's heavily guarded everywhere he goes.
This will be one of the few times
that he'll be out in the open.
This will be when K strikes.
What do we do then?
We could just have him
cancel the showcase.
Will that make K give up killing him?
No. She'll wait for the next chance.
She won't give up.
You know her so well
as if you two are friends.
The same goes for Ko Dam. I doubt
he'll agree to cancel the showcase.
The showcase will proceed as planned,
and K will try to kill him somehow.
What do we do then?
We can't just let him die.
We'll have to stop her.
How?
I'll set the stage for her.
Whoever is on stage
could be considered vulnerable.
There's no telling who could attack
and from where.
That's what K is like.
We can't expect
when and where she'll strike.
Since we won't be able to
stop her from attacking,
we'll predict her next move
and prepare ourselves accordingly.
Will that be enough?
It won't be.
Just cut to the chase, will you?
The person on stage
has the upper hand in one thing.
Knowing that their attacker
is watching them.
My snacks!
They're mine!
Give me back my snacks!
Give them back, they're mine!
They're mine!
Let's take a look.
-They're mine!
-Bad Kyung-yi!
Let's go.
-I hate you, auntie!
-She's horrible, isn't she?
-Let's go over there.
-They're mine!
Yes. She ate them all, didn't she?
So you want us to use a hostage.
It's just an idea.
Then what do you need from me?
Be careful.
It will blow up at the slightest shock.
Is this what you're up to these days?
Since when did you start
speaking casually to me?
-What is it?
-Move it.
FACTORY 1
-It's really there.
-What's that box?
What is that? A parcel delivery?
Call the police. Now!
Hurry and call the police!
I told you to tighten up the security
since we have a showcase coming up.
I'm glad someone tipped us off.
Don't you think so?
Who gave us the tip-off?
I'm sorry, sir.
It's fine. You look like
you want to tell me something.
I think you should either cancel
or postpone the showcase, sir.
There have been numerous
irregularities. We--
Gosh.
Those damned beasts
keep barking away day and night.
Is that all you had to tell me?
Cancel the contract we have
with the 25 Hour Guardians
and file a claim for breach of contract
and compensation.
And tell the reporters
that their captain is a problematic--
I'm sorry, sir.
Please give me another chance.
You know what?
This isn't just about money.
This is about the trust between us two.
I'm sorry, sir.
You're sorry?
How do I know if you mean it?
If you're truly sorry,
you should show me how sincere you are.
Only then will we be able to
rebuild the trust we had.
Please tell me how.
Let's see.
How about some volunteer work?
Don't worry. I've got this sorted.
That's right. He did.
Then he told me
to go feed the dogs at the shelter.
Mr. Ko may be a little eccentric
but he's a good man.
Yes. He'll give us a second chance.
Hold on.
REQUESTING COMPENSATION
FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT WITH KD PEACE LAB
CLAIMS FOR DAMAGES
This can't be.
Children and dogs are better when quiet.
-Don't you agree?
-Sir.
What's going on?
You won't be away for too long
with animal abuse charges.
So just keep quiet and do your time.
Your wife will be devastated
if she has another miscarriage.
BEWARE OF DOGS
How could you?
How could you do such a thing?
Tell me it isn't true!
How could you do this to the poor things?
How could you?
DELICIOUS ANCHOVY NOODLES
SAVING
FLAVOR HUNTER
Hello? This is Top Bodyguard.
Yes.
"KD Peace Lab"?
They hired new security.
WHEN WILL YOU COME?
GRANDMA MISSES YOU
SOMETIME THIS WEEK.
WAIT A LITTLE.
You'll get caught if you keep using that.
-Are you surveilling my phone as well?
-We need to make this perfect.
Could I have
the most popular drink you have?
Hold on.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
POSTAL SERVICE
CONFERENCE HALL, EXIT ONLY
These are the people
who will be allowed in that day.
VIPs, reporters, and caterers.
Ko Dam is quite meticulous.
He hasn't invited anyone
who isn't trustworthy.
I had to do three interviews.
I failed my first interview.
So he doesn't use anyone
who he finds suspicious.
Yes, it seems that way.
Hey, you.
You've grown quite mature.
Since we're in charge of security,
you can join the security team.
Santa will be inside
and you will be outside.
Let's see.
He'll give an introduction
and introduce some of the guests.
Then he'll get on the robot himself
for the showcase.
He'll have some people on stage
to give him flowers after that.
Then he'll pose
for some photos as a finale.
The press conference was canceled
due to security reasons.
He'll just announce his candidacy.
But why did you say that earlier?
What do you mean?
You said he'd be a pain in the neck
if he ran for mayor
when we were at his office.
Who's neck will he end up hurting?
Director Yong's first son
is running for mayor.
Everyone knows.
You do too, right? Gyeong-su?
Of course, I do.
Well, you only care about games
and have no interest in the real world.
I was saying it'd be a pain in the neck
for Director Yong.
We work together. I can say that, can't I?
The pitch of your voice
still gets higher when you're anxious.
I told you to get that fixed
since it won't help with police work.
Stop accusing me.
There aren't any other entrances
apart from the ones we see here, right?
No. That's the final blueprint.
What about Jung Jeong-yeon?
She's on her way back.
How will K know what's going on in there
when all the cameras have been cut off?
She'll have her people out there.
That will be the chink in her armor.
So this is your big plan.
Will it work?
She can't help but take the bait.
It's the only thing K has to protect.
The view here sure is great.
Could it be time for dinner?
I can't even tell what time it is.
I wonder if there's a place
that sells budaejjigae nearby.
If I knew where I was,
I could recommend you a great restaurant.
-Ms. Jung Jeong-yeon.
-Bathroom.
I need to use the bathroom.
What is it?
Are you going to
follow me to the bathroom?
Take her with you.
I don't feel like it anymore.
Then sit down.
We've failed to track her phone.
Is she in Korea or is she abroad?
Is she in Seoul or somewhere else?
You're driving me nuts.
I told you already, didn't I?
I don't know where Yi-kyung is.
Just give me back my phone.
I'll ask her myself.
No, I'll just go find her for you.
I'll bring her and we can talk this out.
You can't keep me here like this.
Ms. Jung Jeong-yeon.
You're free to leave whenever.
Just say you'll cooperate with us
and we'll let you go.
You know that.
Are you one of them?
Long time no see.
You are behind this, aren't you?
You're the one who framed Yi-kyung, right?
Tell me.
I'd love to tell you.
How about we talk outside?
Let me talk to her for a second.
It's so bright.
What the hell are we doing here?
A plate of raw flounder
and a bottle of soju.
Then a couple of hours playing games
on the computer. That'd be perfect.
You knew all along, didn't you?
Know what?
That Yi-kyung is different
from the other kids.
You don't have a child, do you?
Every child is special to their mothers.
Of course she's different.
Yi-kyung is a good kid.
She's not even your daughter.
The message you got,
saying your mother was sick.
You know that was Yi-kyung, don't you?
No good kid in the world
would tell such a lie
to have their aunt travel to the States.
There's no evidence
to prove that it was her.
It's a baseless accusation.
You flew back based on what we told you
when there isn't any evidence.
That itself is enough evidence.
You were worried about it
deep in your heart.
You believed that
the suspicion you've had
may have been true all along.
I'm only here
because I'm worried about her.
You're not worried about
what will happen to her.
You're worried about what she'll do.
Stop saying that!
That's right.
Yi-kyung killed people.
What do you know about Yi-kyung?
Who are you to say such things about her?
What the hell do you know about Yi-kyung?
Are you done?
We want the same thing, Ms. Jung.
We both don't want anyone to die
or get hurt at the showcase tomorrow.
No one will die or get hurt.
Because Yi-kyung isn't a murderer.
I'm going to meet Yi-kyung tomorrow
and set things straight.
Then you'll have to…
apologize for saying
such horrible things about her.
When you see her,
ask her about your suspicions.
You're the only person
she can be honest with in the world.
How do you even
know about restaurants like this?
I mean, the fish just
melts away in my mouth.
You can come here regularly now.
I'll give you more money.
Did you get a promotion?
That could happen
if I tried a little harder.
Then I guess
you'll be even busier.
So please take good care of Na Na for me.
Nice!
Here we go!
Let's go. One more.
We'll go again.
Hit a home run like Lee Seung-yuop!
One, two, three!
My turn.
Hey.
-Where should I--
-Quiet!
What are they doing?
The computer hasn't frozen, has it?
It's working fine.
They changed the signal again.
They closed off all connections
and reset the system.
This isn't going to be
easy to get through.
Does she think this is enough to stop me?
How cute.
I did what you asked.
Why were you crouched like that?
Can we talk now?
You can.
But talk as if K is listening in on us.
Wasn't Joan of Arc burned at the stake?
We checked all the flammable items.
I thought I had to whisper.
Sometimes I envy how simple you are.
Here you go.
JOAN OF ARC
This book contains
so many ways to kill people.
I told them to report to me
if they find anything suspicious.
What's that?
What?
Over there.
My eyes have gone bad.
Let's see.
Diameter of 1mm. Black.
There's a lot of them.
I've heard Israel has developed
tiny bombs like these.
Aren't they rat feces?
They must have come through here.
What did?
Rats.
-Do I really have to--
-We can't have any gaps left.
Stay focused.
They're quite good at this.
I think you enjoy playing with Ms. Koo
more than taking care of Ko Dam.
It's fun seeing her struggle.
Dealing with Ko Dam…
is too easy.
They say you'll miss the big picture
if you're hunched too low.
When are we going to eat?
Go and hide yourself.
Hurry.
-Who is it?
-It's me.
-Did you take your medicine?
-Yes.
The fever's gone.
I told you you didn't have to.
You haven't eaten, right?
I brought a lot of food
so we can eat together.
Hello.
What? Hi.
I'm Geon-uk's cousin.
I came to visit him while I was in Seoul.
I see.
Hi, I'm… Well…
I know him from work.
Jeez, you two must be very close.
You brought him porridge
when you just know him from work.
Can I join you?
-Sure. She can do that, right?
-Yes, why not.
Let's go take a walk after we eat.
It looks delicious.
That's mine.
-What?
-That's mine.
Geon-uk doesn't drink.
Right.
You shouldn't touch
someone else's property like that.
Well, he's not "someone else."
But you just know him from work.
-Are you going to be here long?
-Why do you ask?
This stuff isn't good for Geon-uk.
I want you to throw them out.
My gosh!
What's gotten into him?
Some colleague you have.
-Is he your wife or something?
-Yi-kyung!
What are you doing? Just eat the porridge.
Didn't you say you were busy?
All right. I'll get on it right away.
It tastes so good, Dae-ho.
-Slow down, will you?
-Okay.
K isn't looking for ways
to murder people in the playscript.
She's reading them for inspiration.
At first, angels appeared from the sky…
and the stones from the enemy catapults
fell on Joan of Arc's head.
I think the cables here are damaged.
I think it may be these.
In the second battle,
the angels bring rain
to keep the British army at bay.
SPRINKLER MAIN PUMP
Joan of Arc is shot in the leg
by the French army.
She is abandoned
in the middle of the battlefield.
You sure are reckless for
someone who's suspicious of everything.
Are you all right?
Thanks.
Let's put the cover back on.
How many more do we have to go through?
One more. And it's the most suspicious.
It looks pretty sloppy from the back.
MR. KIM
Can I take it for a ride?
You can't operate it right now.
You're scared to get in, aren't you?
How long will this thing be operated?
Let's see.
In the rehearsals,
it averaged 13 minutes 40 seconds.
How long does it take
for this to open and close?
It takes 13 seconds to open.
from a completely closed state.
What are you doing?
Anyone have a knife?
Move over.
It wasn't the robot, but the stairs.
It's made of ferrocerium,
so it's like flint.
When it comes into contact with metal…
It would be dangerous
to enter the robot using this.
If there's anything flammable
inside the robot,
a fire will start.
But Ko Dam won't be
scratching the stairs on his way up.
His ring. He never takes it off.
And to operate the robot…
Shoe polish.
It's perfect to start a fire with.
And the insides have been
wiped clean with alcohol
just in case he could be poisoned.
And they'll clean it again
before the showcase tomorrow.
"Raise the cross!"
"Yelled Joan of Arc as she was
engulfed by the flames."
Here's our man of the day.
KD Peace Lab's CEO, Ko Dam!
With Peacehero 2, our future will be
full of peace and only peace.
Everything seems fine so far.
Maybe K gave up.
This will only be the beginning for her.
Did you check
who placed the stairs there today?
We'll trace their whereabouts
after the showcase is over.
It'd be better if we caught her
before we did that though.
Is it really moving? I want to see it too.
We're not here to have fun.
Stay in position.
You should stay focused too.
I'm just checking if it's been poisoned.
What is it?
It's so good.
This guy may be smarter than you are.
It's just as I expected.
How many are there to go?
There aren't that many left.
I see.
I'll put them away. Here.
Thanks.
What's with your voice?
Why are you being so kind?
You should talk to me like that too.
Whatever. How many are there left?
The fireworks were just the appetizer.
This will be the main course.
When?
Now.
That one.
No, the one before.
Bingo.
Jeez, this thing is heavy.
But you've been
exercising with your lover.
Where did your strength go?
Hey, you.
Yes?
Come here for a second.
Do you have any drinks?
I'll get you some right away.
-Please bring us some drinks.
-Sure thing. Bye.
Thank you.
I need to get
the security team some drinks.
Please.
Why not flirt some more?
Isn't he your type?
Next up, we have a guest speaker
from the Sexual Assault
Victims' Support Center.
Je-hui. Are you ready?
Yes. She's on her way.
A guest of honor,
invited by Ko Dam himself.
In the hopes of creating a just society,
Peacehero 2, operated by Ko Dam,
will present
our female guests with flowers.
It's about time
the chink in the armor showed.
We, at the center,
support Ko Dam's candidacy
to become the next mayor of Seoul.
I was going to pretend I didn't hear that,
but the mic is just too loud and clear.
With a heavy heart,
I will accept your support.
He's putting on quite a show.
Helping the victims one by one
on my own is nowhere enough.
I understand very well
that society as a whole must change
for there to be no more victims.
I, Ko Dam,
will become the next mayor of Seoul
and create a brand new Seoul
where you will be able to go about
your day without worrying about crime.
-I'm out.
-Hold on.
-What now?
-Get me a view of the robot again.
What is it?
-Ko Dam!
Aunt?
What's she doing there?
I think something's gone wrong.
Get my aunt out of there!
The robots. What happened to the robots?
They're already out.
-Ko Dam!
What's that? Robots? They're adorable.
-My goodness.
-They're so cute.
Is this a part of our plan?
Those robots are adorable, aren't they?
They're dancing in unison
as if to show that they were made
in the birthplace of K-Pop.
AUNTIE
-The number you have dialed…
-Damn it.
Get her out of there now.
Was this on our list or not?
It wasn't.
-Evacuate the hall.
-What about you?
Where are you?
Ma'am. You have to come with me.
Who are you?
Yi-kyung wants you out of here.
Where is she?
Does Yi-kyung have
something to do with Ko Dam?
Hurry and get out of there!
Hurry!
Is Yi-kyung
trying to kill Ko Dam?
Everyone, get out!
Stop him!
Go keep Jung Jeong-yeon safe!
Where is Ko Dam?
Damn it.
This can't be.
Yi-kyung wouldn't do something like this.
Santa!
SEOUL MAPO
NA 0545
I saw the number.
Did you secure Ko Dam, Je-hui?
Je-hui!
Those useless bums.
How dare they do something like this
during my showcase?
How embarrassing.
911 FIRE DEPARTMENT
Where is my aunt?
Where is she?
He's so useless.
I'm glad I secured an escape route.
I bet you didn't know about this.
How dare they try to kill me.
Did you secure Ko Dam?
Je-hui. Je-hui!
MR. KIM
I've secured Ko Dam.
I'll send someone over.
-What's going on?
-Ms. Jung.
This isn't what you think it is.
Is this why
you told me that Yi-kyung
was going to kill that man?
Because you wanted to kill him
and frame her for it.
You're wrong.
You saw what happened back there.
It was Yi-kyung who did that.
How am I supposed to believe that?
This was so that you could kill that man.
No, he's not dead yet.
He's still alive. Take a look.
I was only trying to get him to safety.
Cut the crap.
Where's Yi-kyung?
Tell me where Yi-kyung is!
Where is she? Why did she even come here?
Where is Yi-kyung?
Hello?
Why are you answering the phone?
Where are you right now?
Is this Yi-kyung?
How did you…
Are you hurt?
Is that Yi-kyung?
Where are you right now?
Why are you with Ko Dam?
You're not hurt, are you?
Yes. He's not dead yet.
Where are you right now?
Don't move an inch from where you are.
Yi-kyung. Are you all right?
Yi-kyung!
Ms. Jung!
Are you nuts? Move it!
No.
This can't be…
We should go.
We need to get out of here!
-I did as you told me.
-Okay. Great job.
I just wanted to ask you something.
And say my goodbyes before you go.
You must really love your sons.
I'll do anything you want.
Let's stop now.
You sure have taught me a lesson.
I've learned a lot.
It would be great if I could believe you
but I'm quite skeptical.
I'm the only one who knows
and only I can access that information.
There's no way anyone would find out.
I'll take it to the grave with me.
Really?
Then I guess I'll let you.
What?
What are you doing?
No…
You'll burn your hair.
Ko Dam of KD Peace Lab,
a charitable human rights lawyer,
has died from the unintended
acceleration of his vehicle.
The police have reported
that the accident may have occurred
due to a faulty safety check.
Meanwhile, the fire that broke out
during the showcasing of Peacehero 2
caused a stampede at the conference hall
due to mass evacuation,
killing one and injuring twelve people.
While the cause of the death
is unclear at the moment,
it was reported that…
I just don't get how both Ko Dam
and Jung Jeong-yeon could have died.
It's because of me.
An innocent woman died because of me.
We won't be seeing each other anymore.
-So is this how you'll end it?
-Team B has officially disbanded.
What about K? Who will catch her then?
You don't look excited.
You look like a cow
being taken to the slaughterhouse.
After what happened to your aunt,
you're not the same as you used to be.
I should have realized that when you were
after me even though you're not a cop.
You must think we're running
some big operation just to catch you,
but you're not that important.
How could you be so laid-back
when I could be coming for you any minute?
You find that suspicious too, right?
She was a horrible person.
It wasn't because he was a bad man
that they killed him.
I don't know
whether she's right or not anymore.
Subtitle translation by: Alan Smithee