NO OUTSIDE FOOD OR DRINK
Does this
look good on me?
Ms. Koo!
How does it look?
EPISODE 9
Is this any better?
What have you done with Je-hui?
I don't know what you mean.
Tell me.
A spoon?
Should I show you what I can do with this?
Who do you think I am?
I'm not here to see you.
I'm here to see Ms. Yong,
who's calling for help.
"Ms. Yong"?
What? Why did you want to see me?
I thought you two
had some unfinished business.
You're a powerful person.
And I, too, have powers.
So I thought maybe we could work together.
-That's why I'm here.
-What do you mean?
Do you want to work
for the Children's Foundation?
No.
There's something I want to do.
I need someone with a lot of power
to watch my back.
What do you want to do?
I want to kill people.
It's tiring looking for people to kill
and cleaning up afterward
when I do it alone.
I see.
You must know a lot of bad people.
Like Ko Dam for example.
You say the most frightening things
with that pretty face of yours.
But how can I trust you
when you're intimidating me like that?
I see.
First of all,
I'm not killing anyone right now.
I'm holding my composure like a lady.
Secondly, if you ask me
for a favor right now,
I can make it happen right away.
Don't you do anything stupid.
Should I?
Let's see…
Right. I heard someone say this yesterday.
"Je-hui."
"I don't know anymore
whether you deserve to die or not."
What do you think happened to her?
If you promise to clean--
-Did you kill her?
-No.
But can you believe me?
You won't believe it
unless you see for yourself.
-Stop them!
-No, stop!
I could have died twice
in the time it took you to get here.
She's working with me now,
so leave her alone.
Which one?
Kimchi stains are impossible to remove.
Don't you have to go check on your friend?
You'll die too if she's dead.
Isn't it too easy?
Killing someone who nobody would look for
wouldn't be any fun for you.
What are you doing? Get her.
I see. Hey, come with me.
Gosh, that was amazing.
I think we're going to get along famously.
I guess you could be useful.
Why couldn't we have met earlier?
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let her go.
You can't run from us.
Just get in.
Why not just finish me off here?
She doesn't like things getting messy.
You know exactly why.
Just tell me if Je-hui's okay.
She's dead.
Why ask
when you're not going to believe me?
Yes?
Yes, that's right. I'm Flavor Hunter.
I'm a Power Blogger?
Okay. I'll do that.
Yes, thank you.
This is so cliché.
Knockout gas? Are you kidding me? Hey!
Ms. Koo.
I don't like doing this,
but Yong Suk's put me up to it.
Don't hate me for it.
You like to drink.
This isn't too bad, is it?
Right.
Thank you for your hard work.
WASTE DISPOSAL
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING INSPECTOR KOO
She's done this before.
She probably went for a walk.
Do we really need to do this?
It's because she never goes out
this early in the morning.
There she is.
She seems to be on her own.
She's not the type of person
to take long trips alone like this.
At six in the morning at that.
The number you have dialed--
Ms. Na.
Are you all right?
Ms. Koo disappeared all of a sudden.
Call me right away
when you get this message.
UNREAD MESSAGES
MS. KOO
What is it? Did she contact you?
"I'm going to go collect my thoughts."
"Don't look for me for a while."
See? She's fine.
She's not.
She never writes long messages like this.
SANTA?
WHERE?
Where did she go?
ELDERLY TRACKER
ELDERLY TRACKER, TRACKING LOCATION
MY LOCATION
Is anyone around?
Is there anyone there?
Anyone there?
I'll be fine
as long as I "wit" my "keeps" about me.
That's right.
Come on.
Let's see.
Wait.
Careful.
And now…
My gosh.
This isn't a place she'd go
to collect her thoughts.
Are you sure she's here?
TRACKING LOCATION
SHARE LOCATION
Watch out, Santa!
Does that belong to Ms. Koo?
How do you know?
Seriously?
No, not me. Go away.
Shoo. Get away. Don't come.
No…
Go away. Don't.
Get away.
Anyone out there?
Anyone?
Kyung-yi.
Je-hui?
Je-hui!
Are you all right?
I'm over here.
Where?
"Where"?
I'm in way over my head.
Why are you trying so hard?
I thought you didn't have
a reason to live anymore.
That's what you said
when your husband died.
I did.
Then why are you trying so hard to live?
Because I'm a suspicious person
and I have to see with my own eyes
whether you're okay or not.
Let's see. Calm down.
Hold still.
Here we go.
Let's go. I can do it.
Hurry.
This is good.
I'm almost there.
Slowly…
Hold on.
Wait.
I have to…
I have to make it in one go.
One.
Two.
Three!
SPAIN
KASSANDRA ALONSO
NATIONALITY: SPAIN
No way.
I came all the way here.
I can't go back after just a day.
Muy bien. Muchas gracias.
Спасибо, Danke!
That annoying brat.
She really must be powerful.
KING LEAR, HANSEL AND GRETEL, JOAN OF ARC…
This place is so hip.
What is this?
They've put in a lot of effort.
This is a prison.
I was just going for a walk.
What the hell was that?
What have I gotten myself into?
Is that the sun or the moon?
Is this oil?
Wait.
Over here!
This is fun.
I'm down here!
Hey!
I understand that you don't trust anyone.
But I bet no one in this world
cares about you more than I do.
I won't be there when you regret this.
You were right.
Oil! Where did it go?
No, wait.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Koo!
Mr. Dokkaebi. Please find Ms. Koo for me.
I was determined
not to lose her this time.
I don't know where she is.
Help me.
SEHM KIDS CHILDREN'S HOME
You're doing great.
Don't go easy with the salt.
You two get along so great.
Why didn't you get more reporters to come?
We're doing this so that
we can feed our children good kimchi.
It's nothing to boast about.
Would you like to taste it?
I'd prefer it if he gave me some instead.
Right. It'd taste better
since he's better looking than I am.
Let's see. Here comes the kimchi.
Please move aside.
Open wide.
How is it?
You're not only handsome
but a great cook too.
Looks like we're out of the marinade.
Right. I'll go get some more.
You should come too.
Would this be enough, Mom?
Do I have some on my face?
Did you get it undone?
What do you mean?
Mom. Gosh, how embarrassing.
Have you, or haven't you?
I didn't. It just came undone naturally.
And now to snip it again--
Which hospital was it
and who was the doctor?
Do you know what I went through
to have you snipped?
Who was it that dared to undo
the procedure without my permission?
Mom. Why are you doing this?
-Someone might--
-Heo Hyeon-tae!
Gosh, Mom. It's not what it looks like.
I didn't impregnate her
and she didn't give birth.
It was just a visit to the OBGYN.
And the person who's blackmailing us.
He's not even her brother. It's her pimp.
He's quite well-known for being a scumbag.
I'll make this go away quietly.
How much does he want?
I'll help you.
Mom…
We should go back.
Seong-tae will be waiting.
Right. Okay.
You mess with Seong-tae's campaign,
and I'm going to end your life.
Come in.
Hyeon-tae's left
because he had prior engagements.
It's too bad.
Right.
Did you find the thing Ko Dam had?
Yes, we're almost there.
"Almost"?
I wonder
what your kimchi tastes like, Mr. Kim.
-Hurry it up.
-Yes, ma'am.
I say this every time I visit,
but this place has great Feng Shui.
It's overflowing with positive energy.
What are you doing?
No, let me.
You're a guest here, after all.
You've made yourself at home.
I looked around
and found a lot of old tea.
They say tea gets better with age,
so I tried creating my own mix.
Try it.
Fine.
What about you?
All right.
What happened to Ms. Koo?
She won't bother you anymore.
Is she in a better place?
It's you who's in a better place.
I see.
Right. I sure am.
Aren't you spending too much time indoors?
You should go out for some fresh air.
Can I actually go out?
His name is Park Du-mok
and he lives in Ssangbong-gu.
Is this enough?
Enough for what?
Isn't this enough
for you to use your powers?
Should I get the car ready?
It's not that simple.
There's a lot to prepare for.
It seems we need more time
to get to know each other.
Mr. Kim will get you everything you need.
What do you need?
What does he do?
Is he so bad that he deserves to die?
He's the vilest man
to have walked the earth.
He sells girls like you
who have nowhere to go.
He's a very bad man.
That bastard.
I asked him for two million
and I haven't heard from him since.
I guess I'll have to go to the reporters.
Do you know any?
Give me their number.
I'm going to show the world
what a scumbag he is.
Come on. They don't call him
"Rabbit" for nothing.
Why would I split the money with her?
I'm the one putting in all the work.
All she did was lie on her back
and spread her legs for him.
Am I wrong? I'm hanging up.
Gosh, that startled me.
You should have taken the stairs.
I'm sorry.
But who's Rabbit?
What?
I'll let you live
if you tell me in ten seconds.
Mission accomplished.
It won't kill you to compliment me
every once in a while.
I'm coming.
What's this?
This is creepy.
Tell me one good reason
why I should get out of here.
There isn't any.
I don't drink anymore.
Did you think I played computer games
because I wanted to?
I do miss drinking though.
Is that all?
It's not like you'd be there
even if I get out.
I'd have a better chance of meeting you
if I just stayed here.
It's always you who end up saving me.
There's no way this would work in one go.
I'm off. Bye.
Just a little more.
Just a little… I'm almost there.
Ms. Koo!
In this world, Santa can talk.
Get a hold of yourself.
I could use a round of applause about now.
Kyung-yi!
-Are you real?
-Kyung-yi!
Hurry!
Careful.
Wait. Slow down.
My goodness.
Come on. Slow down.
My gosh.
-My goodness.
-Careful.
No, wait.
Are you all right?
What did you get yourself into?
Je-hui? Is that you?
I should have given you
something more unique.
My gosh.
Geez, seriously.
Thank god…
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Is that what you did to Ms. Koo?
Can't you hear me?
"This is the flower of breath…
the flower of bone…
and the flower of flesh."
"Father. Mother. You are to
travel back to the realm of the living."
"Come back to me!"
And then it goes, "boom!"
The smoke rises and it rains flowers.
The two come back to life and…
You're back.
I've missed you.
I knew you'd be back.
You should go see a doctor.
Hurry it up, Santa.
What flavor is that one?
The yellow one and the white one.
I want them both.
Hurry it up. Geez.
They'll probably think I'm dead.
Let's have them think that
for the time being.
But still…
What?
Do you want to go rat on them
that I'm still alive?
I'm not that horrible.
She searched all over with us
after she found out you were gone.
If I knew they'd do this to you,
I wouldn't have joined them.
Really? Are you sure?
You're being too harsh.
So why did K let you live?
She was here.
What do you mean?
I thought very hard
how K might have found Director Yong.
I knew how the moment I saw you alive.
How can you tell from just that?
And Na Na told me
that a pretty girl visited the place.
This is a nice house.
It looks like you have it good.
I wasn't going to kill her,
but I don't think I can resist.
If I pull a little harder,
you'll be dead.
What?
How can you faint already?
Hello? Are you there?
My gosh. I came to talk to you!
Geez.
You're just too much.
I'll tell you.
Tell me what?
The person who's after you.
The person who ruined everything.
I thought it was you.
Tell me then.
It's Yong Suk.
She's Heo Seong-tae's mom,
and she's controlling everything
from the shadows.
She contacted us
saying she wants to catch you.
Ko Dam, your aunt… It was all her.
Hold on.
-But why?
-What?
Why does she want to catch me?
There must be a reason.
I don't know that.
You don't?
She must be able to
sleep through anything.
I'm not lying.
I'll look into why she wants to catch you.
So please…
You're overreacting.
Do you know why
I won't kill you right now?
You go to a better place when you die.
That's what Ms. Koo said.
I don't want you…
in a better place.
Instead…
I could make your life a living hell.
You better be quick.
Before I take Na Na
and give Mr. Na Jong-jun a visit
at Munmin Villa apartment 302.
Let's keep our encounter
a secret between us two, okay?
K knows that Na Na's seen her face.
But K won't do anything to her.
She has a rule that
she only kills those who deserve it.
You'll be fine, Ms. Na.
Nonsense. She's just another murderer.
She's just saying that
to justify her actions.
So you're telling me
that you managed to stay alive
by promising you'd do what she wants.
You're being too harsh on her.
Then what was I supposed to do?
The team was disbanded because of me,
but I still had to make a living.
And she came to find me at my place
and you went missing.
What else could I have done?
What would you have done?
I wouldn't have worked for someone like
Director Yong in the first place.
-Stop bullying my mom!
-My gosh.
I know that I shouldn't have done that.
You have a lot to protect,
but I don't have anything.
What's the use in making such comparisons?
Don't you think so?
Let's find what K wants.
If you don't agree, get out.
But this is my house.
Why did Director Yong
want to catch K in the first place?
She contacted us all of a sudden
after the incident in Tongyeong.
Hold on.
That incident with Kim Min-gyu…
I had forgotten about it
since you went missing.
I found something shocking.
Well, it's…
-It's…
-Hurry and tell us.
The tattoo.
K's right-hand man from Ko Dam's showcase.
We don't know for sure
if that was her right-hand--
The tattoo that was on the right arm
of the right-hand man.
I found out what it is.
What is it?
It was the same tattoo
that Lee Jun-hyeon had.
Who's Lee Jun-hyeon?
That boy who died on the boat
during the Hyochang Bio party.
LATE LEE JUN-HYEON
These are from Lee Jun-hyeon's
place of residence.
There isn't much here.
K's right-hand man
is Lee Jun-hyeon's acquaintance?
It's more than that.
It's a tattoo that juvenile offenders
get to mimic the mob.
It means they won't forget each other
even after their release.
So this means
that K's right-hand man served time
in a juvenile reformatory
at the same time as Lee Jun-hyeon.
-Gyeong-su.
-What is it?
They say the "primer" near the school
sings the "sparrow."
That's quite a discovery.
You did well.
I got all the information
of the people who were in
Lee Jun-hyeon's contact list.
Let's have a look.
PERSONAL INFO
FROM LEE JUN-HYEON'S CONTACT LIST
AN GEON-UK, 25
WORKS AT MEK SECURITY
What? He just quit without a word.
Do you know if he was at work on this day?
But why would the insurance company
want to know this?
It's just that the days he worked
can affect
the maximum age he can work until.
I see. Hey, Dae-ho.
Yes, sir?
Take a look at this.
Was Geon-uk at work on this day?
-Do you remember?
-What's this for?
He's from an insurance company.
He's not close to Geon-uk,
so he wouldn't know either.
I've got to get back to work.
I'm Oh Gyeong-su from NT Life Insurance.
Did something happen to Geon-uk?
No. It's just that we need this
for some paperwork.
He wasn't at work that day.
He's quite frail.
He has problems breathing.
Then was he at work on this day?
He had the morning shift that day.
And…
We're done, right?
Wait.
Do you by any chance know
if Geon-uk had a tattoo like this one?
I don't know what he did,
but I don't want anything to do with him.
So stop bothering me.
I wonder if there's anything useful.
Don't touch them! They're mine!
Gosh, fine.
I thought you were throwing them out.
My goodness.
Will you hold my hand?
Be with me forever
Are you kidding me?
LET'S KEEP EXERCISING
Nice to see you again, you bastard.
We're here to read the gas meter.
How can anyone live like this?
Who the hell are you?
Go on. Back to sleep.
There, there.
When I was left to fend for myself
because nobody helped me
as I was a single mom…
What is she saying?
She must think she raised you on her own.
…it was candidate Heo Seong-tae,
who reached out to me.
It was like a miracle.
Na Na. It's your turn.
Gosh, it's my child.
He's good to moms
-He's good to the children
-We love Mr. Heo Seong-tae
He's good to moms
He's good to the children
We love Mr. Heo Seong-tae
With Heo Seong-tae
-Let's go, Na Na.
-You're no longer lonely
He's kind and he gives you hope
Candidate number seven, Heo Seong-tae
I'm the best!
-Heo Seong-tae!
-Sir.
-Go, Heo Seong-tae!
-How about you join them?
-What?
It would look better that way.
-What is it?
-Well…
He's good to moms
He's good to the children
We love Mr. Heo Seong-tae
With Heo Seong-tae
You're no longer lonely
He's kind and he gives you hope
How adorable.
Candidate number seven, Heo Seong-tae
-Heo Seong-tae!
Good job.
What are we doing here?
-Let's go grab some snacks.
-Okay.
Well done.
You've done great.
Your idea was great, Ms. Na.
You look great on film too.
They'd think we hired a model.
Thank you, sir.
This is why we need young blood.
Time passes by quickly.
It's all thanks to you.
It would have been great
if your second son was here too.
I think Mr. Heo Hyeon-tae
might be better suited
to bring in the mothers' votes.
Why do you say that?
I guess I'm not good-looking enough.
That's not what I meant.
Your brother must be very busy.
I haven't seen him lately--
-I should get to my next schedule.
-Sure.
You're still taking
that ginseng regularly, right?
Go ahead.
Are you looking for a husband?
So…
do you want me to look for one?
No. That won't be necessary.
When did you last contact Ms. Koo?
It's been a while.
Do you need her for something?
No. It's just that
I haven't seen her in a while.
I was curious.
I'm rather relieved since she's so quiet.
The same goes for K.
It feels at peace
since they're not around.
I'm sure they're alive.
You still have that.
That scar, I mean.
Tell me if anything's bothering you.
Don't keep it to yourself.
If you keep eating everything we feed you,
it'd be way too easy for us to kill you.
I have no reason to kill you.
I meant Yi-kyung.
We've met before, right?
We met a few days ago
and we also met
a long time ago in Bongbaek.
LET'S KEEP EXERCISING
You shouldn't touch that.
I was wondering
if Yi-kyung did something to it
since you were passed out after eating it.
Why would she try to kill me?
Because you know too much.
Lady. You don't seem to know anything.
Then that would mean that you know a lot.
You're making me curious.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
I'll let you go if you give me
the answers I'm looking for.
Do I look that naive?
Do you think we enjoy
holding you captive here?
And you smell bad too.
Even if we don't, Yi-kyung will…
Or Yi-kyung's new friend
will come to take care of you.
She's made a powerful friend, you see.
She must have not told you.
There are others who are helping Yi-kyung?
I know that you two killed everyone
who was related to Lee Jun-hyeon.
But something kept bothering me.
You must still have what you dug up then.
Don't you know
that we leave no traces behind?
You're right.
Then how did you know
that the people you killed
had something to do with Lee Jun-hyeon?
Gosh, my legs feel cramped.
The security footage from the ship
and the port were wiped clean,
so we had a hard time finding them.
But people talked and rumors spread.
They said all sorts of crazy things
go down on that boat,
and that it's no big deal
even if someone ends up dead.
So we went after the people
at Hyochang Bio
who didn't go home that day.
You worked so hard.
Too bad it was for something stupid.
What? "Stupid"?
There's definitely something bigger
behind what happened to Lee Jun-hyeon.
What are the chances of there
being a backup of the footage?
There's no way it exists
since I couldn't find it.
Gosh, Mr. Know-it-all.
You didn't know that the protein you ate
was laced with sleeping pills.
You're lying.
If you want to live,
you better start suspecting everything.
Mind your own business.
Who knows?
Someone might
set fire to your house while you sleep.
Or maybe they'll send you a bomb.
You can go now.
Gosh, don't come near me.
I said, get away from me!
Get away from me! Don't!
Is it someone's birthday?
Can you wait just a second?
I have something to show you.
I'm testing the method for my next kill.
You're going to kill someone with that?
Why? Don't you think it will work?
That was close.
The bomb worked just fine.
Don't touch my stuff!
Yes, there's nothing but trash here.
Something's been delivered.
What are you doing here?
-I ought to…
-This is fishy.
Is it a bomb?
How will you survive in this world
when you get scared so easily?
What if it's really a bomb?
I'M ALL YOURS
-Shouldn't they have killed him first?
-We got him.
You made all that fuss
just to kill one person.
What does it feel like
when you're on the job?
It feels as if I'm doing
what needs to be done.
Ms. Na, you're like my mother at times.
-You knew already.
-Of course.
Why do you think
I didn't tell Director Yong right away?
If she gets hurt,
Yong Suk will get really mad…
-There was someone who we left out?
-Is she alive?
Tell K to contact me herself if she
wants to know who it is that she missed.
-Then we'll be able to find it quickly.
-Did you think you were perfect?
The person you and I really want to kill.
Do you have to keep doing this?
My aunt is still angry.
It's too late.
Subtitle translation by: Alan Smithee