(My Boss)
(Episode 14)
(Cheng Yao. With me here, you don't need to tolerate anything.)
Boss.
Boss, I will definitely control myself and not let you down.
Really, I won't
disappoint you.
Boss, what's wrong?
Why aren't you sleeping in your own bed?
Why did you take my spot?
I took your spot?
You don't even remember, do you?
Okay, let me help you remember.
Last night, someone sneaked into my bed in the dark
and even took my blanket.
It's one thing you took my blanket,
but you also pushed me to the side.
I could only sleep on this side. That's not all.
From this side, you still pushed me.
So, I could only sleep on this edge.
The worst part is, you gave me an elbow strike and a knee strike.
And, I ended up on your bed.
Really?
Why don't I remember anything?
It must not be my fault.
It's probably your fault.
My fault?
Right.
It's my fault.
My biggest mistake was letting you in my room.
What did I say last night?
As expected, you turned against me.
Now, please leave my room.
Get out.
Hurry up.
It hurts so much.
- Mr. Tang. - Lawyer Qian. I'm in a rush this time.
I'm sorry to trouble you to make another trip.
You're too polite.
Lawyer Qian, I didn't expect you to bring
a female assistant on your business trip.
Mr. Tang.
Our firm doesn't differentiate between male and female assistants.
This is my colleague, Lawyer Cheng Yao.
She is highly professional and fully capable
of handling your company's case.
I have thought too much about your relationship.
- Hello, Lawyer Cheng. - Hello, Mr. Tang.
I am not good. I am only good when you both are here.
Mr. Tang, let's save time.
Let's go.
This time, I invited you not only to discuss the family trust matter,
but also to ask you and Lawyer Cheng
to help us plan the future ownership structure of the company.
All the documents you need are prepared and placed in the conference room.
When we get to the conference room, we will thoroughly study and discuss.
Hello, Mr. Tang.
Keep it up.
Tiffany.
I really like your hairstyle design today.
But, please change the shade of your lipstick to the one I gave you,
which is Blue Enchantress Purple, okay?
Thank you, Mr. Tang.
Look. This is our company culture.
It's just so harmonious. Come on, please.
We've arrived at the conference room. Please.
(Business Leader)
The steps are a bit high, let me help you.
No need. Thank you.
Lawyer Qian, Lawyer Cheng.
Before you start handling the situation of our company,
let me introduce our four senior executives.
Legal Director.
I hired him from France.
Marketing Director.
I hired him from the United Kingdom.
Human Resources Director.
I hired him from the United States.
Finance Director.
My wife brought her from her parents' home.
There's no other way. If women don't control the money,
they won't feel secure.
But,
she's already on my side now.
Mr. Tang. Let's begin.
Let's start. You four.
Follow my example from earlier.
Have no secrets and nothing left unsaid to the two lawyers.
All right, let's begin.
(If I knew there wouldn't be any food, )
(I should have eaten more before leaving.)
(Now, everyone is immersed in work.)
(And, I'm the only one feeling dizzy due to hunger.)
(It's so embarrassing.)
(Is he a robot?)
(He can go a whole day without eating and not feel hungry.)
Cheng Yao,
call Bao Rui.
He has some documents in my bag.
Read it to him.
What materials?
He just sent me a WeChat message, saying it's urgent.
- Go now. - Okay.
(It's strange. What case materials have Bao not backed up?)
(Why does he have to get them from the boss?)
(No need to call Bao Rui.)
(I have chocolate in my bag.)
(Eat outside.)
(Boss, did you deliberately find an excuse)
(to let me eat outside?)
(Your stomach growling is bothering me.)
(Don't worry. Just eat it. It's not cilantro-flavored.)
(Later, I'll find an excuse to invite him to eat outside.)
Mr. Tang,
I suggest gradually transitioning all natural person shares
to be held by a holding company.
In addition, from a reasonable tax avoidance perspective,
holding companies have greater room for development
in terms of equity dividends,
transfers and conversion of undistributed profits into equity capital.
(His look when he works is really attractive.)
(No wonder his previous dozens of assistants all fell for him.)
Cheng Yao.
Do you have anything to add?
I just took a closer look
at the company's personnel and financial situation.
I found that some employees' labor contract liability clauses are vague
and can easily lead to misunderstandings.
I suggest we revise them uniformly
or sign supplementary agreements.
Anything else?
For example,
this type of labor contract
is usually for temporary workers hired for a period of one to two months
with the longest being six months.
There is a high turnover rate for employees,
which can indirectly increase the management burden for the HR department
and workload for the finance department.
It is recommended to adjust this type of casual labor to
the labor dispatch model.
This can reduce the hidden costs of business operations,
improving efficiency.
Every word of yours is a gem.
It's thought-provoking, everyone.
Mr. Qian,
this is called "no weak soldiers under a strong general."
Look at these two individuals.
In just one afternoon,
they have clearly sorted out our company.
Did you see that, everyone?
This is what professionalism means.
This is what ability means.
This is what "when people of opposite genders work together,
it's not tiring at all" means.
They not only don't get tired,
but everything they say is also on point.
What are you waiting for?
Clap your hands!
Great!
Very good!
After hearing what you guys said,
my mind is now clear.
Lawyer Qian, I have something to take care of tonight.
I won't accompany you guys. Let the driver take you back first.
Tomorrow, I'll treat you both to a meal.
About the family trust matter, let's talk about it over the meal.
- See you tomorrow. - See you tomorrow.
Be careful of your head.
Thank you, Mr. Tang.
You're welcome.
See you later.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Boss, what's wrong?
Is your stomach not feeling well?
You have chocolate in your bag. Do you want to eat some?
It's nothing, just my old problem.
I really don't understand.
You're already the boss, but you're still so stressed out.
You have trouble sleeping and stomach pains.
Did you not care about your life at all before becoming the boss?
This is an issue with work attitude.
It has nothing to do with me being the boss.
Do you really not need to eat some chocolate?
(Boss, is Tang Group's financial statement with you?)
(Boss?)
Have you fainted due to hunger?
Okay, fine.
Since you treated me to chocolate,
I'll reluctantly show some concern for you.
Boss, are you in there?
- What's wrong? - I ordered some porridge for you.
Okay.
Boss. Wait a minute.
What are you looking at?
Don't even think about using last night's incident to blackmail me.
That's impossible.
I just wanted to show my concern for you. What are you thinking?
And, about last night, I didn't mean to do it on purpose.
If it's a big deal, I'm the one taken advantage of.
Fine.
If you really think I took advantage of you,
I can find a way to make it up to you.
But, let's not mention this again in the future.
Boss, please don't do this.
I didn't mean that.
Cheng Yao, don't be too much.
Boss, you're overthinking. I didn't mean that.
Then, why did you come to my room?
I'm afraid you'll just put the porridge aside and go to work.
So, I wanted to watch you finish it before leaving.
You eat. I won't eat.
Boss, eat a little bit.
This is specially for you.
You can eat it. I'm not hungry.
I have a lot of work to do.
You're not hungry because you've already been too hungry.
If you're often too hungry till you avoid meals,
this will ruin your stomach.
That's my business.
How about this?
As long as you eat,
I'll give up five days of paid leave.
How does that sound?
Plus one month of cleaning service.
It tastes terrible.
But, this is made by a five-star hotel.
Top chef.
You cook better.
Fine. Since you're my boss,
I must personally cook for you.
Wait a moment.
Done.
Boss, you can eat now.
I knew you wouldn't be able to eat.
Thank you.
Boss, did I hear wrong just now?
Don't push it too far.
I mean I'm afraid I misunderstood your instructions.
- Did you just say... - Thank you.
In your dictionary, there is actually the phrase "thank you."
I just added it.
Remember to eat it while it's hot. Be careful not to burn yourself.
I'm going to bed now.
I didn't expect the intensity of this business trip to be so high.
I also have to take care of his stomach.
Luckily, I was prepared early.
(I finished my porridge. Give up five days of paid annual leave.)
(And, the one month of cleaning service is effective immediately.)
Boss, I just said that to make you drink the porridge.
Drinking porridge is also for your own good.
Can you not count on it?
(When we verbally agreed, )
(there was no coercion, and I did not deceive you.)
(You are not a person without legal capacity)
(or a person with limited legal capacity.)
(There're no conditions that would make the contract revocable or invalid.)
- Are you crazy? - (I have followed the terms...)
If I show any pity toward you, I won't be surnamed Cheng!
Please, both of you.
Mr. Tang.
Thank you for coming.
Lawyer Cheng.
Today, you are the only lady among us.
We are like two green leaves surrounding a red flower.
Lawyer Cheng, you sit in the middle.
Sure, then I'll be the red flower.
Lawyer Cheng. You sit...
Sure. We coincidentally prefer the same seat.
Service.
My guests.
This is a wine I asked the Italian modern wine master, John, to make.
It is a newly brewed wine which combines grapes
from China, America, England, France, and Russia.
One glass of wine brought together
the five permanent members of the United Nations.
What a grand perspective.
Let's taste it carefully.
Mr. Tang, I don't drink while working.
Understood.
I respect you.
Then, we can just talk about work while drinking, right? Lawyer Qian.
For the sake of the grand perspective,
let's make an exception.
Sorry, it's my rule.
You can be a bit stubborn.
What about you, Lawyer Cheng?
Since Lawyer Qian doesn't want to drink, will you have a drink with me?
There's an old saying,
"good wine goes well with a beautiful woman."
Don't think too much.
What I mean is, after we finish this drink,
we'll be like family.
(I never expected to encounter a situation like this even at Junheng & Co.)
(Boss just had stomach pain. He definitely can't drink alcohol.)
(But, Tang Bing is a client worth billions.)
(We can't not give him a face.)
(The bigger picture is more important.)
Mr. Tang.
I won't drink.
She can't drink either.
If you don't eat, she won't eat.
If you don't sleep, she won't sleep, right?
Just a little joke.
This doesn't make sense.
Besides, Lawyer Cheng is an adult.
You can't interfere with what she wants, right?
Lawyer Cheng.
If you can't handle alcohol, how can you work properly?
Serving our clients is our most basic duty.
Mr. Tang, I am willing to...
You can't do it even if you're willing.
My assistant lawyer is not allowed to drink.
Lawyer Qian,
you're being a bit
too stubborn.
Mr. Tang.
This is my work principle.
No one can make an exception.
Okay, we won't drink.
Let's not drink.
Your aura is so strong.
I don't know who between us is the boss.
What are you waiting here for?
Aren't you embarrassed by this situation?
Let's replace the Wuchang red wine with Wuchang rice.
Let's just have a meal.
Boss.
Thank you just now.
Cheng Yao.
Don't bring your old habits and ulterior motives to Junheng & Co.
What do you mean?
Junheng's business relies on professionalism, not drinking parties.
There's no need for you to accompany clients.
- I was just trying to help you. - I don't need it.
I don't need you to act like a fake good person.
This is an insult to my reputation.
If I catch you with such intentions again, you'll be fired immediately.
Also, I warn you. Don't go meet Tang Bing alone.
You speak so rudely.
I really don't understand Qian Heng.
The client invited me for drinks. How could I refuse?
(You went drinking with the client?)
No, the client wanted to drink.
But, Qian Heng wouldn't allow it.
The situation was a bit unpleasant just now.
And also, I just got scolded by him.
(Isn't he helping you?)
I know he wants to help me.
He meant well by telling me these things.
Every time he speaks, it's so hurtful.
Doesn't he know?
Wait. What about your client?
He wouldn't really have any bad thoughts about you, right?
Be careful. Don't let him take advantage of you.
It does feel a little weird.
But, don't worry. I'm not easy to bully.
Anyway, as long as I listen to the boss
and don't meet the client alone, I'll be fine.
Why are you playing games alone?
- Where's Hao Zi? - (Don't mention him to me.)
What happened? Did you guys fight again?
He's been so busy lately.
He doesn't come home for days.
(It's driving me mad.)
Ting Ting, you two are about to become parents.
Isn't it normal for Hao Zi to feel more stressed?
Can't you understand him a little more?
(Stop defending him.)
(Am I not suffering during this pregnancy?)
I'm giving birth to his child.
He is supposed to treat me well and take care of me.
A child is not something someone gives birth for someone else.
Ting Ting, relationships and families need continuous care, don't they?
You sound like you understand it very well.
(Lawyer Cheng, can you come to the hotel conference room?)
(There are some materials that need your help to review)
(so as not to delay the efficiency of the two bosses.)
I won't chat with you for now. I have to work.
- Goodbye. - (Goodbye.)
(Mr. Tang's assistant called me to go to the hotel conference room)
(to help him organize some materials.)
(Also, I warn you not to meet Tang Bing alone.)
I'm meeting with his assistant, not Mr. Tang himself.
It should be fine.
Forget it. I'm just a subordinate.
I can't bother the boss with everything.
(Is Mr. Tang coming over?)
(Do I need to inform Lawyer Qian?)
(No need. Mr. Tang still has to meet a client.)
(He'll be a little late.)
Miss Cheng, please come this way.
Lawyer Cheng is here.
Isn't Mr. Tang in a meeting?
Just a regular client, not important.
In that case,
I'll invite Lawyer Qian to join our meeting.
Wait. No. Lawyer Cheng.
Lawyer Cheng, let me explain.
Come here.
This is what happened.
I'm just temporarily returning to China this time.
Lawyer Qian asked me to prepare a lot of materials. Take a look.
They're all on my computer.
I just had the receptionist print them out and send them over.
If I ask Zhang to organize them,
I'm afraid he'll be clumsy and not organize them clearly.
I thought you could come and help.
Lawyer Qian's time is so precious.
I don't want to disturb him with this.
It's just a small matter.
Lawyer Cheng, you should have no problem, right?
Of course.
This is what I should do. Let's get started.
Zhang, I suddenly remembered
that there are some new documents printed out at the front desk.
Can you go get them for me?
Remember. Go and come back quickly.
No problem, Mr. Tang.
Lawyer Cheng.
I have one more thing to trouble you with.
Can you help me connect this power source?
I might need that projector for some materials later.
I've been working hard for so many years,
and now I've hurt my back.
I can't bend down properly.
Can you please help me,
Lawyer Cheng?
Lawyer Cheng.
Can you please lend a hand?
Please continue working. I'll take a break.
Yes. You need to open it.
It's inside.
Lawyer Cheng,
you must be tired
working with Lawyer Qian.
Not really.
Following him can help me learn a lot.
That's good.
Mr. Tang.
Lawyer Cheng, don't be nervous.
I just wanted to say this.
I have also been trained by others.
Things change over time.
After so many years, I have finally succeeded.
But, my heart is tired and cold.
I feel like a little boy with a serious illness.
I long for and need a ray of light to warm me and heal me.
For this ray of light, I have been searching for many years.
And now,
I feel like I have found it.
You are that ray of light,
my Miss Right.
Lawyer Cheng.
Shine your light on my heart without restraint.
- Save this little boy. - Get away.
Let me tell you.
You're already harassing me.
This is illegal.
You hit me.
Exciting.
I haven't experienced
the feeling of being rejected for a long time.
Come on.
Yao Yao, what about this?
Let's play a little game to liven things up.
From now on,
every time you slap me,
I'll give you a hundred thousand.
After that, we'll settle together.
Do your best,
or else I'll use your incompetence
as a reason to reject working with Lawyer Qian.
Yao Yao.
Let's start the game.
Go away!
Wow, a new program, Little Pepper.
I'm not afraid to tell you,
your kick completely ignited me.
All these years, I have encountered countless challenges.
Every time, I burn myself out to overcome challenges
and stomp on them fiercely.
Now,
the surveillance is off
and the door is locked.
No one will disturb us.
Come on, Little Pepper.
Let's burn together.
- Wait. Lawyer Cheng. - Let's take a look at Mr. Tang Bing's true face.
- No. It's a misunderstanding. - He's openly harassing a female lawyer.
Lawyer Cheng, don't...
Give me your phone. The closer you get, the clearer the picture.
- Lawyer Cheng. - No need to block yourself. I've recorded everything.
Wait. It's a misunderstanding. Lawyer Cheng.
Lawyer Cheng.
Hooligan, I'll expose you.
- Who is it? - It's me.
I have some documents here. You need to take a look.
- What's wrong? - I'm fine, boss.
Do you need something printed? Just give it to me.
Say it.
Why are your eyes red?
If you don't tell me, don't bother coming to work after this.
Nothing.
Didn't I say that if you want to cry, you need my approval?
If you cry behind my back and don't tell me the truth,
I'll deduct all of your year-end bonus.
Has Tang Bing harassed you?
(I feel like a little boy with a serious illness.)
- Boss, don't watch. It's disgusting. - Stand there.
(I need a ray of light to warm me...)
Stand there!
(For this ray of light, I have been searching for many years.)
- Turn around. - (I feel like I have found it.)
(You are that ray of light, )
(my Miss Right.)
(Lawyer Cheng.)
(Shine your light on my heart without restraint.)
(Now, the surveillance is off)
(and the door is locked.)
(No one will disturb us.)
(Come on, Little Pepper.)
(Let's burn together.)
Boss, stop watching. I won't post it then.
I know Tang Bing is worth billions as a client.
I won't make things difficult for you. I just wanted to vent my anger.
I wasn't really prepared to post it.
Actually,
I've suffered no substantial loss.
I just wanted to vent.
Boss, whatever decision you make, I can understand you.
If you want to downplay this matter, I also support you.
This may be the most rational and best solution to solve this issue.
Do you really think so?
Okay. Then, let's go find Mr. Tang and make up for it.
Mr. Tang.
Mr. Qian. Why are you in such a hurry to see me?
Is there any new progress in the case?
Thank you for your hard work.
Lawyer Qian.
What do you mean?
The surveillance is off and the door is locked.
- Now, no one will disturb us. - Yeah.
Wait. Why does this sound so familiar?
It's good if it's familiar.
I heard that you're a little boy who got seriously ill.
Let me treat you now.
Boss.
Qian Heng, how dare you hit me?
I'll fight you.
Ouch!
Which hand did he touch you with?
Right hand.
Qian Heng, it's dislocated.
Qian Heng, what are you trying to do?
I believe that, with your character,
not only did you touch her, but also looked at her inappropriately.
I only took a quick glance.
Qian Heng, let me explain.
This is just my bad habit. I just teased Lawyer Cheng a little.
- Thanks for the reminder. - Wait, no!
I can see that you have a lot of tricks up your sleeve.
You must have put in a lot of effort.
Of course, Lawyer Cheng is not easy to tease.
I definitely have to put in some effort.
No. Lawyer Qian, listen to me.
Lawyer Qian.
You're too domineering.
Can't I have some thoughts?
You are not allowed to have any thoughts about her.
What do you mean...
Boss.
Calm down. Otherwise,
he might accuse us of intentionally hurting him.
It will be difficult to handle.
Qian Heng,
you are being unreasonable.
Where is my phone?
I'm going to call the police.
I will make sure you go to jail
and have your license revoked.
My actions have at most violated
the Public Security Administration Punishment Law
by physically assaulting or intentionally harming another person.
I may face detention of more than 5 days but less than 10 days,
and a fine of more than 200 yuan but less than 500 yuan.
For less serious injuries,
I may face detention of less than 5 days or a fine less than 500 yuan.
The beating I just gave you?
I can earn it back in three minutes,
and it won't affect my lawyer's license.
Cheng Yao.
I have never done anything that cannot be resolved in my life.
Can you please study the law properly?
Mr. Tang.
How is my medical skill?
- Do you want me to give you another treatment? - No, Doctor Qian.
Sorry. It's Lawyer Qian.
I have already fully recovered.
Lawyer Qian, I don't know that she's your girlfriend.
Otherwise, I wouldn't dare to have any crooked thoughts.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Brother.
Cheng Yao.
Go get a piece of A4 paper and a pen.
Sign it.
Sign what?
I won't do your business anymore.
Sign the termination of the agency agreement.
Okay.
Signed.
Done. Write a contract for the termination of the agency representation.
Then, archive the file.
Wait.
I have a video of you in my hands.
If you dare to make any moves against Lawyer Qian,
I will post your video online.
I'll make you a social outcast first, and then let the law punish you.
Let me educate you that your actions are crossing
the boundaries of the Criminal Law of the People's Republic of China.
Violating the law can land you in jail.
I'll keep an eye on you from now on. See if you dare to violate others.
Wait. Do what you want.
At least give me those videos.
If you want to retaliate, come at me.
No one has been able to defeat me in court.
Of course not.
Thank you, boss.
Don't you have anything to say?
Boss, you were amazing just now.
I used to think you were just good at talking.
I didn't realize you were also skilled in martial arts.
Just this?
I'm sorry, boss.
I'm causing trouble for you and the law firm again.
Cheng Yao, let me ask you. If I hadn't found out about this,
were you not planning on telling me at all?
No, boss. I don't want to make things difficult for you.
You don't want to make things difficult for me?
You get bullied, and I should turn a blind eye?
What do you take me for? A pimp?
No.
My ex-supervising lawyer always made us go out
to accompany clients for drinks.
He said it's normal to do so.
So, I thought...
Cheng Yao, no matter where you learned these rules from before,
it won't work with me.
With me, you never have to tolerate anything.
If someone harasses you again, just slap him.
His net worth, whether hundreds of millions or billions, doesn't matter.
- But what if I can't beat him? - Tell me, and I'll help you fight.
Hone your professional skills
so you never have to comply with the client's unreasonable demands.
This market is huge,
and you can always find the right client for yourself.
Remember. It's we who choose the clients,
not the other way around.
Also, don't always think about the big picture.
I know,
you don't tell me because you don't trust me.
You think that, just like your ex-supervising lawyer,
I'd choose money over my subordinates' self-esteem, right?
No, boss.
I really didn't want to bother you.
Do you know how dangerous your actions are?
He's a man.
If he takes it a step further, can you handle it?
If he snatches your phone and deletes the video, can you handle it?
If he turns around and threatens you with a scandalous video,
can you handle it?