(My Boss)
(Episode 16)
(Pretending to be my girlfriend? Are you that casual about relationships?)
I really don't know how to thank you.
If there's anything that you need my help with in the future,
I will definitely not refuse.
I heard from Wu Jun that you have insomnia.
This is something that the locals recommended to me
when I was traveling in Southeast Asia.
It's effective in treating insomnia.
I hope you can accept it.
Senior,
Cheng Yao encountered danger when she and I were
on a business trip together.
I am grateful that you didn't blame me. I really can't take this thing.
I...
This thing is worthless.
You know what happened to me before.
That's why I couldn't sleep.
But now, I'm almost fully recovered from insomnia.
It's because of its effectiveness.
And I bought a lot of it at the time.
They're all collecting dust at home.
Finally, there's a chance to give it away. Just take it.
Okay.
Senior, some dishes in this restaurant are quite popular.
Let me take a look.
Qian Heng.
I have some experience in the trust business.
If your law firm needs my help in the future,
please let me know.
Sure. If I have any questions, you'll be the first person I ask.
Qian,
you're getting naughty.
You're starting to play tricks on me.
Do you have any conscience?
I helped you turn down Tang Bing's case.
And, you actually met Cheng Xi behind my back.
Why did you do that?
What gave you the impression
that if I wanted to hide it from you,
you would easily find out?
Then, shouldn't you have taken the opportunity to bring me along
so we could have more chances to meet?
I don't do things that annoy people.
Oh, right. I almost forgot to tell you.
Senior Cheng Xi gave me a few pieces of calming incense.
You don't have this treatment, right?
Okay.
How much? Just give me a price.
A fixed price of 100,000 yuan.
Are you crazy?
Although my sleep has improved recently,
if I don't accept Senior Cheng Xi's kind gesture,
it's not appropriate, right?
Okay. Then, I'll call Tang Bing now and tell him
that we are discussing again whether to re-take his case.
Anyway, he went to the Law Association to file a complaint.
It affects the reputation of our entire law firm.
Which one is more important?
Someone needs to think about it.
Cheng Xi met me because of Cheng Yao's matter.
Don't drag Cheng Yao into this. What does she have to do with it?
Tang Bing wanted to take advantage of her and got beaten up by me.
Is it true or not?
Have I ever lied to you?
And, he still dares to complain to the Law Association?
This bastard. I'll make sure to sue him until he's bankrupt.
Don't make a fuss. Cheng Yao has finally forgotten about this incident.
Do you still want to look for him?
Then, let's not look for him for now.
Well.
Fine. I give up the firm's profit sharing next month, all right?
Wu,
the way Cheng Xi talked to me today,
I feel like it was too serious.
Maybe, when Cheng Yao explained it to her, she was too vague.
I don't know. Maybe she misunderstood.
- Did she say anything to you? - No.
Qian.
Can you teach me Sanda?
Do you think you can beat me just by learning it?
Who wants to fight you?
I have someone to protect.
Can we have a session tomorrow?
Where did you go?
You dressed well.
You went on a secret date, didn't you?
What does it have to do with you?
You let go of our relationship, just like that.
Do you think that's fair to me?
Letting go is the biggest mercy I have for you.
Don't push me. I could reveal all the things you did in the past.
Is it fun to keep bringing up the past?
I have explained it to you so many times.
No matter what I do, you are always in my heart.
Since you are always in my heart,
can I just watch you be with another man?
I need you to understand that I am single.
It's only natural for me to go on dates with anyone now.
Come back. Don't you know what's good for you?
Let me tell you.
I'm doing this for your own good.
You're in your thirties,
divorced, and have nothing.
Except for me, your ex-husband, who accepts you without any grudges,
who else can be as tolerant as me toward you?
Divorce is the end of our previous relationship.
Don't always belittle me and elevate yourself every time you see me.
What now? Will you be happy for a few days
just by saying these few words?
Cheng Xi, do you always think
that our divorce is all my fault?
Do you not have any flaws at all for our marriage to reach this point?
Let me tell you.
A divorced woman is just someone who got dumped.
You got dumped. Why are you still here acting all high and mighty,
feeling like you're different from others?
Do you see yourself as a modern woman?
Cheng Xi, you're a lawyer,
an intellectual.
Stop reading those inspirational quotes every day.
And, stop going out every day to search for a new life, to find love.
It's all just deceiving young girls.
So, according to you,
a divorced woman,
no matter how successful she is in her career,
she's worthless. Is that right?
Yes, a woman's primary task
is to return to her family and be a virtuous helper.
A divorced woman is considered damaged goods.
You are damaged goods. Shouldn't you try harder to please men?
Dressing up and going out on dates every day,
what's the point? What are you thinking?
Wu Jun has been pursuing you for a few days, and you are already tempted.
Let me tell you.
He's just attracted to the novelty of you.
Once the novelty wears off, he will dump you.
Then, you'll know I'm still the best to you.
Deng Ming.
It's not that you're good,
but that I am.
You won't find anyone else who will treat you as well as I did.
But, let me tell you,
I was willing to do anything to be with you back then.
But now, when I say I'm leaving you, I will leave you for good
because I will always be true to myself.
But, look at you.
You are incompetent in life, like a giant baby.
When I wholeheartedly treated you, you were arrogant.
Now, in your marriage, you are at a disadvantage.
And, you turn around to harass me. You're disgusting!
You're miserable, not me.
- What are you doing? - Calling the police.
Calling the police? Who are you trying to scare?
Come on. Call the police.
Call the police.
Cheng Xi, let me tell you.
One day, you will come crying to me.
I'll be waiting.
Will you leave or not?
I'll just leave. Why are you yelling at me?
Lemon Mascot.
Why are you here?
Boss.
What does this mean?
I'm giving this Lemon Mascot to you.
Giving it to me?
I don't want it anymore.
But, didn't you like it so much?
How is this possible?
This thing doesn't match the style of my villa at all.
I don't want to live with it.
Oh, right.
Aren't you supposed to live in the villa?
Why are you wearing pajamas?
Have you decided to move back completely?
What's wrong?
I'm a legal tenant who pays rent.
Do I have to report to you when I come back?
You already stood me up once. And now, you're questioning where I live.
Boss, you do you, as long as you're happy.
This is for you. No need to thank me.
Breaking news!
Zhu the admin said
that we will have a second retreat this year.
- Our boss specially arranged it. - Really?
Let's be more cautious.
The firm hasn't sent an official email yet.
And, we just lost Tang Bing's case recently.
A vacation? Can we even meet our year-end performance goal?
Yu Xiao Fei, try to relax a little, all right?
With your team lead here, it will only take a few minutes to meet it.
We must have a life outside of work.
- This time, I stand with your team lead. - That's right.
I told you.
I thought of a place.
There are mountains and water.
The air is fresh and it's quiet there.
It's much more fun than an amusement park.
There's also a flower field.
The scenery is beautiful.
When you walk in,
you'll feel like time has slowed down.
The whole scene is full of the spring vibe.
Cheng Yao.
Do you think our boss has some good news recently?
He looks and feels different.
When people have good news, they'll be in a good mood.
Last time, when I was on a business trip with him,
he said that your performance this year is particularly good.
So, he's rewarding you with a retreat.
Is it true?
Was it arranged specifically for me?
Although I know that I hold an important place in his heart,
I feel quite embarrassed that he always favors and spoils me.
After all, I don't want to be the troublesome companion of a ruler
who makes him tyrannical, issues stupid orders, and causes trouble.
I'm worried.
Are you worried or just showing off?
I see that your face is bigger than the three of us combined.
I recently found out about a face mask that has a buy-two-free-one deal.
It's just enough for you to use all at once.
Jealousy.
Blatant jealousy.
The boss wants to give me a big case.
I'm his true love. It's a big case.
Well...
This doesn't seem like a big case.
- Let me see. - What kind of case is this?
Luo Yang Yang's inheritance dispute case.
The amount involved is 2 million yuan.
The opposing lawyer is Yao Feng.
The executing lawyer is Bao Rui.
And the assistant lawyer is Cheng Yao.
(So, he still remembers.)
(He took on this case to avenge me, right?)
(He has been so good to me, )
(but I've been causing him trouble.)
(It's fine if I don't have any achievements at work.)
(But, I'm also putting my mind on other things.)
(Cheng Yao.)
(You're such a failure.)
Our boss is really abnormal.
Usually, he shouldn't have taken this case.
Who is Yao Feng?
I don't know. But there's no such name
in the list of partners in major law firms across the country.
Cheng Yao, do you know him?
How could she know him?
I don't even know him. How could a newcomer know him?
Cheng Yao, don't worry. I will protect you.
I will prepare well.
Annoying. This is such a small case.
(I must win this case.)
(I can't let the boss down.)
Our client and Yao Feng's client are siblings.
And, she has taken care of her father alone for almost 10 years.
Now, she is sick herself.
So, she really needs this inheritance.
No matter what, I have to help her win this lawsuit.
But, from my interactions with her, I feel like she has been
influenced by her family's traditional views on gender roles.
I'm afraid that if she is provoked in court,
she might change her mind last minute.
So, you must
communicate with her more, guide her in the right direction,
and strengthen her confidence
so that she won't think we're only refusing to settle
because we're after the lawyer fee.
If that happens, it'd be tricky to handle.
No problem, Bao.
But, Bao,
I didn't expect you to be so attentive and considerate toward girls.
I learned it all from our boss.
Actually, he has a very meticulous mind.
So, here's the question.
If he has a very meticulous mind, why hasn't anyone noticed it yet?
Because his meticulous mind is all directed toward me.
But, don't worry. I have already investigated that lawyer, Yao Feng.
This guy only knows how to drink and socialize.
He doesn't even know the laws well.
On the contrary, I am the one who will inherit the future of Junheng & Co.
And now, with you as my assistant, we can handle him together.
Not just handle, but handle him to death!
Stop chatting. You have work to do. Work.
I just can't figure it out.
Our boss just rejected Tang Bing's big case,
and then took on this very small one.
What's the point?
And, he said we must win this case.
Maybe he wants a diverse portfolio for the firm.
What do you mean by "diverse"?
I've taken on dozens of these cases.
I win every time. I don't feel any sense of accomplishment anymore.
But you're promoting justice, Bao.
That's true.
But our boss told me that I can't lose this case.
If I do, I won't get my year-end bonus.
Why?
I understand now.
He wants to help me relieve stress.
You see. I've recently handled many cases,
all kinds of messy ones.
I am under a lot of pressure, all right? So, our boss specifically chose
a lawyer with bad character and skill to let me bully.
Bullying is so satisfying. He even reminded me
not to care about the other party's feelings.
Just offend him to my heart's content
and let myself go wild.
I will use my legal knowledge
to humiliate him, trample him, and crush him.
I will trample on his soul.
I want him to kneel before me in court. He will learn his lesson.
He will cling to my leg and say, "Bao Rui, you're amazing.
You're a star in the legal world, while I'm just a peanut.
Can you let me off the hook?
Do you still have job openings?"
Ah, feels so good.
The case hasn't even started yet, but I already feel good.
I feel victorious.
Our boss is so considerate toward me.
To repay his favor,
we must definitely win this lawsuit.
Okay, I got it. All right. I will pay attention to this case.
Okay, no problem. Don't rush me.
Just trust me.
- No problem. - Bao. Go in first.
- I will come in later. - Okay.
It's almost a sure win, you know?
No problem.
Okay.
Mr. Yao.
- I'll hang up first. - Long time no see.
Cheng Yao, it's really you.
Although you used to be my pupil,
I won't show any mercy in court later.
Please don't show any mercy.
Although you used to be my mentor,
I will do my best in court later.
If I win against you, please don't be upset.
Wow, you're quite arrogant.
How could I not know how good you are?
Let me tell you, Cheng Yao.
You entered Junheng & Co out of pure luck.
The truth will be revealed in court.
Don't cry and go to your boss later.
Who the heck are you?
- What happened? - It's nothing. I ran into the opposing counsel.
He's an old fox
who uses pre-trial communication as a cover to intimidate young lawyers.
You don't have to worry about it. With your current level,
you can handle him one-on-one without any problem.
Our boss just loves me too much.
He wants me to be involved in every case.
Otherwise, you alone would be enough for this case.
Not to mention, I'm here.
Let's go.
(Authorized Agents)
(Authorized Agent, Claimant)
(Defendant, Authorized Agent)
Lawyer Yao.
Actually, I really admire you. Really.
I've heard about your name for a long time.
Can we have dinner together tonight? I'll treat you, really.
So we can discuss how you lost your case.
What's wrong? Don't be angry.
You have no grace at all.
Who the heck are you?
How was it? Was it satisfying?
Extremely satisfying.
This is the love our boss has for us.
This kind of satisfaction
can't be bought with any amount of money.
Why did he choose Yao Feng?
It's a bit too easy.
There's no challenge in winning this.
Let's go.
(Should I send a message to thank him?)
(No need to thank me.)
(Just treat me to the seafood dinner as you promised.)
(I'm on my way to buy groceries.)
(Okay. That's good.)
(Besides seafood dinner, )
(I'll work even harder to repay you, boss.)
(Forget about the seafood dinner. Just come home! Now!)
Mom.
Why are you here?
Your dad and I came to visit
and bring you some food.
I didn't expect you to live with this person.
Luckily, your dad went fishing.
If he saw this, I don't know what would happen.
Madam, I've already told you.
I am Cheng Yao's boss.
Just admit that you're her boyfriend.
Don't you have the courage to admit it?
Cheng Yao. Look at your taste in men.
Explain it yourself.
Mom, he really is my boss.
When I first came to this unit,
it was double-rented by the landlord.
So, we agreed eventually that we'd share the unit.
But, when I got to work, I found out he's actually my boss.
This is like the plot of an idol drama.
Do you think your mom doesn't watch TV dramas?
This person will make up any excuse to take advantage of you.
Madam, what does taking advantage mean?
Men and women are equal.
Even if it's cohabitation before marriage,
everyone has the right and chance to cut their losses in time.
You wouldn't have really taken advantage of Yao Yao, would you?
Mom. He really is my boss.
And, even if someone were to take advantage,
with his status, it would be me taking advantage of him.
Don't lie to me.
You often complain on the phone that your boss
always exploits his subordinates,
has no morals and conscience,
and accepts any client just to make money.
Besides,
what is the rent for this unit in this neighborhood?
Can't I tell?
Your boss is so rich.
Why would he live in a place like this with you?
Yes, Mom. He is my boyfriend.
I knew it.
Cheng Yao. Don't be fooled by his handsome appearance.
He can be very cunning.
Don't be naive and let him deceive you.
Mom.
We really live here to save money.
Really. Also, we've been sleeping in separate rooms.
If you don't believe me, go check it out.
We follow the principle of "love comes from understanding and respect".
There's nothing like what you're imagining.
I actually want to check it out.
Boss.
I'm sorry, boss.
Can you please pretend for me? Just for a little bit.
Otherwise, my mom won't leave today.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Qian.
What do you do for work?
- Madam, I... - He worked in a factory.
He recently got laid off and has just become unemployed.
Unemployed?
What is your education level?
What did you study?
Is it easy to find a job?
He has a vocational degree.
He graduated from a vocational school.
He was just a factory worker.
Yes. Just a laborer.
No. You don't seem like it based on your demeanor.
Did you drop out of school because you were poor when young?
Young people should strive for progress.
You don't even have a bachelor's degree.
It's not easy for you to make a living.
His family background is still decent.
It's not a problem for him to go to school.
Mom,
don't be fooled by his smart appearance.
In fact, he's not very bright.
He only has a good-looking face.
What now that he is unemployed?
I'll support him. I work full-time in the morning and part-time at night.
How can that be?
Now, women aren't just homemakers, and men aren't just breadwinners.
If he can't make money,
it's also good to stay at home and be content. Right?
- Uh... - Mom, don't worry.
You finally came out to have some fun.
But, you're monitoring me here. What a waste.
Also, next time, make sure to call me if you want to visit me,
so I can come pick you up.
Don't think I don't know what you're up to.
You're afraid that your dad and I will disturb you, right?
Qian, let me tell you.
Her dad and I don't live too far from you.
It only takes half an hour by high-speed rail.
You can't bully Yao Yao.
If you bully her, you'll regret it.
He definitely won't.
Mom. You see, this place can't fit you.
Let me take you downstairs first. It's late.
- Dad must be waiting for you. - I won't stay at your place.
I'm staying at my relative's place. Don't pull me.
I still have something to say to him.
- Let's go. - No, I'm telling you...
You're such a bad kid.
I haven't finished talking yet. And, you're already pushing me out.
- Why are you... - It's pretty late.
It's pretty late?
Yao Yao.
I didn't say you can't date.
With your qualifications,
dating a laborer
is not appropriate.
Well, I don't dislike him just because he is poor.
You two will have to live together for a lifetime. It's not a good match.
You two will think differently in the future. It'll be miserable.
- Do you know? - I know.
I will seriously consider it. Go find your husband.
- Remember what I said. - I will remember.
You better remember it. You, bad kid.
(Yeah. It's really a mismatch.)
Boss, I'm sorry.
Boyfriend?
My mother didn't believe me when I said you are my boss.
I just wanted my mom to leave quickly. That's why I said that.
Okay, then tell me.
How will you support me?
I said what I said because I really had no choice just now.
If I said your net worth is over a billion,
my mom would definitely rush me to marry you.
That's why
I said you're a factory worker.
This way, it will be easier to tell her that we broke up in the future.
It's all part of the act.
Boss, I know I was wrong. Please don't stoop to my level. Okay?
Boss, if next time, your mom pressures you to get married,
I'll pretend to be your girlfriend. Is that okay?
Pretending to be my girlfriend?
Cheng Yao. You treat relationships so casually.
Your year-end bonus is gone.
Boss.
Your behavior doesn't quite comply with the Labor Contract Law.
As a lawyer, you shouldn't break the law.
Boss, can I take you out to dinner to make it up to you? Is that okay?
I'm really sorry.
Also, thank you for helping me
with the Yao Feng incident.
(Boss)
(Boss. To apologize sincerely for my offense yesterday, )
(I would like to invite you to have Western food after work tonight.)
(I have already made a reservation.)
(I hope you can receive and reply to this message soon.)
You don't seem to be in a good state early in the morning.
Did you not rest well last night?
Maybe I've been too tired lately, so I caught a cold.
Thank you, Tan Ying.
Take care, since you're working with Lawyer Qian, a workaholic.
All right, I'm going out on assignment. All the best.
You too. All the best.
Why haven't you replied to my message?
You wouldn't actually deduct my year-end bonus, would you?
Ting Ting.
(I'm so angry! I can't take it anymore!)
(I don't want to spend another day with him! I want to divorce him.)
What? Where are you?
(I'm at the place where we often have desserts.)
Wait for me. I'll be there soon.
Let's leave it at that for today.
Lawyer Qian. Let's have a casual dinner tonight.
Sorry. I have another appointment tonight.
I will do my best with the case. You can trust me.
I absolutely trust you.
Take care.
What's wrong, Ting Ting?
I can't take it anymore.
I can't spend another day with him. I want to divorce him.
Okay. Calm down.
Tell me slowly.
What happened?
So, as you know,
when we got married, we didn't have a wedding banquet.
I thought at that time,
when we move into our new home,
we'll invite everyone over for a meal.
Right? I told him about it a long time ago,
and he agreed at the time.
But, when I asked him yesterday, he just told me he's not doing it anymore.
Why not?
You can just have a small gathering with your close friends and family.
Exactly. I asked him too.
He didn't say anything
and even found me annoying.
And I rarely saw him in the past half month.
So, we ended up arguing.
He said I don't earn a single penny
and spend all his money.
He called me useless
and said he doesn't want our kid anymore.
I feel like I can't go on like this even for one more day.
Ting Ting, you're pregnant now.
Being angry is not good for your health.
What if Hao Zi was just saying it out of anger?
Right?
All right. Don't worry for now.
If he really bullies you, I won't let him get away with it.
Sir, would you like me to heat this up for you?
No. Thank you.
Okay. Enjoy your meal.
Where did you go?
You're back, boss.
I went to my friend's house.
She needed to talk to me about something.
What's wrong?
Boss.
Have you gone to have the meal?
I forgot about having a meal with you. I...
You didn't reply to my message. I thought you rejected me.
I'm sorry. Did you go?
No.
That's good. Otherwise, I would have made a mistake again.
Boss. Are you hungry now?
Can I treat you to supper?
No need. I have already eaten with the client. I'm very full.
Let's walk to a place to have some supper then.
Maybe you'll get hungry on the way.
I owe you a meal. I don't feel at ease.
Let me treat you to supper.
Otherwise, I won't be able to sleep well tonight.
Are you feeling unwell?
I have a slight headache.
We don't need to have supper. Let's go for a massage.
Massage?
Although this goes against my usual habits,
if you're not feeling well, it will affect your work,
and in turn, affect my work efficiency. Let's go.
Right here.
Press harder.
Don't make noise.
I have to call out for the masseuse to know where to press.
Madam, right here. You can press harder.
Sir.
Your shoulders and neck are so stiff.
Have you been having trouble sleeping lately?
I'm fine.
Boss. You have to let it out.
If you let it out, you can release the stress.
Don't be so reserved.
Madam, you can push harder.
- Okay. - I'm talking about him.
Okay.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Just keep track of the fees.
Boss. Didn't we agree that I would treat you?
This spa is really nice.
Let me tell you. In our hometown, there's nothing of this level.
Today, I'm going to take you to enjoy it to the fullest.
Okay.
- Cheng Yao. - Yao Yao.
How did you guys end up here?
Yao Yao. Who is this person?
Sir, I am...
He is Yao Yao's housemate.
Hello.
He looks quite decent.
Why did you bring him to such a high-end place?
Did you pay for him?
You can't spoil him like this.
No one should pay for this.
He's so young and already doing massages.
Qian.
Do you have any health problems?
- Sir, I... - Dad, Mom.
We are not here to spend, nor are we here to date.
We're here to work.
- Work? - Work. Yes.
Mom, didn't you complain about him not having a job?
So, I asked my boss and got him a job as a masseur here.
Since it was his first day at work, I accompanied him here.
You want some massages, right?
The front desk is over there. Let's go, Dad.
Let's go, Mom. Come on. It's right over there.
Massages are relaxing. Do you want a leg massage or a back massage?
Or a neck massage? They have it all here.
- Come on. - How did he end up working here?
I'm treating you today. What kind of massage do you want?
Madam, I specially arranged it for you. Is it okay?
It's all right.
Wait. Isn't this my son?
How did he end up here?
Usually, when I invited him to have a massage with me here,
he never wanted it.
How did he end up here today?
Is this your son?
I was wondering who this man with such a grand demeanor was.
And, the lady who came with him earlier,
is that your daughter-in-law? She's very pretty.
You're really lucky.
Daughter-in-law?
You saw her with your own eyes?
They just finished paying here.
If I knew he was your son, I'd definitely give him a discount.
Okay. Thank you.
Next time, it's on me.
Working here?
(Boss, I'm sorry.)
(I'm taking my parents to a relative's house.)
(Next time, I'll really treat you to a meal.)
(It'll be a feast.)
Whatever.
Hey. Honey.
I have something very important to tell you.
I just went to the spa
and you know who I bumped into?
I bumped into our son.
And, he was with a girl there.
(Really? That's great.)
As long as you're happy, all right?
Honey, what kind of girl do you think
can handle our cold and aloof son?
Could it be that she's just an ordinary and average girl?
I really want to know.
It's simple.
It's late today.
(You should mark the place first.)
Tomorrow morning, I'll have the driver take you there.
Okay. I'm currently following him.
I'm hanging up now.
Goodbye.
Stop the car.
Why is it so dark here?
I can't see anything clearly.
Oh my, no wonder.
Honey, are you there?
Let me tell you.
Our son is truly too kind-hearted.
He's actually willing
to stay in such a place with her just to be with her.
He's really adaptable.
Turn around.
But, why can't I see the girl's face?
They're leaving. Okay, wait a moment.
Boss, I really can't eat anymore.
I need to lose weight recently. I've gained weight.
Lose weight?
How about jogging with me tonight?
I still have to study the case files.
And, what if we run into my mom again?
I can't afford to owe you any more favors.
I didn't say you have to pay me back.
Why don't you decide what to eat tonight first?
Enough. I've had enough.
Oh my god.
She can make our ice-cold son
go grocery shopping with her.
(This little girl is quite capable.)
Honey.
You've worked hard.
Why don't you come back and I'll go check. Is that okay?
No.
I'm so bored at home.
I finally got to see my son up close like this.
Besides,
I found it fun to follow him.
I have to keep doing it.
(I have to persevere till the end.)
Fine. Honey, don't tire yourself out too much.
(The secret scandal between an arrogant CEO and his little assistant.)
(This title is too common.)
(And, the boss is really just showing concern for his assistant.)
(The arrogant CEO is only pretending to be tough)
(because he hasn't won over his assistant yet.)
(His assistant is currently in the kitchen making a special lunch.)
(So what?)
(It only shows that his assistant is still under the tyrant's control.)
(If they're really in love, )
(they should be cooking together in the kitchen.)
Cheng Yao.
- Boss. - I've had enough!
Let me wipe it for you. Boss, I'm sorry.
It's not coming off.
Then, take it off. I'll wash it for you.
I'm sorry, I had headphones on
and didn't notice you behind me.
I caught you.