(My Boss)
(Episode 30)
(Yao Yao, happy 100th-day anniversary.)
Senior.
You're here.
- Sorry for letting you wait.   - Sit.
Why isn't Lawyer Qian here?
Sit down and let's talk about it.
Sure.
Well, Qian ordered me to treat you to dinner.
Oh, I bought you a bouquet.
I don't know if you like it or not.
I do, it's very pretty. Thank you.
How was it?
Did Qian trouble you?
No.
I was the one who didn't know his preferences and gave him the wrong gift.
I became a laughing stock.
Not at all. No one will laugh at you.
He is just
a dull guy who doesn't know anything.
Let me tell you, Yi Ran.
If you find a boyfriend in the future,
you mustn't find someone like him.
Got it.
Lawyer Qian reminded me
that Junheng & Co has a high requirement for its partner.
I need to put in all my effort in my work.
I don't have time to date anyone.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
Let me use water instead of wine
and hope we can work well together.
In the future, we will be Junheng & Co's iron triangle.
- To a successful partnership.   - Do your best.
(Qian Heng.)
(I have finally come to be by your side.)
(Why do you still not notice me?)
Come in.
Lawyer Qian,
I just got a few cases but I don't know Junheng & Co's style.
Do you have time? Let's discuss it together.
I still need to go out and work later.
Find Wu Jun if you need anything.
All right. I won't disturb you, then.
Remember to rest.
You were so busy that you missed my welcome meal last night.
I was busy indeed.
Hello. Can I do color photocopies here?
Yes. Let me help you.
Thank you.
Is it tough for you to work with Qian Heng?
Not bad. It is good training for me.
It's fine. I've known him for many years.
He has been the same since university.
He is a very cold person and has a sharp tongue. Right?
However, he's not a bad person.
He is capable
but he has a stubborn personality.
He doesn't know how to accommodate others.
He is too firm.
So, it's normal for young girls like you
to not get used to his personality.
If he says anything blunt,
please forgive him and don't take it to heart.
Don't worry, Lawyer Liang. We are all professionals.
There's no such problem.
Qian Heng has trained you well. I was worrying about nothing.
Do you know him well?
For example, the restaurant he likes
or the gym he frequents.
Why do you ask this question suddenly?
Think of it as me wanting to assimilate into Junheng & Co.
Why don't I treat the colleagues to dinner tonight
to know everyone better?
Lawyer Qian is simple.
He has high requirements for his work
and always forgets to eat when he's busy.
(Cheng Yao, you better watch your boyfriend closely.)
(Every time he came to our side, he would stop and stare for so long.)
(I got PTSD from that.)
(I am sad. I thought he was checking to see if I was doing a good job.)
(You are excellent and capable.)
(I'm sure you can get along with him just fine.)
It's done.
I still have work to do tonight so I can't join you.
Let me treat you next time.
Sure.
Let's talk again.
(Liang Yi Ran)
(Sneak shots of the boss' happy moments)
Trying to compete with me when you are just a rookie lawyer?
Are you watching "Nothing But You"?
Lawyer Liang?
It's all right. Just watch.
I know the male lead of this drama.
I have some autographed pictures of him at home.
If you like him, I can give it to you next time.
Thank you, Lawyer Liang.
You are Wang Lu, right?
Lawyer Liang, you are like a God.
You can already remember all our names so soon.
I'm not as great as you described.
I do mix up your names sometimes.
For example, I saw
the young and pretty assistant lawyer in Qian Heng's group.
She is...
Lawyer Liang, are you talking about Cheng Yao?
She is quite pretty indeed.
Otherwise, she wouldn't be so lucky.
Yes. I remember now. Her name is Cheng Yao.
Qian Heng always tells me
to take care of his cute little girlfriend.
What? Cheng Yao and Lawyer Qian are in a relationship?
Don't you know that?
Sorry. I didn't know they hadn't made it public yet.
I didn't consider this enough.
Help me keep a secret and don't tell anyone.
Don't you think the atmosphere's weird today?
Someone called me the lady boss at the reception.
That's weird.
Reasonably speaking, both of you are quite reserved.
No one should find out.
Even so, you are his girlfriend.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Wang Lu, do you think the rumor is true about Cheng Yao?
Think about it. How long has it been since she joined?
However, she can take charge of such a big trust case.
Why do you think it is?
But I heard that her sister is also a capable lawyer.
Perhaps she is also capable.
Capable?
I heard her sister, Cheng Xi,
is also in a relationship with Lawyer Wu.
In my opinion,
both of them must be doing the same thing.
Besides, her status is different
from normal employees like us.
She is different now.
It's no use for people to work hard.
You still need to look pretty.
Cheng Yao, do you need an assistant?
Leave pouring water to me.
Water? Cheng Yao likes to drink coffee.
No need. I can do it myself.
- Are you all right?   - Sorry.
Sorry, Cheng Yao.
You can't even do a good job flattering the lady boss.
Everyone in Junheng & Co is lining up to flatter her.
Interns like you two won't get a chance.
Are you done?
Lawyer Liang.
Wang Lu, you should apologize to Cheng Yao.
Although I just joined Junheng & Co,
I know what I should do as a partner.
I think the atmosphere at Junheng & Co should be harmonious.
I also believe Cheng Yao and Lawyer Qian's relationship
won't affect her work and capability.
The team's purpose is to face our enemies and not fight among ourselves.
From now on, I don't want to hear anything that harms Lawyer Cheng.
Cheng Yao.
Come to the office with me.
Sorry, Lawyer Liang.
My personal matter has affected everyone's work.
Relax. Have some water.
I'm not like Qian Heng
who is a leader that only wants my staff to work.
Sorry.
Do you mind me describing your boyfriend like that?
We wanted to make it public when our relationship had stabilized.
I never expected the situation just now.
My mind was blank.
Thankfully, you were around.
How did you two get together?
Don't you have many work
as a rookie lawyer?
It's a long story.
I never expected to be in a relationship with Qian Heng.
Perhaps it's a situation of
the more you hate a person, the more the person will get closer to you.
It's probably the Murphy's Law.
But Lawyer Liang,
you are so much better than what others say.
You are capable, forgiving, and understanding.
I hope to learn from you if I have a chance in the future.
What a coincidence. I just came to Junheng & Co.
I'm lacking a capable assistant.
If you sincerely want to learn from me,
why don't you come to my team?
Then, you and Qian Heng can avoid suspicions better.
After all, this matter
has caused a stir in the company.
I will consider it.
I'm leaving first.
Ridiculous.
Why are you at my home?
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
My phone ran out of battery.
Let me get you a charger.
There's no need.
It gives me a moment of peace.
You don't know. There were so many bees
buzzing around my ears today.
Bees?
Who noticed this pretty flower in our family?
My relationship with Qian Heng has been found out by my colleagues.
How did they find out?
- I don't know.   - What did they say?
They called me the lady boss and some other things.
That was what they used to call me.
As long as they start calling you the lady boss,
your capability will be stripped.
Promise me.
Don't give up on your work.
I'm sure it's difficult for you right now
but you must hold on. Understand?
Don't worry, Cheng Xi. I won't give up.
I think
that I might need to sacrifice something.
I'm wondering if I should go to another team
and not stay at Lawyer Qian's anymore.
However, doing this means
I need to give up on the trust case that I spent a lot of time preparing.
Do you think this is a good decision?
Is there
a new female lawyer at Junheng & Co?
Her name is Liang Yi Ran.
I heard she is your junior.
I know her.
She has become a partner at such a young age
so she is capable.
Her style is also bold.
Forget about that. Let's talk about the trust case.
I took a long time to prepare it.
I feel reluctant to give it away to other people.
Even if you lose the case, you still have your capability.
We can just find other cases.
Can you lend me your computer?
I want to study Lawyer Liang's working style.
Of course.
My younger sister can make a killing anywhere she goes.
Let me make some food for you.
Where is Wei Zhen Tian?
Bao Rui, you've worked hard today.
- It's all right.   - Rest early and don't go out having fun.
Boss.
There's one thing that I'm not sure if I should tell you or not.
If it's something normal that you hesitate about, don't tell me.
Not even when it's about Cheng Yao?
What happened to her?
I don't know. The group sent a text.
They said there were rumors in the company about you dating Cheng Yao.
- Who spread it?   - I don't know.
I, Tan Ying, and Yu Fei.
The three of us will never do this.
Who dares to spread it even if you allow us?
If you let me spread it... If I...
Anyway, I know about it now.
I can't reach Cheng Yao as well.
(Sorry, the number you are calling is engaged.)
You can't call her, right?
Actually, I can manage things here alone.
Why don't I book an early flight for you?
However, you'll only reach the firm earliest by tomorrow afternoon.
Bao Rui, help me reserve a car.
All right.
Who spread this rumor?
Cheng Yao, are you all right?
Some people can't see you achieving success.
If you have something on your mind, don't keep it inside and tell us.
- Come here.   - Why are you back?
Come with me.
Yu Fei.
Everyone,
since everyone already found out about it,
I don't have to hide it anymore.
Cheng Yao and I are lovers.
We didn't announce it because we haven't been together for a long time.
However, I'll tell everyone now
that Cheng Yao is my girlfriend.
Oh, one more thing I want to tell everyone.
She didn't pursue me.
I was the one who pursued her.
There has been no favoritism between us.
She also hadn't done anything that oversteps her boundaries.
I like her first.
I spent a long time to obtain this luck.
If anyone suspects me of biasing her,
you can come and verify with me anytime.
But from today onwards,
I don't want to see Cheng Yao
bear any pressure from the rumors.
Everyone, don't worry.
Since joining Junheng & Co, I've been putting work
above my personal life.
I never thought about using this relationship
to gain any benefit for myself.
I understand that all of you will have that idea.
To avoid any suspicions, I will hand over my trust case to Bao.
If you can come out with a tutorial about dating the boss,
it'll be better.
Lawyer Qian, does it mean
I can cancel that weird office romance talk?
Of course. You can cancel it.
However, it won't affect your work.
- Thank you, boss.   - Don't worry!
- Thank you, boss!   - Long live the boss!
Oh, since we've announced our relationship,
I want to transfer to Lawyer Liang's team.
I will do my best to hand over my work.
All right.
From today onwards, Lawyer Qian's charm
has achieved new heights in my opinion.
If he doesn't have a sharp tongue usually
and I just joined the company,
who would be able to stop us?
I have to thank his sharp tongue.
(Great. How moving.)
Why are you crying? Look at Bao Rui.
Why are you crying?
Isn't this a good thing?
(It was so suffering for me.)
(I don't have to keep this a secret anymore!)
You didn't see anything, right? Greet everyone, come.
Lawyer Qian.
Thank you for helping Cheng Yao yesterday.
How rare is this?
It's your first time thanking me.
It seems like you quite like Cheng Yao.
I see. This is your type.
Well, Cheng Yao is young and pretty.
She is not just young and pretty.
She is excellent in every aspect.
I've never shown her any favoritism at work.
She has her current achievement
because she worked hard for it.
Junheng & Co is a large firm. Can no one be compared to her?
In my heart,
there is no one.
Lawyer Liang,
- I came to you because...   - I understand.
I already received Cheng Yao's letter.
I thought you wouldn't agree to it at first.
(Work Transfer Request)
I will support every decision she makes.
Don't worry. I will take good care of her.
I am also a female lawyer. I'll bring her along when I work outside.
Then, you'll be at ease, right?
Thank you so much.
Cheng Yao.
I was the one who led you in your first case, right?
I feel reluctant to see you leave so suddenly.
No matter where you go, remember that you are a part of Glory and Wealth.
Do well. Don't embarrass Glory and Wealth.
Yes. Cheng Yao has been on our team since he joined the company.
Now that she is leaving, I feel a little reluctant.
The firm is so big.
Where are you moving to? Can we still meet in the future?
Where are you moving to?
Stop measuring.
She will be moving 3.5 meters further at least.
I wondered where she would be moving to.
Just 3.5 meters.
I feel that things are not what they seem like.
Do you think this is all an act by Liang Yi Ran?
I don't think so.
If that's the case, she is overestimating me.
It's all right. I can go and study there.
I'm here to report in, Lawyer Liang.
Welcome.
They are two assistant lawyers I brought in from my previous team.
They are slightly older than you.
Don't feel pressured.
This is Cheng Yao. She is a new member of our team.
Both of you must take good care of her.
This is an order Lawyer Qian gave me in person.
- Welcome.   - Hello, Lawyer Cheng.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Wang, it's done.   - Thank you.
This is already done.
All right.
Lawyer Zhang,
do you need any help?
You can just call me Zhang.
I'll be done with my work soon.
Just take a break.
There's no need to be polite with me.
I was tortured in Lawyer Qian's team every day
so I have high endurance.
Let me do these contracts for you.
No need, Lawyer Cheng. I can do it myself.
Miss Cheng,
you are our lady boss.
Just leave these trivial matters to us.
It's really fine.
I used to arrange hundreds of pages of evidence in the past.
You arranged evidence yourself?
I am also a lawyer.
I hope all of you still treat me like a normal lawyer.
Miss Cheng,
these are the legal opinions I just arranged.
If you have time, can you give me some suggestions?
The way you think is similar to Lawyer Qian.
What Lawyer Qian thinks is the standard answer.
Wang, you wrote it well.
I should be learning from you instead.
Gosh, I'm so happy
to receive your motivation and praise.
Thank you.
Come in.
Lawyer Liang,
my colleagues are shy about asking me for help
but I have adaptability.
So just let me know if you need any help.
I do have many things that need help.
However, I'm afraid of wasting your potential.
No way.
Work is all the same to me.
My assistant lawyers are busy.
They have no time to gather evidence for me.
Leave it to me.
Thank you so much.
I thought you wouldn't want to scan documents.
Gathering evidence and scanning.
Can you finish them in three days?
I'll submit it tonight.
Sure.
Both of you, let's have a meeting in the meeting room.
All right.
- Come in.   - Boss.
Stop looking.
Cheng Yao is going to the State Administration for Market Regulation.
I wasn't looking.
Tan Ying asked me to tell you that you shouldn't worry about Cheng Yao.
Even if Lawyer Liang is exploiting her,
she wouldn't be as bad as you previously.
She has gotten used to it.
If there's nothing else, I'll be leaving.
Wait.
Isn't it an intern's job to get files at
the State Administration for Market Regulation?
- Why did she go?   - She said it was some key evidence.
Maybe Lawyer Liang is afraid that an intern might make a mistake
so she asked Cheng Yao instead.
(Cheng Yao, there's a document at Nancheng.)
(Can you go and pick it up?)
(On your way back, go to the color printing shop)
(and pick up the documents the company ordered to be distributed.)
(Help buy some coffee for the team as well.)
(Is it too troublesome?)
(No problem.)
What's that smell?
Are you back?
The steak I was cooking got burnt.
I couldn't move it at all.
This is an expensive steak
but the quality is bad.
I won't buy it again.
You need to defrost a steak before you cook it.
What do you mean?
What? It means it has to be defrosted.
All right. Put it there and let me do it.
I asked a restaurant to deliver our food.
I heard that someone ran around the whole day.
So, you need more rest.
Come. Sit down. Let me massage your feet for you.
I do feel a little tired.
- Be careful.   - However,
it was much better than when I just joined someone's team.
Have you forgotten about me running around in the rain?
I sincerely apologize to you
for my behavior in the past.
I'm willing to accept any punishment.
What I mean is that
I could even complete your tasks
so I can also complete Lawyer Liang's tasks.
I can't let others think
I'm useless after I'm in a relationship with you.
Besides, aren't you going out to work tomorrow night?
So, I want to do more work today
and have dinner with you tomorrow night.
My girlfriend is too hardworking,
but you've worked too hard.
I still need to work outstation often for a few different cases.
Why don't I transfer you back from Liang Yi Ran's team
- so we can go together?   - That won't do.
I just joined Lawyer Liang's team today.
I can't break my promise.
All right. Tell me whenever you are facing problems.
Don't worry.
(100 days together with Qian Heng tomorrow)
100 days together with Qian Heng tomorrow.
- What is that?   - What do you mean?
It's just a reminder alarm.
It's reminding us that we've been together for 100 days.
How do you think I've performed?
You did well.
- 99 points.   - So high?
Can you tell me why I'm missing a point?
The perfect score is 2,000.
2,000?
How can I get 2,000 points?
I want to drink orange juice right now.
I'll get it immediately.
Done.
Here you go.
How is it?
You already know how to use the blender now.
Are you complaining about me now?
Sorry.
My work was scheduled previously.
However, I didn't forget about our 100th-day anniversary.
We'll celebrate together while having dinner tomorrow.
All right?
How is this nice? It's not clean at all.
Why don't I blend it some more?
(Do they look nice?)
(Yes.)
(They are simple and have great design sense.)
(They suit Lawyer Qian's temperament.)
Are you choosing a gift for Lawyer Qian?
Good morning, Lawyer Liang.
It's fine. It's not working hours yet.
Just be casual.
Are you going to buy the necklace for Lawyer Qian?
Today is our 100th day together
so I want to choose a gift.
It's an important day indeed.
But don't you think the price of that necklace is not suitable
for an elite like Lawyer Qian?
I'm sure the intention is more important than the price when giving a gift.
Did Qian Heng tell you that?
Are you a fool?
He wouldn't say something honest to hurt you
because you are his girlfriend.
When you are a student,
giving a small gift in this price range can show your sincerity
but after joining the society, it'll be too childish
if you still give such gifts.
That is why men all love young women regardless of their age
because young women are naive and won't think too much.
Their thoughts can easily be grasped.
However, a person will soon get bored of things
that are too transparent.
That is why young people need to grow.
I'm not giving Qian Heng gifts to please him.
I just want to make it a little ceremonious for this moment in our lives.
Cheng Yao, come with me.
Do you like this handbag?
After you use a real branded bag,
you will realize
why the top brands are expensive.
Whether you are working outside or socializing,
you will feel its convenience.
Just like the outfit you are wearing now.
If I were a client, I wouldn't choose you.
It's all right.
You can use this occasion to ask Qian Heng to buy you one.
I don't think it's necessary.
You don't know. It is a marketing tactic.
If you package yourself,
those who want to buy it will still do so even if you are highly-priced.
From what I know about Qian Heng,
I'm sure he wants Junheng & Co's image to be classier.
It's fine. It hasn't been long since you joined this industry.
It's normal if you can't feel these things.
It hasn't been long since I joined this industry indeed
but Qian Heng has been telling us
that Junheng & Co prioritizes one's capability
and not meaningless packaging.
You can ask him if you don't agree with it.
I won't disagree with it.
I was just testing you.
It is very important for a young lawyer
to resist temptation and his or her impulsive nature.
After a few days of observation,
I already have a basic recognition of your ability.
I have an international trust contract here.
Help me circle the parts that need to be amended. Can you do it?
This will help you get familiar with the international trust field quickly.
Everything is in English.
To wear the crown, one must first bear its responsibility.
I'm prioritizing you and giving you this opportunity to learn.
No problem, I will work hard.
(Qian Heng, Depart from Jiangcheng Airport)
My dear, Cheng Yao.
There's a delivery at the reception. I brought it here for you.
Did you order all these?
Can you eat so much?
You know your stuff. This dessert has gone viral recently.
It's difficult to buy it.
This restaurant too. It's very delicious.
Let me take a look at this.
Can you eat this alone? Not even four people can finish this.
Fruits with imperial plating.
You are living a good life.
Enough. Move aside.
Even if you are busy until you have no time to reply to my texts,
I still can't let you starve.
Do you need to attract people's attention?
You are the girlfriend of Junheng & Co's boss.
You can no longer keep a low profile.
I feel a little too.
I feel lonely and cold.
Go back to work.
We will celebrate when we get home.
Sure.
Lawyer Qian is so romantic.
Yu Fei, learn from him.
I won't order delivery for you.
I will only cook for you.
Come on.
One is a refrigerator and the other is a freezer.
All right. Give it to me.
Go to work.
Do you hear that? She's talking about all of you.
Don't you have work to do?
Boss,
I don't want to disturb you two
but tonight's flight has been booked.
Should we discuss work first?
It feels cold suddenly.
Who turned on the air con?
All right, I'm coming immediately.
I need to report on my work.
Go.
Lawyer Liang.
The contract you gave me in the morning has 128 pages.
Since it's all in English,
I need to translate and label them.
Do you think I can show you the first half?
Next morning, the remaining half will be...
The contract has a Chinese version.
It doesn't need to be translated.
You didn't tell me.
Why didn't you ask me?
Professional international contracts have Chinese versions.
Don't you know that?
It's all right. I won't blame you for being inexperienced.
I will send you the digital version now.
Verify it with the digital version.
After that, send the digital version and the printed contract to me.
When you're done, hurry and get some clients.
There's an event by the Family Law Association this afternoon.
A law firm like Junheng & Co
doesn't need to get clients, right?
I'm worried that they won't be good enough for Junheng & Co.
The firm's standard is one thing
but it is another thing to train you with this.
Finding clients is an important skill for a lawyer.
It is a good cycle.
It'll be a pity if you miss it.
All right. I'll depart immediately after I'm done with the contract.
All right.
(I have no choice but to give the present later.)
(If I run faster,)
(I might be able to arrive home for dinner.)
First, let's talk about this.
After the Civil Code is amended,
everyone knows that the original Marriage Law becomes invalid.
Today, we will also talk about
the marriage and family section of the Civil Code.
I believe this question is on most of our audience members' minds.
First of all, let's talk about the issue of the divorce cooling-off period.
I heard some noise and guessed you were still here.
You still have a flight to catch later so don't tire yourself out.
Have a safe trip.
All right. I'll see you later. I'll go and greet other people.
Our law firm is called Junheng & Co.
Our firm has many ace lawyers
like Qian Heng, Wu Jun, and Liang Yi Ran.
Our firm is in charge of domestic proceedings.
If you want a divorce, inherit assets, or various...
Cheng Yao?
Lawyer Li.
Is Junheng & Co having trouble recently?
Why do they let a girl find clients alone?
Gender has nothing to do with finding clients.
Sorry.
Cheng Yao, if you are free, we can have a meal together.
You can also visit Jincheng & Co.
I don't think today works.
Let's do it next time. Sorry.
Qian Heng!
Happy 100th-day anniversary.