(My Boss)
(Episode 13: Boss, this is the first time I feel that)
(being your assistant lawyer is truly worthwhile.)
- Don't bother.  - Don't move.
Does it hurt?
You are my employee.
If you get injured during work,
as the boss, I have to compensate
to avoid potential losses in the future.
So, once I joined Junheng & Co,
my bodily tissues are no longer under my control, right?
In theory, yes.
Cheng Yao.
This time, with the complete loss
of the biological father's bodily tissues, we still won the lawsuit.
We can definitely make it to the list of Annual Classic Family Cases.
To celebrate, let's have a barbecue this weekend.
I'll treat you. How about that?
I won't go. You guys go ahead.
Cheng Yao, come to my office.
I'm really treating you.
I'm really not going.
Li.
I can tell you the reason I'm taking on Chen Qing Mei's case now.
But, I feel like the answer is not that important to me anymore.
I just don't really like Chen Qing Mei.
I also feel a little sorry for Dong Min.
But from now on, I will try my best to control my emotions.
I know that since I have entered this profession,
I shouldn't be so sentimental about what is right or wrong.
You are fighting for justice,
but there is not just one kind of justice.
You only focus on the justice of individual cases,
but for the progress of law and the rule of law,
procedural justice is more important than substantive justice
because, sometimes, you don't know
what is true and what is false,
and what is right and what is wrong.
Lawyers are not judges
and are not present at every dispute scene.
They are not responsible for determining right and wrong.
Given the imperfect development of the law,
there are many times
even if the judge can distinguish right from wrong,
absolute justice is still impossible.
I'll say it again.
For the progress of law and the rule of law,
procedural justice is more important than substantive justice
because it is a visible justice.
I know.
I know procedural justice refers to the fairness of the trial process
and the justice concerning legal procedures.
But, it is exactly because procedural justice is overly emphasized
that we see mistakes like the judgment in O.J. Simpson's case.
It's because of the justice system
that there are so many bad people escaping legal punishment.
But, it also protects more innocent people who are wrongly accused.
Every case you handle now is upholding procedural justice
and making the legal system a little better in this country.
But, we also have the right to choose to represent good people.
Besides, boss, you're so rich.
Why do you always choose controversial cases?
Do you really not care about you being called a "tumor"?
You mean, a "tumor" that only cares about money but not morality?
Cheng Yao.
The law always protects everyone's basic rights and dignity.
No matter good or bad, there's no difference.
Even if they commit a crime, it must be thoroughly investigated
whether there a sympathetic reason for this person's wrongdoing.
For example, a wife who has been subjected to domestic violence
finally kills her husband in anger under the pressure of depression.
For example, self-defense and surrender.
Even for those extremely wicked murderers,
they have the right to accept the punishment of the law with dignity.
The law will punish them, but torture for confession is not allowed.
They cannot be tortured to death, even as punishment.
They should be made to clearly understand
why they are being punished,
and have the chance to learn from their mistakes and turn over a new leaf.
The law protects the basic rights and dignity of every person,
even the bad guys,
because the greatest significance of the law is fairness.
I will now answer your previous question.
What we uphold is not narrow individual fairness and justice,
but procedural justice.
This is the greatest value of being a lawyer.
Boss.
This is the first time I feel that
being your assistant lawyer
is truly worthwhile.
If, in the future, I become a famous lawyer,
I will calculate your consultation fee in hours
and pay accordingly.
No need for consultation fees.
Just do me a favor.
Eat this.
Cilantro-flavored chocolate?
Imported, limited edition.
I've always been curious about the taste
but I'm too scared to try it first.
But looking at your expression, I understand.
(Becoming famous.)
(Working hard and earning money diligently)
(to repay my boss for his cultivation.)
(Cheng Yao, are you crazy?)
(Why are you obsessed with Qian Heng again?)
(Haven't you learned your lesson from before?)
Time to work.
What's up? I just fell asleep.
Wu.
I still want to talk to you about my friend.
You know, something really coincidental happened.
He's also having trouble sleeping.
To him, that friend is quite important.
- He...   - (Tell your friend this.)
Either listen to me obediently
or just block and delete her.
(Which kind guy stays up every night worrying about these trivial matters?)
With his crappy personality, he deserves to have insomnia.
I'm hanging up.
I...
I haven't finished yet.
(I don't even know if Qian Heng really sleeps well.)
(Forget it. What does this have to do with me?)
Honey, didn't you just get off work from the police station?
Someone is knocking on the door. Can you go check it out?
Honey!
When did you find a husband who works at the police station?
Boss.
Boss, why is it you?
It's 2am. What are you doing here?
I might have dropped a pen here.
I came back to look for it. Can I go in?
Of course you can.
But, it's just a pen.
You can call me, and I'll bring it to the firm.
Why bother to make a trip personally?
That pen was given to me by my father when I won my first lawsuit.
It's very important to me.
I'm sorry, boss. I didn't know about your father's...
My father is alive and well.
Have you found it, boss?
Not yet.
What kind of pen is it?
Let me help you look for it.
Black, made of metal.
After you left, I cleaned the room for you.
But, I didn't see the black metal pen you mentioned.
Could it be
somewhere else?
Do you think I'm lying to you?
Of course not. What I mean is,
it's normal for such a small pen
to have been accidentally placed in the wrong spot.
Anyway, I have to find it today.
But boss,
can you take off your sunglasses when you look for it?
It's so dark,
it will affect the search.
You take your time. I'll go out.
Have you found it, boss?
Not yet.
What should we do?
I don't know what to do.
It's already 3am, and I still haven't found it.
You must be tired from searching for so long.
Yeah, it's really tiring.
I have a meeting tomorrow morning.
It's too late to drive safely.
I know, boss. That's why I've already arranged a driver for you.
The driver is waiting for you downstairs to make sure you get home safely.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm about to start.
Go on.
When I first took over the Dong Shan case,
I underestimated it because I thought it was too simple.
But after this incident, I realized that as a lawyer,
not only do I need to improve my professional skills,
but also have good communication skills.
If I can give people more trust,
then Dong Shan might have told me the truth from the beginning.
In Chen Qing Mei's case,
I let my personal emotions affect how I handle the case,
resulting in me neglecting procedural justice, law and morality,
fairness and...
What was it again?
Fairness and justice, and process and substance.
Learning how to balance these relationships in our profession
is the main homework of every lawyer.
The language is very sincere
but the tone is a bit harsh.
I don't think so.
Cheng Yao, I think you've spoken well.
Really, admitting mistakes is a good thing
just like what Yu Fei did back then.
- Thank you for that.   - You're welcome.
Not at all. I just realized now
that our boss's intention is thought-provoking.
I will continue to learn from our boss
and be positive.
You did a good job on this case.
As for you...
Cheng Yao, don't be discouraged.
For the 13 assistants before,
our boss has only one word for them.
But for you, it's...
Both of you, get out.
Boss.
Have you found your pen?
That's good.
If there's nothing else, I'll go out too.
Oh, boss. Why have you been wearing your glasses...
I didn't stay up late. It's not because of insomnia.
Why did you come at 2am?
I think I left my pen here.
Do you want to take off your sunglasses and look for it?
Boss, how about you...
How about...
You...
- Boss, how about you...   - Shut up.
You finish what you were saying.
When will you give me my bonus?
You stuttered just to tell me about this?
Boss, I...
I need it urgently.
(I can't just tell you to move back in front of Bao.)
Today, I'll treat everyone.
Feel free to eat, especially Bao.
In theory, I must treat everyone.
But, this is the first case we won with Cheng Yao in our firm.
So, Cheng Yao must properly treat us for this celebration.
Let's...
- Have some pizza!   - Come on.
Come on.
Here's to Cheng Yao's future victories in our firm!
Cheers!
Delicious.
So good!
Speaking of which,
I definitely want to stand on the side of justice.
But there's no way.
Our boss took on the case, and I had to help him win.
Otherwise, I would never lower my noble head,
trample on my pure soul,
and taint...
Oh, the phone is ringing. What a coincidence.
I'll take the call.
- What's wrong?   - I've heard about it.
You are the first among the 14 assistants
to make Lawyer Qian have that expression with your questions.
What kind of expression?
The expression of constipation.
Because Lawyer Qian always takes the initiative to give money.
But, you are the first one to ask him for money.
Of course he'd have that expression.
Oh my god.
Do you know what happened?
- What happened?   - Chen Qing Mei just gave birth.
Wasn't her due date still a month away?
How did she give birth?
On her way home, Chen Qing Mei fell and hurt herself,
leading to premature birth.
She preferred a natural birth to avoid stomach scars.
After the test results came out, she was in a great mood.
She didn't control her diet, and the baby was too big.
She struggled during delivery.
At that point, they couldn't switch to a C-section.
The baby was born with a lack of oxygen
and seemed to have inhaled some amniotic fluid.
Is the baby still alive?
If the child is not alive, Chen Qing Mei won't get a penny.
He's still alive
but he suffered from a lack of oxygen during a difficult birth
and can't suck milk on his own.
He was just diagnosed with cerebral palsy.
It's Grandpa Dong.
Lawyer Cheng,
I regret it.
Help me withdraw the kinship test.
I don't want to recognize this grandson.
I have Min, and that's enough for me.
But, the verdict has already been announced.
The child in Chen Qing Mei's belly
is related to you by blood. This is a fact.
If I had known that the child would have problems when born,
I would never agree to do any testing.
Now, Wen Xiu and Min
don't come to see me anymore.
I heard that Wen Xiu is taking Min abroad
and will never see me again.
Lawyer Cheng, don't you know Min?
Can you please talk to her on my behalf?
I'll give her all of the assets.
I don't want anything.
Mr. Dong.
About Madam Jiang and Dong Min, what they cared about has never been money.
Don't you know what truly makes them upset and want to leave?
Do you know?
Grandpa Dong is causing a scene with us
while also causing trouble for Chen Qing Mei.
Chen Qing Mei's health hasn't fully recovered since childbirth.
I heard she has a high fever now.
What about the child?
Yes, the child.
The child can't die.
If the child dies, who will inherit the inheritance?
Chen Qing Mei.
Will Grandpa Dong be willing to do that?
Grandpa Dong now has someone watching Chen Qing Mei closely,
fearing she might harm the child for financial gain.
Cheng Qing Mei has a young boyfriend, right?
Grandpa Dong hired someone to beat and scare him away.
For this inheritance, she sacrificed her whole life.
Did Chen Qing Mei envision this as her destiny?
Who could have predicted this?
Where's Cheng Yao?
She...
Grandpa Dong went to her for comfort.
I'm sure she's not in a good mood lately.
I told her to finish her work and then go rest.
After all, she's a young lawyer, unlike us...
What do you want to say?
Actually...
Oh, right. In Tang Bing's case,
he has signed the agency contract and wants to meet with you.
Is that okay?
- Yes.   - Then, I'll book the tickets.
Two business class tickets.
Wait. Boss.
That's not good.
Your favoritism toward me is already very obvious.
It's even a bit shameless now.
Others will be jealous when they see it.
Actually, as an assistant lawyer,
economy class is enough for me.
I forgot about you.
It's okay. You don't have to go.
Two business class tickets?
I'm jealous.
- Hey, Mom.   - (Yao Yao.)
(Let me tell you. Your dad and I will come to see you next week.)
(We plan to stay with you for a few days.)
Okay. Then, let me know when you arrive.
It's good that the boss moved out.
If they encounter each other,
I don't know what kind of tricks they'll pull.
Cheng Yao is my employee.
You have no right to say she's incompetent.
Don't try any sneaky moves.
In my villa, there are a few rare edition records.
I'll give them to you.
I don't even have a decent record player.
If you give me, it'll just go to waste.
If you like it, it's not a waste.
(Since he doesn't like me, why is he still so good to me?)
(Forget it. Don't think about it.)
Boss, why are you here?
Can I come in?
Yes.
I heard
that Grandpa Dong asked you to meet him.
He said he wanted to withdraw the results of the kinship test.
I can understand that.
His long-awaited grandson suddenly has a physical defect.
Boss, don't worry. He didn't give me a hard time.
And as a lawyer,
it's normal to encounter these problems.
You're able to think positively.
Thank you for caring about me, boss.
Since you're already here, let me make you a meal.
Don't overthink it.
I just came to inform you
that you have a business trip tomorrow. It's a family trust dispute case.
A new case?
But Bao is more familiar with family trusts, right?
He talks too much.
- Yu Fei is more steady.   - He talks too little.
So, you think that I am
professional, presentable,
and even the amount of words I say is just right?
Well, it's not that. It's your self-control that I trust.
We've been living together for so long, and you've been doing well.
Is that all?
Don't I have any other advantage?
Okay. Then, I won't embarrass myself.
It's getting late, boss. Let me send you off.
No need. Go make dinner.
You said it's getting late.
The restaurants are all closed.
You can watch your TV dramas.
Aren't you the one who dislikes me watching dramas?
I'm a very open-minded person.
(Are you being so kind?)
(I bet you just want to watch it yourself.)
(You just think it's good too.)
(Let me scare him a little, so he'll leave earlier.)
Watch this.
Do you have to watch such terrifying and bloody movies while eating?
It's quite scary.
Really?
Boss, how can you still eat
after saying it's so scary?
It's quite scary.
I mean you are quite scary.
I'm sorry.
But, I have a stack of threatening words
that are scarier to read than this.
The bloodiness can bring you nightmares.
Do you want to listen to the stories?
Let's stop watching.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
Are there any new toiletries at home?
I want to stay overnight.
Stay overnight?
This place is close to the airport.
You can refuse. Then, I'll give the case to Yu Fei.
Oh, why would I refuse?
It's an honor for you to come back and stay.
And, this is also your home.
I welcome you...
I welcome you warmly.
Let me tell you.
During dinner tonight,
I wanted to play a horror movie
to scare Qian Heng.
But, he wasn't scared at all. I was the one who got scared.
I couldn't even finish my meal.
Qian Heng is the type of person that even ghosts are afraid of.
I think you're the one who really scared him.
Look at what you're holding in your hand.
Qian Heng is definitely a sadist.
When did you become a masochist?
Put down the pan.
What happened to your courage when you used to argue with clients?
It's always good to be prepared. What if I want to eat too?
But,
do you feel like Qian Heng does have some issues?
You've only handled two cases with him
(and two persons have died.)
(Could it be that something unholy is involved?)
No way.
They probably won't be able to find me either.
Is this your first day at work?
Don't you know the role of employees is to protect the boss?
(How about I come over and keep you company tonight?)
(I remember, in the past,)
(you couldn't sleep after watching horror movies.)
Forget it. You're already pregnant.
Don't come here unless it's necessary.
Besides, I haven't done anything wrong.
Why would I be afraid of ghosts?
Let me pack my luggage first. I'm hanging up now.
Go to bed early and get some rest.
Goodbye.
Don't be afraid.
It'll be fine.
Sleeping with the lights on should be okay.
Boss!
Why are you shouting in the middle of the night?
Did you notice the power outage?
So what?
So, does your computer still have battery?
Do you need to work?
I can lend you my computer.
- No need.   - Boss.
I have a question.
What is it?
I'm embarrassed to ask.
Cheng Yao.
I knew I was wrong about you.
You couldn't hold it in anymore. You're finally showing your true colors.
No, boss.
There's no need to say anymore.
Please behave yourself.
I have questions.
I have
questions about the family trust dispute case.
I wanted to ask you about it.
It's too cold in the living room to chat.
Can we chat in your room instead?
Is that okay?
I just want to go in
and ask you a few simple work-related questions. Okay?
I really don't have any ulterior motives toward you.
- The TV drama you recommended has a similar plot.   - What do you mean?
In the drama, the second female lead and the male lead share a room
and she tries to seduce him but fails.
As a result, she becomes hateful
and ends up falsely accusing the male lead.
So what?
So, in case you accuse me of
trying to take advantage of you while we share a room,
how can I explain myself?
Even if you really don't like me,
you don't have to say such things about me.
Do you really think I'm that kind of person?
Forget it. Sorry for disturbing you.
Which aspect?
I'm talking about the family trust dispute case.
Which aspect do you want to know?
Since the Trust Law 2001, the practical use of family trusts
has been relatively infrequent, correct?
After my research,
I don't quite understand some of the operations.
For example, the issue of independence of trust property,
as well as transfer and registration issues.
There are also issues related to taxes.
I have many, many questions.
Just five minutes.
The issues you just mentioned
are also what I have been researching recently.
They are indeed quite complex.
It's hard to explain in a short time.
How about you come in with me
and we can compare the information I have organized before?
It will be easier to explain this way.
That's great.
Thank you, boss.
Domestic trusts, just like banks require approval
from the Banking Regulatory Commission in order to establish it.
At the same time,
it is also regulated by the Banking Regulatory Commission.
This condition makes it very difficult for domestic trusts
to be established.
Look, Article 11.
Under any one of the following circumstances,
the trust shall be invalid:
The purposes of the trust constitute a violation of laws...
- Are you listening?   - Yes.
- Is everything okay?   - It hurts.
I'm okay.
Where's my phone?
Where did it go?
Boss, can you help me switch on the phone's light?
I can't find my phone.
Why are you always doing unnecessary stuff?
Thank you, boss.
Can you explain this?
(Silly Stinky Boss)
This is a lovely nickname I have for you.
Lovely nickname.
After you see the word "silly,"
do you feel a hint of
sadness, helplessness,
and love?
Plus the word "stinky".
Boss, many parents call their children "stinky babies."
How much love is contained in that one word?
Lovely nickname, huh?
Do you also use this nickname for your parents?
Not really.
What about this circle? Can you explain it?
Boss. About the insurance law, I have a question to ask you.
- About the inheritance of the family's wealth...   - Go out.
I haven't finished studying yet.
- Leave now.   - Boss.
Boss, can you not cast me out?
Cheng Yao, if you keep doing this, I'll accuse you of sexual harassment.
- Get out.   - Boss.
- Let go.   - I'll tell the truth.
I'm afraid of the dark.
I just watched a horror movie.
And now, the power is out.
I'm really scared of being alone.
Can I stay with you for a while?
Please, I beg you.
Let go of my hand.
Why would you watch a horror movie if you're afraid of ghosts?
Don't do it again.
Thank you, boss.
Boss, are you still awake?
Actually, sometimes, you may be harsh with your words
but you are very caring in critical moments.
If you're not tired, let's chat for a bit.
What do you want to talk about?
Just talk about
your feelings and insights since you started working.
Would someone as outstanding as you have faced challenges like us newbies?
How could someone as talented as you face the same struggles as us?
I became a lawyer
despite my family's persistent opposition.
You're planning to go back and inherit the family business, right?
My parents used
comprehensive financial sanctions to force me to comply.
I just wanted to prove myself,
so I resisted them.
At that time, I couldn't afford anything to eat
and didn't have time to eat either.
So, I often had stomachaches.
One day, I finally got a case.
I had to run around to communicate and deliver documents
just to retain the lawyer's fee worth 5,000 yuan.
But I remember Bao told me that since you started working,
you have always been very glamorous.
That's because I was pretending.
Before my dad imposed financial sanctions on me,
I bought the most expensive suit.
At that time, I could barely afford to live,
but I still wore it every day
to be in the most professional
and dedicated manner when facing everyone.
It's a pity my supervising lawyer didn't like me at all.
He thought I was just a rich second-generation
playing the role of a lawyer for fun.
He gave me a hard time every day
causing me to almost lose several lawsuits.
Which law firm is that? How can there be someone like this?
It's a big law firm.
I don't want to mention this anymore.
I had high hopes when I joined
but in the end, I realized that many experienced lawyers
put all their energy into suppressing dissidents and forming cliques
instead of focusing on improving their own professional skills
and business standards.
At that time, I made a vow
that I would rather establish
a boutique law firm
with a team of elites which may be small but has strong unity.
That way, I could help each member
reach their potential in terms of professional abilities.
That's how Junheng & Co which we now know came into being.
But boss, how about the lawyer who suppressed you?
What happened to him now?
How can such a person
survive in the fierce competition?
It's just that his vision is just too poor.
Exactly. How dare he underestimate you, boss?
Boss, for someone like you,
anyone with a discerning eye
can see that one day you will shine and make a name for oneself.
It's not because of that.
With my eloquence and demeanor,
he actually thought I was just a regular rich second generation.
I was so angry at the time.
At that time...
I'm sorry.
My stomach is growling at the wrong time.
It's okay.
I'm actually hungry too.
Let's get some supper.
No singing allowed.
Why are you looking at me?
Boss.
I used to think you were perfect like a mannequin.
I didn't expect that you would
experience so many setbacks and troubles just like me.
Just like you?
I don't think we're very similar.
No. Actually, in terms of our experiences,
we're actually quite similar.
I used to work at a law firm with a salary of only 2,000 yuan.
My parents often had to give me some living expenses.
It's actually quite embarrassing.
But, what hit me the most
is not being able to see a future there.
For a period of time, I didn't even want to be a lawyer anymore.
I would often go home and cry alone.
Let me tell you, my ex-supervising lawyer
only assigned me administrative tasks.
He only let me handle superficial tasks.
I was never allowed to attend important meetings.
He only made me do trivial things.
For example, giving gifts to his wife,
running errands, printing documents, and so on.
However, there is one thing
that he was particularly concerned about us.
When having meals with male clients, he always brought us along
and made us drink with them
while listening to their jokes which made us uncomfortable.
Are you stupid? Couldn't you refuse?
Are you a hostess or a lawyer?
- What's his name?   - Yao Feng.
What is his area of expertise?
Inheritance law.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Do you still cry now?
Last time, after the Bai Xing Meng case, I cried once.
After that, I dared not cry anymore
because you said I'm ugly when I cry.
In the first two years of practice, it's like that.
Just bear with it.
If you feel any pressure or have any difficulties,
just talk to me.
Or else, Bao Rui and Yu Fei may also help you.
If you can't hold it in, you can cry.
You're not that ugly when you cry.
Just don't cry alone.
You can tell me. I'll buy you some chocolate.
The normal kind.
Thank you, boss.
But, if I catch you crying alone again,
I'll deduct your year-end bonus.
Boss. Can I ask you one more question before I go to bed?
One last question.
Go ahead.
Last time, you said I'm not suitable to be a lawyer. Is that true?
Why do you have to be a lawyer?
I want to help my sister get justice.
Deng Ming?
But, will I ever be able to defeat him?
In the Bai Xing Meng case, he tricked me again.
There's no chance for you to defeat me.
But defeating him? No problem.
Your talent is far inferior to mine.
But your attitude is decent.
You still have a little hope.
So please, boss, help me save myself.
Give yourself two more years.
During these two years,
my only requirement for you is don't get married. Don't fall in love.
Use all your time for work.
Even if you put a high-quality man like you in front of me,
I will treat him like dirt and never be tempted.
- Sleep.   - Good night.