[ALL PEOPLE, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
APPEARING IN THIS SERIES ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL]
Yes, I'm really sorry, chairwoman.
Yes, chairwoman.
OK. Goodbye.
What did she say?
Did she give you an earful?
There's no need to be tense.
It's not like
we're opposing her directly.
I'm sorry I'm late!
I shouldn't have been tardy
especially since I invited you here.
You must be so busy moving
into your new office
and getting used to your new job.
I'm sure Prosecutor General Cho
has nothing to worry about.
He's probably prepared for everything.
I informed the chairwoman that
we won't be attending like you asked.
I hope she understands the situation.
Of course.
You've been under
her influence for a long time
so I understand your concerns.
You should relax.
Relax.
Give me my racquet.
It's time for some tennis.
I can't wait!
Don't be so surprised.
He's trying to assert his dominance.
Now that he's attacked us first,
we'll have to fight back.
That's true, Mother,
but this is all so sudden.
Why? Don't you think you can fight back?
I just can't think of what to do.
How about that key?
Have you forgotten about it?
She was being blackmailed
by the person No Yeong-ju
was living with.
I thought you had it under control
so I didn't say anything.
[NO YEONG-JU, FRIENDS,
KWON MIN-SEON, MY LOVE]
[MY LOVE: WAIT]
[NO YEONG-JU, FRIENDS,
KWON MIN-SEON, MY LOVE]
[MY LOVE: WAIT UNTIL
THE TRUTH IS REVEALED]
How you use this on Cho is up to you.
[ARTIFICIAL CITY]
[STOP REDEVELOPMENT NOW]
[EPISODE 6]
[APARTMENT 208]
Hello?
Is anyone there?
No one lives there.
Did a lady named No Yeong-ju live here?
I'm Han Dong-min, a reporter for JBC.
Most of the apartments here are empty
and the residents change frequently
so I don't know anything.
I understand, ma'am.
Where should I go?
[KIM YI-SEOL]
Thank you for your interest.
I caught a turtle! It's so heavy.
[HYEONGSAN STATION]
Only the maids are here
and they don't know much.
- I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
- It's all right.
- Take a seat.
- OK.
Why would they hide anything?
Cho Gang-hyeon, Kwon Min-seon, Oh Ye-rin
and Jun-hyeok's wife.
What's going on?
[JBC STATION MANAGER]
Hello.
A reporter? So what did he say?
I gotta go.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's fine. I'm not hurt.
Why don't you
call me later just in case?
I'm sorry.
Please call me.
I'm fine.
Call me!
I'm sorry.
So, what was the name of the reporter?
[REPORTER, HAN DONG-MIN]
Let's put on some lotion.
Show me your cheeks.
Let's do this.
Jeez!
Stop it or I'll beat you up!
Hyeon-wu, you're so strong!
Does that hurt?
Aren't I a strong puncher?
Daddy!
Daddy, can you
stay home with me every day?
Maybe.
You're late.
Hey.
You look like you just saw a ghost.
Is Hyeon-wu asleep?
Yeah. He was so excited
that I barely put him to bed.
He seems happy that I'm home with him.
He wants me to stay home every day.
Oh.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I'm just a little
scatterbrained these days.
But you're so young and you received
a clean bill of health the last checkup.
Did you order something
from the Internet?
I'm so scared.
Are you going to nag me?
I'm just asking.
Actually, that package is for you.
[SENDER: YUN JAE-HUI
RECIPIENT: YUN JAE-HUI]
Who is it?
Why didn't you change your passcode?
I just bought it thoughtlessly.
I knew that you've give me an earful
but I sent it to you anyway.
Who do you think you are,
sending me this? It's true I'm angry...
You said you'd ask me
for help if you needed it
and that you wouldn't apologize,
didn't you?
Go ahead. What do you need?
No Yeong-ju
didn't kill herself.
Did Yun Jae-hui say anything to you?
What do you mean?
Did she ask you about me
and what I've been doing?
I didn't think you needed to know
so I didn't tell you,
but I caused a misunderstanding
with Chairwoman Seo.
So, my friendship with Jae-hui
is a little difficult, right now.
So, there's still a spark
between you and her?
So, Kwon Min-seon hired someone
to kill No Yeong-ju
and Cho Gang-hyeon used his influence
to make it look like a suicide?
And that's why the person who lived
with No Yeong-ju took revenge?
I didn't even know this
so I helped Cho become Prosecutor General
and forged a partnership with him.
He can make a deal with Chairwoman Seo
for the Directorship of the CIO so…
He wants to tame me
to become his errand girl
or discard me.
If Yun Jae-hui
asks about me by any chance,
put in a good word.
[CONGRATULATIONS ON THE 100TH YEAR
SINCE CHAIRMAN SEO JONG-TAE'S BIRTH]
They're sending us a sign
by using their wives
to send congratulatory wreathes.
They want to make it clear that
they're going after you, not me.
So, have you found a way
to teach Cho a lesson?
I can't fight him
without decisive evidence.
I'm going to obtain evidence
that Cho can't deny.
That video isn't enough.
So, you'll blackmail him
with his dirty secrets?
Yes. He betrayed me
after everything I did for him.
What is it?
I'm sorry, Mother.
The hundredth year celebration for
your father is such an important event.
It's an important event in name only.
But Father is no longer
with us so what's the use
of celebrating his birthday?
There is a get-together of the wives
of billionaires and politicians.
First, make these women your allies.
Do your best to win them over.
[MYEONGSUNG DEVELOPMENT COMPANY]
Hello?
What about Jun-il's tailor?
Huh?
But Jun-hyeok has lots of suits.
Ouch, my ear.
OK. I'll find out and call you back.
[MYEONGSUNG DEVELOPMENT COMPANY]
Is there a business called
Minerva in this building?
Minerva?
Well, they sell alcohol and food.
It's like a wine bar, I think.
I'm sorry, but we don't have
an F&B division.
I see. Thanks anyway.
Did that reporter return?
I don't know. It's not like
I stay home all day, you know.
If he does return, be careful
not to raise any suspicions.
You be careful and don't
get found out by that woman.
One of these days,
I'm gonna let you have it.
Yeah, right!
That little…
Hello, Da-eun.
I'll be right there. Bye.
[CONGRATULATIONS ON THE EXHIBITION,
OH YE-RIN]
- Where should I leave this?
- Leave it there.
[KWON MIN-SEON]
- Hello.
- You're here.
Who's that from?
Madam Kwon Min-seon. Secretary Go said
we shouldn't leave it in the lobby.
You're dismissed.
- Enjoy the food.
- Thank you.
Mrs. Yun doesn't have any parents.
That's why she was very close
to Madam Kwon. They were like sisters.
I don't know
why she acted like that just now.
Madam Kwon was a regular here
for thirty years.
Now, I come here once in a while.
Enjoy.
I didn't think
you'd like this kind of food.
Have you talked to Mr. Cho?
Is he going to register the marriage?
He should be happy that I'm willing
to marry an old man like him.
But he's changed completely.
He used to buy me
luxury handbags and shoes.
But now, he checks my spending.
I can't even go to the nail shop.
I lost my Bluetooth earphones
so I have to buy new ones
but I can only afford the cheapest ones.
Don't you think it's unfair?
You shouldn't have
sent me that potted plant.
Gang-hyeon asked me to send it to you
and Big Sis would have done it
if she were still alive.
And I took the opportunity
to skim a little for myself.
Good.
By the way,
have you ever seen No Yeong-ju?
Yeah, once or twice.
Madam Kwon as well?
She didn't just see her.
She did a lot more than just see her.
You were on good terms with Sis
so you probably have no idea
what a scary person she was.
Does Mr. Cho know?
Of course he does.
He lived with her for over twenty years.
Do you know what he said to me
after I'd taken a walloping from her?
He told me to make sure
to not tell anyone.
You've been through
quite a lot, I see.
My mother always said that
you shouldn't cry while you eat.
Why did you have to get me so emotional?
Hold on! It's on me!
It's only fair that
I pay for today's lunch.
It's only decent.
The food was delicious.
Thank you.
You know the get-together of wives
Madam Kwon used to attend?
You mean the Okryeonhoe Club?
What about it?
Me?
Yes, you should attend now
since you're with Mr. Cho.
Oh my, Jae-hui!
But don't tell Mr. Cho
for the time being.
Of course.
There's no reason he should find out.
Let's go, Jae-hui.
You're the best!
I can't make it because
I have a prior engagement.
Oh no. I don't want to
go there by myself.
Mother knows they're all there
to make amends for their husbands.
So I'm sure she
won't be too hard on you.
Jae-hui is really making it
tough for everyone.
You'll be fine, Aunt.
Call me and tell me how it was.
Did you eat dinner?
I ate with Father and Mother.
Living under the same roof as Mother,
it's been so long since we've cooked.
You'd cook us pasta once in a while
when Yu-ri was here.
Isn't it uncomfortable
to eat with Father?
I've never thought of it that way.
Why don't we eat separately from now on?
Mother would be hurt if we do.
Don't you think you're
drinking too much these days?
It's not wine, it's pomegranate juice.
They say it's good for women.
You practically made me beg
so we could have Yu-ri.
Were you jealous of Jun-heok's son?
You never smiled
at Yu-ri like you did to him.
Why do you want a son all of a sudden?
It's not like that, Ju-yeon.
Then? What is it like?
Hello, Sister.
Hello.
You look much more relaxed
than I expected.
I was worried that you'd all be tense.
It's been a long time
since we met a hotel.
Nowadays, there's no reason to visit
hotels as there's lots to do elsewhere.
But when we were young,
hotels were the only option we had.
Everyone we knew were from elite families
so we had to meet where
there were no prying eyes.
But nowadays, a woman could cause
a scandal by visiting a hotel.
Yeah, even if you have
coffee in the hotel lounge,
they'll start talking about you.
This must bring you back
to the good old days.
I like it.
Hello.
Hello, Mother.
Everyone has been praising
your choice of venue.
They tell me that coming to a hotel
takes them back to old times.
I was worried what you might think.
I'm glad you like the hotel.
Let me introduce myself formally.
I'm Yun Jae-hui.
I'm Oh Ye-rin and I'm with
the Prosecutor General.
Take a seat.
I'm sorry, Sister, but I don't think
I can let this slide.
Look, Jae-hui.
You should answer when you are addressed.
I am CEO now.
Please address me respectfully.
Who says so?
That's not a position you can get
because you say so.
Chairwoman Seo Han-suk has approved it.
OK, Madam Yun.
Yes, Aunt?
As you are well-aware,
I really don't like you.
I think everyone here
shares my sentiments.
But if Sister wants it,
I can accept you into our club.
But not that woman.
She seduced a married man
and even had his child out of wedlock.
Now, she's moved into his house
and pretends to be his wife.
Do you really expect us
to consort with her?
I'm sure you're offended.
But Aunt and everyone here,
have you forgotten why we've gathered?
It's to make amends to Sister.
That's right, because Cho instigated
your husbands to go after me.
Cho is a man who had a bastard child
despite the fact he was married
and even invited his mistress to
live with him in his dead wife's stead.
Your husbands are all allied
with that kind of man.
That's not the same thing.
It's a completely different situation.
I guess I'll have to put it another way
since you don't understand me.
Min Seon-sik.
Park Gyu-hwan.
You're Choi Hui-jun's sister, aren't you?
This is for you.
These are records
of your husbands and brother
that show their infidelities
including their affairs
with women of ill repute
all the way until now.
Assemblyman Min Seong-sik
has never hired a hooker.
But he's been
sexually harassing his aids.
How do you manage not only to consort,
but to live with such men?
Madam Yun, how can you do this?
You're a woman too.
Do you think your husband
is any different?
But you don't treat me as another woman.
If you treat me as another woman
and a human being,
I can help you
so your husbands never
cheat on you again.
Hold on! We need to talk.
I don't have anything to say to you.
You were planning to use me
from the beginning, weren't you?
Yes.
I had no idea. I really thought
you were looking out for me.
You trusted me?
You and I aren't close enough
to trust each other like that.
Don't cry in public.
They'll think you're weak.
You'd better get your act together
if you don't want to be used again.
You can use me
just as I used you today.
[CEO INAUGURATION VIP LIST]
[LIST OF INVITEES]
Da-eun, why are
all these people declining?
They say that they're busy.
But rumor has it that they're
boycotting Mrs. Yun's inauguration.
Why?
I don't know.
[SUNGJIN ARTSPACE JIN]
I wish you came sooner.
I wanted you to see them put up the sign.
[SUNGJIN ARTSPACE JIN]
I prepared the exhibition
for three years.
Why is everyone against
you becoming CEO?
So, you heard the rumors?
Is it true?
Get in. I'll tell you all about it.
[SUNGJIN ARTSPACE JIN]
I bet you've never experienced
such humiliation in your life.
What do you think?
I'm sure they all bought it.
Even I was convinced for a second
and my husband is in the hospital.
A husband's infidelities leave
a woman deeply wounded.
It smells a little like
the art gallery.
It's paraffin oil.
You mix it into the oil paint.
That's the smell.
At first, I didn't like it.
It smelled funny and musty
and it made me feel sad.
I wanted to go to a top university
but my grades kept falling.
That's why I memorized how to paint
for the painting test.
There's a school that teaches you how
to paint for the college painting test.
So, you aren't the only one
who got into college like that?
Those words are not very comforting.
The gallery vault also smells like this.
Paraffin oil.
Even priceless paintings
carry with them
the unpleasant smell of paraffin.
But that smell excited me
and I thought I could succeed
if I studied hard enough.
I was scared when we criticized
each other's art.
That always made me realize
that I lacked talent.
The kids that didn't even have
enough money to buy paints
would create stunning works of art
while the kids who created
mediocre paintings
carried luxury handbags
that I could never dream of buying.
I was like neither of them.
So, I became the object of ridicule.
Jeez, so that's it.
I thought you were rich enough to swindle
but it turns out you're poor.
That's why everyone opposes your
inauguration and looks down on you.
Master Jung, you are growing more
like your grandfather every day.
What do you think?
Instead of deep gray, Master Jung
should wear navy blue to show
that he comes from the highest class.
Granddad!
You're here, Hyeon-wu!
Good to see you.
Jun-il has been getting
fitted for a suit.
Only you can tell the Vice Chairman
of the Sungjin Group to come and go.
You're here, kiddo!
Grandpa, I'm bored.
Oh my, you're bored?
So, you're bored, are you?
Why don't I take you
to get some chocolate milk?
OK.
That's good!
We're off!
He loves chocolate milk
just like you when you were young.
I can't wait to see
how clever he turns out to be.
Senior Secretary of Civil Affairs
is quite a powerful position.
You'll have enough power
to do whatever you please.
And you can prepare
to run for president.
It's completely different
from other politicians who have to
Make out a living accepting bribes.
Completely!
I'm afraid I'll have to get going now.
I'm sorry, Jun-hyeok.
You've wasted enough time here.
Come again, Vice Chairman Jung.
Are you still in contact
with your birth father?
I don't care if you disrespect me.
But if you even have a shred
of affection for your mother,
you shouldn't be
going behind her back like that.
The man punched your mother
while she was pregnant with you.
It's no wonder she left him
even if it meant
having you out of wedlock.
You're cold and callous
just like your birth father.
Be careful.
Daddy, I'm going to eat dinner
and play with blocks with grandpa.
So don't come
pick me up too early.
Come late.
OK.
- Goodbye!
- Bye!
Let's go!
What is it?
I'm just wondering how you
manage to be so patient with him.
Why don't you just rebel against him?
Sons are supposed to rebel
against their fathers. I did that.
It might be hard to believe,
but I've never been angry at him.
I can't rebel against him
when I don't feel any anger.
I guess he's not someone
you can easily rebel against.
I thought you were so cool
when I was young.
Now, you pity you.
Have a little dignity, will you?
[EXAMINATION RECORD]
You have a healthy uterus and ovaries.
And you have good hormonal balance.
You've taken good care of yourself.
Can I still get pregnant again?
Have you used birth control since
giving birth fourteen years ago?
You have to have relations frequently
if you want to get pregnant.
It's true that it's harder
to get pregnant when you're in your 40s.
But that doesn't mean it's impossible.
Why don't you come back
with your husband?
OK. I understand.
Just try to relax.
Your sister-in-law got pregnant
only after she gave up
on in vitro fertilization
and relaxed.
Let's jump! You can jump so high.
Hello, sir.
What is that?
Mrs. Lee's family sent it.
I think she's trying for a second child.
Hyeon-wu, it looks like
you'll have a cousin.
I'd have dinner with you if
I didn't have to pick up my son.
You know, this is the second time
you're flaking on me.
I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
It's all right. I understand.
After all, you're poor.
Mr. Jung, would you like me
to call your wife?
It's all right.
I don't mind waiting.
Still.
Thanks anyway.
You should go home.
Yi-seol.
Mr. Jung is here
so please call Mrs. Yun.
I'll see you tomorrow.
OK. See you tomorrow.
I'm so sorry. I saw you there
sitting by yourself on my monitor.
How could you fail to recognize Mr. Jung?
I'm sorry.
It hasn't been long since he started
so he doesn't recognize
all the VIPs yet.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Don't be too hard on him.
We meet again.
I thought you'd left.
I didn't want to disappoint you.
My friend is supposed to come.
I never asked you.
Dong-min?
Hi, Jun-hyeok.
Long time no see.
What brings you here?
I came here to meet my wife.
How about you?
Well, I…
Huh! I'm over here!
Did I keep you waiting?
No, I just got here.
So, how are you feeling?
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm so relieved.
I was really worried.
I realized that I forgot to get
your number after I gave you my card.
I was so disappointed.
Why don't we go somewhere and eat?
You should join us, Jun-hyeok.
No. I should be getting home.
Come with us.
I have something to ask you.
We'll meet up later on.
OK. I'll give you a call.
- OK. Bye.
- Good night.
Drive carefully.
Have you eaten?
- Huh?
- Food.
This is delicious.
This is a lot of food for the two of us.
Eat up.
Hello, ma'am.
Where is everyone else?
Well, they're…
Grandpa is scolding Mommy.
I don't want to hear any excuses.
Have another son.
Hyeon-wu will be lonely by himself.
Even though you're thirty-seven,
you're still not too old.
These days, even women
in their forties have babies.
The clock is ticking so hurry
and get pregnant.
I've gone through too much
to get to where I am
to let this opportunity to go to waste.
Why won't you answer me?
I don't know how I should
answer such nonsense.
What?
I already told you that whether we have
children or not is our own business.
Now that you have Han-suk's backing,
you've become quite insolent!
If that's how you feel, Father,
that's because you fear Mother.
Did you already forget?
I've always been insolent,
from the very beginning.
But that never
caused you to even blink.
So, even though you've
married my precious son,
you'll stop with Hyeon-wu?
There will be no more children
and that's final.
Why did you have to cause
such a commotion today?
This isn't the first time
your father-in-law has behaved like that.
Let Hyeon-wu sleep here.
He may seem young,
but he sees and hears everything.
I'll be careful in front of Hyeon-wu.
But I'd feel more comfortable
if Hyeon-wu slept at home.
Why? Is there a reason
you won't let him stay here?
No, Mother.
OK. Take a walk and calm down.
I want you to be smiling
when you say good night to your son.
Yes, Mother.
Mommy, did Grandpa scold you a lot?
Don't worry.
He only scolded me a little.
OK. Go home and have fun with Daddy.
Aunt's gonna buy me
a scooter tomorrow.
Wow, you must be so happy, Hyeon-wu.
Yeah.
Good night.
Good night, Hyeon-wu.
Bye, Mom.
Oh, my little angel.
I have my doctor's appointment today.
I can't go with you. They're having
a demonstration in Hyeongsan-dong.
I can go alone
so just focus on your work.
You just got the head anchorman job.
Don't worry about me.
Still, it's our anniversary.
Let's have dinner somewhere nice.
I'll make a reservation.
Sounds good.
What's this?
I've never seen this before.
It's your anniversary present.
You're not pregnant.
Should I take a break and try again?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Your hormone levels are always low
and you've miscarried numerous times.
[FATHER]
[YOU HAVE FOUR MISSED CALLS]
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm afraid it's closing time.
I'm sorry.
[JH]
[INCOMING CALL FROM JH]
Your sister-in-law
got pregnant only after
she gave up on in vitro fertilization
and relaxed.
[YUN JAE-HUI]
There must be a nail clipper somewhere.
Where could it be?
The customer cannot answer the phone.
Please leave a message after the beep.
[JH LOVES JH]
[ARTIFICIAL CITY]
Are you with Dong-min?
No. Why do you ask?
I don't know.
I wonder why.
Why? Can't you handle it?
I misjudged him.
I know he's a bad man.
But you've known that as well.
There are no secrets in this household.
I saw your wife
at Cho Gang-hyeon's place.
It's a little fishy.
I didn't think you'd call
Prosecutor Park Jeong-ho here.
What are you doing here?
I saw your phone.
I won't allow you
to be used by your old flame.
What is it, Daddy?
JH.
- Jae-hui.
- I'll raise him.
I'll take good care of him.