Bethesda Quick
E betrayal
Rank 3
Get fully players
You can still get full
Save Mits instance
Let's go.
No, no, no.
Not that I don't have it.
I'll go back tomorrow.
Do you have it?
Tomorrow?
Pardon?
There's an eraser in my head.
I'll forget you tomorrow.
Now.
For an hour.
Oh, my.
Hello, sir.
I'll briefly brief you on today's schedule.
We're going to have an hour of meeting today.
After the meeting, we have a meeting with the CEO of the agency.
Mr. Jang.
Yes.
You talk too much.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry.
Shall we get started?
That's before the sales team leader and the strategic planning manager arrive.
Why are you always like that?
You mean the people who are later than the director were fired from the company?
Jung's team, just lock the door in the meeting room.
Yes, sir.
Let's start with Hansang XP.
Yes.
Hansang XP is a Korean whiskey business that is being prepared by the group.
It's a mainstream that will pair with L'Arcel and Moto.
It's a new product developed through a tree.
Who are you explaining to?
Is there a new employee here?
I heard you got a comment from the national agency.
Yes, the Jojo side is a separate branch.
The national agency...
Don't sell it as whiskey.
Turn it into a traditional drink.
But the whiskey business that's already going on...
Hey, team.
Yes.
What's the percentage of the traditional liquor stock?
I'll check it right away.
72% of the evidence, half of the traditional liquor, 36%.
Team.
Yes.
It's left after the meeting.
Yes, sir.
Is this something you don't know about me?
But the traditional liquor license is either a national liquor or a local specialty.
Hey, team.
Yes.
Find local specialty or traditional liquor that is currently on sale and develop a high-grade liquor that can be aged.
Hey, sales team.
Yes.
Can you hire a master, an expert, and a company that can sell liquor and OEM?
I'll check it.
It's not a favor, it's what I'm telling you to do.
Yes, sir.
Now, the next one.
Yes, the next one.
Recipe thief Han Beom-hoon!
Apologize and compensate!
One award for the big company's
reprimand is responsible and compensated.
Recipe thief Han Beom-hoon!
Apologize and compensate!
One award for the big company's
reprimand is responsible and compensated.
Recipe thief Han Beom-hoon!
You've done a lot.
You're working hard.
Big company's reprimand!
You're coming this way.
Why?
What?
What if I come?
What? Where?
What?
You look so scary.
Hey, run!
Excuse me!
Get the car out!
This is where customers wait.
Mr. Yoo Soomin?
Yes.
Is that right?
Move!
When did you see me?
I was talking to myself. Did you hear me?
Sorry.
Wow, there are so many people.
I heard that the abalone soup is so famous here.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Wait a minute.
You're here.
What are you doing?
What?
You're talking to yourself.
Hide it.
What if the client finds out that you're pretending to be a worker?
Right?
Boss?
So you're the mother, right?
Please talk to her.
I heard that you're going to sign up for the abalone soup restaurant right away.
What did you do, sir?
Who are you?
I don't know you.
Are you here?
What's wrong with your face?
You look like a dog.
How did you come all of a sudden?
This is mine.
Our chef didn't answer the phone these days.
He hasn't answered the phone these days.
Well,
Chef Jang is busy these days.
I'm busy, too.
The food looks more appetizing
when it was in the restaurant.
Right?
If you plate it roughly like this,
the judges will come to the three stars
and kill the stars that were there.
If you do this,
I'll be rewarded for bringing the recipe.
Will you eat it?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Gold rice.
Not bad.
Right?
Hunyeon?
Yes, I'm going to make Hunyeon at home.
I told you not to explain.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to cook.
You're the ones who make the food delicious.
I'm going to sell it to make it look good.
From the front of the customer to the plating.
Sequence dining.
I told you to recognize it.
It's not enough just for showing.
You can apply the sauce to the customer.
Experience marketing.
You know?
Yes, I see. I'll tell Chef Jang right away.
What's the main menu for today?
Truffle nabe?
That's not Chef Jang yet.
Where's Chef Jang?
Where is it?
Yes, that's great.
One, two.
I don't know if it's a chef or a student.
That's great.
One more time. One, two, three.
Yes, that's great.
Now, let's listen to the wine glass in front of you.
Let's wrap it up.
One, two, three.
Look at the camera and smile.
I heard that motorbikes are the best in the world these days.
They say it's easier to get a ride.
I heard that the reservation was already full for three months.
How do you feel?
I'm thankful.
I heard from the staff that there are people who sell reservations
like they sell tickets to the concert.
I don't know why they do that.
It's hard to be a person.
Oh, that's it?
Where do you usually get inspiration when you develop a menu?
I get inspiration from my grandmother's food when I was young.
My grandmother made really delicious cabbage kimchi.
Oh, my gosh!
Let's take a break.
Yes, sir.
Look at your grandmother.
Cosmo and Mari said that she was your grandmother in the magazine interview.
Did they?
I'm just confused.
I've never eaten cabbage kimchi before.
Why are you sitting there?
Is it good?
Cabbage kimchi.
You're saying it's good because you're a doctor?
Forget it.
Why do you keep getting an interview schedule without permission from the PR team?
This is a violation of the contract.
Oh, really?
Then launching a menu without the permission of the head chef.
That's also a violation of the contract.
No, who would have thought I didn't give you time to develop a menu?
How do you develop all those course menus in a month?
You're in a variety show, shooting a photo.
If you had time to spare, I would have developed it.
Spare time?
Did I go on a variety show because I liked me?
It's all our motto.
We're going to promote the restaurant.
Three stars.
I'm much more professional than Chef Jang Young-ae in restaurant marketing.
I'll do it myself.
Chef Jang Young-ae, bring three stars.
So, you're going to have to give me time to develop my creativity to bring three stars or not?
Creativity?
Do I ask you for that?
No.
The recipe I brought from Seoul is the most famous restaurant recipe in Korea.
But, you're telling me to follow the recipe and make it pretty?
Is that so hard?
I forgot for a second.
I'm crazy about three stars.
The launch of this season's menu will be as planned.
Until then, the main menu truffle nubian is completely prepared.
Chef Jang Young-ae.
I'm going to the restaurant.
You seem busy these days.
You said you didn't go to the horse racing.
Do you even take my schedule?
It's okay.
It's not easy to run a fine dining in a team that sells frozen food.
I'm having a hard time because I heard it's worse than frozen food.
Even if you look at it, it's only possible for one star to be a two-star.
You know that, right?
Wait a minute.
We can't bring the stars as soon as we open it.
L'Arcèle is a two-star in three years?
Who is being a two-star?
Stop messing around.
Beom-woo.
What's on your face?
I'll let you off today.
Today, residents of Parkdalli Village are gathering to open a restaurant.
The main character of the guest who secretly visited the village is...
Hello.
The owner of the Han-sang Food Fair.
It's corn powder.
The owner of the Han-sang Food Fair prepared corn powder.
Mix it thoroughly in the kimchi.
It looks very delicious.
I'll pack this and deliver it to your house.
I'll deliver it to your house.
I won't do it again.
This is chicken feet from Yeosu.
Mr. Park.
Yes?
How long have you been working at my house?
It's been about seven years, sir.
You should have lived with this precious chicken feet.
Pardon?
You should have made it taste better than the snow.
I'm sorry, sir.
Let's go.
Please give us another chance.
How can they leave behind ten years?
This woman has lived her whole life as a food.
But...
The guide book she made abroad...
Guide?
One star, two star, three star...
I'm so angry with that standard.
But I want to get angry.
I have to be angry to get angry.
In my fantasy group.
Can't you get those three stars?
I'm sorry.
Keep in mind.
Three stars.
The one who brings them is the owner of this fantasy.
I'm not the main menu of the auto.
How long did it take?
From the date you gave the recipe,
exactly one month and five days.
It took a long time.
The kick isn't bad.
But the plating...
It's not bad to launch the original motor.
We'll launch the main menu tomorrow.
We have to get the three stars this time.
Got it?
Sir!
I don't know you.
Why do you keep coming out?
Sir, it's not that.
I'll give you the three stars.
What the...
It's the same sound.
What?
It's exactly the same.
I searched for a similar menu on the smart GPT.
What's the motto of our dining motor?
Unique only one.
That's the three stars.
I got it.
It feels like fine dining.
Where is it?
Jeonju.
Fine dining Jeonju?
Where?
Can I see the D?
One star? Two star?
Jeonju. Jeonju, Jeollabuk-do.
Anyway,
we have to launch it tomorrow.
What should we do?
Hold the order pamphlet.
And I'll take care of the influx reservation.
I'll take care of it.
Do whatever you want.
I'll take care of it today.
So, all of you, stand by.
How dare you mess up my plan?
I'll take care of it.
I don't have time to walk slowly.
I don't have to look at the map.
I'm sorry.
Turn left in a moment.
Turn right about 10 meters ahead.
Turn right. Turn right.
What is this place?
Oh my gosh.
Here.
How do I get there?
Put it down.
I'm sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Turn left.
Turn right in a moment.
Oh my gosh.
Is this right?
Where are you?
Why are you hiding?
This is the right place.
What?
We've arrived at our destination.
We're closing the road.
What?
Well, retro is popular these days.
Jungjae?
It's fun.
Come here.
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
Sir.
Hello?
Where is the owner?
I don't understand.
Excuse me.
Is the owner here?
What?
It's dangerous.
Oh my gosh.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
You're hurting me because of the high-end cabbage.
Never mind.
Where is the owner?
I'm like this.
You know Hansang, right?
I have something to say to the owner.
Where is the owner?
What are you doing?
Wow.
It's been a while since I played a game.
Hey!
Wait!
Were you the owner?
Sir,
you're right.
You can't just tear it up.
It's nothing.
Nubian made it here, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
If you don't mind,
can I have Nubian?
It's break time.
So you can't have it.
Then,
let's have dinner for two hours.
No.
You're right.
Why not?
What?
Shouldn't you apologize first?
Me?
What?
Earlier...
Do you know
how much this dress costs?
You know how much this cabbage costs?
How much?
Are you a king or what?
What did you say?
Water is a disease, and it's a cancer.
He's been through all kinds of diseases.
He's been buried in the ground,
and he's been put on the ground.
How much is his life worth?
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize.
But...
Nubian...
I'm upset.
What?
So,
can you make this for me?
No.
Can you stop talking?
I don't have the ingredients.
You can just buy them.
They're not that easy to find.
What kind of ingredients do you need?
I'm not asking you to reflect on the king's life.
Then,
go and buy them yourself.
You bastard!
Did you just call me a bastard?
What do you need?
Chef?
Udon.
Udon?
Yes, udon.
Udon is enough, right?
The cow I raised in the farm in the garden.
The udon of that cow.
Chef, the udon is all over there.
It's the most expensive and the best...
Aha!
The udon of that cow.
No.
Aha!
The udon is all over there.
Why are you so picky?
I'm just thinking.
Yes, 200g of udon.
The best and the most expensive udon in this restaurant.
The cow I raised in the farm in the garden.
The udon of that cow.
Wait, wait, wait.
The...
The garden?
Anyway, the cow I raised in that farm.
The udon of the cow I raised in that farm.
200g.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you can find it, go to the shop.
The udon of the garden farm.
Oh, this neighborhood.
Is this an event for me?
Is this a hidden camera?
Excuse me.
From here to here.
Give me everything.
And the thing in the refrigerator.
And the udon in the restaurant.
Give me everything.
Wow, wow!
It's a cow.
Wait, wait, wait.
The cow.
The udon.
To me.
Oh, my.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Where's Lars?
Hanson doesn't move much, does he?
Okay, hang up for now.
I'm going to make udon.
The eggs are all broken.
I want to sell them, too.
But my wife
There's an egg temperature.
Her back was broken, so
there's no way to go to the hospital in the morning.
What should I do?
What does that have to do with a sale of eggs?
If someone else goes in, you'll have to sit there and wait.
Aren't you a coward?
You think you can live without selling eggs?
I'm serious.
How can I be a beggar?
If you need money, go and get it yourself.
I guess there's no luck.
Be careful.
Don't let anyone chase you.
açıl
OK, I got it, too!
But you'll never kill me.
As soon as he comes...
What will I do about it?
Just laugh or lose twice
The world ends
Kyaa!
Yaaaaaaaaaah!!!!
Gyaaaaaaaaaaa!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Turn into a thousand earths
There it is!
Teacher−
Hey...
Hey!
Where did you get this?
I got it from Melvin.
But you still keep wanting to get sold by about two billion a month but now you gotı
such a difficult job.
Because of a thing's you would've liked to base it on a real business.
I'm just saying.
How dare you come out and scare me?
If you do that again, I'll shoot you with the arrow you just saw.
What did I do?
In front of your restaurant.
Are you a pervert?
Pervert?
You said you wanted beef.
Beef!
What kind of beef?
Udon?
Udon, udon, gently.
You're a crazy person who keeps messing with the restaurant.
Even if I don't know anyone else, I don't think you'd listen to me.
I told you to buy udon noodles.
You're going to do this?
Udon noodles.
I've been to all the udon noodles in this neighborhood.
Here.
Can you see it?
Mawon Farm.
I'm the kind of person who only says I'm going to do it.
What do you do?
Do you cook right away?
Do you light it up?
What are you doing? Why are you smelling it?
How dare you lie to me?
What?
Teacher, I'm really sorry.
But today, the Nubian...
The Seopsanjo.
Yes, that Seop...
That Sanjo.
You have to eat it.
Why are you doing this?
Because I have to eat it.
Because I want to eat it.
Why are you so loud?
That's what I was going to say.
And with an expression that I don't want to eat anything,
What do you want to eat?
You can't judge people by their expressions.
I really want to eat it.
I want to eat it.
What?
There was a real one in the village.
Do you want to ride the mountain?
No.
Mushrooms!
You can buy mushrooms at the mart.
Why are you riding the mountain?
I'm moving to a big company.
I'm going to...
If I press the emergency button, everyone will come.
Maskers or police.
You...
Don't think about doing anything stupid by bringing me here.
Don't overreact. You won't die.
I just...
I just want to eat!
Here it is!
You said you were looking for mushrooms.
Let's go down.
That's a young man.
Mushrooms are here.
They're already here.
What? Is there something there?
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
I'm picking mushrooms.
You can buy them with money. It's dangerous.
The moment the mushrooms break up on the ground,
the scent is gone.
It's most important to keep it as it is.
Even if you get hurt a little, the flavor changes.
Is there something wrong with you?
What are you talking about?
Is this cabbage kimchi?
It's not cabbage kimchi.
It's radish kimchi.
Can I try it?
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
Chew it.
I like the one my grandma made the most.
It's good.
Wake up.
Business.
I think he's really crazy.
Different ingredients, different recipes.
It's a completely different dish.
The meat looks thicker.
Is it minced?
You baked the mushrooms in the oven.
It may be confusing to decorate the mushrooms similarly,
but it's a different dish.
Did you see it well?
It looks delicious.
What are you doing?
Is this the price of food?
Okay.
The person who made it is sincere.
Let's talk.
He's playing alone, playing the drums, and playing the drums.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
It's a bit of a shame to cut the meat that was thinly spread and marinate it in the sauce.
It's a bit of a shame to chop the meat and knead it and bake it.
The mushrooms were a kick.
I heard it with my ears.
How much is the restaurant's sales?
Is there a business in this place?
The wood is bad, so the rent is about 5%.
But it's a life of ingredients.
If you look at the cost,
20% to 30% per day?
That much?
It's delicious, but it's in an ambiguous location.
It's a bit of a challenge.
The shape of the table? Not bad.
But to go like that, you have to raise the chair by about 10cm.
The lighting is too dark.
If you look at it from the outside, it's a restaurant or a bar.
So I think there's a problem with the overall restaurant management.
So what do you want to say?
I'll take over the restaurant.
I'll take over.
If you're asleep, go in.
I can fill in the commission.
I don't need anything else.
I fell asleep because it sounded ridiculous.
I'm going to sleep.
If the word, commission, is a little bit small,
How about investment?
It's not hard.
Just a simple thing.
Just a small thing.
For example,
Recipe?
Share each other
Like this, close.
Big companies like us have advantages.
Big companies are not all bad guys.
Management, difficult, annoying.
Han Sang supports all of that.
You just have to cook the food you're good at.
Han Sang will take care of all this useless stuff.
What's useless?
Did you just get hurt in your mouth?
I've never eaten anything like this.
This little bastard.
The weather, the way of breeding, the nature of the crops.
I've been looking at it and I've been doing it.
The food supply, the time of the crop, the soil, the fertilizer.
I've been adjusting it, I've been doing it.
It's been 120 days.
You have to look at it for 120 days.
That's when it becomes a white bean.
Do you think that's the end?
If you soak the beans, grind them, strain them, and then make a bean soup.
It's not even a strong fire.
Keep stirring it over a low heat and boil it for a while.
That's how you boil it.
It's going to be the tofu in the pot you ate earlier.
Okay.
I know that, so calm down.
Management?
What, crazy people only care about money make food?
That's it?
Hey, this process and sincerity.
I don't even know how much value it has.
Let's see.
Hey, what if you're crazy about money?
Sincerity?
The sincerity you're talking about.
You have to earn money.
You have to have money to run your favorite restaurant.
Why do you run a restaurant?
Because you want to?
Not money, not business card.
Do you really have this sincerity?
Think about it.
Whatever it is.
Ha ha ha!
It's okay.
If you don't do it, it's a failure.
Where are you?
I'm sorry.
The sincerity you're talking about.
You have to earn money.
You have to have money to run your favorite restaurant.
Why don't you answer your phone?
I heard a sound.
It's like a market.
You've improved a lot.
You could be an actress.
When are you going to pay the rent?
You said you'd pay it in a month.
Was it a month?
I think I said two months.
Are you kidding me?
You should sell bean sprouts soup.
You're not going to be able to eat this.
I'm going to eat it.
You should sell bean sprouts soup.
There's no signboard, no menu.
What are you going to sell?
The signboards are outside.
The menu is here.
What are you talking about?
Pineapple?
I'm going to do that.
I don't have anything to say.
It's a month.
If it doesn't work,
take out the store.
That's...
Where's the thing you took out?
Give it to me.
Shut up.
You're pretty.
I'm going.
It's not a pineapple. It's a pineapple.
My sun cap.
What?
It's on TV.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to do that.
The police are investigating the threat of H.
This is Kim Min-ah.
It's not right to go out with a single shot,
but there's no way to escape.
Let's start with the board of directors.
Let's start voting.
If you agree with the board of directors,
please reject it.
As a reason,
I will inform you that the meeting of director Han Bum-woo has been concluded.
Fortunately, life is not a problem.
It's number 302.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
You have to kneel down.
I'm going out.
Hello.
Yes, yes.
What are you worried about?
The upper part of the car is clean.
I just put the vitamin in.
Money?
I checked.
Wait a minute.
I'll be careful.
Please tell Director Han that I'm grateful.
Yes, yes.
Yes, I'll do it.
Director Han.
Han Sun-woo.
Chairman, Han Bum-woo is calling.
Hello.
So what?
Are you blaming me for getting hit by Director Han Sun-woo?
No, it's not that.
The important thing is...
The important thing is that our stock price fluctuated because of you.
I told you all the time.
It's the wrong guy to meet.
But this is cheating.
Whether it's cheating or not,
you just have to win.
I'm not cheating.
Whatever you say.
You just have to win.
What's the problem?
You do it like Sun-woo.
No, I don't even compare.
Anyway, three stars are the most important thing.
I'll get three stars somehow.
I'll leave it to Sun-woo for a while.
I know that.
If you cut your hands and feet like that, what am I supposed to do?
You have to remember what you can do.
It's your ability to find it.
What the hell is that?
What the hell?
Really?
Shall we talk for a while?
What are you doing?
Pick up the
I'm going to be a three star.
If you're working here, I'll think about it.
Work?
You just have to pick an employee.
What do you mean?
He's the employee who's going to work with us from today.
Isn't it because of your self-righteousness that you're like this?
Did you see him look at me?
He's crazy.
What are you thinking?
I'm gonna have to go.
Who is it?
What's that?