TASTEFULLY YOURS
HANSANG
-Hello.
-Hello. Thank you.
Welcome.
Thank you for accepting our invitation.
The pleasure is mine.
Thank you for the invitation.
Thank you.
Shall we?
Sure.
THE ULTIMATE DIAMANT
THE SHOWDOWN OF THE CENTURY
TO DETERMINE THE ULTIMATE 3-STAR
MOTTO VS JUNGJAE
The showdown of the century
to find the ultimate
three-star restaurant.
Welcome to The Hansang Diamant Show.
-It's starting.
-All right.
-It's starting?
-It's starting.
This will determine
the ultimate three-star restaurant.
First, let me introduce
the judge of this cook-off,
Hansang Food Field's Chairman Han Yeo-ul.
Please step forward.
Hello.
Hello, I'm Han Yeo-ul.
Next, we have a special judge
who will explain the theme
and evaluation guidelines.
Please step forward.
A special judge?
-Hello. Thanks for having me.
-This is Mathieu,
the editor-in-chief of the Diamant Guide.
He's… Hang on a second.
-What's the matter?
-Do you know the guy?
He looks awfully familiar.
It's him!
The couple that came with their parents!
The bride's father!
-Right!
-That's right!
-Santé.
-Santé, sweetie.
-It's him, right?
-It's him.
Hello, I'm Mathieu,
the editor-in-chief of the Diamant Guide.
-He's the editor-in-chief.
-Editor-in-chief.
I'm very honored
to participate as a judge in this event
held in South Korea,
the country of gastronomy.
So it must be him who put our restaurant
in that guidebook.
That's it.
My gosh.
The competitors will be judged
by 30 food-related influencers
who will visit both Motto and Jungjae.
And of course, we can't be left out.
-Certainly not.
-We'll go to both restaurants in person
to taste and evaluate the food.
Now, let us begin the draw
to determine the theme
of the Ultimate Diamant cook-off.
I can't wait to see
what the theme will be.
It's chicken.
-Chicken?
-Chicken…
-The theme for the…
-Korean, French, Italian.
-…Ultimate Diamant cook-off is chicken!
-That's right!
-Goodness gracious.
This. Our secret weapon.
Jungjae's recipe book.
Why didn't I think of this?
-Did I do well?
-Yeah, good job.
-Well done.
-What is this?
-Okay. Something familiar but unfamiliar.
-What is that?
Familiar but new.
-Chicken.
This.
How about this dish?
This is a dish called Coq au Vin.
Cook a van?
-No, Coq au Vin.
-Coq au Vin.
It's a French-style chicken dish
with vegetables.
The Korean equivalent would be…
Jjimdak.
Yeah, jjimdak.
But cooked in wine.
The key point is braising it,
not steaming it.
So you braise it in wine, right?
If we were to balance it a bit
and tweak it to suit the Korean palate,
it would make a nice, hearty meal.
I think this is a good idea.
-My mouth is watering already.
-It's perfect.
-Wait.
-Sounds good.
Do you think you can make this?
Of course.
-Let's do it!
-Let's go with this!
-Okay! Let's go!
All right then.
Shall we get the ingredients?
-Let's go!
-Go!
-Hurry.
-Let's go, sirs.
-We'll buy all the chicken in this town.
-I'll be back.
-See you later.
Let's crush them all.
-Crush them.
-With your skill.
Goddammit.
Goddammit indeed.
You sound just like Chef Mo.
Tell me. Where did we go?
-All the places we could.
-Right?
-Did all the chickens fly off?
-Damn it.
Why are you mimicking Chef Mo
out of the blue?
Just hand over the chicken.
There were none.
What do you mean there were none?
We went everywhere
and checked every store,
but the chicken we want isn't available.
We wanted Korean native chicken
or Silkies,
but they were all sold out.
I think
someone messed with our supply
to make sure we couldn't get any.
Who would do such a thing?
Wait. Could it be those Motto punks?
No way.
They'd go this far?
Yeah, they would.
My gosh.
The rich and powerful are the worst.
No.
Let's not waste energy on stuff like this.
We just have to do what we do best, right?
-Yeah.
Let's find a way.
JUNGJAE
Okay, gather around again.
Choon-seung and you,
search the market from top to bottom.
-Great.
-You and I will go to all the stores
and get all the chicken we can find, okay?
Frozen or not,
we'll just get what we can find.
-You got that?
-Okay.
Beom-woo, but the other guys
are going to use good-quality chicken.
Can we beat them with frozen chicken?
Myung-sook says she has a secret sauce.
-Let's trust her!
-Okay!
-Let's go!
-Sir, you're headed to the market.
-What?
Oh, right, the market.
-Sir, hold my hand and follow me.
-What?
-Why should we hold hands?
-Follow me.
-Hey, don't.
-It's that way.
-Wait. Don't run!
-Let's go!
One, two, three, four.
We sing as we march.
We'll sing "Comrade's Star."
Hey! Call me if you find any chicken!
Nice and loud.
I feel embarrassed now that I'm back.
What?
Say that again?
Yes, sir.
As per Chairman Han's specific order,
we blocked the distribution
of all chicken breeds.
Okay.
By the way, sir,
why did you go all the way there?
Good work.
Jeez.
What the heck do they want a cook-off for?
I know, right?
We meet again.
You seem pretty attached
to the restaurant.
TASTEFULLY YOURS
Okay, put that down there.
It has to face the other way.
Move that slightly forward.
VOTE FOR YOUR TASTE
MOTTO VS JUNGJAE
It has to fit the angle of the camera.
Bring the table forward a bit.
Hurry up.
THE ULTIMATE DIAMANT
BALLOT BOX
We don't have all day.
Move faster, people.
Please turn on Camera 3.
Check this.
Thank you.
-Did you check it?
-Yes, I did.
This tiny thing is a camera?
Move the camera a bit to the left.
-Check the memory cards.
-Okay.
Check the sound, please.
Add two scoops then shake the bottle.
-Two scoops?
-Yes.
Shake it, shake it.
You need to cut it as close
to the bone as possible.
Yes, Chef.
Make sure there's no residue.
How long has it been sitting in the brine?
Four hours.
-Let me check.
-Yes, Chef.
-We're ready.
-Oh, okay.
Okay, everyone. Let's stand by.
All right.
Ready,
action!
Motto is open for business.
Go, go. Let's go.
-Thank you.
-Please come in.
Sir.
Wait, why…
Do it all again!
-Yes, Chef.
I said that wasn't it!
I'm sorry.
Chef.
I don't think you have to try so hard.
What?
I mean, this competition
has nothing to do with us.
We won't get fired
or paid less even if we lose.
No. I don't want to be complacent.
Whether the owner is Beom-woo or Sun-woo,
I'm the one who does the cooking.
This time,
I'm serving my recipe.
It looks good.
FIERY JJIGAE MAN
830,000 FOLLOWERS
I'm so excited.
1.76 MILLION FOLLOWERS
PARK GANG-HAE
870,000 FOLLOWERS
SORANG COUPLE: 1.45 MILLION FOLLOWERS
LEONALD: 880,000 FOLLOWERS
QUEEN GYEOWOOL, KO NA-RI, 5PM
FLAVOR, CREATIVITY, QUALITY
MOTTO VS JUNGJAE
TASTING EVALUATION FORM
Five stars.
It smells amazing.
Can you greet my followers?
-Oh, sure. Hello.
-Hello.
That's good.
That's it.
There. It looks much better.
It's reduced nicely.
YAKITORI KING KIM BYEONG-MUK
670,000 FOLLOWERS
Cue Camera 4.
It tastes very familiar and delicious.
The more I eat…
I brought you some makgeolli.
Apologies for the long wait.
KIM PAN-BAE
790,000 FOLLOWERS
Let me tell you about this makgeolli.
I ground up some sweet potatoes…
Father.
You ground them up to make what?
Well…
I ground them up to make
this sweet potato makgeolli.
You made it yourself?
Yes.
It's good.
We should sell this at our restaurant too.
Shin Choon-seung's makgeolli.
Please enjoy your meal.
KONGNAMUL CHRONICLES SHIN JONG-CHEOL
330,000 FOLLOWERS
Thank you.
This Gwangyang-style grilled chicken
is a local dish
that's crispy on the outside
and moist on the inside.
We grilled Cheongri native chicken
over charcoal made from
wood from Baegunsan Mountain.
The wine we paired with this dish
is a Château de Montépice.
With its spicy aroma
and balanced structure,
the wine pairs beautifully
with the grilled chicken.
Is this the exact same dish
served to the other customers?
Did you do anything differently
for us judges?
It's exactly the same.
It's delicious.
Cut.
We'll now film the judges on the move.
Okay.
We'll shoot the last dinner
and announcement of the results in one go.
Producer Kim.
Oh, yes. Here, take this.
-You should go too.
-I'll share their ride.
Producer Kim.
Yes, ma'am.
The child that's most important to me…
is Hansang.
Yes, ma'am.
Of course.
I'll be separating
the in-house food division
and launching a new brand soon.
You mean you're expanding your business?
That's right.
I don't care about the result.
-Right.
-This is all just for show anyway.
A show to keep people interested
until the launch.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am. I understand.
Thank you for your efforts until now.
Right back at you.
"Until now"?
Yu-jin.
I was able to hang on because I at least
had one decent person around.
No, wait.
You're not quitting, are you?
I think I did what I could do.
The food was good, wasn't it?
Why are you doing this?
Well,
I liked being able to cook my food.
It's not cool
copying someone else's recipes.
If you see the country bumpkin chef again,
tell her I said sorry.
What are you planning to do?
Thanks.
Take care.
That's a bit much.
Wait, Chef.
I'm everyone's favorite doormat.
They stomp all over me.
You seem pretty attached
to the restaurant.
You can't smoke in Hanok Village.
You're even worse than the doofus.
You brothers are unbelievable.
Neither of you is honest,
and all you know how to do is
beat around the bush and put up a front.
You're just the same, damn it.
Didn't Han Beom-woo
-tell you?
-Tell me what?
That food and the restaurants
are more important to our mother
than her sons.
That's the life we've lived.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
For growth and self-improvement.
RESIGNATION LETTER
APPLICANT: LEE YU-JIN
I've done more than enough.
I can't take this job anymore, damn it.
Excuse me.
My goodness.
Darn it, I messed up.
I need another envelope.
Who…
What are you doing here?
To be honest, I feel bad for Director Han.
Growing up with Chairman Han, I mean…
Growing up with a mom like that…
Welcome to Han Yeo-ul's Secret Recipe.
I can't wait to find out
what you'll be cooking today.
I'm so excited.
Today, we'll be making a snack
that children love.
-It's something I often made for my sons.
-I see.
-Really? I'm curious.
-Yes.
-Are you?
-Okay, I will…
-That's right. I'll go over the recipe.
-Mom!
Yes. Just a moment, please.
Mom, can't you stay home
and play with me today?
Hello?
I want to switch distributors.
The ingredients aren't fresh.
Is my baby hungry?
Want to eat with Granny?
All right, Beom-woo. Let's eat.
Try this.
-Is it good?
-Yeah.
Let's have another spoonful.
Chew it properly.
Thank you for coming.
-My condolences.
-Thank you.
Apparently, her daughter is abroad
on a business trip right now.
Isn't she a famous chef or something?
She's a crazy workaholic.
She's skipping her own mom's funeral.
That's just not right.
Both Director Han
and Managing Director Han
probably had it rough.
Of course,
everything Director Han did
was wrong.
But the guy
who used to live like that…
met you and the people at Jungjae
and showed regret and remorse.
He seems to have changed.
I really wanted to tell you that.
He'd be too embarrassed and ashamed
to say it himself.
What an idiot.
Sorry?
They'll reach Jungjae
sooner than expected.
Shall we prepare to open for dinner?
Yes, sure.
Okay then.
Where did she go?
It's time to end their ridiculous show.
I just can't wait!
Come by again even after the cook-off!
It was the best. It was awesome.
-Chairman Han is here. Hurry up.
-I almost let the exterior fool me.
That would've been a huge mistake.
The food was as great as you'd expect
from a Diamant three-star restaurant.
It's time for the judges' evaluation
and the final result.
-Let's go again.
-They're the best.
-They make the best food ever.
-Honey, look.
The judges have arrived.
Hey, the judges are here.
Let's look at that camera too.
Welcome.
It's true that I have
a personal attachment to this restaurant,
but I will judge impartially.
I also
will put my personal feelings aside
and judge fairly and impartially.
All right. Shall we begin then?
This is Coq au Vin.
It's a traditional French dish
cooked with inspiration
from a Korean dish, jjimdak.
Motto served
a Korean dish with a French touch.
Meanwhile,
Jungjae served a French dish
with a Korean touch.
That's fascinating.
Is this the same dish everyone else had?
Did you change anything
or make it special for us judges?
-Myung-sook, get over here.
-What? Me?
Me? Why?
What's the matter?
He asked if this is the same dish
everyone else had
or if there were any special touches
added to the ones served to the judges.
I see.
Well, I wouldn't call it a special touch,
but it is slightly different
from what we served the others.
Well,
it's the doneness
of the meat and vegetables.
I took into consideration
the ages of the judges
and cooked them a bit longer.
Oh, is that so?
Producer Kim, we have the tally
of the evaluators' scores.
-We do?
-Yes.
Okay.
Let's stand by to shoot the result.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Stand by.
-Let's go.
The final result
-will be announced by Chairman Han.
-Sure.
All right.
This is making me a bit nervous.
Okay. Shall we see who won?
JUNGJAE WINS
JUNGJAE: 93, MOTTO: 89
It's a surprising result.
Okay.
Jungjae won.
The final result is…
a tie.
We tied?
Pardon?
-What's going on?
-It's a tie.
Madam Chairman.
-This is unfair!
-Producer Kim.
-Yes?
-This isn't right.
-So…
-I don't agree with this.
-This is wrong!
-Oh, okay. I understand.
I'm sorry, I'm leaving.
-Mathieu. Wait.
-No, don't bother.
Mathieu, just a moment. Let's talk.
Was this it?
This is it?
You put on this show just to do this?
You should be ashamed.
Okay then.
We can always find another judge,
but we can't end the competition in a tie.
So how about
a rematch?
A rematch?
We all
put our restaurant on the line for this.
You want a rematch
after pulling all this crap?
Do you think I'm joking around?
I can't believe the taxi fare
was 300,000 won.
I only just paid off the damn debt.
My gosh. Chef Mo.
I guess I'm not too late.
Let's do that rematch or whatever.
The thing is,
Motto's chef is absent right now, so--
Taste my food.
I'll admit defeat
if you say it's not good.
You don't need to taste
the other restaurant's food.
Wait. First of all, it's great to see you.
-But what are you saying?
-If I lose,
you can wipe out this place,
steal the recipes,
or do whatever you want.
Mo Yeon-joo.
I can't cook right away
as I need time to prepare the ingredients.
If you eat breakfast,
I'll cook for you tomorrow morning.
What do you say?
You seem quite confident,
young chef.
Let's fight fair and square.
Oh dear.
How interesting.
This should be an opportunity.
What do you think
that brazen girl will cook tomorrow?
I don't know.
I guess it doesn't matter.
We just need a clip of me spitting it out.
You only ever think about the company,
don't you?
What?
Never mind.
You should head home first.
What the heck is all this?
What have they done to my garden?
My goodness.
Those damn production people. Jeez.
I sent Myung-sook and Choon-seung home.
What are you still doing here?
So…
About the recipes and stuff…
-I'm sorry for--
-If that's what you want to talk about,
wait until we're done.
Whether you apologize or beg,
I'll hear you out after this is over.
Okay.
I heard you came by.
Yeah.
For me,
cooking good food
for the people who come to the restaurant
is all I care about.
Regardless of who it is that comes,
serving good food
cooked with care and sincerity.
That's what I do.
So don't get the wrong idea.
Let's have a drink.
I didn't expect to find a malt bar
around here.
Who says whiskey bars
should only be in Seoul?
This place…
is interesting and unique.
I don't think we're close enough
to enjoy a drink together.
What's up your sleeve?
You suddenly say you don't care
about Hansang or being the successor
and tell me to keep everything.
Then you participate in a cook-off
to protect that measly restaurant.
What is it that you're really after?
Are you okay…
with living your whole life like this?
Are you really okay with it?
What are you on about?
When Grandma passed away,
-Mother wasn't around.
-Hey.
Don't you know the company would've folded
if she hadn't traveled overseas
to win the contract?
If that had happened…
I know.
She did everything she could
her whole life
to build up the company for our sake.
It was so we could have a good life.
I know she worked like crazy
despite what people said about her.
I do know that.
But…
was it really for our sake?
Or…
was it for her sake?
You're crazy.
In any case, this isn't going to end.
Is Mother…
even happy?
I HAD A HARD TIME
FINDING SOMETHING SIMILAR, YOU DOOFUS
I'm sorry.
It's pretty.
Camera 4, zoom in.
All the cameras are ready.
I can see that.
Stand by, everyone.
Ready, action!
Thank you for coming all this way.
Take a breather, and…
I can breathe just fine.
Let's get right to it.
Can you two sit and wait
instead of bothering me?
I should help--
I can manage on my own,
so just sit and wait.
You're being distracting.
By the way, what are you going to cook?
Something you like.
Forget money. Forget big titles.
Do you actually have a passion for it?
Think about that.
Whatever it may be.
But then what would you know?
Get off.
We're out of ingredients.
What she's making is it.
-We sold out?
-We sold out!
-Myung-sook!
From now on,
I'm the ddakji queen of this area.
Myung-sook. I must be a born farmer.
-Look at this.
-You had a while to learn.
-Beom-woo, I grew this. Isn't it amazing?
-My goodness.
Wait.
Hey, Choon-seung. What is it?
Choon-seung. What did she say?
What did she…
Sir?
What?
Me?
What? Why? Why am I…
What? You want me to sit here?
-Please follow me to your seat.
-Sorry?
You might as well eat together.
Do you mind?
Why did he have them sit there?
Let me go ask what's going on.
No, wait. Let's see how things go.
You must've prepared something amazing
to cover it up like this.
I'd like to say something
before you start eating.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I didn't cook this last dish
for it to be judged.
What does that mean?
I admit defeat.
Hey, Yeon-joo.
What is this?
What do you want me to do?
Jungjae's main set meal today…
is a home-cooked spread.
It's something any Korean
would've had as a child.
Do you think I'd eat something like this?
I was taught that food should be cooked
for those who will be eating it.
I didn't know that my whole life either,
but I only realized it now.
I cooked it with all my heart
for the three of you.
I hope you enjoy it.
Try it. It's good.
You should try it, ma'am.
I can't wait to find out
what you'll be cooking today.
Today, we'll be making a snack
that children love.
It's something I often made for my sons.
Really? I'm curious.
-Are you?
-Yes.
Today, I'll show you
how to make shrimp rice jeon.
-Shrimp rice jeon?
-Yes.
Served with cabbage kimchi,
it makes for a perfect combination
and a delicious meal.
Shall we make it together?
It was good.
Especially the cabbage kimchi.
I like it.
A simple home-cooked meal.
It was nice.
Cut.
-Producer Kim.
-Yes, ma'am!
Did we get some decent footage today?
Oh, it's way better than we expected.
With good editing,
we should have people wiping away tears.
Let's wrap things up then.
Very well.
I enjoyed your antics.
As promised,
we'll shut down Jungjae.
Even if you do,
you're just going to reopen elsewhere,
aren't you?
Of course.
Even if it isn't here,
Jungjae will be wherever we are.
Just stay here.
I got the shots I needed for marketing,
and I'm pleased with the outcome.
Let's…
go for another drink next time.
It must've been a tiring few days.
Let me know…
the next time you visit your grandma.
We jumped a huge hurdle.
I'd have killed you long ago, you know.
That was random.
They say you should
give someone three chances.
Once when you stepped on my cabbage.
Once when you tricked me
with that beef rump.
And once when you pissed me off
with your ideas about plating and whatnot.
-That was--
-And then when Choon-seung came,
you fought him
and turned the restaurant upside down.
Once more then!
Now that I'm listing them,
I gave you way more than three chances.
You know, hearing all that
is making me realize
that we have a lot of memories together.
Anyway,
I'm letting you live despite all you did…
because I like you.
Pardon? What did you say?
I've grown to like you.
I feel the same.
I like you.
No.
I love you.
Oh dear,
what an awkward situation we have here.
My goodness.
Sorry. We were going to
give you guys some alone time.
Yeah, we were about to leave.
Finish up what you were doing.
Just go for it.
-Oh, forget it!
You're a match made in heaven.
You can all go home.
We're going to open as usual
starting tomorrow,
so don't be late.
-Do you think we'd be late?
-I might skip work without notice,
but I'm never late for anything.
Should we continue in the alley…
Jeez, this is seriously annoying.
-Get over here.
-What?
-Come here.
-Why are you picking on me?
You wanted to do it here, right?
Go ahead. Hurry up and do it.
My life was nothing but bitter,
but I tasted something I never had before.
Sometimes, it's so spicy
that it makes me frown,
but at times, not only is it just spicy,
but it's salty, sour, and astringent.
But ultimately, it tastes so sweet
that it even makes my blood sugar spike.
The taste that I've only come to know
because of you.
The taste of you.
AN EX-RESTAURANT CHEF'S BURGER QUEEN
I was cool only when I quit.
You're in the red again today, Young-hye.
Welcome.
How have you been?
What are you doing here?
You chose a questionable location
and an awkward price point.
If you want to sell from a truck,
you need to simplify your menu.
What's this about?
Is Hansang suing me?
No.
I also quit.
Why?
No way.
Do you have feelings for me?
What?
Don't. That makes me so uncomfortable.
I'd rather leave
than listen to this lunacy.
Wait.
If that's not it,
then why are you here?
People say you got big
because of your looks
or because you have a way with words,
but I like your cooking.
I mean it.
Forget Motto and Hansang.
I think you'll do better than them.
So I decided to work with you.
Yu-jin.
I'll take care of the food truck's
sales and marketing.
Even if it's
a small signing bonus, let's--
Please work for free for a while.
What?
But…
Aren't you afraid I might report you
for violating the labor law?
Get up here so we can get started.
JUNGJAE'S CHEF JIN MYUNG-SOOK'S COQ AU VIN
X 2ND GEN. KONGNAMUL GUKBAP COURSE!
2ND GEN. KONGNAMUL GUKBAP
Myung-sook.
People are lined up outside!
Oh my goodness.
I'm so nervous
about this collab thing or whatever.
Places in Cheongdam-dong in Seoul
are all about collaborations these days.
That's how you become
a famous chef nationwide.
Stop talking and get to work.
It's your restaurant, not mine.
Yes, Chef!
You can't come in yet…
-Hey, Myung-sook.
-Stop bothering me.
-No, look.
-Will you stop?
Hello.
Do I have to wait outside?
I've been here since dawn.
Who told my Eun-jae to wait in line?
Come sit over here.
Right here.
Thank you.
First things first,
I must congratulate you.
My Eun-jae's love has borne fruit.
Oh, right.
-Thank you.
-It's so heartwarming!
-Goodness. Well, thank you.
-Oh gosh.
Please wait a moment.
I'm a huge fan.
I can't believe you came all the way here.
You're so handsome.
Thank you.
Oh, it's cold.
If you don't mind me asking,
which high school did you go to?
Enjoy your meal.
THE LATE YOON OK-SEON
Cut.
How was that?
It was incredibly moving.
People really don't change, do they?
What?
Nothing.
I'll come again, Mom.
Don't get annoyed if I visit too often.
It's so hard to cry for the camera.
That was more than enough.
Be sure to get a close-up.
-Great work.
-Thank you. It came out great.
The first episode will air on May 12th.
Or has she changed?
Hey. Did you wrap it up?
Grab that end.
Okay. Take your time.
MALA MALATANG
Let's move it a bit to the right.
-A bit more.
-I just got here.
It's almost done.
That's perfect. Thanks.
Look at that. Not bad.
Yeah.
The owner is really pleased with it too.
That's good to know.
But is it okay to spend so much
on expenses?
We'll make it big
and turn it into a franchise.
We, as in Hansang.
Right, of course you will.
JUNGJAE
Ma'am.
Chef?
Hey.
Didn't you miss me?
I see you every day.
Hey.
I missed you,
you doofus.
I always want to be with you.
I always want to cook for you.
-Thanks to you, at last, I found
-the taste of you.
TASTEFULLY YOURS
I HOPE YOUR FOOD, LOVE, AND DAYS
ARE FULL OF SINCERITY
KANG HA-NEUL AS HAN BEOM-WOO
I HOPE THIS STORY
SERVED AS A WARM MEAL FOR YOUR LIFE
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOUR LOVE
FOR "TASTEFULLY YOURS"
KO MIN-SI
HERE'S TO YOUR DELICIOUS DAY
KIM SHIN-ROCK AS MYUNG-SOOK
ONCE YOU EAT TOGETHER, YOU'RE FAMILY!
YU SU-BIN AS CHOON-SEUNG
WHAT DOES YOUR TODAY TASTE LIKE?
BAE NA-RA AS HAN SUN-WOO
WE ALWAYS SHINE!
I ROOT FOR YOUR TASTY CHALLENGES
HONG HWA-YEON AS JANG YOUNG-HYE
FOR YOUR AND OUR DELICIOUS LIVES!
WE'RE OPEN FOR BUSINESS!
BAE YU-RAM AS YU-JIN
IT WAS DELICIOUS
OH MIN-AE AS CHAIRMAN HAN
I WISH AND HOPE YOUR EVERY DAY
IS TASTY AND SHINES BRIGHTLY!
YOON BYUNG-HEE AS VEGETABLE SHOP OWNER
TASTY FOOD, TASTY LIFE! STAY HEALTHY
LEE JOONG-OCK
WE SPENT A DELICIOUS TIME TOGETHER
I'LL NEVER FORGET JEONJU AND SAPPORO
YOO YEON-SEOK AS JEON MIN
LIKE JUNGJAE'S SET MEAL MADE WITH LOVE,
WE HOPE THIS SHOW WAS DELICIOUS
HAN JUN-HEE
KNOWING THE VALUE OF THIS JOURNEY,
DEDICATION, AND SINCERITY…
YOU HELPED CREATE "TASTEFULLY YOURS"
DIRECTOR PARK DHAN-HEE
THANKS TO PARK JI-HOON
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
A TASTE YOU MADE POSSIBLE,
A TASTE MORE SPECIAL BECAUSE OF YOU
"TASTEFULLY YOURS"!
WITH LOVE AND SINCERITY FROM THE WRITER
"TASTEFULLY YOURS" HAS CLOSED
WE WERE PLEASED TO SERVE YOU
Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim