TASTEFULLY YOURS
I'm serious. Don't come any closer.
Don't come… Don't…
Man, my head.
Oh jeez.
Where am I?
Hello? I'm locked up in here!
Help! I'm locked up!
Director Han!
Director…
Drink up!
This is for you.
This is for me.
-Yu-jin.
-Huh?
Stay here for a while. I'll let you out
when I'm back from Sapporo.
Enjoy your vacation.
Okay.
That son of a gun.
Hello? Is anybody there?
JUNGJAE'S RECIPES
The recipe book.
KONGNAMUL GUKBAP CHRONICLES
"Kongnamul Chronicles"?
No.
No, it can't be.
Hello?
Hello? I'm locked in here!
I'm in here!
Save me!
Goddammit, it's cold!
What? What do you want?
If the recipient can't come to the phone,
stop calling.
What are you,
my actual ex-girlfriend or something?
What the hell are you going on about?
Don't you know I'm returning to Motto?
You change sides as easily
as a chameleon changes colors, don't you?
Since when did that sneaky act
pass for a simple return?
Get a hold of yourself,
Director Han Beom-woo.
We might all go down together!
What did you say? "We"?
"We"?
Since when were you and I a "we"?
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
Stop talking.
Did you see what I sent you?
Look at it now!
You're talking way more
than I am right now.
Your brother screwed me over
and found my replacement himself.
We're seriously done for.
LE MURIR HEAD CHEF JEON MIN
What the heck?
Han Sun-woo's completely determined.
He's using a cheat code
to take over Hansang.
What does he have going with Han Sun-woo?
Hello? Han Beom-woo?
Hansang, Le Murir.
What are you saying?
Hey, Han Beom-woo!
Le Murir, Hansang.
This isn't
what I should be doing right now.
Exactly. This isn't the time for that.
Someone reserved a table at Motto,
and a group of Diamant--
-Seriously.
-How do you remember that?
How could I ever forget that?
-So many ridiculous things happened.
-I know.
-Even the cracker-like thing.
-Yeah.
All sorts of things happened.
You bet.
Who taught the idiot
that couldn't even hold a knife?
So come back.
Hey.
Not just for your sake.
For Murir too.
It needs you.
Do you know…
what kept me going at Murir?
It was the determination…
to secure my place at there.
And yours too.
So that…
I could come back for you.
I just…
I only waited for you.
This is Han Sun-woo from Hansang Group.
Please call me. It's an urgent matter.
I'm sorry.
I have to excuse myself.
Did something happen?
We still have to talk about
what to cook for Chef Tatsuo.
No, nothing happened.
I'll tell you later.
See you tomorrow.
You know, that guy…
I'll have a beer now.
Please, thank you.
Just drink.
Show me how you drained
all the soju in Koreatown.
TASTEFULLY YOURS
Well?
Didn't a few beers fill you with ideas
about what your chef liked?
-Yeah.
-Great. So what is it?
No.
The beer didn't help at all.
That's so odd. How can you not remember?
You chefs must've talked about
your food preferences.
He prioritized
the customers' preferences over ours.
That's why I respected him.
What?
How do you think…
I was able to attend
an expensive school like CIA
after I left the hermitage?
I got a full scholarship.
Think about it. I got a full ride.
How great of a cook must I have been?
You could say
I was born a genius.
This is new.
You're bragging so nonchalantly.
Anyway, I graduated,
and I turned down all the offers
from France and the US
and came here to Sapporo.
It was all because…
I wanted to work with Chef Tatsuo.
That was my only reason.
That's how much I respected him.
I thought he could
show me the direction
in which my cooking should take.
But that damn Diamant.
What's so great about it anyway?
Even Chef Tatsuo changed
after he got a star.
It was just one petty star.
Let's go outside.
For a change of pace.
The izakaya was just a starter, right?
What should we eat? What should we have?
Not sure.
Name whatever you want.
I'll buy you everything.
Can you handle it?
That means
you'll eat a crazy amount, right?
They have this.
"Uni ramen"?
Can they even make a profit
by adding sea urchins to noodles?
Are you going to eat here?
-Hello.
-There are many other places.
-Welcome.
-Why not check them out first?
Uni ramen, please.
Here's your uni ramen.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I hope you enjoy it.
Excuse me.
This ramen…
It's very unique.
It is, isn't it?
It's our original miso ramen recipe.
A longtime friend of mine
taught me how to make it.
A friend?
He was a chef.
Now…
he doesn't remember
this food
or even me.
Here.
Add this.
What's up with you?
Uni in ramen?
And this uni…
isn't even fresh.
What are you even thinking?
Here.
It doesn't taste like what the kid made.
Since then,
he'd sometimes bring me uni
that had almost expired
and ask me to make him ramen.
And each time,
he'd say it didn't taste like
what the kid had made
and never finished it.
So Chef Tatsuo
was a regular here.
Are you…
that kid Tatsuo talked about?
Is there a secret to the recipe?
Tatsuo wanted to eat it so badly,
but I just couldn't recreate it for him.
I felt so bad.
It's doenjang.
I mixed a bit of Korean doenjang
into Japanese miso.
That gets rid of the strong smell of uni.
It was the first staff meal I made
when I was a rookie.
That ramen, I mean.
You cooked ramen for the staff?
We cooked and sold
the most extravagant and expensive foods,
but we ate instant food to get by.
I was young and felt it wasn't fair.
So I added some uni
we were going to throw out
to ramen and made a staff meal.
Everyone loved it.
I think that was when I first realized
how joyful and meaningful it is
to cook for someone.
I did get an earful from Chef Tatsuo
that day though.
He was so upset with me for making it,
so why is he craving it?
I wonder why.
But there's a thing
about stubborn old men.
Hey.
You know what to make now!
What?
The dish your chef, that old man, likes.
If he went everywhere looking for it,
doesn't that mean he really wants it?
And you said you can make it.
How's that?
Isn't it much more useful
walking and talking with me
than sitting around with that guy?
I'd better get some uni first.
Let's meet early tomorrow morning, okay?
Okay.
Yeon-joo.
Yeah?
Never mind.
It's really hard to love a woman
who's crazy about cooking.
Hey.
I'll kill you if you're late tomorrow.
Oh, come on.
THE LE MURIR PUNK
THIS IS HAN BEOM-WOO, LET'S MEET
It was stupid of me to trust that moron.
I think it was somewhere here.
What is this place?
No way.
Even if it's a retro-themed restaurant…
JUNGJAE
Oh dear.
We cleaned the place
and prepared everything for tomorrow,
and it's still early.
It's really nice and chill
to open just for lunch.
Beom-woo's actually quite smart.
-We sold out again. Yes, yes.
-That's right.
Well, that's all good, but…
Oh, you want to know
when Beom-woo and Chef Mo will return?
I'm sure they'll be back this week.
They'll come back when they're ready.
That's not what I meant.
Do you think Yu-jin left for Seoul?
Are you kidding me?
I'm sure he did.
He probably left long ago.
Did you expect him
to live here forever then?
What's with you?
Get a grip, Myung-sook.
You're acting like
you're ready to give that Casano--
You're acting like you're ready
to give him everything you have.
Why would I give him everything I have?
It's just that he came
all the way from Seoul to help us out,
but then he disappeared without a word.
I'm just showing concern
for a fellow human.
Concern?
Why would you worry about him at all?
How ridiculous. Are you afraid
he might be locked up somewhere?
What nonsense is that?
What are you even saying?
Can't I worry about someone if I want to?
Oh, whatever.
If you like him that much,
move to Seoul and live with him.
Congratulations.
You'll be a Seoul lady now.
Who gave you the right
to choose whom I live with?
Why would I do that?
-Forget it! Don't follow me.
-Why would I leave family and friends?
-I'm not talking to you.
-Stop right there.
-Talk to me.
-Don't follow me!
-I'm not following you.
-Ms. Seoul!
-Congratulations.
-I think she just mentioned Yu-jin.
Wait.
Both Beom-woo and Yu-jin
came here to steal the recipes,
but one won't tell where he is
and another is missing?
Oh, whatever.
I'll get the recipes,
no matter what.
Here's your food.
Director Han!
Director?
Oh, Choon-seung. Hello, sir.
What?
Don't call me sir.
I'm way younger than you.
Where's Beom-woo?
Where did that punk go?
Beom-woo said you can rest here
while he's away in Sapporo.
He said to consider it a vacation.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Open up. Let me out!
-Are we being chummy now?
-No, we're not.
See, the thing is…
I really need to use the bathroom.
There's a bucket in there.
I have a really bad headache right now.
I have a bad hangover and need to puke.
-Let me do just that.
-That's why I brought you my gukbap.
Our kongnamul gukbap
is the best cure for hangovers.
Enjoy the food and leave a nice review.
All right, rest up.
What was that?
I'll break
every single bottle of liquor in here!
Why you…
Don't you dare touch them.
I'll crush you into pieces, Casanova!
So let me step outside just for a moment.
-Please?
-Damn it.
I'll give you just one minute.
Okay.
-I knew you'd do this.
-Wait.
-Go back inside.
-Please.
-Come on.
What on earth are you doing here?
Chef Jang.
He kidnapped me and locked me up.
Hey. I've seen you before.
I remember.
You're Beom-woo's ex, aren't you?
No, wait.
I need the bathroom. I'm serious.
Use the bucket.
-Hey, are you leaving?
-Let's go.
Are you really leaving?
Two days.
I was locked up for two whole days.
So you're saying
that lunatic betrayed us…
Yes.
…and went to Sapporo to get a girl?
That's right.
Damn it.
Has he seriously gone mad for that woman?
That's what I'm saying.
What about the recipes then?
I need them by the weekend.
The weekend?
What's this?
"Hansang and Le Murir's
mergers and acquisitions proposal"?
"Le Murir head chef"?
SOUS-CHEF
Hello? I'm busy right now.
Let's talk later.
Wait, Chef.
I called because we have
a special reservation this weekend.
What?
Two foreigners, two Koreans,
one with shellfish allergy,
and one requested
the chef's tasting menu with pairings.
I have a feeling they're…
No way.
Could they be Diamant inspectors?
Diamant inspectors?
Thank you for taking care of my husband.
Not at all.
Excuse me.
What brings you here?
At this late hour and without Yeon-joo.
I'll get right to the point.
You're pretty close to Hansang Group…
No.
You're pretty close to
Managing Director Han Sun-woo.
Do you know him?
Oh.
Han Beom-woo, Han Sun-woo.
Are you…
I don't like it either,
but we are what you think we are.
It's a pleasure.
I guess it's either fate
or the industry is just really small.
It could be neither.
What does that mean?
I heard you're replacing
Chef Jang Young-hye
as head chef at La Lecel.
Well, not permanently.
I'll be helping out temporarily.
I think Hansang and Murir
can give each other what they want.
You start with the recipes,
then slowly steal the chefs one by one.
Meanwhile,
Le Murir gradually goes out of business.
That's how help is usually given,
isn't it?
You know very well.
I guess you've done it a lot.
I see you're not denying it.
Because I have no reason
to tell you anything.
I wondered why
you wanted to see me in private.
Did you ask to see me just for this?
Of course not.
Why are you trying to take
Yeon-joo back to Le Murir?
You shook hands with Hansang,
and you're La Lecel's new head chef.
You don't need Le Murir anymore.
Watch what you say.
What about you?
Why are you lurking around Yeon-joo?
You're an heir to a fortune,
yet you're working at a restaurant
in the countryside.
Isn't that more suspicious?
I'll head back inside if you're done.
CONTACTS
CHAIRMAN HAN
UNI IN SALTWATER FROM RUSSIA
Welcome.
-Hello.
-We have a lot of fresh goods today.
Oh, uni.
They're good and fresh.
-I'll take this.
-Great.
Your call cannot be connected
and will go to voicemail after the beep.
What the heck is this guy doing?
-Thank you.
-Sure. Thank you.
Let's cook for Chef Tatsuo.
Okay. Shall I get started?
Must you enter so chaotically?
Man, that really…
It really hurts.
My goodness, you're such a troublemaker.
Why couldn't I reach you all morning?
You show up now
when the sun's high in the sky?
I had a good reason, okay?
Look what I picked up on the way here.
What is this?
Korean doenjang.
Where on earth did you get this?
I'd been wondering where to get it.
You see,
I have pretty amazing connections.
They're scattered all over the world,
and I can get anything I need
with just one call.
It's a piece of cake.
Good job.
You adorable thing.
Don't ruin my hair.
Hey. Move out of the way.
Move.
I'll clean it up.
Why are there so many pills?
It's nothing.
They're mine.
I got a prescription
because I was stressed with work.
I'm trying to go without.
What's all this?
Have you decided on what to cook?
Yeah.
What is it?
Ramen.
Ramen?
It's the food Chef Tatsuo wants to eat.
Yeah.
It's definitely ramen.
Ramen, huh?
You'll help me, right?
Of course, I will.
What should I do first?
-We should make the broth first.
-Yeah, we should.
It's been so long since we did this.
Gosh, it's hot.
Man, it's hot
standing in front of the stove.
Take off your coat then.
Why complain when you're layered?
Jeez, that's hot!
You're still bad at this.
You need to remove all this.
Is this it?
-Uni ramen?
-Yeah.
Let's taste it.
It tastes just like it did back then.
-Try the noodles too.
-Okay.
Chef Tatsuo eats ramen?
Ramen?
Don't knock it until you try it.
I wanted to prepare something
you wanted to eat.
I made this for you and you alone, Chef.
I hope you enjoy it.
Sophie.
So… Sophie?
Yes, Chef.
There was something…
I wanted to say to you if we met again.
I know it's late…
but about the pufferfish incident
back then…
I failed to stand up for you.
I'm sorry, Sophie.
No, Chef.
That was my own decision.
Sophie…
I'm so sorry.
Chef, there's something
I want to tell you.
What will happen to us now?
It won't be easy running Murir.
There's no point in worrying.
Will we manage without Chef Tatsuo?
I'm sure he'll get better.
Let's believe so and wait.
Let's do what we can.
Why did he want us
to leave the room anyway?
Everyone.
I have an important announcement to make.
-What? An announcement?
-An important announcement?
What is this?
Wait, this is…
CONFIRMATION OF OWNERSHIP TRANSFER
FOR FRENCH DINING RESTAURANT LE MURIR
A change in Le Murir's ownership?
Change in ownership?
I, the head chef of Le Murir,
will take over the restaurant
and move it a step further
as the new chef-owner.
I'm doing this for Chef Tatsuo--
"For Chef Tatsuo"?
Do you mean that?
You're doing it for Chef Tatsuo?
I'm sure you noticed it too.
I'm talking about Murir.
It might've looked great on the outside,
but it was festering on the inside.
Debts were piling up.
And with Chef Tatsuo in that condition…
You know just as well
that fine dining
is all show and no substance.
So what?
To save the restaurant,
I had to bring in an outside investor.
What's this then?
Explain this.
It's the medicine
Chef Tatsuo should have with each meal.
Why did you throw it out?
I'll explain everything later.
No, tell me now.
The medicine he was taking…
It's nothing. They're mine.
The truth is,
Chef Tatsuo threw them out.
He didn't like how the meds
numbed his taste buds.
CLASS 1 PRESCRIPTION DRUG FOR ALZHEIMER'S
He was also afraid
that rumors would spread in the field.
I turned a blind eye
because I wanted him to get through it.
That way,
Le Murir wouldn't shut down and--
No.
You had to earn time
so you could sell the restaurant.
Mo Yeon-joo.
No one has the right
to talk to me that way, not even you.
I thought this was
the best option for Murir--
The best for whom?
Sous-chef Hiroshi.
Assistants Yuichi and Lena.
Hiroshi and Yuichi can't repay their loans
if they miss just one month's salary.
And Lena lives with her parents.
She's the sole earner.
What would you have done?
If your restaurant
was about to close down,
if you couldn't pay your staff…
would you have watched and done nothing?
Even so,
what you did can never be justified.
I'm sorry, Yeon-joo.
I don't care what you say.
The M&A with Hansang…
is a done deal.
That was a moving speech.
It would be great
if life could go the way you wish,
but most of the time it doesn't, does it?
You haven't…
heard the news yet, have you?
We'll take a majority vote on this item.
The M&A of Le Murir…
Man, those early flights are exhausting.
Why are you here?
I'm here to get that agenda thrown out.
What?
How will you do that?
Oh, you haven't heard?
I've been reinstated to the board.
I've already talked it out
with Chairman Han.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Here are all the receipts from my travels.
Reimburse me.
I was in Sapporo on a business trip.
I don't have much time…
so I'll exercise my rights
as a shareholder.
This M&A
will not be happening.
NOTICE ON REJECTION OF HANSANG'S
M&A PROPOSAL FOR LE MURIR
Rejected.
So…
simply put,
Le Murir will not be sold off
to Hansang.
That's basically it.
How…
Keep that if you want.
I have more copies.
Because of you, we…
Our restaurant…
Do you have any idea what you just did?
I don't.
But I do know
that stealing a sick man's medication
and taking what's theirs
without their knowledge
are really nasty things to do.
Hey.
Did you just hit me?
I'll punch you right back.
-Don't.
-Stop.
Let go of me!
-What are you doing?
-Stop it!
Stop!
Why are you only angry with me?
That's enough!
Come inside, all of you.
Sophie.
Did you find it?
What you want to cook.
No, not yet.
But I think I will soon.
Jeon Min.
I sincerely apologize.
I'll…
leave the restaurant.
And if you wish to take legal action…
I know how much Murir means to you.
I've never doubted that.
However,
Murir…
isn't a restaurant
that can just be sold off.
Let's find another solution together.
I'll try to change as well.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I needed Murir.
I thought
that was the only way to get you back
after you'd given up…
your dream, your food, everything for me.
I said I regretted letting you go…
and I meant that.
That I wouldn't have managed without you.
I meant that too.
I know.
But I didn't give up.
I never gave up.
My dream, my cooking.
Just like I told Chef Tatsuo…
I feel like I'm finally
working toward it all.
Time has passed.
And you and I…
are both in different places now.
Just like how Jungjae
and Murir are different.
But I won't forget…
the Mo Yeon-joo
and the Jeon Min from back then.
I'll remember them both.
Take care.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for flying with Han Air.
This plane is bound for Incheon.
We will now demonstrate
the safety features…
Please put your seat
in an upright position.
So…
Please stow away your tray table.
Please put your seat
in an upright position.
-About…
-What now? What is it?
What do you want to know?
You're so restless like a constipated dog.
What?
A constipated dog?
I just wanted to ask
what you two talked about earlier.
I was just a little curious, that's all.
I'd expect nothing less from you.
I'm not telling you.
Hey, I'm not done talking to you.
What should I do about this habit of--
Can you please be quiet?
Sorry.
Hey.
Do you think I'll stop asking
if you lean on my shoulder like this and--
This is really comfy.
Have a pleasant sleep, ma'am.
You owe me
for getting you reinstated to the board.
JUNGJAE
Myung-sook.
We're back!
My gosh.
-Oh my gosh!
-No, wait.
How have you been?
I've been good.
Let's stop. I'm dizzy.
Why were you away for so long?
Where's Choon-seung? Is he inside?
Don't even mention that fool.
What's the matter now?
We had a little argument last night,
and he didn't show up for work today
just because of that.
-Goodness gracious.
-I had to do everything on my own today.
It was so much work.
What did you say that made him skip work?
Yu-jin suddenly disappeared
without a word.
So I asked Choon-seung
when Yu-jin would come back,
and he suddenly flew into a rage.
What's up with him?
What the heck? What's going on?
Hey, Yu-jin.
Hey, Yu-jin! Are you all right?
Beom-woo.
It's me.
What? Who's in there?
Choon-seung.
Choon-seung?
Let me out. Hurry.
You scared me.
What are you doing in there?
I got duped.
By whom?
That Casanova
and your ex-girlfriend.
My ex-girlfriend?
Hug me.
-I need warmth.
-Damn it.
I forget it all the time.
Oh my gosh!
Mo Yeon-joo! Where are you going?
What's the matter with you?
What is it? Is something wrong?
Why are you running
all over the place this morning?
No, nothing's wrong.
What are you stuttering for?
I didn't.
-When did I stutter…
-Whatever. Be quiet.
We're going grocery shopping,
so watch the restaurant.
Clean up as well.
-You're going out?
-Get a grip.
See you later!
Don't be gone for too long.
I'll be lonely.
The recipe book.
The recipes. Damn it.
Goddammit.
What the…
No way.
JUNGJAE
For goodness' sake.
LAST NIGHT
The chef's recipe book is in there.
Do we really have to go this far?
Of course.
You said the inspectors are coming.
There's not much time.
That's true,
but this is illegal.
You like breaking the law. It's fine.
How dare you say that about me?
When did I do such a thing?
-Yu-jin.
-Let go.
This is what they get for locking me up.
Oh my.
Come on. Help me find it.
I found the recipes.
What?
I found them.
The recipes Director Han mentioned.
BROTHER'S VEGETABLE SHOP
HAN BEOM-WOO
-Let me have a taste test.
-Yes, Chef.
They're Diamant inspectors, so stay sharp.
HAN BEOM-WOO
Focus, everyone.
-Yes, Chef.
Come on, pick up.
Pick up the phone.
Answer the damn phone!
TASTEFULLY YOURS
The Diamant inspectors
visited Motto yesterday,
and the feedback
was apparently very positive.
Wrap things up there.
This is your workplace,
not that restaurant.
I have to tell her today, no matter what.
I want to hear your story too.
It's really hard to tell.
Han Beom-woo, you dare deceive me?
I realized that sincerity
means more than money
and that people are more important.
Han Sun-woo!
Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim