TASTEFULLY YOURS
I'm an orphan.
What?
I was a baby, so I don't even remember.
But apparently, I was abandoned
at a hermitage at the base of a mountain.
All I remember of my childhood
is the mountain, the forest,
the temple, and monks.
That's about it.
Then I got older,
and I fell in love with cooking.
That's how I made my living.
Then I studied at CIA
and ended up in Japan.
At Le Murir, which you also know of.
That's where I met Min.
I liked him a lot.
It was the first time
anyone had treated me nicely.
I see, but…
I didn't want to know all that.
Anyway, now,
you're broken up.
So…
why is he here?
He wants me to come back to Murir.
Are you going to go?
Why would I go?
Our restaurant's doing so well.
Right.
We might take over
the entire neighborhood.
BAEKSU INN
JEON MIN
Yeah?
Yeon-joo.
About the thing
I wanted to talk to you about…
The truth is…
Chef Tatsuo is very ill.
This might be…
your last chance to see him.
I'll wait for you.
TASTEFULLY YOURS
Where have you been all this time?
What are you talking about?
She went to Sapporo?
Yeah.
Do you think Chef Mo
abandoned us and the restaurant?
Neither of you showed up on time,
so we were getting ready
to open without you guys.
Then I found this in the kitchen.
Something urgent came up,
so I'm going to Sapporo.
I need you to take over
Jungjae's new kitchen for a while.
I'm sorry I only had time
to leave this short note.
Han Beom-woo. Wait until I contact you.
But…
What is this?
Isn't that an earthenware pot?
The earthenware pot stand.
-The earthenware pot stand.
-This isn't it.
-This is the stand.
-Right.
The earthenware pot stand.
This is too heavy.
What in the world did she leave here?
Hey, I found it!
-Look.
-What is it?
What's this?
JUNGJAE MANUAL
Jungjae manual.
Number one.
Jungjae is a restaurant
that changes with the seasons.
The menus shift
to incorporate seasonal produce.
But we welcome customers
with an unchanging heart.
Beom-woo.
I really will kill you
if you smoke outside again.
Number two.
The seasonal vegetables
growing in the garden
may not always be pretty.
It's because we don't use
chemical fertilizers or pesticides.
They're organic.
Choon-seung.
Wash your hands after being in the garden,
-or I'll wring one of them off.
-That's good.
Darn it.
Number three.
Buy all the other ingredients
at Nambu Market
-where it's guaranteed to be fresh.
-How much is this?
And Myung-sook, don't get into fights
with the elders there.
This isn't right.
-You can't do that.
-What was that?
-Leave it. No.
-Why not?
That doesn't matter.
I'm leaving you with all the recipes
that contain all of Jungjae's past.
Myung-sook, please be Jungjae's head chef
for the time being.
Number four.
How many more are there?
Oh gosh.
It ends at number 135.
This means she doesn't trust us.
This reeks of distrust.
Should I have just given them time off?
Has it been five years?
Yeah.
About that incident…
What?
When I took the fall
for what you messed up and quit?
You're all aware of the customers
we're serving today, right?
We're serving Diamant inspectors.
All because of you!
Given Chef Tatsuo's poor health,
I'm afraid the truth might shock him.
I won't bring it up.
I didn't mess up.
I made a mistake.
I'm only going to visit Chef Tatsuo.
Why did she go? What did she go there for?
And why can't I call her?
They seemed to have a pretty deep past.
Sapporo.
Le Murir.
Also,
why did she keep it a secret
about CIA and Le Murir?
Get lost.
A man fights with his abilities.
I'll show you what I'm capable of.
AFTER HARDSHIP COMES PLEASURE
JUNGJAE'S MEAL OF THE DAY
AUTUMN VEGGIE BUGAK,
SHORT-NECKED CLAM SOUP,
MUSHROOM SEOPSANJEOK,
STEAMED EGG, CABBAGE KIMCHI
& WOLGWACHAE
Watch me.
2. YAKBAP-LIKE RICE
DATES, CHESTNUTS, RAISINS…
On three, say, "We can do it."
One, two, three.
-We can do it!
-The bill, please.
-Yes, sir.
Here's your food.
Chef, two more set meals.
Yes, Chef. Oh no.
That's me. I'm the chef.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
This isn't cooked properly.
That can't be.
It's not cooked.
I'm sorry about that. Excuse me.
Chef.
Apparently, it's undercooked.
Oh no.
But I followed the recipe.
Just hurry up and make a new one.
-A new one? Okay.
-Another one. Quick.
-I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Oh dear.
We'll make a new one for you.
It's okay. We'll just pay.
This place is a mess.
It won't take long.
Excuse me?
I can do it in no time.
We can't do it.
Chef Mo overestimated us big time.
Right?
I see.
This says five, not three.
Take a look. Is this a three or a five?
Am I the only one who's confused?
Is it just me?
-It was five minutes, not three.
-Chef Mo.
I miss you, Chef Mo.
When will you be back? Hurry back.
Chef Mo.
HANSANG FOOD FIELD
Let's wrap up the meeting.
-Good night.
You can't go in.
The meeting's not over yet.
Can I have a word with you,
Managing Director Han?
Can you all excuse us?
I heard an outrageous rumor.
-It's not a rumor.
-What?
It's true.
We found your replacement
as La Lecel's head chef.
How could you do that
without a word to me?
Let's be honest. You don't have
what it takes to get three stars.
You're crazy.
I went to a lot of trouble
to scout this chef.
Why don't you work under them
and learn a thing or two?
You're a total psychopath.
Do you think I'll back down that easily?
What are you going to do then?
What are you going to do?
Unbelievable.
Compared to you, Beom-woo was an angel.
Thanks for the compliment.
If you don't like the idea, quit.
Prepare to return to Motto.
What? Just like that? What about La Lecel?
I don't care about La Lecel anymore.
Tell the team and prepare for the move.
Are you just going to let this happen?
Shouldn't you do something?
What do you mean?
You have to explain so I can--
Let's see who wins.
It's not too late for us.
We can go back.
Was that a ghost?
Show yourself.
No.
That must've been a water deer.
Oh yeah?
-Mr. Manager.
-Did you forget something?
You have a visitor.
Who?
Hey, you. What are you doing here?
"Hey, you"? He said he was older than you.
Yeah, he is older.
Hello. I'm Beom-woo's neighborhood friend.
My name is Lee Yu-jin.
Nice to meet you. I'm Shin Choon-seung.
You look pretty familiar.
I was on my way to the market,
and he suddenly stopped me to say hi.
He said he saw me
at the food truck festival.
-Right.
-What exactly did you say?
You said something
about my striking beauty.
I said, "How could I forget
a lady of such beauty?"
Are you into older women?
Sorry?
Beom-woo.
How have you been?
I missed you so much, Beom-woo.
Didn't you miss me?
You cheeky punk.
You'd better watch it.
You're older?
You're absolutely unbelievable.
You seemed to be struggling,
so I came to help you.
Okay, but why are you
an older friend of mine?
We can't just take it back
when that's what we told them, can we?
We're planning to reopen Motto.
That damn Motto.
Damn Motto.
Sir, I noticed that this place
has some amazing recipes.
If we can just take them
and tweak them
to make them more luxurious--
Yu-jin.
We should
stop doing things like
stealing recipes from other restaurants.
What?
Now you want to be the good guy?
After everything you've done?
I'm not joking.
It feels like my head is about to explode
every single day.
I laugh, cry, then laugh and cry again.
Every day is total chaos.
Forget all that.
At this point, it's all or nothing.
Hey, everyone. Do you know why he's here?
-Come over here.
-What's going on?
Do you know what he came here for?
-He came here to take all the recipes.
-No…
He came here to steal all the recipes!
-Beom-woo?
-What's he saying?
-Is this true?
-Well…
Don't just stutter.
-Is it a yes or no?
-Chef Mo!
Sir, why did you stop mid-sentence?
Huh? What?
What?
-What?
-Me?
Yeah, you, Yu-jin.
Who told you to stand straight?
Stick your head in here.
Come on.
You little punk.
Mr. Seoul!
You offered to help out.
Where are you and what are you doing?
Beom-woo, is that how I taught you?
-No.
-You deserve another noogie.
Here's one more.
Here's another noogie. There you go.
You must be best friends.
-I'll put him right in his place.
-Goodness.
I'll give you a hundred noogies today.
-Don't be too harsh.
-Come here, you.
What's this?
Can't you tell? It's plum extract
that we use instead of sugar.
Oh, plum extract.
-And then--
-What's this?
This?
-This is--
-Yu-jin.
Why do you need to know that?
Hey.
You brat.
-I can ask if I'm curious, can't I?
-That's right.
I can't help but be curious
when I witness such great talent.
Oh, my arms aren't strong enough.
Oh, give that to me.
This is ginger liquor.
What are you doing?
Did we use ginger for this?
I use ordinary cooking wine,
but our chef wrote in her recipe book
that I should use
the ginger liquor she made.
-A recipe book?
-Hang on.
Where did the book go?
I put it right here.
-What? The recipe book?
-What on earth?
Where…
What's this recipe book?
-What is it?
-Where did it go?
-That's so strange.
-Where did you put the book?
Myung-sook, here's the soy sauce.
I'll open it for you.
What was that cold, indifferent touch?
Ta-da!
Did you make this, Myung-sook?
-No, our chef did.
-I see.
-"Myung-sook"?
-It has a different color.
The color and smell are nothing like
what you'd get at a store.
Here. Have a taste for yourself.
You can't let him
taste our secret soy sauce.
You're feeding it to him?
-Isn't it good? Amazing, right?
-Yes.
Our chef made it
with 200-year-old aged soy sauce.
200 years?
It's made in Joseon, huh?
How are you so witty?
Are you a comedian?
I'm a comedian from Seoul.
-You're hilarious.
-I'm not.
Are you there?
Report what you have so far.
Okay. So…
I think I can get the recipes today
if I'm lucky.
Apparently, there's a recipe book.
Bring it with you. How's Beom-woo?
He's out of sorts.
Okay. I'll get back as soon as possible.
Yes.
Okay, got it.
Damn it.
What should I do with that punk?
What should I do?
"Myung-sook"?
Is he out of his mind?
That goes for Chef Jin too.
She fell for the way he talked to her.
I can't stand him! I want him gone!
Oh my gosh.
Should we
get rid of him?
Like forever?
Why would you say that?
What are you thinking?
That's not what I meant.
You're a genius.
I'm the alcohol expert!
Are we allowed to do this?
He's your close friend.
I'll be waiting.
Call me.
I'm doing my very best
to protect Jungjae.
YEON-JOO
Text me back when you get this.
Beom-woo, I don't think we should do this.
I don't hate him enough
to want to get rid of him.
Hey, hey.
Are you okay with an outsider
causing trouble at our restaurant?
Are you okay with that?
Are you going to let him do that?
You're an outsider too.
I'm a local.
-Get a hold of yourself.
-Yeah, okay.
Identify the enemy.
Just remember this, Choon-seung.
-Get him completely drunk.
-Completely drunk.
-Pickle him.
-Sink him.
Got it.
Don't you worry.
I have a secret weapon.
The Shin Choon-seung collection.
Welcome.
Take a seat.
Oh, silly me.
JUNGJAE'S RECIPES
All right, so these are
Shin Choon-seung's special masterpieces
made with dedication and care.
My traditional moju and homemade liquor.
This moju has a whole new level to it.
And this homemade liquor.
It will shock you.
Here. Let me pour you a shot.
The first shot will take you to paradise.
The second to hell.
And the third…
Would you like to see for yourself?
Come on.
Let's go.
-Cheers.
Cheers!
-Cheers!
Here, cheers!
I'm getting drunk.
Man, I'm getting drunk.
Here comes more alcohol.
It's time to start over.
Start over!
What is this, you ask?
I made this with all my pent-up fury
after my father chewed me out.
Choon-seung.
Let's drink from a glass.
Oh, from a glass?
A glass sounds perfect!
Sounds good!
Here.
As much as I love you.
-Here.
-No.
-Just a little.
Now it's Choon-seung's turn.
All right!
Down it all, Choon-seung. Come on.
Bottoms up!
You're such a lightweight.
I'm Shin Choon-seung.
Well done.
-I did well?
-Good job.
I know you're trying.
The hangover will keep him there
for at least three days.
-Let's go.
-Yeah, get out here.
You need to get out.
You're the one who's still in there.
We taught him a lesson,
so he'll stay far away
from our restaurant.
-And from Myung-sook.
-Yes!
You clever punk.
Good job, bro!
Yeah, baby!
I'll let you off this once.
Hello?
Where are you?
Are you in Sapporo?
Hey, do you know how worried I was?
You should've told me
if you were going somewhere.
How are things at the restaurant?
Is everything okay?
That's the only thing you care about.
Don't you want to know how I'm doing?
You picked up, so I guess you're fine.
Forget it.
Stop worrying about the restaurant
and hurry back.
Yeon-joo.
All right. Bye.
Who was that?
Hello?
Did you hang up?
You hung up on me?
-Hey!
-What?
It's that punk's voice.
Why is she with him in Japan?
This isn't good.
She's there with him, huh?
This…
is not…
I've seen those eyes before.
What are you doing? This is confinement.
-Listen carefully.
-Okay.
It's not confinement.
-It's not confinement.
-Okay.
It's a vacation. Say it. "Vacation."
-Vacation.
Yu-jin, stay here for a while.
I'll let you out
when I'm back from Sapporo.
Enjoy your vacation.
-Choon-seung.
-Yeah?
You're the hero
who protected our restaurant.
Come on, I'm no hero.
You are.
What's a hero doing, sitting out here?
Stand up, you brave soul.
There you go.
-Choon-seung.
-Yeah.
-You know what?
-What?
I need to go to Sapporo.
Oh, Sapporo!
-My hero!
-Yeah!
I must ask.
Do you have money?
Hang on.
You barely know me
and you're asking for money?
Hang up, punk.
Why that…
It's for love!
I love her.
That's why.
Don't you think I should go to Sapporo?
You're cool.
You're a thousand times cooler
than that guy, Beom-woo!
You must go.
I'll get you the money.
-Trust me.
-I trust you.
-Trust me!
-I trust you!
I trust you!
You thief!
You bastard!
No, Father, wait. Hear me out.
Stop right there, you punk!
I'm sorry, Beom-woo!
Stop right there!
My goodness…
Don't touch me there.
He's such an embarrassment.
I'm embarrassed to death.
What an embarrassment!
Damn it.
You have to eat
-for your health, sir.
-No.
No, this isn't it!
This isn't the dish I was talking about.
This isn't it.
Who…
are you?
I asked you a question!
Who are you?
What a strange person.
He once was the best chef in the world,
but now…
He has dementia.
He refuses
to eat anything
unless it's what he wants to eat.
I thought seeing you
might revive his memories
before his condition worsened.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think of how you'd feel.
This might be the last time I see him.
Aren't you tired?
How's Chef Tatsuo?
Is he still unable to eat anything?
He can't eat the hospital food.
I cook something for each meal,
but it's no use.
I just don't know
what it is that he wants.
His condition is getting worse
because he's not eating.
Deep-fried butterbur shoots?
That was the first thing I made him.
Apparently, it wasn't it.
What is it that he wants to eat?
He might like what you make.
He doesn't even recognize me.
He might not,
but he'll remember your food.
He loved your food, Sophie.
I don't mean to put pressure on you.
Do you want to drop by Murir
while you're here?
What's the point?
It's where we used to work.
It might be
our last time together.
How does it feel?
Excuse me.
It's good.
Make them even.
Understood.
Am I late?
You're fine.
All right.
You're all aware of the customers
we're serving today, right?
We're serving Diamant inspectors.
Each dish will define Le Murir's name.
Let's focus and do our best.
I'm counting on you all.
Let's get to work!
-Yes, Chef.
Looks good to go.
-I'll bring them to Table One.
-To Table One.
What's the matter?
There seems to have been a problem
in the preparation step.
That was a close call.
Who was it?
Who prepared it?
Who prepared the pufferfish?
I…
It was…
It was me.
Do you know what you've done?
With this incident,
everything I've built and worked for
went down the drain.
Three stars down the drain
and Murir's reputation completely ruined!
All because of you.
All because of you!
I'll take responsibility.
I'll take full responsibility…
and resign.
It's still the same.
It's gotten old.
And now I've become the head chef.
I wanted to change the whole place.
But you know what Chef Tatsuo's like.
We laughed and cried here.
So much happened.
You and I both
learned a lot from Chef Tatsuo.
Right?
Let's look.
-For what?
-Something Chef Tatsuo would eat.
Let's do whatever we can.
I'll start running Murir soon.
So being a head chef wasn't enough.
Now you want to be a chef-owner too?
Did you get Chef Tatsuo's approval?
You saw what state he was in.
After what happened to him,
Murir went through a rough patch.
Someone has to run the place
with a big picture--
Being a chef and running the business
won't be easy.
Why don't you come back and work with me?
That way I can make up for
what I did wrong--
We ended that discussion in Korea.
It's not over for me.
We can start over.
Hey.
What on earth are you doing
in that rundown restaurant?
I get why you're there
doing what you're doing.
But Murir suits you better,
and it needs you.
Stop.
You speak too freely just because you can.
Did you call our restaurant rundown?
So what if you work at
a fancy three-star restaurant
when all that comes of your mouth is crap?
You…
What are you doing here, you doofus?
What about the restaurant?
I left our restaurant
to our trusted family.
Before you worry about our restaurant…
This man here…
Should I say, your former colleague?
You should worry about him, Chef.
He keeps trying to cross the line.
There's something you don't know.
We already…
crossed the line.
Stop talking nonsense.
I'll be in touch when I think of a dish.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey, Chef.
I came here to ask you something.
Hello? Hey.
How are you not slipping?
Hey, wait up.
I came to ask you something!
What do you want to know? What is it?
We held hands, kissed, and dated, okay?
Then I got stabbed in the back
because I was pathetic.
So what?
That's random.
You said you wanted to ask me something.
Why didn't you tell me
you worked at Le Murir?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
You should've stayed at Jungjae.
Why did you come all the way here?
Why do you think I'm here?
I came to get you.
I was worried you wouldn't come back.
Who wouldn't go back?
Me? I'd leave Jungjae?
You were going to come back, right?
I know you're not the kind of person
to ditch your restaurant.
I know that.
But coming to a place like this
and reminiscing about the past
can get you all emotional and whatnot.
That's when you need a friend
who can give you objective advice…
I came because I missed you!
Did your heart skip a beat?
As if.
Come on. Where are you going?
Why did you come to Sapporo?
To tie up loose ends.
I want to sort out some things.
Sort out what things?
You don't need to know.
Oh, I know a good takoyaki place.
Do you want to go?
Forget it.
Can I help you? We're closed for the day.
Who are you? I don't recognize you.
Pardon?
Did they hire new staff already?
Damn it.
Will this do?
What brings you here?
I used to be the head chef here.
I'm here for my stuff.
It won't take long.
You can't go inside.
We're not allowed to admit strangers.
Strangers?
Look up Jang Young-hye.
I'm a chef that's prettier
than most actresses.
Haven't you heard of me?
Oh, that's you.
Managing Director Han told us
to put some stuff in the storage room.
One moment.
What? Storage room?
-Does he think I'll back out that easily?
-Did you finish prepping the ingredients?
I'm Jang Young-hye.
Who is he bringing in as my replacement?
What the heck?
"Hansang and Le Murir's
mergers and acquisitions proposal"?
I think he's asleep.
He didn't eat anything today either.
Should we head to the market first?
We could go to Nijo Market.
Or if we want seafood,
we can go to Kitano Gurume.
It's where we often went.
It's uncomfortable.
It's uncomfortable?
Want me to fix your seat belt?
No.
What you're doing
makes me feel uncomfortable.
What am I doing?
You're being nice to me
like you were in the past.
Then is it fine
if it's no longer in the past?
Let's get going.
That could've been dangerous.
Are you crazy? Do you have a death wish?
Mo Yeon-joo, get a hold of yourself.
How could you leave that behind?
Did you forget something?
Me. You left me behind.
Don't forget me.
This takoyaki is really famous.
Do you want some?
You're a pretty rough driver.
Would you like to try some Hanasaki gani?
Oh, Hanasaki crab.
It's delicious.
-It looks good.
-Indeed.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
It's huge.
It looks good.
It's delicious.
It's nice.
They must be in peak season.
Look at the kegani, horsehair crabs.
The crab miso soup
we had for our staff meal
would be perfect on a day like this.
We'd make the bisque soup first,
then make soup with horsehair crab.
You were the fastest
at making bisque at Murir.
It looks easy, but it's complicated.
It is.
You have to flambé the cognac
and boil it over and over again.
What? Bisque?
How did you know I love a good bisque?
I had bisque with toast
when I studied abroad.
What about bisque?
We need to figure out
what Chef Tatsuo will want to eat.
You do? What does he like?
I don't know.
I've seen him cook for others,
but I've never really seen him eat.
Jeon Min, long time no see.
It has been a while.
How's Chef Tatsuo doing?
Is he still not eating anything?
-No.
-I see.
I wonder when I can give him
the truck full of uni he asked for.
As in sea urchins?
Do any of Chef Tatsuo's recipes
call for uni?
No, they don't.
Uni…
Uni?
Uni.
Should we go get dinner?
I'll be off then.
Is there anything you want?
-What do you want to eat?
-I'll join you if you're having dinner.
Isn't Japan known
for its convenience store lunch boxes?
How about a bento box back at the hotel?
Why would we have convenience store bento
all the way here in Sapporo?
Sapporo has the best horsehair crab.
Crab? You make me feel crabby.
You remember, right?
We had it once,
and you fell in love with it.
You hung around the restaurant,
saying you wanted to steal the recipe.
-I did?
-Yeah.
I guess it kind of rings a bell.
But I don't feel like crab today.
Right? Forget crab, and let's have
a convenience store bento box.
What do you say
to a romantic bento dinner?
-Well?
-I'm off to drink a highball.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wait here and don't fight.
Okay.
Why would we fight?
It's quite surprising
that Yeon-joo is working
with someone else.
She never was the type
to get along with others.
You're really getting on my nerves.
You've known her for a few years,
and you're acting like
you know everything about her.
I'm not acting like it.
I do know everything about her.
Didn't I tell you that we--
Yes, sure, whatever.
Briefly.
You guys dated very briefly.
Briefly?
I wouldn't call three years brief.
Whether it was 3 years or 365 years,
what's important is that you're her past.
Her past, huh?
Do you know why
Yeon-joo opened a restaurant in Jeonju?
What? What are you going to say now?
Why do you think
the restaurant is called Jungjae?
Doesn't it mean "refined,"
as in refined salt?
We'd made a promise.
Goddammit.
That one day, the two of us
would open a restaurant called Jungjae
somewhere other than Seoul--
-Here you go.
-Thank you very much.
Thanks for the food!
What did you say? I couldn't hear.
What are you doing?
I told you to order lots of skewers
and this is all you got?
Are you going to eat or not?
The food's getting cold.
I was about to eat.
CHEF JANG YOUNG-HYE
Goddammit, it's cold!
What? What do you want?
If the recipient can't come to the phone,
stop calling.
What are you,
my actual ex-girlfriend or something?
What the hell are you going on about?
Don't you know I'm returning to Motto?
You change sides as easily
as a chameleon changes colors, don't you?
Since when did that sneaky act
pass for a simple return?
What?
Whatever.
Yu-jin's with you, isn't he?
Why can't I reach him?
How would I know?
Why are you asking me about him?
He must be too busy to talk to you.
Just pretend that he died
because he was too swamped.
Get a hold of yourself,
Director Han Beom-woo.
We might all go down together!
What did you say? "We"?
"We"?
Since when were you and I a "we"?
Whatever. I'm hanging up.
Stop talking.
Did you see what I sent you?
Look at it now!
You're talking way more
than I am right now.
Your brother screwed me over
and found my replacement himself.
We're seriously done for.
LE MURIR HEAD CHEF JEON MIN
What the heck?
Han Sun-woo's completely determined.
He's using a cheat code
to take over Hansang.
What does he have going with Han Sun-woo?
Hello? Han Beom-woo?
Hansang, Le Murir.
Le Murir, Hansang.
What are you saying?
Hey, Han Beom-woo!
-Seriously.
-How do you remember that?
How could I ever forget that?
-So many ridiculous things happened.
-I know.
All sorts of things happened.
You bet.
Who taught the idiot
that couldn't even hold a knife?
TASTEFULLY YOURS
He betrayed us
and went to Sapporo to get a girl?
You're pretty close to Hansang Group.
I think we can give each other
what we want.
Don't you think it's more suspicious
that you're working at a restaurant
in the countryside?
I'll get the recipes.
I feel like
I'm finally working toward my dream.
Do you have any idea what you just did?
What you did can never be justified.
Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim