♪Do you know, our fingertips
are bound by one string♪
♪Tied to an attachment
that blooms only to fade♪
♪By your side once♪
♪I laughed with the world
wild and free♪
♪Yet now there's no one
to carry the story on♪
♪Do you know you are the one string
woven through my fate♪
♪Coiled through the years,
where longing sharpens into pain's line♪
♪If love is meant to fall
more wretched the fiercer its flight♪
♪Yet I still came to answer your call♪
=Shall We Dance=
=Episode 14=
Your Majesty, the fake
(Shangguan Qing)
Yanbo Parlor is nearly finished.
Famed court performers and folk artists
from across the realm
have all taken residence there.
We await only
Your Majesty's honoured visit.
Excellent.
That is truly joyous news.
All my ministers
shall attend my Yanbo Parlor
and partake in the festivities.
Shangguan Qing, how dare you.
Do you not realise this court
is where state affairs are deliberated?
And yet you bring
such entertainers into court.
This is outrageous!
Minister He,
do not fault Shangguan Qing.
This was my doing.
I...
also wished my ministers to see
where the treasury silver
has been spent.
I want you all to relax a little
and judge whether it was worth it.
Shangguan Qing.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Splendid!
General Xiang Gu
returns victorious to court.
(General Xiang Gu)
Xiang Gu, at your service.
Welcome back, General Xiang.
Perfect timing.
I've arranged a new dance today.
Come and enjoy it with us.
Your Majesty,
General Xiang
has campaigned
in the Southern Seas for years
and commands great prestige.
Now that unrest stirs at the frontier,
it would be fitting
to have him lead the expedition
to subdue the barbarians.
(So the force)
(blocking my contact
with the foreign powers...)
(was them all along?)
Minister He,
General Xiang is advanced in years.
He has just returned,
and has yet
to enjoy time with his family.
How can you still urge His Majesty
to send him back to war?
In my view,
Your Majesty should instead
grant him further honours and rank,
so that he may
remain in the capital
and enjoy family life.
Minister Sun, that is mistaken.
Soldiers at the frontier
exist to serve the realm.
Even death
on the battlefield is no cause for fear.
Your Majesty,
I am willing to lead the campaign
and pacify the frontier.
Good.
Great Qian
needs loyal generals like you
true pillars of the realm.
General Xiang,
you haven't returned home in ten years.
Do you not wish to go back?
Director Jia
and Minister Sun are
behaving rather strangely.
No need to increase military spending,
and yet frontier forces
would still be reinforced.
But the two of you
seem oddly reluctant.
Could it be
you have other thoughts?
We wouldn't dare.
Minister He, you misunderstood.
I am only concerned
for General Xiang's health.
Your Majesty,
as the old saying goes,
a gentleman settles his household
before serving his cause.
General Xiang's granddaughter
has now come of age
and awaits marriage.
And Your Majesty happens
to lack an empress.
Minister He is right.
But with the frontier unsettled,
I have no mind to take a wife.
Your Majesty,
you have governed
in your own right for over half a year,
yet the harem remains empty.
That is a grave matter
for the royal bloodline.
If Your Majesty is
unwilling to appoint an empress,
then perhaps you could
announce the identity
of the woman you once mentioned.
The Ministry of Rites can
make the arrangements.
Elevating her as a consort
would not be improper.
This again.
I've already said
the time isn't right.
Besides...
a woman such as her
could only ever be my empress.
Your Majesty,
what could be the reason?
Rumours are already
spreading among the people.
You must consider
the dignity of the royal family.
What rumours?
Well...
It's...
They involve
Your Majesty and a eunuch.
The words are too disgraceful.
I cannot bring myself to say them.
I beg Your Majesty to take consorts
and appoint an empress,
so that Great Qian's lineage
may continue.
Minister He,
please rise.
We beg Your Majesty to
take consorts and appoint an Empress,
for the continuation
of Great Qian's royal bloodline.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
I can't hear you.
Louder.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Louder.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Louder.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Louder still.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Louder. I said louder.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Louder.
Your Majesty, reconsider.
For the sake of succession.
Enough.
I've had my fill of dancing today.
If this matter is raised again,
I'll have all of you dance with me.
My marriage
is mine to decide.
No one is to interfere.
Court dismissed.
Your Majesty was rather impulsive
in court today.
If they keep pressing me,
I'll deal with them the same way.
They say serving
an emperor is like serving a tiger.
But with our young emperor,
it's like serving a dance partner.
They say a tiger's tail
must never be touched.
But our young emperor's tail
is
love.
Aunt, please don't tease me.
I think you did the right thing.
The Chu bloodline has
always been passionate.
We value love as much as the realm.
Let's discuss serious matters.
Serious matters?
Duan Muzhi.
Yes.
Have the men
sent to investigate Sun Gong
reported back?
Your Highness,
nothing suspicious has been found
about his background.
You and Uncle have
shared a loving marriage for years.
What is sincere and what is false
can't possibly
escape your perceptive eyes.
Speaking of perceptiveness,
I fear
I'm no match for you, Your Majesty.
Ever since I learned dancing from you,
I haven't been
able to stop for a moment.
Had I known,
I should have joined
His Majesty in dancing at court.
Serious matters.
Alright.
As for General Xiang,
he is a man of the battlefield, but his loyalty
to the royal family is unquestionable.
He was trusted by my brother.
When the Zhen clan was
condemned for treason,
he carried out the decree
without hesitation.
He led the troops
to execute them.
I know you wish to investigate
the Xiao family case.
So do I.
But now is not the time.
Our priority is to use Xiang Gu
to check Jia Yi's armed ambitions.
And prevent
the capital's calamity from years ago.
General Xiang,
take a look.
Every year,
Jia Yi finds high-sounding excuses
to divert military funds.
This year, he even urged His Majesty
to build a replica Yanbo Parlor,
and recruited famed
performers into the palace.
If enemies were to strike one day,
what would become of us then?
That cursed Sun Gong
has likely taken Jia Yi's favors,
and turned a blind eye.
However,
with the Grand Princess
overseeing things,
Sun Gong appears clean-handed,
with nothing suspicious for now.
But there is one matter.
Doesn't it strike you
that the eunuch
serving His Majesty called Xiao Man
looks rather familiar?
He resembles someone from the past.
A mere eunuch.
I barely noticed him.
Who does he resemble?
Xiao Congrong.
General Xiang,
your returned at the right time.
We should act at once,
and join the court
in curbing the eunuchs' power
to stop Jia Yi's excesses.
Curb my power?
You think to obstruct
our dealings with foreign powers
and our plan
to overthrow the Chu regime?
Wishful thinking.
We must move faster
and finish this soon.
Uncle.
Brother.
If all our actions
only clear Father and Mother's names,
what then?
Must we drag so many others into this?
Many veteran officials were involved.
Are you certain His Majesty can shake
their hold over the court
and clear your name?
Sister,
do not speak of
clearing names again.
Such things mean nothing to the dead.
Brother,
if we follow Uncle's plan,
countless innocent people will die.
Zhen Mujun!
Your father and mother
gave their lives
in service to Great Qian.
And what did they receive in return?
Because of that tyrant's suspicion,
one hundred and eight lives
of the Xiao family
were all cut down.
Tell me,
if the case were overturned,
would my brother and his wife,
your parents,
and your family come back to life?
Why should that tyrant
decide who lives or dies,
and when he regrets it,
he can simply brush it aside?
I will never accept such an outcome.
And neither should you.
Xiao Man,
my heart aches.
As though there is a wound
that never stops festering.
I've endured
this pain for twenty years,
twenty long years.
I can bear it no longer.
Clearing names
won't bring the dead back.
What I want
is the old emperor's
bloodline and his throne.
I want him to pay
for the lives he murdered!
♪I wanted to ask you
the meaning of forever♪
♪Is it longing that never rests♪
♪Love that echoes without end♪
♪Or promises that can't be kept♪
♪All those vows of forever we made♪
♪Are sealed away in darkness now♪
♪How cruel♪
♪Love blooms and withers♪