=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
=Episode 20=
(Does Secretary Bai only
love my handsome face)
(and will not be responsible for me?)
(Secretary Bai)
It's half past ten.
Why hasn't he called yet?
(Did I flatter myself again?)
(He kissed me, too.)
(But in this age,)
(kissing doesn't mean a relationship.)
How about
I call him?
No, no, no.
If I call him, I'll be too proactive.
I can't do that.
98.
99.
100.
(Secretary Bai is ghosting me.)
(Bai Jing, hold it.
You can't call him first.)
(Hold it.)
But...
I can't just wait and do nothing, right?
It's such a sunny day
for a date?
(How dare she date someone!)
(Can it be Chu Zhe?)
(Nagger)
(Nagger is calling.)
Hello.
Secretary Bai.
Anything wrong?
Yes.
What is it?
My showerhead doesn't work.
It doesn't?
I'm good at repairing that.
See you later.
Yes, yes.
It's working, isn't it?
It didn't work just now.
Well,
forget about this.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
No.
No?
Fine, then.
Enjoy your bath.
(What exactly should I say?)
(Jin Shi'an really doesn't want
to be responsible.)
The fireworks we watched?
A nice painting.
(Spicy hot pot is her true love.)
(Swimming is good
for her frozen shoulders.)
(Today, I had her work overtime again.)
(On the first day Secretary Bai got
her driving license,)
(she rear-ended three times.)
(Hope we'll work very well together.)
Don't look.
Hope we'll work very well together?
You keep painting for three years.
What do the paintings stand for?
Umm...
Is it what I think it is?
Jin Shi'an,
do you really have nothing to tell me?
I...
I'm leaving, then.
Bai Jing,
I love you, OK?
Actually, every time
I call you at midnight because...
Because...
Secretary Bai,
why haven't you sent the email yet?
Boss, I'll send it...
Are you getting any better?
Hello?
I want to tell you
I love you.
Hello?
Secretary Bai.
What again?
Where have you gone?
I'm not finished yet.
Hello?
If you dare to leave me, you're screwed.
Hello? Aren't we supposed to talk?
Don't date anyone else.
Date me.
Hello?
I love you.
I love you!
Jin Shi'an,
I love you, too.
=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
(The right of communication through network
exclusively belongs to Tencent.)