Because This Is My First Life
Lee Min Ki
Jeong So Min
- Lee Som
Park Byeong Eun
Kim Ga Eun
Kim Min Seok
Because This Is My First Life
Ji Ho, where are you? I'm out in front of the house.
Ack.
Hi.
Oh. Hi.
You live here? In this neighborhood?
Yup.
What about you? What are you doing here?
I-I was just passing through this area.
I see.
Should I give you my business card?
Huh?
Oh. Okay.
Let's have a cup of tea later on then.
I'm a bit out of it right now.
Alright. Let's do that.
♫ The road I go alone ♫
Writer, are you alright? Did you get to go the restroom okay?
Yes. What about you, CEO? Are you feeling okay?
Oh.
I think I'm all sobered up.
I had fun today, CEO. I'll be going now.
I'll take you to your home.
It's right up in the front and I'd like to walk a bit to sober up too.
Oh. Your husband would be coming out to meet you.
I was dense.
Then, bye now.
MY Entertainment, Go Jeong Min
♫ I could dream ♫
♫ Because I had you ♫
♫ Because it didn't disappear ♫
Hello?
Ji Ho. Where are you?
I'm here.
What?
♫ Next to that cloud ♫
♫ The starlight that sparkles  ♫
Why weren't you answering
your phone?
I didn't have a chance.
I'm sorry. I was going to call you.
♫ I want to believe it ♫
Let's go in.
♫ Because you are here ♫
♫ This road I'm walking on again ♫
♫ Those distant footsteps  ♫
♫ To your side  ♫
♫ Pulling me  ♫
♫ this love  ♫
The liquor went in so smoothly today. I think since it was the first time I drank in a while.
I see.
Did you drink together? The production company . . .
Yes.
CEO is a good drinker too.
Oh, don't drink cold water. Drink this instead or you'll get heartburn tomorrow.
Keep this by your bed and sleep.
You might wake up in the middle of the night from the alcohol.
It's warm.
Thank you.
Good night.
Sleep well.
Ji Ho.
Yes?
Again today . . .
should we sleep together?
Oh.
No. Not today.
Oh. Yes.
I'm sorry.
No. It's not that.
I'm just a bit tired today.
On those days, I snore even more.
I understand.
I'll make more tea, so have more if you need it.
Yes.
But I'm not going to get married.
I did it once, something like a marriage.
In this life, this house, Kitty and myself. These three are what I can handle.
We dated and we got pregnant.
Since marriage isn't just about the two people.
It's a system where the surrounding understanding is more important.
When we lost the baby,
we broke up, and his family was opposed to me as well.
As for me, in my life
I would just like nothing to happen.
MY Entertainment, Go Jeong Min
I met the CEO of some drama production company.
She wasn't someone common, that CEO.
She's strong, but how should I say this?
That sturdiness isn't to break her surroundings,
but to embrace it, it seemed.
Someone like a tree, maybe?
♫ Just stay still like this quietly  ♫
♫ Like we are together by coincidence ♫
Hello?
It's me.
Yes.
I know.
It's late.
I'm sorry, but I have something to tell you.
Yes.
You starting to write again . . .
Congratulations.
This person is agonizing over it.
For starting again.
He's afraid.
It's really
a relief.
He's anxious.
Thank you.
Sleep well, Ji Ho.
Yes.
You too, Se Hee.
Epiisode 14
Because It's My First Time with Confession
Trim like usual, right?
No.
You're here.
Sorry to call you suddenly when you're busy.
What's there for the CEO to be busy about? It's the employees who are busy.
Wow. Ho Rang, you got a cut.
Oh. Yes.
Recharge my mood.
It really suits you.
About Won Seok.
He's sincere, right?
Please tell me. I also need a final
closure too.
But I had no one else to ask but you.
He's sincere, right? Won Seok.
For now,
yes, I think so.
Then . . .
Even if tried to hold onto him,
he wouldn't return to me, right?
Hmm.
Won Seok
thinks he's making you miserable, I think.
So he seems to have made the decision he must let you go.
It's not that he wants to let go?
Though I don't really know it well.
when someone thinks that they are the one causing the person they love to go through difficulties because of them,
I think it makes that person hate himself.
And it's also miserable.
Yes.
It's just... that this was as far as we were supposed to go.
CEO!
Oh! Deputy Shin.
Are you leaving after dropping by the office?
Yes, I had a meeting for the third and fourth quarter financial analysis.
Aren't you going to introduce me?
Perhaps... CEO's...
Ahhh, no. She's my closest younger brother's grilfriend... no.
She's my girlfriend's best friend, Ho Rang.
Ms. Yang Ho Rang.
Ahhh... So she's your girlfriend's best friend.
Hello.
I'm in charge of CEO Ma's company's finance. Shin Young Hyo.
Ah, yes.
I don't have a business card.
I will be going ahead, CEO.
Ah, right. Ms. Ho Rang.
I will call you. Take care.
Yes.
I heard from CEO Ma that you are headed to Silim-dong.
I will give you a ride. The bus in this neighborhood comes really late.
No, it's okay. You don't have to.
I'm not a bad person. I have known CEO Ma for a long time.
You must live there?
No. Just...
I just need to get my things.
I see.
But then, Ms. Ho Rang, do you really not know who I am?
Pardon?
I want to get married.
Huh?
Gyeolmalrae! We chatted on it after you accepted my 'like.'
Ahhh.
Honestly, I was really startled earlier.
I recognized you at first glance.
Yes.
After I installed that app, the first person I talked to was you.
But you haven't replied since then,
so I thought I was rejected for sure.
That...
That time, I too just registered for the first time so I just replied without any thoughts
since it was CEO Ma's app.
Are you trying to draw a boundary now?
- Pardon?
- What's this?
If you're startled like that, you are acknowledging as such?
For real, an irrefutable part?
Thank you for giving me a ride. Take care.
Yes—
Take care.
Celebrating 100 days, 1 year, 2 years, 1000 days, 5 years.
Let's love forever -Seok, Rang
Honey Hon Hon, I love you. Yang Ho Rang, I love you
Love forever. Seok. Rang.
Honey, Hon, Hon. I love you
Yang Ho Rang, I love you
100th day. At Campus
Our happy home.
100th day, At campus
Let's love forever, Seok Rang
Honey, Hon, Hon. I love you.
Yang Ho Rang, I love you
What you said was right.
Now, I... will be true to my heart.
♫ All has faded ♫
♫ those small papers on which I've recorded the days past ♫
Why are you here? You didn't leave?
No, since you said you were here to get your things and I thought maybe they would be heavy.
And I noticed you weren't in a good condition since earlier.
Pardon?
Give it to me. I will give you a ride.
No.
I would be too burdened if you do this.
At a glance, it's obvious that you are about to get sick.
You've got a body flu, acknowledge to the left, acknowledge to the right, acknowledge to the front?
Pardon?
No, your face shows that you're on the edge of collapsing.
How could I pretend not to notice and just go?
Give it to me, Ms. Ho Rang.
Then, should I?
♫ Though I endure a day like today  ♫
♫ Living through each day that keeps coming back  ♫
♫ Like a fool repeating these things ♫
♫ And I stand alone on one side again  ♫
♫ Just in case somehow tomorrow might be different  ♫
♫ I cannot even move one step  ♫
The lawsuit, we will proceed with it as we discussed.
In the process of investigation, you would have to personally be investigated as the victim.
Are you alright with that?
Yes.
I already know that.
Thankfully, you have the call and text records with that assistant director
so it will help.
Just that, once their side starts playing with the media
it will be noisy,
especially since it's in the broadcast field to begin with.
Yes. Once it starts I should prepare myself.
Okay. Then we will proceed as is.
And also,
this is the contract.
Program format: 20 70-minute episodes for a mini-series, Pay: 10 million won (~$92,000)
There's no need for you to sign right away.
You can take it and look through it,
and if you want any adjustments to be made you can just tell me.
But then...
the amount is...
Is more negotiation needed?
Ah, it's less than the amount you expected.
No.
I think it's too much.
Writer, you can't be like that.
Pardon?
Even if you are surprised, you should go out and be surprised on your own.
We are doing a contract, so how could you show what you feel in front of an enemy?
CEO, you are not an enemy though.
It's not a lot.
By our company's standard, that is the starting for newbie writers.
Honestly, our company doesn't sign contracts with writers that much.
But if we do, we do it the right way.
If we think it's a person we will be working with for a long time.
CEO.
Yes?
Today...
should we eat?
Sure.
Remember
Rather than a lot of projects, good projects are more important.
"My dream was to become a writer at first."
Aren't you greedy for money? / Yes, I am very greedy about money. I grew up in a very poor family. I started this line of work because I needed "money" right away.
What is that? / In this world working for money is the easiest thing. Of course, there are things you can't put a monetary value on. You shouldn't just say it's good or valuable. Sometimes you must show it.
Go Jeong Min
Writer, did you cure your hangover this morning?
I drank warm honey water before sleeping
and it was okay.
Ahh. Did you husband prepare it for you?
Yes.
My husband...
prepared it for me.
Before we sign a contract, I have something I am curious about.
Yes, Writer?
Regarding the person you told me before.
The one you almost married.
Yes.
If you were to meet him again,
how do you think it would be?
Even if you meet him again,
do you think you will love him still?
This...
is this question related to the contract?
Yes.
It is an important question that is related to the contract.
Honestly, I met him.
That friend.
The day when we went to your neighborhood,
that day,
by coincidence.
That's why right now, your question is a bit...
all the more
strange, I feel.
For me, on that day...
He came to get me.
Se Hee did.
The way I see it, you have never faced the world properly.
Using the company as an excuse and your mom as your shield,
you lived only criticizing the world.
For once, grab the world and stand properly in front of it
and face it head on.
That's what I think you must do.
And when you start, I will be by your side to hang in there with you.
Have you been to K Ventures again today?
Yes, I had some additional investments to discuss with them.
Okay. Work hard.
That... Deputy Park.
Would you like to smoke a cigarette with me?
Right now?
Yes.
No. I'm okay.
What do you want to say?
It was 2015 when I came to this team
and it's already been three years that we've worked together.
If you calculate it by work days it would be 800 days.
If you calculate it by time it's 7,200 hours.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
But you know, those many hours,
for me, in general, it was horrible.
- Horrible?
- Yes.
If it was a day where we would have a company dinner I would be pondering how I should smile to your sexual innuendos.
And if it was after my vacation, you would probably ask where I went with my boyfriend.
Then what would I give as an answer?
When I didn't feel good, I'd be afraid that you'd ask, "Is it that time of the month?"
So I couldn't even act as if I was sick.
So when I think about you, all I have is just horrible and painful memories.
But you are still a colleague that I've worked with for 7,200 hours.
Isn't that so sad?
Well. So what do you want to say?
About all the hurt that I have received all this time
I want you to apologize.
What?
I need to receive an apology
from you.
In a place where all the people from our team are present, please apologize officially.
Apologize?
I really want to end this horrible connection with you.
Today, I gathered all my sincerity to talk to you, so
please show your sincerity, too.
Then, I will be waiting.
♫ The leaves are "swish swish" (Woo Soo [Ji]) falling
Soo Ji, why? Did something happen?
No.
It's nice to see you.
Why are you so cute?
What you said was right.
I just avoided it and cursed.
I have never conversed with Deputy Park while looking at each other.
He is someone's son and a family's head of household though.
My Soo Ji is really cool.
This punk! Come here!
What's wrong with you?
You don't like this?
No.
So you don't like it. At least not yet.
Go Jeong Min?
Go Jeong Min
Jeong Min?
How in the world... could the two meet like this?
Sister-in-law— No.
Does Ms. Ji Ho know?
Well, how could she know?
This unbelievable situation.
So they are working together?
Probably.
Shouldn't you be the first one to tell her about it?
It's not even a job where they can bump into each other once in a while.
If it's a production CEO and the writer, then they would see each other a lot.
What...
should I say?
How much should I tell her?
That she was someone I dated long ago.
Or... that time I spent with her was stained
with my pride and my foolishness?
Whatever I say, she would get hurt
because Ms. Ji Ho is a transparent person.
To add my stain to her transparent self...
I don't want that.
I didn't mean Ms. Ji Ho, though.
I was talking about Jeong Min.
I was going to ask how you are going to explain Ms. Ji Ho to Jeong Min.
You... it wasn't that you couldn't forget Jeong Min?
Isn't that why you
married with a contract?
After all, Ms. Ji Ho
has just a contractual relationship with you.
Wasn't she just a tenant to you?
So you weren't worried about Jeong Min.
♫ Let me briefly borrow your warm shoulder ♫
♫ please be a shelter for my tired soul ♫
I had thought that as we lived on,
that one day, I may meet her (Jeong Min) again.
I even practiced.
How are you?
It's been a long time.
However, from the moment I saw her,
what I was most worried about
was only one person.
Just how... ?
When did it start?
The only thing that was left in my life
was just dried leaves.
That is what I thought.
That for the remainder of my life, I would only spend waiting for those leaves to fall.
That if I lived on, quietly, alone, then that would be fine.
That's what I thought.
♫ please be a shelter for my tired soul ♫
♫ Let me briefly leave my wounded heart in your care ♫
To be in a position to make decisions that affected another person's life,
I didn't want to do that anymore.
♫ all you have to do is to give it a quick glance as you pass by ♫
"Although Nothing Changes If You Cry About It" by Poet Park Joon
Causing someone to cry, I thought there would never be any reason, ever again.
That is what I thought.
Here he comes. Unit 401!
What about Se Hee-nim?
Ahhh, he left work already.
Are you thinking of screwing up our company's program just because of your ex-girlfriend?
After just two weeks of employment?
Pardon?
Ahh. I'm sorry.
No.
But how did you know?
How could I not know? It's written all over your face.
My face?
Break ups happen when people date.
Why are you making it so obvious?
It's not like it's your first time dating.
I dated only once, though.
Ah. Is that so?
Then,
it must have been your first time doing that, too?
What? What is my first time?
What would I mean? I mean breaking up.
You worked hard. Goodbye.
Ms. Ho Rang, you seem to be very busy.
Did you go home safely that day?
If you are not busy, how about dinner tonight?
Ms. Ho Rang!
I'm not late, right? The moment you replied I started the engine.
Yes.
You must be hungry. What would you like to eat?
Never mind food. How about a simple beer?
Beer?
I am in total agreement with that one.
Let's go.
Cheers.
Wow. You must've been very thirsty.
Did you go home safely that day?
I had a boyfriend for seven years.
However, recently we broke up.
To be honest, the day you gave me a ride
was to the house that we shared up until now.
Ah.
However...
How could you have so little luggage?
What?
It's understandable.
Even if you date for a long time, when you break up, there isn't really that much stuff to pack.
Ah, I also dated my first girlfriend for seven years.
However,
why did you two break up?
We just fought a lot because of the topic of marriage.
Turns out, dating and marriage are very different.
So how are you planning to overcome this situation?
What?
Your break up. Have you come up with a plan on how to overcome it?
Well, I don't really have one as of now.
Well, time is medicine, they say.
How can time be medicine?
Time is just merely time.
The thing I hate most are these don't-go-over, triple, tuna board cliched phrases.
You can't get fooled by these cliches, Ho Rang.
Don't-go-over, triple, what?
You see, for a person, when they really want something, they have to speak it aloud in order for it to happen.
So every morning, noon, and night, I would say my wishes out loud looking at my reflection in the mirror.
So what did you say?
"I can forget her. I can overcome this breakup."
Like a zombie spirit, I will end this for all and get the whole world.
Please don't say those multi-syllable words in front of me. I'm not that smart, so I don't understand those.
Ah, those aren't multi-syllable words. Those are abbreviations that young people use these days.
What?
No. Why do you say those types of things?
It makes me feel better.
It also makes me feel younger.
Uhm, I've been here before.
Director Gye Yong Seok
Some man told me this was for Unit 401 and left it here.
Okay.
Since you told me not to call you, I'm leaving your bag here.
Gye Yong Seok
I'm sorry.
Yes.
I know
that you came before to leave some luggage.
I see.
I didn't know she got married.
I'm sorry.
I just had a lot of drinks that night, so I don't really remember.
I'm being serious. Please believe me.
I will do whatever I can to make up for it. I will pay you as much settlement money as you want...
So, first, could she please withdraw the criminal complaint?
I need to work on this new project.
What?
I had a dream about me walking alone
in an endless tunnel.
I... well...
I thought you knew about it.
I think this is something that I need to talk to her about directly.
Then, sorry for bothering you.
I'll talk to her.
Sit down.
You will talk to me.
Properly. And everything.
Thank you
for telling me something that's hard to share with anyone.
I also have something I'm curious about.
If I met Se Hee again, would I love him again.
If my answer was yes,
what would your conclusion be?
If that was your answer,
I would probably end up being your enemy.
Then were we supposed to be fighting?
Right here, grabbing each other's hair?
I would probably have waited
for Se Hee's heart.
You would've waited.
Why? Is it because it's a contract marriage?
Even if it was a real marriage,
I would've done the same thing.
Being a married couple doesn't mean
you automatically have all of each other's heart.
Is that so?
However, honestly, isn't that what marriage is?
Isn't it an institution to show that you have each other's heart
and are officially declaring it?
So even if you have a change of heart, it ties you down and makes it hard for you to leave.
I'm not quite sure
since this is my first time getting married
and experiencing love, too.
So there are a lot of things I don't know,
but there's one thing I'm sure of.
A heart isn't something that is taken or grabbed.
It just comes to you.
Please keep it a secret from Se Hee that I know about this.
Be well.
Go back and live like nothing ever happened
Instead, don't ever love anyone.
You have no right to.
I know, right?
A heart wasn't something to be stolen or grabbed.
Imagine, she already knows that.
I'm envious of you, Writer.
Your phone call was long.
Ah, yeah. It was the lawyer.
There was a problem with Writer Yoon's criminal charge with that guy.
What?
What happened?
About that...
That Assistant Director must've gone to find her to beg her to drop the criminal complaint,
but he got beaten up. Pretty badly, I hear.
By whom?
Writer Yoon's husband.
What?!
He...
hit a person?
It's been a long time.
Deputy Park, you did well this year. Let's have a good year next year, too.
Hey, should we all have a toast? Fill your glasses.
Everyone fill their glasses.
You should give the toast, Deputy Park.
Alright!
There is not much more left of 2017. Our Team Leader, who we respect, we love you!
And our business team family, this year, you have all worked so hard.
With love in our hearts for our Team Leader, when I say, 'Team Leader!' you say,
'We love you.' You got that?
Ah, that's right, the apology.
I'm sorry, Deputy Woo.
I've been a bit mischievous, haven't I? Well, take a drink and let's forget everything, okay?
All together now. Team Leader,
- I love you!
Drink up.
Where shall we go for the second round?
Did something happen between you two?
No. Nothing happened. Drink.
Drink, drink.
Have a glass.
Chief.
Okay, I'm leaving first.
- Have a goodnight, Team Leader.
- Don't be out too late.
- Goodbye.
- See you!
How about we have a round 2, Deputy.
Deal!
Let's have some beef sashimi and afterwards, karaoke, deal?
Karaoke, deal!
I'm going to stop by the office really quick.
Wait for me!
- Okay!
- We'll wait for you there!
Yes, a deserted island.
Whose turn is it now?
Yes, Baby?
Language was created for humans to communicate with each other, right?
That's right.
If you can't use words to communicate with it, it's not human, is it?
Of course. If words don't work, then it is not human.
Either they are an animal, insect, or water flea. But why are you asking all of a sudden?
Oppa, were you sincere when you said you'll have my back once I begin?
Of course, I was sincere.
- Take your turn.
- Hurry and roll the dice, CEO.
CEO.
All right, roll the dice well.
I love you.
Hello? Hello, Baby?
What was that?
She's speaking like it's her last will and testament.
- It's your turn, CEO.
- Hurry up.
Is that Seoul?
No way...
No, no, no, no!
What do you mean no? You have to buy Seoul now, CEO.
That scaredy cat, seriously.
Deputy Woo needs to show her body in her profile picture.
B? B? No, no no.
A full A. A very full A.
If only I wasn't married,
together with Deputy Woo... Yeah?
Oh? Deputy Woo, why did you come here?
There's something I need to settle.
Is that so?
Jin Ho!
What?
Ouch.
Oh.
Here it goes.
Tak, tak, tak. Pak. I'm buying Taipei.
I was going to buy that though.
They say that a place where when the tiger (horangi) is not around the rabbit plays king.
What? Is this all Won Seok-nim's land?
- Yeah.
- Whoa. We really raised a baby tiger (horangi).
That's why you should have bought it earlier.
You need to get in the tiger's (horangi) den in order to catch the baby tiger (horangi).
Let's stop playing this now.
Why? It's getting fun.
What's fun about it? We're not even kids. We just play stuff like this every day.
Let's go have a drink. My treat!
Really?
Your treat?
Yes. I will treat everyone today. Let's have a crazy night.
Then I will be going first.
No, Bo Mi-nim should come too.
No thanks, I have an appointment today.
At this time, what appointment?
Should I call it an appointment with myself?
Have fun. I will be going first.
Ah! It's Friday, right? Bo Mi-nim must be going to Itaewon again.
Itaewon?
There's a famous figure shop there.
Every Friday she calls it an appointment with herself. I think she must be geeking out at that shop.
Ah. It does suit her well.
Ah! Since you mention Itaewon, should we go to a club just us guys?
C-Club?
Yeah. Club. What's the point of leaving our perfectly fine bodies?
We should play hard while we're single, isn't it so?
Oh, it seems like you go to clubs a lot.
I haven't gone even once.
- I think my ears are going to bleed.
- I didn't know it would be like this either.
Ah! I think my eyes are going to bleed.
Let's not stay here. Let's go down there and have fun!
No.
You should go ahead.
Then I will play downstairs so follow me later.
Yes. Yes.
Then I will be going down.
Yes.
Yang Ho Rang, I will forget you. Yang Ho Rang, I will forget you!
I will forget you!
Oh.
Oh?
Him? What's with him?
Oh! Bo Mi-nim!
Get down!
Hey, I'm so scared.
Then do you want to go to the internet cafe? Let's go!
No...
You said you had an appointment!
On the stage, you talk with your body and not with your mouth.
Body?
Mr. Se Hee
Can you do me two favors?
Ji Ho, later on
when she says she wants to write
[Assistant Writer: Yoon Ji Ho]
can you allow her to do so?
[Assistant Director: Gye Yong Seok, Kim Seong Mi / Assistant Writer: Yoon Ji Ho]
Even if it's later on, so that she can be able to write
[Assistant Writer: Yoon Ji Ho]
so she doesn't give up on her dreams.
So that she doesn't live like her mom.
Please do that.
♫ among so many hours ♫
♫ those days that passed by like a breeze ♫
Hello.
♫ please stay just like this ♫
♫ I am leaving on another path alone ♫
♫ please stay, quietly, just like this ♫
♫ as if we were together by coincidence ♫
Books
Korean & Leading Writers
Excuse me.
Perhaps, do you have this book?
"Although Nothing Changes If You Cry About It" by Poet Park Joon
Ah, the one that was here got sold today.
Ah. Thank you.
Yes.
Hello, Father-in-law.
A bit...
you hit him a lot.
Will it cause problems
for Ji Ho?
I think it will be okay.
Just in time, I just met the CEO from that side.
We know each other from before, so he won't make it into a bigger problem.
Okay. Thanks.
That...
Me being Ji Ho's husband,
does that
affect you?
And on Ji Ho's writing career?
Is that why you came to see me?
Because of the dregs of an old love
that I might ruin Writer's work?
That I might hurt her career?
Yeah.
When I got married, there's a favor that Ji Ho's mother asked of me.
When Ji Ho would want to write again
she asked that I allow her to write again.
So that she doesn't give up on her dreams
she asked me to do that for Ji Ho.
But honestly, I don't know how to do that,
so I just promised that I won't be a hindrance.
But
you do know. So that Ji Ho...
How to help Ji Ho to not give up on her dream.
So that is why you came to see me.
To an old lover who you met after 12 years,
and this is all you have to say to me?
I hate you for this, a little.
I'm sorry.
But then, there was nothing that I could do.
Why she decided to stop writing,
I only found out for the first time today.
And the only thing that I could do was swing my fists.
I heard that you were a very good producer.
Jeong Min...
Not as my wife,
but please look at her as a writer.
I ask that of you.
"Words are born from a person's mouth
and die in a person's ear."
"Although Nothing Changes If You Cry About It" by Poet Park Joon
But some words don't die
Be well. Go back and live like nothing ever happened. Instead, don't ever love anyone. You have no right to.
and go into a person's heart
and continue to live.
Those words that lived in my heart for 12 years,
how did they suddenly
disappear completely?
I tried so hard,
but those words
would not be erased.
I have something to ask you, too.
You.
Have you confessed your love to her?
What?
Confession.
"I like you" or
well...
A confession similar to that, have you tried?
No. I just... Must one say those words aloud?
So you haven't.
Do you know that?
That you never did that
for me, not even once?
Confession.
♫ among so many hours ♫
I will be going.
Okay.
Words, too...
have to get into a person's heart in order to live on.
And you have to get it out of your mouth so that it can go into a person's heart.
It was not a coincidence.
So now,
drawing a line on purpose,
please don't.
It was due to those words.
It's no one's fault is what I think.
Like how some waves just flow by
while others break apart.
It's just how it is.
Her warm words piled up and piled up more.
You too, Se Hee.
You shouldn't worry too much either.
Just because you've lived yesterday,
it doesn't mean you know
everything about today.
In my dead heart
this word lived.
Woori (we/us).
Are you still doing that part-time job?
Oh, yes.
But I think I might quit soon.
Good. Good thinking.
Yes.
After I quit, I think I will start writing again.
By writing, you mean, what?
That drama?
Yes.
Didn't you say you quit that? To focus on homemaking?
Yes, but
a good opportunity came to me somehow,
so I thought I might try to start again.
What about kids?
What?
When are you going to have a baby, then?
Oh.
I haven't really . . .
You should think about having babies, even though work is important too.
You're still young but Se Hee's not.
Use that to pay off the loan and later on, when you've had a baby, you can use it to supplement the living costs.
What?
I promised him I would do this when he got married.
Oh.
I don't think it's something for me to accept.
Then who should accept it?
Oh. Of course, you should give it to Se Hee directly.
What would he and I meet and talk about?
If I gave it to him, he wouldn't take it anyway, so it's right for you to take it.
The wife taking care of these things behind the scenes is important, too.
Let's go now.
Wait, Father-in-law.
I have something to say to you.
It's cold, so careful going back.
Where are you? Why aren't you coming?
Oh, I'll be coming in a bit.
What time is it! Hurry and come home!
Hey, am I a kid? Don't-go-over, triple, tuna board!
See you later!
Over, triple?
What tuna?
At least it's a relief that she seems to be in a good mood.
Tada.
Soo Ji. You know the movie, "The Graduate," right?
Of course. It's your favorite movie.
I saw that over ten times.
I saw it for the first time when I was a first-year in high school.
When Benjamin barged into Elaine's wedding
and grabbed her hand and led out, I fell for that scene.
How should I say it?
To my seventeen-year-old eyes, that seemed so romantic.
That's a famous scene. Lots of parodies were made of it, too.
But . . .
After I was over 20, I saw it again, and I noticed something different.
What?
The two's expressions afterward.
After they fled excitedly from the wedding, they rode the bus.
But strangely, the two have no words to say to each other.
Feeling anxious and empty.
I didn't notice that when I was young,
but I started to notice that scene at some point.
Why?
You see that scene between you and your landlord?
Are you having a hard time?
Yeah.
Yup.
Now?
Alright.
It's so cold.
Hurry and go on.
Nah. Why?
Hurry and go. CEO Ma's waiting.
Then, call me after you've arrived. Okay?
What happened? Are you alright? What happened?
Did you do something to Deputy Park?
Your way didn't work so this time, so this time, I did it my way.
Your way, what?
I punched him hard in his stupid mouth.
What?
You did good. Good job!
Come here!
Hey!
Ack.
I only knew after love existed,
the reason our marriage was easy
was because there was no love.
I'll pay for half of your wedding attire cost.
No, it's alright. It's not that much anyway.
But you had to pay for wedding shoes and the bouquet, unlike me.
So I'll deduct them from next month's rent.
Marriage is supposed to be done out of love.
But why . . .
Then what about kids? When will you have a baby then?
After there is love,
why is it that the wounds just get bigger?
Have you ever confessed to her?
Do you know that words have to reach a person's heart in order to survive too?
They need to come out of the mouth in order to reach the heart.
Yeah, I know that too. It's very awkward.
But more than I imagined,
it suits you.
Let's give it a
good try today.
You went to Soo Ji's?
Yes. I had a can of beer.
I see.
Today, were you able to sign the contract okay?
Yes. The CEO is really very nice.
I see.
That's a relief.
You seem tired.
A bit worn out, today.
Hey, Kitty! You came out to greet us?
I have something to tell you.
Yes. I also have something to tell you too.
Maybe this isn't very noticeable?
- Now—
- We—
Oh.
You go first.
Yes. So . . .
Now, we . . .
No. You go first.
Our contract.
I'd like to end it.
Words are always
slower than
the heart.
♫ Though I endure a day like today  ♫
♫ Living through each day that keeps coming back ♫
♫ Repeating these foolish things ♫
♫ And I stand alone on one side again  ♫
♫ Just in case somehow tomorrow  ♫
The bigger the love, the bigger my disarray.
Isn't that Ho Rang?
This morning she looked like a duckling who got rained on.
Which sentence is less cheezy for confessing?
[Shall we 1. get married now? 2. really become a married couple now? 3. really be together now?]
Who else would CEO Ma's friend's friend's friend be?
It's me. Would you like to go on a date with me?
What exactly is marriage? Do you know it, Se Hee?
A marriage out of love would be happy, right?
Woori (us/we)