(Aiko) Even before you got married, you only had eyes for her.
Because I know everything.
(Seiichi) I had been dating Mr. Ando since before we got married.
(Okada) Did you marry Aiko even though there was no love from the beginning?
(Seiichi) That's...
(Aiko) You're a liar!
⟨My husband married me for one reason⟩
⟨It was just camouflage⟩
(Aiko) Seiichi-san.
(Aiko) I love you.
⟨This is about me and my husband who loved each other so much that I wanted to kill them →
It is a story of rebirth⟩
♪～
(sound of door closing)
(Okada) Aiko-san?
(Aiko) Huh…｡
(Okada) Aiko! Aiko-san!
Please be strong, Aiko-san!
Excuse me, an ambulance please. (Salesperson) Understood.
(Okada) Aiko! (Ambulance siren)
(Yuki) Aiko-san?
(Aiko) Mr. Yuki...
(Okada) Ha, good.
(Yuki) This is a hospital.
Aiko collapsed after the discussion →
I received a call from Mr. Okada.
(Aiko) Ha, I…｡
(Okada) Please rest assured.
No X-rays or medications were given.
>> Why didn't you tell me?
You're pregnant, right?
(Doctor) [Congratulations, you are now in your 7th week of pregnancy]
[This is still very small]
[I think the due date will be clearer at the next checkup.]
[Just to be sure →
Do you wish to continue your pregnancy? ] (Aiko) [Huh? ]
>> [Ah, this is what I'm asking you all]
[Our hospital only accepts people who wish to give birth →
Because it is not accepted]
(Aiko) [Ah...]
(Reception) [Mr. Sasashima]
(Aiko) [Yes]
>> [If things go well at your next visit →
Please go to the government office and get a maternal and child health handbook.]
(Aiko) [Yes]
>> [Please take care of yourself] (Aiko) [Thank you]
(Aiko's voice) I found out I was pregnant →
This was after I found out about Ando-san's abortion.
(Okada) You haven't talked to Seiichi.
>> Do something with your precious body.
(Aiko) I'm sorry.
But I→
I really wanted to give birth.
(Okada) I understand how you feel.
But I'll calm down after I get back in shape...
(Aiko) I'm calm.
(Okada) I don't think so.
What Seiichi did to you is outrageous.
(Aiko) But it has nothing to do with children.
This child came to me.
I think it's a miraculous connection.
That's why I want to cherish that.
Child support and alimony from husband →
I don't want to receive even a single yen.
please.
Until the divorce is finalized...→
No, even after the divorce is finalized →
I absolutely don't want my husband to know about our child.
I gave birth to this child alone →
I will grow it alone.
>>You must have been worried.
But you're not alone.
You've been working hard.
(Okada) I will inform the teacher that I have woken up.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
Although I say harsh things with my mouth →
Professor Okada is also worried.
(Aiko) I understand.
(Seiichi) Aiko! Ah...
>> Sorry for the sudden change. My name is Yuki and I am a lawyer.
(Seiichi) Hello...
(Aiko) What is your job? what happened?
(Seiichi) Where have you been?
>> Aiko-san, she felt a little unwell after the discussion yesterday →
I was resting overnight at the hospital. (Seiichi) Eh, hospital?
(Aiko) It's just anemia, so it's not a big deal.
>> I'm sorry, but →
Mr. Sasashima, please never raise your hand against Aiko again.
(Seiichi) Sorry...
>> Rest in peace, Aiko. (Aiko) Yes, thank you very much.
What about breakfast? (Seiichi) I haven't eaten it though...
(Aiko) Well, I'll get you something simple right away.
(Seiichi) No, it's fine, don't push yourself too hard.
(Aiko) I'm still your wife, right?
(Seiichi) Yes, but.
(Aiko) Then let's make something.
Let me do my job as a wife until the end.
(Seiichi) Work...
📱(vibration sound)
(Seiichi) Ah, wait a minute... 📱(Vibration sound)
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(Seiichi) Hello. 📱(Ayaka) What's wrong? You're late.
(Seiichi) No, Aiko is not feeling well.
📱 It doesn't matter anymore!
(Seiichi) I have to make sure I don't lose my temper any further.
📱 Haha~ The reason you don't do well is because of the money.
📱 I absolutely hate 10 million.
(Seiichi) I understand.
Well then.
♪～
(Aiko) Sit down.
(Seiichi) Are you still sick?
(Aiko) Until the divorce is finalized →
I will continue to do the housework as usual.
This is my last intention as a wife.
(Seiichi) As a job?
(Aiko) Yes, my job as a wife.
(Aiko) I didn't think so from the beginning →
If you don't make that distinction →
I felt like my heart would break.
(Aiko) You didn't know, right?
My married life with you→
I've been lonely forever →
It was always painful.
(Aiko) I'll make some tea.
(Seiichi) I am aware that I did something terrible.
sorry.
(Seiichi) Yesterday, I met that lawyer →
I was asked if I got married even though I didn't have love →
I flinched for a moment.
(Seiichi) Pathetic...
(Seiichi) Aiko You see...｡ 📱(Vibration sound)
(Seiichi) Ah, sorry...｡
I have to go now.
(Aiko) Seiichi-san.
I have one request.
(Seiichi) What?
(Aiko) On the last day →
Would you like to have dinner with me?
(Aiko) My punishment.
(Seiichi) I understand.
(Aiko) Thank you.
(Aiko) 《I was really happy when I got married》
(Voice of MC) The bride and groom are entering.
(applause)
\Congratulations! /
(Sawako) Aiko~ Cute!
To Sawako Shigemoto, a friend of the bride Aiko →
I would like to ask you to give a congratulatory speech.
I'm Sawako Shigemoto, a friend of Aiko's since high school.
Aiko since her school days →
Taking care of my grandmother who lives with me →
He is a kind person who always thinks about the people around him more than himself →
He is a friend I truly respect.
What if my friend got married to such a cool and elite husband?
To be honest, I'm a little jealous →
But since she is Aiko, I am filled with congratulations from the bottom of my heart.
Aiko surely→
Grandma in heaven is happy too.
From now on, put yourself first and be happy.
Congratulations! (applause)
(Aiko) 《I don't have time to play because I'm caring for my grandmother and helping around the house→
For me, who has zero love experience →
The first boyfriend I met was Seiichi.
(Seiichi) Everyone, please come today for the two of us →
thank you.
Although we are immature, from now on, Aiko and I will be a couple →
We will overcome any difficulties.
From now on, for the sake of my family →
I intend to work even harder.
>>What is your vow of love? (laughs)
Oath! Oath! Oath...! (claps)
(Seiichi) Aiko...
I love you and I will make you happy!
(Aiko) Hehehe…｡ >> ＼Huh~! /
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss...! (claps)
(Aiko) 《Married with my first boyfriend》
《It was like a fairy tale happiness》
>> ＼Fu~! /
(Aiko) 《But one year after the peak of such happiness》
《I was thrown into hell》
Where was the tree?
Hmm?
Hmm, that side?
Yeah?
a….
(Aiko) I don't need something this expensive.
♪～
(Aiko) Okay... not yet?
📱(vibration sound)
♪～
(The sound of the front door opening and closing)
(Aiko) Ah... thank you for your hard work.
(Seiichi) I said you could sleep. (Aiko) Oh... I'm sorry.
(Seiichi) No, I'm sorry, it's Eve.
(Aiko) No, I have to work, so I can't help it.
(Seiichi) I'll eat the food tomorrow. I'm sleepy. (Aiko) Yeah, rest.
(Seiichi) Ah, this is Happy Merry Christmas.
(Aiko) Well, that's fine...｡
(Seiichi) I heard from someone at work that this restaurant is popular.
(Aiko) Thank you. (Seiichi) Yes.
Well, I'm tired, so I'll take a rest first.
(Aiko) Good night.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
♪～
📱(Transmission sound)
\Welcome/ \Welcome~/
(Aiko) Rena!
(Rena) Aiko~ It’s been a while! (Aiko) It’s been a while~｡
Hey, I'm sorry for contacting you all of a sudden. >> Hmm, I'm glad.
Isn't it since the wedding? (Aiko) That's right.
>> I'm sad that Aiko left the company, and to be honest, work is hard.
(Aiko) Huh?
>> Aiko did all the invisible chores →
All the section managers were once again grateful to Aiko.
Things went smoothly because Aiko was there→
There's so much going on, I really want you to come back.
(Aiko) Haha... Something makes me happy.
>> However, Aiko would have been able to balance both →
Why did you quit your job? (Aiko) Hmm…｡
Seiichi's wish was for him to join the family.
>> Hmm, that's rare these days.
Well, my company→
All of my bosses have old ways of thinking, so I wonder if they've been influenced by this.
Ah, do you mean that you simply want to have Aiko all to yourself?
(Aiko) No, it's not like that...
>> It's okay, they're so in love, I'm jealous.
You had fun last night anyway, right?
(Aiko) It's really different because I'm busy with work every day.
>> Well, Mr. Sasashima, even in the business department, you are an elite person.
But see, Wednesday and Friday are no overtime days →
Aren't you coming back early today?
(Aiko) Huh?
>> Huh? It's Friday today.
The company is also strict →
If you stay for even 30 minutes, you'll get angry.
(Aiko) Ah, I see.
(gurgling…)
(Aiko) 《Painful...》
(gurgle gurgle…)
(Aiko) 《Wednesday and Friday are always late》
>> [Wednesday and Friday are no overtime days →
Aren't you coming home early today? ]
📱(vibration sound)
(Aiko) Huh…｡
(Aiko) Ha ha ha ha...｡
♪～
(Aiko) Password...｡
(Aiko) Ah... there it was.
(Sound of keyboard hitting)
(Aiko) Opened.
《There should be a location search app》
(Aiko) There it was.
(click sound)
(Aiko) A restaurant? I guess it's entertainment.
yeah?
Huh?
(click sound)
(Aiko) An apartment?
Ha ha ha ha...
(gurgle gurgle…)
(Aiko) 《I can't breathe》
Moon pair apartment? Ha, somewhere...
(click sound)
(Aiko) Moon Pair Mansion Moon Pair Mansion…｡
(Aiko) There it was.
(Aiko) Ayaka Ando…｡
>> [Applause]
(Aiko) Huh... That's a lie...
(Sound of pouring into glass) (Ayaka's voice) It's especially delicious today.
(Seiichi) Yeah?
(Ayaka) Because I have Eve and Christmas all to myself.
(Seiichi) Ah...
>> Hey, was it okay for Eve to come home in the morning?
(Seiichi) What do you mean by holding me back?
>> Hehe…｡
(Seiichi) But it's okay because I'm trusted.
>> Hey.
That kid doesn't know how to doubt people →
You're insensitive.
He's such a bad man.
(Seiichi) Because I thought it was bad→
I ate homemade chicken this morning.
>> Handmade? Hehe... I'm jealous that you have free time.
If I have time, I'll do it for Seiichi →
I wish I could do more things for you.
(Seiichi) He was also happy about the cookie tin that Ayaka told him about.
>> Stupid person.
As expected of the person I chose to marry.
(Seiichi) Haha. >> Hey...
Thank you for this.
(Seiichi) It suits you.
>> Hehe…｡
♪～
Hey... turn off the light.
(Aiko) ⟨This is how I was thrown into hell⟩
⟨But→
The real hell was still waiting for me ahead of me⟩