Next.
Come on, next.
Tang Tang, you're so skinny.
Give me your food.
That's Tang Tang's.
You...
Thanks.
Run faster next time,
or you won't get any food.
What's that?
A birthmark.
What's a birthmark?
A mark only I have.
Why don't I have one?
Not everyone does.
Yours is really pretty.
It's like a little flower.
That's really high.
Looks fun.
My parents took me on it before.
From the top, you can see the whole city.
That's nice.
You had parents?
I've never seen mine.
You'll meet good people someday
to take you home.
You'll have a home too.
Can we go play?
You need tickets.
I don't have money.
Me neither.
When I grow up,
I'll take you on the Ferris wheel.
Deal?
Deal. I'll remember that.
Always.
=The Hidden Truth=
=Episode 5=
What's that?
A birthmark.
What's a birthmark?
A mark only I have.
Why don't I have one?
Not everyone does.
Yours is really pretty.
It's like a little flower.
Tang Tang,
want to go somewhere fun?
Honestly,
I don't know why,
but I've forgotten
a lot from childhood.
(Incoming call: Tang Tang)
Ms. Tong?
Ms. Tong.
Yimo.
Your door's shut.
Look at me.
It's fine. I have my keys.
I made milk tea with grass jelly.
It's sweet.
You'll like it.
Open the door.
Let me bring it in.
No need. I'll take it myself.
It's fine. I'll help.
No need.
I mean,
I was cleaning.
It's a mess.
Give it to me.
Okay.
Hey,
didn't we say we'd go shopping?
Didn't get to last time.
You busy today?
Let's go out later.
Sure.
Then go back first.
I'll come get you when I'm done.
Okay, I'll wait.
See you in a bit.
Alright.
Ms. Tong.
This one looks good.
It'd suit you.
Let me see.
It's nice.
Yimo,
no wonder you studied design.
You have great taste.
Let me help you try it on.
No need.
It's fine.
Yimo,
I'll do it myself.
Okay.
Hey,
your dad told me
about what happened at the station.
He really laid into me.
I know you were saving your friend.
I understand.
But you're his only daughter.
If something happened to you,
what would he do?
It was my fault.
I never thought
things would get that far.
How did you know those people
at the teahouse?
I didn't know them.
I had no choice.
I didn't dare to tell my dad.
So I asked a classmate.
Turns out he's so unreliable.
Listen.
From now on,
if there's anything you can't tell your dad,
just tell me.
At least you'll have someone to talk to.
Besides,
your dad's a grown man.
Men think differently
from us sometimes.
Okay.
Here.
Tang, not just you.
Whenever your friends
or coworkers come by,
just let me know.
It's on the house.
Thank you.
You and Yimo are close, right?
Not really.
In the dog theft case,
Yimo stepped in to help.
That was the first time we met.
Do detectives handle dog theft too?
Of course.
Big or small,
it's our job.
Well,
she's my only child.
Here's to you.
Thanks.
You're a good guy.
Hold on, sir.
I can't drink this yet.
I think you misunderstood.
Yimo and I are just friends.
That's it.
You're making me feel
kind of embarrassed.
I really think
you're a good guy.
What do you think of Yimo?
She's great.
Kind and warm.
Honestly,
when I first met her,
it feels like
she's familiar.
It's like
we knew each other as kids.
But she said
she doesn't remember anything
from back then.
Ms. Tong.
What's that scar from?
Oh, that?
An old accident
back home.
Did it scare you?
There's a dermatologist
at Third City Hospital.
Great with scar removal.
My friend Xiaoqian
had a scar on her forehead.
She got it removed.
Now you can't even tell.
If you want, I'll go with you.
I'm used to it.
Besides,
it's on my back.
I barely see
or think about it.
If you ever change your mind,
tell me.
Okay.
Ms. Tong,
where's your hometown?
I'm from Shancheng.
I thought so.
Your accent sounded like it.
Not many people from there here.
It's pretty rare.
Funny thing is,
everyone I've met from there is really nice.
I've never visited though.
There's nothing to see.
You'd regret it.
Sir,
did something happen to Yimo
when she was little?
I mean, when I mentioned
the welfare home,
and being adopted,
she said she can't remember a thing.
Yimo is my daughter.
That won't change
no matter what.
Don't take this wrong, sir.
I just want to look out for her.
Cheers, sir.
So Ms. Tong,
how did you meet my dad?
I asked him,
but he won't say.
I had a ton of luggage
when I moved in,
but the movers
dumped them in the hallway.
Said carrying it inside cost extra.
Can you believe that?
And then,
your dad came home
and got blocked.
In the end,
he carried everything in for me,
piece by piece.
Seriously?
He hates chores.
Right?
He was exhausted.
So I thought,
I couldn't just ignore that.
Since then,
I've been baking
for him.
Day by day,
we got familiar.
What?
The way you two met
was too coincidental.
Even a screenwriter couldn't make it up.
It's been tough for Yimo.
So I just
don't want her hurt again.
I worry she might feel unhappy.
So I've been checking in on her.
I grew up in a welfare home too.
So I can really relate.
You did?
Which one was it?
I wasn't there for long.
I was about that tall.
I don't remember much.
My master took me away.
And I just
grew up healthy, right?
Want anything else? We can order more.
That's enough.
Your beer.
Yimo, you ordered beer?
Ms. Tong,
can you drink?
Not really.
Two glasses and I'm tipsy.
I don't buy that.
You look like you can handle it.
I really can't.
Here. Have some meat.
Come on, Ms. Tong.
My dad's not around.
It's just us.
He never lets me
drink outside alone.
Says it's not safe.
But you're here,
so he can't say anything.
Alright. I'll drink with you.
How could you drink this much?
And it's so late.
Really unsafe.
Don't do this again, okay?
Yimo,
if anything's wrong,
tell me.
You're a good kid.
Your dad's a good man.
You're all good people.
If we could be one family,
that'd be even better.
Let me pull over.
Ms. Tong.
Just let it out.
Get her a bottle of water.
Ali,
trust me.
I'll treat Yimo well.
Just like you do.
Like my own daughter.
You're really drunk.
Ms. Tong, drink some water.
(Qingcheng Public Security Bureau)
Li Xu's file. Take a look.
Can I have a sip?
(Personal File: Li Xu)
Master, I found something.
Back at the old teahouse,
I felt something was off.
Li Xu
is one of the hidden investors there.
And also in the dog shelter.
I've got a hunch
that he's playing a bigger role
behind the scenes.
(Personal File: Li Xu)
I think we should
dig into him.
Li Xu needs checking.
But we still need the dog thieves.
Alright.
You've already narrowed that down.
Keep on it.
I'm on it.
However,
you've shown your face at the teahouse.
The round of checks.
I'll handle it.
Captain Zhao.
I heard from Mr. Qin
you chased a racer fugitive
for 80km back in the day
and forced him to stop.
All that old stuff.
Only Qin still remembers.
With skills like yours,
why don't you drive yourself?
You brat.
What captain drives his own car?
What are you here for?
Me?
Tea.
Tea?
You want it
light or strong?
What's the difference?
Big difference.
If you come during the day,
people usually go light.
But in the evening,
they prefer it strong.
I see.
I'll just have whatever.
Hello, what would you like?
(Old Teahouse)
No prices listed here?
How much for Maojian?
Eighty one cup.
Eighty?
Scan here.
Bai.
You sure
your plan'll work?
Li,
everything's set.
We're about to move.
What are you worried about?
Not worried.
Just that guy you picked.
I don't know him well.
Haven't worked together.
Sounds like you don't trust me.
That's not it.
I mean,
if we're running a honey trap
to lure rich suckers
and big shots,
we don't need a real chef.
We got to use the best ingredients.
Li,
we need a proper front.
No good chef,
no bait.
Fine.
I won't interfere.
But let me be clear upfront,
if your guy
screws up,
you're fully responsible.
Seven Character.
Dad? You're home?
Not at the restaurant?
Everything's arranged.
We're closing early tomorrow.
Taking the next two days off, too.
You've never
closed early
except for New Year's Eve.
What's so important?
A banquet.
What kind?
Client provides the venue.
We send the chef.
How's Li Tong?
She's fine.
Don't worry.
But,
I realized I made a big mistake.
What's that?
Not inviting you along.
The three of us have never eaten together.
So,
I had an idea.
A crazy one?
I'm having dinner with Ms. Tong tonight.
Come with us.
I booked a really nice place.
We can all have dinner
and chat.
I don't have time.
You always say that.
I already booked it.
No refunds.
You wouldn't waste my money, right?
Yimo...
Dad, please.
Ms. Tong and I already agreed.
Please.
Come with us.
I booked
a really nice place for tonight.
I got my dad to come.
Dress nice, okay?
(Yimo)
(Goes as planned)
Tea lovers,
I'm at a new spot today.
Check out the place.
Look, a rickshaw.
Nice. Very old-fashioned.
There's even a rooster.
Must be a historic building.
Oh, an old gate.
Great.
Nice vibe,
actually.
Your Maojian. Receipt.
Thanks.
Add more tea.
Extra tea's 20. Want it?
What are you doing?
You call this Maojian?
It is.
Maojian's green tea.
But you served me red.
Sir,
you didn't say
red or green when you ordered.
Why are you mad now?
Of course I'm mad.
I heard this place was classy.
Good views, good tea.
I came to enjoy myself.
You serve me this?
Think I can't afford better?
Well, sir,
it's not at this hour.
During daytime,
the tea's all like this.
What do you mean?
Did I come at the wrong time?
Night tea's much better?
Guaranteed.
But you know,
it's a bit more pricey.
Price doesn't matter.
My pension's high.
Please have some tea first.
Let me get you a fresh pot.
- Go on.
- Yes, sir.
(Community Service Center)
Officer,
here's the rental list.
The info you asked is in here.
Thanks. You carry on.
Sure.
(Rental Tenant Registry)
(Zhang Junlong; Wang Hu)
(Qingcheng Public Security Bureau)
What's up, old man?
Had a spending spree?
You ordered an 80-a-cup tea?
Didn't that hurt when you paid?
Work-related. I'll get reimbursed.
I'm not paying out of pocket.
Well,
after that cup,
can you still drink
a five-yuan pack?
It's fake. Not real Maojian.
You could tell?
I don't buy it often
doesn't mean I don't know tea.
Fake tea.
Fake teahouse too.
I need
to dig a little deeper on Li Xu.
I just went
over the dog thieves' info again.
Turns out they're pretty interesting.
Lately they've been all over the place.
And I think they're not too bright.
Doesn't feel like
they could plan that many thefts.
And I keep thinking
they're somehow connected
to Hongyun Restaurant.
If you suspect it,
find evidence
to prove it.
So I'm not forcing connections now?
What's that supposed to mean?
Recognition.
Then say it.
Why do you
always talk in riddles?
You stubbornness and little mind games.
Straight talk's boring.
If you won't say it straight,
neither will I.
Anyway,
someone's been acting different lately.
Don't copy my tricks.
What are you hinting at?
Funny how some grumpy old guy
was dead-set
against this case a while ago.
Now his eyes light up
when he works it.
Master,
can you tell me
why you didn't
want this case back then?
We're at this point now,
please just tell me.
Is the Nude Banquet Case
connected to the welfare home
I grew up in?
Yes.
Back then, we realized
the banquet
happened more than once.
The time it all went wrong,
those kids
were from
the welfare home you lived in.
Captain.
We can't call off the task force.
We can't just shelve this case.
No new leads.
We can't put all our manpower on this.
Other cases are piling up.
Give me more time.
I'll keep digging.
There will be leads.
It's not that I won't give you time.
Zhao Fengcheng, listen.
You're not working just one case.
Cases are piling up.
- Captain.
- If you keep burning yourself on this,
you'll be drained.
You get that?
No, Cap...
(Captain)
The welfare home was shut down.
The kids
were sent for adoption
or transferred.
You know,
Tang Tang was there too.
Tang Zhigang was your buddy.
Would you
look after his son?
I...
I'm not fit to raise a kid.
Zhao Fengcheng,
don't forget you're a detective.
You have to adjust
and move on.
The case is shelved,
not dead.
I believe that one day,
we'll crack it.
Even if we can't,
the younger ones will.
The next generation will.
Come.
Had I not been so lost back then,
I should've adopted you.
You wouldn't have ended up there.
After the case,
I got scared.
So I took you out.
But now,
the case's reopened.
It's not I'm against it.
It's just...
I don't want you dragged into it.
What's wrong with you?
What's with the low spirit?
You look like a rookie.
Look at me.
Young,
brilliant,
and full of promise.
Who trained me?
You did.
Where'd you learn that thick skin?
From you, who else?
That's better.
Yell at me once in a while.
That makes me feel better.
Master,
I found Huahua.
My friend at the welfare home
who went missing.
I found her.
You did?
Yes.
Not just that.
I also found out
why she disappeared
and why she forgot everything at the time.
How did you find her?
Who is it?
Wang Yimo.
You're sure?
Absolutely.
You know what I felt
after I knew?
Regret.
Even though I was a kid,
why didn't I
stand up back then?
If I had,
maybe things would've been different.
She wouldn't have
gone through that.
forgotten everything.
You were just a kid too.
Nothing you could do.
But now I'm not.
I've got this case now.
I'll see it through.
I'm not that clueless kid anymore.
Though I'm still a bit green.
I'll give it everything I've got.
I'm gonna reel in every last one
of those scumbags
from that case.
I'll fulfill
your long-held wish.
And for the victims,
including Huahua,
I'll see justice done.
Boss,
is there really no other way?
What are you saying?
Ali,
all these years,
we've been keeping our heads down.
If we take this job,
we're back in the mud.
I've said all I need to.
Get to work.
Coming.
Let's go.
Stop drinking.
We're not late.
Still got time.
Dad,
we can't go empty-handed.
What do you mean?
Come with me.
Please enjoy.
Thanks.
Dad, hurry up.
What's wrong?
Let's go inside.
Sure.
Ms. Tong.
You're here.
These are from my dad.
Traffic?
A bit.
Good thing we left early.
I saw someone talking to you.
Who was it?
Wrong table.
Is this for three?
Two.
Dinner's already arranged.
Alright.
My job's done.
I'll leave you two to it.
Have a lovely night.
I'm heading out.
This feels like a TV show.
(Wang Li was at the restaurant today.
Wang Li had a business dinner.)
(He stayed home today.)
(No text for days.
He hasn't been at the restaurant.)
(On a business trip. Back tomorrow.
Didn't find out what for.)
(Be sharp; His daughter's back.
Got it.)
♪Dreams of the past sleep in the chill♪
♪Now I run toward the light♪
♪What does the fire burn,
what does it reveal?♪
♪Is the answer found when the sun rises♪
♪If it's all a lie♪
♪Should I tear it open?♪
♪If it's all part of the journey♪
♪Then face the blaze head-on♪
♪Let the sun awaken my heart's crave♪
♪Pain reminds me I'm alive♪
♪The world can't take away every clear sky♪
♪The hotter it gets, the fiercer I fight♪
♪Let the sun burn away all I lean upon♪
♪Leave me only what endures♪
♪At the cliff's edge, all fear shatters♪
♪With a grounded heart, a soul like fire♪