(Jaeseung)
(Seungjin)
(Minseon)
(Hwi)
(Youngjoon)
(Seongmin)
(Hanmin)
(Myeongkyun)
(Episode 6: A Secret Night Date)
(Myeongkyun's car)
(Myeonggyun driving his car to get to the date location)
(Minseon: I'm really curious about the date location)
(Myeongkyun: You'll know when you get there)
(Minseon: Do you know what we do there?)
(Myeongkyun: Of course)
(Minseon: Really? Wow, I'm looking forward to what we'll do)
(Myeongkyun: I was thinking where to go)
(Myeongkyun: Look forward to...)
(Minseon: Is it worth looking forward to? Or don't look forward to it?)
(Myeongkyun: Isn't it better to look forward to it?)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Myeongkyun: If you don't look forward to it at all...)
(Minseon: Of course. I'm (looking forward) to it to begin with)
Yeah.
(Myeongkyun: If you don't look forward to it at all...)
(Minseon: Of course. I'm (looking forward) to it to begin with)
(Myeongkyun: I think)
(Myeongkyun: you'll like it very much)
(Myeongkyun: Even if you don't like it very much, you wouldn't dislike it)
(Minseon: Something I like?)
(Minseon: It feels like something active)
(Minseon: Or crafts? Maybe that...)
(Minseon: I'm just guessing)
It's a bit of both.
(How accurate is the perceptive Minseon's prediction?)
-A bit of both? -Yes.
(Minseon: You didn't sleep much last night. Are you okay?)
(Minseon: You stayed up last night. You barely slept for a few hours)
(Myeongkyun: Actually...)
(Myeongkyun: my condition's not great)
(Myeongkyun: But I'm excited)
(Minseon: Oh, really? That's a relief that you're excited)
(Minseon: When you shot me the "arrow" right away, I was really touched)
(Myeongkyun: I happened to get an arrow card)
(Minseon: Luckily you chose it)
(I wanted to go on a date with you)
(Myeongkyun: You took the initiative to call me yesterday)
(Minseon: I didn't receive a single call yesterday)
(Hesitant) (Myeongkyun: It was... a bit...)
(Minseon: I'm not upset about it)
(Minseon: Just that that was the situation)
(Minseon: I felt like I said something wrong)
(Minseon: Just because he didn't call me,)
(Minseon: I didn't want him to feel sorry)
(Minseon: I kept wishing I could take what I said back)
(Myeongkyun: But we can talk while on a drive. It's nice)
(Minseon: Yeah. I feel relaxed too)
(Minseon: Since yesterday, I thought you were so funny every time I talked to you)
Really?
(Minseon: I think we have a similar sense of humor)
(Myeongkyun: Is it a good thing?)
(Minseon: Of course)
(Myeongkyun: Cracking jokes requires only one thing)
(Minseon: What is it?)
(Myeongkyun: Courage)
(Hahaha. That's right)
(Myeongkyun: As long as you have courage, there's nothing you can't say)
(Hahaha, that's right)
(The two men on a date where they laugh even about trivial things)
(Location of Myeongkyun & Minseon's date: Diffuser and solid air freshener workshop)
I'm so excited.
I love diffusers.
(Location of Myeongkyun & Minseon's date: Diffuser and solid air freshener workshop)
I must have it at home.
(Myeongkyun: The first date I prepared was the diffuser workshop)
(Myeongkyun: I like things related to fragrances)
(Myeongkyun: Minseon also said he made soap yesterday)
(Myeongkyun: So I thought about having a date at the workshop)
(Myeongkyun: I decided on the diffuser workshop)
(Minseon: If I take home what I make,)
(Minseon: I think I'll be very happy)
(Minseon: I was very happy as soon as I went in)
(Minseon: What kind of flower do I remind you of?)
(Myeongkyun: Hmm...)
(Myeongkyun: Because I like roses)
-Roses? -Yes.
(Roses?)
(Myeongkyun: Among roses, if there are pink roses like this, it'd suit you)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Myeongkyun: A shade between beige and pink)
(Minseon: When I see you... I don't know many kinds of flowers)
(Minseon: Anyway, my favorite flower is the sunflower)
(Myeongkyun: Sunflowers?)
(Minseon: When you look at flowers, you have to bend down or go close)
(Minseon: But even if you look from far away, you can see it's a sunflower)
(Myeongkyun: I understand what you mean)
(Minseon: Right?)
(Myeongkyun: Eye-catching at a glance)
(Minseon: Yes. Eye-catching at a glance)
(Minseon: No matter who looks at it, it's obviously a sunflower)
(Nodding)
This is good.
(Minseon: Oh! It's pretty)
(Myeongkyun: How about finishing up after this?)
Just do that?
(Myeongkyun: It's been a while since I felt the agony of creation)
(Minseon: Oh, but it's colorful. It's pretty)
(Myeongkyun: I'm in big trouble)
(Minseon: What's wrong?)
(Myeongkyun: I want to start designing the flowers again)
(Minseon: Why?)
(Myeongkyun: I feel... like...)
(Minseon: We still have a lot of time. Take your time)
(Myeongkyun: Oh, that's a good idea)
(Myeongkyun: I really wanted to make a perfect one)
(Myeongkyun: to make him 100% satisfied)
(Myeongkyun: Although it's my first time, I really want to make it well)
(Minseon: When you had to invite someone on a date, why did you pick me?)
(Minseon: I was curious)
(Myeongkyun: When I invited you on a date?)
(Hmm...)
(Myeongkyun: First, I've been interested in you since yesterday)
(Myeongkyun: I was curious what you were like. I wanted to have a deeper conversation with you)
(Myeongkyun: The moment I saw you holding the heart card, I thought...)
(Myeongkyun: I should just (invite you) right away. That's what I thought)
(Minseon: That's a relief. Did you want to go on a date with me from the beginning?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Minseon: Oh, really? I'm so happy. Thank you)
(Minseon: When I called you yesterday,)
(Minseon: I was really nervous. When I called you yesterday)
(Myeongkyun: Thank you)
(Minseon: It's positive nervousness)
(Minseon: I'm suddenly curious)
(Minseon: What was your first impression of me?)
(Myeongkyun: First impression? You looked very cheerful)
(Minseon: Do I look cheerful?)
(Minseon: We said the same thing)
(Minseon: I said you looked bright)
(Minseon: My first impression of you was that you looked bright)
(Myeongkyun: Because of my big eyes?)
(Minseon: No, it's not because of big eyes)
(Minseon: What I meant was your vibe? The atmosphere?)
(Minseon: It felt like the atmosphere changed with your entrance)
(Minseon: Something like that)
(Myeongkyun: (People usually tell me) their first impression of me is that I have bright eyes)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Minseon: That you look kind?)
(Myeongkyun: To put it childishly, it's like they're shiny)
(Minseon: It's not childish but a cute description)
-Really? -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: Because I graduated from Waffle University)
(T/N: "Waffle University" is the name of a Korean waffle shop)
(Myeongkyun: I have a limited vocab which extends up to "shiny")
(Minseon: Gosh, I shouldn't laugh)
(Minseon: I crack up easily)
(Minseon: at goofy stuff and jokes)
(Minseon: I laugh really easily)
(Minseon: But he always makes me laugh)
(Minseon: So I think we're really compatible (in terms of humor))
(Myeongkyun: Some people might not think it's funny)
(Myeongkyun: and not understand why we're laughing)
(Myeongkyun: As they say, it's a niche sense of relating to each other)
(Myeongkyun: Only those who know it, know it)
(Ah, it smells so good)
(Minseon: I can't smell this one, but I love this one. It's so pretty)
(Myeongkyun: It smells like the flower shop I used to go to often when I was young)
(Minseon: Ah, really?)
(Minseon: You can't smell it. Because the bottle cap is closed)
(Minseon: Oh, it smells good. I can't help but smell it)
(Minseon: Where should I put this? Somewhere precious)
(Myeongkyun: By your bed)
(Minseon: By my bed? Okay)
(Minseon: This time when I received (the diffuser and solid air freshener) from Myeongkyun,)
(Minseon: to a certain degree, it felt precious to me)
(A fragrant date that pulled them closer together)
(Location of Myeongkyun & Minseon's second date)
(Outdoor cafe by the blue river)
(Minseon: I love stuff like that. Blue sofa)
(Myeongkyun: It has a nice vibe)
(Myeongkyun: There)
(Minseon: Oh! Pink chairs!)
(Minseon: We can go up. Shall we take photos here?)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(A chair sculpture that attracts their attention)
(Minseon: This way or this way? Look this way from this way?)
(Focused)
(Minseon: I should include the chair and the background scenery)
(Minseon: During my date with Myeongkyun,)
(Minseon: I had so much fun)
(Minseon: I really wanted to commemorate it)
(Minseon: with many photos)
(Giving each other the photos they took)
This came out on the black side.
(Minseon: Shall we sit over there?)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Myeongkyun: The whole scenery is nice, but my pose is so-so)
(Minseon: I think photos will turn out well on this sofa. Because there's a river behind)
Yes.
(Myeongkyun: Shall we take a selfie here?)
(Minseon: I'd like that)
(Taking selfies full of excitement)
(Myeongkyun: A train just passed by)
(Minseon: A train?)
(Myeongkyun: A train, whoosh, passed by)
(Minseon: Did you get it in the photo?)
(Myeongkyun: I should've taken it)
(Minseon: Your face is so handsome)
(Minseon: The photo turned out nice)
(Minseon: Because the model looks good)
(Myeongkyun: But this...)
(We look good together)
Really?
(Chemistry is evident in their hearts and eyes)
I didn't expect that.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
(Here's the food)
-Looks yummy. -Looks yummy.
(Myeongkyun: There's more meat in the middle)
(Minseon: It's rare to hear someone talk about meat for pizza)
(Myeongkyun: Pizza is also meat)
(Myeongkyun: Cheese is key. Do you agree?)
(Minseon: Agreed)
(Minseon: Cheese is the most important in pizza)
(Myeongkyun: Thank you for the food)
(Minseon: Thank you for the food)
(Minseon: I'll be the king's food taster)
(King's food taster)
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(Mmm!) (Is it delicious?)
Then I'll try it with the mind of a king.
(Hahaha) (Myeongkyun: Then I'll try it with the mind of a king)
(Minseon: I'll be your food taster, Your Majesty)
(Myeongkyun: It's the satisfying taste of a king's meal)
(Myeongkyun: It's been a long time since I ate outside)
(Minseon: Me too)
(Minseon: Because it's hot in summer,)
(Minseon: I don't think about eating outdoors)
(Myeongkyun: I was curious about something. Can I ask?)
(Minseon: Of course you can ask)
(Myeongkyun: It's about ideal types)
(Minseon: About ideal types?)
(Myeongkyun: Looks-wise and personality-wise, what's your type?)
(Minseon: Looks-wise...)
(Minseon: I like those who look active)
(Minseon: Personality-wise, someone who seems cold but is considerate)
(Minseon: When I say that, people will ask if I mean a "tsundere")
(Minseon: I think it's right too)
(Minseon: But anyway, no matter what, he needs to be considerate)
(Minseon: I think being considerate is the best)
(Myeongkyun: I think I get what your type is)
(Minseon: What about you?)
(Myeongkyun: I don't think I have a fixed type)
(Minseon: Oh. Looks-wise?)
(Myeongkyun: Someone who fits me well when they're with me)
(Myeongkyun: I like that type)
(Myeongkyun: Personality-wise...)
(Myeongkyun: I'd say random nonsense from time to time)
(Myeongkyun: It'd be great if they're receptive of it)
(Minseon: I never thought you were talking nonsense)
(Minseon: So do you think I'm close to your ideal type?)
(Myeongkyun: It's very... very close)
(Minseon: Nice. That made me very happy)
(Minseon: I think you're close to my ideal type too)
(Myeongkyun: Actually, when I invited you on a date,)
(Myeongkyun: rather than saying it through words, I was glad I could do it through a card)
(Myeongkyun: I'm not good at saying cheesy stuff)
(Myeongkyun: So I invited you on a date with my card)
(Myeongkyun: I was wondering how you felt when you received it)
I also thought...
(Minseon: I wished I could get your date request)
(Minseon: If you gave me your card,)
(Minseon: how should I react?)
(Minseon: That was what I was thinking)
(Minseon: When I really received your date request, I was surprised and stunned)
Okay.
(Minseon: Then... This question just occurred to me)
-What is it? -Well...
(Minseon: What do you value the most in a relationship?)
(Myeongkyun: I hope we don't become too overly dependent on each other)
(Myeongkyun: Take care of yourself first and maintain your condition)
(Myeongkyun: Rather than compromising without question)
(Myeongkyun: An appropriate amount of selfishness?)
(Minseon: An appropriate amount of selfishness? With your own opinions?)
(Myeongkyun: I think it's good to express your opinions)
Yeah.
(Minseon: For me... As long as you don't lie)
(Myeongkyun: Lies?)
(Minseon: I don't like lies)
(Minseon: If you don't get caught, I won't know either. So it doesn't matter)
(Minseon: But if I find out, it'll upset me)
(Myeongkyun: Lies? Lies...)
(Myeongkyun: It's not easy for me to lie)
(Minseon: I think so too)
(Myeongkyun: It's really easy to know my real thoughts)
(Myeongkyun: I wear my heart on my sleeves)
(Did the two get to know each other's true feelings?)
(Myeongkyun: In general, what did you think of the date?)
(Minseon: In general?)
(Minseon: I had so much fun)
(Minseon: Time flew by)
(Minseon: Not a moment did I feel tired)
(Minseon: I'd love to go on another date with you)
(Myeongkyun: Similarly, I was...)
(Myeongkyun: I tried to have a relaxing date, and I had a lot of fun)
(Minseon: Oh, really?)
(Minseon: That's a relief)
(Myeongkyun: I feel like the more I talk to you,)
(Myeongkyun: the more we seem compatible)
Really?
(Myeongkyun: Very interesting!)
(Minseon: Thank you for the positive feedback)
(Myeongkyun: To be honest,)
(Myeongkyun: I thought it'd be nice to go on a date)
(Myeongkyun: with others too)
(Minseon: Before we went on a date, I was really curious about him)
(Minseon: After the date, I felt we got along well)
(Minseon: I became a lot more interested in (Myeongkyun))
(Minseon: What could the others be doing?)
(Myeongkyun: Right. I'm curious about Jaeseung, who's at home)
(Minseon: Ah, yes)
(Myeongkyun: He's at home, right?)
(Minseon: I... I had so much fun)
(Minseon: I thought everyone else is on a date too)
(Minseon: Right, Jaeseung and...)
(Myeongkyun: I'm most curious about (Jaeseung & Hwi))
(Minseon: Jaeseung and... who was it? Hwi!)
(Minseon: I'm really curious how Hwi's doing)
(At the same time, in Men's House...)
(Hwi's taking a nap)
(Jaeseung goes back to his bedroom to rest)
(Checking his face)
(Patting)
(Notices something)
(A mysterious letter on Jaeseung's bed)
(What is it?)
(Jaeseung: What is this? Is there another mission?)
(Smiles)
(Here's a secret date chance for Jaeseung, who received the most calls yesterday)
Invite the man you like on a date)
(Invite the man you like on a date)
(Jaeseung: Life's not just a string of misfortunes)
(Jaeseung: Today's gonna be a really long day)
(Which man will Jaeseung choose for a date?)
(Seongmin and Seungjin come back from their date)
We had a fulfilling day today, right?
Yes, we did.
(Seongmin and Seungjin come back from their date)
(Jaeseung: You came back earlier than I thought. Did you have fun?)
(Seongmin: Did you have fun?)
(Seungjin: We went to a brunch cafe. It wasn't just a serious conversation)
(We had a super (?) serious conversation)
(Seongmin: We just had serious conversations the whole time)
(Jaeseung: It must be memorable)
(Seongmin and Seungjin's candles)
(Seongmin: What did you do?)
(Jaeseung: We're making Tanghulu)
(Jaeseung: But till now, the white sugar is still not turning into syrup)
(Seungjin: Why not? Did you add water?)
(Seongmin: Can you make Tanghulu?)
(Jaeseung: Based on the recipe: three servings of white sugar and two servings of water)
(Seungjin: Yes, yes)
(Seungjin: It's not boiling?)
(Jaeseung: It's boiling. It has been boiling for a long time, but...)
(Sugar Expert Seungjin)
(Seungjin: (The syrup) can’t be brown. You have to dip it when it's white)
(Seungjin: Also, it doesn't need to be sticky)
(Seungjin: It becomes stiff after cooling down)
(Jaeseung: You know it well. Should you've made it instead?)
(Seungjin: Have you ever stirred (the syrup)?)
(Jaeseung: No. Isn't it about to turn brown now?)
(Seungjin: In my opinion... hang on)
(Analyzing why the Tanghulu failed)
(Jaeseung: Is this ruined?)
(Seungjin: I think you should throw this away)
(Out!)
-No wonder it didn't work. -It's pretty, the Tanghulus.
(Jaeseung: No wonder it didn't work. I can't do it)
(Tanghulu: failed!)
(Seungjin: But we can eat... the delicious fruit skewers)
(Seungjin: But it'd be really yummy if they were made into Tanghulus)
(Jaeseung: Hwi said he couldn't give up on the Tanghulu and to keep boiling it)
(Jaeseung: We failed in the end~)
(Jaeseung: You're back?)
(Go on a date with me)
(How?)
(Seongmin: I really wanted to (go on a date) with him)
(Seongmin: I was so happy)
(Next, Minseon & Myeongkyun return from their date)
We're back. We're back.
We're back.
(Next, Minseon & Myeongkyun return from their date)
-Hi -Hi.
(Minseon: What are you doing?)
(Seongmin: We just came back)
(Minseon: You just came back? Where's Jaeseung?)
(Jaeseung: Me? I made Hwi do weight training)
(Myeongkyun: That's not a date)
(Minseon: We made diffusers)
(Seongmin: Wow, good for you)
(Myeongkyun: I made this (diffuser ) for him. Tada!)
(Minseon: There's one more)
(Minseon: The lid needs to be opened to smell the fragrance)
(Minseon: This one. Smell this)
(Seungjin: Did you make soap?)
(Minseon: It's not soap. It's a kind of air freshener)
A solid diffuser.
-It smells good. -Right?
It smells so good.
I happen to need this at home.
This is my favorite smell.
(Wow)
I made it myself.
(Hanmin & Youngjoon came home last)
Hide your hand.
Hide it.
(Hanmin & Youngjoon came home last)
-Tada. -You're back.
(Minseon: You're back)
(Minseon: What did you do?)
(Youngjoon: Guess what we did)
That sounds so...
(Minseon: What did you do?)
(Youngjoon: Guess what we did)
That sounds so...
(Youngjoon: I think we're the happiest ones today)
Really?
(Minseon: We had a good time too)
(Youngjoon: What were you doing?)
(Minseon: We were eating this)
(Hwi: We made Tanghulu)
-This is Tanghulu? -It's really yummy.
(Youngjoon: It's Tanghulu? You didn't just put fruits on a stick?)
-No, no. -It's Tanghulu.
-It's really delicious. -The sugar's amazing.
(Seungjin: It's so well done that you can't even see it)
-See? -Really.
(Laughing)
But it's delicious.
-Really. -It's delicious.
(Laughing)
(Youngjoon: It looks like you just washed them and put them on a stick)
(Seungjin: No, no, no)
(Seungjin: Look at the sheen)
-I don't see anything. -Look at the glaze.
(Disguised Tanghulu made by Jaeseung and Hwi?)
No, no.
-Did you dry it? -No.
It's shining. Look.
It shines under the light.
It's almost SK-II. Look.
(T/N: SK-II is a skincare brand)
(So funny)
It's almost SK-II. Look.
(T/N: SK-II is a skincare brand)
(So funny)
He said SK-II.
(Youngjoon: But I love Shine Muscats)
(Feeding him)
(Seongmin: I can feel it from their mannerisms that Youngjoon and Hanmin)
(Seongmin: are very close)
(Myeongkyun: He's trying hard)
(Myeongkyun: He doesn't even really like him. Why did you do that?)
(Myeongkyun: I don't think it was a romantic expression of love)
You'll get the wrong idea.
(Jaeseung: Then... let's go)
(Seongmin: Where to?)
-A date. -Me?
(Seungjin: What's this?)
(Seongmin: All of a sudden?)
-Me? -Yeah.
(Seungjin: What's this?)
(Seongmin: All of a sudden?)
-Me? -Yeah.
(Hwi: Did I hear it wrong? What happened?)
(Minseon: I was so shocked)
(Minseon: So suddenly? He's leaving so suddenly?)
(Seungjin: I was really shocked...)
-Wow, this is crazy. -Why?
(Seungjin: This is crazy)
(Let's go on a date, Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: I didn't have time to call Seongmin out alone)
(Jaeseung: So I did something rash)
Let's go on a date, Seongmin.
(Seongmin: I was surprised but also really excited)
(Seongmin: Frankly, I was really happy)
(Seongmin: Jaeseung was really assertive)
You chose the pairing?
I think Seongmin chose it.
(The men are confused by the unexpected situation)
Not Seongmin. I meant Jaeseung.
-Jaeseung? -Yes.
(Seungjin: Something must've happened)
-Do you have something too? -Hwi!
(Youngjoon: Oh... Hwi!)
(Youngjoon: Did you play a game?)
((Troubled) Hwi: No. Nothing)
Nothing?
(Youngjoon: Did you play a game?)
((Troubled) Hwi: No. Nothing)
(Seungjin: What’s going on? x2)
(Jaeseung: Get ready. Let's meet at 7 p.m.)
(Seongmin: Okay)
(Jaeseung: What did I just do?)
(Jaeseung reads the mission card again)
(Here's a secret date chance for Jaeseung, who received the most calls yesterday)
Invite the man you like on a date)
(Seongmin: I've wanted to go on a date with Jaeseung)
(Seongmin: What kind of date will it be?)
(Seongmin: I'm nervous and excited)
(Half-nervous and half-excited, preparing for the date)
(Seungjin: Something must've happened)
I really don't know.
(Seungjin: I suddenly have an idea)
(Seungjin: Something must've happened)
(Seungjin: Yesterday, only (Jaeseung and Seongmin) called each other)
(Devastated)
(Hwi: Ah, hang on, ah...)
(Hwi: This is agonizing)
(Hwi: Sigh... Ah... I was so annoyed)
(Hwi: Everything's annoying)
(Jaeseung & Seongmin finish preparing for their date)
(Hwi: Where are you going?)
(Jaeseung: I don't know either)
(Seongmin: I really don't know what's going on)
I don't know either.
(Jaeseung & Seongmin leave in a hurry)
Why did you smoke without me?
(Hugging him tight)
(Hwi: After (Jaeseung and Seongmin) left, I felt wronged)
(Hwi: Youngjoon consoled me with a hug)
(Hwi: I really almost cried)
(Seungjin: Did Jaeseung know about this since the morning, so he didn't pick a mission card?)
(Seungjin: He knew this since the morning)
(Seungjin: That's why he didn't pick a card even when Youngjoon kept asking him to pick one)
(Minseon: It's possible!)
(Youngjoon: Was he acting the whole time?)
I feel like a genius.
(Minseon: It's possible!)
(Youngjoon: Was he acting the whole time?)
(Hwi: Right. He was the first to go down in the morning)
I feel like a genius.
(Youngjoon: It was so close to him)
-Right. -Right.
(Gosh, I'm really...)
(Youngjoon: We were all tricked)
(Seungjin: Crazy)
(Youngjoon: This might be a far-fetched assumption)
(Youngjoon: If that's really the case, (Jaeseung) is too scary)
(Youngjoon: It'd be too scary)
(Hanmin: Or maybe when (Jaeseung and Hwi) were at home,)
(Hanmin: when you were separated, another (mission card) was left on the table?)
(Minseon: It's possible too)
(Youngjoon: Maybe when Hwi was asleep, there was something on the table)
In my opinion, this is the most possible option.
(Minseon: This is the most possible option)
It must be this.
(Youngjoon: But it was a chance for one of you two)
(Youngjoon: But you fell asleep like a fool)
That's the most possible option.
(Sleeping ruined your life!)
(Youngjoon: But you fell asleep like a fool)
(Minseon: This makes the most sense)
Yes, that's the most possible.
(Youngjoon: Then he hid the (mission card))
(Minseon: It must be this)
Yes, that's the most possible.
(Youngjoon: Then he hid the (mission card))
(Minseon: It must be this)
(Men's House in chaos after Jaeseung's sudden date request)
It must be this. Accurate.
-I think... -I heard that sound.
(Men's House in chaos after Jaeseung's sudden date request)
-What? -I think...
It's almost 90% right.
I heard a duck sound, like a beep.
(Youngjoon: We need to check the table in the living room every hour)
(Hwi: Wait! I want to check it first)
(Nothing)
(Checking the table for additional(?) mission cards)
(Minseon: For us, today's surprise is over)
-Yes. -We have no more surprises.
(What other changes will happen in Men's House today?)
(Men are here to check their love fortunes)
I want to get one.
I'm most curious about Hwi's.
(Men are here to check their love fortunes)
-Yes, Hwi. -It feels meaningless.
(Cheering for Hwi wholeheartedly)
What is it? What is it?
(Please get a good one)
(Hanmin: At least get a good fortune)
Which one do you want to get?
(Youngjoon: Go get the one you want. Got it?)
(Youngjoon: Not what you can catch but what you want)
(Got it, little baby?)
-Got it? -Got it.
(Hanmin: Heart thumping)
(Seungjin: Will you read it thrice?)
Read it yourself first.
(Hanmin: Heart thumping)
(Seungjin: Will you read it thrice?)
(Ah, so accurate)
(Why) (Why) (Why) (Why)
Be quiet.
(You'll be plunged into confusion)
-Is that all? -Yes.
-How's it... -How can it be so accurate?
(Hwi: Why is it so accurate?)
(Youngjoon: There's a reason you wanted the purple one)
(Hwi: If I'd known this would happen, I wouldn't have drawn (my love fortune). It's just like my current situation)
(Hwi: I was upset, so I threw it slightly)
(Hwi: I threw it slightly, without much force)
(After the storm-like time...)
♫I didn't mean it; I'm really sorry♫
(Hwi & Seungjin laying on the third floor to calm down)
(That wasn't intentional
I'm really sorry)
(Hwi: Is this the song you sang in the morning?)
Yes, so sad.
(Who knows)
(Hwi: It's really the OST of today.)
(Hwi: To be honest, I feel a deep sense of betrayal.)
But I'm not worried that they will progress further.
(Hwi: But I'm not worried that they (Jaeseung & Seongmin) will progress further.)
(Seungjin: Good. Good. That’s the spirit.)
(Seungjin: But where are they going this late at night?)
(Hwi: Right? Where are they going now?
Seungjin: Are they going to spend the night outside?)
(No way, no. That can't be...)
(Angry)
(Seungjin: I don't know anything now.)
(Seungjin: I was just so shocked that they said they were going on a date.)
-I hope they go somewhere boring.
-That's right.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
-I hope they go somewhere boring.
-That's right.
Somewhere really tough.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
That's right. The two of them.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
-Sweat a lot.
-They must've gone to Seoraksan.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
-Somewhere they can't see the night scenery...
-That's right.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
-And is boring.
-That's right.
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
(I hope they go somewhere boring... Somewhere really tough
Sweat a lot
Somewhere they can't see the night scenery and is boring)
(That's right
They must've gone to Seoraksan
(That's right)
(Cries)
I don't know.
(It's okay...)
Are you crying?
(No it's okay)
It's okay. You seem to be gritting your teeth.
(You seem to be gritting your teeth)
(Hahaha)
It's okay. You seem to be gritting your teeth.
(You seem to be gritting your teeth)
(Hahaha)
It's okay.
(Seungjin: I didn't get a call back from Jaeseung today,)
(Seungjin: but if I don't develop feelings for anyone else,)
(Seungjin: I will still call Jaeseung.
Hwi: Yes.)
(Hwi: I won't give up either.)
(Hwi: Should I be assertive from now on?)
(Hwi: But talking about this among brothers...)
(Why care about that!)
(Exactly, why do I care about that?)
(Seungjin: Love needs to be fought for.
Hwi: That's right)
(Seungjin: But I wasn't able to fight for it...
Hwi: Yeah, me neither.)
(Seungjin: But I wasn't able to fight for it...)
(I'm a loser, loner)
(Seungjin: It makes me see the truth again, something like that?)
(Seungjin: That Jaeseung has a perfect liking for Seongmin now.)
(Hwi: The polaroids taken today...
Seungjin: Are you going to tear all of them?)
(I'm going to put them in the waffle machine!)
(Laugh)
(Hwi: Did I go too far? I suddenly feel sorry.)
(Hwi: I take that back. I take that back.)
It's really funny.
(Seungjin: Yes, you think the same.)
(Seungjin: Like how you want to get along well with Seongmin,)
(Seungjin: Jaeseung shares the same thought.)
(Seungjin: Seongmin may not have any thoughts about it.)
(Hwi: No, Seongmin and I are more compatible.)
(Yeah)
(That's right!)
(Hwi: Why did you turn your head? Why did you turn your head?
Seungjin: This is fate.)
(Seungjin: But what do you like about Seongmin?)
(Hwi: I don't know either. Just...)
(Hwi: I don't have a fixed ideal type to start with. A wide range.)
But feels like it's slowly becoming Seongmin.
(Hwi: I feel like my ideal type is slowly becoming Seongmin.)
((Ha...))
But feels like it's slowly becoming Seongmin.
(Hwi: I feel like my ideal type is slowly becoming Seongmin.)
((Ha...))
(On the other hand,
what are the other men in Men's House doing?)
(The men who are sharing about today's date)
Did you make two things at the same place?
No, no.
(The men who are sharing about today's date)
-Wax and... -Yes one place.
We did it at the same place.
(The men who are sharing about today's date)
-After that we went to a cafe.
-Yeah, we went to a cafe.
(The men who are sharing about today's date)
-After that we went to a cafe.
-Yeah, we went to a cafe.
(Youngjoon: You always do a lot of things.
Minseon: Yes.)
It's good.
(Youngjoon: You always do a lot of things.
Minseon: Yes.)
(Youngjoon: Making a ring which was something I've never done even when I was dating.
Minseon: I've never worn a ring before either)
It's good.
(Youngjoon: You always do a lot of things.
Minseon: Yes.)
(Youngjoon: Making a ring which was something I've never done even when I was dating.
Minseon: I've never worn a ring before either)
(Myeongkyun: Me neither!)
I've never worn a couple ring.
(Minseon: I've never worn a couple ring. I'm so jealous.)
-It's my first time making it.
-I'm so jealous.
(Minseon: I've never worn a couple ring. I'm so jealous.)
(Youngjoon: We're wearing a couple ring so stop eyeing us.)
(Myeongkyun: I don't like it. It looks like a thorn.)
(Myeongkyun: Hanmin is not the type that Youngjoon would like.)
(Myeongkyun: Given Youngjoon's type, I should attract him more.
I have nothing to say.
(Leaving only Youngjoon and Myeongkyun
after Hanmin and Minseon left)
The last person to leave should turn off the lights.
(Leaving only Youngjoon and Myeongkyun
after Hanmin and Minseon left)
The last person to leave should turn off the lights.
(Youngjoon: But we are not eating dinner, so when are we going to say it?
Myeongkyun: Say what?)
(Youngjoon: That we know each other.
Myeongkyun: Right.)
(Myeongkyun: We don't have to say it.)
(But there's no need to hide it.)
(Minseon enters the room at this time)
(Myeongkyun: There's no one who's curious about it.)
(Youngjoon: But I feel like... Rather than hiding it...)
-Go ahead. -I just want to casually mention it.
(Minseon is watching their conversation)
-I don't care.
-That we knew each other before.
(Minseon is watching their conversation)
I don't care. Just say.
I don't feel comfortable cause it's so vague.
(Youngjoon and Myeongkyun's conversation which seems like a secret to Minseon)
-I got it.
-What's wrong?
(Youngjoon and Myeongkyun's conversation which seems like a secret to Minseon)
(Minseon: What's wrong?)
-I got it.
-What's wrong?
(Minseon: What's wrong?)
(Youngjoon: Actually, we knew each other.
Minseon: Really?)
(Youngjoon: So I was going to gather everyone tomorrow and talk about it.)
(Youngjoon: We're talking about when we should talk about it.)
-I don't care.
-But everyone's out.
(Youngjoon: We're talking about when we should talk about it.)
-I don't care.
-But everyone's out.
(Youngjoon finally revealing that
he knows Myeongkyun)
-I don't care.
-But everyone's out.
He kept trying to discuss the timing with me.
(Youngjoon finally revealing that
he knows Myeongkyun)
-They're all out.
-Right?
(Youngjoon finally revealing that
he knows Myeongkyun)
(Youngjoon: It feels like lying if we act like we don't know each other.)
-They're all out.
-Right?
(Youngjoon finally revealing that
he knows Myeongkyun)
(Youngjoon: It feels like lying if we act like we don't know each other.)
(Minseon: How did you meet?
Youngjoon: Oh?)
(Myeongkyun: A long time ago.
Youngjoon: A long time ago... Well...)
(We used to contact each other and know each other's Instagram...)
(Ah...)
(Youngjoon: It's been three years, right? Two to three years.)
(Youngjoon: As I expected, the question I was worried about, "How do you know each other?"
(Youngjoon: Was asked by Minseon.)
(Youngjoon: I wanted to discuss how to answer this at first,)
(Youngjoon: so I took the initiative to talk (to Myeongkyun).)
So I took the initiative to talk.
(Youngjoon: But we got asked even before we discussed it.)
(Youngjoon: So I feel like I wasn't able to answer properly.)
(Minseon: I couldn't tell.)
(Minseon: I did think "they look pretty close,")
(Minseon: but I was more curious about how they met each other
(Minseon: and why they know each other.)
(Youngjoon: That's why I told him from the beginning.)
(Youngjoon: The fact that I was unforgiving to him was because we knew each other.)
(Minseon: Oh, really? That makes sense then.)
I'm not someone who does that to someone I just met.
(Youngjoon: I'm not someone who does that to someone I just met.)
(You are)
I'm not someone who does that to someone I just met.
-That's right.
-You're someone like this.
(Youngjoon: I'm not someone who does that to someone I just met.)
(You are)
(You are, you are)
(No)
(Minseon: Who should I believe?
Youngjoon: Believe what you see.)
(Minseon: Just trust myself?
Youngjoon: Trust yourself.)
-Got it.
-Nah, it's all fake.
(Minseon: Just trust myself?
Youngjoon: Trust yourself.)
-Got it.
-Nah, it's all fake.
(No, it's all fake)
-Got it.
-Nah, it's all fake.
Trust yourself.
(No, it's all fake)
(Youngjoon: You're the only person you can trust in the world.)
Yes.
(Myeongkyun: It feels more like if I were to go "eh?" when he first saw me, I'd go "yeah!")
-Right. -But I can't do that on my own accord.
You might not want that.
Yes.
(Youngjoon: So, as I just talked to you about,)
(Youngjoon: every time I talk to Myeongkyu, Hanmin would follow.)
So... So the two of us...
(Youngjoon: From Hanmin's points of view, he's someone who came to Men's house later, and is someone we met for the first time.)
-That's right.
-But we kept talking...
(Youngjoon: From Hanmin's points of view, he's someone who came to Men's house later, and is someone we met for the first time.)
(Youngjoon: But we kept talking among just the two of us somewhere. So I thought about what he would think.)
-That's right.
-But we kept talking...
Among just the two of us somewhere.
(Youngjoon: But we kept talking among just the two of us somewhere. So I thought about what he would think.)
-So I thought about what he would think.
-Yeah.
(Youngjoon: But we kept talking among just the two of us somewhere. So I thought about what he would think.)
(Youngjoon: When I was talking about that, I don't know if I was shying away a little,)
(Youngjoon: I wasn't able to properly look at Hanmin's face.)
(Hanmin: I didn't notice it at all.)
(Hanmin: They said they were just friends.)
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are on their way to the secret date venue)
I've always wanted to go on a date with you.
-That's great. That this happened.
-Yeah.
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are on their way to the secret date venue)
-That's great. That this happened.
-Yeah.
(Jaeseung: You're curious why we're on a date like this, right?
Seongmin: Yeah.)
-That's great. That this happened.
-Yeah.
-That this happened.
-You're curious why we're on
(Jaeseung: You're curious why we're on a date like this, right?
Seongmin: Yeah.)
-a date like this, right?
-Yeah.
(Jaeseung: You're curious why we're on a date like this, right?
Seongmin: Yeah.)
Today?
(Jaeseung: You're curious why we're on a date like this, right?
Seongmin: Yeah.)
(Seongmin: Today? Thinking about it,)
(Seongmin: I did say I wanted to go on a date with you yesterday.)
(Seongmin: He looked handsome from the side too, so my heart was fluttering.)
(Jaeseung: There's a privilege that's only given to me.
Seongmin: Is that so? Did you use it on me?)
(Jaeseung: I used my privilege on you.)
(Jaeseung: First, let me explain.)
The person with the most votes,
(Surprised)
(Jaeseong tells Seongmin about the secret mission)
The person with the most votes,
can get this privilege.
(Surprised)
(Jaeseong tells Seongmin about the secret mission)
-Really?
-Yes.
(Seongmin: Really? Yesterday?)
-Really?
-Yes.
-Yesterday? -Yesterday.
(Seongmin: Really? Yesterday?)
(Jaeseung: It's a privilege that the person who got the most votes during the call time can get.)
(Seongmin: It's an honor.)
(Jaeseung: If I were on the receiving end, I might get flustered.)
(Jaeseung: To relieve this kind of confusion,)
(Jaeseung: I think everything should be in order.)
(Jaeseung: I thought I should start with explaining (the secret mission).)
(Seongmin: Were you going to ask for a date with me?)
-Today? -Yes.
(Jaeseung: If I got the arrow card today, I would've asked to,)
(Jaeseung: But actually... Between arrow card and heart card,)
(Jaeseung: I would prefer to get a heart card more.)
(Seongmin: But I thought you were always interested in Hwi.)
(Jaeseung: But it's not wrong to say that I'm interested in Hwi.
Seongmin: Ah...)
(Jaeseung: I was interested in Hwi.
Seongmin: I see.)
(Jaeseung: So on the first day, and on the second day before a moment,)
(Jaeseung: I've always had more interest in Hwi.)
Really?
(Jaeseung: But anyway, I think one's interest can change.)
(Seongmin: Right. It's only been three days.)
(Jaeseung: It's only the third day.)
So now I'm just talking about my current situation.
(Jaeseung: So now I'm just talking about my current situation.)
-I don't want to hide these parts.
-Mm.
(Jaeseung: So now I'm just talking about my current situation.)
(Jaeseung: I don't want to hide these parts.)
-I don't want to hide these parts.
-Mm.
(As they were having the honest talk in the car, the sky starts getting dark)
(Jaeseung: We're here.)
(The two people's secret date venue,
a cafe with a beautiful view)
The weather is nice too.
(The two people's secret date venue,
a cafe with a beautiful view)
It's really nice.
(The two people's secret date venue,
a cafe with a beautiful view)
The view here is beautiful too.
(The two people's secret date venue,
a cafe with a beautiful view)
The backdrop is really beautiful.
(At dusk, the scenic date venue)
You can see it from there.
(A beautiful day
at a beautiful place)
You can see it from there.
(A beautiful day
at a beautiful place)
Wait.
-The view is really beautiful.
-Yeah.
(Seongmin: The view is really beautiful.)
-The view is really beautiful.
-Yeah.
(Jaeseung: Isn't it nice?
Seongmin: Yes, totally.)
(Jaeseung: Did you have fun today?)
(Seongmin: I just shared an honest conversation with Seungjin.
Seongmin: An honest conversation?)
(Seongmin: I spoke sincerely with Seungjin.)
(Seongmin: We talked about life.)
(Seongmin: What did you do?)
I taught Hwi workouts.
(Jaeseung: I taught Hwi workouts.)
(Jaeseung: We went to the pool and played with the water a for a little.)
You were a personal trainer for a day?
(Nodding)
(Seongmin: You were a personal trainer for a day?)
You were a personal trainer for a day?
(Nodding)
(Seongmin: You were a personal trainer for a day?)
(Thank you)
(Jaeseung: It looks delicious.
Seongmin: Amazing.)
(Seongmin: What did you order?
Jaeseung: Mine's orange juice.)
Can I put this like this?
(Seongmin: What did you order?
Jaeseung: Mine's orange juice.)
Can I put this like this?
(Busy)
Let's change.
What should I do?
(Busy)
(Jaeseung: Are you nervous? Seongmin: I am nervous.)
Here.
(Jaeseung: It's really awkward.)
-Me. -Yeah you go first.
(Seongmin: I thought you were handsome the first time I saw you.)
(Jaeseung: It's really awkward.)
(Seongmin: I thought you were handsome. So I was happy.)
(Seongmin: I was quite out of it then. But thinking about it now...)
(Jaeseung: It feels like we haven't had the time to know each other well.)
(Seongmin: It was a situation where we couldn't talk much.)
-It's like I was at a loss for words.
-Right.
(Seongmin: It was a situation where we couldn't talk much.)
(Jaeseung: It's like I was at a loss for words.)
-It's like I was at a loss for words.
-Right.
(Jaeseung: It should've been a day where I just spoke anything.)
-I haven't sorted out what to say.
-Yes.
(Jaeseung: It should've been a day where I just spoke anything.)
(Jaeseung: I haven't sorted out what to say.)
-I haven't sorted out what to say.
-Yes.
(Jaeseung: We've never met each other before.)
(Jaeseung: But now we're quite familiar with each other, right? As compared to then.)
(Jaeseung: So I think we can share some deeper conversations)
(Jaeseung: now.)
(Seongmin: What kind of person do you like?
Jaeseung: What kind of person?)
(Jaeseung: Someone pure.
Seongmin: Someone pure?)
(Jaeseung: From a certain point, I feel like I started putting more emphasis on this.)
-That I'm like this and the other party too.
-Yes. At a certain age.
(Jaeseung: From a certain point, I feel like I started putting more emphasis on this.)
(Jaeseung: That I'm like this and the other party too.)
-That I'm like this and the other party too.
-Yes. At a certain age.
(Jaeseung: When I was young, I would do something with a pure heart)
(Jaeseung: that would then turn into passion and excitement.)
(Jaeseung: But now when my heart flutters and things become passionate, I feel like I trip over something and calm down.)
(Jaeseung: That, because of this obstacle, I keep thinking "this won't work, neither would that.")
(Jaeseung: There are moments like this where I can't help myself.)
(Jaeseung: And I can see these from the other party.)
(Jaeseung: Should I say it feels like a reality check?)
(Seongmin: But I feel the same.)
(Jaeseung: So I think, I really don't want to date.)
(Jaeseung: There was a moment where I thought "I don't want to date for now" because of this.)
(Seongmin: I'm almost 30 too, so I understand what you mean.)
But I think that's because...
(Seongmin: But I think that's because... I want to find someone I can date for a longer time.)
-I want to find someone I can date for a longer time.
-That's right.
(Seongmin: But I think that's because... I want to find someone I can date for a longer time.)
(Seongmin: Actually, I joined Men's House cause I want to find a partner.)
(Seongmin: To be honest, I'm almost 30.)
(Seongmin: I don't want to enter a relationship that's going to end quickly easily.)
(Seongmin: I want to find someone who can accompany me
(Seongmin: like a partner for a longer time.)
(Seongmin: I think this is a very special experience.)
(Jaeseung: I think you're right.)
(Jaeseung: I think I've been looking for a partner too.)
(Jaeseung: I'm looking for something long-term, where it won't be easily abandoned.)
(Seongmin: Between humans,)
-Being abandoned is a very negative thing.
-That's right.
(Seongmin: Between humans,)
(Seongmin: Being abandoned is a very negative thing. It's sad.)
-Being abandoned is a very negative thing.
-That's right.
It's sad.
(Seongmin: Being abandoned is a very negative thing. It's sad.)
(Jaeseung: Someone that isn't like that.)
(Seongmin: The time? That you date for?)
(Jaeseung: Rather than someone that won't abandon,)
(Seongmin: it's more like I hope to find someone who doesn't even think of abandoning.)
(Seongmin: Someone who doesn't break up?)
(Jaeseung: Someone who doesn't break up easily.)
(Seongmin: Ah, I get what you mean.)
(Jaeseung: Someone who doesn't do things too easily.)
(Seongmin: But it's difficult to find someone like that.)
(Jaeseung: In Men's House, Seongmin showed a more playful side of himself.)
(Jaeseung: On this date, I saw more sides of him being more serious.)
(Jaeseung: His lifestyle? How he treats other people, his attitude, and his values.)
(Jaeseung: I think we are quite similar in these things.)
(Seongmin: Have you been interested in anyone other than Hui in Men's House? Other than Hui and I.)
(Jaeseung: Rather than the feeling of "I want to date this person once cause I am interested in them,"
(Jaeseung: there are people I want to try going on dates with.)
(Seongmin: Who is it? Can I ask?)
(Jaeseung: Hmm... Youngjoon.)
(Seongmin: Youngjoon? Ah, Youngjoon is younger than me. Youngjoon?
Jaeseung: Youngjoon.)
Youngjoon.
(Seongmin: Youngjoon? Ah, Youngjoon is younger than me. Youngjoon?
Jaeseung: Youngjoon.)
(Seongmin: Ah, I see.)
(Seongmin: I had no idea.)
(Seongmin: I didn't know you were interested in him.)
(Jaeseung: Rather than saying interested... I'm not that interested.)
(Jaeseung: Just quite literally, I want to try going on a date with him.)
(Jaeseung: The reason is simple.)
(Jaeseung: Youngjoon is very different from me. Personality-wise.
Seongmin: Oh, feels like it.)
(Jaeseung: From a certain angle, I feel that we have a similar personality.
Seongmin: I think so.)
(Jaeseung: At a certain level.
Seongmin: I get you.)
(Jaeseung: So it's more like curiosity.)
(Jaeseung: I don't know if it's an interest.)
(Seongmin: In Men's House, honestly,)
I'm only, literally curious, about Hwi and you.
(Seongmin: I'm only, literally curious, about Hwi and you.
Jaeseung: Literally just curious.)
I'm only, literally curious, about Hwi and you.
-Literally just curious. -So...
(Seongmin: I'm only, literally curious, about Hwi and you.
Jaeseung: Literally just curious.)
(Seongmin: But I'm lucky to have a date with Hwi today and also you.)
(Seongmin: But as I have gone on a date with both of you, I realize...)
(Seongmin: Hwi and you are really different.)
(Jaeseung: I'm different from Hwi?
Seongmin: Completely different.)
(Jaeseung: I went on a date with Hwi today too.
Seongmin: Right?)
-So I...
-It looks like we can all go on a date...
(Jaeseung: I went on a date with Hwi today too.
Seongmin: Right?)
(Jaeseung: It looks like we can all go on a date with everyone once.)
-So I...
-It looks like we can all go on a date...
-I think it's too...
-With everyone once.
(Jaeseung: It looks like we can all go on a date with everyone once.)
(Seongmin: No, wouldn't that make it really complicated to look at?)
(Ha...)
(Jaeseung: Why are you sighing?)
(Seongmin: I suddenly thought of Hwi.)
(Seongmin: I just thought of Hwi.)
(Seongmin: That if he were here, at this cafe with a beautiful view, what would we talk about?)
(Seongmin: When I said the view is great,)
(Seongmin: I thought, would we talk about more things?)
(Seongmin: Don't you want to take that? The yacht-like thing.
Jaeseung: The yacht?)
(Jaeseung: Will there be water activities on the dates?)
(Seongmin: I can't do that. Do you like extreme sports?)
(Jaeseung: I think I can do it if I'm told to.
Seongmin: Really?)
(Seongmin: I've been so happy until now.)
(Seongmin: But suddenly talking about "you have to fall into the water" makes it difficult.)
(Jaeseung: Speaking of that, it's a little like...)
(Jaeseung: The date you and I want to have are completely, different.)
(Seongmin: Really? What do you want?)
(Jaeseung: When you first mentioned going to the museum on the first day...
Seongmin: Mm.)
(Jaeseung: I actually went to a museum before. But I dozed off.
Seongmin: Really?)
(Seongmin: Why? You don't like museums?)
(Jaeseung: It's not that I don't like it.)
(Jaeseung: It's more like I was thinking what I should think about when I'm looking at these and I dozed off.)
(Seongmin: That's a difference in our perspectives.
Jaeseung: Something like that.)
(Seongmin: Being different can also be attractive.)
(Seongmin: So that's what you think.)
(Seongmin: I thought, if I go on a date with Jaeseung somewhere else, would it be fun?)
(Seongmin: The more we talked, the more we realized our hobbies are different.)
(Seongmin: And I didn't really know if I resonate with what he told me.)
(Seongmin: "Is the conversation going well? The flow seems to have been broken," I had thoughts like this.)
(The night has come)
The weather is really nice.
I'll never forget this night.
(The night has come)
(The secret mission date is over,
please return to Men's House.)
(Jaeseung: It says that our secret date is over.
Seongmin: What a pity.)
(Jaeseung, we should go. Seongmin: Where to?)
(Seongmin: Somewhere else?(
(Seongmin: We're going somewhere else, right?)
(Jaeseung: I started to like Seongmin more after the date.)
(Jaeseung: He's innocent and likes smiling. I'm attracted to his puppy-like appearance.)
(Jaeseung: It says we have to return to Men's House.
Seongmin: All right...)
(Seongmin: Let's go.)
Let's go.
(A moment that feels regretful even though they are together)
-But it's really nice here, right?
-Yeah.
I will come again.
("The two men's sudden and secret date")
-I'll come again if I can.
-Come again.
("The two men's sudden and secret date")
I'll really make the trip down.
Come again next time.
("The two men's sudden and secret date")
(Men's House at this hour)
(Seungjin is lying alone by the pool)
(Seungjin: I thought a lot today.)
(Seungjin: I may not look like it, but I have a low self-esteem.)
(Seungjin: I realized that I've been eating away at my self-esteem.)
(Seungjin: I'm angry at this situation.)
(Seungjin: "If this is what I'm going to do, why did I bother coming on this?" I can't stop thinking about that.)
(Seungjin: "I've been too relaxed." I keep having thoughts like this.)
-Cheers. -Cheers.
(Minseon, Myeongkyun, and Hanmin who are having snacks
at the kitchen)
-Cheers. -Cheers.
Cheers.
(Minseon, Myeongkyun, and Hanmin who are having snacks
at the kitchen)
Cheers to the three of us.
(Minseon, Myeongkyun, and Hanmin who are having snacks
at the kitchen)
Three people, three colors.
(Minseon, Myeongkyun, and Hanmin who are having snacks
at the kitchen)
(Minseon: Night dates must be fun.)
(Myeongkyun: But I still don't understand.)
What?
(Myeongkyun: Seongmin and Jaeseung.)
Still...
(Minseon: They both called each other yesterday.)
(Minseon: I think it's true that Jaeseung picked the date himself.
Hanmin: I think so too.)
I think so too.
(Minseon: I think it's true that Jaeseung picked the date himself.
Hanmin: I think so too.)
(Minseon: Why did you choose Youngjoon?)
(Hanmin: Yours was an arrow card, right?)
Yes.
(Hanmin: First of all, we are the same age.)
(Hanmin: I want to go on a date with him.)
(Hanmin: We can't date if our cards overlapped.)
Yes.
So I carefully selected the card. Fortunately, I chose it.
(Hanmin: We can't date if our cards overlapped.)
(Hanmin: So I carefully selected the card. Fortunately, I chose (a different card).)
So I carefully selected the card. Fortunately, I chose it.
Although they say that,
(Myeongkyun: Although they (Hanmin & Youngjoon) say that,)
(Myeongkyun: do they really like each other?)
(Myeongkyun: No, 100%.)
(Minggyun: I think they just think it's fun and they are friends, that's why they're enjoying it.)
(Myeongkyun: I think that's all.)
You're here.
(Seungjin who's done with his self-reflection (?)
joins in)
You're here.
-I feel like I'm getting sick of it.
-Feels nice.
(Seungjin who's done with his self-reflection (?)
joins in)
-What's going on?
-Beer?
(Seungjin who's done with his self-reflection (?)
joins in)
(Joking)
(I didn't say hello to Seungjin's eyebrows today)
I didn't say hello to Seungjin's eyebrows today.
(Joking)
(I didn't say hello to Seungjin's eyebrows today)
(Eyebrows that are under his hat)
(Seungjin's snack, banana)
(Minseon: Bananas again?)
(Minseon: I think you ate all the bananas.)
What? You startled me.
(Minseon: Want some fruit? Myeongkyun: Fruits?)
(Minseon: Shall we cut some fruits and have it?
Myeongkyun: Should I cut it for you?)
(Minseon: I want to eat apples. Are there still apples?)
-I want to eat apples. -Apples?
(Myeongkyun cuts apples for Minseon himself)
(Myeongkyun: Do you eat it with the skin on?
Minseon: I'm fine with anything.)
(Myeongkyun: Is that so? That's good.)
(Somehow anxious)
(Ah!)
Are you okay?
(Minseon: Did you cut your hand?
Myeongkyun: I'm fine.
(Minseon: I think you're bleeding though?)
-I think you're bleeding though?
-He's bleeding.
(Minseon: I think you're bleeding though?)
I'm fine. I just have to wipe it.
Let me see.
(The wound seems to be cut deep)
Hold on. Thank you. Thank you.
Is the wound deep?
(The wound seems to be cut deep)
(Minseon rushes up to the second floor)
(Looking around)
(Minseon gives Myeongkyun antiseptic cream and band-aid)
Oh, so considerate.
(Minseon: Come over.)
It's not good, right?
(Careful)
-Perhaps.
-Really?
(Careful)
I'm bleeding more than I thought I'd.
(Minseon: Are you bleeding a lot?
Myeongkyun: Not anymore.)
(Minseon: Try to see if your thumbs feel uncomfortable when bent.
Myeongkyun: It's fine.)
(Myeongkyun: Because I'm left-handed.)
(Myeongkyun: Don't worry.
Minseon: Then don't make me worry, sir.)
Nah.
(Myeongkyun: Don't worry.
Minseon: Then don't make me worry, sir.)
(Touched)
(Double room
Hwi,
Seongmin)
(Hwi is alone in a double room without Seongmin)
(Time seems to pass slowly when he's alone)
(Hwi pauses at the photo of Jaeseung he took today)
(Hwi: I thought I had a good day today.)
(Hwi: I felt betrayed.)
(Hwi: Ah... How could you do that?)
(Hwi: I'm a little frustrated now.)
(Hwi: I want to delete the (Jaeseung's) photo.)
I want to delete the photo.
(Knock knock)
What?
-Why?
-What are you doing?
(Seungjin: What are you doing?)
-Why?
-What are you doing?
(Hwi: Are they looking for me?
Seungjin: No. I just didn't see you.)
Hwi, come in.
(Seungjin: Are you asleep?
Hwi: Just lying in bed.)
(Seungjin: Are you okay?
Hwi: Yes. I'm fine.)
Really?
(Seungjin: Are you okay?
Hwi: Yes. I'm fine.)
(Hwi: You're speaking like a robot.
Seungjin: Yeah.)
(Hwi: Lie down and talk. Seungjin: It's nice.)
(Seungjin: Who are you going to call today?)
(Seungjin: To Seongmin, right?)
(Hwi: Up till yesterday, I could press the phone number without hesitation.)
(Hwi: Ah, but thinking about today, it's too...)
(Hwi: That if I’m persistent... Would it)
(Hwi: be burdensome to him?)
(Seungjin: Why are you conflicted about this?)
(Seungjin: I said to be more perseverant! Huh?)
(Seungjin: Who should I call today?)
(Seungjin: Jaeseung?)
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are back at Men's House
after the secret date)
Are you okay?
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are back at Men's House
after the secret date)
Are you okay?
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are back at Men's House
after the secret date)
Right?
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are back at Men's House
after the secret date)
I'm fine.
(Jaeseung and Seongmin who are back at Men's House
after the secret date)
It's a secret.
(Seongmin: Keep our date a secret?)
Keep our date a secret?
(What kind of influence will their secret date bring?)
Don't say anything.
-Be careful.
-I had fun today.
(What kind of influence will their secret date bring?)
(Seongmin is finally here)
-You're back.
-Where did you go?
(Seongmin is finally here)
(Seungjin: Hello.)
-You're back.
-Where did you go?
(Seongmin is finally here)
(Seungjin: Hello.)
Where did you go?
-Where did you go?
-What did you do?
(Seungjin: Hello.)
(Hwi: Where did you go?)
-Where did you go?
-What did you do?
(Seongmin: I will tell you in a week.)
(Hwi: In a week?)
(Seungjin: What...)
(Seongmin: We really just went out.)
In a week...
(Hwi: I asked him where he went.)
(Hwi: But he didn't tell me.)
(Hwi: So I felt more conflicted.)
(Hwi: Why a week later?)
-Why one week later?
-Yeah.
(Hwi: Why a week later?)
(Seungmin: Yeah. Why so many days later? Why one week later?)
-Why one week later?
-Yeah.
(Hwi: Why a week later?)
Why so many days later? Why one week later?
(Seungmin: Yeah. Why so many days later? Why one week later?)
(Seongmin: Because it'll be over in a week.)
I guess.
(Hwi who's really upset about
Seongmin keeping the secret)
Until then, I thought we're quite a good match–
Is it call time?
(Call time starts now.
Please call the person you're interested in and convey your feelings within 30 seconds.)
Oh right.
(Call time starts now.
Please call the person you're interested in and convey your feelings within 30 seconds.)
-I told you. -What?
(Call time starts now.
Please call the person you're interested in and convey your feelings within 30 seconds.)
It's call time.
(Call time starts now.
Please call the person you're interested in and convey your feelings within 30 seconds.)
Really?
(Call time starts now.
Please call the person you're interested in and convey your feelings within 30 seconds.)
(Seungjin: I'm staying here today.
Hwi: Stay here.)
Who should I call?
(The call time that has come back
to the confused men)
(Where are the men's hearts facing tonight?)
(Jaeseung is waiting for the call time alone)
(Jaeseung: I'm not prepared to share)
(Jaeseung: who I'm going to call)
(Jaeseung: and who I got a call from yet.)
After the date, I felt complicated.
(Seongmin: After the date (with Jaeseung), I felt complicated.)
(Seongmin: I need time to collect my thoughts.)
(Seongmin: But it was call time immediately. I was really confused.)
Lie down.
I'm so tired.
Can I use your blanket?
(Seungjin who decides to be in the room with Hwi and Seungjin during the call time)
Yes, its' fine.
(Seongmin: You know it's call time, right?
Seungjin: Yeah.)
(Seongmin: I wanted to be alone today though.)
(Seongmin: Seungjin was lying down on my bed,)
(Seongmin: and Hwi was on the other side, which all made me really uncomfortable.)
Because of the invisible vibes between the two of them...
(Seungjin: Because of the invisible vibes between Hwi and Seongmin...)
(Seungjin: I'm just looking at them happily.)
(Seungjin: It's like a couple who had a fight.)
(Seungjin: How do you feel about having two dates today?
Hwi: Oh right.)
(Seongmin: No. I said it wasn't a date.)
(Seongmin: It was not a date.)
(Seungjin: Were you kidnapped, then?)
(Seongmin: We just went out for a spin.)
(What do you mean? That is a date!)
(Seongmin: We went to a venue. And that venue was outdoors. Shocked, right?
Seungjin: Ah, outdoors?)
No, in any way, you went on an outdoor date.
(Seungjin: No, in any way, you went on an outdoor date.)
(Panic)
(Seungjin's sharp (?) questions keep coming)
It's just outside.
(Panic)
(Seungjin's sharp (?) questions keep coming)
(Seungjin: Did you go outside? Was it out of Earth?)
That's funny.
(On the other side,
Youngjoon and Hanmin are alone in a room)
Where could Seongmin be?
(On the other side,
Youngjoon and Hanmin are alone in a room)
I think he's in the bathroom.
(On the other side,
Youngjoon and Hanmin are alone in a room)
(Youngjoon: Seungjin was just lying in Seongmin's bed.)
He could be in the entertainment room, on the sofa. Entertainment room?
(Thinking where other men are)
The two of them went upstairs.
He could be in the entertainment room, on the sofa. Entertainment room?
(Youngjoon: Minseon and Myeongkyun went upstairs to the third floor.)
The two of them went upstairs.
(Youngjoon: Jaeseung went to his own room.)
Yes.
(Hanmin: I really don't understand Jaeseung's thoughts.)
(Youngjoon, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
I'll be right back.
(Hanmin: Go ahead.)
(Hanmin: I was nervous.)
(Hanmin: I was happy on the date,)
(Hanmin: but he may call someone he wants to know more.)
(Hanmin: Even if (he doesn't call), I shouldn't be disappointed.)
Even if it doesn't come, I shouldn't be disappointed.
(Hanmin: I kept telling myself that.)
(Hanmin: Even if (he doesn't call), I shouldn't be disappointed.)
(Youngjoon: I'm even more sure today than I was yesterday,)
(Youngjoon: so I called him without hesitation.)
(Youngjoon: Are you wearing the ring?)
Hello?
(Youngjoon calls Hanmin without hesitation)
Of course I am.
Wait.
(Hanmin: I was looking at the ring thinking, "What if he doesn't call me?")
(Hanmin: I was worried.)
Really?
(Youngjoon: I don't know. If I have a chance to call,)
(Youngjoon: I'll keep calling the same person.)
(Hanmin: I might do the same too.)
I'm hanging up.
(30 seconds passed quickly)
When I heard his answer...
(Youngjoon When I heard Hanmin's answer,)
(Youngjoon: I thought, "Oh, at least he would call me,"
(Youngjoon: and stopped worrying.)
(Hanmin: I'm happy and nervous at the same time.)
(Heart racing,
can't stop smiling)
(Youngjoon goes back to his room with Hanmin)
(Youngjoon: Were you worried?)
(Hanmin: A little?
Youngjoon: Why?)
I should be the first one, right?
(Youngjoon: I should be the first one (to call), right?)
(Refreshed)
Isn't it good?
(Myeongkyun: I've always let my hair down.)
(Myeongkyun: I only have my hair down.)
(Minseon: Try putting it down tomorrow.
Myeongkyun: Shall we?)
(Minseon: Tomorrow, I'll put mine up, and you let yours down.)
(Myeongkyun: You look good with your hair down too.)
(The two of them who are different in many ways)
I think so too.
I'm curious.
(The two of them who are different in many ways)
I've heard from people that letting hair down could be very suffocating, cause I have a lot of hair.
Is it my turn?
(Minseon, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
Go ahead.
Why am I the first?
(Minseon, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
Are you the first?
-I'm either the first or the second.
-Really?
(Minseon: I'm either the first or the second.)
-I'm either the first or the second.
-Really?
(Myeongkyun: You always call first.
Minseon: Yes. Why am I so popular?)
(Myeongkyun: Take care. Minseon: Okay.)
(Somehow nervous)
(Minseon: The person I'm calling is pretty much confirmed.)
(Minseon: I've already confirmed it.)
(Minseon: So I didn't feel pressured.)
(Who is the one who gives Minseon confidence?)
(-Hello? -Hi~)
(Minseon: Today's date was fun.)
(Minseon: I guess I'm the one who's calling you first.)
(Myeongkyun: Yeah.)
-See you upstairs later. -Okay.
(Minseon: See you upstairs later.)
See you upstairs.
(Minseon expresses his feelings to Myeongkyun two days in a row.)
I was very happy.
(Myeongkyun: I was very happy.)
(Myeongkyun: I'm not good at saying cheesy things.)
(Where is Myeongkyun's heart headed after receiving Minseon's call?)
(Seungjin: I had a bad feeling today since the morning.)
(Hwi: I was really surprised after I drew my love fortune.
-Seongmin: What did you draw?)
-I was really surprised after I drew my love fortune. -Yeah.
(Hwi: I was really surprised after I drew my love fortune.
-Seongmin: What did you draw?)
What did you draw?
(Hwi: I was really surprised after I drew my love fortune.
-Seongmin: What did you draw?)
What was it again?
(Hwi: I was really surprised after I drew my love fortune.
-Seongmin: What did you draw?)
It's a secret. You have a secret, too.
(Seungjin: It's a secret. You have a secret, too.)
(Hwi: The creepy thing is)
('you will be confused.')
(Seongmin: Confused?)
(Seongmin: What do you mean? -Hwi: I don't know.)
(Seungjin: It must be so confusing.)
(In the hot seat)
I'm not confused.
How confusing must it be?
(In the hot seat)
This is the first time I've drawn something positive.
(Seungjmin, love fortune: This is the first time I've drawn something positive.)
What is it?
Seungjin: It told me to only dig into one well.)
Hwi: That way it will shine.)
That's right.
(Seongmin: What well are you going to dig?)
-What well are you going to dig? -Me?
(Hwi: You already dug, right? I thought you already started digging.)
(Seungjin: First of all, the water stopped this morning so I dug the front yard...)
First of all, the water stopped this morning so I dug the front yard...
Do you want to pick up the dew early in the morning?
(Always getting used to playing tricks)
What are you talking about?
(Seungjin: Is life a joke?)
(Always getting used to playing tricks)
(Thanks to Seungjin, Hwi and Seongmin are relieved from their nervousness to call)
Stop it.
Is life a joke?
(Thanks to Seungjin, Hwi and Seongmin are relieved from their nervousness to call)
(Seongmin: Then is your well Jaeseung?)
See, he got a text as soon as I asked.
(Suddenly nervous. Seungjin, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
Go, go find Jaeseung.
I really want to die.
(Suddenly nervous. Seungjin, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
(Seungjin goes to the phone booth without sorting out his thoughts.)
(Seungjin: After finishing my date and going back to Men's House today,)
(Seungjin: I've been panicking.)
(Seungjin: Who should I call?)
(Seungjin: I'm in a dilemma.)
(Seungjin was constantly confused during dinner.)
(Seungjin: Should I keep showing my feelings to Jaeseung?)
(Seungjin: Or someone who's closest to my ideal type based on appearance)
(Seungjin: which is Hanmin.)
Really, who should I call?
(Who should I call..?)
(Seungjin: I've never been this stuck before.)
(Who is the person Seungjin is calling?)
(Hwi: Have you decided? Who you're going to call?)
(Hwi: I think I'm 80 percent sure.)
(Seongmin: Who are you going to call?)
(Hwi: Who do you think I'll call?)
(Seongmin: Someone you like.)
(Hwi: Someone I like... yeah...)
(Seongmin: Oh, wait. -Hwi: What?)
Hello?
(Seungjin calls his date today, Seongmin)
Wait.
(Seongmin: I did not expect it at all)
I became even more confused at the time.
(Hwi: I became even more confused at the time.)
(Hwi: People's thoughts are hard to guess.)
(Seungjin: I seem to have gotten closer to you since yesterday)
I feel comfortable around you.
(Seungjin: Thank you for today and have a good night.)
(Okay~)
(Seungjin chose Seongmin tonight.)
(Seungjin: First of all, I'm just really satisfied with today's date.)
(Seungjin: The biggest reason why I called was)
(Seungjin: the people I'm slightly interested in)
(Seungjin: all found their other half already)
(Seungjin: so I didn't want to interfere and disturb them.)
(Because of the unexpected call from Seungjin, Hwi and Seongmin are confused)
Was it Seungjin?
(Seongmin: I really didn't expect this.)
(Seongmin: Wait...)
(Seongmin: I'm a little flustered.)
(Seongmin: I'm thankful for Seungjin,)
(Seongmin: but I'm not interested in Seungjin romantically.)
(Seongmin: 'Do I need to hurt him unintentionally?')
(Seongmin: 'Am I doing something wrong?' was what I thought.)
(Seongmin: I feel complicated.)
(Seongmin: Wait... I actually feel really flustered right now.)
(Seongmin: What should I do? Ah... wait...)
(Hwi: Did I say something wrong to Seungjin?)
(Hwi: I think I told him everything too casually, like about what was bothering me.)
Why? Did something happen?
(Why? Did something happen? *Pretending to not know*)
(Why? Did something happen?)
(Seongmin: You...)
(Seungjin: Why? What?)
(Seongmin: Nothing, nothing.)
(-Seungjin: Why? Why? Why? -Seongmin: Nothing, nothing.)
Why? Why? Why?
(Seongmin: You're asking what happened?)
(-Seungjin: Why? Why? Why? -Seongmin: Nothing, nothing.)
(Seongmin: Has your mind been reset?)
(Seungjin: What? What? What?)
(Why? Why? Why?)
(What? What? What?)
-What? What? What? -Nothing. What?
(Their heads are full of question marks)
What? What? What?
(Ha...)
(Hwi: Do we have to stay in our rooms during call time?)
-What’s wrong? -Nothing, nothing.
(Seungjin: What's wrong?)
(-Seungjin: Do you want me to leave? -Hwi. No, no, no.)
(-Hwi: I'm just kidding, just kidding. -Seungjin: Do you want me to leave?)
(Hwi: I'm just kidding~ just kidding~)
-I should leave. -No, no, don't go.
(Seungjin: I should leave.)
(Getting up at once, Hwi: No, no, don't go. -Seongmin: Where are you going?)
-I should leave. -No, no, don't go.
-Where are you going? -Don't go.
(Getting up at once, Hwi: No, no, don't go. -Seongmin: Where are you going?)
(Seungjin: I'm going to lie next to him.)
-Where are you going? -Don't go.
(Getting up at once, Hwi: No, no, don't go. -Seongmin: Where are you going?)
-I'm going to lie next to him. -Okay, okay.
(Seungjin: I'm going to lie next to him.)
(Hwi: Oh, wait, this...)
(Seungjin: Let's get closer together.)
(-Hwi: Okay, let's get closer. -Seungjin: Today, we...)
(Seungjin: We talked a lot today.)
(Hwi: Yeah we talked really seriously. -Seungjin: Yeah~)
(Seongmin: Did you two have a serious chat? -Hwi: Yeah.)
(Seungjin: I think I'll end up leaving after watching other people date.)
(Haha)
Seriously.
(Seungjin: It's almost like a fantasy novel.)
(Sad Seungjin: It's basically Harry Potter now...)
(The next caller is Hanmin)
(Youngjoon: I don't have much expectations or anxiety.)
(Youngjoon: I think I'll naturally and calmly)
(Youngjoon: end up talking to Hanmin.)
(Hanmin: Actually, the time I spent with him today is longer than anyone else.)
(Hanmin: So I didn’t leave any space for others to enter my heart.)
(Who is the man in Hanmin’s heart?)
("Hello.")
(Youngjoon and Hanmin called each other today as well.)
They called the same person again.
(Youngjoon: Hurry and come back.)
(Hanmin: First of all, I don't know if the ring we made today will turn out to be a couple ring or a friendship ring)
(Youngjoon: Oh... Why are you saying that?)
(Hanmin: Even if you go on a date with someone else, remember to take a look at this ring.)
(Hanmin: I'm leaving, bye.)
(Hanmin: But to be honest, I thought about a lot of things at the time.)
(Hanmin: There was something I felt like I needed to tell him)
(Hanmin: so I told him that.)
(Youngjoon: 'Did he have to say that?')
(Youngjoon: It also sounded like he's giving himself some space.)
(Youngjoon: I wasn't very happy after hearing that,)
(Youngjoon: but I understand.)
(Hanmin came back after the call.)
(Youngjoon: Why did you say something so scary? -Hanmin: What?)
(Hanmin: Anyways, for the both of us...)
(Hanmin: it's our first formal date with someone)
(Hanmin: and there is still a lot of time left)
(Hanmin: so I thought, 'maybe it's too early to settle.')
(Hanmin: That’s what I thought when I told him.)
(After Hanmin's call, the two became slightly awkward.)
(Youngjoon: I don't wear friendship rings.)
(-Myeongkyun: I have a level one certificate in psychology. -Minseon: What?)
(-Myeongkyun: I have a level one certificate in psychology. -Minseon: Really?)
(Minseon: You look smart now after saying you have a level one certificate in psychology.)
(Myeongkyun: It's simply just identifying something through another person's perspective.)
You should go call first.
(Myeongkyun, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
(-Minseon: I was thinking about what to say and then we started talking about this. -Myeongkyun: Exactly.)
Have a safe trip.
(Myeongkyun: What should I say?)
(-Minseon: We've already come so far, you're not going to call someone else, right? -Myeongkyun: What?)
(Myeongkyun: What I thought at the time was)
(Myeongkyun: my feelings for Minseon are not 100% yet)
(Myeongkyun: but does Minseon think I'm 100% sure of him now?)
(Myeongkyun: Will he think that?)
(Myeongkyun: I'm a little worried that he'll think that way.)
(Minseon: He'll probably call me.)
(Minseon: Actually, as long as Myeongkyun calls me)
(Minseon: I don't care if other people call me or not)
(Minseon: is how I feel.)
(Myeongkyun spent a long time with Minseon today)
(Does Myeongkyun feel the same way as Minseon?)
(Thinking)
This is so hard.
(Myeongkyun: Hello?)
(Myeongkyun: Did it take a while?)
Hello? Yes.
(Myeongkyun calls Minseon)
(Myeongkyun: I actually already said what I wanted to say)
("I had fun today.")
(-Minseon: Okay, I'll see you upstairs. -Myeongkyun: Thank you.)
(Minseon: First, I felt relieved.)
(Minseon: I was relieved and happy that he called me.)
(Minseon: That's what I thought.)
We had a great time today.
(Myeongkyun: We had a great time today)
(Myeongkyun: so when he had this 'Will he call someone else?' anxious look)
(Myeongkyun: it made me worried.)
(Myeongkyun: I also wanted to express my feelings towards him)
(Myeongkyun: because I'm interested in him, too.)
(Hwi: Wow, seriously, this place is like a mosquito nest.)
(Seongmin receives a call)
Wait, who is this?
(Seongmin: Hello?)
(Seongmin: Ah... hi.)
(Jaeseung: Hi, it's Jaeseung.)
(Jaeseung: I felt like I should call you today.)
(Seongmin: Ah... thank you.)
(-Jaeseung: I had fun when you came out on a date with me today. -Seongmin: Yeah.)
("Good night.")
(Seongmin: Good... good night.)
(Jaeseung: Okay, I'll hang up now.)
(Jaeseung: Honestly, I'm not sure)
(Jaeseung: how Seongmin thinks.)
(Jaeseung: Was his reaction positive?)
(Jaeseung: What does his reaction mean? I'm not sure.)
(Seongmin: I was hesitant as to whether or not I should call Jaeseung.)
I was very confused.
(Confused Seongmin: I was very confused.)
(Hwi: Who was it?)
(Hwi: Who? Who?)
(Hwi: Who was it...)
(Hwi: To be honest, I wasn't happy.)
(Seungjin: I was listening next to him, so I knew)
(Seungjin: that Jaeseung called Seongmin.)
(Seungjin: I feel like Jaeseung is really sure of his feelings towards Seongmin.)
(Confused)
(Hwi, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
It's me.
(Hwi: I'm doomed.)
(Seongmin: Wait, I'm going to... I don't want to stay here.)
(-Seungjin: Why? -Seongmin: Wait, I just want to be alone.)
(Seongmin: No, wait.)
(In this complicated situation, Hwi walks towards the phone booth.)
(Hwi: This is the first time in my life)
(Hwi: that I'm feeling nervous because of someone)
(Hwi: so that's why I think I feel even more sad.)
(Hwi calls with a sad mood.)
(On the other side, Seongmin found a place to be alone: the amusement room)
It's not easy.
(Seongmin: What should I do? What should I do...)
(Seongmin: I wanted to avoid Seungjin and Hwi.)
(Seongmin: I wanted to be alone.)
(What should I do?)
(Hwi's heart remains the same and is still on Seongmin)
Seriously... what should I do...
Hello?
(Hwi's heart remains the same and is still on Seongmin)
(Hwi: Um... I felt like if I called you today as well)
(Hwi: it would be too obvious so I wasn't going to call you)
(Hwi: but I wanted to express my feelings honestly through the call... so I called.)
so I called.
(Seongmin: Thank you.)
(Hwi: Good night.)
(Seongmin: We're not sleeping yet.)
(Hwi: See you later.)
(Seongmin: See you in the room.)
(Hwi: See you in the room.)
(Because of Hwi's call, Seongmin is even more confused)
Wait, I'm going crazy.
(I'm going crazy.)
(Seongmin: I'm really grateful for how consistent he is)
(Seongmin: but I also feel really sorry. I'm so confused.)
(Seongmin: 'Am I going to betray him again?')
(Seongmin: and 'am I doing something wrong?')
(Hwi: I was very sure yesterday)
but then today I saw the two of them going out...
(Hwi: (Jaeseung&Seongmin) today I saw the two of them going out...)
(Seongmin: Seriously...)
Seriously...
(Seongmin: I'm constantly filled with thoughts.)
(Seongmin: I feel like my head's going to explode.)
(Seongmin, please come to the phone booth and convey your feelings to the person you like within 30 seconds)
(Sighing)
(Seongmin: Ah, really...)
(Seongmin: Ah, really... What should I do?)
(Even when in front of the phone, Seongmin is still confused.)
(Seongmin: But, focusing on my feelings at the moment,)
I'm going to call the person I like more.
(Seongmin: I'm going to call the person I like more.)
(Seongmin: I think I became more confident after going inside the phone booth.)
Seriously.
(Who is Seongmin more interested in right now?)
(Jaeseung: I think Seongmin will call me today.)
(Hwi: I actually didn't have any expectations)
(Hwi: but I thought it would be nice if I got the call.)
(Two men waiting for Seongmin's call)
(Seongmin: What are you doing?)
(-Hwi: Hello? -Seongmin: What are you doing?)
(-Seongmin: What are you doing? Why were you confused? -Hwi: Oh? It's just...)
(Seongmin: I'll see you back in the room.)
(-Hwi: Thank you. -Seongmin: Okay. What are you thanking me for?)
(Hwi: Bye. -Seongmin: See you later.)
(Seongmin: Did he hang up?)
(Seongmin: The moment I decided to call Hwi)
(Seongmin: was after my date with Jaeseung)
(Seongmin: when I realized that 'I got along better with Hwi')
(Seongmin: and that 'Hwi made me feel safe')
(Seongming: so I made the decision.)
(Happy twists in silence)
(Hwi: 'Is this a prank?' was what I thought.)
(Hwi: I'm so happy.)
(Hwi: I couldn't stop smiling for several minutes after getting the call.)
(Hwi: I was very happy.)
(Seongmin comes back after the call.)
(Seongmin can't comfortably go back to the room)
Seriously...
(No, I'm a little... I'm a little...)
Wait.
(They can't look at each other after the call)
Gosh.
(-Hwi: Should we sleep for a bit? -Seongmin: Ah~)
(They can't look at each other after the call)
(-Hwi: Where have you been? -Seongming: Me? I went to make a call.)
(-Seongmin: Oh are you asking about today? Today? -Hwi: No.)
(After calling each other, the two are flustered.)
Wait, I'm...
(Hwi: It’s too hot.)
What?
(Hwi: It's too hot.)
(Hwi: It’s too hot.)
(Day 3, the call time is over.)
(Call time has ended)
("It's a sad thing to not receive a call you were expecting.")
(Jaeseung: I feel like I want to start from zero.)
(Jaeseung: If I need to make a call tomorrow, I might not.)
Don't look.
I'm not looking either.
(The call time is over.)
It's over.
Why am I always the last to receive it?
(The call time is over.)
(Seungjin: I didn't get a single call today again.)
(Seungjin: I'm not that happy.)
(Seungjin: The person I called wasn't someone I actually wanted to call.)
(Seungjin: I'm also disappointed at myself for not being able to call the person I'm interested in.)
So it was a bad call.
("So it was a bad call.")
(Seongmin: Did you have fun today?)
No.
(-Seongmin: Was it boring? -Hwi: It was fun)
(Hwi: I just missed...)
I just missed...
(-Shy, Hwi: I just missed... -Seongmin: Me?)
-Me? -Yeah.
(Shy, Hwi: So I put two photos here.)
(Hwi put Seongmin's photo next to his bed)
I didn't put it here.
(-Seongmin: We look like kids here. -Hwi: Yeah.)
(Hwi: I'm going to take it with me after the show ends.)
(Seongmin: But this is me. I'm the only one in the photo.)
(-Hwi: I'll take both. -Seongmin: I'm taking this one.)
(What should I do?)
(Seongmin's "what should I do?" time is back)
(Hwi is shy, too.)
It's over.
(Youngjoon: Hanmin got a call today, too.)
(Youngjoon: I don't think anyone approached him...)
(Youngjoon: so I felt reassured?)
(Myeongkyun: I want to go on a date with Hanmin.)
(Myeongkyun: I don't think I feel romantically towards Youngjoon.)
(Myeongkyun: But even so,)
(Myeongkyun: I want to make sure.)
(Seongmin: 'I want to go on a date with Hanmin' was what I thought.)
I want to try it out with the three people I like.
(Seongmin: I want to try it out with the three people I like.)
(Seongmin: Because that way I won't have any regrets.)
(Seongmin: This is a jungle afterall.)
(Hanmin: Honestly, I don't know if it's because)
(Hanmin: I haven't gone on a date with anyone yet,)
(Hanmin: but I want to go on a date with Jaeseung.)
(The hearts of men that don't know where to go)
Also...
(-Seungjin: I feel so stressed. -Hwi: Why? Why?)
(Seungjin walks towards the phone booth)
(Seungjin: I really don't know who to call.)
(-Hwi: Were you worried until that moment? -Seungjin: Yeah.)
(Seungjin: Ever since yesterday, with Seongmin,)
(Seungjin: I became closer to him)
(Seungjin: so I don't want to call anyone else.)
(Hwi: To be honest, I thought you'd call Jaeseung.)
I really couldn't bring myself to.
(Seungjin: I really couldn't bring myself to call Jaeseung.)
(Seungjin: So in the end I called Seongmin because I had fun on the date today.)
(Hwi: I felt a little relieved then.)
(Hanmin: Why are there so many secrets?)
Yeah, somehow...
(Jaeseung: Somehow I became a man with lots of secrets.)
Whatever.
Are you teasing me?
(Are you teasing me?)
Whatever, I'm not curious.
Are you teasing me?
(I'm not curious~)
Whatever, I'm not curious.
Whatever~
I'm not curious. Cheers.
(Cheers)
(Minseon: Oh? My slippers are gone again.)
(Minseon: At this point, I feel like someone is taking them.)
(-Minseon: Every time I wear them... -Myeongkyun: I feel more comfortable barefooted.)
Really?
Oh yeah!
(Myeongkyun takes off his slippers for Minseon)
Try it.
Whatever.
Earlier I said I had cold soba noodles...
(-Hanmin: Earlier I said I had cold soba noodles... -Minseon: He said McMorning. -Youngjoon: McDonald's breakfast?)
He said McMorning.
McDonald's breakfast.
(-Hanmin: Earlier I said I had cold soba noodles... -Minseon: He said McMorning. -Youngjoon: McDonald's breakfast?)
No, because the pronunciation...
(Myeongkyun xplaining for Minseon: No, because the pronunciation...)
(Youngjoon: Are you two going to be like this? (Myeongkyun&Minseon))
(-Youngjoon: Are they playing a couple? -Hanmin: I think so.)
-I think so. -No.
-I think I'm jealous. -No.
I'm always like this.
(I think I'm jealous)
I think I'm jealous.
(Hehe)
(Seongmin has been in his room ever since the call)
Gosh...
(Hesitating)
(Awkward Seongming, and Jaeseung who is avoiding Seongmin)
(-Youngjoon: You don't have bangs anymore. -Seongmin: Yeah.)
I got rid of my bangs.
But the cold soba noodles...
What did you do? What were you doing?
(-Youngjoon: What did you do? What were you doing? -Minseon: I didn't do anything.)
I didn't do anything.
(-Hanmin: Did you eat something good? -Seongmin: Yeah.)
Did you have dinner before coming back?
(The men are curious about Jaeseung and Seongmin's date)
Cold soba noodles?
What did you eat?
(The men are curious about Jaeseung and Seongmin's date)
We didn't have dinner.
(Seongmin: We didn't do anything.)
(Youngjoon: You didn't do anything? Why?)
(Youngjoon: Did you two promise each other that you won't do anything?)
(Sad)
(Hanmin: He's smiling.)
(Jaesung: We just chatted and chatted. Happy?)
(Seongmin: I'm going to... I'm going to head back to my room.)
(Seongmin leaves in the end)
(Jaeseung's expression looks even darker after Seongmin leaves)
(-Seungjin: I'm not feeling good today. -Minseon: Since the morning?)
(Seungjin: Not from the morning.)
(Seungjin: I've been like this ever since coming home.)
(Seungjin: I keep spacing out.)
(Minseon: Do you have someone you like?)
(Seungjin: I'm actually the most interested in Jaeseung right now.)
(Seungjin: But it's not like I like him a lot.)
(Seungjin: No matter what, everyone now knows how Jaeseung feels towards Minseon)
(Seungjin: so I don't want to bother him.)
(Seungjin: I don't want to get hurt so I also don't want to hurt others.)
(Seungjin: I'm not that kind of person.)
(Seungjin: I've been thinking about this phrase for a while,)
-"You have to love yourself first to love others." -That's right.
(Seungjin: "You have to love yourself first to love others.")
(Seungjin: This phrase keeps lingering in my mind.)
(Seungjin: I may look like this on the outside,)
(Seungjin: but my pride is actually pretty low.)
(Minseon: I think you know it, too.)
(Minseon: How you should love yourself.)
(Minseon: I think you love yourself enough)
(Minseon: but you always lack confidence.)
(-Seungjin: I feel better now after talking to you about it. -Minseon: Yeah, I can tell.)
(Seungjin: I thought, 'if I don't say it, I'm really going to suffer inside.')
(Seungjin: I really wanted to cry today... so...)
(Seungjin: What do you like about Myeongkyun? -Minseon: What I like about him?)
(Minseon: At first, I was attracted to his nonsense.)
(Minseon: four-dimensional! -Seungjin: Oh.)
(Minseon: I think it's funny. I couldn't stop laughing.)
(Minseon: I just wanted to get to know him more.)
(-Seungjin: Did Myeongkyun tell you who he called yesterday? -Minseon: No, I didn't ask.)
(Seungjin: Oh, you didn't you ask? Well done.)
(Seungjin: Well done, well done.)
(Minseon: I don't want to ask.)
(-Seungjin: It's better to not know sometimes. -Minseon: Yeah, I don't want to know.)
(Seungjin: It's better to not know sometimes.)
(And...)
(Seongmin's phone suddenly gets a notification)
(Seongmin, who received the most calls today, has the chance to choose his room and roommates.)
(But he can't pick his current roommates and this mission cannot be revealed to anyone.)
(Seongmin is flustered after receiving a secret mission)
(Why should I go through this?)
(Seongmin: I think this is too much.)
(What should I do?)
(Seongmin: I want to be roommates with Hwi.)
(Seongmin: We've gotten closer)
(Seongmin: so I kept writing and deleting.)
(Seongmin can't decide to assign the rooms.)
(Hwi: Are you asleep?)
(Seongmin: Ah, wait...)
(Seongmin: Let's sleep.)
(After thinking about it, Seongming sends a text message behind Hwi.)
(Confused)
(Seongmin: I need to make a wise choice.)
(Seongmin: I'm so lost.)
(You scared me. The rooms are sorted.)
You scared me.
What did you receive?
(You scared me. The rooms are sorted.)
(Hwi: What text did you receive?)
What did you receive?
(-Hwi: I feel uneasy. What text did you receive? -Seongmin: Nothing.)
(Why did you send it... Why did you send it? Why did you send it?!)
(Ah...)
(-Seongmin: What am I doing? -Hwi: What's wrong?)
(Seongmin: Ah, I'm going crazy.)
(Hwi: Who? Who sent it to you? Who is it?)
-Hurry up and say it. -I don't know either.
(Seongmin is in pain and Hwi is confused)
(Ahhhhhh T T)
(Seongmin: Are you out of your mind? You must be out of your mind.)
What's wrong? What's wrong?
(Hwi: Hurry, tell me what is it?)
What is it?
(Seongmin: I should do it based on my instincts.)
(Seongmin: My choice is...)
(The next morning)
(Seongmin: The three men I like are: Hwi, Jaeseung and Hanmin.)
(Today is the day to change rooms. The room and roommates have already been decided by someone. Third-floor single room: Hwi. Second-floor four people room: Minseon, Seungjin, Myeongkyun, Youngjoon. Second-floor single room: Jaeseung. First-floor double room: Seongmin, Hanmin.)
(A sudden change of roommates. The men are confused.)
(Oh? Who made the decision?)
(I want to avoid it)
(Hwi: How's the four people room?)
("This is driving me crazy.")
(A new mission keeps coming.)
(Please ask a question to the man you're interested in. Questions will be anonymous.)
(To. Youngjoon: I can't feel your sincerity. Can't you be more straightforward?)
I can't feel your sincerity.
Can't you be more straightforward?
(To. Youngjoon: I can't feel your sincerity. Can't you be more straightforward?)
(I swear I never hid my true feelings.)
(I never did anything fake.)
(The only person who would say that to me)
("is probably Myeongkyun.")
(To. Jaeseung: Q. Are you sure about your feelings for Seongmin?)
Are you sure about your feelings for Seongmin?)
(A question that makes the men flustered)
So fierce
("I'm not sure.")
(Seongmin: I'm disappointed that he said he's not sure.)
(I can see the signs of internal split.)
(We're kind of like...)
(Survival Battle)