(Jaeseung)
(Seungjin)
(Minseon)
(Hwi)
(Youngjoon)
(Seongmin)
(Hanmin)
(Myeongkyun)
(Episode 3: Familiar Faces)
(Jaeseung & Seungjin's second date location)
(Jaeseung: Hanok?)
(Seungjin: It's totally a Hanok)
(T/N: Hanok is the traditional Korean house)
(Korean food date in a Hanok)
(Seungjin: Thank you for the food)
(Jaeseung: Thank you for the food)
(Jaeseung: What do you want to eat first?)
(Seungjin: Me? Scallion pancakes)
I'll give you a piece of scallion pancake.
(Jaeseung taking care of Seungjin first)
Thank you.
(I'll dig in)
(Happiness)
We might eat without saying a word for a while.
(Seungjin: It's really delicious)
(Jaeseung: I'm not just saying it. It's really delicious)
(Jaeseung: This is delicious too. The sauce is good)
(Jaeseung: Honestly, do you know you look the happiest now?)
(Jaeseung: Want some pollack? Remove the bones?)
(Seungjin: I'll eat it later)
(Jaeseung: You aren't eating it because you don't want to remove the fish bones, right?)
Yes.
(Jaeseung: Have this then)
(Jaeseung: You aren't eating it because you don't want to remove the fish bones, right?)
(Touched) (Jaeseung gives Seungjin the fish after removing the bones)
You're so sweet.
(Seungjin: Jaeseung removed the fish bones for me)
(Seungjin: That was most memorable)
I think he's very warm-hearted.
(Warm-hearted)
(Seungjin: When we return to (Men's House),)
(Seungjin: if someone asks about our date, what will you say?)
(Jaeseung: I'll say it was fun)
(Jaeseung: I really had fun too)
(Seungjin: You're saying this now, but will you turn around and say you were dying from the heat?)
(Jaeseung: That's not about the date, but another aspect?)
(Jaeseung: (I had fun) when it's just about the date)
(Jaeseung: When was your last relationship?)
(Seungjin: Secret)
(Jaeseung: Do you know you have too many secrets?)
(Jaeseung: Okay, I accept that)
(Jaeseung: How long was your longest relationship?)
(Seungjin: That's a secret too)
But I've dated before.
(But I've dated before) (Kidding)
(Jaeseung: I'll let it go)
(Jaeseung: This term really fits you:)
("Annoying One")
No.
(Jaeseung: I'm calling you "Annoying One")
(Jaeseung: not just because you annoy me)
(Jaeseung: You have a cute side too)
(Seungjin: Me?)
(Jaeseung: Your overall image is kind of cute)
(Seungjin: Not many people think of me that way)
(Jaeseung: What he does is annoying)
(Very playful)
(Jaeseung: but cute too)
(Jaeseung: Annoying)
(Jaeseung: but cute. That's why I called him "Annoying One")
("Annoying One")
(Seungjin: It was funny)
(Seungjin: Seeing him give me such a nickname, I became more sure,)
(Seungjin: that he must be)
(Seungjin: a lot older than me)
(Seungjin: Honestly, yesterday I felt most at ease around Youngjoon)
(Seungjin: After today's date, I feel very at ease with you now)
(Jaeseung: I knew it)
(Seungjin: I'm fine when it's a 1-on-1 date)
(Jaeseung: You need to talk to know a person)
(Seungjin: I was always talking to Youngjoon)
(Seungjin: with other people)
It's just the two of us today.
(The two getting closer on a 1-on-1 date)
(Jaeseung: I'm more at ease with you today too)
(Seungjin: That's a relief)
(Jaeseung: You didn't tell me yesterday,)
(Jaeseung: but I guessed that you'd have made the phone call to Youngjoon)
(Jaeseung: That's what I thought)
(Jaeseung: You two have similar styles and other aspects too, right?)
(Jaeseung: To be honest, you two looked good together)
(Seungjin: For me, when I see)
(Seungjin: someone similar to me,)
(Seungjin: I think it's what I can see in the mirror)
(Seungjin: It feels a little like that)
-Oh, you could think that way too. -Yes.
(Seungjin: When I see people)
(Seungjin: who look fancy, I think they're cool)
But I don't think I've ever fallen for them romantically.
(Seungjin's more interested in people who are different from him)
(Jaeseung: I get it now)
(As they say, opposites attract)
(Jaeseung: I think (Seungjin) expressed his interest in me through that)
(Jaeseung: It felt unusual)
(Jaeseung: But I'm not sure if it's romantic for me)
(Was the two men's unusual date romantic?)
(Seongmin & Hwi's second date location: A cafe resembling nature)
(Hwi: Ah, this is nice)
(Seongmin: It's really therapeutic)
(Hwi: It smells so nice)
(Seongmin: I like places with fresh air)
(Hwi: Me too)
(Hwi: How was our date today?)
(Seongmin: I had fun today. What about you?)
(Shy) (Hwi: I really loved it)
(Seongmin: Don't you think we have a lot in common?)
(Hwi: It felt like it was a really relaxing time)
(Seongmin: Yeah, I agree)
(Hwi: Should we arrange this?)
(Seongmin: Arrange what? Oh)
-The (rattan cup holders) we made. -Sure.
Wow.
(Hwi: They even packaged it for us)
(Hwi: But it's really pretty)
(Seongmin: Yes, even here)
(They arrange the flowers that they bought for each other in the vases)
I think it'll look good. Oh, it really does.
Really.
(Hwi: Pretty)
(Seongmin: It looks really pretty together)
(Tada)
(Seongmin: Wow, it's really beautiful)
(Hwi: It's really beautiful)
(Seongmin: It's so full)
-Yeah. -Right?
(Impressed)
(Hwi: Should we take photos?)
(Seongmin: Oh, selfie?)
(Please take it with a beautifying app)
(Laughing)
Hold on.
(Taking pictures with the flowers)
(Hwi & Seongmin with the first bouquets they've received in their lives)
(Seongmin: I liked all three activities we did)
(Hwi: Me too, really)
(Seongmin: Buying flowers, making rattan...)
-And here, a cafe in nature. -I love it.
(An obviously cozy and relaxing time for the two)
(Seongmin: Who do you think will have the most unlikely occupation?)
-Occupation? -Yes.
(Hwi: I’m really curious)
(Seongmin: Minseon guessed I was a student)
(Seongmin: It made me so happy)
(Hwi: You do look like a student, really)
(Wait...)
(Hwi: Like a Korean literature major)
(Seongmin: A Korean literature major?)
(Seongmin: Why?)
(Hwi: Because you look gentle)
(Smiling)
-Really? -Yes.
-Korean literature... -Korean literature.
-Oh no. -It's ruined.
(The vase suddenly collapses)
Oh no.
(Panicking)
(Startled) (It's ruined)
-Oh no. -It's ruined.
-Oh no. -It's okay.
(Seongmin: What's wrong with me?)
-What's wrong with me? -It's really okay.
(When the two are panicking, a car heads towards them)
(Clueless about what's about to happen as they clean up busily)
-I'm hopeless. -But...
(It's the first gift, sigh)
At least it didn't wet the camera.
-It's a little... -Now...
(It's the first gift, sigh)
(Seongmin: I'm so sorry)
-It's a little... -Now...
(It's the first gift, sigh)
(Seongmin: I'm so sorry)
(And here comes the last man)
(Myeongkyun: Actually I've a lot of worriese too)
(Myeongkyun: What if the person I like is...)
(Myeongkyun: already in good terms with someone else?)
I really love it. Since coming to Men's House, right now's...
(Myeongkyun: Hello)
(Hwi: Hello)
Right now's my favorite...
-Hello. -Hello.
-What a surprise. -Gosh.
(With Myeongkyun's arrival, the vase falls again)
(Seongmin: Hello. What's going on?)
Hold on.
(Seongmin: What a surprise)
What a surprise.
-Hello. -You surprised me.
(Seongmin: I was really surprised. Really surprised)
(Hwi: Sigh, it was nice with just the two of us. Why did he come here?)
(Hwi: It really left me feeling deflated)
(Myeongkyun: I'm Jo Myeongkyun. I'll be moving in with you from today on)
-Jo Myeongkyun? -Yes.
-Myeongkyun? -Yes.
(Seongmin: Myeongkyun?)
(Hwi: I'm Kim Hwi. Single-character name)
(Seongmin: I'm Bae Seongmin)
Your name.
(Seongmin: You're joining us today)
(Hwi: I was really surprised)
(Seongmin: Wow. So suddenly?)
(Hwi: It suddenly became awkward)
(Hwi: He looks like the kind where everyone would call him handsome)
(Hwi: He’s tall. He looks kind of like a model)
(Awkward atmosphere surrounding the three of them)
(Myeongkyun: When Hwi first saw me, he looked confused)
(Looking carefully)
(Myeongkyun: First, Seongmin looked gentle)
(Myeongkyun: He seemed shy)
(How will Myeongkyun's arrival change the dynamics among the men?)
(Seongmin: How did you come here?)
(Myeongkyun: Based on a one-phrase self-introduction,)
(Myeongkyun: I'd to pick someone I like. I chose this card)
-Self-esteem Guardian with beautiful eyes and hands. -Wow.
(Seongmin: Wow... Who could it be?)
(Seongmin: Who do you think it is?)
-I can't tell yet. -You can't?
Yes, both your eyes and hands are...
(Embarrassed for no reason)
Wow. Really.
(Seongmin: Based on these introductions...)
(Seongmin: The introduction is a really beautiful phrase. "Self-esteem Guardian with beautiful eyes and hands.")
-The introduction... -Yes.
Is a really beautiful phrase.
(Seongmin: The introduction is a really beautiful phrase. "Self-esteem Guardian with beautiful eyes and hands.")
Self-esteem Guardian with beautiful eyes and hands.
-After reading this phrase... -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: After reading this phrase,)
-I heard he was here. -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: I heard he was here. So I came here)
(Seongmin: Because I know it's my introduction, I feel embarrassed)
(Hwi: It made me nervous)
(Hwi: Because he likes the self-introduction of the person I like,)
(Hwi: I feel a little uneasy)
(Seongmin: Who do you think the card belongs to?)
(Seongmin: I'm curious)
(I'm. So. Curious)
-Pretty eyes and hands. -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: Pretty eyes and hands)
-Hands? -Hands.
-Pretty eyes and hands. -Yes.
(Hands) (Curious)
-Hands? -Hands.
(My hands aren't pretty)
(My hands aren't either...)
(I should hide my hands)
(Myeongkyun: I think the self-introduction belongs to...)
(Myeongkyun: Judging from your reactions... Seongmin?)
(Seongmin: Me?)
(Myeongkyun: Is it not?)
(Seongmin: Maybe? Maybe not?)
(Trying to stay calm)
(Seongmin: I thought Hwi's eyes are pretty when I first saw him)
Really?
(Ha. Ha. Ha. Who. Could. It. Be?)
(Seongmin: But besides this one, what's written on the other cards? I'm curious)
(Myeongkyun: Other cards...)
(Myeongkyun: What I remember was...)
(Myeongkyun: "A large dog who doesn't match his size")
(Hwi: I think I know who it is)
(Seongmin: Who is it?)
(Hwi: Isn't it Minseon? He has a larger frame)
(Myeongkyun: And "A fun old cat if we get close")
(Seongmin: But I think the old cat...)
(Seongmin: What's the rest of the phrase?)
(Seongmin: For the old cat)
(Hwi: "A fun old cat if we get close")
(Myeongkyun: "A fun old cat if we get close")
(Seongmin: "If we get close")
-That was what it said. -Who do you think it is?
(Hwi: Seungjin)
(Hwi: He has a cat-like face)
(Myeongkyun: Another one was... "Dexterous person")
For that...
(Seongmin: Wait, Hwi, aren't you included too?)
(Who knows? Haha)
Don't tell me you're the old cat?
(Seongmin: Don't tell me you're the "old cat" (keyword)?)
(Maybe)
-You must be the dexterous one. -Am I?
(Seongmin: You must be the dexterous one)
(Myeongkyun: I chose this card for a reason)
(Seongmin: Why?)
-I... -This card.
(Nervous)
(Myeongkyun: I like guys with beautiful eyes)
-Beautiful eyes. -Yes.
(Annoyed)
-We... -Because I like beautiful eyes.
(Seongmin: We both have beautiful eyes)
(Myeongkyun: So I was conflicted)
(Myeongkyun: I don't really care about hands)
(Myeongkyun: And especially about him being a "Self-esteem Guardian")
(Myeongkyun: I thought he'll have a good personality,)
(Myeongkyun: speak nicely,)
(Myeongkyun: and be gentle too)
(Myeongkyun: That's what I got from it)
(Seongmin: This situation is very interesting)
(Hwi: I feel so awkward now)
Really.
(Seongmin: This situation is very interesting)
(Hwi: I feel so awkward now)
(Seongmin: We barely... But we)
Really.
(Seongmin: arrived yesterday, so our situation's similar too, right?)
(Seongmin: You don't have to be nervous)
(Hwi: He doesn't seem nervous at all)
(Myeongkyun: I'm very nervous)
(Myeongkyun trying his best to not seem nervous)
(Seongmin: What do you think of this flower?)
(Myeongkyun: Are they both real flowers?)
-Yes. -Yes.
(Seongmin: What do you think of this flower?)
(Myeongkyun: Are they both real flowers?)
(Hwi: We gifted them to each other)
(Seongmin: This is a gift I received)
(Seongmin: We made these ourselves)
(Seongmin is trying to break the ice)
That's right. This...
-Cup holder. -Cup holder. At a rattan workshop.
(Seongmin is trying to break the ice)
(Looking carefully)
-Cup holder. -Cup holder. At a rattan workshop.
-May I ask... -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: I'm a little curious. What kind of flower are these?)
(Myeongkyun: Or what they symbolize?)
(Symbolize...)
(Hwi: There's no special symbolism. It's just...)
(Seongmin: We didn't ask)
(Seongmin: We should've asked about the symbolisms, right?)
(Hwi: I just wanted to gift it to him)
-It's a gift for each other, right?
-Yes, that's right.
(Hwi: I just wanted to gift it to him)
-It's a gift for each other, right?
-Yes, that's right.
(Myeongkyun: That's romantic)
(Myeongkyun: They look good together)
(Myeongkyun: I felt that strongly)
(Myeongkyun: I felt like...)
("I felt like I was intruding")
That's how I felt.
(Seongmin: Personality-wise, what do you look for?)
(Myeongkyun: Personality-wise?)
(Myeongkyun: Rather than very extroverted people,)
(Myeongkyun: I prefer calm people)
-Calm people. -Calm people.
(Nodding)
(Myeongkyun: I like people who are relatively mature)
(Hwi: I can tell that Seongmin is curious about Myeongkyun)
(It made me a little jealous)
(Myeongkyun: Do you stay in different rooms or the same?)
Us?
(Hwi: We are roommates)
(Myeongkyun: Do you stay in different rooms or the same?)
-Roommates? -Yes.
(Hwi: We are roommates)
(Seongmin: Today's the time for roommates to get closer)
(Seongmin: We're all on dates with our roommates)
(Seongmin: The two in the single rooms are on a date)
(Seongmin: Those in double rooms are with their roommates)
(Myeongkyun: I haven't been assigned to a room yet)
(Seongmin: Oh, really?)
(Seongmin: Assigning rooms...)
(Seongmin: What should I do?)
What will it be like?
Totally...
(Seongmin: What should I do?)
I'm curious.
(Worried)
(Seongmin: It'll be interesting tonight)
I'm curious.
(Worried)
(Seongmin: It'll be interesting tonight)
Gosh.
(Worried)
(Seongmin: It'll be interesting tonight)
(Myeongkyun: Wouldn't it be fun to exchange (roommates)?)
Rooms?
(Ah, I don't want to change)
The camera is interesting.
(Myeongkyun changes the subject in a hurry)
It can do this too.
(Hwi: In this case, since we haven't taken a photo together,)
Shall I take a photo for you?
(Hwi: can you take a photo for us?)
(Seongmin: Hwi was cute)
(Seongmin: When he asked him to take a photo of us,)
(Seongmin: it's like he's trying to emphasize we're very close)
You can hold the flowers
(Myeongkyun takes photos for Hwi and Seongmin)
you gave each other.
With the flowers?
(Myeongkyun takes photos for Hwi and Seongmin)
What should I do?
(Shy)
Hold the flowers.
What should I do?
(Posing with the flowers they gave each other)
Hold the flowers.
Flowers...
(Posing with the flowers they gave each other)
(One, two, three)
(The first photo taken as roommates)
(Myeongkyun: Will anyone take a photo with me?)
(Seongmin: Both of us?)
It's hard for the three of us.
(Hwi: I'll take them for you then)
(Let's take it together then)
Move the chairs closer.
-Here I go. -Okay.
(Here I go)
(Sitting side by side)
At our first meeting...
(I wanted to burn it)
(Hwi: I wanted to throw it away right when I took it out)
(Seongmin: Why don't we talk about that now?)
About what?
(Seongmin: Hobbies?)
-Hobbies -Yeah.
Hobbies.
(Seongmin: Hobbies?)
(Hwi: I like to go to art exhibits)
(Hwi: I like making crafts)
(Hwi: Creative stuff?)
(Crafts)
Crafts.
(Myeongkyun: I go to shooting ranges)
(Hwi: Shooting?)
-Shooting? -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: I go to shooting ranges)
(Hwi: Shooting?)
Shooting?
(Myeongkyun: I go to shooting ranges)
(Hwi: Shooting?)
Shooting range sounds fun.
(Myeongkyun: I go to shooting ranges)
(Hwi: Shooting?)
(Myeongkyun: (I've been going to shooting ranges) for about two years)
(Seongmin: I think it's my first time meeting someone with this hobby)
(Hwi: I think it's my first time too)
(Myeongkyun: (I've been going to shooting ranges) for about two years)
(Seongmin: I think it's my first time meeting someone with this hobby)
(Hwi: I think it's my first time too)
(Myeongkyun: I go for drives on a nice day)
(Seongmin: Do you go to shooting ranges?)
(Myeongkyun: I'll also go to fields to shoot)
Shoot at the fields?
(Myeongkyun: It's a privately-owned land by someone in my shooting gathering)
(Myeongkyun: It's environmentally-friendly shooting)
It's environmentally-friendly shooting.
(Hwi: I don't think we'd quite get along)
(Hwi: We don't have similar hobbies)
(Hwi: Our conversations also don't flow well)
(Myeongkyun: If we go to Men's House,)
(Myeongkyun: can I ask about what kind of people are there?)
(Hwi: They're all very different)
-Very different? -Yes.
(Seongmin: They all have different styles)
That's right.
(Seongmin: Everyone has their own style)
-There's someone with tattoos like this. -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: I think he's the "large dog" (keyword))
-No. -No?
(Hwi: No)
(Seongmin: He's not large)
-No. -No?
(Hwi: No)
(Seongmin: He's not large)
Not large?
(Hwi: No)
(Seongmin: He's not large)
-A "small dog"? -A "small dog".
(Hwi: He's small)
(Myeongkyun: When I heard there's someone short with tattoos,)
(Myeongkyun: it reminded me of some people I've dated)
(Myeongkyun: I started to worry if it's one of them)
(Myeongkyun: Talking with you,)
(Myeongkyun: I became very curious about the others in Men's House)
(Seongmin: It seems so)
(Myeongkyun: Should we head home?)
(Seongmin: The start of my date with Hwi was really nice)
(Seongmin: I didn't feel like it got more fun)
(but more like the good feeling lasted throughout)
(Hwi: I had a great day)
(I don't think he'll be stolen away from me)
(Myeongkyun: Finally, it feels real now)
(It's starting now)
(Jaeseung and Seungjin arrive at Men's House first)
Do we just unpack now?
-Just us? -Yeah.
(Jaeseung and Seungjin arrive at Men's House first)
(Jaeseung: I guess we're the first to come back)
(Seungjin: Are they hiding?)
(I know everything, so come out)
Is no one here?
(Who is it?)
-Jaeseung. -Yes?
(Seungjin: Jaeseung)
(Seungjin: I'll prepare dinner. Please help me)
(Jaeseung: Sure)
(Jaeseung: I should know what you're cooking, so I can help you)
(Seungjin: You don't have to)
(Jaeseung: Oh, come on)
(Seungjin: Are we really the first?)
(Oh! Oh!)
What's wrong?
(Why's there two now)
(The second-floor double room turns into a quadruple room)
See? I told you.
But...
(The second-floor double room turns into a quadruple room)
(Jaeseung: There are more blankets but no luggage)
(Jaeseung: They're still on their dates)
(Wow)
These scary people.
(Jaeseung: They're on their dates)
(Seungjin: Let's keep this a secret)
(Seungjin: Wow. Are we really the first to come back?)
(Searching Men's House carefully)
(Oh!)
(Look! There are more chairs!)
Look.
These scary people.
(They find out there'll be two new men)
(How will they be affected by the new men moving in?)
(Youngjoon, Minseon, and Hanmin returning from their date)
Hello.
Are you back?
(Lacking energy) (Seungjin: You're back)
(Youngjoon: You got here first)
-The earliest? -Yes.
(Yes) (Yes)
(Youngjoon: The earliest?)
-The earliest? -Yes.
(Yes) (Yes)
(Youngjoon: The earliest?)
Welcome to new face.
(Yes) (Yes)
(Youngjoon: The earliest?)
Welcome to new face.
(New man Hanmin appears)
What?
-Hello. -Hello.
(New man Hanmin appears)
Please sit here.
(Hanmin meets Jaeseung and Seungjin for the first time)
(Oh? What?)
What?
-Hello. -Hello.
(Oh? What?)
(Seungjin: I expected it, but when he walked in,)
(Seungjin: I was a bit taken aback)
Here I am. I'm back.
I'm back.
(Hanmin: He looked familiar to me)
(Jaeseung: I know Hanmin)
(Jaeseung: Just as Instagram friends, but we still know each other,)
(Jaeseung: though we've never met before)
(Jaeseung: So I was a little flustered at first)
(Hanmin: My name is Kim Hanmin)
(Hanmin: Think of it as Hanmin in "Dae han min guk")
("Dae han min guk" means "Republic of Korea")
(Youngjoon: When you can't remember his name, this tip really works)
(Seungjin: Similar to Jaeseung,)
(Seungjin: he has the looks that I like)
(Seungjin: That's how I felt)
(Jaeseung: His smiling eyes are pretty)
(Jaeseung: He looks cute when he smiles)
What's your name?
(Jaeseung: I'm Cha Jaeseung)
(Hanmin: Cha Jaeseung)
(Seungjin: I'm Kim Seungjin)
(Hanmin: Kim Seungjin... Okay)
(Seungjin: Wait. I'm really curious about one thing)
(Seungjin: Did you have an outdoor or indoor date?)
-Indoors. -Indoors.
(We had an indoor date)
Indoors.
(Ugh!)
(We had an indoor date)
(Jaeseung: Wait. Why are you so angry?)
(Youngjoon: Why?)
(Seungjin: Everything was great, but it was really hot)
(Seungjin: It was burning hot)
(Jaeseung: We went to a sheep farm)
(Youngjoon: Sheep farm!)
(Jaeseung: We went to the farm to feed the sheep)
(Youngjoon: So cute. Sounds so fun)
(Seungjin: A sheep sucked my finger)
(Jaeseung: We just gave things without receiving anything)
(Youngjoon: We went to a soap workshop)
(Wow!) (Doesn't it sound fun?)
(Jaeseung: You're already teasing us)
(Jaeseung: Were you always teasing people like this?)
(Seungjin: Did you make soap?)
(Minseon: Let me show you)
(Youngjoon: Seungjin, I thought you'd like it)
(Seungjin: I really went to a soap workshop, not long ago)
-It's pretty. -You made pretty ones.
(Minseon: I made them myself)
-It smells good. -We put some aroma oil in it.
(Youngjoon: We put some aroma oil in it)
(Seungjin: They all (smell) different)
(Youngjoon: We were really busy. To make these five soaps)
(Seungjin: Oh, this smells really great)
(Minseon: But I don't know much about fragrances)
(Minseon: Youngjoon knew so much about fragrances)
(Seungjin: Really?)
(Minseon: I was so surprised)
(Jaeseung: There's nothing he doesn't know)
(Minseon: There's nothing he doesn't know)
They're all good people.
(Jaeseung: There's nothing he doesn't know)
(Minseon: There's nothing he doesn't know)
(Jaeseung: Let's choose the best design out of (the soaps))
(Minseon: Sure)
(Seungjin: I choose this one)
(Youngjoon: (Seungjin & Jaeseung) cared less about the newbie)
(Youngjoon: than the soaps. They talked about the soaps so eagerly)
(Youngjoon: They don't seem interested in him)
(Youngjoon: So, in this aspect,)
(Youngjoon: I felt relieved)
(The chairs! There are eight chairs!)
(Seungjin: The blankets are already on the beds)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Minseon: I'll go take a look)
(Seungjin: The blankets are already on the beds)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Minseon: I'll go take a look)
(Minseon: What's on the beds?)
(Seungjin: The blankets)
(Minseon: No way)
(Youngjoon: Really?)
(Seungjin: There are blankets on your sacred beds)
-Haha. -On your sacred beds.
(Minseon & Youngjoon's double room turns into a quadruple room)
(Seungjin: There are blankets on your sacred beds)
Ah!
(Minseon & Youngjoon's double room turns into a quadruple room)
(Minseon: No way!)
(Minseon: Another set of mint ones)
(Youngjoon: You're right)
(Youngjoon: Choosing places is nerve-racking and...)
(Minseon: What should we do?)
(Youngjoon: Let's just ask them to pick)
(Minseon: Whatever)
(Youngjoon: They came later, so they pick what they like)
(Minseon: Let them decide)
If we have to choose...
(Jaeseung: Since yesterday, I feel like you two are getting more and more in sync)
We became besties.
(Minseon: We even dated)
We're done.
(Minseon: It's natural that we're in sync)
You have great chemistry.
(Jaeseung: Ours was like a "Please Get Closer" date)
(Youngjoon: Since you two aren't even roommates)
I stole his seat.
(Hanmin sits next to Youngjoon)
Have a seat.
Sit inside.
(Hanmin sits next to Youngjoon)
(Jaeseung: Sit in the middle)
(Hanmin: Thank you)
(Jaeseung: I think (the second-floor quadruple room) will be our base)
That's right.
(Youngjoon: It's already our base)
(Hwi, Seongmin, and Myeongkyun are last to come home)
You must be nervous.
-Really. -The first meeting.
(Hwi, Seongmin, and Myeongkyun are last to come home)
-We were really nervous when we first met. -Right.
(Noises)
That order is the most important.
(They're here!)
-Originally... -I want to hide.
(Men getting nervous upon hearing the door squeaking)
I want to hide this time.
-They have flowers. -They have flowers.
(They applaud first to welcome them back)
(Youngjoon: What's going on?)
(Minseon: Where's the newbie?)
Hello.
(Youngjoon: What's going on?)
(Minseon: Where's the newbie?)
Hello.
(Finally, the last man Myeongkyun meets everyone)
What's going on?
(Wow)
(Clapping)
(Minseon: He's handsome and lit up the room)
(Minseon: He changed the atmosphere)
(Jaeseung: He's tall and has prominent facial features)
(Jaeseung: He's cool)
(Youngjoon: My heart dropped)
(Youngjoon's face obviously hardens with Myeongkyun's arrival)
(Youngjoon: I was really shocked)
(Myeongkyun: He still has a great style and dresses up well)
(Myeongkyun: He hasn't changed at all. He looks great)
Did I sit here too naturally?
(Myeongkyun looks flustered as well)
Please sit down.
Can I sit here?
-You brought flowers. -We prepared flowers.
(Myeongkyun sits next to Youngjoon)
(Youngjoon: I avoided looking his way)
(Youngjoon: I didn't know how to act)
(Youngjoon: I suddenly got really nervous)
(Youngjoon and Myeongkyun look a bit confused)
-We... -No, no.
(Youngjoon doesn't look towards Myeongkyun)
(Myeongkyun: He acted like we don't know each other, so I panicked)
(Minseon: Let's introduce ourselves)
(Minseon: Because there are two newbies?)
(Minseon: Introduce ourselves)
(Myeongkyun: I'm Jo Myeongkyun, who will move in from today)
(Hanmin: He looks fancy)
(Hanmin: He looks like a model)
(Hanmin: I'll introduce myself next)
(Hanmin: I'm Kim Hanmin, who'll also move in from today on)
(Staring)
(Seongmin: Looks-wise, Hanmin is close to my ideal type)
(Myeongkyun: He's handsome. I think he works out too)
Nice to meet you. I think everyone's here.
Everyone is here.
We're all here.
(Youngjoon: Our room's now a quadruple room)
(Youngjoon: The double room turned into a quadruple room)
(Minseon: There are two more chairs in the kitchen too)
(Seungjin: Have you eaten?)
(Hwi: No)
(Seungjin: Let's prepare dinner now)
(Jaeseung: We'll prepare dinner)
(Jaeseung: The newbies can unpack their stuff)
(Youngjoon: We'll go help and come back down)
(The first meeting of eight men filled with surprises and shock)
It'd look nice here.
(Hwi & Seongmin are looking for a place to put the vases they made together)
-Just put it there. -We'll donate it here.
(Seungjin: Are these real flowers?)
(Seongmin: Yes)
I want to smell it too.
(Seungjin: Are these real flowers?)
(Seongmin: Yes)
(Smelling)
(Seongmin: I got this as a gift)
(Jaeseung: Who gave it to you?)
(Seongmin: Hwi gave it to me)
(Hwi: Isn't it pretty?)
I want to smell it.
It's so pretty.
(Jaeseung: Put some water in it)
-Cold water? -Cold water.
(Troubled)
(Jaeseung: I realized I'm jealous)
(Seongmin: Does the ribbon (go in the vase) too?)
(Hwi: I'll put this by my bed)
(Seongmin: Why? You gave this to me)
(Hwi: Should I put this here?)
(Seongmin: This is too white, so let's leave it here)
(Seongmin: Take this to our room)
(Hwi: Okay)
(Hwi puts the flowers Seongmin gave him on the dining table)
(Youngjoon: How should we decide (on the sleeping arrangement)?)
(Youngjoon: Do you want to choose? Do you want to know which bed is ours?)
I use this one. -I use this one.
(Youngjoon's bed) (Minseon's bed)
(Youngjoon: So you two can decide after discussing)
I use this one. -I use this one.
(Youngjoon: You get to choose)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Youngjoon: I already know one of them)
(Youngjoon: So I didn't want to choose)
(Youngjoon: and left it up to the newbies)
(Minseon: I kind of want to share a bed with Myeongkyun)
(Hanmin: Which side do you prefer?)
(Minseon: Should we leave? You two can decide)
We'll find out later anyway.
(Youngjoon: Let's leave)
Let's erase this...
((fickle) Youngjoon: I don't want to leave. Let's go there)
Anyway...
(In the meantime, Youngjoon and Minseon fixes the door sign)
Let's just erase it.
(Youngjoon: Should we write "Who & Who"?)
(Minseon: Sounds good. With the symbol '&'?)
(Youngjoon: We need more space, so I'll wipe this off too)
(Minseon: Just wipe everything off)
(Youngjoon: Let's keep the style)
(Youngjoon: It's drawn at the top)
(Minseon: The sun and moon?)
(Hanmin: I'm not a light sleeper)
(Hanmin: So I can sleep anywhere)
(Myeongkyun: I'm not really a light sleeper too)
(Myeongkyun: But I wake up early)
(Hanmin: Do you get up early?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
-So I... -Then...
(Hanmin: Do you get up early?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Hanmin: Let's ask them)
-So I... -Then...
(Hanmin: Do you get up early?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Hanmin: Let's ask them)
(Hanmin: who wakes up earlier)
(Youngjoon: Ask what?)
(Hanmin: Who gets up earlier?)
(Youngjoon: We woke up together)
(Minseon: We did wake up together)
-But Youngjoon got on his feet sooner. -Right.
(Youngjoon: We woke up together)
(Minseon: We did wake up together)
-But Youngjoon got on his feet sooner. -Right.
(Youngjoon: He stretches on his bed first)
(Minseon: I need time to fully wake up)
Meditation...
(Minseon: To put it nicely, I need some time to meditate)
I'll keep dozing off.
-Carry on with your discussion. -Carry on.
(Myeongkyun: I'm the type to get up right away)
(Hanmin: Oh, then...)
(Hanmin: You'll sleep here. I'll sleep inside)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Myeongkyun: I ended up sleeping in the same bed with Youngjoon)
(Myeongkyun: It's okay)
(Myeongkyun: I don't know his sleeping habits, but it should be fine)
-Have you decided? -Have you?
-Yes. -How did you choose?
(Youngjoon: How should I write our names (on the sign)?)
(Hanmin: I'll sleep (with Minseon), and Myeongkyun will (sleep with Youngjoon))
Okay.
(Youngjoon: How should I write our names (on the sign)?)
(Oh, right)
(Youngjoon: We weren't informed)
(Youngjoon: that we'll be sharing the beds)
(Youngjoon: That too...)
(Myeongkyun: What should we do?)
(Hanmin: It's a sudden choice)
(Youngjoon: We just used the bed like it was our own)
(Youngjoon: So if you'd prefer to share a bed...)
(Myeongkyun: I'm fine however)
(Youngjoon: When we first chose the beds,)
(Youngjoon: there were yellow blankets there and mint ones here)
(Youngjoon: I said the mint ones are pretty,)
(Youngjoon: so Minseon let me use the mint one)
(Hanmin: Oh)
(Youngjoon: Do we have to flip palms to decide?)
(Youngjoon: Actually, I really don't want to share (a bed) with Myeongkyun)
(Youngjoon: I tried my best)
(Youngjoon: I tried my best to come up with a way to change the arrangmement)
(Hanmin: Let’s stick with it first)
(Youngjoon: Stick with it?)
(Hanmin: If it doesn't work, we can change it later)
(Youngjoon: If you're bothered by someone's sleeping habits, let's tell each other)
(Hanmin: Okay)
(Youngjoon: All four of us)
(Youngjoon: Since it was decided,)
(Youngjoon: I thought to try to make it work)
(Youngjoon: and went with it)
(What will happen in the quadruple room?)
(Hwi & Jaeseung spend time together while waiting for dinner)
-We end up not taking many photos. -Yes.
(Jaeseung: Want to take a photo together before revealing our ages?)
(Hwi: Yeah, I'd love that. In selfie mode?)
(Click)
Wait.
(Hwi: Oh, it's nice. Print it?)
(Jaeseung: I don't like it)
(Hwi: One more?)
(Jaeseung: Help me fix my hair)
(Hwi: Your hair?)
(Jaeseung: I took a photo with Hwi)
(Jaeseung: He touched me slightly a few times, which made my heart flutter)
(Hwi: I don't know what to do)
(Hwi: Will I make it worse?)
(They try again after his hair's fixed)
One, two, three.
(Hwi: Oops, I closed my eyes)
(Jaeseung: I think it looks good)
(Jaeseung: Again?)
(Hwi: Print it)
(Hwi: It looks good)
(Jaeseung: Print it?)
(Hwi: Okay)
(Taking a glance)
(Jaeseung: It looks like an old photo)
(Hwi: I should take photos of Seungjin cooking for him)
(Jaeseung: Hwi, I think you're kind)
(Hwi: Why?)
-Hwi, I think you're kind. -Why?
(Jaeseung: Hwi, I think you're kind)
(Hwi: Why?)
(Jaeseung: The way you speak...)
(Jaeseung: I noticed you help others take photos a lot,)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Jaeseung: even when they didn't ask you to)
(Jaeseung: It's not common)
(Hwi: Doesn't it look like a Japanese restaurant with an open-kitchen?)
(Jaeseung: There's the vibe)
(Jaeseung: My face looks so fat. Gosh)
(My face is fatter) (Puffed up!)
(Hwi: I look so fat)
(Jaeseung: I ate more than yesterday)
(Jaeseung: Actually I ate a lot yesterday too)
(Hwi: Let’s compare them)
(Hwi: But your hairstyle today's really nice)
(Jaeseung: Yes, it's only been a day...)
(Jaeseung: My hair's nice, but my cheeks are too full)
(Jaeseung: I didn't work out enough)
(Jaeseung: How much harder do I have to work out?)
(Another glance)
(Hwi: Looks like they're setting up the table)
(Jaeseung: Let's go)
Should I put it like that?
(The first dinner of the eight men)
I think this looks better.
What is this?
(The first dinner of the eight men)
(The light boiled pork Seungjin prepared)
What is this?
-My mood... -Wait, I feel so...
(The light boiled pork Seungjin prepared)
I'm so sorry I didn't help much.
The instant noodles' ready. Gather here.
(Seungjin's style of pork instant noodles cooked in pork-based stock)
(Gathering quickly)
(Hwi: It looks delicious)
For the rest of the time...
(Lost)
(Myeongkyun: I'll sit here)
(Youngjoon: Where should I sit?)
(Myungkyun & Youngjoon end up next to each other)
(Myeongkyun: What's going through (Youngjoon's) mind?)
(Myeongkyun: Anyway if he's next to me, I can find out)
(Myeongkyun: You may tell others about me)
(Looks delicious)
(Minseon: Thank you for cooking for us)
(Seungjin: Enjoy)
(Youngjoon: Thank you for the food)
(Thank you for the food)
(Some soup first)
-Amazing. It's really delicious. -Really?
(Hwi: Seongmin, it’s really delicious)
(Seongmin: Yeah?)
Yes.
(Hwi: Seongmin, it’s really delicious)
(Seongmin: Yeah?)
(Hwi: Wow, it's really delicious)
(Seungjin: That's a relief)
(Seongmin: I feel really recharged)
(Minseon: Wow. Instant noodles and boiled pork go so well together. I tried it)
-Are you two lovers? -I've been thinking...
((Thinking) Myeongkyun: I feel like something's missing, because there's no kimchi)
(Jaeseung: I've been the only one complaining about the lack of kimchi)
(Youngjoon: That's right. You've been talking about kimchi since yesterday)
Since yesterday, I...
(Saw something)
(Ew)
What is it? It's a mayfly.
(Grabs it) (Bug that intruded their dinner)
Did it fall into the sauce?
-It didn’t fall in. -Thank goodness.
(Hanmin grabs the bug without hesitation)
Wet wipes.
-What's going on? -He just grabbed it?
(Hanmin grabs the bug without hesitation)
(Shocked)
-What's going on? -He just grabbed it?
-Wait. -What?
(Shocked)
-What's going on? -He just grabbed it?
(Hwi: Wait, wow, wait)
-Wait. -What?
(Shocked)
-What's going on? -He just grabbed it?
(Hwi: Wait, wow, wait)
-Wet wipes. -He grabbed the bug's body with bare hands.
(Youngjoon: He grabbed the bug's body with bare hands;)
(Youngjoon: not even its wings)
(Embarrassed) (Hanmin: Since it's a mayfly)
(Youngjoon: I was amazed and scared,)
(Youngjoon: but I thought he could protect me)
(Hwi: Oh, I was really impressed by that)
(Sincere) (Hwi: The tail was really... I've never seen one with such a long tail)
(Hanmin: Why are they all surprised?)
(Hanmin: Because I was born in Gangwon Province,)
(Hanmin: if there are bugs, you've to catch it before it gets in (the food))
(Jaeseung: I'm really curious about this)
(Jaeseung: How did (Hanmin & Myeongkyun) choose their dates?)
(Youngjoon: Oh, they don't know)
(Minseon: Right, (Jaeseung & Seungjin) don't know)
(Youngjoon: They were busy getting close)
(Jaeseung: We were the "Please Get Closer" team)
(Minseon: Please Get Closer)
(Youngjoon: By our keywords)
(Jaeseung: Keywords?)
(Youngjoon: Yes)
(Youngjoon: A phrase that represents each of us)
(Jaeseung: What did you choose?)
Here, you can start.
(Myeongkyun: I was considering between two)
(Myeongkyun: and chose "Self-esteem Guardian...)
(Myeongkyun: with beautiful eyes and hands")
(Minseon: What's the other one?)
(Myeongkyun: I don't remember)
I skipped...
(Myeongkyun: I skipped two animals...)
(Youngjoon: Skipped two animals?)
(Youngjoon: Skipped the cat and dog)
(Myeongkyun: I skipped the old cat and the dog)
(Myeongkyun: "Playful Tofu")
(Youngjoon: Are you "Playful Tofu"?)
-"Playful Tofu"? -I think it's you.
(Myeongkyun: "Playful Tofu")
(Youngjoon: Are you "Playful Tofu"?)
(Hwi acting confused)
(Seongmin: I think you're "Playful Tofu")
-"Playful Tofu"? -I think it's you.
You're in the same group anyway.
(Hwi acting confused)
(Seongmin: I think you're "Playful Tofu")
(Minseon: Wow, us too)
(Youngjoon: (Hanmin) was choosing between (me and Minseon) too)
Really?
(Youngjoon: Myeongkyun's choices were (Seongmin and Hwi) too)
They'd have ended up in the same places.
(Hwi: Why didn't he choose me instead (of Seongmin)?)
(Youngjoon: If they chose the same person, four people might have met)
(Oh)
Right.
(Minseon: We met as a foursome for the first time too)
(Jaeseung: How did you choose (the card)?)
(Hanmin: I chose "All-rounder with beautiful eyes" and...)
(Youngjoon: Smiling eyes)
(Hanmin: Right. Smiling eyes)
(Hanmin: The other one is "A large dog who doesn't match his size")
(Hanmin: Among these two...)
(Hwi: Oh, I know who it is. It’s you, right?)
("Large dog")
(Hanmin: After a long time, I chose the "large dog")
(Myeongkyun: Based on first impressions,)
(Myeongkyun: personality-wise, I was most interested in Minseon)
(Minseon: Let's decide who's making breakfast tomorrow)
(Myeongkyun: Tomorrow?)
(Minseon: Who wants to do it?)
(Jaeseung: If no one wants to, can I do it?)
(Sure)
Like sandwiches. sandwiches.
(Jaeseung: Sandwiches)
(Myeongkyun: Sandwiches? I'll be the sub...)
Like sandwiches. sandwiches.
-I'll be the sub... -Subway?
(Jaeseung: Sandwiches)
(Myeongkyun: Sandwiches? I'll be the sub...)
-I'll be the sub... -Subway?
(Just kidding)
No.
-Sub. -Sub.
(Just kidding)
(Jaeseung: Oh, to help me)
(Myeongkyun: I'll be the sub-chef)
(Jaeseung: Help)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Youngjoon: Jaeseung, I think (you, Myeongkyun, and I) get up the earliest)
(Youngjoon: (Myeongkyun) said he gets up early)
(Jaeseung: Yeah?)
(Youngjoon: Call me too if I'm awake. Or not, if you don't want to)
What could it be?
(Men's phones ringing at the same time)
What is it? I haven't read it.
(Jaeseung: Here we go)
(Men's phones ringing at the same time)
(Wow!)
Wow.
Next, you can reveal
(Wow!)
your name, age, occupation and so on.
You can also ask questions freely.
(Nervous)
(Minseon: Let's choose who we're most curious about)
(Jaeseung: Like we did for our first impressions?)
(Youngjoon: Based on occupation or age?)
(Minseon: (Occupation or age), whichever. Who you're most curious about)
(Men are cautious about choosing too quickly)
(Seungjin: Let's do it after a count of three)
(Minseon: 1, 2, 3!)
(Jaeseung: 3 votes) (Youngjoon: 3 votes) (Minseon: 1 vote) (Hanmin: 1 vote)
Now...
(Youngjoon: Jaeseung?)
-3 votes. -3 votes.
(Seungjin: 3 votes)
(Youngjoon: I have 3 votes?)
-3 votes. -3 votes.
(Seungjin: 3 votes)
(Youngjoon: I have 3 votes?)
Why is it always 3:3?
(Seungjin: 3 votes)
(Youngjoon: I have 3 votes?)
(Seungjin: (Jaeseung & Youngjoon) each have 3 votes)
Why is it always 3:3?
Three votes each?
(They're most curious about Jaeseung & Youngjoon's personal info)
We're rivals.
(Youngjoon: We can start first)
(Youngjoon: I'll also check if you're really older than me)
(Seungjin: I'm most curious about Jaeseung, who I went on a date with)
(Minseon: We made our phone calls to each other)
(Minseon: That means we want to know each other better)
(Minseon: So I'm more curious about Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: Hello. I'm...)
(Jaeseung: My name is Cha Jaeseung and...)
(Jaeseung: I'm 33 years old)
(Jaeseung: I run a croffle shop)
(Daejeon Metropolitan City)
(Jaeseung: Hello, I'm Cha Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: I'm 33 years old. I run a croffle shop)
(Jaeseung: I was a personal trainer for 8 years)
(Jaeseung: I'm a bit uneasy about long-distance)
(Jaeseung: But I can travel a lot)
(Jaeseung, 33 years old, croffle shop owner)
-I live in Daejeon. -I knew it.
(Oh~ I knew it)
-So.. -Do you live in Daejeon?
(Seongmin: Do you live in Daejeon?)
(Jaeseung: Yes, I live in Daejeon)
(Jaeseung: I've been running my croffle shop for...)
(Jaeseung: almost three years)
(Jaeseung: Less than three years)
(Hwi: I'm fine with being 11 years apart)
(Minseon: Frankly, I was really surprised)
(Minseon: I thought we'd be at most four or five years apart)
(Jaeseung: Also, I used to be a personal trainer)
Really?
(Seongmin: I was surprised that he used to be a personal trainer)
(Now it's Youngjoon's turn)
(Youngjoon: Can I know what you thought)
(Youngjoon: my job was?)
(Youngjoon: Pub owner?)
(Minseon: Just a shop owner, not a pub)
(Jaeseung: I thought you're a pub owner)
(Youngjoon: Pub owner. Shop owner)
(Myeongkyun: He wants to act like we're strangers, so I didn't know)
(Myeongkyun: if I should say what I know. I don't know what he's thinking)
(Myeongkyun: I think everyone's occupations are different)
(Youngjoon: I guess?)
(Youngjoon: First, I'm 28 years old)
(Youngjoon: I have many jobs. I shoot stuff like concept posters)
(Youngjoon: My job's decorating spaces and taking photos)
(Youngjoon: Hello. I'm Son Youngjoon, 28 years old)
(Youngjoon: I work in an advertisement shooting team and run a photo studio)
(Youngjoon: I shoot all kinds of idols or advertisements)
(Youngjoon: To name a few memorable ones...)
(Youngjoon: aespa, SHINee, NCT, and NewJeans)
(Youngjoon: I work with them often)
(Youngjoon, 28 years old, photo studio owner)
(Professional multitasker)
(That's really cool)
(Minseon: Who should go next? How about you two decide?)
(Hwi: Decide for us)
(Jaeseung: I'll choose him)
(Youngjoon: Minseon?)
Yes, Minseon.
(Jaeseung: I'll choose him)
(Youngjoon: Minseon?)
(Jaeseung: He said yesterday that it's really shocking)
(If you knew, you'd be so shocked)
(I didn't emphasize it three times!)
Or did I?
-You kept emphasizing it. -Yes.
(Myeongkyun: Is it one of the professional jobs?)
What?
A professional job?
(Myeongkyun: Is it one of the professional jobs?)
(Minseon: Am I a professor?)
A professional job?
(Myeongkyun: Is it one of the professional jobs?)
(Minseon: Am I a professor?)
Professor?
(Failed guess)
(Myeongkyun: With glasses, Minseon looks smart)
(Myeongkyun: He looked studious)
(Minseon: I'll tell you right away)
Firstly...
(Minseon: I'm 24 years old)
(Puhaha)
(What? Wait)
(Are you laughing at him?)
(So mean!)
(Jaeseung: I felt sorry towards him)
(Jaeseung: I told him I thought he's the oldest)
(Hanmin: When I heard Minseon's age, I was quite surprised)
(Minseon: I'm majoring in acting)
(Minseon: I want to be an actor)
(Minseon: I'm 24-year-old Hwang Minseon, who majors in acting)
(Minseon: I spend a lot of time on playing games)
(Minseon: I'm good at adapting to changes and I'm optimistic)
(Minseon: I'm receptive towards new things)
(Minseon, 24 years old, acting major in college)
(Minseon: Are you okay? You seem taken aback)
(Kidding) (Youngjoon: He can be your son)
(Stop! Stop!)
Okay.
(Myeongkyun: I thought this person would have such charms,)
(Myeongkyun: but he has different charms)
(Youngjoon: My turn? To pick one?)
(Youngjoon: (Jaeseung and Seongmin) were the most unpredictable for me)
(Youngjoon: Because when I tried guessing yesterday,)
(Youngjoon: I haven't talked much with them)
(Youngjoon: Since (Jaeseung) had his turn, I'll pick Seongmin)
(Seongmin: Mine's a bit unique)
(Seongmin: First, I'm 29 years old)
(Seongmin: I'm 29-year-old Bae Seongmin, a Korean tutor)
(Seongmin: I like new challenges)
(Seongmin: So, I graduated from an engineering college)
(Seongmin: but I worked as a brand marketer for four years)
(Seongmin: Now, I'm working towards my new dream as a Korean tutor)
(Seongmin, 29 years old, Korean tutor)
(Oh, it suits you)
(Surprised)
(Hwi: Didn't I guess it?)
(Seongmin: So you surprised me)
(Youngjoon: What did you say?)
(Hwi: I said Korean tutor exactly)
(Hwi: I was just joking yesterday, when I said he's a Korean tutor,)
(Hwi: but I got it right)
(So I guess this is fate)
-Myeongkyun. -Me?
(Minseon: Myeongkyun)
(Myeongkyun: I'm 25 years old, working as a model and actor)
(Startled)
(Myeongkyun: Hello, I'm 25-year-old Jo Myeongkyun, a model and actor)
(Myeongkyun: I started acting in plays since 17)
(Myeongkyun: I've recently moved on to the media industry)
(Myeongkyun: I've been in various web dramas and morning dramas)
(Myeongkyun: I've been a stuntman many times too)
(Myeongkyun, 25 years old, model and actor)
(Minseon: As an aspiring actor,)
(Minseon: I found out he's an actor)
(Minseon: I'm more interested in Myeongkyun now)
(Seongmin: I was really curious)
Really. I was really curious.
(Hanmin: Seungjin looks more fancy)
(Hanmin: I'm really curious about his occupation)
(Seungjin: I'm a dancer. I'm 21 years old)
-21? -21?
21?
(Wow)
(All the way down to 21 years old?)
(Seungjin: Hello, I've been a dancer for six years)
(Seungjin: I'm 21-year-old Kim Seungjin)
(Seungjin: I'm very lively with friends)
(Seungjin: but usually quiet and calm)
(Seungjin, 21-year-old, dancer)
(Youngjoon: Dancer? What genre?)
(Seungjin: I'm a Hip-hop dance major)
Right? It suits him.
It really suits him.
(Hanmin: As expected, he's in the arts field)
Do you have a dancer alias?
(Youngjoon: Do you have a dancer alias?)
(Seungjin: My dancer alias is... Gadi)
Do you have a dancer alias?
(Youngjoon: Do you have a dancer alias?)
(Seungjin: My dancer alias is... Gadi)
(Hwi: It suits you, Gadi)
(Seungjin: The name doesn't mean anything)
(Seungjin: Anyway, that's what I've been doing)
So cool.
(Youngjoon: Myeongkyun, you get the final choice)
(Myeongkyun: Me?)
(Youngjoon: Between (Hwi & Hanmin))
(Myeongkyun: Fellow newbie, Hanmin)
(Hanmin: I'm 27 years old)
(Hanmin: Hello, I'm 27-year-old Kim Hanmin)
(Hanmin: I'm working in the personnel department of an University Hospital)
(Hanmin: I'm also a freelance model)
(Hanmin: My childhood dream's been modelling)
(Hanmin: I happened to get a chance to model)
(Hanmin: Since then, I started devoting to it)
(Hanmin, 27 years old, Hospital Personnel staff and model)
(Wow)
(Youngjoon: When we talked about taking physique photos, he tried to brush it off)
(Youngjoon: He kept emphasizing that it's a common thing)
(Myeongkyun: It's hard to (model) on the side while having an office job)
Wow, is it possible to be that good at time management?
(Myeongkyun: (Respect) Wow, is it possible to be that good at time management?)
(Youngjoon: The last one. Drumroll...)
(Youngjoon: I chose him as the youngest)
(Seongmin: Me too)
(Hwi: I'm 22 years old)
22 years old.
(Surprised)
Now...
(Oh)
I'm a college student.
(Hwi: I'm majoring in visual design in college)
Yes. I was right.
(Hwi: I'm 22-year-old Kim Hwi, majoring in visual design)
(Hwi: I've participated in exhibitions and make album art)
(Hwi: I've won awards in various art competitions)
(Hwi: I'm working actively as a visual designer)
(Hwi, 22 years old, Visual Design major in college)
(Jaeseung: I kind of lost interest in Hwi)
(Jaeseung: After knowing his personal info,)
(Jaeseung: I'm not as interested in Hwi anymore)
(Seongmin: I didn't expect him to be 7 years younger than me)
(Seongmin: I was quite shocked)
(Minseon: So how should we address each other?)
(Youngjoon: Let's not be formal)
(Seongmin: Drop the honorifics?)
(Minseon: Drop the honorifics?)
(Youngjoon: Let's just speak informally?)
(Hwi: Informally?)
(Youngjoon: Then we can get closer sooner)
(Seongmin: Let's say our (ages) once again)
(Seungjin: 21) (Hwi: 22) (Minseon: 24) (Myeongkyun: 25)
(Hanmin: 27) (Youngjoon: 28) (Seongmin: 29) (Jaeseung: 33)
Why do you have to say it again?
(Seungjin: 21) (Hwi: 22) (Minseon: 24) (Myeongkyun: 25)
(Hanmin: 27) (Youngjoon: 28) (Seongmin: 29) (Jaeseung: 33)
(Let's clean up)
(After self-introductions, how have their affections changed?)
Thank you for the food.
-Thank you for the food. -The chef...
(After self-introductions, how have their affections changed?)
(Hwi: I’ll do the dishes)
(Myeongkyun: Here's where the dishes are done)
(Hwi: I had such a great (meal). I should do the dishes)
(Seongmin: I'll do it too)
(Hwi: Really?)
(Seongmin: I should help out too)
(Hwi: Then let's do it face to face)
(Men cleaning up together)
(Hanmin: Are you washing on both sides?)
(Seongmin: Yes, doing the dishes)
(Hwi: Do you have that over there? Dishwashing liquid)
(Seongmin: Yes, here)
(Seongmin: Put it there. Let's share)
(Hwi: I wanted to do the dishes face to face with Seongmin)
(Hwi: So I asked him to do them with me)
(Jaeseung: Can I go inside and rest?)
(Youngjoon: Get some rest)
(Jaeseung: I'm going to rest)
(Jaeseung: I want to be alone)
(So annoying...)
(Ugh, so annoying...)
(Jaeseung: The person I was interested in...)
(Jaeseung: is much younger than I thought)
(Jaeseung troubled after the self-introductions)
((Whispering) Youngjoon: When you're done cleaning up, go there...)
(Myeongkyun: Oh, when I'm done...)
(Youngjoon: For a while, at the entertainment room)
(Myeongkyun: Oh, okay)
(Oh, a cat!)
(Meow) (Youngjoon: A cat? A cat came in?)
Hold on.
(Cute)
(The two face each other for the first time)
(Myeongkyun: Gosh)
(Youngjoon: You didn't know too, right?)
(Myeongkyun: Yeah)
What's going on?
(Youngjoon: I was so shocked I froze in an instant)
(Myeongkyun: I... Me too)
(Youngjoon: Well... How should I put it? I didn't expect you to show up)
(Myeongkyun: I expected one familiar face)
(Youngjoon: But not me)
(Myeongkyun: I never thought it'd be you)
(Myeongkyun: It's a problem)
(Youngjoon: It's not)
We didn't date anyway.
("We didn't date anyway")
(Youngjoon: We were in the flirting phase)
(Youngjoon: But he seemed uninterested in a relationship)
(Youngjoon: Since he wasn't serious,)
(Youngjoon: I was fine with letting him go)
(Youngjoon: and I stopped liking him,)
(Youngjoon: so I gave up on him)
(So why did he join a dating show?)
I'm confused about that too.
(Myeongkyun: As a romantic partner...)
(Myeongkyun: I'd say it's not impossible)
(Myeongkyun: Actually, I think it's the opposite. I don't think (Youngjoon))
(Myeongkyun: felt romantically attracted to me)
(Myeongkyun: First of all, because I'm younger...)
(Myeongkyun: I think he wasn't interested in me)
(Myeongkyun: romantically)
-(What happened between the two?)
-How should I put it?
(I stood on the second floor, looking down to see when he'd come)
(But he didn't come even after a long time)
(Beckoning sign)
(He seems to think about it too lightly)
(That's why I'm angry)
(I feel like he's one-sidedly)
(drawing the line between us)
(Men's conflicts begin)
(To be honest, I really didn't want to make)
(the second phone call)
(I tried my best to avoid him after the call)
(I didn't even look at him)
(I've been waiting...)
(I became confused and troubled)
(It feels like I betrayed him)
(One of us must've been severely mistaken about it)
(Men's House in chaos)
He must've been disappointed.
Who do I think I am?
(Men's House in chaos)