(In the hot summer, these men came here to search for love)
(Because I want to date)
Because I want to find my love.
(Because I want to find my love)
(With the thought of "I must defeat everyone")
(People who are more handsome than me? I don't think there are many of those)
I want to have a relationship like in the romance dramas.
(The men's romance which returns hotter)
(His Man 3)
(The first journey to seek a heart-fluttering love)
(Who are these special men
who have plucked up the courage to look for love?)
(What kind of encounter is waiting for them?)
(Finally, the first man appears)
(Please choose a card
and head to the destination written on it.)
(I think I'm quite popular.)
("You look good when you smile." I get that a lot)
(I like people who are around my height.)
I like people who are around my height.
And I hope he doesn't have double eyelids and that he has a pretty smile.
(I like people who are around my height.)
(And I hope he doesn't have double eyelids and that he has a pretty smile.)
And I hope he doesn't have double eyelids and that he has a pretty smile.
(If I don't like someone,)
(nothing they do will attract me.)
I don't like being wishy-washy.
(I don't like being wishy-washy.)
(If I like someone, it shows on my face.)
(If someone's being wishy-washy towards me?
I will just push them away.)
("Though he's common, but he's not that common;
though he's bad, he's kind.)
(Jaeseung)
(The second person to arrive at Men's House)
I like people with bold and sharp features.
((Ideal type) I like people with bold and sharp features.)
(And I like people with short hair.)
(In terms of personality, someone who's active, and good at socializing?)
(To be honest, I'm quite conscious about education.)
(I studied really hard when I was in school.)
(I went to a college-preparatory school and went to university directly.)
(I want someone whom I can learn something from.)
I want someone whom I can learn something from.
(I haven't dated anyone who is my ideal type yet.)
Anyway, these people participating in this show,
(Anyway, these people are already revealing their faces to the public,)
are already revealing their faces to the public,
("I don't think there will be any trash here, right?")
(To introduce myself in a sentence,)
("An all-rounder who has a pretty nice smile"?)
(Youngjoon)
(The third man)
(I have a similar personality to cats.)
(A little chic?)
(I'm very interested in fashion so I search up on the internet)
(quite a bit.)
(I like someone who wears something different from me, and is clean looking.)
(I like puppy-like faces,)
(and people who are gentle.)
(I... look like a fox?)
I'll definitely choose someone older.
((Ideal type) I'll definitely choose someone older.)
(Anyone who's within 12 years older than me.)
(For people who don't like me, I will just let them go cooly.)
(The reason I came to Men's House is cause I found it fun.)
(To describe myself in a sentence,)
("Though I'm cold, I'm a cat that will warm up when I get close to you.)
You can say that.
(Seungjin)
(More than visuals,)
(I'm more easily attracted to people I talk to easily.)
(If we get along well, I will find them sexy.)
(I think my charm is my eyes.)
(When I look at the person I like, my eyes shine.)
("I put everything into it when I'm in a relationship.")
Being wishy-washy? I think about if it's necessary.
(Being wishy-washy? I think about if it's necessary.)
(I do not want to associate with people who cheats.)
(If I'm in the middle of a love triangle, I might feel quite happy?)
(Cause I'm grateful that they like me.)
I'm the guardian of self-esteem who has pretty eyes and hands.
("I'm the guardian of self-esteem who has pretty eyes and hands.")
(Seongmin)
(My charm is, I don't have my defences up against anyone.)
(Everyone says I'm easy to get close to.)
And I'm tall and my facial features are also prominent.
(I'm tall and my facial features are also prominent.)
(It can be said that I have a "very prominent face")
(Artists that people say I look like?)
(I've heard people say I look like John Park.)
(In the past, there are also people who said I looked like Ji Changwook...)
("It made me so embarrassed I couldn't lift my face...")
I don't really care if someone's handsome or not.
((Ideal type) I don't really care if someone's handsome or not.)
(Skinny and around my height or taller.)
I like people who are skinny and around my height or taller.
(In terms of personality, I like people who look indifferent but are gentle.)
(To describe myself with a sentence,)
I'm a big puppy with a big physique.
("I'm a big puppy with a big physique.")
(Minseon)
(And the sixth man)
My charm is...
(Unlike my looks, I can be quite ditzy. That's a charm of mine.)
(I don't care about their height.)
((My ideal type) is someone who is kind and calm.)
(I like people who have that "older brother" vibe.)
(I like people older than me the most.)
(If I like someone, it shows on my face.)
(It's a little more exciting if there's a little of push and pull, no?)
(Only if there's push and pull will I work harder)
Only if there's push and pull
will I work harder
(Only if there's push and pull will I work harder)
(to get them.)
will I work harder
(To describe myself in a sentence,)
("A mischievous tofu who's cute.")
(Shy)
(Hwi)
(The heart-fluttering first selection
Who will the men be dating?)
(Episode 1: The first meeting, and secret phone call)
(At the place to first meet)
(At the place to first meet: Hwi)
(Hwi: I’m a little worried. But I still feel excited.)
(Who will Hwi meet?)
(Hwi: I hope someone arrives before me.)
(Nervous)
(Hwi: Who will come here?)
(Hwi: How many people will come? I've been looking forward to
(Another man heading to the blind date location)
(Another man going to the blind date location: Youngjoon)
(Youngjoon: First of all, the weather is very nice.)
(Youngjoon: I went there with a thumping heart and good mood.)
(Youngjoon: Every step was nerve-racking.)
(Youngjoon: I was afraid that the sound of me walking would be heard so I was being very careful.)
(Youngjoon: It was really heart-fluttering, my every step.)
(Hwi and Youngjoon greet for the first time)
Hello.
(Youngjoon: When I saw at his back,)
(Youngjoon: I thought he had the dandy and office worker vibe.)
(Youngjoon: But when I saw his college student-like face, it was quite different.)
(Hwi: You have a piercing?
Youngjoon: Yes.)
-I also have one here.
-I see, I have many too.
(Hwi: I also have one here.
Youngjoon: I see.)
-I also have one here.
-I see, I have many too.
-You have a lot of piercings?
-Yes, on the outside of the ear.
(They started the conversation through a common point)
-You have a lot of piercings?
-Yes, on the outside of the ear.
It looks nice here.
(They started the conversation through a common point)
(Hwi: He looks cheerful, so it's good.)
(Hwi: He has a lot of tattoos. He looks fashionable.)
(Hwi: So I thought he's a cool guy.)
-But your tattoos too...
-Yeah.
(Hwi: But your tattoos too...)
-But your tattoos too...
-Yeah.
(Hwi: you look quite fashionable
Youngjoon: Really? Thank you.)
What does this tattoo mean?
(Hwi: you look quite fashionable
Youngjoon: Really? Thank you.)
(Hwi: What does this tattoo mean?
Youngjoon: This one?
What does this tattoo mean?
-This one?
-Yes.
(Hwi: What does this tattoo mean?
Youngjoon: This one?
-This is based around a cross motif.
-A cross.
(Hwi: What does this tattoo mean?
Youngjoon: This one?
(Youngjoon: This is based around a cross motif.)
-This is based around a cross motif.
-A cross.
(Youngjoon: When people see it, they think it was drawn on by a ball pen.)
(Hwi: These are the type that you won't get tired of looking at so it's pretty good.)
(Youngjoon: I haven't gotten tired of them and I don't have any regrets.)
(Youngjoon: Ah! My name is Son Youngjoon.)
-Son Youngjoon
-Yes, Youngjoon.
(Youngjoon: Ah! My name is Son Youngjoon.)
-Son Youngjoon
-Yes, Youngjoon.
(The two who are late to introducing their names)
-Son Youngjoon
-Yes, Youngjoon.
(The two who are late to introducing their names)
(Hwi: My name is Kim Hwi.)
(Youngjoon: Just one character.
Hwi: Yes, one character.)
-Hwi. -Hwi.
(Youngjoon: Just one character.
Hwi: Yes, one character.)
Youngjoon.
(Youngjoon: Just one character.
Hwi: Yes, one character.)
So...
(Youngjoon: Just one character.
Hwi: Yes, one character.)
-But like...
-Yes?
We can't reveal our age and occupation. Only our names.
(Youngjoon: We can't reveal our age and occupation. Only our names.)
(Hwi: So there's nothing to talk about, right?)
(Youngjoon: I don't know what topic to start talking about.)
(Hwi: Do you like art exhibitions?)
(Youngjoon: Art exhibitions? I often go to them.)
(Hwi: I go to art exhibitions quite frequently.)
-Is that so?
-Yes.
(Hwi: I go to art exhibitions quite frequently.)
Not to take photos of, but to actually look at the exhibits.
(Youngjoon: Not to take photos of,)
-but to actually look at the exhibits.
-Yes.
(Youngjoon: but to actually look at the exhibits.)
-but to actually look at the exhibits.
-Yes.
(Youngjoon: but to actually look at the exhibits.)
(Hwi: Like the MMCA, or the Leeum Museum of Art.)
-MMCA.
-Yeah, the MMCA.
(Hwi: Like the MMCA, or the Leeum Museum of Art.)
-Or the Leeum Museum of Art.
-Yeah, Leeum...
(Hwi: Like the MMCA, or the Leeum Museum of Art.)
Leeum. There was that...
(Youngjoon: I went to look at the Maurizio Cattelan exhibition.)
(Hwi: Like the MMCA, or the Leeum Museum of Art.)
I went to look at the Maurizio Cattelan exhibition.
(Youngjoon: I went to look at the Maurizio Cattelan exhibition.)
(Hwi: I really liked that exhibition.)
I went to look at the Maurizio Cattelan exhibition.
(Youngjoon: I went to look at the Maurizio Cattelan exhibition.)
(Hwi: I really liked that exhibition.)
-I think I went there in May?
-May?
(Hwi: I really liked that exhibition.)
(Youngjoon: I think I went there in May? Pretty recently.)
-I think I went there in May?
-May?
Pretty recently.
(Youngjoon: I think I went there in May? Pretty recently.)
(Youngjoon: I went before the banana was taken.)
I went before the banana was taken.
(Youngjoon: There were parts of our hobbies that overlapped?)
(Youngjoon: I can feel that he's trying hard to find something in common with me,)
(Youngjoon: so I'm grateful to him and I feel comfortable)
(Hwi: Because Youngjoon is also interested in art,)
(Hwi: so we are quite similar.)
Then you like art more–
(Youngjoon: Oh?)
(Youngjoon: Looks like someone's here.)
Looks like someone's here.
(The third man who came to look for Hwi and Youngjoon)
(The third man who came to look for Hwi and Youngjoon: Seungjin)
(Youngjoon: As we were talking, I saw someone.)
(Youngjoon: I went "Oh?" and turned to look at him.)
(Youngjoon: He's my type.)
(Youngjoon: He has dark skin, and tattoos.)
(Youngjoon: His fashion is a little kitsch and hip hop,)
(Youngjoon: so I think I'm happy to see him.)
(Hwi: He's really fashionable, so I think I had raised anticipation.)
(Seungjin: Before I went in, I thought I was the first person.)
(Seungjin: But as I went in and found out I wasn't, I got anxious.)
(Youngjoon: Let's exchange names first.)
Okay, I'm Kim Seungjin.
(Seungjin: I'm Kim Seungjin.)
-Seungjin.
-Yes.
(Seungjin: I'm Kim Seungjin.)
(Seungjin?) (Seungjin)
-Seungjin.
-Yes.
(Seungjin?) (Seungjin)
-I'm Son Youngjoon.
-Okay.
(Seungjin?) (Seungjin)
(Youngjoon: I'm Son Youngjoon.)
-I'm Son Youngjoon.
-Okay.
(Youngjoon: I'm Son Youngjoon.)
(Hwi: My name is Kim Hwi. It's one character.)
(Seungjin: We are all wearing white pants.
Youngjoon: Oh that's true. Interesting.)
(Nervous)
(Youngjoon: It's getting awkward again.)
(Seungjin: I'm shy with strangers.)
-Are you an introvert?
-Yes.
(Youngjoon: Are you an introvert (MBTI)?
Seungjin. Yes.)
-Are you an introvert?
-Yes.
(Youngjoon: Are you an introvert (MBTI)?
Seungjin. Yes.)
(Hwi: But your glasses...)
(Hwi: they don't look very introverted...)
(Youngjoon: But even introverts)
(Youngjoon: have their own (?))
(Hwi: But your bleached hair color is really nice.)
-Me?
-Yes, it suits you.
(Seungjin: Me?)
(Hwi: It suits you.)
-Me?
-Yes, it suits you.
(Seungjin: Thank you.)
(Seungjin: I think Hwi's closer to my ideal type?)
(Seungjin: That he's innocent.)
(Seungjin: As for Youngjoon, he felt like someone who's similar to me.)
(Seungjin: That's what I thought.)
I thought you were here to deliver drinks.
(Who are these three men more attracted to?)
I'm the only one who didn't bring the card.
-Oh that's true.
-I didn't bring the card.
(Who are these three men more attracted to?)
I forgot the card.
(On the other hand,
another date venue)
(The first man to come to the cafe)
(The first man to come to the cafe: Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: My heart was beating really fast.)
(Jaeseung: Cause I've never been in settings like a blind date)
(Jaeseung: like this in my life.)
I can only look forward to what kind of person would come.
(What kind of person would come in?)
(Jaeseung: I hope it's someone I want to)
(Jaeseung: get to know.)
(The man going towards Jaeseung)
(The man going towards Jaeseung: Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: I think his facial features are very prominent.)
His facial features are very prominent.
(Jaeseung: And his eyes are pretty. I quite like them.)
(Seongmin: My first impression of him was, he's really handsome.)
(Seongmin: He looks like a warm guy.)
(Jaeseung: Nice to meet you.
Seongmin: Nice to meet you.)
(Seongmin: Hold on.)
(Seongmin: Gosh.. I'm really nervous.
Jaeseung: Me too.)
(Jaeseung: It's hot outside, right?
Seungmin: Yes.)
(Jaeseung: Aren't you hot? Seongmin: I'm hot too. It's too hot outside.)
(Awkward atmosphere, awkward smiles)
Really...
To be honest, I was really nervous.
(Awkward atmosphere, awkward smiles)
(Jaeseung: To be honest, I was really nervous.
Seongmin: I was really nervous too.)
To be honest, I was really nervous.
I was nervous too. As I was walking down.
(Jaeseung: To be honest, I was really nervous.
Seongmin: I was really nervous too.)
(Jaeseung: I am...)
(Jaeseung: My name is Cha Jaeseung.)
-Cha Jaeseung?
-Yes.
(Jaeseung: My name is Cha Jaeseung.)
(Seongmin: My name is Bae Seongmin.)
-Bae Seongmin.
-Yes.
(Seongmin: My name is Bae Seongmin.)
Nice to meet you.
(Among awkwardness and heart flutters)
-It's really awkward.
-Yeah.
(Among awkwardness and heart flutters)
(Seongmin: Is the address written on the card?
Jaeseung: Yes, it's the same.)
-This address?
-Yes.
(Seongmin: Is the address written on the card?
Jaeseung: Yes, it's the same.)
-Gangnam District Industrial Park.
-Yes, it's the same.
(Seongmin: Is the address written on the card?
Jaeseung: Yes, it's the same.)
(Jaeseung: Have you been on a blind date like this before?
Seongmin: A blind date?)
(Seongmin: This is my first time.)
(Jaeseung: It's my first blind date too.)
(Jaeseung: It's a complete mystery to me)
Yes.
(Jaeseung: As I opened it,)
-it felt like I was opening a gift box.
-That's right.
(Jaeseung: As I opened it,)
-it felt like I was opening a gift box.
-That's right.
(It felt like I was opening a gift box.)
-it felt like I was opening a gift box.
-That's right.
(It felt like I was opening a gift box.)
(Seongmin: But it's still nice to meet the person at first.
Jaeseung: I agree.)
(Jaeseung: I'll definitely remember your name.
Seongmin: I will definitely.)
(Jaeseung: What's your ideal type?)
(Seongmin: My ideal type... is someone taller than me.)
(Seongmin: Someone I can trust.
Jaeseung: Someone you can trust.)
(Seongmin: Someone I can communicate well with.)
(Jaeseung: So for appearance, just someone taller than you?)
(Seongmin: Yes. I hope he's taller than me.)
(Seongmin: What's your ideal type?)
For me...
(Jaeseung: I haven't decided on my ideal type.)
(Jaeseung: But I like eyes without double eyelids.)
(Seongmin: You like people with single eyelids.
Jaeseung: Yes.)
And someone with a nice nose.
(Jaeseung: And someone with a nice nose.
Seongmin: Someone with a nice nose.)
And someone with a nice nose.
-Someone with a nice nose.
-Yes.
(Jaeseung: And someone with a nice nose.
Seongmin: Someone with a nice nose.)
(Jaeseung: When I look at people with nice noses, I'm envious.)
(Jaeseung: So I like people with nice noses.)
(Seongmin: What's wrong with your nose? Your nose is pretty though?)
But I...
(Shy)
Can we not talk about it?
Okay, okay. We don't have to talk about it.
(Shy)
(Seongmin: But, can I ask again, what's your name?)
(Jaeseung: Cha Jaeseung.)
-Cha Jaeseung.
-Yes.
(Jaeseung: Cha Jaeseung.)
Okay, Cha Jaeseung.
(Seongmin: Cha Jaeseung. I'm Bae Seongmin.)
-I'm Bae Seongmin.
-Yes.
(Seongmin: Cha Jaeseung. I'm Bae Seongmin.)
(Seongmin: I was too nervous. When we first talked,)
(Seongmin: I don't even remember what I talked about. Things didn't connect.)
(Seungmin: Do you have any hobbies?
Jaeseung: I like lifting weights.)
And also swimming.
(Seungmin: Do you have any hobbies?
Jaeseung: I like lifting weights.)
And also swimming.
(Jaeseung: And also swimming.
Seongmin: Do you like swimming?)
And also swimming.
Do you like swimming?
(Jaeseung: And also swimming.
Seongmin: Do you like swimming?)
(Jaeseung: I prefer sports that I can do alone.
Seongmin: Swimming is so cool.)
(Jaeseung: What's your hobby?)
(Seongmin: I like watching movies. And listening to JANNABI's music.
-Really? JANNABI? -Yeah.
(Jaeseung: Really? JANNABI.)
(Seongmin: Isn't it cool that they have such a distinct style?
Jaeseung: That's true.)
(Jaeseung: Because there's a charm to it.
Seongmin: That's right.)
(Jaeseung: Do you have a distinct style?
Seongmin: I think it's pretty distinct.)
It's quite distinct.
(Jaeseung: Do you have a distinct style?
Seongmin: I think it's pretty distinct.)
(Jaeseung: This is fun.)
(Jaeseung: Unlike what we worried about, we are getting along well.)
Really?
(Seongmin: Did you think we wouldn't communicate well?)
(Jaeseung: After all, for blind dates,)
(Jaeseung: it puts people in a difficult spot.)
(Jaeseung: But we are communicating better than I expected.
Seongmin: That's right.)
(Seongmin: I thought it would be awkward.)
(Seongmin: But it's much easier than I thought.)
(Seongmin: We can feel all sorts of complex feelings now, right?)
-Yes,
-For example, nervousness, excitement, fear.
(Seongmin: We can feel all sorts of complex feelings now, right?)
(Seongmin: For example, nervousness, excitement, fear.
Jaeseung: Anxiety.)
-Yes,
-For example, nervousness, excitement, fear.
-Anxiety.
-Anxiety. All mixed together.
(Seongmin: For example, nervousness, excitement, fear.
Jaeseung: Anxiety.)
-All the emotions.
-Happiness is part of it too.
Because there is some anticipation.
(The first meeting with all sorts of emotions)
Right we were just about to talk about hobbies.
(Youngjoon: We were just about to talk about hobbies.)
Right.
(Youngjoon: Do you have any hobbies?
Seungjin: Me?)
-I don't really like to move.
-Is that so?
(Seungjin: I don't really like to move.)
-I don't really like to move.
-Is that so?
(Seungjin: I don't really like to move.)
(Seungjin: I went fishing a while ago. I found it pretty nice.)
(Seungjin: Cause I liked looking at the water.)
(Hwi: I find fishing boring...
Youngjoon: Have you tried it before?)
(Hwi: I did, but I felt bored.
Youngjoon: I only did fishing once. When I was young.)
I did, but I felt bored.
-I only did it once. When I was a kid.
-Really?
(Hwi: I did, but I felt bored.
Youngjoon: I only did fishing once. When I was young.)
(Seungjin: I like doing boring things.)
(Youngjoon: I can see there are a lot of differences.)
(Youngjoon: It felt new.)
For example, I'll stay home alone and watch the ceiling.
(Seungjin: I'll stay home alone and watch the ceiling.)
-Looking at the ceiling.
-Looking at the wallpaper's pattern.
(Seungjin: I'll stay home alone and watch the ceiling.)
(Youngjoon: Do you count the patterns on the wall?
Seungjin: Count the patterns...)
-Looking at the ceiling.
-Looking at the wallpaper's pattern.
Count the patterns...
(Youngjoon: Do you count the patterns on the wall?
Seungjin: Count the patterns...)
(On the other hand,
another man who arrives at the date venue)
(I'm nervous and excited.)
(I'm worried too, and have mixed feelings.)
-The background music.
-Someone's here.
(Surprised)
-The background music.
-Someone's here.
(Surprised)
-The background music.
-Someone's here.
(Panic)
-Hello. -Hello.
-Someone's here.
(The fourth man shows up unexpectedly)
Hello.
(Minseon: To be honest, I didn't expect there would be three of them there.)
(Minseon: I just kept a poker face.)
(Minseon: If I look surprised, they'll be flustered too.)
(Minseon: Let's walk in as cheerfully as possible. That's what I thought back then.)
(Youngjoon: I never thought it would be a meeting of four)
(Youngjoon: for our first meeting.)
(Hwi: I've never been on a blind date.)
(Hwi: Four people meeting at the same time is beyond my imagination.)
(Seungjin: What kind of combination is this?)
-Hello. -Hello.
(Putting the anxiousness behind and greeting each other)
(Oh, white pants again!)
-Hello. -Hello.
(Putting the anxiousness behind and greeting each other)
(Oh, white pants again!)
-White pants again.
We're all wearing white pants.
(Putting the anxiousness behind and greeting each other)
(Oh, white pants again!)
(Youngjoon: We're all wearing white pants.)
-Because it's summer.
-We just talked about this.
(Youngjoon: We're all wearing white pants.)
Let's introduce our names first. I'm Son Youngjoon. Youngjoon.
(Youngjoon: I'm Son Youngjoon.)
(Seungjin: I'm Kim Seungjin.)
(Hwi: I'm Kim Hwi. Single-character name.)
Okay, I'm Hwang Minseon.
(Minseon: I'm Hwang Minseon.)
Minseon.
Okay, I'm Hwang Minseon.
(Youngjoon: He has prominent features and deep double eyelids.)
(Hwi: He's tall and strongly-built. He looks like a big brother.)
(Seungjin: When he walked in, he looked lively.)
(Seungjin: I thought this person has quite a good personality.)
(Hwi: What's your ideal type?)
-My ideal type? -Yes.
-I like prominent facial features.
-Prominent.
(Youngjoon: I like prominent facial features. And a strong looking face.)
-I like prominent facial features.
-Prominent.
And a strong looking face.
(Youngjoon: I like prominent facial features. And a strong looking face.)
-A little like a punk?
-Like a punk?
(Youngjoon: I like prominent facial features. And a strong looking face.)
(Youngjoon: Like a punk?)
-A little like a punk?
-Like a punk?
(Youngjoon: I like the bad boy vibe.)
-Bad boy.
(Youngjoon: But his personality is the opposite.)
(Youngjoon: Like smart, and hardworking.)
(Youngjoon: When I see these characteristics, I find it attractive.)
(Minseon: Youngjoon said he liked)
(Minseon: people with prominent features.)
(Minseon: Wherever I go, people will say my facial features are very prominent.)
(Minseon: So I thought I seem to fit this part very well.)
(Hwi: I don't really care about appearance.)
(Hwi: If I have to choose, like you said,)
(Hwi: either a punk vibe, or someone who's reliable.)
(Youngjoon: That's so different, punk? A gangster and someone who's reliable.)
There's no fixed requirement.
(Hwi: No fixed requirement (for appearance).)
-A reliable punk?
-Yes.
(Hwi: No fixed requirement (for appearance).)
(Hwi: But as for the inside, as you said,)
(Hwi: someone who is working hard in their own field.)
(Kidding)
(Youngjoon: You can't copy me.)
You can't copy me.
(Kidding)
(Youngjoon: You can't copy me.)
But that's my original type...
(Kidding)
(Youngjoon: You can't copy me.)
Why are you copying my answer.
Yeah. Something like that.
I prefer mature people.
(Hwi: I prefer mature people.)
(Youngjoon: What kind of mature person does Hwi mean?)
(Youngjoon: Do I look mature?)
(Hwi: Among the four, Youngjoon is the closest to my ideal type.)
(Minseon: It's going in this way, right?)
Clockwise direction.
(Minseon: For appearance, someone who looks good at sports.)
(Youngjoon: I get the vibe.
Minseon: You get the vibe?)
(Youngjoon: Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
Minseon: Yes, something like that.)
Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
(Youngjoon: Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
Minseon: Yes, something like that.)
-Yeah, that kind of feeling.
-That kind of feeling.
(Youngjoon: Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
Minseon: Yes, something like that.)
Something like that.
(Youngjoon: Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
Minseon: Yes, something like that.)
(Minseon: In terms of personality. Someone who looks indifferent but is actually considerate?)
Something like that.
(Youngjoon: Someone who doesn't really dress up, like...
Minseon: Yes, something like that.)
(Minseon: In terms of personality. Someone who looks indifferent but is actually considerate?)
(Minseon: I like tsunderes.)
-I like people who look like boiled dumplings.
-Boiled dumplings.
(Minseon: I like tsunderes.)
(Seungjin: I like people who look like boiled dumplings.
Youngjoon: Like they look like tofu?)
-I like people who look like boiled dumplings.
-Boiled dumplings.
-Like they look like tofu?
-Yes.
(Seungjin: I like people who look like boiled dumplings.
Youngjoon: Like they look like tofu?)
(Seungjin: In terms of personality, as long as they don't want to meet all the time...)
(Seungjin: That tires me out. Just other than that, it's fine.)
(Seungjin: I haven't met someone I liked yet... That might be it.)
I haven't met someone I liked yet... That might be it.
(Minseon: What is the most important thing in love?
Youngjoon: What's the most important?
(Youngjoon: I don't tolerate lies.)
(Youngjoon: Even for small things.)
(Youngjoon: You can't lie even if it's for my sake.)
(Minseon: Like a white lie
Youngjoon: Yeah. That won't do either.
(Youngjoon: Because even so, it's a lie after all.)
(Youngjoon: No matter the intention, it's still deceiving me.)
(Hwi: I usually accept white lies.)
(\Hwi: He said he disliked it so it made me kinda shocked how different we are.)
(Minseon: Are you all done drinking?)
(Youngjoon: Everyone is drinking fast.)
(Minseon: We seem to drink too fast.)
Yes.
(Minseon: Although the blind date of four is novel,)
(Minseon: there's small talks here and there,)
(Minseon: leaving people with no opportunity to feel attracted, honestly.)
(Seungjin: Rather than saying that it's a pity, it just went by like a gust of wind.)
(Seungjin: It was all over the place. As I was trying to adjust to the vibe,
(Seungjin: I don't remember what I said anymore.)
(Youngjoon: Maybe it's because I instinctively felt that I should ease the awkwardness.)
(Youngjoon: I forced myself to interact actively.)
(Youngjoon: to lead everyone.)
(Hwi: It would've been nice if we could have been given more time to get to know each other.)
(The novel but chaotic first meeting
of the four men)
(Jaeseung)
(Seungjin)
(Minseon)
(Hwi)
(Youngjoon)
(Seongmin)
(And...)
(Hanmin)
(Myeongkyun)
(His Man 3)
(The Men's House that the men will be living in)
(A emotional house that suits the hot summer)
(The four men heading to Men's House)
Over there.
Men's House.
(Youngjoon: It's really starting. The reality started to hit me.)
(Youngjoon: My heart was pounding and I felt really excited.)
(Seungjin: It felt really extravagant.)
(Seungjin: It's such a huge house. How many people will be entering it?)
(Seungjin: That was my first thought.)
It's so cooling.
So cooling.
(Hwi: How should we sit?)
We can sit in line like this, right?
(Minseon: Ah. This is where we're going to live for a week.)
-It's cooling.
-It's really nice.
(Minseon: I'm going to live here for a week with people I just met.)
I'm going to live here for a week with people I just met.
(Men's House that will reveal the men's stories)
(Will they find love here?)
(Youngjoon: When all six are here, please check the envelope.)
(When all six are here, please check the envelope.)
This should be the phone we will be using.
(Men's House's exclusive phone)
I think so.
(Hwi: There are two more to come.)
There are two more to come.
(Youngjoon: It seems like the two of them met one on one.
Hwi: It must be awkward.)
(It's already awkward)
(Youngjoon: They could've gotten close.)
(Minseon: When the two of them come, they can sit here, right?)
-Or let's sit here.
-Let's sit here.
(Minseon: When the two of them come, they can sit here, right?)
(Hui: One here. One here.)
-Or let's sit here.
-Let's sit here.
How about we make them sit apart?
(Hui: One here. One here.)
-Or let's sit here.
-Let's sit here.
How about we make them sit apart?
(The strategy for the remaining two men's seating arrangement)
Let's see if they'll sit between us.
Coming over here and sitting in the middle.
-Going from here.
Let me take this seat with pillows.
(Blocking the seat with a pillow)
Put your legs up there.
Like this.
(While the four men are having a happy conversation)
(Men's House)
-This place is amazing.
-Yeah
(Men's House)
-This is Men's House.
-It's nice here.
(Men's House)
-It's amazing.
-Amazing.
(Jaeseung & Seongmin arriving at Men's House)
-It's amazing.
-Amazing.
(Jaeseung & Seongmin arriving at Men's House)
-Don't you think it'll be fun?
-Right?
(Jaeseung & Seongmin arriving at Men's House)
I'm sorry. I'm speaking informally.
It's okay.
Open the door first.
Is anyone inside?
(Hwi: Are you all looking forward to the rooms?)
Me too.
(Turn around)
They're coming.
I...
How do we sit?
(Shy)
I want to hide.
What should I do?
(What should I do?)
(Busy)
What should I do?
Should we sit separately?
(Busy)
There are shoes.
(Jaeseung: Looks like we're not the first to come.)
-Hold on.
-Looks like we're not the first to come.
(Jaeseung: Looks like we're not the first to come.)
(Jaeseung: Hello.
Seongmin: Hello.)
Hello.
(Jaeseung: Hello.
Seongmin: Hello.)
-Hello. -Hello.
(Jaeseung: Hello.
Seongmin: Hello.)
-Hello. -Hello.
(The six men who are greeting each other for the first time)
(Jaeseung: It's so awkward.)
(Youngjoon: Please sit.
Seungjae: Where should we sit?)
(Youngjoon: Take a seat anywhere.)
-Where do I sit?
-Sit here.
(Youngjoon: Take a seat anywhere.)
(Finally,
all six men are here)
-Where do I sit?
-Sit here.
(Youngjoon: Take a seat anywhere.)
It seems there are only seats on the two sides.
(Finally,
all six men are here)
Really? We wanted to separate you two delibrately.
(Finally,
all six men are here)
(Minseon: They're pretty tall and attractive.)
(Minseon: I think we can change the atmosphere of the four of us very quickly.)
(Minseon: That's what I thought after seeing Jaeseung.)
(Seungjin: I think he's the closest to my ideal type's appearance.)
(Jaeseung: Then it's the six of us, right?
Youngjoon: Yes, for now.)
(Seungjin: Does that mean we can check the envelope?)
(Youngjoon: Let's start with introducing ourselves.)
-Let's introduce ourselves.
-Okay.
(Youngjoon: Let's start with introducing ourselves.)
(Jaeseung: My name is Cha Jaeseung.)
Jaeseung. Is it "ae"?
Yes.
Cha Jaeseung. Jaeseung.
(Youngjoon: I'm Son Youngjoon.)
-Son Youngjoon. -Yes.
(Hwi: My name is Kim Hwi. It's one character.)
Kim Hwi.
(Jaeseung: From the visuals, he's someone that I felt)
(Jaeseung: the most attracted to. Based on his looks.)
(Seungjin: I'm Kim Seungjin.)
Kim Seungjin.
(Minseon: I'm Hwang Minseon.)
Hwang Minseon.
(Seongmin: I'm Bae Seongmin.)
-Seongmin.
-Yes, I'm Bae Seongmin.
(Seongmin: I'm Bae Seongmin.)
(Youngjoon: Seongmin...)
-Seongmin.
-Yes, I'm Bae Seongmin.
(Youngjoon: Seongmin...)
Nice to meet you.
(Youngjoon: Seongmin is the first one to attract my attention.)
(Youngjoon: He has a calm and quiet vibe.)
(Youngjoon: Because of that vibe,
(Youngjoon: I was attracted by Seongmin first.)
(The heart fluttering first meeting, first feelings)
(The six men have moved in)
(Men's House)
(Seungjin: Shall we look at the envelope?)
Okay, how?
(Youngjoon: Let me open it.)
(Youngjoon: I think it's about the room assignment.)
(Minseon: The moment we are looking forward to.)
You're right.
Gosh!
(Youngjoon: Please choose your room and roommate as you wish.)
(Please choose your room and roommate as you wish.)
(Third floor (single room))
(Second floor (double room) (single room))
(First floor (double room))
(The situation where they have to pick their room and roommate)
-Who wants a single room then?
-Who wants a single room?
(Please choose your room and roommate as you wish.)
(Third floor (single room))
(Second floor (double room) (single room))
(First floor (double room))
(The situation where they have to pick their room and roommate)
(Minseon: Who wants a single room?)
-Who wants a single room then?
-Who wants a single room?
(Seungjin: Me.
Youngjoon: Seungjin.)
(Youngjoon: Who wants the single room?)
(Seongmin: I think it's better to live in a double room.)
-A double room.
(Jaeseung: Me too, a double room.)
-It looks like there will be a fight for double rooms.
-Me too.
(Jaeseung: Me too, a double room.)
(Youngjoon: It looks like there will be a fight for double rooms.)
-It looks like there will be a fight for double rooms.
-Me too.
(The only person who likes the single room, Seungjin,
gets the right to pick the room first)
(Happy)
Do you want the third or second floor?
(The only person who likes the single room, Seungjin,
gets the right to pick the room first)
(Happy)
Are you going to live completely alone on the third floor?
(The only person who likes the single room, Seungjin,
gets the right to pick the room first)
(Happy)
Are you going to live completely alone on the third floor?
I'll choose the third floor.
(Seungjin who will be staying in the third floor's single room)
I was already...
(Seungjin: I was already in the state where I am sure that I want to stay in a single room.)
(Seungjin: So I don't think I really need a roommate now.)
(Jaeseung: Who shall stay in the remaining single room?
Minseon: That is the problem.)
(Minseon: Then it's the roommates for the double rooms.)
That's right.
(The men who are trying to read the room)
(Looking away)
-Well.
-We shall.
(Jaeseung: I'll take the single room.)
-Well.
-We shall.
(Jaeseung: I'll take the single room.)
Really?
(Jaeseung gives up the double room for everyone)
(Jaeseung: It's a situation where someone has to make a decision for it to move.)
(Jaeseung: Though it's not what I really want, I thought I should just take the single room.)
(Jaeseung: I think it's fine living in the single room.)
-So I'll go to a single room.
-Are you sure you won't regret it?
(Jaeseung: I think it's fine living in the single room.)
-So I'll go to a single room.
-Are you sure you won't regret it?
(Youngjoon: Are you sure you won't regret it?)
-So I'll go to a single room.
-Are you sure you won't regret it?
-No.
-Regret...
(Youngjoon: Are you sure you won't regret it?)
-So I'll go to a single room.
-Are you sure you won't regret it?
-No.
-Regret...
(Jaeseung: Should I regret...)
-No.
-Regret...
(Jaeseung: Should I regret...)
-Come and hang out.
-Okay.
(Jaeseung: Should I regret...)
(Youngjoon: Come and hang out.
Jaeseung: Okay.)
-Come and hang out.
-Okay.
(Youngjoon: Come and hang out.
Jaeseung: Okay.)
Second floor. I will go with the second floor's single room.
(Jaeseung: I will go with the second floor's single room.)
(Minseon: I'm just human.)
(Minseon: I want to be roommates with someone I have taken a liking to.)
(Minseon: So I just felt it was a pity.)
So the four of us have to choose our roommates.
(Youngjoon: The four of us (Youngjoon & Seongmin & Hwi & Minseon) have to choose our roommate.)
(Youngjoon: Can you decide for us?)
-It's so funny.
-You two should discuss.
(Youngjoon: Can you decide for us?)
(Youngjoon: The two of you (Jaeseung, Seungjin) discuss.
Seongmin: Not a bad idea to decide for us.)
-It's so funny.
-You two should discuss.
Can you two decide for us?
(Youngjoon: The two of you (Jaeseung, Seungjin) discuss.
Seongmin: Not a bad idea to decide for us.)
Not a bad idea to decide for us.
(Youngjoon: The two of you (Jaeseung, Seungjin) discuss.
Seongmin: Not a bad idea to decide for us.)
What do you think?
(Youngjoon: The two of you (Jaeseung, Seungjin) discuss.
Seongmin: Not a bad idea to decide for us.)
You two discuss it.
(Deciding on having t hose in the single room to decide the roommates)
I think it's good.
-Really? Switch seats with me.
-Okay.
(Deciding on having t hose in the single room to decide the roommates)
(Minseon: First and second floor aside. Just pick our roommates for us.)
-Really? Switch seats with me.
-Okay.
(Deciding on having t hose in the single room to decide the roommates)
(Minseon: First and second floor aside. Just pick our roommates for us.)
-Yes roommates.
-Roommates.
(Minseon: First and second floor aside. Just pick our roommates for us.)
(Youngjoon: Then we will decide first and second floor.
Minseon: Okay, we will decide on first and second floor.)
(Jaeseung: What do you think?)
(Looking out)
At first...
Those two in the blue t-shirts. Like this.
(Seungjin: Those two in the blue t-shirts (Youngjoon & Minseon). Like this.)
(Youngjoon & Minseon who are in blue shirts)
The two in blue.
(Thinking)
(Jaeseung: In my mind, the person whom I'm attracted to most)
(Jaeseung: is firstly Hwi, and also Seungmin. These two people.)
(Jaeseung: In that case, I've made the decision.)
You made the decision?
(Jaeseung: Given my standards,)
(Jaeseung: these two people look quite similar.)
(Nod) (Nod)
(Jaeseung: That's the standard I made the decision on.)
(Jaeseung: Hwi and Seongmin.)
(Jaeseung: You two can share a room.)
-Okay. Then Youngjoon and I...
-The two of us.
(Jaeseung: You two can share a room.)
(Minseon: Then me and Youngjoon.
-Okay. Then Youngjoon and I...
-The two of us.
(Minseon: Then me and Youngjoon.
(Jaeseung: Between those who are similar attract)
(Jaeseung: and opposites attract,)
(Jaeseung: I believe in the latter more.)
So that's why I put them together on purpose.
(Jaeseung: So that's why I put them together on purpose.)
Because we couldn't decide,
(Hwi: Because we couldn't decide (on a roommate),)
(Hwi: so Jaeseung made a random decision for us.)
Because we couldn't decide,
(Hwi: Because we couldn't decide (on a roommate),)
(Hwi: so Jaeseung made a random decision for us.)
(Hwi: I was really happy about that.)
(Hwi: He has a good physique and is handsome too.)
(Hwi: I think Seongmin places first when it comes to first impressions.)
(Youngjoon: Since we've chosen a room. Shall we take a look around the rooms?)
-Okay
-Okay, let's go.
(Youngjoon: Since we've chosen a room. Shall we take a look around the rooms?)
-The phone.
-Should we go to the third floor first?
(Seungjin: Should we go to the third floor first?) Youngjoon Actually I'm most curious about that side
-The phone.
-Should we go to the third floor first?
Actually, I'm most curious about that place.
(Seungjin: Should we go to the third floor first?) Youngjoon Actually I'm most curious about that side
(Minseon: Shall we go to the first floor then?)
-The entertainment room.
-The entertainment room. I look forward to that the most.
(Minseon: Shall we go to the first floor then?)
-The entertainment room.
-The entertainment room. I look forward to that the most.
(Going to the most anticipated entertainment first)
Amazing.
-This place is really amazing.
-It's really amazing.
(Going to the most anticipated entertainment first)
Great.
-It's so...
-It's rattan vibes.
(Wow)
-It's so...
-It's rattan vibes.
(Seongmin:It's rattan vibes.)
-It's so...
-It's rattan vibes.
(Seongmin:It's rattan vibes.)
(The entertainment room that suits summer)
(Oh? There's a doll catcher?)
There's a doll catcher?
-Once a day.
-Love.
(Seungjin: Check your luck once a day.)
-Once a day.
-Love.
(Seungjin: Check your luck once a day.)
It's love luck.
Check your luck once a day.
(Youngjoon: Check your luck once a day.)
(A daily love luck doll catcher)
(Jaeseung: Let's go look at the swimming pool.)
-Really?
-Can we wear these slippers out?
(Jaeseung: Let's go look at the swimming pool.)
(A swimming pool that can drive away the summer)
(The men getting excited when thinking about swimming)
-Then we can play for a while before taking a shower.
-Sounds good.
(The men getting excited when thinking about swimming)
Sounds good to me too.
(Jaeseung: Is it cool?
Youngjoon It's cool, just right.)
(Youngjoon: We can play during the day when it's hot.
Minseon: It'll be more fun to play here at night, though?)
(After visiting the first floor of Men's House...)
But it's really hot
(Youngjoon: Shall we move our luggage up?)
Let's start moving our luggage.
(Youngjoon: It'll take a while to unpack.)
(His Man 3)
(1. You can only use Men's House exclusive phone.
You can't share your SNS or contact information with each other.
2. You can't share anything except your name before the set time.
3. You can't change your roommate at will.
4. You can only talk on the phone to convey your feelings for 30 seconds every day.
5. You can only check your love fortune once a day.)
(Third floor single room)
(Second floor double room)
(Second floor single room)
(First floor double room)
(Seongmin: I'm looking forward to how the dates will turn out.
Hwi: Right?)
(Seongmin & Hwi who are unpacking their luggage in the room)
-I just hope that it's not that hot.
-Right.
(Seongmin & Hwi who are unpacking their luggage in the room)
(Seongmin: What did you say your ideal date would be?)
(Hwi: I hope it's a one-day class.)
(Seongmin: It'll be fun. One-day class.)
(Seongmin: I said museum.
Hwi: Oh, you like museums?)
(Seongmin: Yeah, I wanted to go to one.)
(Hwi: I like going to exhibits, Seongmin: Really?)
-Do you like MMCA?
-I go to MMCA really often.
(Hwi: I like going to exhibits, Seongmin: Really?)
(Seongmin: Do you like MMCA?
Hwi: I go to MMCA really often. Leeum Museum of Art too.)
-Do you like MMCA?
-I go to MMCA really often.
Leeum Museum of Art too.
(Seongmin: Do you like MMCA?
Hwi: I go to MMCA really often. Leeum Museum of Art too.)
(Seongmin: As for Leeum Museum of Art, I could never get a reservation so I have never been.
Hwi: Is that so?)
(Seongmin: It's nice to go there with your lover.)
-Yes, it's good for taking photos.
-Yes.
(Seongmin: It's nice to go there with your lover.)
(Seongmin: It's nice to go there with your lover.
Hwi: Yes, it's good for taking photos.)
-Yes, it's good for taking photos.
-Yes.
(Seongmin: It's nice to go there with your lover.
Hwi: Yes, it's good for taking photos.)
(Hwi: We seem to get along well.)
(Hwi: Be it in both literature and art, we both have something in common.)
(Seongmin: I'm very satisfied.)
(Seongmin: We communicate well. Yes.)
(First floor double room
Hwi and Seongmin who are getting close with each other quickly as they talk about their hobbies)
(Third floor single room
Seungjin's room)
(Seungjin: I like my room the most.)
(Seungjin: It's an individual space that is only used by me, so I liked that a lot.)
But because the ceiling is too low, I often hit my head.
(Bang!)
(Seungjin: But because the ceiling is too low, I often hit my head.)
But because the ceiling is too low, I often hit my head.
(Seungjin who's organizing the dresser)
(Seungjin: I'm quite sensitive towards the body wash I use and scents.)
(Spray)
(Seungjin: So as soon as I went in,)
So as soon as I went in...
(Spray)
(Seungjin: So as soon as I went in,)
(Seungjin: I sprayed a lot of the scents I like.)
I can smell nice scents every time I enter,
(Seungjin: I can smell nice scents every time I enter (my room), so it feels good.)
so it feels good.
(Second floor double room
Youngjoon & Minseon's room)
If I'm done first, I'll help you.
(Second floor double room
Youngjoon & Minseon's room)
I'm almost done.
(Second floor double room
Youngjoon & Minseon's room)
-Are you good at cooking?
-Me?
(Youngjoon: Are you good at cooking?)
-Are you good at cooking?
-Me?
(Youngjoon: Are you good at cooking?)
I can cook fine for one to two servings.
(Minseon: I can cook fine for one to two servings.)
I really can't do big portions.
I can cook fine for one to two servings.
Use these two.
(Minseon: Use these two (hangers).
Youngjoon: Thank you.)
Use these two.
(Minseon: Use these two (hangers).
Youngjoon: Thank you.)
Thank you.
(Minseon: Use these two (hangers).
Youngjoon: Thank you.)
(Hwi who got changed)
You got changed?
(Hwi: I changed into comfortable clothes
Seongmin: Yes, that's great. It's not bad.)
Did you change your pants too?
(Hwi: I changed into comfortable clothes
Seongmin: Yes, that's great. It's not bad.)
(Seongmin: Did you change your pants too? It's the same?)
Did you change your pants too?
-I didn't change my pants.
-It's the same?
(Seongmin: Did you change your pants too? It's the same?)
(Hwi: You've changed.
Jaeseung: I'm bored.)
(Hwi: Come hang out.)
(Jaeseung: Hwi and Seongmin are people I'm interested in,)
(Jaeseung: so I came down cause I want to talk to them.)
(Jaeseung: That outfit looks nice.
Hwi: Oh. Is it okay?)
(Hwi: I was afraid it might look too casual.
Jaeseung: It looks good. I'm very casual right now.)
(Jaeseung: My clothes are very casual.)
(It looks like Jaeseung left the room, but he walks back again)
(Jaeseung: Looking at the two of them together, it looks like they suit each other very well.)
(Jaeseung: I'm a bit jealous. But it's not like I can't swoop in to steal them.)
It can't be helped.
(Sad)
(Jaeseung: It can't be helped.)
It can't be helped.
(Sad)
(Jaeseung: It can't be helped.)
(After unpacking...)
(Youngjoon: Is everyone hungry?)
Is everyone hungry?
Yes.
(Youngjoon: Is everyone hungry?)
-Very hungry.
-Really?
(Youngjoon: Is everyone hungry?)
(Youngjoon: Shall we make dinner earlier?)
(Hwi: What time is it?
Seongmin: 4 p.m.)
(Youngjoon: I plan on cooking tonight.
Seongmin: Really? That's amazing.)
I'm looking forward to it.
(Youngjoon: I plan on cooking tonight.
Seongmin: Really? That's amazing.)
I'm looking forward to it.
(Looking forward to it)
Don't get your hopes up.
(Seongmin: What are you going to cook?)
(Youngjoon: Do you like western food
Seongmin: I like western food.)
(Youngjoon: I'm going to make pasta and risotto.
Seongmin: Wow, amazing.)
-Do you know how to cook?
-Why?
(Youngjoon: I'm going to make pasta and risotto.
Seongmin: Wow, amazing.)
(What's with that expression?
Seungjin, what's wrong?)
-Do you know how to cook?
-Why?
What's with that expression?
Seungjin, what's wrong?
(What's with that expression?
Seungjin, what's wrong?)
(I think it must be delicious)
What's with that expression?
Seungjin, what's wrong?
(What's with that expression?
Seungjin, what's wrong?)
(I think it must be delicious)
Why did you go away with your back facing me?
(Youngjoon: It's a way to ease the awkward atmosphere)
(Youngjoon: of the first day.)
(Youngjoon: I thought I'd better cook first.)
(Men's House's first chef is Youngjoon)
He said he would cook dinner.
Really?
(Men's House's first chef is Youngjoon)
I'll cook today.
(Youngjoon: If you all watch here I'll be under a lot of pressure.)
(Men's House's first chef is Youngjoon)
Go and relax
(Youngjoon: If you all watch here I'll be under a lot of pressure.)
(Leaving)
Go and relax
and come again when you're board.
(Leaving)
It's so funny.
I need to learn how to use this induction stove.
(Stressed)
(Minseon: We all came to sit on the sofa.)
Right?
(Jaeseung: What did you talk about?)
(Minseon: When the four of us were at the cafe?)
(Minseon: We talked about our ideal type and...)
(Minseon: the criteria we value in our lover?)
(Seungjin: You have a good memory.)
(Seungjin: I've forgot it all.)
(Jaeseung: I feel like I can't really remember what I talked about.)
(Seongmin: I don't really remember it.)
(Jaeseung: It's the first day. So...)
(Youngjoon is fighting alone in the kitchen)
(Staring)
Is he here?
(Seungjin: Should I go help?)
(Seungjin: I think (Youngjoon) is someone who takes initiative a lot.)
(Seungjin: That was the first impression I had.)
(Seungjin: Because he volunteered to cook dinner, so I went over to help him.)
(Youngjoon: Seungjin said he was shy with strangers.)
(Youngjoon: But even so, he took the initiative to come over and help me)
(Youngjoon: so I was surprised.)
(Seungjin: Should I cut these up first? The garlic and onions?
Youngjoon: It'd be great if you could do that.)
(Youngjoon: Help me slice them up.)
(Seungjin washes onions first)
(Youngjoon: Does everyone eat a lot?)
(Seungjin: After all, we all haven't had a full meal yet,)
(Seungjin: we might not be able to eat much.)
(Can I help you?)
(Youngjoon: Not yet. It's just the beginning.)
((Who's here?))
(Youngjoon: I'm still getting familiar with the kitchen.)
(Trash bag?)
(Youngjoon who's still exploring the kitchen)
That's is the most important.
(Trash bag?)
(Youngjoon who's still exploring the kitchen)
Trash bag?
(Trash bag?)
(Youngjoon who's still exploring the kitchen)
(Minseon: Trash bag? Let me find it for you.)
(Minseon: It's our first day here. We don't know where the everything is.)
(Minseon: And he has to cook a huge portion for six.)
(Minseon: If I don't help,)
(Minseon: it's the middle of summer, he will definitely be covered in sweat. That's what I thought.)
(Minseon: I thought, "I must go help" so I came over.)
(Youngjoon: There's something I need your help in.
Minseon: What is it?)
Very sincerely...
(Youngjoon: There's something I need your help in.
Minseon: What is it?)
(Youngjoon: Very sincerely... Minseon: Just stir it?)
Very sincerely...
-Just stir it?
-Yes.
(Youngjoon: Very sincerely... Minseon: Just stir it?)
(Youngjoon: Just stir it slowly. To prevent it from sticking to the pot.)
(It's like a witch's spoon (?))
(A witch's potion(?))
The steps of making potion.
(Working hard)
(Endless time of stirring the cream...)
(Youngjoon: Are you bored?
Minseon: No. It's okay. It's not that bad.)
This requires patience and causes suffering the most.
(Cream sauce that requires patience and suffering)
(Chop chop chop)
(Youngjoon's knife skills)
(Seungjin joins to cut the vegetables.
(Sizzle)
(Beside two busy men...)
(Minseon is still enduring and suffering)
(The three men who found the room layout)
Here.
There's a layout.
(The three men who found the room layout)
(Jaeseung fills up the names of the roommates)
(Seongmin: Your handwriting is so cute. It looks like a font.)
(Hwi: Who lives in a double room on the second floor?)
(Seongmin: I want to write my name on the blackboard. So I wrote it.)
Along the way, I'm also revising the names of the people who are here.
(Jaeseung: Along the way, I'm also revising the names of the people who are here.)
(Jaeseung: And I wrote them down.)
And I wrote them down.
(Roommate)
(First floor double room: Hwi, Seongmin
Second floor single room: Jaeseung\MSecond floor double room: Youngjoon & Minseon
Third floor single room: Seungjin)
(Done filling it in)
(Hwi: Now, for in the room...
Jaeseung: Oh right. So we have to write it in the room too?)
(Jaeseung: We can just write the ones in our rooms ourselves, right?)
(Second floor single room
Jaeseung goes towards his own room)
(Single room
Jaeseung)
(Clear)
(Should I write it or not?)
(Jaeseung also wrote down names for the other rooms' door signs)
(Jaeseung: The door looks empty.)
(Jaeseung: So it felt a bit weird.)
(Double room
Youngjoon, Minseon)
(Jaeseung: I've wrote it all for the second floor. I think I'll be scolded.)
(Wow, you wrote so well)
Hwi is good at drawing.
(Double room
Seongmin, Hwi)
(Seongmin: Hwi is good at drawing.)
Hwi is good at drawing.
He would even decorate it with doodles.
(Double room
Seongmin, Hwi)
(Seongmin: Hwi is good at drawing.)
Hwi is good at drawing.
(Double room
Seongmin, Hui)
(Seongmin: He would even decorate it with doodles.)
He would even decorate it with doodles.
(Double room
Seongmin, Hui)
(Seongmin: He would even decorate it with doodles.)
(So cute)
(Jaeseung: Are you talking about what you wrote?)
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Hwi completes the door plate of the first floor double room with his own vibes)
Let's go draw mine.
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Hwi completes the door plate of the first floor double room with his own vibes)
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Hwi completes the door plate of the first floor double room with his own vibes)
Let's go.
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Hwi completes the door plate of the first floor double room with his own vibes)
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Hwi completes the door plate of the first floor double room with his own vibes)
(Oh! That's so cute)
Please add to it.
(SOS
Please add to it)
Please add to it.
(SOS
Please add to it)
-Should I draw you grass. Like ours?
-Okay.
(SOS
Please add to it)
(Should I draw you grass?)
-Should I draw you grass. Like ours?
-Okay.
(Jaeseung: I wrote my name, but it didn't look very pretty.)
(Jaeseung: So I asked (Hwi) to make it nicer.)
(Single room
Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: Yes, I like it.)
Yes, I like it.
(Single room
Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: Yes, I like it.)
His drawing leaves room for imagination.
(Single room
Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: His drawing leaves room for imagination.)
His drawing leaves room for imagination.
(Single room
Jaeseung)
(Jaeseung: His drawing leaves room for imagination.)
It's a double room, so make it bigger.
(The door plate boys who are wandering around looking for door plates)
(Seongmin: They were almost all drawn by Hwi.)
(Double room
Youngjoon, Minseon)
(Hwi: The door sign of other rooms is like)
(Single room
Jaeseung, Hwi)
(Hwi: I drew them without thinking much about it.)
I drew them without thinking much about it.
(Single room
Jaeseung, Hwi)
(Hwi: I drew them without thinking much about it.)
(Hwi: I put the most effort for Seongmin and my room.)
(Hwi: Actually, I wanted to draw a heart.)
(Shy)
(Hwi: But I just drew a butterfly.)
(Double room
Hwi, Seongmin)
(Can the butterflies become hearts?)
(What are you guys doing?)
-You look busy.
-Yeah.
(What are you guys doing?)
(Youngjoon: You seem busy.)
-You look busy.
-Yeah.
(Jaeseung: Actually, we're not that busy.)
Are you leaving us out?
(Joking)
(Youngjoon: Are you leaving us out?)
Are you leaving us out?
(Joking)
(Youngjoon: Are you leaving us out?)
We are hanging out in threes now? That can happen.
(Joking)
(Youngjoon: Are you leaving us out?)
Can I help you?
(The panicking door plate boys)
No.
Just the three of you?
(Startled)
I got a shock.
((My goodness, that scared me...))
It's okay. It's because there's water inside.
(Youngjoon: It's because there's water inside.)
((My goodness, that scared me...))
(Youngjoon: The pot is too hot.)
(Seungjin: Is the fire turned off?
Youngjoon: I turned it off. I wanted to cool it down for a while.)
(Jaeseung takes a polaroid)
Okay, take a picture for him
(Youngjoon: If I put it in the pot now, it'll splash badly. Don't be surprised.)
Okay. Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Youngjoon: If I put it in the pot now, it'll splash badly. Don't be surprised.)
(Seongmin and Hwi hold hands gently)
I'm sorry.
(Hwi: Seongmin and my hand touched gently.)
(My heart fluttered)
(Shy)
If it splashes...
(Youngjoon who continues to cook skillfully)
(Trembling)
(We are all cowards)
(Youngjoon: It's not a big deal. Don't you think you're wasting the polaroid?)
-It's okay.
-It's the best now.
(Youngjoon: It's not a big deal. Don't you think you're wasting the polaroid?)
(It's okay)
-It's okay.
-It's the best now.
(It's okay)
(Looking straight)
(Minseon: If I weren't helping Youngjoon cook,)
If I weren't helping Youngjoon cook,
(Looking straight)
(Minseon: If I weren't helping Youngjoon cook,)
If I weren't helping Youngjoon cook,
(Minseon: and I were with the other three, Seongmin, Hwi, and Jaeseung...)
Minseon: 'What would it be like if I were there?'
Minseon: 'What would they talk about?' That's what I'm curious about.
Youngjoon: Can someone help me set the table?
Youngjoon: There's a placemat in the drawer
Youngjoon: I put jalapeños and olive oil in the freezer.
(Following the chef's instructions)
(Can't open the lid)
I'll do it.
-Jaeseung: I'll do it. -Seongmin: But this really won't open.
Seongmin: Try it.
Jaeseung: Since you're saying that, if I can't open it it'll be...
Seongmin: It really won't open
Seongmin: Oh?!
Seongmin: It won't open, right?
Seongmin: It really won't open.
(Trembling)
Is the olive oil in there?
(Finally opens)
Did you open it?
Yeah, but it splashed all over my clothes.
(Finally opens)
-I need a plate. -Sorry.
Yeah, but it splashed all over my clothes.
I know, right?
(Worried)
What should I do?
Wait, can I wipe it with this?
(Peeping)
Wait, I'll get you some wet tissues.
(Do you have wet tissues?)
This is bad. It smells sour.
(Going to the kitchen to get paper towels after hearing what Seongmin said)
(Seongmin going to find wet tissues himself.)
I need water.
(Sorry)
I was afraid that something like this would happen
so I wanted to wear an apron.
(Sorry)
It's okay.
Why won't it come out?
(Just like that, the six men's first dinner is ready.)
Minseon: Good job everyone.
Good job everyone.
Jaeseung: Let's eat everyone.
(Cheers)
The food looks great.
(Nice to meet you.)
(Cheers)
-Nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
(Nice to meet you.)
-Let's get along well. -Let's get along well.
(Let's get along well this week)
(The first meal the six men are sharing at the house)
Youngjoon: I'm nervous because I haven't cooked in a while.
It smells good.
(Takes a big bite)
(Nodding)
This risotto isn't spicy, but this one is.
Minseon: This risotto is really good.
-I don't usually eat risottos. -The olive oil smells delicious.
I like spicy food.
(Serious Foodie)
The appearance looks like something you see on delivery apps.
(A delicious appearance like the ones seen on delivery apps)
Are you sure this is a compliment?
No, what I mean is...
It's totally a compliment!
It's like the one's sold outside
Seongmin: It's like a takeout that costs 32,000 won for a bowl.
I would order it.
(Everyone is satisfied with Youngjoon's cooking)
Each bowl.
Seongmin: You can confidently tell others that you can cook.
Youngjoon: It's not that I'm confident, I just enjoy cooking.
Youngjoon: I like cooking for my friends.
Seongmin: When you cook for your friends, it makes you happy when they enjoy the food, right?
Yeah.
Youngjoon: I like home parties.
Seongmin: I think I can guess your MBTI.
ENFJ.
You guessed all wrong earlier, but you got it right this time.
(You got all the others wrong, but you got mine right)
I'm right, right?
Youngjoon: Then out of the six of us, I'm the only J?
Youngjoon: And only Seungjin is I?
Seungjin: Am I the only I? -What are you?
I'm INTP.
(What are you? I'm INTP)
-Really? -Yes.
One I, one S, and one J.
(Seungjin is I, Jaeseung is S, Youngjoon is J)
Seungjin: This is bad...
Seungjin: How is it that there are six of us,
Seungjin: but I'm the only introvert?
Jaeseung: Are you really all NF?
(Minseon suddenly leaves his seat)
I'm half ENFP and ENTP.
(Minseon casually brings wet tissues)
ENFP and TP.
Wait, tissues...
(Minseon casually brings wet tissues)
Hwi: Wait, tissue...
I'm the only J among the six.
(Minseon looks after Jaeseung)
I'm an S.
I'm so happy.
(Minseon looks after Jaeseung)
I'm an S.
I'm so happy.
Hwi: You got something on your mouth.
Am I the only I?
What are you?
Hwi: You got something on your mouth.
Minseon: I feel like I care,
What are you?
Hwi: You got something on your mouth.
Minseon: I feel like I care,
Minseon: But I'm not sure if it's an attachment.
It's E, right? Or is it I?
E.
There's only one I.
(Embarrassed)
(Hwi and Jaeseung)
Hwi and Jaeseung
'Isn't there something going on between them?' Was what I thought.
Seongmin: Just a hunch?
Jaeseung: Since we're done, let's clean up.
Should we clean up?
-I'm so full. -What should I do?
Jaeseung: Since we're done, let's clean up.
-Wash the dishes. -The dishes...
The three of us will do the dishes.
(Seongmin, Hui, Jaeseung will do the dishes)
I'll do it.
Okay.
(Seongmin, Hui, Jaeseung will do the dishes)
-I ate well. -Take it to the front please.
(They became closer during dinner time)
I found a bag earlier.
(Cleaning quickly)
(Thinking)
Seongmin: I feel like I'm slowly getting more relaxed.
-Jaeseung: I feel like it's important to get familiar with the faces first. -Seongmin: Right.
When it's my turn to prepare, you have to help me.
(Jaeseung: When it's my turn to prepare, you have to help me.
Seongmin. Of course, we're a group of three.)
When it's my turn to prepare, you have to help me.
Of course, we're a group of three.
(Jaeseung: When it's my turn to prepare, you have to help me.
Seongmin. Of course, we're a group of three.)
(A glance)
I can't do it alone.
(Seongmin and Jaeseung are having fun while washing the dishes)
Hwi: I was washing the dishes behind them
Hwi: and I saw Jaeseung and Seongmin cleaning together
Hwi: and thought that the atmosphere was great
Hwi: so I was a little sad.
Youngjoon: Did someone write my name wrong?
Youngjoon: Why did it become like this?
-Right. -Who wrote it?
(Youngjoon: I was busy cooking so I didn't get to write it even though I wanted to.
Minseon: I wanted to write it myself, too.)
I was busy cooking and didn't write it. I wanted to write it.
(Youngjoon: I was busy cooking so I didn't get to write it even though I wanted to.
Minseon: I wanted to write it myself, too.)
-I wanted to write it myself, too. -Right?
(Youngjoon: I was busy cooking so I didn't get to write it even though I wanted to.
Minseon: I wanted to write it myself, too.)
-Let's go find chalk. -Aren't there other colors?
(The men on the second floor want to rewrite their door signs)
There are many other chalks over there.
Look over there, it's well decorated.
(The men on the second floor want to rewrite their door signs)
What? So they made their signs pretty,
and just roughly made ours?
Youngjoon: I saw Jaeseung's room.
He decorated his room beautifully with many colors.
(Single room Jaeseung, Youngjoon)
Youngjoon: I'm thankful that they wrote it for us so I felt bad to erase it
but they made theirs so pretty
so of course we can't just sit here and do nothing.
Youngjoon: Of course not.
(Minseon: Youngjoon and I
said, "we can't lose! We need to decorate it well, too."
so we started decorating right away.)
(Youngjoon: We're making it more splendid. More than anyone else.)
Good!
(The splendid sign is complete) (Double room: Youngjoon, Minseon)
(After dinner, Seungjin is focused on the draw of love)
No!
(Sad) (The first challenge failed)
(What a pity)
Seungjin: Can I try it one more time?
(Serious Seungjin)
I really can't pick it up.
Seungjin: Is it really possible to pick it up..?
(Seung-jin: I became stubborn and thought "I'm going to pick one today".)
(Sigh)
(Failure+1)
I tried four times why can't I get it?
(He's talking about his failure)
-Draw your luck of love. -Love.
I tried four times why can't I get it?
(Draw the luck of love)
-Draw your luck of love. -Love.
You're not lucky today, are you?
(Draw the luck of love)
Seungjin: I'll try again.
Minseon: Oh you're not able to pick it up?
-Is it one draw per person? -Yeah.
(Trying to draw the luck of love again)
You have to pick up this one, right?
(Excited)
The yellow one on the inside.
Pick it, pick it, pick it.
I think it's working?
(Minseon succeeds in one try)
-What? -I got it!
Seungjin: So I was the problem.
What are you talking about?
Next player, let's go!
(Next player!)
(Seungjin's Nth challenge!)
Minseon: I'll read it.
"Someone who's different from what they seem like on the outside may appear. Be careful."
This isn't a good thing.
Minseon: I keep getting bothered by that after seeing it.
You need to raise it.
(Men are enthusiastic about drawing love fortune)
It's time.
Seungjin: This is impossible
Seriously.
Seungjin: I don't know how many times I've tried already.
Hwi: You couldn't get it out?
Seungjin: No, I couldn't.
No this...
-It's this one. -I think you can get this one.
Seungjin: No, I couldn't.
(The draw of love is hard)
-It's this one. -I think you can get this one.
But I can't.
(The draw of love is hard)
It's perfect right now.
No.
(The draw of love is hard)
This...
-I think you got it. -There's too much.
Oh, I think you got it.
Or not..?
No, this...
(No no)
I think it'll work this time.
It's working, it's working.
It's done.
-Why can't I pull it out? -Very good
(Feeling wronged)
"Take a step back and spend some time alone to observe him."
Youngjoon: Take a step back...
There's only one chance.
-It's so fun. -There's only one chance.
(A glance)
It's working, it's working.
(He seems to be looking for someone)
Or not..?
(Where is he looking?)
Jaeseung: How many times have you tried? -Youngjoon: Four? Five?
Jaeseung: So other than me someone else took one, too.
He looks cute.
He looks like a coach.
He's a management coach.
(Seongmin comes a bit late)
It'll be nice to gather them together.
(Notices Seongmin)
-What's this? -I don't think it'll work.
(Turns)
(Startled)
-What's this? -I don't think it'll work.
It seems to be &Rose.
(Startled)
-I think this is &Rose. -&Rose.
Stickers, stickers.
(Please!)
Let me draw one... I did it!
(Seungjin didn't give up. He finally got it!)
-I got it! I got it! -I'm so touched.
(Cute)
I got it. How do I take it out?
(Happy)
-I tried so hard... -You have to read it now.
(Seung-jin: I tried so hard, if I get something bad...)
If I get something bad...
Bad luck is more effective.
(Seung-jin: I tried so hard, if I get something bad...)
When I was alone,
"You're not on the right path."
(Unhappy)
(Fate of love: Check your luck once a day. Is your love fortune right?)
Jaeseung: Should we play an impression game?
(An impression game?)
-In Son Byungho mode? -Son Byungho.
This should be fun~
Youngjoon: You start first.
(Jaeseung starts first!)
Like this?
Youngjoon: You start first.
-Clockwise? -Okay.
Who do you think is the oldest here?
(Q. Who do you think is the oldest?)
Youngjoon: The oldest person here?
Young-joon Why are you asking so carefully?
Jaeseung: Someone who looks the oldest here.
-Everyone looks young. -The oldest...
Hwi: But let's promise whoever gets picked won't get hurt.
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
(Jaeseung: Okay. Okay.)
One, two, three.
Okay. Okay.
Why aren't you pointing?
(The finger is lost)
Why aren't you pointing? You have to point.
(Chooses Jaeseung)
I chose.
Because...
(Chooses Jaeseung)
he seems really mature.
- Oh, really? -Three votes.
(Trying to calm down)
Three votes,
(Jaeseung 3 votes, Minseon 2 votes, Youngjoon 1 vote)
two votes, and one vote for me.
Jaeseung: I asked the question and I got picked.
I remember.
It's similar.
I...
(This is too much)
I got picked.
Jaeseung: I got more votes than I thought.
Jaeseung: The senior...
I think I exploded.
Jaeseung: I want to hear the reason.
Well...
Because I look old?
No, what are you talking about?
(Let's move on)
Do you have a reason?
Minseon: Yeah, there's a reason why I chose Youngjoon.
Why?
Minseon: I think he makes a decision after making lots of mistakes.
(It makes sense.)
But rather than making decisions
based on mistakes
it's more like because his MBTI is J, right?
-But compared to that... -I've never made mistakes. I'm always perfect.
(Youngjoon: I'm always perfect)
(Youngjoon: I make perfect plans because I don't want it to fail.)
So cool.
(Respect)
Jaeseung: The reason I chose him is...
(Jaeseung chose Minseon as the oldest)
I noticed that...
(Jaeseung: Even if no one asked,)
He's always the first to step up and help. -Right.
(Jaeseung: He's always the first to step up and help)
So I saw his kindness.
(Applauding)
So I think that's why I think he's older.
Minseon: I'm so curious about everyone's age.
I really want to know.
Youngjoon: Everyone looks young.
Minseon: Yeah, everyone looks young.
(Minseon: I've always heard other's say that about me,)
(Minseon: so I'm not upset.)
(Minseon: I kind of just thought "that's right".)
(Minseon: I've already accepted it.)
I want to ask something interesting.
(Playful)
-No, but... -His expression is so cheeky.
(His expression is so cheeky)
His expression is so cheeky.
(Youngjoon: If I'm in a double room,)
aside from those who are my roommates,
who would want to be my roommate?
(Q. Other than my current roommates, who would want to be my roommate?)
Excluding my roommate?
Yeah, excluding your current roommates.
(Q. Other than my current roommates, who would want to be my roommate?)
-It's a bit unexpected. -Wow, so cruel.
(Wow, so cruel)
(Scared)
(A little hesitant)
(Youngjoon: I did it on purpose. I wanted to know how other's are feeling,)
(Youngjoon: that's why I asked that question.)
One, two, three.
(Jaeseung 2, Youngjoon 2, Minseon 1, Seongmin 1)
I got two votes, right?
(Jaeseung and Minseon chose each other)
Did you choose Minseon?
Yeah.
(Jaeseung and Minseon chose each other)
-Jaeseung: I think I'd get along well with him. -Minseon: Oh, me too!
(Minseon: Oh, me too!)
Jaeseung: I feel like we'll get along well.
Should I change rooms with you?
You can't change your roommate.
(Minseon: I was happy)
(Minseon: The person I want to be roommates with
said we "get along" so I'm happy.)
(Jaeseung: Instead of sharing a room with someone I like,
I prefer living with someone I get along well with.)
What about you?
(Quietly)
(Seongmin chose Youngjoon)
What about you?
Seongmin: I feel like I'll feel calm and relaxed if I lived with him.
Really?
(Youngjoon: Seongmin chose me.)
(Youngjoon: That makes me happy. Really happy.)
Youngjoon: I also chose Seongmin.
Youngjoon: When we first met and were chatting on the sofa
he made me feel relaxed.
He's also a great listener so I'm really grateful.
I felt like we can get along well.
It's Seongmin's turn to ask.
The last question.
-The last question? -Yes, last one.
Q. Who do you think will receive the most calls today?
The one who will get the most calls?
(Flustered men)
(Hwi: Answering this question means we'll be showing who we like.)
(Thinking)
One, two, three.
One, two.
One.
One. One.
(Jaeseung 3; Seongmin, Hwi, Youngjoon gets 1 vote each.)
-Three votes. -He got three votes.
Three votes, one vote, one vote, one vote.
(Jaeseung 3; Seongmin, Hwi, Youngjoon gets 1 vote each.)
(Shy)
The atmosphere here is
all focused on him.
While playing the game
(Jaeseung gets the most votes for getting the most calls)
I thought he'll receive the most calls.
I think so, too.
(Jaeseung gets the most votes for getting the most calls)
I think he'll be popular.
(Seongmin: Jaeseung will be popular)
I was a bit sad to see him choose Jaeseung.
(Hwi is sad to see Seongmin choose Jaeseung)
(Shy)
Go jump in the water and come back later.
I wanted to say that, too.
Hwi: So the reason...
Minseon: I think many people
agree it's comfortable to be with Youngjoon.
Don't call me because you feel comfortable. Don't make me misunderstand.
Jaeseung: I chose Hwi
because of his eye smile?
I think that left a strong impression on me.
(Hwi: I was very happy.)
(Seongmin: I chose Hwi and Jaeseung
because I'm interested in them so I've been observing.
But they seem to like each other.)
Who else?
Hwi: I chose Seongmin.
I think he has a personality that everyone likes.
So...
(Thank you)
I think he has a personality that everyone likes.
I got praised,
(Thank you)
so I should work hard.
(Men subtly expressing their feelings)
I should praise you.
I should compliment him when I pick up the phone.
(Men subtly expressing their feelings)
I think he's showing his affection.
Jaeseung: I think Hwi is expressing his feelings to Seongmin.
(Jaeseung: I felt a bit conflicted.)
Minseon: I really don't know who's going to call who.
I really don't know.
It's even harder to know now.
It doesn't feel real right now.
Youngjoon: I'm not interested in who's going to call who.
I don't even know who I'll call.
It's cool at night.
What is it?
No way.
(The phone call session is about to start.
Please call someone you like and talk to them for 30 seconds.)
Finally, something.
(The phone call session is about to start.
Please call someone you like and talk to them for 30 seconds.)
Oh.
(The phone call session is about to start.
Please call someone you like and talk to them for 30 seconds.)
(Nervous)
(Search)
((Crying))
Let's all do it separately.
Okay, bye.
-Let's go. -Bye.
See you later.
Okay, bye.
I want to find a seat first.
Youngjoon: I want to find a seat first.
My phone is missing.
(The men heading to their own space)
-Did you lose your phone? -What did you send?
Where did it go?
(The men heading to their own space)
Hwi: Where... What are we supposed to do?
What did you get?
Hwi: What is the message?
Seongmin: It's time to call.
What should I do?
(The men's first call time)
To whom are their affections going to? (The first night: Where are the men's hearts heading towards?)
(Second-floor single room, Jaeseung's room)
I feel anxious and excited.
Jaeseung: I also have expectations. It's a complicated feeling.
(Third-floor single room, Seungjin's room)
Seungjin: Who should I call?
(Seungjin: I kept thinking about this.)
(Second-floor double room, Youngjoon & Minseon's room)
I haven't...
Youngjoon: Have you decided?
(Shaking his head)
Minseon: What should I do?
Minseon: I should have had a drink earlier.
(Minseon: Maybe I could have chosen faster that way.)
-Youngjoon: The power of alcohol. -Minseon: Yes, with the power of alcohol.
Youngjoon: I don't even have that kind of power.
-(Minseon: If I face everything sober...)
-(Youngjoon: Even if I drink, my head is clear and my body just feels sick.)
(Youngjoon: Should I go somewhere else?)
-Minseon: How? -Youngjoon: Privately.
Minseon: Where are you going?
-Youngjoon: Somewhere I can be alone. -Minseon: Really?
(If Youngjoon stays with Minseon)
If we're together...
(Youngjoon: I'm afraid that Minseon might call me,)
(Youngjoon: but then I won't call him,)
(Youngjoon: then it'll be really awkward,)
Youngjoon: so I left the room.
(In case something awkward happens, Youngjoon searches for a private space.)
Seongmin: Do you want to take a picture? Even though you look really tired.
Can I?
-Are you okay? -Yes.
Look at the camera from afar.
(V)
-Can I? -Yes.
One, two, three.
(One, two, three.)
(Seongmin: Let's take one more to show how worried we are)
Let's show our tension.
-Like this. -I must take it well.
(Tightly)
(One, two, three.)
(#Tension(?)_filled_two-shot_JPG)
Hwi: Do you like diffusers?
-Seongmin: This isn't mine. -Hwi: Oh, really?
-Seongmin: It was originally here. -Hwi: Oh so it was here in the first place.
-Hwi: I was going to say so earlier but I really like diffusers. -Seongmin: Really?
-Seongmin: You like fragrance. -Hwi: Yes, I like it when it smells nice.
Hwi: What kind of perfume do you like the most?
Seongmin: Lately...
(Seongmin: I used to like woody scents,)
Seongmin: but lately I like fresh and sweet scents.
Seongmin: Like the smell of a temple.
Seongmin: The fresh smell of a temple in summer.
-Hwi: Temples smell really nice. -Seongmin: Yes, I like that.
Seongmin: I like fresh summer scents.
Seongmin: What songs do you like?
Hwi: I'm not picky about the genre. I like them all.
-Seongmin: Really? -Hwi: I like Jannabi.
I really like Jannabi!
Hwi: I really like them all.
Awesome!
-Seongmin: I really like the distinct characteristics of Jannabi. -Hwi: Really?
Seongmin: From beginning to end, Jannabi
Seongmin: maintains the same emotions when releasing an album.
That's right.
Seongmin: I really respect that. It's so cool,
Seongmin: people who have strong emotions.
-Hwi: Every song is great. -Seongmin: That's right.
Seongmin: When I'm talking to someone
Seongmin: it's rare for me to feel comfortable.
Seongmin: But with Hwi, I think we get along well.
(The first person on the phone)
(Minseon, please come to the phone booth and call someone you like within 30 seconds.)
(Minseon, the first man, leaving calmly)
Minseon: What I thought about before heading out to call was to,
“face it honestly.”
That's the most important thing.
Minseon: My heart suddenly started to pound and I thought, "what should I do?"
Minseon: I walked into the phone booth with my heart pounding.
(Nervous)
(Who does Minseon have feelings for?)
(The signal is ringing through the speaker)
(Which man is Minseon's heart heading towards?)
-Hello? -Minseon: Hello, the guy who voted me as the senior.
(The person Minseon called is Jaeseung.)
Hello?
Minseon: Hello, the guy who voted me as the senior.
Jaeseung: Hello.
Jaeseung: Can you tell me?
What?
Jaeseung: Can you tell me who you are?
Jaeseung: Who... Who are you?
Minseon: I'm Minseon.
Jaeseung: Nice to meet you.
Minseon: Nice to meet you.
Jaeseung: Thank you for calling me.
Minseon: You're the only person
Minseon: who chose me as a senior, right?
-Jaeseung: Thank you for calling me. -Minseon: For what?
(The call ends after 30 seconds)
Minseon: Hello?
(Shy)
(Laughs out of joy)
Jaeseung: I wasn't expecting it.
Jaeseung: I was in an anxious state when I got a call from Minseon
Jaeseung: but the call made me feel better.
Minseon: Did it end?
(Pity)
Minseon: Is 30 seconds this short...?
Minseon: I didn't know 30 seconds was such a short time.
Minseon: So I thought I should have organized what I wanted to say beforehand.
Minseon: But the call itself was meaningful.
Minseon: I called with the intention of "wanting to know about him more."
(Youngjoon, please come to the phone booth and call someone you like within 30 seconds.)
Youngjoon: I actually already decided before heading out
Youngjoon: but on the way I was still choosing.
Youngjoon: Choosing between two people.
(Who are the two people Youngjoon's choosing?)
Youngjoon: The two people that I'm choosing between are
Youngjoon: Jaeseung, whom I haven't talked much to,
I'm Bae Seongmin.
Nice to meet you.
Youngjoon: and Seongmin.
(Pushes the button after thinking)
Reo.
(First-floor double room, Hwi & Seongmin's room)
Hwi: Roylla? Reo?
Russia!
Ah... Aria!
-Asia! (Laughing)
Asia.
Seongmin: Asia?
Seongmin: Wait... Aria, Asia...
(Hwi and Seongmin are waiting for calls while playing with words)
Let's sort out our thoughts.
Yeah, let's sort it out.
(Hwi and Seongmin are waiting for calls while playing with words)
Wait.
Seongmin: Hello?
Seongmin: Ah, yes...
(Youngjoon calls Seongmin)
Hello?
-Youngjoon: Can you tell who I am? -Seongmin: I'm not sure.
Who is it?
Youngjoon: You can't tell? Seongmin: Ah,
I know.
Youngjoon: Do you know now? -Seongmin: Yes.
(Staring)
Youngjoon: We didn't talk much today
Youngjoon: so I called you hoping I can get closer with you.
Seongmin: Ah, sure, thank you.
Okay.
(The call ends after 30 seconds.)
He hung up.
Youngjoon: "Let's get closer" was what I was thinking
so I thought I needed to call one of them.
(Youngjoon needed to call either Jaeseung or Seongmin)
Youngjoon: So I call Seongmin who made a great first impression.
-Seongmin: Did he hang up? -Hwi: He hung up.
Seongmin: He hung up? Ah...
-Seongmin: I actually don't know who that was. -Hwi: Really?
Seongmin: I couldn't tell.
Seongmin: I really don't know who that was.
-Hwi: He didn't tell you his name? -Seongmin: He didn't.
Seongmin: But he said we didn't talk much.
Seongmin: I don't know who it is.
I don't know who it is.
Hwi: I was a bit sad and worried.
Hwi: I found out that there's someone other than me who's interested in him.
(Hwi, please come to the phone booth and call someone you like within 30 seconds.)
I got a text.
Did you?
(Hwi, please come to the phone booth and call someone you like within 30 seconds.)
Seongmin: Even I'm nervous.
Seongmin: Go ahead.
(Nervous)
Hwi: I was so nervous.
Hwi: Even though I already decided who I want to call,
Hwi: I didn't know what I was going to say.
(What will Hwi say to express his feelings?)
Hello?
Hello.
I'm your roommate.
(Hwi's calls Seongmin)
Hello.
I'm your roommate.
(Hwi's calls Seongmin)
Yes.
Seongmin: I think I just saw him earlier.
Hwi: I don't know what to say...
From the first time we met till now, I always had a good feeling.
Seongmin: Ah... Thank you...
(Hwi mustered up his courage to express his feelings for the first time)
Hwi: I called Seongmin today.
Hwi: I wanted to express my feelings.
Hwi: I also had a great first impression of him.
Seongmin: Ah... How am I supposed to face him?
How should I face him?
Seongmin: What should I do... What should I do...
Seongmin: I was really surprised.
Seongmin: To be honest, I was really shy.
Seongmin: But I was really happy.
(Hwi comes back to the room after the call)
-Hwi: Hello. -Seongmin: Hello.
(Hiding under the blanket)
(Shy)
Hwi: Ah...
Hwi: I'm so nervous.
I'm just going to try to sleep.
Seongmin: Thank you for calling me.
Hwi: I was so nervous that I couldn't breathe.
Seongmin: I was so shy I couldn't even look at him.
Seongmin: I've never felt like that before in my life.
Hwi: Ah, this is so embarrassing.
Seongmin: I can't look directly at you.
Seongmin: I'm looking at you through that mirror.
(Seongmin's looking at Hwi through the mirror)
Seongmin: When's it my turn?
(Excitement and awkwardness coexists between the two men)
It's hot.
Seongmin: I'm so shy.
(Who is the next man to express his feelings?)
(Seungjin, please come to the phone booth and call someone you like within 30 seconds.)
Seungjin: So the time has come.
(Who does Seungjin have in mind?)
Seungjin: Even till the end, I was hesitating about who I should call.
Seungjin: I thought about it for a long time.
Seungjin: About who I should call.
Seungjin: I was still thinking even after going into the phone booth.
Seungjin: Someone who made me feel comfortable.
It's comfortable.
-It's spacious. -It's nice.
(Seungjin: Of the people closest to my ideal man...)
(Seungjin: I was conflicted for a long time.)
(Which of the two touched Seungjin's heart?)
(Seungjin is calling)
(Seungjin is calling Youngjoon)
(Youngjoon: Hello?)
(Seungjin: Hello?)
Hello?
(Seungjin: Do you know who I am?)
(Youngjoon: Uh... Seungjin?)
(Seungjin: That's right.)
(Seungjin: Today... was our first meeting. I'm shy with strangers,)
(Seungjin: but I still want to thank you for making me feel comfortable. That's why I'm calling.)
(Youngjoon: Thank you for feeling comfortable.)
(Youngjoon: That's a relief.)
(Seungjin: Hope you have a lovely night.)
(The call ends after 30 seconds)
(Seungjin: Anyway, it was the first call of the night.)
(Seungjin: I mostly felt relieved/good inside.)
(Seungjin: I didn't want to show my feelings from the start.)
(Seungjin: So I called Youngjoon,)
(Seungjin: who made me the most comfortable.)
(Seungjin took a step back and called the one he wanted to thank)
(Youngjoon: He kept expressing his feelings to me,)
(Youngjoon: but did I just brush them off as gratitude?)
(Youngjoon: After the call, it finally dawned on me)
-I think—
-Got a call.
What should I do?
(Seongmin, please come to the phone booth and express your feelings for someone for 30 seconds)
I have to go.
-Go ahead.
-I'll be right back.
(Seongmin, please come to the phone booth and express your feelings for someone for 30 seconds)
(Hwi: Go ahead.)
-Go ahead.
-I'll be right back.
(Hwi: Go ahead.)
-Go ahead.
-I'll be right back.
(Hwi: Go ahead.)
-Go ahead.
-I'll be right back.
(Seongmin: I'll be right back.)
-Go ahead.
-I'll be right back.
(Seongmin: I'll be right back.)
(Seongmin, who leaves, and Hwi, who is nervous for some reason)
(Seongmin: Why am I so nervous?)
(Seongmin: What should I do?)
(Seongmin: Really, what should I do?)
(Nervous)
Wait.
(Seongmin: I was so nervous.)
(Seongmin: I couldn't see anything.)
(Seongmin: I kept shaking. I picked up the phone and put it down.)
I'm going crazy.
(Why can't Seongmin call easily?)
(Seongmin: I was very conflicted between two people. Jaeseung and...)
(Seongmin: And Hwi. I was conflicted.)
(Among Jaeseung and Hwi, who will get Seongmin's call?)
(Seongmin: Hello?)
(Seongmin called)
(Seungjin called Hwi)
(Hwi: Hello?)
(Seongmin: Hello?)
Hello?
(Hwi: Hello?)
(Seongmin: Hello?)
(Seongmin; Do you know who I am?)
(Hwi: Yes, I do.)
(Seongmin: No... Your voice sounds nice.)
(Hwi: Ah, thank you.)
(Seongmin: I feel relaxed having you as a roommate.)
(Shy)
(Hwi: Me too.)
(Seongmin: Sorry, I'm hanging up.)
-Okay.
(Hwi: Me too.)
(Seongmin: Sorry, I'm hanging up.)
(Hwi and Seongmin confirmed each other's feelings through the phone)
(Seongmin: I think this conversation was very important to me.)
(Seongmin: I feel even more positively about Hwi now.)
(Seongmin: After deciding on Hwi,)
(Seongmin: I pushed the button right away.)
I pushed it right away.
(How will the roommates' relationship change after the call?)
(Faced with the awkward situation again)
(Shy)
(Seongmin: Super... super shy?)
(Embarrassed)
(Hwi: Oh, thank you.)
(Seongmin: But really...)
(Seongmin: It's amazing. I was going to call you in the first place.)
(Seongmin: When I was working, my MBTI showed I was equally extroverted and introverted.)
(Seongmin: Now, it's almost 60 to 40.)
(Seongmin: Recently, I feel tired when I meet people.)
(Seongmin: But I feel safe now.)
Really.
(Hwi: When we... played the image game earlier,)
(Hwi: many people chose you.)
(Seongmin: Me? Really? I don't remember.)
Well...
Did you get a call?
(Someone called Hwi)
(Hwi. Hello? Hello.)
(Who called Hwi?)
(Do you know who I am?)
(Hwi: Who are you?)
(I said you got the most... votes today, right?)
Yes.
(I called because I wanted to be close to you.)
("This is Cha Jaeseung")
(Jaeseung: It disconnected.)
(Hwi: Ah, it disconnected.)
(Seongmin: Who was it?)
Cha Jaeseung.
(Seongmin: What? Ah, it was Cha Jaeseung.
(Seongmin: Cha Jaeseung.)
(The two are silent because of the unexpected call)
(Jaeseung: It disconnected.)
(The phone suddenly rings)
(Jaeseung receives a suspicious call. Who is it?)
(His Man begins officially)
The atmosphere suddenly changed.
Today is a date day.
(His Man begins officially)
(Very happy after seeing my date...)
(Laugh)
I'm not in a good mood.
(Their reactions are totally different)
(A man walking towards Men's House)
I've been there recently.
(Surprised)
("It's today. Ah, it's him.")
(More handsome than me?)
(I don't think there are many.)
(I have to go in with a lot of energy.)
The mindset of having to defeat them all.
("Defeat them all.")
(A new man who attracts all 6 men comes)