(Jaeseung)
(Seungjin)
(Minseon)
(Hwi)
(Youngjoon)
(Seongmin)
(Hanmin)
(Myeongkyun)
(Episode 10: The man I'm thinking of right now)
(Hwi & Seungjin's date location is within a green forest)
(Seungjin: What could it be?)
(Hwi: This building is really nice)
(Seungjin: Is this a cafe?)
(Hwi: Cafe? Isn't it a place to make things?)
(Seungjin: Firstly, I can strongly feel the phytoncides)
(Seungjin: It smells so good now)
(Hwi: Because Seungjin and I often talk about our feelings,)
(Hwi: I just want to have a casual chat and have a good time together)
What is it?
(Hwi: It's pottery!)
It must be pottery.
(Seungjin: I said I wanted to go to a pottery workshop on the first day)
(Seungjin: I wanted to go to a pottery workshop)
(Hwi: Me too)
(Seungjin: I'm comfortable with Hwi)
(Seungjin: I think it'll be fun)
(Pottery workshop date that is to their liking)
(Teacher: Practice making a small cup first)
(Teacher: From the second one, I'll help you make what you want to make)
Okay.
Wrap it with your hands like this.
(The first one is to make a cup)
Then try hugging it like this.
How does it feel?
(Wow)
How is it?
(Hwi: Very soft)
-Right? -Yes.
(Softness that calms the heart)
(Seungjin: Wow, this is really...)
(Seungjin: To calm my body and mind...)
(Seungjin: Firstly, I've...)
(Seungjin: repeatedly said)
(Seungjin: I wanted to go to a pottery workshop)
(Seungjin: I was so excited. It was so fun)
(Hwi: It's soothing)
(Hwi: It’s my first time (making pottery). I really liked it)
(Hwi: It feels good too)
(It's hard to make a round pillar)
Yes.
(Teacher: Those who are good at that are good at controlling the pottery wheel)
(It's hard to make a round pillar)
(Hwi: I've made pottery before. But this is my first time using a pottery wheel)
(Focused) (Hwi: It’s really hard)
I know.
(Hwi: It's taking shape)
(Hwi: More and more like a cup...)
(Hwi: Seungjin and I were both so focused)
(Hwi: on making ours look good)
(Hwi: We forgot to talk)
(Hwi: It might seem like we're not close)
(Seungjin: Mine is done)
Good.
Pull it out harder.
(I'm done too)
(Seungjin: I'm most worried about this)
(Oh no)
(Hwi: It'll be funny if you drop it now)
(Dangerous)
(Phew)
Yours is voluptuous.
(Staggering)
See.
(Seungjin: You get me now?)
Put it here, right?
Good.
This is the first item made with a pottery wheel.
(Hwi: It’s like a mud festival)
(Seungjin: I'm so happy)
(Seungjin: I know why people come to make pottery)
-Doesn't it feel nice to mold clay? -Yes.
Next, make what you want.
Tell me what you want to make.
(Seungjin: I suddenly want to make a jar)
(Teacher: Like a vase?)
(Seungjin: Yes)
(Hwi: I... want to make a pasta plate)
-Didn't you have the step of forming the hole? -Yes.
(Starting the second artwork: Seungjin's vase & Hwi's pasta plate)
This time, put it in deeper. All the way.
(Hwi: It’s so fun)
(Seungjin: It's really fun)
(Hwi: It's so therapeutic)
(Hwi: It’s so therapeutic)
(It feels so great?)
(Seungjin: I knew it)
(Seungjin: I knew we'd be so focused)
(Hwi: Really. This is the most concentrated I've been)
(Hwi's paste plate is taking shape)
It's taking shape.
It looks like a plate.
(Hwi's paste plate is taking shape)
-Isn't it amazing? -Yes.
(Teacher: You made it yourself)
(Hwi: I have to eat (pasta) with this)
(Seungjin's vase is taking shape too)
Awesome.
What are you making?
(Seungjin's vase is taking shape too)
-A vase. -A vase?
(Hwi: I’ll share the flowers on the third floor with you)
(Seungjin: Great)
(Seungjin: Maybe because I feel comfortable with Hwi,)
(Seungjin: I could focus in making the pottery)
(Seungjin: It's really nice)
(Seungjin: Also, when making pottery, I didn't think about other things)
Stop here.
(Hwi's pasta plate is finished first)
(Hwi: It already looks pretty)
(Hwi: How is it?)
(Seungjin: Oh~)
((Sad) Hwi: When I picked it up, I made a dent)
Don't worry about that.
(Finger print)
-Are you happy with it? -Yes.
(Next, Seungjin's vase is done)
Then stop.
(Hwi: This is the most nerve-racking moment)
(Carefully)
(Thump)
You're afraid to ruin it.
I'm nervous.
(Putting down the precious vase carefully)
(Seungjin: But I think it’s nice to have a fingerprint too)
-Do you like it? -Yes.
(Even satisfied with the mistakes in their precious works)
(Hwi & Seungjin's therapeutic pottery workshop date)
(The two go to the cafe after making pottery)
(Hwi: Wow, the view is awesome)
(Seungjin: Sit here?)
Sit here.
(With the window as a photo frame, the view's like a painting)
This place is great.
(Hwi: The view here is really great)
(Seungjin: I know)
(Seungjin: It's great)
(Isn't it better for us to hang out?)
(I'm really happy)
(Seungjin: I feel comfortable)
(Hwi: Like besties)
Very comfortable.
(Seungjin: Really. I like that I did what I wanted to)
Right.
(Seungjin: And I did it with someone I'm at ease with)
(Hwi: Yes)
Right.
(Seungjin: Really. I like that I did what I wanted to)
(Seungjin: And I did it with someone I'm at ease with)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Today is a relaxing and carefree day)
(Hwi: Are you going to give (the pottery you made) to anyone?)
(Seungjin: Me?)
(Seungjin: I can't bear to give it away)
(Will you keep it for yourself?)
(Seungjin: Anyway, for the past 4 days,)
(Seungjin: no one's called me)
(Seungjin: If someone calls me,)
(Seungjin: I might give it to him)
(Seungjin: Are you going to give it to Seongmin?)
(Give what? Haha)
(Hwi: I wanted to give (Seongmin)...)
(Hwi: At the first date, I gave Seongmin flowers)
(Seungjin: So you wanted to give him a vase?)
(Hwi: So I thought it'd be nice to give him a vase)
(Hwi: So I'll give him a vase)
(Seungjin: So persistent)
(Hwi: That's how it is)
(Seungjin: Hwi is in love with Seongmin)
(Seungjin: He's so infatuated)
(Seungjin: Looking at him...)
(Seungjin: He's cute and very innocent)
(Seungjin: Didn't you talk to Seongmin alone yesterday?)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Seungjin: What did you talk about?)
(All kinds of... what I feel deep down)
(Seungjin: So now... do you think (you & Seongmin) will work out?)
(Hwi: I really don’t know. I don't know)
(Hwi: That's why I've been talking to him)
(Seungjin: Your feelings are clear)
(Seungjin: But Seongmin's feelings are still uncertain?)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Gosh...)
(Hwi: But I’ve tried my best)
(Hwi: There's nothing more to say)
(Hwi: There's nothing more to do too)
(Seungjin: Yes... You gave your all)
(I have no pride in front of him)
(Here are the drinks and desserts)
Here's your order.
-Thank you. -Is this yours?
(Here are the drinks and desserts)
-Berry berry? -Yes.
-It looks good. -Thank you.
(Seungjin: Let's see who takes better photos)
(Seungjin: Oh, you're even standing up to take photos?)
When taking food photos...
(The two are sincere about the photos)
Yes.
(No blank space)
(Click)
(Oh)
(I'm satisfied!)
(Mine look like Europe)
(It's amazing)
They can use them as promotional photos.
(Immersed)
Let me see.
Awesome.
(They feel like they're on a trip)
It's like London.
(Seungjin: It's different indeed)
Let's try this.
(Seungjin: Thank you for the food)
(Wow!)
(Seungjin: Did I act like an old man?)
(Oh!!)
The smell!
(Hwi: This is amazing)
Awesome.
(Yum)
-Is this basil? -Yes.
(Second therapeutic session after the pottery session)
(Hwi: Is it delicious? Amazing? Moving?)
(Hwi: It's really delicious)
(Seungjin: But you chose me to be your date today)
(Seungjin: What's the exact reason?)
-Today? -Yes.
(Hwi: When I got the card, it said)
(Hwi: to date someone you've never dated)
(Hwi: I thought of you right away)
(Hwi: because when I'm with you... You're good at comforting me, and we're close friends)
(Hwi: I feel comfortable with you. So I asked you out right away)
(Seungjin: Thanks to you, I had so much fun)
(Seungjin: Pottery workshop)
(Hwi: It was so awesome)
(Seungjin: So exciting)
(Seungjin: From the third day, I started overthinking things)
(Hwi: Why?)
(Seungjin: First, I like being alone)
(Seungjin: So 8 people living together at all times)
(Seungjin: is a lot to me)
(That's right)
(Seungjin: And on the third day,)
(Seungjin: a few major things happened)
Yes.
(Seungjin: After all those things, I felt a little...)
(Seungjin: I felt confused)
(Seungjin: I don't have anyone I like a lot either)
(Seungjin: There's no one who's expressed interest in me too)
(Seungjin: So, I felt...)
(Hwi: But before, who was it... Jaeseung?)
(Hwi: Didn't you say you were interested in him?)
(Seungjin: On the third day, when I saw)
(Seungjin: Jaeseung take Seongmin out,)
(Seungjin: I felt like he's very sure)
(Seungjin: about Seongmin right now. So,)
(Seungjin: I don't want to intrude)
(Hwi: Does Jaeseung know you have feelings for him?)
(Seungjin: I doubt (Jaeseung) knows what I feel)
(Seungjin: about him)
(Seungjin: Since I've never told him)
(Hwi: For me, to Seongmin and Jaeseung,)
(Hwi: I was honest with both of them)
(Hwi: I told them my feelings honestly)
(Hwi: After that, I think I became more sure)
(Hwi: about my feelings)
(Hwi: So I think it’s good to tell him)
(Hwi: Tell him first and then come to a conclusion)
(Seungjin's conflicted after Hwi's advice)
(Seungjin: With my personality... I can't do that)
(Seungjin: So I had a headache until yesterday)
The third day.
(Hwi: I kept breaking down on the third day)
(Hwi: I'm someone who likes people)
(Hwi: I get along well with people around me)
(But it’s the first time I kind of disliked people)
It's the first time feeling this way.
(Hwi: So I'm not used to myself being like this)
(Seungjin: After coming to Men's House,)
(Seungjin: wow, I didn't know I could be like this)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Seungjin: What came to my mind until yesterday was)
(Seungjin: that I'm more timid than I thought)
(Hwi: You?)
(Hwi: I think you're more lively than I thought)
(Hwi: Compared to my first impression of you)
(Seungjin: To be honest, that (lively) self)
(Seungjin: isn't my true self)
(Seungjin: To make sure everyone has fun...)
(Seungjin: I don't like to show my feelings. That's why)
(Seungjin: But how I am when I'm with you...)
(Seungjin: When I'm really energetic with you, it's genuine)
(Hwi: It looked so genuine)
(Hwi: While I've been (in Men's House), I think I've found a new side of myself)
(Seungjin: I think so too)
(Hwi: I didn't know I was such a crybaby)
(Hwi: I've never cried in front of anyone before)
(Seungjin: All our conversations were real)
(Seungjin: You could say I've expressed my innermost feelings)
(Seungjin: That conversation impressed me the most)
(Hwi: I was honest with him)
(Hwi: That means I feel more comfortable (with Seungjin))
(Hwi: I think we became closer as friends. So I’m grateful)
(Q. How was your date today?)
(Very, very satisfied. Perfect)
(Hwi & Seungjin's relaxing, enjoyable, and therapeutic date)
(It's already dinner time)
(After Youngjoon & Myeongkyun left, Jaeseung & Minseon are left alone)
More and more spectacles every day.
It's really shocking.
(After Youngjoon & Myeongkyun left, Jaeseung & Minseon are left alone)
(Minseon: I think today's been the most peaceful)
(Jaeseung: It's been peaceful so far)
I don't know what will happen at night. -Yeah.
(Jaeseung: I can't ignore it)
(Jaeseung: Anyway, everyone knows everything now)
(Jaeseung: Who likes whom and the developments)
(Jaeseung: I'm in a love triangle with Hwi and Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: I'm a bit isolated)
(Jaeseung: At least Seungjin's beside Hwi)
(Jaeseung: (Hwi) has someone who)
(Jaeseung: he can talk to)
(Jaeseung: And I felt that strongly during the anonymous chat)
(Jaeseung: Seungjin was with Hwi the whole time)
(Jaeseung: And the sound of them talking even reached my room)
(Jaeseung: I felt...)
(Jaeseung: It's not their fault)
(Jaeseung: But as a listener, it upset me)
(To be honest, I hate him)
(Jaeseung: I hate (Hwi), but I understand him too)
(Jaeseung: But I still feel bitter, you know?)
(Jaeseung: I can understand (Hwi), but I feel bitter)
(Jaeseung: I didn't hear their conversation clearly)
(Jaeseung: It's muffled, but I could hear my name and whatnot)
(Jaeseung: Since it's easier to catch familiar words)
(Jaeseung: They seemed to have mentioned me and Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: Just hearing it upset me)
-I'm hungry. -Are they all home?
They should be here.
(Seongmin & Hanmin coming back from their date)
Let's see.
-You're here. -Hello.
(Seongmin: Hello)
-You're here? -Hello.
Hi, hi.
(Minseon: What did you do on your date?)
(Seongmin: We went to a exhibition hall)
(Minseon: Really?)
(Minseon: They went to an amusement park)
(Really?)
(Hanmin: I said I wanted to go to an amusement park!)
(Ah!)
(Seongmin: But I had fun)
Yeah?
(Minseon: What exhibition?)
(Seongmin: We went to Lee Jae Hyo Gallery that's filled with wooden sculptures)
(Minseon: Oh, really? I've heard of the name)
(It was really nice)
(Hanmin: I said I wanted to go to an amusement park!)
We're in sync.
(Minseon: Both must've been fun. Exhibition and amusement park)
(Hanmin: If I went to the amusement park with Youngjoon,)
(Hanmin: I'd have had a great (date))
(Hanmin: Of course, since (Youngjoon and Jaeseung) had fun,)
(Hanmin: it's a relief)
(Hanmin: But to be honest, I'm jealous)
(Hanmin: Actually I think exhibitions are nice,)
(Hanmin: but I prefer active stuff)
(Jaeseung: The amusement park date was really dynamic)
(I'm so jealous)
(Jaeseung: The swing carousel rotated very fast)
(Jaeseung: The Viking was... Wow)
There are many who prefer active stuff.
(Men's House members who prefer active stuff:
Hanmin, Jaeseung, Youngjoon, and Myeongkyun)
There are many who prefer active stuff.
(Men's House members who prefer active stuff:
Hanmin, Jaeseung, Youngjoon, and Myeongkyun)
(Hanmin: It seems to be about half of us)
(Hanmin: Based on what I've heard, (Seongmin) likes non-active dates)
(Hanmin: Hwi and Seungjin also like non-active ones)
(Minseon: I like exhibitions too...)
(Hanmin: I still took a lot of good photos)
(Minseon: Really? Let me see)
(Jaeseung: I find art museums very boring)
(Jaeseung: as a date)
(Jaeseung: So if I go to a place like that with (Seongmin),)
(Jaeseung: I don't know either)
(Seongmin: So everyone's back except (Hwi & Seungjin)?)
Yes.
(Minseon: Did you check your room?)
(Room?) (Your bed!)
(Why?) (Your bed!)
-Did you see it? -Is something different?
(Minseon: Gosh, why are you so unobservant?)
(Seongmin: What is it?)
(Minseon: Go check again)
What is it?
I'm not very perceptive.
(Minseon prepared a small surprise for Seongmin?)
Exactly.
(Oh!)
(Hey~)
(Minseon: How could you've not noticed it?)
(What is this~)
(Minseon: Take a photo. I'll take photos for you)
-Oh, my. -Do you have a camera?
(So sentimental)
(The birthday banner hanging above Seongmin's bed)
It's so pretty.
I'll take it for you. Go there.
(The birthday banner hanging above Seongmin's bed)
One, two, three.
(One, two, three)
(Thank you)
(Seongmin: I'm so happy)
(Seongmin: It's so cute that they thought to celebrate it by pasting it here)
(Seongmin: I'm so touched)
(I'm so, so touched!)
This is Men's House.
(Hwi & Seungjin are the last to return from their date)
Da-da-da-da-da.
Du-du-du-du-du.
(Hwi & Seungjin are the last to return from their date)
(Minseon: Hi, hi!)
(Hi, hi)
(Minseon: Did you have a good time?)
(Minseon: What did you do?)
(Hwi: We made pottery)
(Minseon: You made pottery? It must be fun)
(Starting already?)
(Seongmin is on duty for dinner today)
I'm going to prepare the salmon first.
(Starting already?)
(Seongmin is on duty for dinner today)
I'm going to prepare the salmon first.
(Hwi promised to help Seongmin cook)
Deal with the fish.
(Hwi: I'll be back soon, but I...)
(Seongmin: Take your time)
(Hwi: I’m not confident (in cooking))
(Seongmin: We can do it together)
(Hwi: Wait for me)
(Seongmin: Take your time)
(Seungjin: A blissful day)
(Minseon: To be honest, I had a very peaceful day today)
(Minseon: So this is peace! I enjoyed the calmness)
(Seungjin: Did you go into the water?)
(Minseon: Of course)
(Minseon: The weather's great for being in the pool)
(Seungjin: If the sun hadn't set after I came back, I wanted to sunbathe)
(Seungjin: But the sun set already)
(Hwi comes back in comfortable clothes)
-Can I wear this? -Yes. Wear an apron.
(Hwi: I'm so tired. What did you do today?)
(Seongmin: I went to an exhibition)
(Exhibition?)
(Seongmin: I'm so satisfied)
(I'm so jealous. Exhibition)
(Seungjin: It's okay. We did something more fun)
(Seungjin: It's okay. We did something more interesting)
(Hwi: True)
(Are you jealous?)
(Hwi & Seongmin cooking for the first time in Men's House)
I'm not used to the stove. What should I do?
I don't know either.
(Seongmin: This is more like a challenge than cooking)
(Seongmin: The guys won't enjoy the food)
(Hwi: The fishcakes must be delicious)
(Seongmin: It's a meal kit, so it'll be delicious, right?)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Sneeze)
Gosh.
(Hanmin: Are you okay?)
(Jaeseung: What should I do?)
Gosh.
(Hanmin: Are you okay?)
(Jaeseung: What should I do?)
(Seongmin: Did you catch a cold?)
(Jaeseung: My throat hurts)
(Seongmin: I have medicine)
(Jaeseung: Give it to me later. I'm fine now)
(Jaeseung: I just took cold medicine)
(Take a look at this)
(Hwi shows Seongmin a video of Seungjin he took)
Wow.
This is a proper Reels video.
(Jaeseung: My head hurts)
(Jaeseung: I'll go upstairs)
(Jaeseung is bothered by Seongmin and Hwi's interaction)
-It's really... -This is really amazing.
This is really... really amazing.
(Jaeseung is bothered by Seongmin and Hwi's interaction)
It's like a proper, uploaded Reels video.
(Jaeseung: Excuse me. I'll get something warm)
There's that in the back, the warm...
(Seongmin: Water?)
(Jaeseung: I want some warm water)
Get warm water from the water purifier.
(Seongmin: Water?)
(Jaeseung: I want some warm water)
Get warm water from the water purifier.
(Conversation ends with Jaeseung's appearance)
(Jaeseung: Can I help you?)
(Seongmin: Me? I can do it myself. It's a meal kit)
(Jaeseung: Meal kit?)
(Wary)
(Seongmin: What will happen if you eat that? It's green tea powder?)
(Seongmin is uneasy being between Jaeseung and Hwi)
Just dissolve it into green tea.
I see.
(Seongmin is uneasy being between Jaeseung and Hwi)
(Seongmin: Did Youngjoon bring the green tea powder?)
(Jaeseung: Yes)
(Jaeseung: Can you come to the balcony later?)
(Okay!)
(Jaeseung: You must come)
(Seongmin: Got it. After I finish cooking)
-I won't help you cook then. -Okay, it's fine.
(Tension among the three people)
(Seongmin: I think Jaeseung didn't want to see me cook (with Hwi))
(Seongmin: I think he didn't want to see me being with Hwi)
(Jaeseung & Hanmin come to the second-floor balcony)
I think in this aspect...
(Jaeseung: The balcony is a great spot)
(Jaeseung: It’s like a privilege of the second-floor single room)
(Hanmin: A place to hide away)
(Jaeseung: I didn't look. I came up directly)
(Jaeseung: I didn't want to see them)
(Jaeseung: What bothers me now)
(Jaeseung: is honestly just Hwi)
(Jaeseung: Just now... Little things were bugging me)
(Jaeseung: Once I got back to Men's House, I saw that Minseon hung up the birthday banner in Seongmin's room)
(Jaeseung: I was suspecting if Hwi hung it up before he left)
(Jaeseung: Every little thing is bugging me)
(Jaeseung: I'd be bothered by so many things if I stayed there)
(Hanmin: Right, and it so happens that (Seongmin and Hwi) are cooking together)
(Jaeseung: So when I came back,)
(Jaeseung: I wore red on purpose because,)
(Jaeseung: well, since I brought it,)
(Jaeseung: but anyway, red always stands out)
(Jaeseung: So I was in fighter mode)
(Jaeseung: But (Hwi) was wearing pink too)
(Hanmin: Yes, totally bright pink)
(Jaeseung: It's interesting...)
(Jaeseung: This is really interesting)
(Jaeseung: But I can't help feeling frustrated)
(Jaeseung: The biggest reason I avoided fighting)
(Jaeseung: with Hwi is)
(Jaeseung: the fact that he's so young)
(Jaeseung: Why do I want to fight with a young kid?)
(Jaeseung: But this is a different thing)
(Jaeseung: This seems to be a different thing)
(Jaeseung: As long as I'm here, I'll stay true to my feelings)
(At least for now, I've to go all out)
(Jaeseung: Show them that I'm not a pushover)
(Jaeseung: Since he provoked me first)
(Jaeseung: Fine. I felt attacked)
(Jaeseung: I didn't ask an anonymous question to Hwi)
(Jaeseung: I only asked Seongmin an anonymous question)
(Jaeseung: I'm not curious about (Hwi's) thoughts either)
(Jaeseung: But Hwi seems to be wary of me)
(Jaeseung: He asked me a question that showcased his anxiety)
(Jaeseung: He must be desperate to keep Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: Okay. Got it. I understand (Hwi's) stance)
(But, fine. Bring it on)
(Jaeseung: So I told Seongmin just now)
(Jaeseung: to talk here with me after dinner)
(Jaeseung: If my weapon is this spot, I'll use it)
(Hanmin: Talk to him here and...)
(Hanmin: You must go on dates with him if there's a chance)
(Jaeseung: They were roommates for a long time)
(Jaeseung: They're also preparing dinner together now)
(Jaeseung: Okay)
(Bring it on)
(Jaeseung: I'm sure Hwi wrote that anonymous question)
(Jaeseung: I received yesterday)
(Jaeseung: I think I dislike Hwi now)
(Searching)
(Hwi: 10 servings of stir-fried spicy pork)
I can't find it for 10 servings.
(Worried about cooking many servings for the first time)
(Minseon: I'll help you with the seasoning at the side)
(Minseon: I roughly know what to do)
(Hwi: Then sit down and instruct me)
(Minseon: You have to stir-fry the vegetables first)
(Minseon: Stir-fry the scallions and make scallion oil first)
(Hwi: Just chop the onions into pieces?)
(Minseon: Chop the onions into pieces and put them in to make the scallion oil)
(Hwi: Should I add garlic too?)
(Minseon: That'd be good. Garlic oil is good too)
(Nervous cooking avatar)
Okay, I'll try.
(Hwi: This is the cutting board, right?)
(Minseon: Yeah. Huh?)
Okay, I'll try.
(Hwi: This is the cutting board, right?)
(Minseon: Yeah. Huh?)
(Minseon: That's not the cutting board)
(Hwi: It's not?)
-It's a tray. -You're right.
(Minseon: That's not the cutting board)
(Hwi: It's not?)
-It's a tray. -You're right.
(He doesn't know what the cutting board is, but he's attempting stir-fried spicy pork)
It's so obvious it's my first time, right?
It's okay.
(I'll show my skills)
(Chopping)
(Meanwhile, Seongmin's fishcake stick soup is cooking well)
It looks good.
How about this? Right now.
Doesn't it look good?
(Hwi: It looks presentable)
(Seongmin: Right?)
Doesn't it look good?
(Hwi: It looks presentable)
(Seongmin: Right?)
(Minseon: Just be careful it doesn't overflow)
(Seongmin: What if it overflows? What should I do?)
(Minseon: If you use low heat, it won't overflow)
(Seongmin: I think it's cooked. I'll leave it)
(Seongmin: I'll try this fishcake first)
(Hwi: Give me some. Just one bite)
(Mmm, it's delicious)
(Chomp)
(Is it good?) (Mmm!)
(It's hot) (Minseon takes a bite too)
-Don't have high expectations. -It's delicious.
It's hot. -What is Hwi cooking?
(It's hot) (Minseon takes a bite too)
(Mmm!!)
-Isn't it good? -What are you cooking?
-It's a secret. -It's delicious.
(Mmm!!)
-What secret? -Look forward to it.
This is for tasting.
(Mama Bird Seongmin gives fishcake to everyone)
Isn't it good?
(Passes)
(Hwi: Is this edible?)
(Minseon: You can eat the leaves too)
Really?
(Hwi: Is this edible?)
(Minseon: You can eat the leaves too)
-You can eat everything except the root. -Is this edible?
(Funny) (Hwi's cooking is worrying...)
Some eat the root, but I don't eat it.
(Hwi: The onions...)
(Minseon: Later. Just leave it separately)
Fry the scallions first to make scallion oil, and add garlic.
(Hwi: The onions...)
(Minseon: Later. Just leave it separately)
Fry the scallions first to make scallion oil, and add garlic.
(Human recipe book)
Chop the garlic first.
(Minseon: You can do it)
(Hwi: What should I do next?)
(Minseon: Add three or four spoons of minced garlic here)
(Minseon takes over)
-Should we add the meat? -Okay.
(Minseon takes charge of the cooking in the end)
-Do I add it too? -Yes.
It must be delicious.
(Minseon takes charge of the cooking in the end)
Cooking together is fun.
(Minseon: No. You don't have to separate the meat)
(Seongmin: It's fun, right? It's much more fun than I thought)
(Seongmin: To be honest, I was worried)
About cooking.
(Seongmin: But Minseon saved us)
(Minseon: Nah)
(Today's chefs aren't Seongmin & Hwi)
(Today’s chef is Minseon)
(Minseon: I think I did 80% of the stir-fried spicy pork)
-Should I add more? -Yes.
(Dinner is almost ready)
-It should be okay. -Yeah?
-The scallions are flying out. -Stop it.
(Chef Hwi has showmanship)
-It’s not a big deal. -It’s no big deal.
Stir-fried spicy pork is easy.
(Hwi: I think I can tell people I can cook now)
(Minseon: You can add the sauce now)
Okay.
(Minseon: Add the sauce slowly)
(Minseon: Don't pour too much at once)
Put three to four spoons first.
(Seongmin holds up the handheld fan for Hwi, in case he's too hot)
Don't add it like this.
(Hwi: I sweated a lot)
(Hwi: At that moment, he came over to face the fan at me)
(Hwi: He was worried I might get hot)
(My heart fluttered)
(Seongmin: But is everyone back?)
(Seongmin: Right. You're the last to come back)
(Seongmin: We can set the table now)
(After chatting, Jaeseung & Hanmin return to the first floor)
You're sweating. Just wipe it here.
Okay.
(A glance)
You're sweating. Just wipe it here.
Okay.
(A glance)
(Surprised)
Are you done?
(Seongmin: If Jaeseung saw me holding the fan...)
(Seongmin: Will he be upset?)
(Seongmin: Would he misunderstand?)
(Seongmin: I'm a little worried)
(Tada)
-Wipe this and place it down. -Okay.
(The dishes placed on the table one by one)
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
(Dinner made by Seongmin & Hwi (feat. Minseon))
-Thank you for the food. -Thank you for the food.
Please enjoy.
(Dinner made by Seongmin & Hwi (feat. Minseon))
It looks delicious.
(Minseon: I should try the spicy pork. I wonder what it tastes like)
Me too.
(Minseon: I think it was cooked well. Look at the color. Wow! Delicious!)
(There were many hiccups while making it, but the taste is great)
The spicy pork is really delicious.
It's good.
(There were many hiccups while making it, but the taste is great)
I have to taste the fishcake too.
Thank you.
(Seongmin: It's really delicious)
(Seongmin: I think our dinner's the best)
(Hwi: It's really delicious)
(Hwi: I must be gifted)
(What?)
What?
(Jaeseung: It's delicious)
(Seongmin: Thanks for eating the fish cake)
(Seongmin: Jaeseung sat directly opposite me during dinner)
(Seongmin: He was cute)
(Seongmin: It was cute that he kept praising my cooking and eating it well)
(Jaeseung: But it's really delicious)
Really, the fishcake is amazing.
(Minseon: Do you remember the spicy pork recipe now?)
(Jaeseung: Right, actually Minseon, you made it)
-No, no. -Minseon made most of it.
Hwi made it.
(Jaeseung: But it's really delicious)
(Seongmin: The spicy pork is really good)
You don't have to eat so many fishcakes.
(Hwi's bothered by their sweet conversation)
Don't fill your stomach with fishcakes.
It's protein.
(Hwi's bothered by their sweet conversation)
The fishcakes are delicious.
Did you add garlic too?
(Hwi's bothered by their sweet conversation)
(Jaeseung: But the spicy fishcakes are my favorite)
(Seongmin: That's a relief)
(The men unusually don't talk much)
(Full of awkwardness...)
(Minseon: I think we need some conversation at the dinner table)
(Jaeseung: I think it's not an atmosphere to just have light-hearted fun)
(Jaeseung: It's probably because of me and Hwi)
(Hwi: Jaeseung and Seongmin were talking face to face)
(Hwi: I was really bothered, so I didn't eat well)
(Seongmin: Hwi looked upset)
(Seongmin: While Hwi was listening to us,)
(Seongmin: he should've realized that I like Jaeseung)
(Seongmin: That's what I thought)
(Jaeseung: Did you leave food for (Myeongkyun & Youngjoon)?)
(Minseon: Ah, I didn't)
(Hwi: Where are they?)
(Minseon: They're still talking)
(Hwi: Where?)
(Minseon: I don't know)
(Seongmin: When did they start?)
(Minseon: It's been about one or two hours)
One or two hours?
(Seongmin: When did they start?)
(Minseon: It's been about one or two hours)
(They're talking for so long)
-We shouldn't have scooped out their rice. -Right.
(Seungjin: Anyway, among eight of us, whenever there's a problem,)
(Seungjin: it doesn't just apply to them)
(Seungjin: The subtle hostility they share)
(Seungjin: spread throughout the group)
(Seungjin: Because of such situations,)
(Seungjin: the atmosphere is (so quiet) now)
(Minseon: I'm not curious about what happened)
(Minseon: Even if I try to ignore it...)
(What was their relationship?)
Why did it come to this?
(Minseon: What happened to have led to this?)
(Minseon: I can't help but think of it)
(Can the messy and confusing tensions be relieved?)
-It feels serious. -Yes.
(Meanwhile, Youngjoon & Myeongkyun came to a cafe
to have a conversation)
(What kind of conversation will they have?)
(Myeongkyun: I feel more conflicted)
(Myeongkyun: I don't think the atmosphere was good)
(Myeongkyun: If I don't talk this time, I don't think I'll ever have a chance to fix this)
(Myeongkyun: I want to talk to him honestly while we can still)
(Myeongkyun: meet face to face)
(Youngjoon: Do you have anything else to say?)
(Myeongkyun: I think I've sorted it out in my head now)
(Myeongkyun: Actually, I...)
(Myeongkyun: I thought we were dating)
(Youngjoon: Back then?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes, yes)
(Myeongkyun: So I thought... we were...)
(Myeongkyun: in a stable relationship)
(Myeongkyun: Then I suddenly lost contact (with you))
(Myeongkyun: So I got very anxious alone)
(Youngjoon: Because I didn't reply you?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Myeongkyun: I told you this a few days ago,)
(Myeongkyun: but once I start to contact someone,)
(Myeongkyun: I will focus only on one person)
(Youngjoon: Then why do you think)
(Youngjoon: I cut off contact with you)
(Youngjoon: Back then?)
(Myeongkyun: I thought about it a lot)
(Youngjoon: It's like this)
(Youngjoon: I don't hate you enough to block you)
(Youngjoon: It's not like I wanted to erase your existence in my life)
(Youngjoon: I didn't reply to you properly)
(Youngjoon: for over a year)
(Youngjoon: So I thought that was enough to express that)
(Youngjoon: I'm no longer interested in you)
(Myeongkyun: (When a relationship's over), people usually)
(Myeongkyun: block each other on social media and whatnot)
(Myeongkyun: So I kept hanging on to some glimpse of faith)
(Youngjoon: It might sound a bit exaggerated,)
(Youngjoon: but I'm looking for someone I can spend my life with)
(Youngjoon: If he couldn't be it, I didn't want to...)
(Youngjoon: So I wanted to end the relationship naturally)
(Youngjoon: I was sad too)
(Youngjoon: Because you never expressed it, I didn't feel your affections for me)
(Youngjoon: I didn't see that,)
(Youngjoon: so I gave up on this relationship first back then)
(Myeongkyun: That's a little...)
(I was still hoping for a reconciliation)
(Myeongkyun: Since it wasn't ended clearly, (I was still hoping for a reconciliation))
(Myeongkyun: I'm not good at saying cheesy stuff)
(Myeongkyun: that lovers do)
(Myeongkyun: I also think I wasn't a good enough lover)
(Youngjoon: Yes. It's not that I wanted to hear those stuff)
(Youngjoon: I just felt like our interactions)
(Youngjoon: didn't make me feel like we were lovers)
(Myeongkyun: But when I was dating you,)
(Myeongkyun: I gradually felt that our relationship was progressing)
(Myeongkyun: So I started the relationship like this)
(Myeongkyun: and I wanted to maintain it. It takes some time for me)
(Myeongkyun: Because it was my first relationship...)
(Myeongkyun: I should've been more expressive)
(Myeongkyun: We didn't really discuss)
(Myeongkyun: about each other's dating style)
(Myeongkyun: That was the root of the problem)
(Myeongkyun: It was just me that thought things were going well)
(Youngjoon: I'm not sure)
(Youngjoon: what you thought of me then,)
(Youngjoon: so I was confused)
(Youngjoon: While meeting you,)
(Youngjoon: I felt there were aspects where we're compatible)
(Youngjoon: but also aspects that we weren't)
(Youngjoon: Also, with our living routines and habits)
(Youngjoon: You were very busy then)
(Youngjoon: These minor issues accumulated)
(Youngjoon: But I didn't think I had to talk everything out)
(Myeongkyun: Right)
(Youngjoon: I thought (our relationship) ended naturally)
(Youngjoon: But from your point of view, you thought there was still room for reconciliation)
(Youngjoon: You might've thought I was still open to reconciliation)
(Youngjoon: From what you just said)
(I always... thought of you)
-That's why I kept contacting you. -Yeah.
(Myeongkyun: As I've told you, when I saw you again (at Men's House),)
(Myeongkyun: I was surprised but also really glad to see you)
(Myeongkyun: I was the one who kept one-sidedly contacting you)
(Myeongkyun: If it goes well, we might be able to talk)
(Myeongkyun: We might be able to talk earnestly again)
To ask why you
gave up on us without saying a thing.
(Myeongkyun: But after that, I was a little...)
(Myeongkyun: I hoped we could talk about the past first)
(Myeongkyun: To tell me why you you cut off contact with me,)
(Myeongkyun: whether you hate me,)
(Myeongkyun: or feel sorry about what happened)
(Myeongkyun: I wanted to talk about that first)
(Myeongkyun: We know each other, but we can try to get to know each other again)
(Myeongkyun: I hoped you'd say that first)
(Myeongkyun: As soon as you called me over,)
(Myeongkyun: you asked if we should tell everyone that we know each other)
(Myeongkyun: That didn't matter to me)
(Myeongkyun: I thought it's possible for me to)
(Myeongkyun: fall for you again)
(Myeongkyun: But after listening to what you said,)
(Myeongkyun: it felt like you wanted to draw the line with me)
(Myeongkyun: So from the get-go, I felt very...)
(Youngjoon: Sad and unappreciated?)
(Myeongkyun: Yes)
(Myeongkyun: Why didn't you think I could still like you?)
(Myeongkyun: I was very hurt but also felt unappreciated)
(Myeongkyun: I thought you were cool and lived your life to the fullest)
(Myeongkyun: when I was dating you)
(Myeongkyun: I could learn a lot from you)
(Myeongkyun: You also have a good personality)
(Myeongkyun: So I kept wanting)
(Myeongkyun: to maintain and develop our relationship)
(Myeongkyun: But from the get-go, you...)
(Myeongkyun: didn't even consider this possibility)
So you were shocked.
Yes.
(Youngjoon: First of all, I'm most surprised that he hopes I can apologize)
(Youngjoon: for the way I ended things)
(Youngjoon: That never crossed my mind)
(Youngjoon: From Myeongkyun's point of view, he must feel sad and unappreciated)
(Youngjoon: I made him feel this way)
(Youngjoon: From the moment you came in,)
(Youngjoon: I thought you came on the show to make a name for yourself as an actor,)
(Youngjoon: rather than to look for love)
(Youngjoon: I thought of it very negatively)
(Youngjoon: Because I thought of you)
(Youngjoon: as someone who doesn't want a proper relationship)
(Youngjoon: For the memories of us that you remember...)
(I've actually forgotten a lot of it)
(Youngjoon: It didn't cross my mind that)
(Youngjoon: you'd even think this way)
(Youngjoon: On the first call session,)
(Youngjoon: if you still have feelings for me,)
(Youngjoon: since you haven't gotten to know the others,)
(Youngjoon: I thought you might call me)
(Youngjoon: But you didn't call me, so...)
(Youngjoon: I thought it wasn't possible)
(Youngjoon: and that I shouldn't overthink things)
(Youngjoon: That's what I thought)
(Youngjoon: Now I also feel like maybe things might be different)
(Youngjoon: if you brought things up with me first)
(Youngjoon: I didn't say what you wanted to hear,)
(Youngjoon: so you were also upset)
(Youngjoon: I don't hate that you liked me)
(Youngjoon: But you've never expressed your affections to me)
That means you don't like me.
So I was confused as to why you kept
provoking me.
(Myeongkyun: I really thought for a long time before making the call)
(Myeongkyun: But you just called me over and drew the line with me)
(Myeongkyun: So I thought if I tried to...)
(Myeongkyun: If I give up my pride and make the call to you,)
(Myeongkyun: it'd really be...)
(Myeongkyun: Yeah. I wasn't brave enough. I was very scared)
(Myeongkyun: I got hurt a lot)
(Myeongkyun: So rather than clinging onto you, I just made a new attempt)
(Youngjoon: I sort of caught on to it when he said it's his weakness yesterday)
(Youngjoon: That he wass more sincere about our relationship)
(Youngjoon: than he thought)
(Youngjoon: Yesterday, I swore and yell at you in the heat of the moment)
(Youngjoon: I made everyone walk on eggshells around me)
(Youngjoon: I'm really sorry to you and the others too)
(Youngjoon: Actually, I was having a tough time yesterday)
(Youngjoon: The fact that others have to be wary about)
(Youngjoon: what happened between us in the past)
(Youngjoon: is stressful for me)
(Youngjoon: I couldn't deal with it alone)
(Youngjoon: But no matter how I talked to you, no progress was made)
(Youngjoon: I was at a loss)
(Youngjoon: Then I got the anonymous question from you)
(Youngjoon: What exactly does that mean?)
(Youngjoon: It sounded so cryptic,)
(Youngjoon: like there's something behind it)
(Youngjoon: So I felt wronged)
(Youngjoon: Even until now, I want to ask you)
(Youngjoon: whatmade you feel that way)
(Youngjoon: I still have no clue)
(Youngjoon: Were you overreacting because you were angry with me?)
(Youngjoon: Or is it some metaphor?)
(Youngjoon: I really don't understand it)
(Myeongkyun: The you that I know...)
(Youngjoon: Isn't how I'm acting now?)
(Myeongkyun: That...)
(Youngjoon: That feels like the real me?)
(Myeongkyun: From what I've seen,)
(Myeongkyun: you are...)
(Youngjoon: Very aggressive?)
(Myeongkyun: you aren't acting out of your interest towards someone,)
(Myeongkyun: but considering a lot of other factors)
(Myeongkyun: (Youngjoon's) actually very calm)
(Myeongkyun: He's not the type to act so loud and try to hype things up)
(Myeongkyun: It felt strongly like he was putting up an act)
(Myeongkyun: so that he'll be perceived in a certain way)
(Youngjoon: When spending time with others)
(Youngjoon: as friends,)
(Youngjoon: the me who's talkative, directing the cooking,)
(Youngjoon: and hyping things up is also my true self)
(Youngjoon: I've never shown that side to you)
(Youngjoon: Back then, it's also because)
(Youngjoon: I wanted to impress you)
(Youngjoon: as a romantic)
(Youngjoon: partner)
(Myeongkyun: But I think you're more natural now)
(Myeongkyun: When we were dating, it felt like this)
(Myeongkyun: It was a bit more relaxed than now though)
(Youngjoon: Myeongkyun's expression now is unusual too)
(Youngjoon: But from Myeongkyun's point of view,)
(Youngjoon: I could've seemed too different)
(Youngjoon: You can consider that maybe the me you saw back then)
(Youngjoon: is not my true self)
(Youngjoon: Because I wanted to please you back then)
(Youngjoon: I wanted to show you a good side of me)
(Youngjoon: So you need to understand that)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Youngjoon: Yes)
(Myeongkyun calmly organizes his thoughts)
(Myeongkyun: Okay. I'm sorry)
(Youngjoon: What?)
(I'm sorry)
(Youngjoon: Now that I think about it, I should be thankful)
(Youngjoon: He was sincerely interested in me)
(Youngjoon: and expressed it to me)
(Youngjoon: Apart from feeling upset because of me, are you still)
(Youngjoon: interested in me?)
(Myeongkyun: Not anymore)
(Youngjoon: Not anymore?)
(Youngjoon: I saw that his gaze was shaky)
(Youngjoon: and nervous)
(Youngjoon: His voice was also shaky)
(Youngjoon: It felt like he said)
(Youngjoon: he wasn't interested in me anymore because he knows how I feel for him now)
(Youngjoon: and he will stop liking me)
(Myeongkyun: I just feel a little empty)
(Myeongkyun: It was just me that was troubled by it for a long time)
(Myeongkyun: I felt empty)
(Youngjoon: Then...)
(Youngjoon: You don't like me anymore)
(Youngjoon: I've made myself clear too, that I don't have any feelings for you)
(Youngjoon: So let's focus our remaining time)
(Youngjoon: on what we each want to do)
(Youngjoon: Amicably...)
(Youngjoon: You'll live your life, and I'll live mine)
(Youngjoon: Be true to our feelings. Let's get along well until we leave this place)
(Youngjoon: Let's get along amicably and say goodbye)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Youngjoon: I wanted to say to get along well in the future,)
(Youngjoon: but it might cause a misunderstanding)
(Youngjoon: So I rephrased it)
(Myeongkyun: I think I can be good friends with him)
(It depends on what Youngjoon thinks though)
(Youngjoon: We were so different, with different ideas)
(Youngjoon: We were so clueless...)
(Youngjoon: Let's get along with ease like friends as before)
(Youngjoon: Let's just say it's our mission)
(Myeongkyun: Okay)
(Youngjoon: Our homework)
(Myeongkyun: Oh, and...)
(Myeongkyun: I really didn't shower first on purpose on the third day)
(Youngjoon: I'll never forget it)
(Myeongkyun: I really didn't do it on purpose)
(Youngjoon: I really won't forget that)
(Myeongkyun: I was dazed and made the best choice I could)
(Youngjoon: No, you did it on purpose)
(Myeongkyun: No, I didn't)
(Youngjoon: It's already a problem that you set an alarm at 7:30 a.m.)
(Myeongkyun: I...)
(Youngjoon: You told me 8 a.m.)
(Youngjoon: But why did two alarms ring at 7:30?)
(Myeongkyun: I set two at 7:30 and one at 8)
(Youngjoon: That's what I'm saying. Why did you set them like that?)
-Just in case... -That was the root of the problem.
(They seem more relaxed after letting out their suppressed feelings)
-I forgot I set them before. I just added an extra alarm.
-I added two new alarms. -Exactly.
(They seem more relaxed after letting out their suppressed feelings)
-Seriously. -Sorry.
(Myeongkyun: I'm sorry. I didn't mean it)
(Youngjoon: It's okay. Everyone said it was funny)
(Youngjoon: That we're like Tom and Jerry)
Okay.
(Youngjoon: During all my past conversations with Myeongkyun,)
(Youngjoon: he'd never responded to my questions properly)
(Youngjoon: Today, he bravely expressed his true feelings first)
(Youngjoon: It's more relieving and relaxing than I thought)
(Myeongkyun: I'm glad that that we'd at least)
(Myeongkyun: no longer be awkward with each other anymore)
-I think they're back. -Hello.
(Youngjoon and Myeongkyun return home after the conversation)
You're home.
We cooked...
(Youngjoon and Myeongkyun return home after the conversation)
We already had dinner.
(The men welcome Youngjoon and Myeongkyun warmly)
-We just ate. -Did you eat?
I was wondering if we should clean up.
(The men welcome Youngjoon and Myeongkyun warmly)
What are the dishes?
(Minseon: It's quite different from what I saw this morning)
(Minseon: As long as they get along like this, it won't be awkward)
-Spicy pork and fishcakes. -Fishcakes.
Both dishes are delicious.
-Hello -You can eat now.
(Welcome)
(Seongmin: You can eat now)
-Hello -You can eat now.
(Welcome)
(Seongmin: You can eat now)
(Youngjoon: Did you have fun?)
I worked hard.
(Seongmin: Did I have fun? I had fun on the date)
(Youngjoon: What did you do?)
(Seongmin: We went to an exhibition)
(Hanmin: It was like work)
(Seongmin: Work?)
(Hanmin: He was more cheerful. I think their talk went well)
We’ve been photographers all day.
(Hanmin shows Youngjoon photos of his date)
(Youngjoon: It's an interesting exhibition)
(Youngjoon: It's Go-Stop cards)
(Hanmin: Go-Stop cards)
(Hanmin: It's actually very big)
(Myeongkyun: Thank you for the food)
(Myeongkyun: It looks delicious. Have you all eaten?)
(Minseon: Yes, you can get some rice from here)
Do you mind eating this bowl? It was untouched.
(Myeongkyun: It looks delicious. Have you all eaten?)
(Minseon: Yes, you can get some rice from here)
Do you mind eating this bowl? It was untouched.
(Minseon takes care of Myeongkyun's dinner)
Thank you.
(Myeongkyun: It's a new bowl)
(Minseon: Yeah. Thigh meat)
(Myeongkyun: Thigh meat? Oh)
(Minseon: I made most of the spicy pork)
(Myeongkyun: Really? Thank you)
Hwi and I...
(Minseon: I made most of the spicy pork)
(Myeongkyun: Really? Thank you)
(Youngjoon: There were no chilis, so you added peperoncino?)
(Myeongkyun: Didn't you say you'll make pork cutlets tomorrow?)
(Minseon: Tomorrow)
(Minseon: Today is Hwi's dish)
(Minseon: I helped a lot. 80% to 90% was my work)
(Youngjoon: We made up and decided to be besties)
(Minseon: That's a relief)
(Myeongkyun: Try it!)
(Myeongkyun: I made this)
(Youngjoon: I don't want to eat it)
(Why?)
(Because you made it!)
(Myeongkyun: It's delicious)
(Youngjoon: I'll maintain this vibe) (Haha)
(Minseon: That's good)
(Youngjoon: The people most influenced by my relationship with Myeongkyun)
(Youngjoon: are Hanmin and Minseon)
(Youngjoon: That's why I said it's settled)
(Youngjoon: and we'll get along well without issues)
(Youngjoon: to relieve the tension)
(Myeongkyun: After the honest talk, we're almost back to our old selves)
(Minseon: In my opinion, it was settled because one side made concessions)
(Minseon: I'm afraid the other hasn't let it go yet)
(Minseon: He said it was settled,)
(Minseon: but to be honest, I don't believe it)
(Unlike the two who are relieved, Minseon still has a lingering fear)
It's my first time eating spicy fishcakes.
-Really? -Not bad, right?
(Unlike the two who are relieved, Minseon still has a lingering fear)
-Yeah -Delicious.
(Hwi: Let’s go to the third floor)
-What -3rd floor.
I was about to eat.
(Passing Seongmin and Jaeseung in the living room, Hwi goes to the third floor immediately)
(Falling down)
(Oh...)
(Didn't we agree to take a photo?)
We agreed to take photos.
(Ah, yes)
That's right.
(Wow, so beautiful)
(Click)
So beautiful.
(Good. It was natural)
(Wow, you're so pretty and charming)
(It hurts)
(Seungjin: Are you going to stay here?)
(Hwi: Shall we have some relaxation time?)
(Seungjin: Okay)
(Hwi & Seungjin's relaxation time = Lying down)
ASMR.
(Hwi: After dinner,)
(Hwi: a little bit later...)
(I told Seongmin I wanted to talk to him)
(Seongmin?)
(To talk to him)
(Why?)
(No reason...)
(And then?)
(What are you going to say)
(Hwi: I’ve already told him)
What?
(Seungjin: He never backs down)
(Hwi: What should I do?)
(Seungjin: What do you mean?)
(Seungjin: Tell him you love him)
(I think I'm in love with you)
I'm so pissed off.
(I'm so bloody pissed off)
(Hwi: I won’t eat croffles anymore)
(Sigh..) (Hahahaha)
(Hello X2)
(Yeah?)
(Yeah X2)
(Go ahead)
-Go ahead. -Yeah.
(Hehehehe)
(Go ahead X2)
-Go ahead. -Yeah.
(Go ahead)
(Hehehehe)
(Go ahead X2)
(Hwi: Should we brush our teeth?)
(Seungjin: Okay)
(Hwi: Let's go brush our teeth)
(A glance)
(Jaeseung & Seongmin still chatting in the living room)
(Notices Hwi)
-I'm just worried. -Worried?
(Jaeseung & Seongmin still chatting in the living room)
(Notices Hwi)
(Wary)
(Sigh)
(Stopping)
(Hwi is eavesdropping on Jaeseung and Seongmin's conversation)
(Jaeseung: Your birthday is coming)
(Seongmin: Right. July...)
(Jaeseung: I hope I'll be the first)
(Jaeseung: to wish you a happy birthday)
(Shy)
(Seongmin: I'll accept it with gratitude)
(Gosh)
(Wary)
(Hwi doesn't move)
(What's wrong?)
(Shhh)
(What is it?)
Isn't it funny?
(Seongmin: I thought Hanmin was my rival)
(Jaeseung: Right)
(Seongmin: When I went to your room after the anonymous chat,)
(Seongmin: you were with Hanmin)
(Seongmin: I wondered what was going in)
(Seongmin: When I was in the room with Hanmin,)
(Seongmin: I saw Hanmin enter your chat group, so I...)
(Jaeseung: Hanmin was just observing)
(Seongmin: Observing?)
(Seongmin: I feel comfortable with Hanmin. He's like a younger brother)
(What is Hwi thinking?)
Two years younger?
Yes, he's two years younger than me.
(What is Hwi thinking?)
So he's like a comfortable younger brother.
-What are they talking about? -I'm so pissed off.
(Second-level anger)
(Seungjin: What are they talking about?)
Do you have that? The toothbrush...
(Brushing teeth in anger)
(Hwi: Jaeseung... I won't let you off)
(Hwi: I'll teach you a lesson)
(Hwi: What is he doing to me, who's 10 years younger than him?)
(Hwi: Doesn't he feel guilty at all?)
(Hwi: To be honest, Daejeon and the capital is too far apart)
(Hwi: I don't think they'll work out)
(A glance)
(Jaeseung & Seongmin are no longer in the living room)
(Hwi puts the toothbrush back and rushes down to check out the first floor)
(You can see the balcony from this window)
(Hwi: Seongmin & Jaeseung)
(Hwi: were talking at the second-floor balcony)
(Hwi: I was so angry that I wanted to lock the door)
(Hwi: Make them unable to get out)
(Hwi: Then they'll fight)
(Seungjin: Were (Jaeseung & Seongmin) talking about Hanmin?)
(Hwi: Who? No)
Who? No.
(Seungjin: Were (Jaeseung & Seongmin) talking about Hanmin?)
(Hwi: Who? No)
(Hwi: They are...)
(Seungjin: Are they talking about something serious?)
Who? No.
(Seungjin: Were (Jaeseung & Seongmin) talking about Hanmin?)
(Hwi: Who? No)
(Hwi: They are...)
(Seungjin: Are they talking about something serious?)
(Hwi: (Jaeseung & Seongmin) went to the second-floor balcony)
(Serious)
Really?
(Seungjin: Are you suddenly troubled?)
(Hwi: What?)
(So XX annoying)
What? So XX annoying?
So XX annoying.
(What? So XX annoying?)
(Hwi: No, it's really annoying…)
(Hwi: I really want it)
(Hwi: So nothing's off limits)
(Hwi: So I came up with a few strategies)
(Hwi: to win Seongmin back)
(Hwi: The first thing I thought of was the "seduction strategy")
(Hwi: I'll do the opposite. I'll seduce Jaeseung)
(Hwi: Get along well until the last day.)
(Hwi: Then I'll choose Seongmin)
(Hwi: I came up with this thrilling script)
(Hwi: (My next strategy) is an extension of the seduction strategy)
(Hwi: When Jaeseung's asleep, I'll place a plate of croffles by his bed)
(Hwi: I'll make him some croffles)
(Hwi: When he sees it, he'll be curious who made it)
(Hwi: I'll admit that I did it)
(Hwi: Then he might be interested in me and ask me to follow him)
(Hwi: Seduce him in this way)
(“I’m good at making croffles”)
(It feels good just thinking about it)
(Myeongkyun: Where did you go? Museum?)
(Hanmin: An exhibition)
-An exhibition. -An exhibition.
(Myeongkyun: Where did you go? Museum?)
(Hanmin: An exhibition)
An exhibition.
(Myeongkyun: Where did you go? Museum?)
(Hanmin: An exhibition)
(Minseon: They went to an exhibition, a pottery workshop, and an amusement park)
(Youngjoon: Pottery workshop)
(Minseon: Today's a peaceful day)
(Myeongkyun: That's right)
(Youngjoon: You two must feel better since you napped)
(Myeongkyun: Yes? For about one and a half hours?)
(Minseon: We slept for an hour and a half, but what's shocking is...)
(Youngjoon: They slept the least)
(Hanmin: Right. We talked about it)
(Minseon: What's that?)
(Why are the men shocked?)
-What's that? -What's that?
(Getting up)
(Youngjoon: Please express your feelings to the person you're thinking of through a letter)
(Guys!)
(Please express your feelings to the person you're thinking of through a letter)
(Tiem for the men to express their feelings through letters)
(Guys!)
(Myeongkyun: We were just talking here. Why didn't anyone notice?)
(Youngjoon: I know, right?)
(Youngjoon: How did you find out?)
(Minseon: While we were talking, I saw something that shouldn't be here)
(Youngjoon: But it's not urgent)
(Minseon: It's letter writing)
(Youngjoon: Guys, let's write letters)
(Minseon: Event)
(Seungjin: Please express your feelings to the person you're thinking of through a letter)
(Jaeseung: Is it another card again?)
(Jaeseung & Seongmin come out after hearing noise)
(Youngjoon: Letter writing)
(Seungjin: I'm going upstairs to write~)
(Minseon: I'm really bad at this)
(Hanmin: Me too)
Write to the person you're thinking of now.
We did it yesterday. Why all of a sudden?
(Jaeseung & Seongmin are the last to check the mission card)
Please express your feelings to the person you're thinking of through a letter.
The person you're thinking of now.
(Jaeseung & Seongmin are the last to check the mission card)
(Seongmin: Express your feelings through a letter)
(Jaeseung: Where should I write it?)
(Jaeseung: I have my own room anyway. Fighting)
(Jaeseung: Wait. Isn't this only for one person?)
(Minseon: One for each person)
Yes.
(Minseon: After writing this letter, shall we gather to clean up the (dining table) together?)
(Youngjoon: Okay)
Okay.
(Minseon: After writing this letter, shall we gather to clean up the (dining table) together?)
(Youngjoon: Okay)
Okay.
(Minseon: After writing this letter, shall we gather to clean up the (dining table) together?)
(Youngjoon: Okay)
(Youngjoon: It's easier to write on the dining table)
(Seungjin: Sigh... I'd rather make phone calls)
(Hwi: Instead of who to write to,)
(Hwi: I was thinking of what I should write)
(Myeongkyun: I think I prefer writing letters)
(Myeongkyun: Because I have time to think about it)
(Minseon: When I saw the mission, I knew who I'd write to)
(Seongmin: Should I wrote an apology letter or a love letter?)
(What kind of letters will the men write?)
(Hesitant)
(Struggling from the first sentence)
(Thinking)
(Hanmin: What should I write?)
(Myeongkyun: I really can't say cheesy words)
(Myeongkyun: but I wrote a lot of things I wanted to say)
(Youngjoon: It's hard to start)
(Youngjoon: But once I start writing, I can write non-stop,)
(Youngjoon: filling two to three A4 papers)
(Youngjoon: Because I have a lot to say)
(Youngjoon: I think I can organize my feelings before expressing it)
(Youngjoon: So I prefer letters)
(Hanmin: I've never written a love letter before)
(Hanmin: I just wrote it...)
(Hanmin: Did I do it correctly?)
(Hanmin: I hope at least he'd like it when he sees it)
(Men carefully selecting their words and conveying their true feelings)
(Hwi and Seungjin write letters side by side on the third floor)
(Seungjin: Well... has it been seven years?)
(Seungjin: I don't think I've written a letter except during my school days)
(Serious)
(Seungjin: Today's promise to only be happy became a lie)
(Choked up) (No, no, no)
-No, no, no. -Okay, okay.
(Hwi is trying to suppress his tears)
No, no, no.
(♫I don't mean anything else; I'm really sorry♫)
(Seungjin: Everyone must feel the same)
(Seungjin: I'll sing for you)
(Looking)
(Seungjin: Wow, so many words...)
(Hwi: I thought a lot)
(Hwi: I wrote it for a long time)
(Hwi: That's why I filled up the card)
(Who is Seongmin thinking of? What's he writing about?)
(Seongmin: I think what you write with sincerity is a letter)
(Seongmin: So I think it's an opportunity for some people)
(Seongmin: while a sad thing for others)
(After writing their sincere letters)
(Choked up)
(Patting and comforting)
(Hwi: Crying every day)
(Seungjin: So what if you cry every day? Just cry)
(Hwi: Pretend to massage my back)
(Seungjin: Does it hurt here?)
(Seungjin: Oh, you mean it hurts here?)
Yes, there.
(Seungjin: I think he's really being true to his feelings)
(Seungjin: Why don't he try to be less obsessed with Seongmin?)
(Minseon: Why are you giving him a shoulder massage?)
(Seungjin: He's aching)
(Minseon: Should I get some medicated plasters?)
(Hwi: It's okay)
-No. -No.
(Minseon: Should I get some medicated plasters?)
(Hwi: It's okay)
A massage will do.
(Hwi: Something went into my eyes)
(Comfy? Comfy)
(Comfy?)
(It's okay) (Sad)
-Can I chain-smoke? -Yes.
Smoke five if you need.
(It's okay) (Sad)
(Hwi: It's absurd. Maybe I have too much water in my body. I'm sweating from my eyes)
(Minseon and Seungjin stay by Hwi's side silently)
(Hwi: Should I not have come here?)
(No) (No)
Not at all.
(Hwi: Should I not have come here?)
(No) (No)
(Hwi: I think I'm really clueless)
(Seungjin: Not true)
(Seungjin: Why are you doing this?)
(Minseon: Please don't blame yourself)
(Minseon: Why do you keep belittling yourself? Don't do this)
(It's time to send their heartfelt letters)
(What confessions do the men make through the letters?)
(Jaeseung: There were two letter boxes)
(Jaeseung: I think it must mean something)
(Hanmin: Oh? Why? Is it divided into two (letter boxes) because there are many people?)
(Minseon: There must be something hidden behind it)
(Minseon: One of the letter boxes may not send out the letters)
(Minseon: This was the first thing I thought of)
(Minseon: That's really shocking)
(Hwi: I'm conflicted again)
(Hwi: Right or left? Which letter box should I put it in?)
(Seungjin puts his letter in directly)
(Myeongkyun carefully observes the letter boxes)
(Ding-dong-daeng)
(The rainbow is out)
(Peter Pan)
(Coca Cola)
(Myeongkyun: What is it?)
(Youngjoon: What is it? Do I get to choose?)
(Youngjoon: Why are there two?)
(Seongmin: Why are there two?)
(Seongmin: What's going on?)
(Seongmin: What is it? What's going on?)
(Seongmin: I checked if there was a letter from someone else)
(Seongmin: I looked to see if I can put it safely, but there was nothing)
(Seongmin: So I just... thought to make a choice)
(What's the meaning of the two letter boxes?)
(Mail time is over)
(Each man spent the fifth night in their own style)
♫Lezzgo, lezzgo♫
(Seongmin: Are you tired?)
(Jaeseung: @%$^&^%)
(Seongmin: What's wrong?)
(Jaeseung: Seongmin)
(Jaeseung: If there's a date tomorrow, do you want to go on a date with me?)
(Seongmin: Yeah)
(Seongmin: Why?)
(Jaeseung: That's enough)
(Seongmin: Of course. We missed the first three dates)
(Hwi: Oh? Seongmin)
(Hwi: Come outside...)
(Seongmin: Hang on)
(Hwi: Well, I...)
(Hwi: Well, I have something to ask you)
(Hwi: Can I ask?)
(Seongmin: Yes)
(Seongmin: What is it?)
(Hwi: Well...)
(Hwi: I don't know. I have a lot to say)
(Hwi: Can I ask you just one question?)
(Hwi: Before...)
(Hwi: You said I was your first choice)
(Hwi: Then we talked more...)
(Hwi: I want to ask if you've a change of mind...)
(Seongmin: Now?)
(Seongmin: I think I've changed...)
(Hwi: Oh... I have nothing to say...)
(Seongmin: Sorry...)
(Seongmin: Shouldn't we go in?)
(Seongmin: Staying here's a bit...)
(Hwi: Got it)
(The two men go back in)
(Hwi: I just want to talk)
(Hwi: I want to talk)
(Hwi seems to have something to say)
(Hwi: Goodness, I need to lie down for a while)
I need to lie down for a while.
(Hwi: Tomorrow is the sixth day)
(Hwi: Time flies)
(Hwi: I’m curious now)
(Hwi: Why... has your interest in me dropped?)
(Seongmin: No. It's not your fault)
(Hwi: I didn't say it's my fault)
(Hwi: I'm just... curious why)
(Seongmin hesitates to answer Hwi's question)
(Seongmin: I'm slow to warm up to others)
(Seongmin: I felt it after some time)
(Seongmin: I realized I have stronger feelings for Jaeseung now)
(Seongmin: I didn't want to hide it from you)
(Hwi: Honestly, no matter how much I respect you,)
(Hwi: I still...)
(I still get jealous)
Well...
(Hwi: I don’t know. I get jealous when I see you (& Jaeseung) together)
(Hwi: Although I respect you...)
(Seongmin: What do you want me to do?)
So...
(At that time, Jaeseung goes to the double room)
Sorry.
(Seeing them together, Jaeseung's lost in thought)
(Hwi: Anyway, the situation has changed)
(Hwi: But I don't think there's such thing as 0% or 100%)
(Hwi: When we first went on a date,)
(Hwi: we didn't know much about each other)
(Hwi: After I expressed my feelings)
(Hwi: and going through all kinds of things,)
(Hwi: if we go on another date,)
(Hwi: I'm sure I'll realize some things)
(Hwi: and you will too)
(Seongmin: To be honest, I don't know what to do now)
(Seongmin: Are you not interested)
(Seongmin: in anyone else?)
(Hwi: Yes, I've been only been attracted to you)
(Hwi: since the first day)
(Seongmin is conflicted because of Hwi's honest response)
I don't know what to do now.
(Seongmin: I think I should be true to my feelings)
(Seongmin: So I'm thinking about going on a date with Jaeseung)
(Seongmin: I've always hoped you'd try dating)
(Seongmin: someone else too)
(Hwi: I don't think it's necessary now. Even if (I go on a date with others)...)
(Other than you, it's all meaningless)
(Hwi: I'm afraid you'll be troubled because of me,)
(Hwi: so I thought about it a lot)
(Hwi: But I can't help it)
(Seongmin: Do you hate seeing me with Jaeseung?)
(Hwi: No, it's not that I hate it)
(I just feel sad)
(Hwi: Today... yesterday and today,)
(Hwi: you seem to be avoiding me)
(Hwi: Maybe it's just me)
(Hwi: But I feel so. That's why it's harder)
(Seongmin: It's true that I can't face you because I feel guilty)
(Seongmin: So I did avoid you a bit)
(Seongmin: It's true)
Really
(It'd be nice if you could smile at me)
(Hwi: You're so cold...)
But I think...
(Seongmin: Honestly, think about it)
(Seongmin: I don't know how Jaeseung and I will turn out. Right?)
(Seongmin: Putting aside the results,)
(Seongmin: I want to follow my heart)
(Seongmin: to make a choice)
(Seongmin: I also don't want to lie to you)
(Seongmin: That's why I'm telling you first)
(Seongmin: Even if Jaeseung decides not to choose me in the end)
(Seongmin: and he has a change of heart,)
(Seongmin: I'd have no regrets)
(Because of Seongmin's decisive words, Hwi looks visibly upset)
(The awkward atmosphere in silence)
(Hwi: Do you want me)
(Hwi: to stop liking you?)
(Seongmin: I wasn't lying)
(Seongmin: when I said our personalities fit the best and whatnot)
(Seongmin: Just think of it as me having a change of heart)
(Seongmin: I think those were feelings in the past)
(Seongmin: Just like I have different feelings now)
(Hwi: That's a bit...)
(Hwi: I don't know how to accept it)
(Seongmin: I don't know what's the right thing to do)
(Seongmin: So I'm going to follow my heart now)
(Seongmin: I'm sorry)
(Hwi: We talked too long, right?)
(Hwi: Don’t avoid me because you feel sorry,)
(Hwi: okay?)
(Hwi: It hurts me more when you avoid me)
(Hwi: Good night)
(Seungjin: Where are you going?)
(Hwi: My room)
(Seungjin: Do you want to be alone?)
(Come here)
(Hwi: I'm giving up)
(Seungjin: Why?)
(Hwi: I'm giving up. He said no)
(Seungjin:, Mr. Whistle...)
(Hwi: It won't work)
(Seungjin: Why...?)
(Hwi: I'm giving up)
(Seungjin: What happened?)
(Hwi: I don't know)
(Hwi: I don’t know. I must be crazy)
(Seungjin: Did something happen in that short period of time?)
(Seungjin: Am I the only one out of the loop?)
(Hwi: It’s not like that...)
(Hwi: I went out to have a chat with him)
(Seungjin: You know this?)
(Seungjin: It feels like you'd die without him)
(Seungjin: But if you look around, you realize it's not true)
(Seungjin: It's not about)
(Seungjin: if you should give up your feelings for Seongmin)
(Seungjin: But that you should...)
(Seungjin: You might feel better)
(Seungjin: if you let go of a bit of your persistence on Seongmin)
(Seungjin: I'm not asking you to stop liking him)
(Seungjin: But you have to get rid of the feeling that he's the only one for you)
(Seungjin: Then you might feel better)
(Seungjin: We agreed to only be happy today)
(Seungjin: But it became the worst day in history)
(Seungjin: You must be upset)
(Hwi: Yes)
(Seungjin: It means you're growing up)
(After Seungjin left, the third-floor single room feels extra empty)
(Hwi's night that is particularly sad and lonely)
(The next morning)
(Those who left their letters in the same letter box will go on a date together)
(Right box: Hwi, Seungjin, Seongmin)
(Left box: Jaeseung, Hanmin, Minseon, Myeongkyun, Youngjoon)
I want to see what it is.
(So this was what the letter boxes were about)
(Oh!)
(Jaeseung: Why is it so hard for me)
(Jaeseung: when it's easy for others?)
One, two, three.
(Jaeseung: I felt like how a typical single man would when stuck with couples)
(I can't go on more rides)
(He suddenly cancels on their date)
(I miss Seongmin)
(Meanwhile, the two who are getting closer)
You did it on purpose.
(Pretty)
(Seungjin: I think I have a huge change of heart)
(I'm interested in Hwi)
(Seungjin: And I have something to ask Seongmin)
(Seungjin: Right now, what's your relationship with Jaeseung?)
(Seungjin: Are (Seongmin & Hwi) really done with each other?)
(Seongmin: Right now, I...)
(A new man joins the battle; Is this the beginning of a love square?)