[Opening OST: "The Best of You in My Mind"]
[Melody by Guofeng Zheng - Lyrics by Qiao Lin]
[Singer: Song Xu]
♫ I hesitate to talk. ♫
♫ Some words haven't been spoken yet ♫
♫ but you are already laughing at something, ♫
♫ whether you understand or not, ♫
♫ or pretend to be indifferent. ♫
♫ If only I could remove your sadness. ♫
♫ Afraid some words would breakdown the mask, ♫
♫ suddenly, I found myself speechless. ♫
♫ You are chatting about the plot of a dream ♫
♫ and sadly, cry your eyes out. ♫
♫ Love is like a migratory bird waiting for the season. ♫
♫ How long does it take for them to be aware of each other? ♫
♫ You are like summer night, ♫
♫ I'm like a little star in the sky, ♫
♫ accompanying you to blink until indispensable. ♫
♫ Deliberately, I hit your shoulder, ♫
♫ and listen to your reprimand. ♫
♫ The caring feeling is so sweet! ♫
[The Best of You in My Mind]
[Episode 15]
Open up, let me see your closet.
Look, how about this? It's neat.
My father has this jacket, too. Throw it away!
Try another one.
Look at this one! It's newly bought.
It looks quite nice.
It's so ugly! I've never found this sort of childish shirt to be attractive.
Throw it away! It's so ugly.
Thermal underwear?
Throw it away.
But it's so cold outside.
We're girls! We must wear clothes that make us look slim.
You don't want to look like a walking bucket in front of boys.
Moreover, you're not tall.
Xin Zidan, why are you being so honest?
Nie Yue.
Look at your clothes! I can't wear them.
Quiet. Quiet.
Shut up!
It's cold! Aren't feeling you cold?
Of course, I am.
But I can't let the cold make me become a walking bucket, I must hang in there.
Why are you here?
I was just passing by, so I thought I'd drop by.
Wait, Lin Xichi, did you put on lipstick?
I thought you didn't wear makeup.
Do I look good?
You look like you just ate a dead mouse.
I... I didn't eat that.
It's cold! Why are you taking off your jacket?
You're not wearing enough clothes.
Xu Fang! You're so amazing!
- What?
- What's wrong with Lin Xichi?
What's going on? They used to fight a lot.
What's happening?
- What's wrong with her?
- Lin Xichi.
What's going on here?
Your movements are so good!
Nice shot!
Something's wrong with her.
Awesome! You're my number one!
Lin Xichi, what's wrong with you today? Can't you see we're practicing? Don't you find it embarrassing?
I'm telling you! Keep quiet; otherwise, I'll—
I'm off to work.
- Xu Fang, you're awesome!
- Xu Fang, nice shot!
Xu Fang, I love you!
Carry on practicing! Stop it! Practice.
Why did you scold Lin Xichi today?
She wasn't wearing enough clothes, and she started flattering herself.
Flattering herself?
I've seen this situation before.
If a tough girl starts flattering herself and dressing up,
that means she's into someone.
Did she tell you where she's going?
She said she passed by there on her way to work.
Oh, dear! If that's the case, that means she's seeing Ye Shao Wen.
I've told you so, Bro.! If you don't do something now,
she'll become someone else's girlfriend.
[Plan to tackle Fang Fang]
- Wait, what did I do wrong?
Did I not do it right?
Or, should I stop doing unnecessary things?
I tried so hard today but Fang-fang's not calling me at all.
Having a crush on him is tiresome.
[Lin Xigeng] Tomorrow's the weekend. See you in Rong City!
Again?
[Pupurazzi pet lifestyle center]
Sit, sit, sit! Hand! Good dog.
Hand! Here you go! Hand!
She's over there.
Chi-chi.
Sister.
Why are you here again? Do high school students, nowadays, have that much free time?
I have a reason for coming.
I'll get you some drinks.
He's quite caring.
Does he work here, too?
His family owns this shop.
Really?
What a handsome and rich guy.
I'm telling you, don't you say anything weird!
Thank you.
Senior, how many years are you ahead of my sister?
Three years! I'm a fourth-year student, so I don't have many classes and am writing my thesis.
Then I should call you Big Senior.
Senior, do you have a girlfriend?
No.
There's dog food, I'll get you some. Come here!
Sister! Why are you leaving so soon? I still want to talk to Senior Ye.
If I had known this would happen, I wouldn't have told you.
But you're my sister after all.
Of course, I need to find out about my future brother-in-law. Okay?
Why do I feel that you're worse than my future mother-in-law?
Of course! This will determine what your future mother-in-law looks like.
Lin Xigeng, can you stop it?
I find him quite good. Just pick him up!
I'm willing to let him be my brother-in-law.
But I'm not.
Why not? He's so eligible.
- Xu Fang's way better.
- What did you say?
I... I'm not talking about you.
Where did you come from?
But I heard you calling my name.
Lin Xigeng, why did you call him?
I...
Are high school students nowadays this free? Why did you come to Rong City?
I... I'm taking a break from revision.
That's right! My sister said she wanted to treat us to a meal. Let's go to eat later!
Sure.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat hot pot.
You're here because you knew I got my salary today?
I know everything about you.
Let's go!
Push it!
- What are you doing?
- Push it!
[Tan Ya Xue Old Hot Pot]
I'm going to the washroom.
He's gone!
Did Xu Fang hear what we said?
I think he did.
He came right after you said he was way better.
I'm sure he's heard it, providing he's not hard of hearing.
Seriously?
You've fallen in love with Brother Fang?
- What do you want?
- I'll tell him later.
- I dare you!
- Give me money and I'll keep quiet.
- I will kill—
- What are you doing?
Lin Xigeng lost his money.
Found it?
- No.
- Yes.
Why is your jacket so dusty?
There's no water in the cup.
I need to go to the washroom.
Brother Fang, I want to eat meat.
Lin Xichi, what are you doing? You're such an idiot!
[Lin Xigeng: That was obvious. You'd better not talk. Sit there quietly. Please]
Is Ms Wang your math teacher right now?
No, it's Ms He.
Sister, eat! It's so delicious.
His exam is around the corner.
Here! You need to eat more.
Sister, I think you should talk to our parents.
Eat faster, Lin Xi Geng! Your sister's going to finish them all.
How's your recent result?
Can you not talk about my studies while we're eating?
Just like Brother Xu Fang said, your exam is around the corner.
Many people redo the exam, so it's okay if you redo it.
What are you saying? Just don't say anything if you don't know how to comfort me.
I'm telling you, I'm a different person now.
In what way? You eat more nowadays?
I'm not telling you.
Sister, I have something to do later so I'll go to the train station now.
You should go back first.
Go home and study well!
Don't worry! See you after the exam.
I'm off.
Bye-bye.
I'll take you back.
No, thanks! I hurt your arm during our last ride.
I'm not doing it again.
I'm recovered. See!
All good!
Why are you suddenly being so nice? I'm not used to it.
Let's go!
Sit tight!
-I'm sorry.
-Go slowly.
- Watch your way.
- I didn't see them.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You're alright? Your arm...
I'll go slowly.
I'm sorry!
Is anyone here?
[Jiang Zheng Xu] I think she likes me.
You're really something! You've been working hard during the holiday.
I'm planning to finish two more papers on my way home.
Why are you here?
I came here because of my sister.
It has to do with my future brother-in-law, that's why I came here.
Brother-in-law? Are you talking about Xu Fang or Ye Shao Wen?
You know about it all?
I can't jump to conclusions now.
You must help me to keep an eye on my sister.
Let me know if something happens.
This is my stupid sister's first relationship.
I can't help but worry about it.
I need to help you with that?
If you're not willing to do so, I'll go to school and tell Ms. He
in very details about her daughter.
What's wrong with her daughter?
Are you going to help me?
You brat! You win.
I need to go now! Tell me if you come here again. Oh, right!
What's this?
You can look at it after I leave.
What's the situation? What's the situation?
I heard her saying 'Xu Fang's way better.'
Tell me! Under what circumstance would a girl compare two guys?
For a girl, unless she likes one of them,
only then would she do so.
Brother, well done!
My ex-girlfriend used to compare me and Daniel Wu.
You have an ex-girlfriend?
Seriously?
What's so strange about it?
Captain Fang, who are you talking about?
Don't you have a girlfriend? You're thinking of cheating on her?
It's Lin Xichi.
Lin Xichi?
You still haven't confessed to her?
Even if she likes you too, if you don't confess you'll end up being friends only.
Why are you being such a coward?
Enough! Stop discouraging him.
Brother.
There's just a piece of paper between you two.
One of you needs to get rid of it.
My monthly salary! It's time to say goodbye to you.
Fang-fang's birthday plan.
One, buy a cake.
Two, buy a present.
Third, confess to him by candlelight.
But what should I buy for his present?
- Good morning.
How can I help you?
I want to buy a birthday cake.
Okay, a birthday cake! Here's the menu.
Have a look at it.
- I want this.
- Sure, please wait for a while.
Hi! here's your cake.
It's done?
How much?
Altogether, 278 yuan.
Okay. Including the bread?
Yes.
[CCTV in operation]
[Boys' dorms, no girl allowed]
I can't get mad.
I like her! I shouldn't get mad.
Gentle! I need to be gentle.
It'll be over soon.
Oh gosh! Why isn't it coming off?
He's going to beat me to death.
This time I'll teach you a good lesson!
Hurry up! What kind of internet is this?
The speed is so slow.
Hurry up!
You're going to break the screen.
- Lin Xichi!
- Wrong person.
No matter how you hide, I can still recognize you.
Fang-fang, Happy Birthday!
Why don't you say something?
Didn't you wish me a happy birthday?
I'm pretty sure it's your birthday.
Do I look happy now?
Stop laughing!
Today's my birthday!
Stop laughing.
- Are we even now?
- No.
I've had enough of this!
Hurt! Hurt, hurt, hurt!
- Why are you pulling my hood?
- Stop talking! This is a male dormitory.
I can't see!
Quick!
Xu Fang, who's that?
- Wait! what's the matter with you?
- It's none of your business.
I've used up my shampoo. Lend me yours!
No, no, no!
No!
I've looked it up! It's said that essential balm can get rid of the ink.
Do you have some?
I'll do it for you.
Am I hurting you?
Fang-fang, you're nineteen years old.
You must learn to be mature... and control your temper.
Don't get mad at cute and kind people!
Can you shut up?
Done! Go and clean your face.
Today's my birthday, I can't get mad.
I can't get mad!
Make a wish first!
I wish Lin Xichi would be less troublesome this year.
Can you make a wish related to yourself?
This is your birthday gift!
You're calling me a dog again?
Of course, not! I spent a night making this.
And I embroidered this myself.
I wish it could protect you
from injuries
while you're having matches or training.
I think, sometimes I don't know what's on your mind.
- What are you doing?
- But I think, this time I got it right.
Lin Xichi.
Do you have a crush on me?
You still need to make a wish first.
Then
I wish you could forget what I just said.
Why did you blow out my candles?
Be-Because...
Because I don't think I can do that.
I...
I think I'm feeling a bit... nervous.
Then, let me make another wish.
What is it?
You just blew out my candles.
Now, you need to be my girlfriend.
Will you?
I
like you.
I think I can make your wish come true.
Xu Fang! What's happening here?
Where's my watch?
-I—
- Let's go out!
You've lost your watch?
- Comrade, hurry up! The leader's on his way here.
- Get lost!
I don't get it! !hy is Lin Xichi here? What's going on with them?
Don't ask me! I don't know.
That... Let's go!
Hi!
Lin Xichi, Xu Fang's had a crush on your for a long time.
You can do it!
Xu Fang, how did you find me?
Since you've been had a crush on me for so long, did you time travel to find me?
Stop flattering yourself!
Why are you still being this fierce? I gave you such a nice present.
That's worth it! You just got yourself a boyfriend like me.
♫ In our long life ♫
Look! You're short-tempered
but you managed to find me as your girlfriend.
I find myself very great!
You should be touched.
♫ Went through the messy youth ♫
Don't worry! I'll take good care of you.
I will never bully you again.
Because I made you who you are after all.
♫ Give my hands into your heart.  ♫
- Catch Up!
- You'd better not let me get you.
♫ Different lives have the same direction  ♫
♫  In the darkest world  ♫
♫ We're the light for each other ♫
Here we are!
♫  Regained all the lost embraces ♫
Go up now.
♫ Don't waste youth  ♫
I'm off.
♫ Withered flowers blossom again ♫
- Goodbye.
- Goodnight!
♫  With sweeter fragrance ♫
♫  Wandered in the crowd ♫
♫ Enjoyed silent moonlight  ♫
♫ By then, I knew what's the most important. ♫
Xu Fang!
♫  Promises don't end, time went back  ♫
♫Don't waste youth ♫
What?
♫ All we missed out, it will arrive  ♫
Xu Fang.
What?
♫  In those years  ♫
- What?
♫ Two persons  ♫
♫ lost beautiful memories  ♫
I find all this so unreal.
♫  Finally became happy ♫
Everything has changed all of a sudden.
♫  Finally became the happiness  ♫
♫  That's our reward  ♫
♫ Promises don't end, time went back ♫
♫ Don't waste youth  ♫
♫  All we missed out, it will arrive ♫
Is this real enough?
♫ The eternity at last  ♫
It's just become more unreal.
♫  In those years ♫
♫ Two persons lost beautiful memories.  ♫
♫  Finally became happy ♫
You're back!
Why are you acting so silly?
♫ That's our reward  ♫
Are you doing yangge? (a form of Chinese folk dance developed from a dance known in the Song dynasty as Village Music)
Tell me, what's the good news? Look at how excited you are!
You're such a big mouth.
Xu Fang and I are in a relationship.
- Really?
- Oh, gosh! You scared me.
Really?
It's you who scared me! That's very quick.
I'm telling you, don't tell anyone else!
What's the next plan?
I wish we'd kiss next year.
Next year?
Three years.
I wish we will kiss after three years.
[Lin Xi Geng]
- Congratulations, you just got yourself a brother-in-law.
- Brother-in-law?
Sister, whom did you choose?
That's fast! Who told you that?
Cut the crap! Tell me the truth.
Who else could it be?
Brother Fang?
Listen here! Don't spread the news.
Keep it between both of us! You heard me?
Of course, I know he's good.
[Lin Xi Geng]
Do you still need my help?
Of course, I do!
[Yes, I need to know the progress of her relationship] .
[I can't let Xu Fang bully her]
How did I get myself into this mess?
[Ending OST: "It's not that Difficult!"]
[ Melody by Qiao Lin - Lyrics by Xueran Chen and Qiao Lin]
♫ Not so difficult! ♫
♫ Making a choice is not so difficult. ♫
♫ It’s all warm and scattered expectation. ♫
♫ Not so difficult! ♫
♫ Making a decision is not so difficult. ♫
♫ Nothing more than day and night mediocre bravery. ♫
♫ People hesitate so they've missed many fulfillment, ♫
♫ always at a loss and in a hurry but feel terribly upset. ♫
♫ It's actually not that difficult. ♫
♫ A smile is really not that difficult. ♫
♫ Unconsciously, we will eventually dry our tears. ♫
♫ It's actually not that difficult. ♫
♫ A promise is really not that difficult. ♫
♫ How could the regret of the past represent today? ♫
♫ It's actually not that difficult. ♫
♫ A hug is really not that difficult. ♫
♫ Our time isn't worthy to be entangled with loneliness. ♫
♫ It's actually not that difficult. ♫
♫ Loving someone is really not that difficult ♫
♫ Even if it hurts, being together or not, ♫
♫ those are all the best moments of life! ♫