Do you feel a little empty inside?
It's a bit hard to let go.
But I know it belongs to the sky.
It doesn't belong to me.
Don't worry, Nana.
Grandpa said,
they are brave spirits of the plateau.
They can fly over the Tianshan Mountains,
over the Taklamakan Desert,
and over the Kunlun Mountains.
Kids,
remember,
a single bird can't cross the snowy mountains.
Mom, where are you going?
Mom is going to the Kunlun Mountains to be a fairy.
Can I go find you then?
Wait until you grow up.
Nana.
Don't come here.
Mom.
I've looked for you so many times.
I came here when I was little.
I've grown up now.
I even know how to tie my shoes.
Nana, Mom knows.
But someone is still waiting for you.
Nana.
What's wrong?
Everyone has one.
Group one, search over there.
Group two, this way.
Group three, the hillside.
Yes, yes.
Nana.
Mom.
Don't fall asleep.
Wake up, let's go home.
Let's go home.
Nana.
Wake up, Nana.
Wake up, wake up.
Let's go home.
In the end,
it led us to the rocks over there.
That's how we found you.
Such a legendary thing happened.
To someone legendary.
If I ever see it again,
I must thank it properly.
If you see it,
please thank it for me too.
Don't make me worry like this again.
Okay?
Okay.
I promise.
I'm sorry.
I made you worry.
Aisha and I,
we've never really competed.
Running businesses on the same street
isn't easy.
We should
look out for each other more,
and compete less.
My barbecue,
everyone on this street knows it.
Hong Shiliu Restaurant has been open for thirty years.
Hong Shiliu is more than just a restaurant.
It's also a symbol for Urumqi,
a benchmark for small restaurants here.
Since Hong Shiliu Restaurant opened,
there's been Free Pilaf seats.
I remember it clearly.
On opening day,
a few of us old friends
bought a table together
and brought it to the restaurant.
That very day,
we met a
customer in trouble.
Aisha not only let him eat for free,
she turned that table into the Free Pilaf table.
All these years,
so many customers
ate a free pilaf from Aisha
and found the strength to move on.
Don't worry, Mingliang.
Ankar took great photos.
He even shot two videos.
Kept one as backup.
Don't praise me.
Dong guided me the whole time.
Bro.
When are you coming back?
The doctor will check in soon.
If everything's fine,
we can go home tomorrow.
Alright.
Sister Nana,
come back soon.
I'll make you something delicious.
I'll make sure you get a good meal.
Okay.
Make lots of tasty food for me!
During this time,
you two have worked hard.
When I get back,
I'll gather all the info you collected
and combine it with what Mr. Hu found.
We'll go see Lawyer Tian together.
Is Mr. Hu also looking for evidence?
Mr. Hu and I
want to get our two million back.
Can we do it?
Let's give it a try.
You never know.
Alright, I'll stay with Nana first.
I'll stop chatting now.
We'll talk in person when I'm back.
Okay, goodbye.
It's my fault you had to sell the house.
I know Old Mu
feels awkward living in Hu Yue's new place.
So you guys
have been looking for a place.
It's a bit small here,
but I've tidied it up.
Three people can squeeze in.
After all, we're all at the restaurant.
We can look out for each other.
I've already bought the bed.
It'll be delivered today.
If you really mind,
I... I can move out.
Alright.
Okay, I'll move out this afternoon.
No, no, that's not what I meant.
You...
You've already bought the bed.
My dad and I both hate wasting things.
Okay.
Then...
Let's split up and handle things separately.
You go to Hu Yue's and pack up your things.
What about you?
I need to go to the notary office.
Ask them to come along.
Get the evidence from Fang Tao's shop.
Like the storefront,
the signboard,
and the decorations.
We need to compare all of them.
I'll also gather the photos I have
and the videos,
plus data from major websites.
I'll compile everything.
Then submit it all to the court.
Okay.
Let's go, let's go.
What?
Withdraw investment?
Boss Fang.
What I mean is,
please return my five hundred thousand principal.
I asked when the second round of funds would arrive.
But you immediately talk about withdrawing.
And mention that five hundred thousand principal.
Where is the principal?
Tables, chairs, ceiling—
all of these are the principal.
Are you out of your mind?
Jianping.
What do you think this place is?
I'm running a legitimate business here.
Not some small workshop.
Old Liu,
let me be honest with you.
Lately,
I've contacted a few wealthy friends.
They all want to invest.
Don't forget,
you're one of the shareholders too.
If you withdraw now,
what does that look like?
You're undermining me, you know?
Right now, Anton
is itching to sue us.
I'm telling you,
don't start infighting with me now.
Boss Fang,
I'll be honest with you.
Back then,
when you asked me to set up Anton,
I felt uneasy about it.
I couldn't sleep at night.
Now we've set up
a knockoff Hong•Shiliu.
Trying to take down the real Hong Shiliu.
This... this isn't right.
How is it not right?
They're called Hong Shiliu.
We're Hong•Shiliu.
Is it the same?
Bo—Boss Fang,
I'm grateful you helped me make money.
It's just lately
I've had some cash flow issues.
You have problems,
I don't have any.
Let me tell you, Liu Jianping,
you and I
signed a contract.
Your signature is right there in black and white.
If you want your principal back,
that's possible.
Want to withdraw?
Fine.
But that's a clear breach of contract.
What,
you want to be like Anton
and pay triple the penalty?
That's not what you said before.
When you brought me in as a shareholder,
you said I could withdraw my funds anytime.
Did I say that?
Did I ever say that?
When did I say that?
If you insist,
Boss Fang,
please don't get mad.
Just pretend
I never said anything.
Alright.
That's more like it.
You'd better hope now
our Hong•Shiliu Restaurant
gets more and more prosperous.
And the money
keeps piling up.
You'll count cash till your hand cramps.
I'll head back now.
So greedy,
yet so timid.
Just right.
I bought you two quilts.
If they're not thick enough,
I'll get you more.
Why worry about this?
Mingliang asked you back
for this kind of thing?
Use your time to figure out
how to win back all our customers.
Old Mu,
it's getting late.
Why don't you go freshen up first?
You and Mulati's dad
even did a deep cleaning.
Alright.
To show my thanks,
I'll give you a big gift too.
Cheers!
But let me tell you,
I read your letter.
In your letter,
you only mentioned Mingliang's hard work
and Aisha mom's health.
Why didn't you mention me?
Is our relationship not good?
Am I not worth mentioning
in your heart?
Dad, um...
It's getting late.
Why don't you go rest upstairs?
It's the first day, so it'll feel strange.
But we'll get used to it.
Go ahead.
Um...
Your business journal—
can I borrow it to read?
Of course.
Just go and take it.
Also,
I have lots of other books in my room.
Whatever you want to read,
just help yourself.
Okay.
Thanks, Dong.
Smells so good.
About the restaurant.
Teach Ankar more.
He’s improving fast as a chef.
Management
Still has a long way to go.
No.
You
still trust me
and let me take care of your son?
What I trust
isn’t you.
It’s my son.
Old Liu,
what do you think?
We’re back!
You’re back.
Everyone’s moved in.
That’s great.
Really great.
On the intellectual property side,
the evidence chain is solid.
But
the investment contract
is tricky to handle.
It’s fine.
Let’s prepare for this lawsuit first.
That’s enough to give him trouble.
If I’d known we couldn’t get back the two million,
I should’ve recorded
when signing the contract.
Fang Tao wouldn’t leave such obvious evidence.
It’s okay.
By the way,
there’s more good news.
Last night,
pretty late,
Liu Jianping called me.
He agreed
to testify in court and make amends.
Good.
That’s great!
So,
I’ll make a call.
I’ll set up a meeting with Lawyer Tian.
Does that work?
I’ll contact Liu Jianping.
I’ll get in touch with Liu Jianping.
Have him meet the lawyer together.
Right?
Sure, sure.
Let’s go.
Ankar,
go see the lawyer with Dong.
Okay.
Get some rest early.
Now we have witnesses
and physical evidence.
We’ve got it all.
The IP case looks solid.
What about the investment agreement?
Mr. Liu,
let me confirm again.
When Fang Tao approached you,
he promised to help you recover
the one million loan Anton owed you.
After it was done,
he gave you a hundred thousand as a kickback.
Is that right?
Yes.
Do you have any evidence?
When I talked to him,
I recorded it.
Jianping, if this works out,
I’ll treat you well.
Alright.
If the evidence holds up,
this is
a classic case of malicious collusion
harming a third party’s interests.
I’ll organize the materials I have.
File the lawsuit as soon as possible.
I’m telling you,
with this evidence,
we’re set.
Really set.
Bro,
it’s not a big problem.
Okay.
Pack up your things
and move into my room.
Why?
You three are squeezed into one room.
Isn’t it crowded?
I’m studying, aren’t I?
I have lots of questions
to ask Dong.
Alright then.
Up to you.
Anytime.
Okay.
Mingliang,
I’ve made up my mind.
I’ve decided.
Decided what?
What are you two talking about now?
As long as you’ve decided.
I’ll send some materials to Lawyer Tian.
They’ll be useful in court.
Alright.
Bro,
What’s our plan next?
What do you think?
I think
I should follow your plan.
while we wait for the verdict,
our restaurant
still needs to run.
So I have an idea.
Dong filmed some videos before.
Let’s re-edit them
and make a Hong Shiliu brand story.
Then,
ask Guangtian to make a QR code.
Everyone at the restaurant
can scan and watch.
Isn’t this intellectual property?
Good lad.
Nice!
Don’t underestimate me, okay?
I really didn’t like studying before.
But look at me now—
I’m so self-motivated.
Not just reading books,
I even study Dong’s notes.
Let’s do it your way.
Ankar,
you’ll run the restaurant from now on.
If you’re unsure,
talk it over with Dong.
What about you?
The restaurant’s been open so long,
you’ve forgotten I’m a painter, right?
I still owe a few paintings.
I need to finish them.
Don’t tell me you’re painting apples again.
Bro,
do you think I can do it?
You’re a young and ambitious lad.
Online, they say
this is the gentlest time
in Urumqi.
Whenever I have time
I'll come here with you.
Really.
Nana,
there's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
I want to rethink
my own future.
This time, it's not for Mom,
not for the restaurant,
it's what I truly want
after thinking it over.
Because I don't know
what the future holds,
I want to hear your thoughts.
But
no matter what comes next,
no matter which path I take,
I'll hold your hand
and never let go.
Go do what you want.
I'm here for you.
Thank you.
Nana.
Top up two thousand yuan
to unlock the secret menu.
Can I still join this event?
Sorry,
that's not our restaurant.
Look,
we're Hong Shiliu Restaurant.
That one has a dot in the name.
Isn't that your branch?
No, we don't have any branches.
And look,
we have an open kitchen.
You can see how every dish
is prepared.
We've never had
any secret menu or anything.
Hong Shiliu Restaurant.
Hong•Shiliu.
It's way too easy
to get confused.
Don't you think?
Yes, yes.
How about this—
scan this QR code.
It has
the real Hong Shiliu brand story.
Take a look.
Alright, alright.
Okay.
That's all for now, okay?
Coming, coming!
Here you go!
Fried pork noodles.
Six skewers of kebab, here!
That's awesome! (Xinjiang dialect)
Who came up with
such a clever idea?
Lately, our restaurant
has been doing much better.
It wasn't my idea.
Who was it?
It was Ankar's suggestion.
Mulati,
one big plate chicken,
two rice.
Okay.
Ankar.
Why are you looking at me?
Go on.
A bunch of dishonest people.
I had the contract ready.
They just backed out.
No integrity at all.
Boss Fang,
they probably heard
Hong Shiliu is suing us.
They're scared.
If you want a golden bowl,
you've got to take risks.
So what do we do now?
People's Court.
Call Liu Jianping.
Hello,
the number you dialed
is busy.
He hung up.
Call again.
Hello,
the number you dialed
is busy.
That rascal Liu Jianping
actually stabbed me
in the back.
I'm contacting a lawyer
right now.
Liu Jianping.
That kid Ankar
is really talented.
Lately,
he's like a whole new person.
He's doing great.
I can finally relax.
Mingliang can truly
let go now.
Of course.
I called everyone here today
to go over
the art exhibition venue.
Nana and I searched
for a venue for you,
we ran our legs off.
Mingliang,
I also looked online
for some options.
But I think
none of them are suitable.
I asked several places too,
but none would take it.
I get it.
I'm not famous.
And I can't afford
their venue fees.
Most importantly,
I can't confirm
the exact date
for my exhibition.
It depends on my painting progress.
Basically, professional venues
probably won't accept me.
Don't get discouraged.
Keep searching.
If professional venues
don't work out,
maybe we try a new approach.
I saw online that some people
hold art shows in cafes.
Maybe this place
is a good choice?
An art show in a cafe—
low cost and good traffic.
Art and life blend together.
If a cafe can host an art show,
why not a restaurant too?
Would you like extra noodles?
No, that's fine. No extra noodles.
Alright.
Hello.
Add one order of stir-fried morel
with meat.
Okay, got it.
One oil-seared meat noodles.
No extra noodles.
And one stir-fried morel
with meat.
Barbecue's here.
It's hot, it's hot.
Come on, eat while it's hot.
Waiter.
What do you need?
Two barbecues.
No problem.
Waiter.
Add one wheat gluten here.
Okay.
Two barbecues.
One wheat gluten.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Welcome.
Looks really real, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Actually, it's fake.
What nonsense!
Really nice.
Sadik Dad.
Nana.
Mingliang.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
A gift for you.
Congrats on your art exhibition.
Soulmate.
Thank you.
I'll take Dad to see the paintings first.
Alright.
Sister Nana.
Sadik Dad.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
This is the Hong Shiliu Restaurant.
Sorry about that.
We're not open today.
We're holding an art exhibition.
We're here for the exhibition.
Look.
You're a fan of the blogger?
Been following for so long.
Finally get to see the real work.
Come in, come in!
What's wrong, bro?
Are you worried about Dong?
A little.
If once doesn't work, try twice.
We'll definitely get a fair result.
Alright, great artist.
Stop worrying.
Lots of new faces today.
Go take care of them.
Let's go.
Ankar.
Get me a drink.
I've seen many paintings
of the Kunlun Mountains.
Some are rugged and strong,
some are majestic and lofty,
some are mysterious and deep.
But yours is different.
There's warmth in the vastness.
Powerful yet still serene.
Very powerful.
Thank you for your encouragement.
My name is Mingliang.
Mingliang.
Yes.
That's a nice name.
That decorative painting
feels very commercial.
Is that yours too?
Yes.
To be honest,
I painted those
just to make money.
But putting them here
isn't very harmonious.
It kind of ruins the exhibition's artistry.
But,
you're really bold.
Aren't you afraid that one day,
as an artist,
these paintings
will bring criticism?
Honestly,
I've struggled with it for a long time.
But every painting here
is a part of my life.
The people I've met,
the scenery I've seen,
the stories I've lived,
they're all my journey.
These paintings belong here.
Even if they seem a bit out of place,
they're real.
In art,
sincerity matters most.
That's interesting.
Secretary Xu, any instructions?
Mingliang.
Let me tell you something.
Did the art academy director
visit your exhibition?
The director?
Is he in his fifties?
Speaks slowly and calmly?
Yes, that's him.
This year,
it's the 70th anniversary
of the autonomous region.
Our publicity department
and the art academy
want to co-host an exhibition.
We hope these paintings
can fully showcase Xinjiang.
I know about that.
It's gathering works from everywhere.
But I heard
the exhibition pieces
are already set?
Yes.
They're basically chosen.
But,
we all agree
it's missing a painting that
shows the Kunlun Mountains
from a new angle.
I've seen your Kunlun Mountains.
I recommended you to the director.
That's why he stood in front of
"Kunlun Morning Light"
for so long.
Yes.
The director will have someone
contact you.
Xu Lai.
I really
thank you.
No need to thank me.
Without a talented horse,
even a good judge is useless.
If you thank anyone,
thank yourself.
Alright.
That's all.
Just this.
I'll get back to work.
Thank you for coming.
And thank you so much for testifying.
I'm not doing this just for you.
It's also for my daughter.
I don't want
my daughter to have a dad she dislikes.
By doing this,
Yaya will definitely be proud of you.
As for Fang Tao and me,
we'll return the two million penalty
back to you.
The fake Hong•Shiliu
has also been ordered to fix things.
Luckily, Hong Shiliu
is still Hong Shiliu.
Yes.
What are your plans next?
I've had enough of all this.
I've stayed long enough.
I miss home.
I have a friend
who's run a restaurant for over ten years.
He's a very reliable person.
If you're interested,
I can connect you.
Introduce you to each other.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Their restaurant
isn't doing great right now,
but
he's truly sincere.
I think it's worth considering.
Really.
You can give it a try.
Let me share some good news.
It's finally coming to an end.
The money should arrive soon.
That's great!
That's great, wonderful news!
Thank you, everyone.
We really appreciate you, bro.
Dad, we can buy a house now.
A villa.
We can't afford a villa yet.
Last time I went to Sister Yueyue's
and checked out their neighborhood.
It's pretty nice.
Really?
Maybe we should think about it.
Sure.
Then we'll come over for meals often!
Bro,
aren't you and Nana thinking about it?
We haven't planned that far ahead.
Right.
Our short-term plan
is to travel Xinjiang with our parents.
Try the pike Nana keeps recommending.
Aisha, I'm so jealous of you.
When I retire,
I'll take you there.
You said it!
I've got my little sweetheart too.
It's not like anyone's missing one.
Right?
Me too.
On such a wonderful day,
let's take a photo.
Yes, yes!
We must capture this moment.
Um,
how about we
stand under the pomegranate tree
for a big group photo?
Good, good!
Mingliang,
then you can paint it.
Okay.
Yueyue,
let's go get ready.
Yes, yes!
Let's go, let's go! Sounds good.
Aisha,
let's go, let's get ready.
Right?
Okay, Dad.
Mingliang, when you
Mingliang, when you were little,
just one apple as a kid.
I remember my first time at Hong Shiliu,
I sat right here.
Had Free Pilaf.
I finished one plate,
then ordered lamb chops,
and got rice two more times.
Bayar was so annoyed
he kept rolling his eyes at me.
Now,
all the problems are solved.
Hong Shiliu is getting better and better.
I should also
You weren't here when we picked pomegranates.
Bayar saved this one just for you.
Here.
Time for a photo!
Photo time!
Hurry, hurry!
Let's go!
I'll sit here.
Slow down.
Okay.
Ten-second countdown.
Look at the camera, don't move.
Papa Hu,
you're too serious.
Let's all shout together.
Is the pomegranate sweet?
Sweet!