Mom
What pattern is this?
It's a pomegranate.
This fabric feels so smooth.
It's really comfortable.
This isn't ordinary fabric.
It's Adilais Silk.
Mom's wedding dress.
So beautiful.
Did Dad give it to you?
It was from someone else important.
Sister Hatiman.
Xu Lai.
No.
You're Secretary Xu, aren't you?
You two know each other?
Yes.
Sister Hatiman.
So you didn't invest that one million?
Ha, Sister Hatiman.
That one million.
Did you give it to the restaurant?
What about this one million?
It was when I divorced An Dong.
Splitting my assets.
I didn't like how he ran things.
I worried something would go wrong.
So I never touched that money.
After Secretary Xu arrived,
he focused on saving our cooperative.
The cooperative is the village's mainstay.
Mom was chosen as the legal representative.
I truly wanted
to invest this one million in the cooperative.
But...
An Dong caused big trouble again.
Most importantly,
the one affected was Aisha.
I really couldn't just stand by.
It's okay.
I'll think of another way.
As for me,
I happened to contact my old factory boss.
Boss Qian.
I briefly told him
about our cooperative's situation.
He
agreed to meet with us.
He's on a business trip in Chengdu now.
Before returning to Jiangsu,
he'll fly here once.
He should arrive this afternoon.
If we can make this deal,
there'll be plenty of orders.
Alright.
Let's try to secure the orders first.
Then, Sister Hatiman,
please send me Boss Qian's info.
I'll do some research in advance.
Okay.
Alright, you two talk.
I'm leaving.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Ming Liang.
This has nothing to do with you.
Don't worry too much.
I...
I'll handle it.
Alright.
Secretary Xu.
The sheep's been found.
Come on.
Let's return it quickly.
I've checked it.
Its horn is injured.
It almost ran into the desert.
What's wrong with its leg?
You should check my legs instead.
I've run three times this month.
Tell the old man,
if it runs off again, don't look for it.
I'll buy him a well-behaved one.
Secretary Xu.
This guy's really pitiful.
It's about a girlfriend.
He can't find one.
He can't win fights with other rams.
So he ran away in anger.
Alright, alright.
Return it to the old man quickly.
I'm off to eat.
It's midday.
I haven't even eaten yet.
Xu Lai.
What trouble is the cooperative facing?
I came to ask you
if I can help with anything.
This is an internal township matter.
It's not convenient to share with outsiders.
Ming Liang.
I know about you and Nana.
I respect Nana's choice.
I do have feelings.
But they're not directed at you.
It's not because I can't let Nana go.
It's because of that money.
It affects all of Yipoke Township.
And its future development.
I hope you understand.
I know.
Your company,
mainly targets
young urban consumers.
Adilais Silk is a traditional craft,
but in recent years,
it's been trying
to blend with modern fashion.
See,
these big brands
also use Adilais Silk elements.
The traditional pattern craft,
is truly exquisite.
But,
it's just too outdated.
It's hard to promote.
Hatiman,
you've worked at our factory
as a mid-level manager for years.
Your professional skills
I know them well.
It's because I trust you
that I came here today.
You've worked in marketing for years.
You know better than anyone
old things,
no matter how good they are,
if there's no innovation,
they can't match modern tastes.
They'll definitely be eliminated.
Okay, Boss Qian.
I'll discuss it with my mom.
It's just the timing.
Yes, Boss Qian.
Please give us a bit more time.
We can improve this design plan.
Right now,
time is the one thing I can't give.
The market competition is fierce.
I don't have time
to wait for your redesign.
Secretary Xu,
sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
So,
right now,
I need to visit other factories.
I won't take up your time.
Boss Qian, please wait a moment.
We
have a finished design draft.
I'll go get it now.
Xiao Ai, come here.
Quickly,
let Boss Qian try our Hotan herbal tea.
No matter what it takes,
we must make him stay.
Grandma Parida,
can you make this pattern?
Is it possible to make?
It's self-designed.
Yes.
We have so many Atlas silk patterns.
None of them appeal to you?
No,
I just want to make
one I designed myself.
He's trying to please his girlfriend.
A unique one shows sincerity.
Let me take a good look.
Hatiman,
what's up with this car?
Uh, uh...
Can you ask him to move it?
Let me out first.
Okay.
I'll talk to him.
Boss Qian looks so serious.
How did you work under him
for so many years?
What did he say?
He praised you.
Said you're dignified.
You look like a cultured businessman.
He also said you're my friend.
I'm his friend.
A friend's friend is a friend.
So he plans
to treat you to roast whole lamb.
With our unique Hotan method,
stuffing lamb fat in the belly,
piyazi (Xinjiang dialect for onion),
then roasting it.
The skin turns golden and crispy.
It's really delicious.
So, so tasty.
That's too kind.
So warm.
He said so much.
I just polished it a bit.
Xiangxiang is for tourists' photos.
It's not for eating.
What did he say?
He, he said
he specially found you
an unmarried lamb.
It's our highest honor.
for welcoming distinguished guests.
Thank you, thank you.
I appreciate your hospitality.
But I'm really in a hurry.
I...
This lamb,
I'll buy it.
I'll take it away.
Move your car.
I'm leaving first.
I'll tell him.
If you really make him stay,
what if he eats Xiangxiang?
Don't worry, bro.
We won't eat your lamb.
Mingliang,
Mingliang.
Nana.
Let me borrow this painting.
I'll explain later.
Xu.
Hello, Ankaer.
Bro,
let me tell you,
Fang Tao, that jerk,
opened a knockoff of our restaurant.
I'll show you.
Boss Qian, Boss Qian
Jump, jump, jump
I—I'm in a hurry
That's how warm we are in Xinjiang
Th-this...
If I'd known you'd go this far
to get what you want
Back then,
I shouldn't have let you quit
Oh, come on, Boss Qian
If we work together this time
I'll work for you in Hetian too
Alright, alright
Secretary Xu
Sister Hatiman and I
managed to keep Boss Qian here
Good
Boss Qian
So that's how you kept me here
Sister Hatiman came up with the idea
She invited her warmest Xinjiang friends
So warm, so warm
But I'm in a hurry
I have to go
Boss Qian, sorry to keep you waiting
Sorry for the wait
Secretary Xu
You all are just too warm
Yes, yes
Boss Qian, take a look at this
Take a look
This—this is interesting
Your Atlas silk before
was too bold in color
But this design
keeps the Atlas silk elements
and adds a lot of trendy touches
Young women will definitely love it
I've been in silk for years
Never thought about this direction
Nice, nice, very nice
This is good
Just—just this one?
Yes
To be honest, Boss Qian
This designer
is a big name
Very gifted artistically
And knows Xinjiang's culture
extremely well
It took me ages to get him on board
Our budget
only covers this one design
I understand, I do
But if we want to work together
One design isn't nearly enough
Yes, yes
If in the future
your designs can all
keep this style
and add trendy elements
I'll order more from you
It's possible
That's all we need to hear
Good
Goodbye, Boss Qian
Make more designs
Next time, I'll treat you to roast lamb
How was that, Secretary Xu?
Did I act well just now?
This is—
His name is Muzapati
He's from Hetian
the best travel photographer here
Hello, hello
Thank you
Thank you so much
No problem, it's my duty
Call me if you need anything
I'm always available
Alright
Thank you, thank you
We're leaving, Secretary Xu
Goodbye, goodbye
Goodbye
Alright, let's go
Secretary Xu
Between you and Ming Liang
I feel like there's something going on
Mingliang, did you see that?
No wonder Buli was surprised.
He even came to congratulate us.
He said they opened some kind of branch.
I was all muddle-headed about it.
I didn't figure it out.
Now I finally get it.
Come on.
Look at the color of that door.
And that signboard.
Hong Shiliu
It's exactly the same as ours.
What Hong Shiliu?
Why do they get to call it Hong Shiliu?
Isn't this just copying?
Can we sue them?
Is it possible to sue them?
It's not Hong Shiliu.
Look, everyone.
There's a dot in the middle.
A lot of knockoff shops do this.
It's hard to sue for this, kind of tricky.
Seems like it.
Yeah.
There really is a dot.
Wait, wait.
Let me take a closer look.
Ankar
Check out that sign.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
Just like the one at our place.
The free Aisha pilaf sign.
It's exactly the same.
Mingliang, look quickly.
Even the one they use
Our Aisha free sign
is just like ours.
They even copied this.
Using Aisha's goodwill sign for business.
They've got no conscience at all.
Dad, dad.
Keep your voice down.
Mulati, Dad.
Please don't get worked up.
Everyone's watching us.
They're hoping we'll make a scene.
Can't curse.
Can't fight.
Can't sue either.
Isn't this just bullying?
Don't say anything.
They've spotted us.
Ankar.
I said, take notes.
Got it, I'll note it down.
Come on, hurry up.
First,
Take clear photos of all the evidence.
Signboard.
Menu.
Dishes.
Flyers.
Don't miss a single thing.
Second,
Contact Hu Dad.
He knows a lawyer.
Ask about defending our restaurant's rights.
Bro, wait, wait.
Can you explain slowly?
My mind is totally blank right now.
I can't remember all this.
Yeah, yeah.
Slow down, slow down.
Wait, what was the second thing?
We agreed you'd run the restaurant.
But here I am giving orders again.
Ankar.
Tell us what you think.
My thoughts?
As soon as I got here,
I saw this restaurant.
Now I'm all flustered.
I don't even know what to say.
I have no ideas right now.
Don't panic yet.
Just think it through.
No rush.
Bro.
I've realized now
I'm really not cut out to be the boss.
Who says that?
When we renovated the restaurant,
your ideas were great.
Bro.
I was just pretending.
Just messing around.
Otherwise, how could
things get so messed up?
Let me tell you all,
if you ever have something really big,
don't ever put me in charge.
I'm afraid I'll mess it up for you.
This Fang Tao issue
won't be solved in a day or two.
Let's take it slow.
But right now, there's one thing
you need to decide.
An Dong went back early.
He guessed Fang Tao would cause trouble.
He said he wanted to help out.
But whether he stays or goes,
it's up to you.
An Dong.
I don't want to see him again.
Bro.
You decide this.
You're in charge now.
It's your call.
Let me think about it.
Take your time.
Stay calm, don't panic.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Okay.
I've got something to handle here.
I'll hang up now.
Are you Mr. Mingliang?
Secretary Xu asks you to come over.
Mr. Mingliang.
I heard you.
He should come himself.
Secretary Xu was worried you'd be upset.
He asked me to explain first.
He'll apologize to you in person soon.
Go and check it out.
We'll talk about the restaurant later.
Talk it out calmly.
Don't argue.
The specific situation
you already know as well.
Taking your painting
was thoughtless of me.
But it all happened so fast,
I didn't have time to explain.
Is Secretary Xu asking me for help?
If you're willing to do the series design,
you set the design fee.
Copyright stays with you.
We only want priority production rights.
Secretary Xu is really flexible.
But I have a lot to handle at my restaurant.
I have to go back early tomorrow.
I can't take this job.
If you need,
I can recommend a designer to you.
But they want your work.
No one else will do.
Ming Liang
Unless I have no other choice,
I wouldn't ask you.
The pattern design for that painting,
I can draw it for you separately.
But for the series design,
I really don't have time.
Or the energy.
Sketchbook
Alright.
I won't take advantage of you.
You'll get the design fee.
Don't worry, it's not broken.
What does that mean?
What do you mean?
What does this mean?
This is Aman’s notebook.
You both have the same notebook.
Aman was here.
Probably took the wrong one.
Aman isn't home.
No one at her classmate’s house either.
Abu, hurry up!
This is Sister Zhang’s car.
She delivers to the county’s restaurants
with beef every day.
I know where Aman is.
I’ll go to the county.
Secretary
Our car was lent out.
I’ll drive you there.
Hurry up.
Hello.
Hello, ma’am.
Your child is over one point two meters.
You need to buy a full ticket.
What child?
Your child.
She’s not my child.
Little one,
isn't this your mom?
Aman
Uncle Xu
How did you get here by yourself?
Can you take me to Urumqi?
I want to see my mom.
I have money.
I can buy my own ticket.
Aman
Let’s go back first.
Why wasn’t this child watched?
What if she got lost?
Sorry.
Sorry for the trouble.
Come on, come on.
Come on, let’s keep checking tickets.
Aman
I’m not leaving.
I want to find my mom.
I dealt with kids a lot in college.
Let me try.
Aman
You’re a brave boy.
You need to behave.
I’m a girl.
See, my clothes are all pink.
Can’t you tell?
It’s grandma’s fault.
She cut my hair.
When mom was home,
she always braided my hair nicely.
I miss my mom.
I want to go find my mom.
Ming Liang, I miss my mom.
I...
I want to go find her.
Nana, don’t cry.
Come here.
Aman, it’s okay.
It’s all right.
How about this—
Does this sound good?
Uncle promises you,
this weekend,
Uncle will take you to Urumqi to find your mom.
Okay?
Really?
Of course it’s true.
When has Uncle ever lied to you?
Sorry about that.
I didn't realize Aman was a girl.
She used to wear lots of little braids.
Then,
her parents left for Urumqi to work.
Her grandma found washing her hair troublesome.
She cut it while Aman was asleep.
Can't really blame grandma.
She's getting old.
She can barely care for herself.
How could she look after a child?
So how did you know she'd go to the station?
Because of her drawing.
Aman still looks lovely now.
Look, uncle's hair is even shorter than yours.
Doesn't it look good too?
But...
But Secretary Xu's haircut is the ugliest.
Looks like a sheep chewed it.
Alright.
I had a dream last night.
I dreamed my mom came back.
I went to the bus station to meet her.
She brought me lots of pretty hair clips.
One was a glowing butterfly clip.
This big.
Pink.
But I don't have long hair anymore.
So Aman,
just draw this dream.
Show it to your mom when she returns.
How about that?
When mom sees the drawing,
she'll know I miss her every day.
Then she won't leave again.
Right?
As parents,
how could they not know their child is hurting?
But there's nothing they can do.
They really can't come back.
Even on weekends,
if Aman visits her mom,
it's just a temporary fix.
That's why you want
to make the cooperative succeed.
So they can earn money at home.
Yes.
Aman has a close friend.
Her mom also gets patterns from the cooperative.
She makes Adilais Silk at home.
But business isn't good.
She can't make money.
She's mentioned it to me more than once.
She wants to quit.
Go work elsewhere.
If she leaves too,
her child
might become the next Aman.
We grew up with our parents around,
so it's hard to understand how Aman feels.
You know,
that day,
Aman held her hair in her hands,
crying,
begging me to put it back.
It broke my heart.
I thought,
no matter what,
I must make the cooperative work.
So her mom can come home.
That feeling you described,
I understand it.
Xu Lai,
about this,
I'll think it over carefully.
Child,
Mom doesn't understand art.
But mom knows
when you're upset,
you can't make tasty pilaf.
I really was too impatient.
Ming Liang,
stay in Hetian.
When Hong Shiliu was struggling most,
Sister Hatiman gave a million
to help us keep our home.
We should help her keep her home too.
Not just Sister Hatiman.
If we save the cooperative,
we can save more
homes for kids like Aman.
You actually know deep down.
You've already made your choice.
But about the restaurant,
I'm still really worried.
Then you really can't go back.
Ankar relies on you a lot now.
If you go back,
he'll listen to you for everything.
He'll be even less likely to decide for himself.
He's a boy.
He can't always hide behind his brother.
You're right.
He should face things on his own.
But...
I can't just wash my hands of it.
I've already contacted
Hu Baba's lawyer friend.
Asked him to look over
An Dong's investment contract.
He got back to me saying
the contract does have loopholes.
Evidence.
The compensation amount in the contract is unreasonable.
We can start from that point.
This time our restaurant is opening.
I can't feel happy at all.
Originally, our restaurant's sign
should be called Hong Shiliu No. 1 Branch.
But in the end,
these tough folks
actually scraped together three million.
They really managed to hold on.
Our restaurant's sign
can only be called just Hong Shiliu.
Boss Fang,
the name is so similar.
Won't we get sued for this?
Jianping,
you know,
you're a good person,
but you're too timid.
Even if they want to sue us,
it's hard for them to gather evidence.
The process is slow, too.
If that kid really has evidence,
it'll take at least two or three years.
They paid us this three million,
no idea how they scraped it together.
Where did they get it from?
Plus, now the suppliers
are pushing them to settle up.
So tell me,
will they sue or protect their business?
Jianping,
even if we take a big step back,
what if they win the lawsuit?
By then, our profits
will have covered the compensation.
These country bumpkins
don't know business at all.
They just act on emotion.
Without An Dong,
they're nothing.
Ankar,
you promised your brother
to stay calm.
How can I stay calm?
Just looking at him annoys me.
Ankar,
Laomu,
don't hold him back.
If you want to hit me, go ahead.
I accept it.
I deserve all of this.
But I hope
after you hit me, you'll let me speak.
About how to solve the Fang Tao issue.
If you don't want me to stay,
I'll leave right now.
If you still do,
I'll do my best to help the restaurant.
You said you accept it.
Then remember this.
We didn't beat you this time
because everyone wants to give you a chance.
If you can't handle Fang Tao,
you won't escape a beating.
Go ahead,
how will you solve the problem?
If Fang Tao
takes the three million and leaves,
maybe
we'll just have to swallow the loss.
But he's greedy.
He opened a competing restaurant
to put us out of business.
But this actually gives us
a chance to strike back.
We can use
the anti-unfair competition law against him.
But the key is getting evidence.
Find where he
misleads customers
and maliciously copies us.
Would you
like to hear the details?
Your things are untouched.
You want to stay.
Then stay.
Mingliang,
Nana sent you a package.
Open it and take a look.
Nana—
How did she know about Aman?
You told her.
Nana kept asking
about you, in every way.
I need to stay here a few more days.
Nana,
I need your help.
What's wrong?
I'm helping them design
patterns for Adilais Silk.
But I feel something's missing.
This one
was inspired by Bogda Peak under pink sunset.
What do you think?
My mom told me a legend.
She said Adilais Silk's earliest inspiration
came from ripples on water.
If you imagine the pink sunset
as pink lake water,
and Bogda Peak as a stone dropped in,
wouldn't that be even better?
Cut it out.
When you come back,
we still need to talk.
You're right about everything.
Hetian—
What is he up to?
Their restaurant is almost crushed by me.
Why is Mingliang in Hetian
just painting so leisurely?
No, that's not right.
This isn't as simple as it seems.
What's he really planning?
You know, before,
we calculated
they couldn't get three million in ten days.
But that kid still managed to pull it off.
Mingliang is quite something.
Don't underestimate him.
Bro, look—
their decor here,
the dishes, the menu,
even the sign,
all copied from our restaurant.
Fang Tao is way too bold.
This one's pretty good.
The kitchen shot is clear, too.
This entrance—
Take another photo of it.
Alright.
Shoot one more, one more.
Film the whole thing.
An Dong.
That's enough filming, right?
What do you want?
Here's the thing, An Dong.
Fang Tao gave special instructions.
He insists you catch up with him.
Fang Tao.
We have an honored guest.
An Dong.
So many talented people from Jiangdong.
A comeback might be in the cards.
What wind
blew An Dong here today?
Fang Tao.
An Dong is really interested
in our restaurant.
He's been filming downstairs nonstop.
An Dong.
I always thought you were smart.
Why use such a dumb way
to film my restaurant?
And you drank, too.
I thought after talking with Fang Tao so long,
you'd switched sides,
joined forces with him.
Their Hong Shiliu restaurant
won't last much longer.
And you're still working for him.
What's the point?
At least he
helped pay off three million for me.
I have to work for them
to pay off my debt.
But me, An Dong,
I'm confident
if I want,
a second, third,
even a fourth Hong Shiliu,
I can open them all.
Alright.
That's what I admire about you.
Ming Liang still has time to paint in Hetian.
He's not cut out for business.
You and I,
strong together,
would be great.
If you join me,
I'll return those two million right away.
Fang Tao.
Don't set me up again.
Can you really pay me back?
Of course.
I gave you a chance before.
This is the second time.
Third time's the charm. It's your choice.
Hey, Baokun.
What do you mean by this?
Where's An Dong?
To keep his taste sharp,
he never touches alcohol.
I've known him nearly ten years.
Big and small dinners,
we've attended plenty together.
I've never seen him drink.
He never does things just to please others.
Alright.
I get it.
An Dong.
My door
is always open for you.
Do you think he'll believe it?
Just play along.
Make him drop his guard.
Let's stick to the plan.
I've found something even bigger.
When the time comes,
I'll tell Ming Liang too.
Take me to get some antacid first.
I'm really uncomfortable.
Fang Tao.
Can we trust what he says?
Herbal tea with baked naan
is the classic Hetian breakfast.
My mom's from Hetian.
That's right.
We gathered veteran tea masters from the herbal tea factory.
They serve tea for free at the Grand Bazaar.
I'll have Aizezi pack some for you to take back.
Try it at your restaurant.
If it tastes good,
make it your restaurant's specialty.
It'll help the tea factory too.
Thank you.
You've changed a lot.
A lot.
What's wrong?
Darker.
Uglier.
More rustic.
No.
Your personality.
We haven't spent much time together,
but back in Urumqi,
you seemed humble,
but always felt above everyone.
Now,
you're more down-to-earth.
Alright.
I'll take that as a compliment.
So,
about the pattern design,
have you thought it over?