Ming Liang
There are rivers in the desert too.
Of course.
Watch me.
Ming Liang, you're amazing!
Ankar is too scared to jump.
Ankar is a coward.
That's awesome!
Ming Liang
I want to jump in too.
You can jump off my shoulders.
Say something, what's going on?
You.
Go ahead, say it.
Murat
Speak.
Murat, Murat.
Murat
An Dong
You need to make yourself clear.
Only then can we help you.
Do you understand what I mean?
Let me say this.
I'll tell you everything from the start.
When I first started out,
when I started my business,
I began with a small restaurant too.
That restaurant
wasn't even half the size of Hong Shiliu.
Driven by my love for food,
bit by bit,
I built it up slowly.
Finally, I turned a small restaurant
into a big restaurant.
Then, within a year,
I opened dozens of branches at once.
I made a lot of money.
I'd never seen so much money before.
I thought I'd made it, I was An Dong.
I could do anything.
So I started playing with capital.
Overnight,
all those branches went bankrupt.
I ended up deep in debt.
Yes.
That's right.
When I came to Hong Shiliu,
I had other motives.
I wanted to use the restaurant
to make a big profit.
To pay off my own debts.
An Dong
You told us
you'd help make Hong Shiliu
the top restaurant in Urumqi.
You kept stirring things up here every day.
Training Ankar,
training Murat,
it was all for yourself, wasn't it?
Yes.
I did it for myself.
An Dong
The day you first came to our restaurant,
sat in that seat,
eating A'isha's Pilaf,
I didn't like you from the start.
Everyone in our restaurant
gave you their heart,
treated you with total sincerity.
We all treated you this way.
Why did you treat us like that?
What kind of person are you?
I'm just a selfish person.
But in the end,
you won.
I thought I was so smart,
but you bunch of
naive fools
completely moved me.
Your sincerity,
your honesty,
truly touched me.
I, An Dong, really
I want to be one of you.
I want to be family at Hong Shiliu.
An Dong
You don't know what family means.
An Dong,
You're playing the emotion card well.
Even I'm moved.
So, tell us,
how do we handle this?
I still...
It has nothing to do with them.
I'll use my dividends to pay.
From now on, every month,
as soon as the dividends arrive,
I'll send you every cent, no delay.
I guarantee it with my character.
Do you even have any character left?
He wants to guarantee it with his character?
And with dividends?
You're just making empty promises.
How can I trust you again?
I'm not stupid.
We're all businesspeople here.
The contract
still needs to be honored, right?
We should at least respect the spirit of the contract.
Integrity is the foundation of being human.
Isn't that right, Ming Liang?
Fang Tao
Whether you're after the restaurant
or after An Dong,
it's all for profit.
Since it's about profit,
let's talk business.
An Dong is part of Hong Shiliu.
We'll discuss it internally.
and then give you an answer.
Ming Liang,
you all are just too kind.
Sometimes you're so kind and naive
it makes me want to laugh.
You're making this way too simple.
This issue involves
more than just An Dong.
I have another contract here.
Ankar Murat
forged a shareholder authorization.
Used the company seal to sign contracts.
This is no small matter.
His actions amount to fraud.
That's illegal.
I will call the police.
No.
No, no, that's not it.
Fang Tao, I... I didn't know.
Dong-ge
Did I really break the law?
Is this really illegal?
Of course.
This could mean jail time.
This
Did you hear that?
Murat
Sit down
Murat's dad
Fang Tao
I know about this
Our people did it
We'll take responsibility
Don't worry, Fang Tao
Hong Shiliu, thirty years
Never owed a single cent
Alright
That's great
An Dong
Look at them
They're loyal and true
Now look at you
I'm completely disappointed in you
We'll pay the money back
Ming Liang
Fang Tao
Please leave
Okay
Either the money
Or the restaurant
Don't forget
You only have ten days
Fang Tao
No
Something's fishy here
You contacted Liu Jianping long ago, didn't you?
You two are in cahoots
You forced him
You made him demand I pay up, right?
An Dong
People
Should know themselves
You could've just run the restaurant
Fame and fortune, isn't that good?
But you had to mess with shady tricks
Trying to play the capital game
Can you handle it?
You failed once and still didn't learn
This time
Remember it
Within ten days
Bro
It's okay
We'll find a way
Mom
Should we go to the hospital?
Why go to the hospital?
No need
I was just anxious
I'm fine now
My mind is clear
You noticed something was wrong before, didn't you?
I saw An Dong earlier
Talking to Liu Jianping
I thought it was odd then
But I didn't ask much
It's a pity
Still a step too late
This is all my fault
A few times I noticed An Dong
Seemed to be hiding something
I didn't think much of it
If I'd told you earlier
You could've been prepared
Maybe we could've avoided this
Mom
It's not that you didn't think
You just didn't want to think deeper
If you really found out about An Dong
He'd leave
And I couldn't leave
Three million
That's not a small amount
Mom
Don't worry too much
I'll find a lawyer to check the contract
It's not that simple
It's not just whatever they say
But Fang Tao is clever because
He dragged Ankar into this too
That makes things more complicated
Ming Liang
Worst case, we give the restaurant to Fang Tao
Life goes on
No, Mom
We can't give in on this
After all that's happened
I kept the restaurant going
I just wanted a way to earn money
I thought I
Could make a bit more
So my son could go further
And steadier
After all that's happened today
You're not worried at all
Even if we lose the restaurant
Or lose me
Mom
You still have to live well
Our family
This restaurant
Will always be here
Stand tall
The sky won't fall
Your back
Mustn't bend either
I was wrong, Dad
Yes, you were wrong
You were wrong because
You didn't trust Dad
Didn't trust your brother
What you fear most
Dad
Is Dad not understanding you
But
You can always talk to your brother
It's not like that, Dad
I just wanted
To do something worthwhile
Then tell you all
I'm grown up now
I can't always be under your protection
I did think about opening a branch
Wanted to be a boss
But I'm not that vain
I really want to share your burden
And my brother's too
What I want most
Is to make you proud
What you just said
this loss
let's say
wasn't for nothing
I've worked in the kitchen my whole life
tasted all the ups and downs
I've swallowed every flavor
But this time
it's a big deal
but
it's not the end of the world
Besides
even if the sky falls
you still have
your old man to hold it up
Dad
This time
don't let
your brother take it all on
We'll figure it out ourselves
Okay
Son
In our family
the most valuable thing
is that house
No, Dad
You saved your whole life for it
to buy that house
I can't let you at your age
end up with nowhere to live
No way, Dad
Son
You once told me
you'd buy me the biggest villa
So
did you forget
or give up
lost your confidence
I'm still waiting for that villa
Sorry, Dad
Son
I still
can't get used to you talking to me like this
I'd rather
you talk back to me
It's my fault
I used to
be too strict with you
too harsh
No, Dad
Dad, I'm sorry
Dad
There's over 133,000 yuan in here
What I mean is
we take out over 30,000 yuan
for living expenses
and give the remaining 100,000
to Ming Liang
How about that
What do you mean
Over 30,000 yuan
isn't enough for our living expenses
We don't spend much now
Can you give your opinion
No
What do you really mean
Don't rush
I mean
give all the money to Ming Liang
I have my salary, don't I
We'll be fine financially
I think we should give as much as we can now
Since when has Old Hu been so generous
We've been married over twenty years
Don't you know me by now
The Hong Shiliu restaurant is struggling
How could I still be stingy
I wish we had three million right now
I'm thinking
about the insurance Yue Yue bought for us
can we cash it out
I'll call her and ask
Alright
Dad
Mom
Yue Yue
Guang Tian
Why are you here
Uncle, Aunt
Guang Tian
When did you get back
With such a big problem at home
I had to come back
These are mine and Guang Tian's salary cards
Take them to the restaurant together tomorrow
No, no
Uncle
Yue Yue and I discussed it
We agreed to use this money for the emergency
I called my parents too
They're gathering money as well
How come
your parents got involved too
No, no
It's not right
Aunt
Family doesn't keep things separate
Take it
Alright
If we're not family
we wouldn't be under one roof
The lawyer says it's complicated
There's not enough solid evidence
Ankar said he wanted to open a branch
I should've asked clearly
An Dong ran the restaurant for years
and still got tricked by Fang Tao
You're not Zhuge Liang
You can't foresee everything
This is the money my dad and I raised.
He asked me to tell you
the sandstorm will pass.
The Karez water will never run dry.
No matter how long the winter lasts,
the pomegranate flowers will bloom again.
No, no.
Nana,
I can't accept money from you and Sadik's dad.
If this money came from Murat's dad,
Bayar's mom,
Yueyue and Guangtian,
would you take it then?
We agreed before,
no matter what the future holds,
we'll face it together.
You even told me yourself
that you'd fight by my side.
We're companions,
confidants,
lovers,
able to share joy together,
and walk through hardships side by side.
Nana,
this is different.
How is it any different?
I...
Even if we were just friends,
I still wouldn't leave you alone.
Let alone being your girlfriend.
It's exactly because you're my girlfriend
that I can't take this money.
Nana,
having you by my side
is more than enough for me.
All I've brought you is trouble,
a mess everywhere.
Now I'm buried in debt.
I don't want to drag you into this swamp,
let you get stuck in it.
Do you understand what I mean?
Ming Liang,
the most important thing now is saving the restaurant.
Only if you keep the restaurant
can you protect the people you care about.
And the only way to save it
is to raise these three million.
Nana, I won't give up.
I know
you're worried this will affect my life.
But you need my help now.
I have to be here.
Because I know
no matter what I face in the future,
you'll be there too.
If you can't even accept my help,
how can we walk side by side?
How can I keep walking with you?
Think it over carefully.
Nana,
she put that bank card in my hand.
Right in my hand.
Just a moment before,
I hadn't even
really thought about my own situation.
But in that instant,
I suddenly realized
I'm someone with no future,
no prospects.
No.
Why do you say you have no future?
You can pay back the penalty money.
Your art will shine.
Why worry so much?
I reached out to a classmate from art school.
He
is the most successful among us
in our group right now.
What are you planning?
He just landed a big project.
A huge villa.
He's painting decorative art for the villa.
Are you crazy?
What was all those years of persistence for?
Ming Liang,
let's think of another way, okay?
If you paint a decorative piece,
your art will never sell in your life.
My classmate is a good guy.
He takes a very small commission.
The deposit is generous too.
From now on,
whether it's the restaurant
or at home,
there's always a need for money.
A painting is a painting, isn't it?
You don't know,
Van Gogh tried to sell his art for money.
He couldn't sell any of his paintings.
He wasn't even as successful as me.
Bro,
since you've made up your mind,
then go for it.
Worst case, start over.
We're still young.
You... you know I don't drink.
Fang Tao,
I'm begging you.
Please spare Hong Shiliu.
It has nothing to do with them.
I'm the one who dragged them down.
Okay?
Punish me however you want.
Sue me,
send me to jail if you must.
I'll accept it.
Just don't drag them into this.
An Dong,
do you really think I want to ruin you?
You're mistaken.
Back when you had trouble,
many people kicked you when you were down.
In front of others and behind your back,
I never said
a single bad word about you, An Dong.
Later, I heard
you made another restaurant a hit in Urumqi.
I was really happy for you.
Really.
I'm truly proud of you.
You're not an ordinary guy.
You're a real talent.
I didn't misjudge you.
No, Fang Tao,
if you put it that way,
I really don't understand.
What do you mean?
Let me be honest with you.
My goal isn't just Hong Shiliu.
It includes you, too.
Me.
Right now, except for me,
no one else would trust you.
But I'm willing to give you a platform.
You can fully show your talent.
Do you know why?
I value talent.
I cherish it.
And also,
I could give you Hong Shiliu.
We could invest and open branches.
All these places
would be managed by you.
No.
Fang... Fang Tao.
Hong Shiliu isn't mine.
It's theirs.
If you give it to me,
what about them?
Winning hearts is hardest.
You won their hearts,
but stabbed them right in it.
You think by doing this,
they'll forgive you?
An Dong,
you chose this path yourself.
How about this:
If you want to keep them, fine.
Just pay them a salary.
But remember this:
I only care about profit.
I'm off to get the money.
Be back before the deadline.
Are you okay?
Sorry.
Move your foot.
Get out of the way.
Can't you see I'm mopping?
Filthy thing.
Let me tell you something.
We welcome friends here.
Not wolves like you.
I'm telling you,
you're supposed to run a business.
Is this how you treat guests?
Who are you filming?
I'm filming you.
Who are you filming, huh?
Is this how you treat customers?
What are you doing?
Who are you filming, huh?
How could I just let it go?
Bayar's mom.
No, he...
Don't let the wolf bite back.
Look at him,
smearing our restaurant.
See that?
This place of theirs,
it's a shady business.
What are you doing?
Murat.
Come on, come on.
Come, look.
He's got a weapon!
Come on, fight!
Friends,
go
and get An Dong down here.
He brought this guy.
He caused this mess.
Let him fix it.
An Dong.
An Dong, come down.
I know where An Dong is.
An Dong ran off.
What?
I'll talk to him alone.
What the heck?
What is this?
Look at your staff here.
What kind of manners are these?
It's the age of social media now.
I could post her attitude online.
What will Hong Shiliu do then?
An Dong.
He'll definitely say he went out
to borrow money.
Don't believe a word he says.
He's a master at lying.
I know him all too well.
You all...
picked the wrong person to trust.
So, Ming Liang,
I suggest you all
go and sue him right away.
I'm willing to be a witness.
This is an internal matter
of our restaurant.
No need for you to worry about it.
Since your goal is money,
stop bothering us
while we run our business.
If our business does well,
we can pay you back sooner.
Ming Liang.
With a place like yours,
your turnover...
can you really pay back my three million?
Let me be honest with you.
The ten days I mentioned
is just time for you to pack up.
You all...
don't need to struggle pointlessly.
In ten days,
this Hong Shiliu restaurant
will definitely belong to me, Fang Tao.
I know.
Ten days.
Thanks for the reminder.
Fine.
This place is actually pretty nice.
When I first came here,
I thought the feng shui was good.
Look,
it's open and airy front and back.
Once this is mine,
I'll have to renovate it.
If you ask me,
this...
backyard...
add a few more tables.
Turn all the upstairs rooms
into private dining rooms.
By the way,
you painted this, right?
It looks almost real.
Yes.
They say these paintings
document your journey
as an artist.
Your growth, right?
Save this one for me.
Name your price.
Probably not worth much, right?
Two plates of chicken should cover it.
Oh, and...
your free meal table.
That's a clever move.
You're a smart kid.
No,
you're a sly one.
A serving of A'isha's Pilaf
costs so little.
This gimmick of yours is pretty good.
You play the emotional card,
and attract customers.
Right?
I plan to use this idea too.
And also...
this pomegranate tree in the yard.
It's such an eyesore.
Takes up too much space.
It needs to be chopped down.
Dig a pool right there.
Soaking in the bath,
eating naan,
and scrubbing away.
This is my home.
It's not your place to boss me around.
In ten days,
this will belong to me, Fang Tao.
I'll do whatever I want with it.
What?
What's wrong?
What are you trying to do?
Dad.
Murat, Dad.
He's just trying to provoke us.
Let's not stoop to his level.
If he ruins us,
the restaurant will really be his.
The deadbeat is hitting people!
What are you doing?
Fang Tao!
I'm warning you.
If you want mutual destruction,
I'll go down with you.
Mutual destruction?
Keep dreaming.
Let me tell you,
the net won't break even if the fish dies.
You... you...
If you won't let me be comfortable,
I won't let you have it easy either.
What kind of place is this?
You...
Closing up!
Crooked restaurant!
Don't come here anymore!
It's closed!
Crooked restaurant, hitting people!
I'll pay An Dong's money.
If I can't pay you on time,
the restaurant is yours.
Alright.
Well said.
That's exactly what I wanted to hear.
I've recorded the whole thing.
Okay.
My back...
Let's close for a few days and rest.
Everyone's been tired lately.
Come on.
This...
is what our family pooled together.
This is from me and Ming Liang.
Bro.
I've transferred the recent dividends
and some cash I had on me
all to you.
At critical moments,
we still rely on the old hands.
Here...
is eight hundred sixty thousand.
Take it.
Old Murat,
when did you ever have so much money?
I didn't want to reveal it,
but I had no choice.
Today, I'm coming clean.
I've always been a secret rich man.
This money
for this street's
first ladle
is nothing.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
I'll take it all.
Guys,
keep your heads up.
This is just a small thing.
It can't bring down us old folks.
Cheer up.
Alright?
Right.
Everyone, lift your heads.
It's fine.
We're family.
Nothing can defeat us.
A'isha,
We've lived half our lives already.
This restaurant—
thirty years of ups and downs.
All kinds of people, all kinds of things—
we've seen it all.
As long as we're together,
and our hearts stay close,
no hardship can defeat us.
Yes.
Did you hear that?
That's too much.
We're still short a little over one million.
I bet Murat and Bayar
even chipped in the last bit.
You should leave some for them.
Everyone still needs to live.
Mom,
Nana gave me a card too.
But unless I have no choice,
I don't want to use it.
I understand.
There will always be a way.
But you—
how did you save so much?
Your son used to be
a top teacher at the training school.
The hourly pay was high.
I was afraid you'd be wronged.
I won't, Mom.
I'm just curious—
Murat's dad,
where did he get all that money?
Yeah.
He's the kind of person
who doesn't spend much.
But—
he paid the down payment for his eldest son.
He shouldn't have much left.
Murat's dad—
over eight hundred thousand.
And Bayar's mom—
Honestly, holding this money
makes me uneasy.
If you don't take it,
Bayar and Murat will feel worse.
Especially Murat.
A hero all his life—
he's not just helping you,
he's also helping Ankar.
If you don't let him pay,
he'll regret it forever.
So many people drift apart
because of money.
But our family,
because we have none,
we've grown even closer.
As the old saying goes,
life is made by people,
not by money.
A family—
hearts united,
strength together—
that's stronger than anything.
Darn it, I'll go check.