Finally.
This is now...
The real deal.
(Last, Moon Se Hoon)
Everything comes down to Se Hoon's choice.
(Jin Joo has 0 votes right now.)
Jin Joo is the only one left alone.
So choosing Jin Joo...
- I don't think that'd be a bad choice.
- I agree, it wouldn't be bad.
(Who will Moon Se Hoon choose?)
(Turn)
Right up until the moment I stepped out,
I was really torn about who to choose.
Either Myo Jin or Tae In.
I knew Seung Hak would be next to Myo Jin,
and Hyun Jun would be next to Tae In.
That kept bothering me.
Deep down,
I kind of hoped he'd come to me.
(After much thought,
Se Hoon finally steps forward.)
Where? He went to Myo Jin.
- Who?
- To Myo Jin.
There?
(Moon Se Hoon chooses Kim Myo Jin.)
Did you sleep well?
The person I chose was Myo Jin.
In the middle of
that emotional whirlwind...
between Tae In and Hyun Jun,
I think we three were
having a really hard time.
And since Myo Jin
is also someone I'm interested in,
I felt it was a very natural choice.
But Seung Hak is there too.
What about Seung Hak?
Why isn't he mentioning Seung Hak?
Why is it not okay to go to them,
but okay to go there?
- So what happens to our cutie Seung Hak?
- What kind of situation is this?
(All the men have made their choices.)
(Men's choice date
Kim Jin Joo, 0 votes)
Jin Joo.
For two days in a row,
Jin Joo has received zero votes.
She must be feeling absolutely terrible.
(Min Cheol chooses Hyun Jin
instead of Jin Joo.)
(Myo Jin's team heads out
in Se Hoon's car.)
- I'll be your driver, boss.
- Thank you.
Sorry for interrupting your date,
Seung Hak.
No, it's fine.
Seung Hak, do you have any lip balm?
I don't it with me now.
Do you want some lip tint?
For real.
Lip tint?
I haven't heard about lip tint in forever.
But you might end up looking
like a man wearing makeup like a woman.
(Up close)
This hurts my heart so much.
Our cutie Seung Hak
is sitting right behind them.
I really hate that.
(A scene too painful to watch)
Right in front of him...
This isn't like bringing a nephew
along your date or something.
What is this situation?
Exactly.
You do look cuter with your hair down.
My heart hurts so much.
If you push your bangs back,
you have an intense look,
so it's kind of hard to approach.
But with them down,
I seem easier to act rude to.
Yeah, kind of.
Not exactly "easy to act rude to."
But it feels like it'd be easier
to relax around you
But somehow...
seeing Seung Hak sitting back there...
feels like I'm looking at myself.
The guy sitting in the front
is Kim Yo Han.
The one in the front is Kim Yo Han,
and the one in the back is me.
That's how it feels.
It feels like I'm the one
sitting back there.
(Korean set meal)
It smells amazing.
(Myo Jin's team arrives
at the restaurant.)
Myo Jin, you sit there.
(An awkward tension
fills the 2-on-1 date.)
(Silently chugging plain water)
I've never eaten a meal like this before,
with two guys sitting across from me.
Of course.
What?
- My goodness.
- Hello, ma'am.
(The sound of a door opening
breaks the awkwardness.)
Hello.
(Myo Jin's mother appears?)
- Her mother?
- Her mother? All of a sudden?
Myo Jin's mother just walked in.
(Startled)
Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- I missed you.
- Hello, ma'am.
Nice to meet you.
Are you eating together with us?
I guess we are.
I see.
That really surprised me.
What a shock.
What were you doing before you came?
What were you doing?
We went on a little trip.
- Really?
- The mothers had a great time together.
Without cameras?
Yeah, without any.
- Completely without?
- None at all.
To our youth.
(For 2 days, the mothers
forgot about their children...)
(and enjoyed themselves.)
They must've had so much fun.
(Then they make a surprise return
to eat with their kids.)
You should've let me enjoy my date.
Why did you turn it
into a matchmaking date?
I was honestly shocked.
It wasn't a date chosen by the men.
Once a choice is made,
they end up meeting the mother together.
- Basically a formal family meeting.
- A family-meeting date.
It's a different concept.
Unbelievable.
We totally forgot
about the mothers for a moment.
Where did they go?
How does it feel
now that two men are here?
It's nice.
Are you sure you can eat with us?
- Yes.
- You're not going to get indigestion?
- No.
- No?
Seeing two men sitting there...
was surprising,
and I was also very grateful.
I had so many mixed emotions.
I was really grateful.
This is totally Mom's style.
That scared me.
Hello, ma'am.
This is totally Mom's style.
(Seung Hak's mother also appears.)
Hello.
Welcome.
You were chosen. You look beautiful.
Nice to see you again.
Yes, it's so nice to see you too.
From start to finish,
you haven't changed your mind.
He really hasn't.
(Se Hoon's mother also appears.)
Welcome.
This way.
Hello.
- Mom, this way.
- Over there.
(Bustling)
It's a family meeting.
I guess they all have the same taste.
My son and Se Hoon.
Thank you so much.
Now that two teams
have already chosen one person,
what happens to the remaining one?
I'm worried.
We know exactly how that feels.
You and I were best friends.
So what happens to us now?
Exactly.
Yes! Two pairs of shoes.
Hello.
(Cho Eun Na Rae and Seo Han Gyeol's room)
(Overjoyed)
Have you been well? How have you been?
Why is my mother being like that?
- I'm nervous.
- Please sit.
The same person was sitting there,
just like always.
And that made me happy.
You're so sweet.
This is exactly the picture I wanted.
You're making us uncomfortable.
I should say this before his mother comes
because she might be upset.
No, my mother wouldn't be upset.
I just love
seeing the two of you together.
Why would his mother be upset?
No, not me.
My mother? She's not upset at all.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
You always say that.
But from his mother's point of view,
since there's quite a big age gap...
Don't.
It's okay.
My mother really won't mind that much.
Really?
I feel like she might mind that a lot.
Let's see
how Han Gyeol's mother will feel.
(Knock, knock)
- I think my mother's here.
- Must be his mother.
- Hello .
- Mom.
Have you been well?
Hey.
(Han Gyeol's mother arrives,
making Eun Na Rae's mother worried.)
- You're wearing something bright.
- Yeah.
Good choice.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
Please have a seat.
I never imagined we'd meet like this.
Neither did I.
They said the man made the choice.
Since Han Gyeol was the one choosing,
given his personality,
rather than meeting
several people in a short time,
"Even focusing on one person
isn't enough time."
He probably thought like this.
So he likely just followed his feelings
and kept choosing the same person.
(Kim Hyun Jin and Jang Min Cheol's room)
- Hello.
Welcome. I'll hang your bag for you.
Mom, it's so good to see you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Shall I close the door?
- Yes.
Nice to meet you.
It's so nice to see you
after such a long time.
(My goodness)
Two nights and three days.
Since that secret meeting,
- it really has been a long time.
- It really has.
They say Min Cheol and Hyun Jin...
were both the mothers' picks.
Apparently,
the mothers really liked the two.
His mother liked her,
and her mother liked him.
(Meanwhile,
Jin Joo arrives at the restaurant alone.)
Seeing her sitting alone again today,
her mother must feel so heartbroken.
You don't have to feel too discouraged.
- That's true.
- In the end,
it all comes down to the final moment.
Yeah!
(The noise from the next room
stirs her emotions.)
(Jin Joo's mother appears.)
So it's just the two of us eating?
Sit there.
Have you been okay?
How were you, Mom?
I was fine. I rested comfortably.
I was worried, Mom.
You didn't even take your bag.
How about your health?
I'm fine.
Did you cry?
Don't cry.
You must've been really upset.
What about breakfast?
Did you eat this morning?
You didn't?
Why are you crying?
(Heartbroken)
What if I can't get married?
Then don't. Just live with me.
Seeing things here,
I realized you were still too young
to get married.
No one chose me,
but it's not the zero votes
that hurt, but...
What matters
is protecting your mental strength.
Out in the real world,
have you ever not been chosen even once?
When you were dating outside?
I mean outside of here, outside this camp.
You're a great and amazing person.
Don't let this shake you so much.
I should be honest with you
about that day.
On the day of the self-introductions,
I wrote about you more honestly
than the other mothers did, right?
You were sorry about that, right?
No.
When you told me "I'm sorry," I cried.
When did I say I was sorry?
Mom, you must be embarrassed
because of me. I'm sorry.
- No.
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just the fact
that you had the courage to come here...
Haven't you thought about this?
(A daughter blaming herself
for not being chosen)
Maybe I shouldn't have come at all.
(A mother whose heart aches watching her)
When you said you were sorry,
that really upset me.
Did I say I was sorry?
Yes, you said, "Mom, I'm sorry."
In the room.
(Hoping her daughter
won't blame herself today)
Are you okay right now?
I'm not okay.
Of course, I'm not okay.
It's natural to feel like crying
in front of Mom.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
- She's still young, that's why.
- She shouldn't give up already.
This isn't a final decision.
Of course, she knows that,
but from a woman's perspective,
not being chosen feels...
How can anyone be chosen every time?
How can you always be picked?
And since her mother experienced that
with her twice in a row,
that probably made it
even harder for Jin Joo.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Please enjoy your meal.
Hyun Jin, serve Ms. Kang.
I want to give her the big piece.
That line.
- Hyun Jin is doing an amazing job.
- She really is.
She's so good at those things.
She's doing great.
I want to give her the big piece.
(She picks the king-size rib.)
She might not look so,
but Hyuh Jin is very good with elders.
Really?
I've talked to her, right?
I can tell.
When I first saw Hyun Jin,
she gave off
a "Korean eldest daughter" vibe.
I raised my three kids...
pretty strictly, almost Spartan-style.
So my kids are all...
very sharp and capable.
She's good-looking
and very capable in real life too.
There's nothing lacking.
She's very capable.
Like I said before,
I personally like people
who are knowledgeable.
- Knowledgeable?
- He went to Seoul National University.
In terms of knowledge, he's top-tier.
I personally like people
who are knowledgeable.
who are academically strong.
Is that so?
It's not just about academic background.
I like that too,
but I also look at character
and responsibility,
and whether someone is thoughtful.
So that's how you see Min Cheol?
Thank you.
(Kim Myo Jin, Lee Seung Hak,
and Moon Se Hoon's room)
I'll serve you.
Just a little, please.
Okay, enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
I think Myo Jin has pretty generous hands.
How she scoops
the soybean paste soup shows.
But honestly,
I'm not very good at cooking.
That always worries me.
My son cooks well.
Cooking is...
You don't need to worry about that.
It's okay if you can't cook.
You can learn after you get married.
That's also true.
The two men are just eating quietly.
You can learn after you get married.
That's also true.
Still, it's nice when a man can cook.
Well, that would be nice, but my son...
is not picky with food, so it's fine.
Is that so?
Being good at cooking is a plus.
(An unexpected loss)
Please eat up.
- Yes.
- My goodness.
The mothers have gone
into competition mode.
I had eel yesterday.
How did you eat eel yesterday?
Did you go out?
Yes, during our lunch date.
Did you keep going out on dates?
- I see.
- Yes.
Who was your lunch date with?
Myo Jin.
Myo Jin, again?
This is basically decided then.
What are you talking about?
Isn't that great?
That's how it looks to me.
Your houses are close too.
Ours is close as well.
If we sit down,
it's practically their place.
My son will move closer there too.
(About to bleed from the ears)
Are you two fighting?
Mom, what are you doing?
She's very proactive.
But...
Se Hoon's mother...
was really staring me down...
like I was a serious rival.
Since Seung Hak likes Myo Jin,
I'm just giving it a shot.
I'm jumping right in.
Just a few hours ago,
she was like a close sister...
I laughed with,
and now she's my rival.
No.
(Cho Eun Na Rae and Seo Han Gyeol's room)
Thank you so much.
You don't have to thank me.
I came because I wanted to.
- I'm a bit sorry to my daughter, though.
- Why?
I honestly thought
it would be just the two of you eating.
You did?
I really did! But...
I walked in and saw two pairs of shoes.
So from outside I was already like,
"This is awesome! Unbelievable!"
Like this.
I'll tell you about my daughter.
When my daughter dates someone,
she's very affectionate and cute.
- Almost like a baby.
- That's true.
I do have a childlike side.
She really does.
- I can really feel that.
- Really?
She doesn't look very happy.
As she gets a year or two older,
her way of thinking seems to change a bit.
So her father keeps saying,
she should marry before it's too late.
(Sigh)
When does he say she should marry?
He says even tomorrow would be fine,
or next month would be great.
He'd welcome it,
but it's not something you can force.
But she wasn't thinking
about marriage at all,
so we just read the room
and didn't bring it up.
That's why.
So I'm really grateful for this.
Even now,
I have water in my cup.
Thanks.
She doesn't look very happy.
My mother was so emotional...
and so grateful that Han Gyeol came,
almost like, "Thank you so much."
"We're the weaker side,
and you're the stronger side."
That kind of dynamic.
Age is a separate issue.
I don't want
a relationship to start like that.
Why be in a relationship like that?
I'm not desperate
to date a younger man, either.
So I don't want it to be that way.
(Eun Na Rae is deep in thought.)
I see.
Is there anything you're curious about?
Well...
Anything, really.
It suddenly feels uncomfortable.
There's nothing
to feel uncomfortable about.
But Ms. Kwon doesn't seem like the type
to feel awkward in situations like this.
My mother...
is great.
She does seem that way.
She doesn't look happy.
She seems really uncomfortable.
But why does this feel so uncomfortable?
What does? The situation?
I don't know what to do.
Yeah.
And since we weren't told in advance,
even my outfit feels a bit off.
Exactly.
But it's okay.
Still.
Han Gyeol wants me
to be friendly and courteous.
That's the kind of person he likes.
With whom?
With his mother.
I see.
But whether it's toward
their partner's mother or anyone else,
there are people who are just naturally
friendly and courteous, right?
He likes that, and he really...
That's me.
He really values that a lot.
That's exactly me.
So, what about that?
Why are you suddenly saying that's you?
Just...
Then go marry him.
I'm just saying that's me.
We're talking about me right now.
Seriously.
(Cho Eun Na Rae is hurt.)
Was there anyone else...
Eun Na Rae might have wanted to see more?
She said there wasn't.
- There wasn't?
- No.
But even today, it was still enjoyable.
The dinner felt comfortable and easy...
being with her mother.
She seems like such a nice person.
For me, it felt like a situation
that could actually be a bit difficult.
Being comfortable is nice,
but I started wondering,
"Is this really right?"
If it's uncomfortable, does that mean
the conversation gets better?
It's not about having
"better" conversations.
I'm saying, is it okay to move forward
based only on feeling comfortable?
I mean...
If we're going to talk more
about it now...
What did you want to talk about there?
The age gap, for example.
I said I'd handle that myself.
Those issues.
What does talking about that
with Eun Na Rae's mother actually solve?
With me...
It's not a conversation
to make a decision or reach a conclusion.
It's just that...
Isn't it okay to at least ask,
"There's an age gap.
How do you feel about that?"
They already know that, of course.
Yeah.
That's something
I want to take responsibility for.
I want to be the one to judge it.
Honestly, you can't really influence me...
that much anyway about that issue, Mom.
I know.
Then why does it feel like, on that issue,
you're so uneasy and...
I'm not "uneasy."
Well, but about those concerns...
- I know you can't just not mention them.
- Even if I can't influence you,
bringing the mother into this means...
I do have a say.
The decision is yours in the end,
but it's about giving me a chance too.
It's bout giving your mother
a chance as well.
Of course.
It's not that I'm ignoring you, Mom.
If I hadn't already thought
about the things you worry about,
then I might ask your opinion.
But I've already been thinking
about those concerns.
It's not like I'm unaware of them.
Yes, you said you know.
I know, and I'm conflicted too.
So should I just not say anything, then?
That's exactly right.
Should I really not say anything?
Yes.
That's what I think.
Is there really a need?
This is upsetting.
(The mood turns cold in an instant.)
If I had to read
Han Gyeol's feelings exactly,
it's that his mother rubbed him
the wrong way in that moment.
She didn't really respond much.
Even if it's just on the surface.
"You may not like it,"
"but you could at least be polite
on the surface."
"So why did you have to make it
so obvious you didn't like it, Mom?"
That's what he's talking about right now.
From a mother's point of view...
- She's worried.
- Right.
I understand both sides,
the son's and the mother's.
It feels comfortable
riding in my son's car.
I thought it would just be a light date,
just some time to talk.
Yesterday, I gave all my picks to Jin Joo.
I see.
So I wanted to talk more
with someone else,
but this matchmaking date vibe...
I like it.
If I really went on a matchmaking date,
it would've felt like this.
That's right.
Still, what I'm grateful for is that
the two people I'm interested in...
- Two people.
- are also interested in me.
I'm grateful for that.
Right.
But for some reason,
Jin Joo keeps coming to mind.
I see.
Because honestly,
Jin Joo is the type I usually like.
That's why I chose her
in the first impression vote.
Right.
I like that kind of gentle and soft...
Well, she's not actually
gentle and soft in personally.
Jin Joo isn't exactly gentle,
but she's pure.
At least that's how she feels to me.
She's pure.
She's honest.
She doesn't say things she doesn't mean.
No empty words.
To some people, that might come across as,
"Why is she so blunt?"
But to me, instead of that,
it feels like she only says
what's honest and sincere.
That's how it feels to me.
Right.
She doesn't sugarcoat things.
She doesn't sugarcoat.
People usually calculate how they'll come
across and act accordingly.
Right.
But she doesn't do that.
She's completely immersed in this show.
So she gets stressed,
and it really takes a toll on her.
Her stomach keeps hurting.
(Min Cheol pours out his feelings
about Jin Joo to his mother.)
So Jin Joo gives me this feeling.
Should I describe it
as a paternal instinct?
I just want to take care of her
and cherish her.
I see.
On the way to the restaurant,
I happened to see Jin Joo getting out of
a car with a really downcast expression.
By chance.
And that image just stuck with me.
I'd already been thinking about it...
for a while now.
(He spots Jin Joo.)
(Jin Joo's expression stayed on his mind
throughout the meal.)
Wait.
He had that meeting-the-parents-style meal
with Hyun Jin and her mother,
but his feelings seemed...
to have changed to Jin Joo.
That's what I felt in the car.
So I thought I needed
to think things through...
and said, "Let's talk more
back at the lodging," and came back.
I keep worrying about
how hurt Jin Joo must feel.
Of course.
What if she's sick again today?
Exactly.
So realistically speaking, for example,
if you choose Hyun Jin,
there's no issue with dating her.
She lives in Gangdong-gu.
It's really close.
But if you choose Jin Joo,
you'd have to go back and forth
to Pyeongtaek.
And one concern I have is this.
Human emotions don't work like this.
Feeling nothing Monday through Friday,
then suddenly being in love
on the weekend.
So the question is whether my feelings
are strong enough...
- Right.
- to overcome those real-life obstacles.
That's the question.
So while I still have time,
I want to tell her honestly...
why I didn't choose her this morning.
So I want to talk with her now.
Do it.
But she might not want to talk to me.
She may be too hurt.
Then what do you do?
(Min Cheol smiles
at the thought of seeing Jin Joo.)
How would I comfort her?
I talked things through...
about all kinds of things with my mother.
"I don't know,
but Jin Joo just keeps coming to mind."
"In the end, I want to go to Jin Joo."
I feel this urge
to work through those real-life issues.
That's when I realized,
"I really do like Jin Joo."
Talking with my mother
actually made it clearer.
If you can't stop thinking about someone
even when you avoid them, that's real.
Right?
- You need some distance to realize.
- Exactly.
I should change
into the cardigan Jin Joo likes.
Okay.
There's a cardigan Jin Joo likes.
- That one?
- Yeah.
So that's the one.
I'll do it.
Look at you.
Yes.
- I'll be back.
- Yeah.
(Meanwhile,
Jin Joo lies down at the lodging.)
It's hard to keep my expression together.
You don't have to anymore.
Jin Joo, don't be like that.
Okay.
But there's really nothing to do.
You can go out.
No today.
I went out a lot yesterday.
Really?
Just let it go, Jin Joo.
I guess life hasn't been
too rough until now. This feels hard.
Of course. You're still young.
You shouldn't be dealing
with hardships already.
She's never been
in a situation like this before.
If she didn't like someone,
she just came home.
Hello, ma'am.
Min Cheol.
Nice to see you.
Did you have a good meal?
Yeah, it was good.
(Hesitating)
Did you have a good time?
Hello.
- Is Jin Joo in her room, by any chance?
- Do you want to talk to Jin Joo? Okay.
Jin Joo.
She's in her room. Jin Joo.
Tell him to wait a moment.
Just a second. She's coming out.
- Wait a bit.
- Okay.
I'll sit here.
Jin Joo, smile, okay?
(Tap)
He's here.
You look more excited.
Where is he?
He's waiting right out front.
Your guy is waiting out front.
Put your shoes on and go.
Jin Joo, you've got this.
Thanks.
She's happy.
Looks like she was waiting.
She looks better now.
(Jin Joo comes outside.)
(The two face each other awkwardly.)
I hope Jin Joo doesn't cry again.
No way.
(A quiet place where they can talk alone)
(Reading the room)
What I was thinking was this.
We talked yesterday, right?
About how we should probably
talk more with others.
(Last night)
Did you talk more actively
with your second choice...
and your first choice as well?
I did. I talked enough.
I think you should talk more.
You think so?
Yeah.
So I went with her
without overthinking it,
just thinking,
"Okay, let's talk once more,"
but that ended up
turning into a meal with the mothers too.
What was the question?
The question?
The question before you made your choice.
This morning?
Not word for word,
but "Please stand next to the woman
you want to go on a date with today."
They didn't say
the mothers would be there today.
It wasn't, "Stand next to the person
you want to meet the mother with."
Anyway, I thought that part
probably hurt you more.
It wasn't that getting
zero votes upset me,
it was just...
that you two went to have a meal,
but the mothers also joined.
And on top of that,
your mother had picked her
and her mother had picked you.
That was just...
the worst part.
In the end, I think I'm the problem.
Yeah, that's right.
Is that what you wanted to say?
You went straight for it.
And you answered
every question I asked to confirm that.
But I kept feeling unsure,
wanting to double-check,
wanting more conversation.
So, did you get your confirmation?
I think I did.
That's why I came to talk to you.
That's it, it's settled.
She's smiling.
She's happy again.
Earlier...
Confirmation complete.
I think this made it even clearer.
It wasn't just asking her out on a date.
- Right.
- He really confirmed it.
"Even after going on a date
with someone else and meeting her mother,"
- "in the end, it was you."
- You.
That feels more meaningful.
(The two confirm their feelings
for each other.)
I cried a lot.
You cried?
When?
After you got back?
On the way?
Want to walk a bit?
To that place we said we wanted to go to.
Shall we walk?
This is perfect. They're together.
I should've brought a jacket.
Your coat?
Do you want to wear this?
Yeah, take it off for her.
This is really warm.
It looks warm.
Is it angora?
- Want me to pull your hair out?
- Yeah.
It suits you better.
It must've been tough for you too,
eating with the mothers.
I didn't really talk much.
Did the mothers
start talking about marriage?
Did they tell you guys
to prepare dowries and gifts?
- Did they?
- What are you talking about?
I love that cute jealousy.
No, marriage never came up.
Do we go this way?
Let's try this way.
(They arrive at a café
with jealous Jin Joo.)
Do you want to grab coffee at the café?
I kind of want coffee.
I worried a lot...
about whether I'd get along
with a mother like that.
Let's recharge with some sugar today.
(Min Cheol and Jin Joo
are fully focused on desserts.)
I see.
Then should we just get drinks to go?
That's Min Cheol, right?
Min Cheol and Jin Joo.
Looks like it.
(She spots Min Cheol with Jin Joo.)
I mean, wherever you go,
everything's visible.
They ran into them at the café by chance.
Wasn't that room blocked off earlier?
You can see everything.
It's honestly annoying.
I saw him talking to Jin Joo
for the second time.
I thought, "I guess leaving her alone
really bothered him."
And it made me think...
about how I actually feel about Min Cheol.
What about you? I didn't see that coming.
Honestly,
I'm not sure if I like him
because he's a good guy,
or if I like him and want to date him.
I'm not sure.
Then who are you
romantically attracted to?
Hyun Jun.
What?
It was Hyun Jun?
Romantically, I'm drawn to Hyun Jun.
That's interesting. I thought
you'd be more into Min Cheol that way.
That's interesting.
So you like cheerful people?
More than the person.
It's the overall vibe.
I'm drawn to Hyun Jun,
but he's so focused on someone else...
that I can't really approach him.
Why can't you approach him?
It's the last day. Go for it.
Be more proactive.
I'm going to talk to Hyun Jun now.
About what? How he feels?
Yes.
Like a business meeting?
Yeah. How is it?
- Good.
- Good?
Interesting.
- They might actually be compatible.
- Right.
An estrogen-driven man
and a testosterone-driven woman.
So they kind of balance each other out.
Yeah, and he'd live under her thumb.
Honestly, the only person...
who showed even a little curiosity
toward Hyun Jun was Hyun Jin.
First of all...
From what I can see...
Wait. Where's Min Cheol's room
and where's Hyun Jun's room?
They're in the same room.
Really? Then I'll check the situation.
If we call Hyun Jun over...
Where would be a good place
for him to come?
I'll ask him to talk together,
like a consultation.
This side seems better.
Around here, then outside that door.
Could we have him come
to that corner spot?
There?
This is Seung Hak's room.
Hold on, I'll go inside.
Here.
But Seung Hak might be in there.
Seung Hak.
Yes?
Hey.
How many people are there?
Are you alone right now?
- Yes.
- There are two of us.
Hello, ma'am.
I'll step out.
No, it's not like that.
We just wanted to check something.
Check? Seung Hak, check.
No, wait.
You don't have to come out.
I'm going out.
Let's send her to my mother's room.
There's space here too.
My mother is in her room.
Go ahead, talk with him.
(Running)
I want to talk with Hyun Jun.
So she's hoping to borrow this room.
Could I use it for a moment?
Sure.
You can stay too, I guess.
But then he'd hear everything.
I'll step out, then.
Okay, I'll take him out with me.
Please tell Hyun Jun to come here.
And...
(The room owner gets ready to leave.)
Yeah, talk.
(Meanwhile, Myo Jin goes to get Hyun Jun.)
- Hello.
- Hey, let's talk for a bit.
Is your mother back?
- Yeah, she's here.
- Hello, ma'am.
Want to go talk in another room?
I don't know, I was just asked.
But anyway, good luck.
Asked to get me?
Someone asked. Hello.
Hi.
Okay, now you step out, Seung Hak.
I'll leave once they come in.
They're here.
- Nice to meet you.
- How about we talk for a bit?
- Where's Seung Hak?
- Here.
You come out.
- What?
- Hi.
You scared me.
It's me.
Did you have a good time?
It's not Seung Hak. It's me.
I see. I was wondering why Seung Hak
would want a one-on-one with me.
Okay, bye.
(Shy)
Hi.
Did you have a good time?
I'm curious
what they're going to talk about.
Did you have a good time?
You should've come out on your own.
- Let's go.
- How was the meal earlier?
The meal?
I seriously thought I was going to choke.
Hello.
(Se Hoon)
Are the mothers together?
Yeah, his mother and my mother.
Okay. Let's talk later.
Okay.
Anyway...
To be honest,
you know I have feelings for you.
She's so direct.
(A blunt confession from Hyun Jin)
- Yeah.
But...
What I find strange is...
Why?
I mean, this also feels strange.
I didn't mean to ask "why."
Are you asking why I like you?
No, that's not it.
It's just that...
Stop covering your eyes.
Don't do weird stuff.
Honestly...
I'm just a little shy.
Didn't you talk with Min Cheol
for a long time last night?
- Yeah, we talked.
- Right?
But my own feelings matter too,
that's why.
I see.
Then,
does that mean I'm number one,
not Min Cheol?
I mean, my first and second picks
are really close.
They're not far apart.
They're pretty even?
But since you still need to talk
before this shoot is over...
Yes, and I talked
with Min Cheol yesterday.
And again today.
And I realized...
I hadn't really had
a serious talk with you.
Right, we were always just joking around.
And honestly, I was too shy.
Really? What's there to be shy about?
Everything.
Yeah?
I don't know.
I'm someone
who's never really known shyness.
You seem like the type
who'd be the most shy.
Anyway, that's why I came.
Even though you knew how I felt...
I still went to someone else.
Yeah, but you knew already.
Before I regretted it,
I wanted to talk to you.
You wanted to do everything you could,
all the way to the end?
Because tomorrow is decision day.
Yeah, full-on testosterone-driven mode.
You're definitely
a testosterone-driven lady.
"I'm going all in, no regrets."
That's honestly really cool.
No, it's not cool.
You're seriously cool.
You really are.
Anyway, I didn't want to have regrets.
I'm really grateful.
But I kept...
being conscious of Tae In.
That's how it felt.
So...
sometimes I think if things had gone
differently with you first,
maybe Tae In wouldn't have stayed
on my mind so much.
The other way around?
But because Tae In came first...
Right.
If we get another chance,
let's talk more then.
Yeah.
Just...
(Good)
Okay.
He explained it...
as "maybe it was a timing issue,"
and I honestly understood that.
If anything, my heart felt lighter.
What I find really unfortunate
about Hyun Jun is this.
If it were me,
at this timing, I would've boldly...
turned toward Hyun Jin at least a little.
He already met her mother too.
Hyun Jin is in an awkward position
right now too.
Right.
This was really the timing to go that way,
but he didn't.
That situation felt too stiff.
Yeah.
And on top of that,
being together with Se Hoon
and his mother instead of one-on-one...
suddenly felt really draining.
Right? I was tired too.
But I think seeing my mother recharged me.
Just now? Seeing your mother?
And having all the mothers together
made me really happy.
So I felt really good.
See you later. Get some rest.
Get some sleep.
Where are you going?
- I'm heading this way.
- Really?
Then on your way, call Se Hoon over.
That'd be better.
(Cry)
This is kind of weird though, right?
Well, what can you do?
You were chosen by two people.
But still...
It's fine.
- Se Hoon.
- I'm so torn.
(His mother gets up instead of him.)
Where's Se Hoon?
Everything feels...
so strange now that the mothers are here.
It's really not easy, right?
Yeah, it's really not easy.
It's okay.
Just pretend we're not here.
Then we can go out again.
Myo Jin.
You're all right there.
How can we pretend you're not here?
Just think of us as ghosts.
Tell the producers to send us out again.
Really?
Then we'll just go out again.
(Fortunately, the son and daughter leave.)
Out of everyone,
why are those two together?
We'll be back.
Are you leaving with Se Jin?
I mean, Se Hoon?
We already had a talk.
(Turn)
It was just a question.
I'm really curious how it was
with the other mothers.
Same.
The mothers looked super nervous.
Exactly.
They kept breaking into a sweat.
If your mother told you
not to see someone, would you stop?
No, I really wouldn't care about that.
I do what I want.
But who knows?
If my mother said, "This person
really isn't marriage material"...
- And had a reasonable...
- Yeah.
and logical reason, then maybe.
But my mother...
mostly trusts my choices.
She knows I'll figure things out
on my own.
That's how she is.
You're confused, aren't you?
- What?
- Are you confused?
Honestly, I think I am.
Right?
Yeah.
Still confused?
Feels like he doesn't
really need to be anymore.
But right now, this feels so good.
So stay with me just a little longer.
Well...
What is this?
What is going on?
I was wondering.
It felt really good,
but I wasn't quite sure...
and it was strange.
It was a mix...
of a lot of emotions and thoughts.
"What is this?"
That's how it felt the whole time.
Complicated, subtle emotions.
That's heart-fluttering.
Those kinds of lines
make your heart flutter.
But now,
she kind of wants to hear "I choose you."
Right. She wants to hear that now.
- But he won't say it.
- He keeps saying he's confused.
He won't say it, no matter what.
That's how you drive people crazy.
Later, when you like someone, Yo Han,
Yes.
tell her quickly.
Yeah. Don't keep saying you're confused.
Don't go, "I'm so confused."
"I'm confused."
Just be honest.
People like Yo Han need clarity fast.
Got it.
(Myo Jin returns
after talking with Se Hoon.)
I think...
I'm definitely more drawn to Se Hoon,
and he's closer to the type
I usually like.
But after talking,
the way he treats his mother...
felt a bit stiff.
Was he stiff with his mother?
It seemed so with his mother.
A bit.
You're not that close
with your mother usually, right?
It shows, doesn't it?
Not exactly. But once you said it,
I could see it clearly.
If I say one thing wrong,
my mother just bursts.
She gets really hurt.
You were pretty intense.
If you talk to her with that look,
of course she'd cry.
People like that end up treating
their wives the same way after marriage.
Right.
(Sigh...)
I don't know.
No one is ever 100 percent my ideal type.
You know what I mean?
I'm attracted,
but it's hard.
- Right.
- Yeah.
The more you go through this,
the harder it gets.
Yeah.
Han Gyeol, do you have a moment?
It's easier to come out this way.
(He rushes to the window
at Eun Na Rae's call.)
- It's a small door.
- That's so cute.
(Glance)
Hey.
Where should we go?
Here. Give it to your mother.
My mother? Why?
And this too.
- For me?
- Yeah.
I think one box will be enough.
(A handwritten letter as well)
Even a letter.
For you and your mother.
There's nothing big in it, but earlier,
during that meal...
That moment just kept bothering me.
What bothered you?
I don't know.
It was just awkward and uncomfortable.
What bothered you?
What exactly?
It felt like I should've said more,
but the words just wouldn't come.
I didn't know what to say.
Same here.
How sweet of you.
Let's talk again later tonight.
See you later.
Okay.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
Eun Na Rae bought us bread.
She bought it for us?
She went out and got it?
I think so. Maybe what happened earlier
was still on her mind.
Why? What was she hung up on?
(Eun Na Rae's thoughtful
handwritten letter)
Isn't it cute?
Yeah.
- Right?
- Yeah.
She asked me to pass it on to you, Mom.
Okay.
(As evening mealtime arrives)
What should we do?
(This space is open only for
filming purposes with permission.)
Look at you.
- You went to freshen up a bit.
- Me?
You should tie your hair up
if you're cooking.
Hello, ma'am.
Hello.
Mom, grill it.
"Mom, grill it?" I knew you'd say that.
It just looked like
you didn't have anything to do.
Ma'am, I'll do it.
No, it's okay, I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
It'll look like I dumped it on you
after Jin Joo handed it to me.
No, it's fine.
Just relax. I'll keep grilling the meat.
Then I'll cut the garlic in half.
Thank you.
(Meanwhile,
Jin Joo, who "passed off" the meat)
I'll wash these with you.
Hello.
(She goes to help Min Cheol's mother.)
Thank you.
Aren't your hands cold?
Hello.
The water isn't cold,
so I'm okay.
(Seung Hak's mother
moves next to Myo Jin.)
Everyone looks so happy.
Thank you for the gift
Enjoy your bread.
(Grin)
I think we can bring all of this out.
It turned into something
like spicy pork stir-fry.
Looks delicious.
It looks so good, nice, and hot.
Give me the perilla leaves, ma'am.
- I've got nothing in my hands.
- Okay.
- It's heavy.
- It's not.
It's heavy. You'll strain your wrist.
- It is heavy.
- Let's go.
(The final dinner, all together)
It's already the last evening.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
I'll try this.
Eat up.
I hardly ever get to eat food
my son makes.
Because he's always out and about.
So I only get it at times like this.
I'll try opening it with this.
(Pop)
Nice.
My goodness.
It's supposed to go "Pop!"
when you do it right.
(Another bottle)
(Tries another bottle in disappointment)
(Pop)
Yes.
I thought only my husband
did things like that.
I practiced this for over a year.
That's amazing.
- She opened it with a spoon.
- Really?
Watch Seung Hak's mother.
Attention.
Watch.
- Watch.
- She's opening it.
Watch.
(Pop)
(Proud)
- The best.
- That's awesome.
(Good job, Mom)
It was great being with you all.
This is seriously so refreshing.
Right? It's got that sharp bite.
How does it go this well with pork belly?
It pairs so well with food.
This is insane.
It's cold.
(Min Cheol hands Jin Joo
his padded jacket.)
This is so thick.
That's warm.
Hyun Jin's mother...
(Awkward laugh)
No.
He went on a lunch date with Hyun Jin,
then went on another date
with someone else in the evening,
and now he's even
taking his jacket off for her.
I honestly don't get what's in his head.
That feels pretty lousy.
(Puts on her own jacket, displeased)
- Pour a drink for your future son-in-law.
- You've got to make a good impression.
Go pour a drink for the man.
Everyone already knows.
It's already way too obvious,
so I don't even need to.
Still, go pour him a drink.
- I can't.
- Just try.
I have a conscience. I don't think I can.
A conscience?
It's embarrassing.
I should do it.
Where are you going?
(Heads somewhere with resolve)
Min Cheol.
Here, have a drink.
Her mother...
Jin Joo's mother.
She...
Min Cheol, I'll pour you a drink.
I'll pour you a drink.
Thank you, ma'am.
(Stands up abruptly)
My goodness.
Looks like he's been chosen.
(Jin Joo's mother gathers courage
and approaches Min Cheol.)
- Nice to meet you.
I worked up the courage.
Thank you, ma'am.
She's honestly so cool.
Young moms really are different.
(I liked that.)
Thank you, ma'am.
Chug it.
That's it.
You've got to finish it
shake it over your head.
That's awesome.
So cool.
I'm happy because Jin Joo's smiling.
What a relief...
that Jin Joo can smile.
Jin Joo also told me this.
(During lunch that day)
Mom, you should go over to Min Cheol.
What? Why would I?
Give him a little nudge.
How am I supposed to nudge him?
Mom, you're popular.
To show my support,
I gathered my courage...
and poured Min Cheol a drink.
(The mother approaches Min Cheol
at her daughter's request.)
I wanted to be a mother
who could help Jin Joo.
Someone Jin Joo can like,
and someone who will like Jin Joo.
I kept thinking he might be that person.
I'm so grateful to my mother,
and also to Min Cheol
for taking it so kindly.
Right.
They're writing a drama.
Jin Joo's mother stepped forward first.
- Even though that's not really her style.
- No, it isn't.
But just now...
She's showing how she feels.
She stepped up for her daughter.
For her child.
She went all in to seal the deal.
That's how mothers feel.
Thank you, ma'am.
That's awesome.
She's really amazing.
Seriously.
That was impactful.
(After the final dinner ends)
Earlier, when we went to dinner,
Hyun Jin didn't look at me at first.
Really?
The moment I walked in, I noticed her.
But she couldn't look at me.
Later, when I kept looking,
she finally smiled at me.
- She must've felt something too.
- Right.
I guess I can't help
being the bad guy to someone.
Yeah.
Jin Joo's here.
How cute.
(Jin Joo comes to return Min Cheol's hat.)
Hello.
Both of the jackets
Jin Joo's holding are mine.
That's wild.
Yes, that's Min Cheol's.
It looks good on you.
You didn't have to do this.
I wanted to talk,
but I didn't get the chance.
Right, that's true.
I think this is the first time
I've seen your face this close.
- Let's sit first.
- Yeah, sit down first.
What did you buy?
What is it?
This is from the café downstairs.
(Gasp)
What do we do? Do we share it?
She brought exactly what you like.
Right.
So the question is, can we share this?
She came to really lock it in.
She's never really talked
to Min Cheol's mother before.
To score points with her.
But what I appreciated was this.
When I first saw everyone,
I thought Min Cheol would be the oldest.
And the women all seemed young to me.
Everyone's pretty,
and it's hard to guess ages.
So I thought, "I should probably
let go of my expectations."
But even on the first night, I chose him.
- Really?
- Yes.
Can we say that
just among the three of us?
I don't know.
(While Jin Joo
and Min Cheol share a secret)
But shouldn't the person involved
be allowed to say it?
Let's go for a walk. I'm really full.
Okay.
(Seung Hak and Myo Jin go out for a walk.)
Should we take a longer walk tonight?
A longer one? Okay.
- To help digest.
- Sure.
So now,
have you decided on anything?
Or are you still torn?
Am I being too mean?
No, not at all.
I'm just torn.
I'm really torn. This is so hard.
I can't really enjoy this situation.
I've never been
in something like this before.
Then do you lean toward...
comfort, or more toward...
If I think about marriage,
I think I'd go for comfort.
But when I'm dating,
I think I seek excitement.
That makes sense.
Right.
But right now,
what do you seek?
Honestly,
what stirs my curiosity more is...
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Se Hoon does have more of that pull.
But when I'm with you,
I keep finding myself smiling.
Just seeing you makes me smile.
Normally, when I'm with Se Hoon,
it's more stimulating,
so you didn't really cross my mind.
But lately, when I'm with him,
your face suddenly pops into my head.
I was like, "Why?"
Am I kind of like smiling like this?
Behind Se Hoon?
"Look at me."
So between the two of you,
without meaning to...
Seung Hak kept expressing
his feelings so steadily...
and so consistently.
But Se Hoon is more like,
"I'm interested in two people."
And I'm similar, but still,
he's weighing two people too.
Taking all that into account,
I think someone
who keeps showing their feelings...
like Seung Hak might be better.
That thought just suddenly hit me.
Maybe that really is right.
Right now, the person I'm most drawn to
is Seung Hak.
And second is Se Hoon.
I had so much fun today.
Today?
It felt a bit different today too.
Right?
I really like your mother.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I was wondering
if my mother was enjoying this.
She looked like she was having fun.
Really?
I keep wondering if I've made things
harder for her because of me.
Like what?
What do you think?
I know this situation...
doesn't perfectly line up with
the kind of spouse she imagines for me.
So the choices I'm making right now...
But look.
The fact that you and I connected here...
came from a genuine place,
but does that mean...
it has to carry
such an overwhelming weight?
I really hope you don't see it that way.
I see it as a choice
that can always be revisited.
But that doesn't feel light.
Whatever choice I make.
The situation...
If she were,
say, born in 1998,
I'd go for her without any concerns.
But if things were to go wrong
halfway while trying to adjust,
then my time and her time
wouldn't feel the same.
To them, that time could feel much more...
like it was wasted.
Even if I don't see it as a waste.
This is really hard, honestly.
It's just...
really...
I'll think about it more.
(The final night comes to an end
amid deep concerns.)
At last, the decision day.
The day of the final decision has arrived.
- Decision Day.
- Yes.
(The long-awaited day
of the final decision)
(Early morning,
Han Gyeol and his mother get ready.)
(Han Gyeol is writing something.)
That's too long, Han Gyeol.
Mom.
I'll take care of this myself.
Putting your feelings
into words like that...
Looks like he's writing a letter.
Is she crying?
This doesn't feel good.
(Han Gyeol breaks down in tears
while writing the letter.)
Why? While writing the letter...
Is it something like, "I just can't
overcome the age difference"?
He must've burst into tears while writing.
Mom.
My goodness.
I feel so bad.
You feel bad?
Yeah.
Did you write your final letter?
The fact that he's crying means...
something he couldn't overcome.
It doesn't seem like a good sign.
In Match to Marry: With Parents,
we are looking for people who want to find
a partner together with their mother.
If you're interested in joining,
please don't hesitate to apply below.
We look forward to your applications.
For a couple to become a final match,
both mothers must approve...
their son's and daughter's choice.
(Everyone is in shock
at the final selection rule.)
This is insane.
(The mothers' final interviews
before the final decision)
What I'm stuck on now...
is not only the age difference.
Life really...
can't be filled with only good things.
Did she call them to persuade them?
Or to tell them to give up?
Then you just shouldn't make a choice.
You think so too, right?
Yes.
I don't think they'll make a choice.
We will now begin the final selection.
I will go to the person
who made my heart flutter.
I choose...
(Who will Han Gyeol choose?)
No way.
(The final gate, the mother's decision
Approval or rejection)
Is she still hesitating?
- My goodness.
Really? Why?
Dramaday.me