[English subtitles are available]
[Road Home]
[Episode 22]
You normally
talk quite a lot
with Lu Yanchen.
We've known each other for so long.
When men come together,
we talk more.
I don't know
what to talk about with a girl.
Are you tired?
No.
Show me around.
Sure.
Where do you want to go? I'll take you there.
Is Qining close?
Yes, very close, it's just half an hour away.
Great.
If we go further down, we'll enter Qining.
When I first came here
to report,
I stood on the prairie and watched for a long time.
It's indeed a scenery
you can't see in Beijing.
Yes.
When we get to a place with a broader view,
let's go down and I'll show you around.
As for things like malls,
since you're here,
I don't think you'd be interested to see them, right?
No shopping malls.
I just want to see the scenery of our country.
Okay, I'll show them to you.
Do you want to ride a camel?
Is there?
There are some nearby.
Tourists would rent them.
I'll go get two.
I will ride one by myself?
I don't know how.
Well...
It's not too good
for the two of us to ride one.
I'm not saying I'd ride one with you,
but that
I'd learn, and would need you to help hold the camel.
Sure, no problem.
Wait here.
I'll go get one.
He's just like his son.
Captain Qin.
Will you help me or not?
Of course.
Well,
I'm afraid I might cross the line.
Captain Qin,
you don't look like someone who had married before.
A wife is a wife.
You are a girl,
of course I should be more careful as to how I treat you.
How feudal.
Come here.
Sit tight.
You look better
on the camel.
I'll hold it
and let it walk.
Okay.
Before I came to Qining,
I've never rode a camel before.
I learned even horseriding
only after I came here.
After I have stayed here
for a long time,
I gradually became like Captain Lu,
and now take this
as my second hometown.
Anywhere on our great
motherland is our hometown.
It's the same everywhere.
I didn't expect
you to have such a broad outlook in life.
What do you mean?
When I was young,
there was a flood.
There were many people
who came to help from everywhere.
So when it comes to crucial times,
it's all the same.
Every province is the same.
The only difference is
the difference in scenery.
They are indeed here.
Qin Mingyu
knows nothing but work,
and has no life.
If I get him to bring a girl around,
good chance he'd bring them
here.
Qin Mingyu.
You're here.
Do you want to ride a camel?
You go ahead.
Don't worry about us.
You can't ride it now.
Next time.
Got it.
You really don't treat me as an outsider?
I'm just...
What are you doing?
Business has not been good these days.
I have to drink with
those bosses at night.
He's a child.
It's not convenient.
All right.
Leave the kid with me.
You're the best in the world.
Stop.
I'm married.
I know, I know.
I wouldn't dare to mess with Qin.
Qin.
I'm leaving then.
Bye.
Xiaonan.
Call me if anything happens.
Keep in touch.
Did you notice that
he's afraid of you?
He's not.
He's a good person.
He's avoiding suspicion.
You're still defending him?
It's rare.
I quite like him.
In the past few days,
some old friends
asked me
if he's reliable to work with.
I said of course.
Stop talking about adult things.
There's a child here.
We don't have children either.
Why don't you try taking care of him?
I'll try?
Hello, I'm Qin Feng.
Hello, Uncle.
My name is Qin Xiaonan.
Good.
We are all
Aunt Gui Xiao,
and Uncle Lu Chen's good friends.
When you are in Beijing,
it's inevitable that we might take turns to take care of you.
You see, with more parents
taking care of you,
and bringing you out to play,
it is quite a good deal too.
Right?
He's so tough.
Duan Rou was not sleepy.
I have nowhere to take her.
Yes.
I was the one who wanted to come here.
Are there
better places suitable for
Lu Chen and I to strengthen our relationship?
Of course.
Take us there.
Yes, take us there.
But it's a bit far.
Take your time to drive.
Okay.
All right.
You can't even talk.
We'll take the same car.
You talked to me about her before she came.
Now that she's here,
you're all so timid.
I'm not.
I'm just afraid that
I will be a bad host to Gui Xiao's friend.
She's been taking care of Xiaonan for you
for so long.
She's just Gui Xiao's friend to you?
Of course.
Where's your conscience?
Fine.
I kind of like her, but
I don't think I deserve her.
You're usually all cool.
Why are you so quiet now?
What?
Actually,
I’m here
to firstly see Lu Chen.
Secondly,
I want you to formally
meet Qin Mingyu.
I see.
I just haven't decided.
It looks like...
he's not too interested
in me.
When I was riding the camel,
he didn't want to help me get on it.
But I don't think that way.
I think he's
quite interested in you.
Really?
Lu Chen thinks so too.
He knows Qin Mingyu.
[Meili Valley]
So beautiful.
Take care of Duan Rou.
I'll look after my wife.
Okay.
Look over there.
It's a bit high up.
Don't be afraid.
Let's go.
I'm here.
Wait, wait.
Let me tie my hair first.
Oh my god.
♫Hey, what day is it today?♫
Look forward.
♫Can I see you?♫
But if I look forward,
I won't be able to see the scenery below.
♫Let the heartbeat continue 110♫
The scenery in the middle is more beautiful.
♫It's so troublesome♫
♫You haven't got up yet♫
♫You didn't see my message♫
♫Did anyone tell you♫
♫I miss you very much♫
♫Love is in vogue♫
♫You still need to be quiet♫
♫Even the moon is awakened♫
♫Even meteors stop♫
♫Love songs are popular♫
♫I'll sing for you♫
♫We need to cultivate our relationship♫
♫I believe you can do it♫
[Beijing, Shanghai, Hangzhou, Hefei, Nanjing, Shenyang]
Do you want to go?
No, no.
I'm afraid of heights.
What about when you travel, then?
Don't you go hiking?
I'm fine normally.
But I can't deal with those that hang
in the middle of the air.
Let's just
enjoy the scenery here.
Muster the courage to try.
I'm here.
Fine.
Since I'm going to try,
then let's try the most exciting one.
[Line A starting point]
Hello, welcome.
Hello.
Let's go back.
I'm here. Go ahead.
Come on.
Look forward.
I'm fine.
Steady, steady.
Step by step.
Go.
Look.
Duan Rou.
This is the first time
Qin Mingyu is on the bridge.
He refused to do it before.
He thought it was not sturdy.
Really?
It's to make him look good.
Is what Captain Lu said
true?
No.
I came here often.
There was once
I even brought Xiaonan
to cross from here to over there.
Then...
Why did he say this is your first time here?
Maybe it's to
leave you a good impression.
You're honest.
It's a bonus.
This is
one of my strengths.
Look at both sides.
No.
It's too difficult.
Take a look.
Otherwise, if we miss it,
it'll be a pity.
I didn't expect it
to be so beautiful.
I didn't think this way
when I came here last time.
But it seems that way this time.
Are you tired?
No.
It's so beautiful here.
Do you come here often?
With what time?
Right.
It's rare that you get a day off.
How about
going to Qining Police Station later?
We can live in the old apartment building.
Is it convenient?
Duan Rou has never been there.
Ask Captain Qin.
Captain Qin.
Is it convenient?
What do you mean?
We're not going back.
Keep playing.
Get everyone who's
off work over.
Okay.
Guys,
bring the things down from the car.
Okay.
Copy that.
Sister-in-law.
Hello.
You came at the right time.
Captain Lu.
We just bought some food
from town.
Let's have barbecue tonight.
You dropped something.
Carbonated water is perfect for barbecue.
Can't you see me?
Every single time.
Why are you jealous of the ex-captain?
I’m jealous
because I love you guys.
I didn't expect you to be the type to get jealous.
Just kidding.
Here, drink up.
This is...
She's sister-in-law's friend,
Duan Rou.
Hello.
She's not just Gui Xiao's friend.
She is Officer Qin's–
Stop.
Didn't you buy a lot?
Carbonated water, right?
Let's go. I'll move two boxes with you. Let's go.
Let me finish.
What are you talking about?
Listen.
When those guys come over,
don't joke using Duan Rou.
Even she doesn't care.
Why do you care?
She doesn't
because she's generous.
Enough.
You’re blushing.
How can you talk to the captain like that?
Captain Qin,
we are wearing plain clothes today.
Well, thank you guys.
It’s my duty.
Captain Lu.
Sit.
Sister-in-law,
we meet again.
I think
sister-in-law has gotten prettier.
Yes.
I don't need
you to say my wife is pretty.
It's a praise. You don't like hearing it?
Captain Lu,
you've really changed.
You're overprotective of your family.
It's smokey here.
Just sit down and wait to eat.
I'm just pregnant.
I'm not so delicate
I can't do anything.
And I've never camped before.
I just want to experience it.
Okay, experience it.
Have a seat first.
As long as I'm here,
you can experience it.
Just have a big appetite.
That's good.
The doctor told me to eat normally.
Eat as much as I can.
It's nutritious for the child.
Gain some weight.
You don't mind?
No.
Zhong.
I've been looking at
that little guy for a long time.
Let me carry it.
Okay.
You haven't eaten anything yet.
You just washed your hands.
It's okay. I'll wash it again later.
Let me carry it first.
Here.
Hey there.
Is it also a police dog?
No.
My wife's dog gave birth to it.
So cute.
Didn't you also use to raise a police dog?
The one that was
buried with the old captain.
Tianwen's police team gave me
a small dog afterwards.
But Lin Nan
is taking care of it for me now.
It's probably all grown up.
I remember when we were studying,
there was a big dog in the garage.
I didn't dare to touch it.
Only you dared to.
They're actually timid.
If you treat them fiercely,
they will be scared.
But I guess the ones that
Lin Nan is taking care of at Tianwen are all grown up.
I don't think they'll recognize me when I go back.
They will.
I heard that dogs
are very intelligent.
Right?
It's rare to have someone do this for me.
No one has done this for me.
I thought you were asleep
since I didn't hear anything coming from here.
Being able to sleep while sitting
is also a skill of mine.
If you're sleepy,
I'll leave now.
I'm not sleepy.
About Xiaonan...
We can
talk about something else.
Okay.
You start.
What about stories from when you were in school?
Things that can be called stories
are exciting.
Mine are
very ordinary.
I'm not full of
ups and downs either.
Most people's lives
are all similar.
But the details are different.
My grades were just average.
The teacher didn't care too much either.
But before the college entrance exam,
just a year ago,
I worked hard,
and my grades went up.
It means you are talented.
You can improve a lot
in just a year.
I'm not exactly talented either.
Anyway, it's something you got from hard work.
Working hard means you have perseverance.
It's senior year.
Who dares to not have perseverance?
Me.
You're being humble.
You must be a straight-A student.
That year,
I suddenly didn't want to learn anymore.
I wasted my senior year.
Why?
Since when I was young,
I worked too hard.
I had always been very tense.
I dared not slack off.
I knew I couldn't slack off.
When I was in senior year,
I suddenly felt it was meaningless.
I ate and slept for a whole year.
I got the same grade for the first test
of the first semester that year
as my Gaokao.
Basically, I didn't study.
You have a personality.
But there's a good thing about it too.
When you relax
when you should be the tensest
in your life,
you will find that
many things in life
are not that important.
It'd be easier to face it.
I don't know if
what you're saying is of bad influence,
but I learned a lot.
Life experiences are very important.
When I was in senior year,
others chose to get high grades,
yet I chose to relax.
Later,
after I got my marriage registered,
I got a divorce
before I could hold a wedding.
Even that was not a big deal to me.
During the English exam in my senior year,
I handed in the paper half an hour earlier.
When I went out,
all parents were waiting at the gate
waiting to pick up their children.
When they saw me,
they'd just think that
I didn't do well in the exam.
But in fact, I did well.
Thinking about it now,
it's all just experiences.
Yes.
Senior year
is a fortune in life.
After starting work,
I don't remember
many things
as clearly as I did from my schooling days.
That's why
my ability to work under pressure
was trained during my time
in school.
Duan Rou.
You're so hotblooded.
That's a nice thing for you to say.
Here.
A toast to you.
I will take it as a praise.
Go ahead.
Duan Rou and Qin Mingyu,
what are they talking about?
When I came in,
I saw them talking and laughing
so happily.
I have no idea.
You have nothing to say to me?
When we were young, you were always the one who talked more.
I didn't talk much.
I came all the way here.
Can't you just talk
a little more?
Don't we call
when we're free?
I read the dozens
of messages you send me
every day too.
Can you recite it?
I'm asking you.
When will you grow up?
You're even asking
the same question as when we were young.
You're sick of me?
I dare not.
Give me a kiss.
That didn't come from your heart.
We're in a tent.
They have sharp ears.
We are legally wedded.
It's late.
You're still up?
I came out to train the solders.
Okay.
You train the soldiers.
I'll watch.
They are soldiers you've taught before.
I can't do it anymore.
You do it.
You're not sleepy?
It's because it's rare that
everyone could relax for a night.
I'm going to go walk the dog.
I'm a little hungry.
I'll go find something to eat.
I-I'm going to go admire the moon.
Take me with you.
Watch the time you spend
in a girl's tent.
No, I...
Well...
I was just chatting.
They went back.
Go on.
I still can't sleep.
The wind here sounds so nice.
It's not noisy.
And it's not unsafe.
Your work is quite effective.
Peace and prosperity.
Thank you for your affirmation.
You're welcome.
Duan Rou.
I won't go in.
Sleep soon.
See you tomorrow.
I thought you were asleep.
The air is fresh here.
Come get some fresh air.
It's good.
Thank you.
Look.
I can't find a topic to talk about again.
No need to talk.
This is good too.
But talking to you
makes me relaxed.
Same.
Why are you smiling so weird?
The night is nice.
The night is beautiful.
What?
Don't disturb them.
I'm curious.
What's there to be curious about?
You've never been in a relationship?
Lie down.
Go to sleep.
If you want to watch the show,
go watch it outside if you have the guts.
Why come and cram this place up?
I dare not go out.
You can hear some things from here.
Come on.
Pair of jokers.
No.
I want to listen carefully.
Focus.
Me too.
What do you think Captain Qin is talking about
with Duan Rou?
Don't talk.
What are you doing?
Practicing my skills.
Let's sleep.
Come.
Me too.
I'm not leaving. Let's squeeze a little.
Wait, you...
Captain Qin’s ears
are particularly good.
He's shy
dating a girl.
Keep your voice down.
Aren’t you afraid Captain Qin will hear you?
So what if he does.
He can't always hit us
with stones.
Captain Qin.
We've already laid down.
Go on.
We can't hear you.
Good idea.
Captain Qin.
All the best.
Should I say something too?
Captain Qin–
Go to sleep.
You're awake.
Good morning.
To be honest,
I understand your work.
But I still think about it when I should.
To be honest,
most of the time,
I think I'm doing a good job.
But when I think of you,
I feel guilty.
I'm a little touched.
They went back.
They had a mission last night
and went back.
I've heard
about your line of work.
Now that I've seen it with my own eyes,
I understand that it's not easy.
There are hardships in every industry.
Let me help you.
No need.
I can do it myself.
I'll help you as much as I can.
But there's no trash left.
They took it with them.
They packed up last night
and took them away.
You're all men
but are quite considerate.
I'll help them pack up.
Pack up?
They're cultivating their relationship too.
So we're not going out?
I want to wash up.
Wait a little.
They'll leave soon.
They are not awake yet.
What are we going to do?
Let's have breakfast.
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Let's just drive out first.
Eat whatever we see.
Okay.
You're right.
I know him.
Let's go.
Where did they go?
No need to ask.
Should we look for them?
No.
If Qin Mingyu wants us
to find him,
he will let us know.
You two
are such a perfect match.
You can finally tell that we're in sync.
Yes.
We've cooperated
on many missions.
We've been through
life and death.
If we don't have any tacit understanding,
we wouldn't dare to give our lives to each other.
A life-or-death friendship.
Those in our business,
it's really...
Captain Lu and I
used to come here often
to buy some delicious food
and bring them to everyone.
There is no delicious food
at where you all are at?
Of course there is. Our team's
benefits are very good.
It's just, sometimes,
I want to eat something special
so I'd come out to buy some.
At the same time.
also get some fresh air.
What's wrong?
I want to go to the train station.
Train station?
Yes.
I've never seen the train station here.
When I go somewhere,
I like to go to their train station.
Every province and county's
train stations are all different.
Each has its own characteristics.
The tourists are different.
It's also a way
of understanding the local culture.
It's curiosity.
Do you understand?
People are different.
Curiosity doesn't matter.
If you want to go,
I'll take you there.
No wonder we get along well.
What?