[English subtitles are available]
Uncle Lu.
Why are you still up?
Will I have to go back to Qining
after your baby comes out?
Qining is too far away.
It's too troublesome to send you back.
Just stay here.
There will be no room for me.
The baby...
Aunt Gui Xiao said
she really likes this house.
It took her a long time to find it.
This is what we adults should think about.
It has nothing to do with you.
You couldn't fall asleep
because of this?
I don't want to leave Aunt Gui Xiao
and Aunt Duan Rou.
It has nothing to do with you.
You forgot me and your dad?
You first looked at the car,
and then looked at the moon.
You're very happy, right?
Yes.
I'm too happy to fall asleep.
Alright, go to bed.
I'm going out.
Go.
Walk lightly when you
go up and down the stairs.
Aunt Gui Xiao
needs enough sleep now.
Go.
Bro.
Well,
I had just got my glass
and taken my first sip
when you called me out.
What is it?
Why must you ask me out?
Say something.
Don't.
I'll get a fracture.
I'm old now.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
You're so garrulous.
Can your girlfriend stand it?
I'm single.
I'm afraid of marriage.
I was dumped.
Are you going to be single forever?
Probably.
Now,
the word "marriage"
always reminds me
that I kneeled in front of her home
and cried
on her wedding day.
The person I want to marry most
married another man.
Finding another one?
No.
I can't forget her.
I only told you about this.
What happened to you?
On my way here,
I was thinking,
what could make you
lose control?
Are you...
I'm going to be a father.
According to the due date,
the baby will come out before the Spring Festival.
What?
You two...
You two took a rocket?
You reunited
and got back together.
Now you're going to be a father.
You're going to be a father!
You...
I...
My God.
Wait.
Let me digest it.
You...
I...
I'm...
jealous.
I'm happy for you.
Of the two couples back then,
one finally made it last
and are going to have a child.
Next,
you'll have children and grandchildren
and grow old together.
We'll grow old together.
I'm happy for you.
I'm happy for you two.
I've lived in many places.
But I've never had
a real home.
Now I have one.
Gosh, it's you who are going to be a father.
Why am I crying?
It's so embarrassing.
So embarrassing. Let me calm down.
I can't.
Enough.
How come you're going to be a father?
I'm going to be an uncle.
Can I be your child's godfather?
Fine, you can.
Let me be your godfather.
Stop it.
Why don't you be my godfather?
Get lost!
I beg you, Lu Chen.
What if…
I mean, what if
the previous doctor got it wrong?
It's nothing.
We'll just keep working on it.
Stop it.
I can't go in with you.
Be careful.
It's just a B-scan.
What's there to be careful about?
Since we were in the car,
you've been absent-minded.
What if you fall down?
I'm not a kid anymore.
Okay.
I'll be careful.
In the next ten months,
I'll walk slowly
and slowly.
I don't know
how long it will take.
Be patient.
I took the robot's manual with me.
I'm going to translate it for the students.
Go in.
Take your time.
No hurry.
Come in.
Give me the form.
Lie down here.
Lift up your top.
It's a bit cold.
Doctor, am I pregnant?
Yes.
How is the baby?
Do I have an ectopic pregnancy?
Is its heart beating?
Don't be afraid.
The baby's fine.
Did you search for information
online?
I searched for
all possible
problems.
Don't be nervous.
Relax.
Look.
12.6 mm
multiplied by 9.4 mm
multiplied by 14.6 mm.
It's this little.
It's too early.
I can't tell if there's any problem.
Go to the obstetrics department for detailed tests
when you're three months pregnant.
Aren't obstetrics and gynecology combined in one department?
No.
They're two separate departments.
When you register,
just choose the obstetrics department.
You can
consult the doctor there.
Now the baby
seems fine.
Just take good care of it.
What should I pay attention to?
The most important thing
is to stay in a good mood.
This is your first pregnancy, right?
Go get a birth permit first.
Only with this permit can you build
your medical record in the obstetrics department.
After that,
you'll be asked to do regular prenatal tests.
Okay.
You can get the permit from the neighborhood office
with your marriage certificate.
As for the procedure in your neighborhood,
you can check online
or make a call.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I asked the doctor about its age.
She said it's more than five weeks.
Do you think
we got it in Qining
or after we came back?
It's hard to say.
I don't remember either.
I just want to know it.
Does it matter?
Yes.
Think about it.
I want to tell our baby
where I got pregnant.
It's hard
to figure it out.
I wish it was in Qining.
That's your second hometown.
It's more memorable.
Besides,
that's where
we reconnected.
It should be in Qining.
Really?
Really.
I'm sure
it was in Qining.
After we go back,
I'll go find my leader in the SWAT team
and ask about the marriage application.
I'll try to
get our marriage certificate this month.
Give me some advice.
I've never booked a wedding banquet.
Your place hosts wedding banquets every day.
What do people like to eat here?
Pick what you like first.
I'll go through it with you later.
Give me your account number.
I'll transfer the money to you.
You haven't chosen the dishes,
yet you're going to pay the deposit first?
That's not what I meant.
I was talking about the money
Hai Dong borrowed from you and gave to Lu Chen.
Are you kidding me?
You didn't borrow the money.
I feel sorry.
It has nothing to do with Lu Chen
and you.
Hai Dong
borrowed the money from me
based on our relationship.
It's between me and Hai Dong.
Listen.
Don't pay the money back
to Hai Dong.
In junior high,
he made trouble with a group of hooligans.
If Lu Chen hadn't stopped him,
he would have been doomed.
Don't get involved in the things
between them.
If Lu Chen wants you
to get involved,
he won't be
the Lu Chen I know.
I understand.
I have Lu Chen's salary account
and salary slip.
He earns a good salary.
He'll be able to pay Hai Dong back soon.
Right.
Let him
solve his own problem.
He has his pride.
Put yourself in his shoes.
If you owe a debt,
and he secretly repays it for you,
will you be happy?
You have
such strong pride.
It's good.
What?
Who doesn't want to cherish the one
they fell for when they were in school?
But not everyone is worth it.
Even if it's worth it,
not everyone has the chance.
Isn't Qin Feng good?
What are you talking about?
I'm not thinking about Hai Dong.
I just
suddenly thought of it.
It seems that what happened between Hai Dong and me
was in my previous life.
But you and Lu Chen
are still in this life.
It's great.
I hope we'll both be fine.
Of course.
We are good people.
What God gives us
is the best.
Goodbye
to my previous life.
By the way,
do you want to hold the wedding first
or get registered first?
We haven't discussed it.
I want to get both things done this month.
If you want to hold the ceremony this month,
you probably don't have enough time.
You need to decide
who to invite,
write invitations,
and customize your wedding dress.
You can take
the wedding photos later.
But you need to leave enough time
to make the dress.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
You can't be careless.
I know a dress maker.
She can finish the dress on time.
No need.
Lu Chen won't run away.
I'll organize the wedding.
I know the process better than you.
Let me give you a suggestion.
You need to leave more time
for the wedding preparation.
Pay attention to more details
so you won't have any regrets.
If you want to
get registered this month
because Lu Chen's birthday is in this month,
you still need
about two
to three months
to prepare for the wedding.
Okay.
I'll go back and discuss with him.
Here, take it back.
Take your time to make a choice.
You're here.
I don't need to introduce him, right?
Captain Lu.
Mr. Shen.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Here.
There's a city called Xinsheng in Qining.
You used to work there.
Everybody wants you, Lu Yanchen.
I managed to
get you from the squadron.
You haven't stayed here for long.
Yet he's here to ask me to second you.
The leader there wants you
to work there for a month
to help train EOD technicians
and form a SWAT team.
First, it's because
you are familiar with things there.
Second, you are experienced.
If you work there for a month,
you can do what takes others several months to finish.
I heard about this
from Captain Qin in Qining.
Yes.
He wanted to go himself.
But they're short-handed
in Qining.
So he asked me to send you there.
I have
more men than him.
So I agreed.
When shall I go?
You can come back early
if you leave early.
Set out tomorrow.
You've received the secondment order?
Yes.
It's a special situation.
We got special approval.
Captain Lu.
Your detachment leader and I
are old friends.
I'm going to
the Civil Explosion Company tomorrow.
Let's go together tomorrow.
We can take care of each other on the way.
You are older than me.
I should take care of you.
Alright.
Since it's decided,
I need to go back and pack up.
Could you please
tell the Fourth Brigade about this?
I won't go there then.
Okay.
Go back and pack up.
Master.
Ever since that night,
I haven't seen you.
But I haven't forgotten
my skills.
I practice every day.
Hold on.
The people in this garage
are my friends.
Go there and tell them
you're Lu Yanchen's apprentice.
Ask them to teach you when they're free.
The number on it belongs to
someone called Mr. Liu.
Ask him to teach you.
It's free.
That's not appropriate, Master.
Take it.
It's fate that made us meet.
After you learn the skills,
check my wife's car
when you have time.
She's careless.
She doesn't know these.
Thank you, Master. Don't worry.
I'll get back to work.
Walk.
Don't run.
Didn't you say you'd be home tomorrow?
I had a shift change.
So I can come back today.
Now that you have a baby,
you are a family man.
But you can't let this affect your work.
I got approval from my leader.
I'm reading the menu of Meng Xiaoshan's restaurant
for the wedding banquet.
But it's hard for me to choose.
Let's choose together after dinner.
Okay.
You may have a miscarriage in the first trimester.
Try not to carry heavy things.
Did he search online secretly?
Are we celebrating the New Year?
Just eat.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Have some meat.
Okay.
Did you come back
after having a meal?
I had some food in the afternoon. I'm not hungry.
Qin Xiaonan, finish your food.
Okay.
Milk is a good source of calcium.
I feel like I've been
soaked in milk these days.
I never like milk.
You know it.
You've never liked it since childhood.
Yes.
But it's okay.
I'm strong-willed.
It takes 21 days
to form a habit.
I can make myself addicted to milk
in three days.
I'm going on a business trip.
How long?
A month.
That's okay.
Will you miss me?
Who else can I miss?
That's more like it.
Go wash up.
Okay.
Let me hug you for two more minutes.
♫When I first saw you, my heart lost its defenses♫
♫I thought about the future♫
Hello, Chen.
What is it?
Don't tell me
you're having a second child.
♫At the intersection in the early mornings and late evenings♫
I'm going on a business trip.
Please take care of my family for me.
Got it.
♫I owe you a hug♫
Roger.
Leave Xiao to me.
♫I've been wandering alone for a long time♫
I have to go.
Bye.
♫As time passes through the years♫
♫I am still here waiting♫
♫I will express my feelings bravely this time♫
♫So that I won't let you down again♫
♫Close your eyes and get closer♫
♫So that I can feel your warmth♫
♫In your world♫
♫I don't want to turn back♫
♫With your warmth♫
♫I won't be suffering from loneliness anymore♫
♫Our reunion♫
♫Takes us back to the beginning♫
♫This moment feels like♫
♫Youth does not seem to end♫
I've been waiting for you.
♫I still love you♫
♫My heart pulls towards the way back♫
Why are you waiting?
A warm bed
and a warm wife.
Hurry.
♫I will express my feelings bravely this time♫
Men should abide by the moral principles
for husbands when they're out.
♫So that I won't let you down again♫
This is going to be a test.
But you'll surely pass it without taking it.
♫Close your eyes and get closer♫
You're talking nonsense.
♫So that I can feel your warmth♫
♫In your world♫
You have a family and a child.
Be careful.
♫With your warmth♫
♫I won't be suffering from loneliness anymore♫
♫Our reunion♫
♫Takes us back to the beginning♫
♫This moment feels like♫
♫Youth does not seem to end♫
♫I still love you♫
♫And that is the best destiny♫
Are you hungry?
You're so ungrateful.
I'm going to see you off.
If only you could put me in your suitcase.
Take me with you.
And your child.
And Qin Xiaonan.
How can I leave when you're like this?
Just kidding.
I know you're kidding.
Are we doing crosstalk?
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook for you.
The food you cook is not delicious.
So picky.
Go to bed
and go back to sleep.
I'm going down and leaving.
I've lain down, Captain Lu.
You're leaving?
Take care of the home.
Got it.
I've seen many scenes like this.
Leave it to me.
Good morning, Captain Lu.
Let me do it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Captain Lu.
You must be anxious.
I asked the driver
to make a detour
to pick me up first.
Because you are different from me.
You have a family.
I wanted you to spend more time
with your family at home.
Which floor do you live on?
The third room
down from the top.
She's still sleeping.
Next time you drink milk,
don't bite the rim of the cup.
This cup is too thin.
Why did you buy such a thin cup?
I've already bought it.
I won't buy it again.
Mr. Shen.
The flight was supposed to take off at 9 am.
More than an hour ago,
we were notified that,
due to air traffic control,
the flight would be delayed for two hours.
It's now scheduled to depart at 11:20 am.
Okay, got it.
Then
drop me off over there.
I forgot something.
Okay.
I'll take your luggage
to the airport.
Okay.
See you at the boarding gate.
Qin Xiaonan, what are you doing?
I'm taking care of this home.
You've grown up unexpectedly.
Being the wife of a policeman
is not easy.
I don't need you to teach me.
I'm not talking to you.
I need to work. Don't disturb me.
You arrived so soon?
Come down.
Wait... wait for me.
Let me put on my shoes
and clothes.
Bring your ID card
and household register.
Wear your favorite clothes.
The clothes that look good on a red background
will be the best.
♫Hey, what day is it today?♫
♫Can I see you?♫
♫Let the heartbeat continue 110♫
♫It's so troublesome♫
♫You haven't got up yet♫
Are you going to
elope with me?
We only have two hours.
♫You didn't see my message♫
I checked it.
The Civil Affairs Bureau opens at 8:30 am.
Let's be the first couple to get registered.
♫Did anyone tell you♫
We are really going to get registered?
Get in.
♫I miss you very much♫
♫Love is in vogue♫
♫You still need to be quiet♫
♫Even the moon is awakened♫
♫Even meteors stop♫
♫Love songs are popular♫
♫I'll sing for you♫
♫We need to cultivate our relationship♫
♫I believe you can do it♫
Let me tell you something first.
You didn't take your ID card?
I took it.
You lost your household register?
My aunt works here.
Gui Xiao.
What?
Are you here to ask for help from your aunt?
No, I...
I'm just passing by.
It's my first time. I'm a bit nervous.
Your cousin happens to be here.
Xiao.
I'll leave you to it.
I'm going to work.
Okay.
Captain Lu.
Xiao.
Come here. I have something to tell you.
Your dad and mom are here to get divorced.
I've heard about it.
They went to the legal department
to have their divorce agreement reviewed.
I think you should persuade them.
Your dad is well-off now.
Why bother?
I haven't said a word.
You're imagining the ending.
Am I wrong?
Didn't...
Didn't you bring your first love,
who's a SWAT officer,
to stop a possible fight?
Why did you come to
the Civil Affairs Bureau early in the morning?
I brought breakfast to my mom.
My dad wanted
to give my mom a surprise,
so he asked me to come here.
Hurry.
My dad is really
a model husband.
Alright.
I'll stop talking with you.
I'm going to get married.
Go ahead.
You two...
It's early in the morning.
We need to queue up?
Do we still have time?
Maybe we have to come another day.
Xiao.
Does your family know about you getting married?
Yes.
I don't have time to talk to you now.
Lu Chen is leaving soon.
You know this place best.
How long do we have to wait?
He's in a hurry to leave?
Yes.
He's on a mission.
Wait for me.
Well...
I'm sorry.
Um,
my brother-in-law is a SWAT officer.
He finally
got round to come here
for marriage registration.
After they get registered,
he'll go on a mission right away.
Can we change our numbers?
Sure. No problem.
Of course.
Thank you.
We kind of cut in line.
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you.
I was just about to say
that you could take our number if they didn't agree.
Let them get registered quickly
so he can go on his mission.
Thank you.
Let's change the numbers.
Xiao, Chen, come here.
They agreed to
let you get registered first.
Thank you.
Is it appropriate?
You're in a hurry, right?
Don't stand on ceremony.
Here.
Sorry about the trouble.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well,
why don't you wait here?
I'll go to my mom's office
to get some wedding candy
to share with everyone.
Today is a good day.
I'll go first.
Go there to take a photo first.
We have an experienced photographer.
You can also take the photo by yourselves.
But I suggest
you let the photographer do it.
Why?
He has feelings.
He can make you smile more happily.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Actually, I've always dreamed of
taking wedding photos in your police station.
I'll keep it in mind.
As long as my leader agrees,
I'll let you do it.
But if we take photos in the police station,
I can't wear a wedding dress that's too gorgeous,
since it won't
look serious enough, right?
It's up to you.
You can wear whatever you want.
Girl,
let's take the photo first.
Okay.
She talks too much when she's happy.
Who won't be happy
when they're getting married?
Show your happiness
on your faces.
Okay.
Hello, do you want to get a premarital checkup?
Yes.
He'll get it.
I get a checkup every year.
We're already here.
Just do it.
We still have time.
Where can he get the checkup?
Over there.
Thank you.
What tests did you take?
A physical
and a surgical test.
What else?
That's all.
You're lying.
They saw that you're pregnant,
and asked what else I wanted to check.
I said my wife
has been curious since childhood.
She made me come in.
I didn't get the checkup.
We just had a few words.
Fill in the form first.
I'll issue
today's first two marriage certificates for you.
You are quite used to
bullying my brother-in-law.
You let him do everything.
His handwriting is better than mine.
Tell your mom that she can't
tell this to my father
in any case.
My mom knows it.
But as for my dad,
I'll think about
what to do later.
Let's share our happiness.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Come on.
Let's share our happiness.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I can't send you home.