[English subtitles are available]
[Road Home]
[Episode 16]
Are you in a hurry?
I thought I could have a chat with you.
Maybe another day.
My girlfriend gets up late.
If I eat fast,
I can rush back
and make her breakfast.
Okay.
We'll talk about it when you're free.
Actually,
I have nothing much to say.
I'm afraid you would be upset
because of what happened yesterday.
I've been used to it.
Lu Chen.
Don't be lazy. Cook it yourself.
Do I still need to cook myself?
[Hongrun Chenghua]
Is it for me?
Lu Chen made it.
Didn't you say you didn't have breakfast?
So I brought it for you.
I got up late this morning.
Then I took Xiaonan to school in a rush.
What is this?
A letter.
Qin Mingyu gave it to you.
Qin Mingyu?
Qin Xiaonan's father.
Oh yeah.
Captain Qin.
Is there something urgent?
What decade is he living in to write a letter?
I don't know.
He's showing his sincerity.
Take your time.
[Letter of appreciation]
This brother is so honest.
Captain.
Where did you go
on a mission?
The sewer.
Why didn't you take a shower before coming?
I have something to tell you.
I'll take my bath after I finish.
Zhong.
Recently,
two new team members
have not gotten used to the climate.
They're not acclimated to the environment.
If you can find time at night,
go and patrol the dorms.
Captain.
Why don't you go by yourself?
It's inconvenient for me.
As a leader,
I should treat everyone fairly.
Right?
If I care too much about the new members,
what about the senior ones?
Besides, if there's a mission,
should the newbies go first
or the veterans?
It's indeed a hidden rule.
Of course.
Our team is special.
We always assign the high-ranked ones
to perform the task first.
I must be the first.
What if I die?
At least, you should say "die in the line of duty."
OK, die in the line of duty.
What if I die in the line of duty?
If you die in the line of duty,
the deputy captain will take over.
You're heartless.
All right, cut to the chase.
An old player
should be prepared to die at any moment
and care more for our new comrades.
Do you get it?
Also,
you have to know...
[Duan Rou]
It's not a big deal. No need to call me back.
Call her back.
Normally, when people say
"I don't want you to call me back,"
it means you have to call them back.
I have a girlfriend.
I know the rules.
I was married before.
But, you're divorced.
Let's add each other on WeChat.
So that I can contact you more conveniently.
Okay.
Okay for what?
What's your WeChat ID?
It is the same as my phone number.
Got it.
[I'm Duan Rou.]
Your girlfriend?
Get lost.
I'll get back to work first.
Keep in touch.
I knew it. She is indeed your girlfriend.
She sent you so many
Xiaonan's photos.
Mind your own business.
Wash my car too.
Did you call Captain Qin?
No.
I thought
you were going to call him.
This is not like you.
Not quite polite.
I did call.
But, he didn't pick up.
I remember you told me
they were often busy with their work
and they couldn't be contactable easily.
So I added him on WeChat.
What does Captain Qin look like?
He's always serious.
He looks skinny,
dark-skinned,
tall,
and he has big eyes.
That's all?
I can't describe him exactly.
Anyway, he's handsome.
Bye.
Miss Gui.
Have a seat.
What do you want?
I need to meet someone.
I just came back not long ago.
I have to be an eager beaver.
I'm also a manager.
I have the same position as you.
Do you think that I am an idle person?
Sit down.
Let me care about you,
the blissful woman
coming back from the prairie.
Five minutes.
Are you two
done?
Amazing.
You know what I am talking about?
The talk is over.
Sit.
Sit down.
You just went off all of a sudden.
How could Captain Lu
hold you down?
Three minutes.
Get to the point.
Okay.
What are you going to do next?
Pick your wedding date?
How do you know?
No way.
Really?
You just made up a short time ago.
Let me see.
From the Spring Festival till now,
has it reached one month?
Almost.
You're going to get married just like that?
Hello, uncle.
Dad.
I came to pick you up.
Pick me up?
I just came back.
I have a lot of work to do.
Your mom came back from overseas today.
Uncle has asked me
for your leave.
Leave the work to me. Just go ahead.
My mom is back?
Why didn't she tell me?
She didn't tell anyone.
She came back alone.
Let's go.
I guess she's still staying in the same hotel.
She came back this time...
Let's talk in the car.
Pack your things.
I'll wait for you outside.
Every time I see your dad,
I can't control myself but stand at attention.
I have to go.
Call me if you need anything.
Is Secretary Liu not here today?
It's our family affair.
We shouldn't involve others.
Your mother came back
to get a divorce from me.
I had done her wrong before.
But these years,
I've been waiting for her
to forgive me
and start over.
Mom.
Why are you here?
Did he bring you here?
It's rare for us to gather together.
I have booked the restaurant.
It's your favorite.
I'm sorry.
I have a lunch meeting with my lawyer.
To deal with the legal department
of a big company like yours,
I need at least
a professional lawyer,
not me.
I won't agree to divorce you.
Mom.
You just traveled a long way by flight.
I'll help you with the check-in first.
Dad.
You're busy. Go back first.
Mom is already back.
You can eat together later.
Your daughter has given you an out.
Do you want me to make you look bad?
Let's go to check in at the hotel.
Where are you going to have the lunch meeting?
I'll call a taxi.
No hurry.
I haven't been back for years.
As usual,
let's go to the Sichuan restaurant we often go to.
Just the two of us.
Then...
You lied to my dad.
How could I eat freely if I didn't lie to him?
You know
his temper.
He won't give up until he achieves his goal.
Also, he thought only what he said
is the truth.
Eat more.
Your first love, Lu Chen.
Do you still remember his name?
Why not?
When you broke up back then,
your eyes were red
every morning you went out.
Your teacher even asked me what had happened.
And I covered for you.
The boy
is really nice.
It's not like you have seen him before.
I've seen his handwriting
and what he wrote.
When?
After Gaokao,
I helped you to pack up your notebooks.
The words behind
were written by him, right?
"Life is tough.
We should support each other during hardships."
A boy who could write these words
must be broad-minded and have good foresight.
How did you know he wrote it?
You were so proud back then.
If it weren't for the person you like,
you wouldn't have let him
write something in your notebook.
By the way,
haven't you gone through
the divorce procedure with my dad?
I didn't know until today.
He didn't agree.
But, I came back this time
to
solve this matter completely.
But, it's different now.
If he wants a divorce,
he will have to deal with the legal department.
Perhaps the PR department will also get involved.
He's now in charge of a listed company.
It's too hard to get a divorce.
I don't want anything from what he owns now.
The year I decided to divorce
will act as a dividing line.
If so, you'll need
a defensible divorce agreement.
I'll get you a lawyer.
Dig in.
Wrap it up if you can't finish it.
You are going to help your mom to find a divorce lawyer
and divorce your dad?
She hasn't come back for years.
She can't find a reliable lawyer
in a short while.
We've worked together
with so many law firms.
Just recommend some to me.
No, sister.
The point is
you're helping your mom and your dad
to divorce.
They should have ended it long ago.
Although my parents divorced when I was young,
and no one cared about me,
I still think
it's not easy to build a family.
They're not young anymore.
But, they still want a divorce.
For what?
You too.
It's fine if you don't want to be the peacemaker.
But, you can't help them
to find a divorce lawyer.
What?
Is there a hidden story?
Not really.
It's the most vulgar one.
Back then, my dad wanted to divorce my mom
because he had an affair.
Does your dad regret it now?
Kind of.
But, my mom
is dedicated to love.
Once loyalty is broken,
she can't forgive the other no matter what.
This is indeed the foundation of marriage.
Actually, the reason I broke up with Lu Chen
was somehow related to this.
My parents fought every day.
One time, they almost hit each other.
This was not
something glorious.
So, I didn't tell others.
I wanted to talk to him.
But, I couldn't find him.
[Winter 2011]
That year, outside the school,
there was a China Unicom's office.
The office had provided payphones.
I often made long-distance calls there.
But even if I phoned him 10 times,
I would only reach him once.
Every time it reached the time we appointed to call,
he didn't answer.
Hey, babe.
I was playing video games just now.
Yes, just a few friends.
You know them all.
Don't think too much, okay?
Let me tell you.
A long-distance relationship
doesn't allow overthinking.
Stop thinking about it.
I'm eating.
I just bought KFC.
And I came here right away
to phone you.
By the way,
I forgot something.
I have class tonight.
I'm hanging up.
I love you. I really love you.
Sorry. Miss.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I still have class later.
I have to go to class.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Tell me when you're free.
I'll call you.
I must wait until you answer today.
It's too cold.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm too tired to take a shower.
Aren't you going to take a shower after standing in the snow for so long?
I can't.
Leave me a pot of hot water.
Where is Squad Leader going?
He was asked to accompany someone for self-criticism.
Someone broke the rules today.
He was late.
Mr. Xing.
Do you have a charger?
What type of charger is yours?
Let me see.
Thank you.
[Incoming call ZZZ]
Why are you calling my cell phone?
My roommate is asleep.
I can't make a phone call in the dorm.
Why have you been
using payphones lately?
A long-distance call is expensive.
I want to save money on phone bills.
We haven't contacted each other for more than ten days.
Don't you miss me?
I'm busy.
I often couldn't reach you.
Are you...
No.
No one else.
Is something so urgent
that you have to wait for my call?
It's not urgent.
If there's nothing urgent,
I'll hang up now.
I've been standing for more than ten hours today.
And I can only sleep a few more hours.
Go on with your work.
We'll talk about it later.
Aunt.
Stop!
I said stop! Did you hear me?
I didn't.
You abandoned my mom
for a woman.
That's between your mother and me.
Am I adopted?
That's my mom.
I don't want to see you. Get out.
Come home with me.
Do you hear me?
Gui Yuanshan.
Let go!
Talk to her nicely.
What are you doing?
After you leave,
don't ever come back again.
This is my home.
She can come back whenever she wants.
Sorry.
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Please redial later.
[Qiwen Police Academy]
You're going to be on duty at the International Summit.
Be serious.
I'll be at the train station.
So I can't take care of the situation.
Are you feeling well?
Have you taken your medicine?
Let's get down to business.
Our squad has made a mistake.
No more mistakes are allowed.
It will affect the overall result.
Haven't you called your girlfriend lately?
I'm being serious.
Got it, Squad Leader.
We'll fulfill our mission.
Let's go.
We can make a call tonight.
Around seven.
I have class tonight.
Maybe another day.
Are you missing your boyfriend?
No.
How about after nine tonight?
I have something to do at that moment.
Didn't you notice
in the past two months,
we had nothing to talk about
on the phone?
After that, I often couldn't reach him.
Even if we made a phone call,
we would have a fight
and then give each other the silent treatment.
We wouldn't contact each other for a month or two months.
The silent treatment in a long-distance relationship
might be fatal.
In the past, we could fight face-to-face.
So,
when you went off and walked away,
he could hold you
and coax you.
But when we were separated,
we could neither see nor touch each other.
If we were upset, we would just keep it bottled up.
Then, we would tend to overthink.
I didn't know
what happened to him every day.
He also didn't know
what happened to my family.
I'm staying at school.
I'm so torn.
There are four people in our dorm.
I don't know if I can get used to it.
I'm saving money.
I'll visit you when I have enough money.
Can we talk for one more minute,
please?
Oh no.
My mom has known who you are.
Do you miss me?
Can't you say more?
Don't we have
any common topics?
Recently,
I can't answer the phone at home.
Don't call me.
Wait for my call.
Lu Chen.
Bye.
Why aren't you saying anything?
It costs me money to call you.
I don't want to talk.
I'm too tired.
♫You gradually feel nothing about my sharing♫
Let's...
break up.
♫Hang on to coldness♫
♫I can't say good night♫
We've been fighting for four months.
♫I once believed hard work would leave no regrets♫
I'm tired.
Everyone is tired.
♫But the ending is too bad♫
It'll affect our studies.
♫Who will shoulder it for me?♫
♫We said it would last forever♫
Even if we are breaking up, you still say nothing.
♫But we were separated in the end♫
♫I wait until I give up all resistance♫
♫Let time pass by♫
At least,
♫Never thought that love♫
♫Is not about the trials and tribulations♫
♫Not that easy♫
say a few more words.
♫Let's wait until the turn♫
♫Still have expectations♫
This is the last call.
♫In the night without you♫
♫I can't shed a tear♫
♫Street lights on the corner and the darkness I passed by♫
I don't know what to say.
♫Everything's too late♫
This is delicious.
Of course.
I went to several places...
I'll take a few more.
to get this.
Have you made up your mind?
♫I once believed hard work would leave no regrets♫
Okay.
♫But the ending is too bad♫
♫Who will shoulder it for me?♫
♫We said it would last forever♫
Well,
♫But we were separated in the end♫
I won't disturb you anymore.
♫I wait until I give up all resistance♫
♫Let time pass by♫
It's time for my class.
♫Never thought that love♫
♫Is not about the trials and tribulations♫
♫Not that easy♫
Bye.
♫Let's wait until the turn♫
♫Still have expectations♫
♫In the night without you♫
♫I can't shed a tear♫
♫Street lights on the corner and the darkness I passed by♫
♫Everything's too late♫
I can't believe I have hit you.
Lu Yanchen.
Your agility is not as good as before.
Are you lovesick again?
♫We said it would last forever♫
♫But we were separated in the end♫
♫I wait until I give up all resistance♫
[Dormitory]
♫Let time pass by♫
♫Never thought that love♫
♫Is not about the trials and tribulations♫
♫Not that easy♫
♫Let's wait until the turn♫
♫Still have expectations♫
♫In the night without you♫
♫I can't shed a tear♫
♫Street lights on the corner and the darkness I passed by♫
♫Everything's too late♫
[Duty Office]
Have you lost your soul?
Why are you pacing back and forth here?
I forgot something.
Good.
Go back and pack up.
It's an emergency muster
for physical training.
We're going out to practice today.
It happened to be snowing.
Let's go to the mountainous area.
Yes.
In the future,
you'll probably be assigned anywhere.
It's common to run on mountain roads.
In the past, in order to arrest the culprits,
I went over several mountains.
Even the police dogs couldn't run anymore.
But, we were still chasing them.
Don't dawdle when you run.
Get up if you fall down.
Got it?
Yes.
The snow is getting heavier.
Stop resting.
Run! Hurry up!
Go.
You go first.
I'll bring up the rear.
It's not safe if someone is left behind.
Come on.
Let's go.
I can't run anymore.
Really?
My nose is frozen.
I need to lie down for a while.
Call me when you're leaving.
Let's...
break up.
I'll cook you a bowl of noodles.
I have eaten at school.
When I was young,
I thought breaking up
was super easy.
So I kept mentioning it.
I had mentioned it many times.
But that time,
he agreed.
Maybe he couldn't stand it anymore.
You were indeed asking for it.
It's common that you don't know how to love the other in your first love.
It feels like
you wanted to use a break-up as a test
to prove that
the other liked you very much.