[English subtitles are available]
[ROAD HOME]
[Episode 12]
I have a call.
I need to answer a call.
Xiao,
how did you
come to know Chen?
He's my old classmate.
He reattended classes for a year
and happened to be in our grade.
Tell me
what Chen was like at school.
He...
was a student with PE specialties.
He had good grades.
Why did he reattend the class if he had good grades?
It was because of his family.
I knew it.
When I heard you say Chen has reattended classes before,
I am shocked.
He has been the best in the police force
since graduation.
Hello, who is this?
I'm Gui Yuanshan,
Gui Xiao's father.
You remember me, right?
Yes.
What can I do for you?
I just found out
you and Xiao are dating.
Right?
Yes.
Not long ago.
You're not a good match.
I have no complaints
about your job.
But your family,
your father.
Such a family doesn't deserve Xiao.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Am I not telling the truth?
Yes.
I admit that it is the truth.
But we are different.
If you want to be together,
Xiao will definitely meet your father.
With your family background,
how can you live a good life?
I remember
when I met you in Qining,
I also told you about this.
Back then, you were young and aggressive.
You said it was not a problem.
Now you have
your own career.
You've worked hard
in society.
It's time to be mature.
A man shouldn't bring trouble,
including trouble from his family of origin,
to a woman.
This is
very irresponsible.
If you like Xiao,
you should want her to be well
and to live comfortably.
You're not young anymore.
You are past the age of simply having a romantic relationship.
Now that you're together.
At this age,
you need to form a family.
The collisions between two families,
be they good or bad,
and the contradictions in values.
Have you ever thought about it?
Gui Xiao.
Your father.
Dad.
Xiao.
I talked a few words to him just now.
Your brother came to give his New Year blessing to me a few days ago
and mentioned
Lu Yanchen who had left Qining.
Didn't you break up earlier?
We've made up.
Did you ask him?
Or did he tell you
why he left Qining?
It's just
a normal job transfer.
You can ask him yourself.
He made a lot of contributions before this.
In Qining,
many higher-ups
spoke for him.
His new position was just confirmed,
but he wanted to leave Qining
and be transferred to a big city.
Xiao.
He came to you again.
But do you think
you still have feelings for each other?
He just wants to get close to you.
I've seen a lot of people like him.
Do you remember
Uncle Zhao's daughter?
It's because she's too naive.
He's not that kind of person.
I was the one who went to him.
To be precise, I begged him
to make up with me.
I disagree with your relationship.
Don't even think about getting married.
You can't see him
and his family clearly
because you are in a relationship.
He just wants to
change his life
by being with you.
No matter what,
this is my own business.
I'm going to hang up.
The signal is bad here.
My dad and I got cut off
after a few words.
Did you encounter the same
just now?
Why didn't you go in?
Your hands are freezing.
How can I get in
without finding you?
What did he say to you?
I forget.
I'm asking you seriously.
Come here.
You smell like a sheep.
You say it as if you don't have any.
We ate the mutton together.
A hero can't get over a beauty.
Captain Lu.
You've opened my eyes today.
But Captain Lu,
you're joking around
with Xiao
beside piles of frozen horse waste.
Aren't you afraid that you'll upset her?
Why are you so good at lying?
What did I lie to you?
You know it yourself.
There is one thing
I did lie to you for more than ten years.
I'm left-handed.
When I was at school,
I was forced to change it.
Only my family knows.
Left-handed?
I'll use my left hand.
I knew it.
There's no way
that someone can defeat me with their left hand.
Lu Chen, you are a rogue liar!
You're too cunning.
You're a big liar.
I'm leaving soon.
I want to talk to them a little longer.
Go.
Do you need someone to trace the characters in red ink again?
One who laid down his life for the country
must have a place for his soul
in this vast prairie.
It's just a formality here.
Was he one of your teammates?
He was one of the rookies
under me.
How did he die?
He was from Jiangsu and Zhejiang provinces.
He was an orphan.
He came here first.
Then he went to
a place at high altitude.
That place is very harmful to the body,
especially with high-intensity training.
It wasn't long before the situation was bad.
He didn't make it.
Before he died, he said he wanted to be buried in Qining.
Captain Lu then arranged for him.
Over the years,
we have buried all those
who are up to a martyr's standard here.
I happen to live nearby.
It's convenient for me to keep a watch over here.
There's one more. I'll go by myself.
That's his former captain.
Captain Lu always has something on his mind.
Every time he comes,
he goes there and talks by himself.
No wonder
he wanted to come even if he took a detour.
This is
for our accommodation and meals over these days.
I calculated it roughly.
Ask me for it if not enough.
I don't want it.
Take it.
You've been transferred.
You have no right to order me around.
You really think I can't catch you,
right?
Little brat.
Take it.
Xiao.
Look at Captain Lu. Is he vulgar?
I'm much wealthier than he is.
What is this?
Is this watch expensive?
It's a watch only for rich people.
I've never seen anyone show off their wealth
in such a cute way.
Yes, I admit that you're rich.
You are really rich.
You have the sheep, coal, earth, and gas.
Last time I came,
I thought the things here were pricey.
That's right.
As brothers,
we only live once.
Don't be so vulgar.
I wished
you could live here forever.
Of course.
That was when I thought
you could be single
for a lifetime.
I don't think so anymore.
Cut the crap. Take it.
I don't want it.
Are you looking down on me?
Just take it as a wedding gift.
When you two get married,
I probably
can't make it to the ceremony.
You can give it to me
only if you don't want to marry her.
Why do you involve me?
It's between you two.
Okay, I'll take it.
That's right.
We have
something to do in Qining.
See you.
Okay.
Goodbye, Xiao.
Bye.
Take care.
What were you talking about
with the groundskeeper?
I wanted to know about
the funeral industry here.
If I remember correctly,
Cai
is kind of your colleague.
I remember she sells
toothed roll crushers.
No.
I'm an investor.
I just look around at
how to spend money for the boss.
A funeral services company
he invested in last year
has been listed.
I just recalled
so I want to know more about this place.
I suddenly have a feeling.
I went back to Beijing once when I was in Qining.
That night,
I looked at the bus stop sign on the street.
I knew none of the stations.
Looking at them one by one,
I suddenly felt like
we were living in
two worlds.
I have the same feeling
hearing you talk about your job.
It's a completely different world.
I help to achieve a prosperous economy
while you protect the country.
Aren't we in the same world?
I suddenly have a feeling.
What?
Looking at you
and the snow here,
I feel like you're wandering
in a vast expanse of whiteness.
What's wrong?
We got a flat tire.
I'll change the tire.
I'm afraid people can't see clearly from afar.
Do you have an umbrella?
Yes.
Why did you stamp on it?
Tell me.
Although my tires are explosion-proof,
I should learn how to change a tire
in case I come across a non-explosion-proof one
in the future.
You don't need to learn.
I'm here.
What are you doing?
Kiss me.
So pretentious.
Well...
Shall I get up?
Forget it.
Even if cars pass by,
no one knows us.
♫How did I get hooked on you?♫
♫I'm asking myself♫
♫I can give up anything♫
♫But I'm reluctant to leave today♫
♫How did I get hooked on you?♫
♫I'm asking myself♫
♫I can give up anything♫
♫But I'm reluctant to leave today♫
Do you need help?
No, no.
It's fixed.
♫You're not beautiful♫
Go ahead if it's fixed.
♫But you're exceedingly adorable♫
We'll arrive in Qining
in half an hour.
Okay.
Thank you.
♫Oh, Cinderella♫
♫My Cinderella♫
♫I'm constantly breaking your heart♫
♫I'm always being cruel♫
♫I told you not to take it seriously♫
It was snowing last time.
Many small houses
were covered by snow.
Now, the snow has melted.
Sir.
Good timing.
I have lots of good news.
We just caught the guy.
Is there any better news?
Of course.
Where is Lu Yanchen now?
We just had a call. He said he had arrived in Qining.
Tell him
his girlfriend
is a lucky star.
I'd like to take the privilege as a host
to treat her to a meal.
Don't bother.
I'll call him now.
You may tell him by yourself.
Sure.
Hello?
Okay, I got it.
Yes, she's next to me.
Okay.
It's not my dad, is it?
My former superior.
I found that people here
like to drive Off-Road Vehicles.
I found out last time.
It's convenient to load things and drive a long way.
Are you happy to be back?
You've been here for so long.
You must have deep feelings about this place.
If I hadn't met you again,
I would live here
for the rest of my life.
Why did you book
such a nice room?
This is my second hometown.
I want you
to live in a nice room here.
Thank you, Captain Lu.
You're welcome.
My former leader
called me
and asked me to see him tonight.
For business?
I can't tell you.
I won't ask.
Go.
I'll talk to you when I get back.
When will you come back?
I want to know if I should sleep first
or wait for you to come back.
It won't take long.
I'll wait for you.
Bye.
I forgot my car key.
Think about what's for dinner.
I'll be back soon.
[SWAT Detachment of Qining City Public Security Bureau]
[People's Police Training Base of Qining City Public Security Bureau]
I missed you.
Stop nagging.
Let's get down to business.
Gui Xiao is a lucky star.
I didn't expect
these car thieves would also do smuggling.
We followed the clues
and went to catch them before the Spring Festival.
We got someone
unexpected.
Does it have anything to do with them?
Did you catch them?
We caught most of them.
We were not supposed to
sit in on the interrogation.
You handled this case.
You must come back and hand it over.
And the detective police believe
they'll get information about the explosive through the interrogation.
Captain Chen also asked us to sit in.
This will be
the end of your work in Qining.
A perfect end.
Let's go.
Captain Lu.
Captain Lu! Captain Lu!
This time, we followed the clues
and caught these people
thanks to your girlfriend.
It was by luck.
I know the situation at the scene
better than anyone.
Go ahead. I'll sit on.
Director.
It's been a while. How's it going?
Captain Lu is more calm than us.
He worked in the SWAT team of Qining for years.
He's experienced in
dealing with this kind of people.
I believe he can handle it well.
I'm going to a meeting.
Send me the report
once you have the result.
Okay.
Come in.
There are two bombs in New Light Mall.
You chased them too hard
before the Spring Festival.
He decided to have a life-and-death struggle
and take revenge against society.
Hurry up. You must go now.
Continue with the interrogation.
Okay.
I'll ask the EOD technicians to go there.
I'll go with you. Let's go together.
If...
Qin Mingyu.
If anything happens,
according to the rule of the EOD group,
whoever has a higher position goes first.
I have a higher position than you as an EOD technician.
Understand?
I wonder
if you want to leave a message to Xiao.
I know.
It's highly confidential.
You can't tell her anything.
But you disappeared right after she arrived in Qining.
I'm afraid she'll be worried.
I'm leaving.
Gao Hai.
Send her the key.
Tell her to wait for me.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Hello.
The subscriber you dialed
is unavailable.
We'll send him a message
to notify him of your call.
Powered off?
His battery died?
Gui Xiao.
Xu Yao.
I'm making a call.
Well, make it short.
Or I can call you tomorrow.
I'm worried about something
and want to talk to someone.
Bin's test results are worrying.
It's different from the tumor
diagnosed by the previous hospital.
It's not confirmed yet.
But her situation
seems more troublesome.
She needs radiotherapy.
Radiotherapy may cure the tumor.
But once she gets this disease,
she'll be likely to relapse.
And the tumor's location will be different every time.
I dare not tell our family.
And I dare not tell her.
I really don't know
what to do now.
You're a doctor.
You should know that,
in the current situation,
it's useless to be anxious.
And you are so close to her.
If there's any change
in your emotions,
she will definitely feel it.
Wait. I need to open the door.
Xiao.
It's from Captain Lu.
Where is he?
He's dealing with something. He asked you to wait for him.
What is it?
How long should I wait?
He'll be back soon.
Did something happen?
Gui Xiao, take care.
Gao Hai.
Nothing.
Gui Xiao.
We can talk later if you have something to do.
It's okay.
I have no work to do these days.
I'm in Qining.
You took your annual leave?
Sort of.
Wait,
you don't sound okay.
Did you shout
just now?
Lu Chen came back to Qining
to visit his former leader and subordinates.
Maybe
he drank too much
and was afraid that I'd be angry,
so he asked someone to send a message.
Alright.
Xu Yao,
stay with your wife now.
Her life is the most important.
Money doesn't matter.
When we come back...
Well.
Did something
really happen to you?
Nothing. I just have a stomachache.
I'm hanging up.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Hello?
Sister.
This is Gui Xiao.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Nothing.
I just want to chat with you.
What's wrong?
What is it like
when you SWAT police are on a mission?
You can't say anything about the mission?
Yes, it's confidential.
Sometimes when we're on an urgent mission,
we don't even know what we're going to do.
We'll know it
only after we get on the car and receive a note.
What's wrong?
Are you ready?
Our fire rescue team
are in place.
We can start a fire rescue operation
anytime.
Thank you.
How's the interrogation going?
They haven't made him answer.
I don't have a big problem here.
The robot can solve it.
As for your side,
there's nothing I can do.
You should get prepared
when you go there.
What should I get prepared for?
The best hospital in Qining
is nearby.
Do you know the consequences?
Thousands of firecrackers and thousands of blood.
Every inch of land is as valuable as gold.
After putting on this uniform,
remember this in your heart
for your whole life.
Yes.
Help me!
Don't speak.
Put down your gun.
Okay.
I'll put it down.
Hurry up.
Calm down.
Don't hurt the hostage.
Hurry!
Don't move.
Help!
Walk forward slowly.
You, the one in the middle.
Okay, I'll go there.
Two more steps.
Okay.
Don't hurt the hostage.
Cut the crap.
Don't move.
I'll blow you up!
Fire!
I don't approve your resignation.
It was an emergency.
You can't take all the responsibility
on yourself.
I didn't handle it well.
I should take full responsibility.
Bye.
Be careful.
[New Light Mall]
[Smoke Vent]
Wait.
I'll ask someone to get you a ladder.
Don't take off your bomb suit now.
If the explosive's TNT equivalent is,
as the criminal said,
enough to destroy a building,
it's useless to wear the suit.
Time waits for no one.
And wearing the Explosive Suit,
I can't get in.
At least let the robot try.
Given the width,
a reconnaissance robot might work,
but an EOD robot is really useless.
Stop nagging.
Wait for my news.