[English subtitles are available]
Go Ahead
Episode 40
What are you doing?
Why the long face?
We had a great talk
and I like her,
so I invited her
to have a dinner at home.
You don't need to explain it.
You can do whatever you like.
But it has nothing
to do with me.
You don't like it
no matter what I do.
Because you only
care about someone else.
Whatever.
But stop doing
those stupid things.
I have a girlfriend.
But I don't like her.
You don't have to like her.
I've tried,
but I really don't like her.
You can be with anyone,
anyone but her.
I just can't accept her.
You don't have to accept her.
I hate her!
What's wrong
with Ling Xiao?
It's nothing.
He's got something urgent.
Come. Take a seat.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you like.
Come.
Have a taste.
Have some tea.
Ma'am, thank you.
I'm too full to have anything else.
I'm sorry.
Ling Xiao left
just because
we had
a little quarrel.
You must be upset, right?
No.
Boys are not like girls.
They're not so caring when they grow up.
Ma'am,
I don't know if I've got it wrong,
but if I have,
please don't be offended.
What's up?
It's fine.
I won't be offended. Say it.
Ma'am,
I think
you like me a lot.
Of course!
You're pretty
and you have a good personality.
You're so likable.
Thank you.
But I take Ling Xiao
as my brother.
Besides,
I think what he and Li Jianjian have
is really great.
They grew up
together
and they get together
so many years later.
They're so in love.
It's like predestined.
Have some tea, or it'll be cold in a while.
Ma'am,
you lived in Singapore,
so you might
not know it.
They've really been close
since their childhood.
And we all envy it.
How did you know
about things in their childhood?
Li Jianjian
posted an essay on Tree Hole
which was reposted on Weibo
and it was trending.
Everyone in our hospital
has read it.
I'll forward it to you.
OK.
Please read it.
I'll read it when I have time.
Ma'am,
thank you for this meal
and I'll leave you to it.
I'm leaving now.
Sit for a while.
No, thank you.
Bye.
Let me see you off.
No, thank you.
I'll ask Chengzi to see you off.
Bye.
So have you persuaded your parents?
My mother won't
be persuaded
unless I make some achievement,
but I'll continue to fight,
only in
a different way.
I will persuade them
with my actual deeds.
Well,
did your parents
really
get a divorce?
Yes.
Why did your father
suddenly want a divorce?
Weren't they a model couple?
Your mother used to be proud that your father always listened to her.
And my mother used to be proud that I listened to her.
Now it seems
it's not a great thing to be obedient all the time.
Both your father and you were planning
something big in secret.
Well,
are you really OK?
I...
I'm not OK.
But I force myself
not to think about it.
My father used to be
like an invisible man at home,
but he was at home.
My mom is actually pathetic.
She used to tell me
that my father and I were her career,
but now her career
is a total failure.
So a woman's career
should be improving
and developing herself.
At critical moments like this,
we can't depend
on husband or children.
I'm back.
You're back.
What did you have tonight?
Hot pot.
It's quite convenient to have hot pot.
Why did Feng Xixi get invited?
Feng Xixi?
I saw
Ling Xiao walk with Feng Xixi
in the residential quarter
after I got off work.
How many people did Ling Xiao's mother invite
for their house warming party?
Why did they invite a female colleague of his?
What house warming party?
I invited Zheng Shuran and Du Juan
to have hot pot tonight.
So your future mother-in-law invited
your future husband's female colleague instead of you
to their house warming party?
How unlikable you are!
My future husband thinks I'm likable.
I really don't understand it.
Why?
These days, parents
always want their children
to be with someone that they're familiar with,
and Ling Xiao
grew up in your home.
How could she...
Were you really annoying
when you were little?
Perhaps.
Back then,
when they just moved here,
I sent them
a basket of walnuts.
What’s wrong with walnuts?
She doesn't like walnuts?
I know this.
Ling Xiao used to have a little sister,
a few years younger than him.
When she went out to play cards,
she locked the children at home.
That little girl choked on a walnut
and the door was locked.
Ling Xiao couldn't get out
and then
this kid died.
Really?
I've never heard about it before.
But
she hates Li Jianjian
just because of a basket of walnuts?
Is she insane?
I don't think
it's because of that.
It's because Li Jianjian knows
all her skeletons.
Mr. Li
and all their neighbors
know that their daughter died
because she went out to play.
And she abandoned her son
after getting a divorce.
Many years later, she had an accident
and asked her son to take care of her.
When she sees Li Jianjian,
it feels like
being naked.
That's what I think.
Well,
according to what you've said,
she wants Ling Xiao
to be with anyone
but Li Jianjian.
So what do you plan to do?
I
have no plan
and I don't intend to.
I will cross the bridge when I get to it.
No need bother myself with it now.
Yeah.
OK.
Then I'm relieved.
I think
as long as you two are in love,
nothing will be a problem.
Yes.
That's right!
Win her over.
Don't stop until you do.
What a great idea!
Eat something when you drink.
Eat more meat,
or it'll be bad for your health.
As your father,
I'm useless.
When you don't tell me your problems
I'm so worried,
but when you tell me about them,
I'm of no help.
I'm not a good father as Mr. Li is.
Look,
he's good at cooking
and straightening things out,
and he's good at chatting with you.
As your father, I...
Dad,
you don't have to do anything.
I feel at ease
when you're with me.
OK.
When I was in Singapore,
my mom was even worse.
I wanted to call you
and ask me to take me home
many times.
Xiao,
I didn't go
to visit you back then
and I'm sorry.
I know.
I know you have a special job
so you can't visit me.
I don't blame you for it.
Dad,
it's been a long time since the last time I dreamt about Yunyun,
so did she
forgive me already?
Have I paid off
all my debts to mom?
Ziqiu.
♫Raindrops rush through the windows♫
What brought you here?
♫Wetting me to the heart♫
I just passed by
and I thought you might not have an umbrella.
Oh, it's fine and I planned
♫Growing and flowing its own way♫
to take a taxi later.
You'll get wet in the rain after getting off.
♫Tell me how I can♫
Then thank you.
You're welcome.
♫Try to hide things♫
Let's go.
♫It never speaks but answers with a patter♫
♫If it rains heavily♫
♫I'll let myself become an ocean♫
♫Put the rain on♫
Because of him,
everything shines.
♫And then fly♫
He's like
♫Take it as wings♫
a smile
♫You made me grow up♫
shining on everything.
So nice!
♫If I turn to your direction♫
It's so beautiful.
♫No wall can block♫
♫The sunshine♫
♫If it rains heavily♫
♫I'll let myself become an ocean♫
♫Flying with the sunshine♫
♫that you gave me♫
♫I've grown wings♫
Chengzi.
What?
Has Xiao contacted you?
Be nicer to him
if you really care about him.
In summer,
a new neighbor moved upstairs.
His parents often quarrel
and the boy always reads comics
on the stairs.
My dad and I
invited him to dinner a lot
♫Darling♫
and before long,
his parents got a divorce.
♫Sometimes♫
His mother abandoned him
and he lived with his father.
♫I feel really exhausted♫
You're still eating!
How could you still eat it?
You want to eat?
♫And I would♫
When did you get it back?
♫shed tears♫
Give it to me!
Chen Ting,
♫in loneliness♫
there is only one group photo left.
Can’t you just let him have it?
Give it to me!
Are you crazy?
How could you hit him?
I'm crazy
and I should be the one who choked on that walnut!
♫This is what growing up is like♫
Let's not talk about it.
Why?
Why did you let your sister
have walnut?
Can't you stop talking about it?
Can't you?
Did I say anything wrong?
♫We used to rely on each other♫
It was him!
It was his fault!
Can’t you stop talking about it?
♫bearing the burden♫
Mrs. Ling!
♫and suffering the loss♫
♫but we still look forward to the future♫
♫Maybe you are trying hard♫
Mrs. Ling!
Are you abandoning Ling Xiao?
♫to forget♫
♫just as I am♫
If you don't want him anymore,
please give him to me.
I always want an elder brother.
You can have him.
Great! I have an elder brother now!
♫I try my best to grow up♫
I've told you
that I don't want it!
Aren't you going back?
Then you can see them every day.
Can't you stop it?
♫Even when I'm lost, I'll still carry on♫
I will die after you leave.
Go!
♫I'll be brave♫
Don't answer it!
Mom,
don't do this!
Mom!
♫The darkness♫
♫will pass♫
It's all my fault,
OK?
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
♫The setbacks♫
You hate your mother and it's not your fault.
♫in life♫
You only care
about your father
and even the neighbors.
♫teach us♫
Because they love me!
Why don't you love me?
♫how to fly♫
♫dauntlessly♫
♫Where are you♫
♫right now?♫
♫Let's go together♫
Hello?
Chen Ting,
it's me.
Xiao can't answer it right now.
Is he
alright?
I just want
to talk with him.
Can't you stop it?
Look what you've done
to him!
He has taken care of you for so many years.
How could you torture him
like that?
I'm begging you.
Please be nicer to him.
Please!
Xiao,
have some milk.
It'll make you feel better.
It was such a big rain last night,
right?
But I
didn't get wet at all.
Because someone picked me up.
She was just passing by.
Better?
Aren't you curious
who she is?
We know it!
It was your mother!
Yesterday, it rained
and your mother went to pick you up
because she didn't want you to get wet in the rain
and she even
walked you home.
So you didn't get wet at all!
You made me jealous in such an early morning.
You blamed me
for keeping everything to myself,
so today
I want to share my happiness with you.
Isn't it nice?
Your timing is really great
because we're gloomy right now.
Who is it that's knocking so heavily
at such an early morning?
What's up, Chengzi?
Come inside!
Brother,
mom is gone!
This is her suicide note.
Do you know when she left?
She was watching TV
before I went to bed last night.
But she's gone
when I got up this morning.
What to do?
I'll go and look for her!
Where are you going, Xiao?
Have you called the police?
Don't cry. Don't cry.
You take care of Chengzi and I'll go with Xiao.
I'll call the police first.
Ling Xiao,
my son.
I'm sorry
that I'm not a good mother.
Maybe my being here
is the worst thing for you.
I've been kidnapping you
with my selfish
and vulnerable love,
and ignoring your feelings.
Over the past few years,
you've done so much for me.
I'm aware
that you're in misery,
but I'm so helpless.
I lost my daughter
and a car accident
took more things away from me,
my
mother,
my husband
and my health.
I'm too afraid to keep losing things,
especially you.
I really regret it.
I should have taken you away with me.
Even when I was breaking down,
even when I couldn't take care of myself,
I should have held your hand
to face it together.
I hate myself for being so weak
and I don't know
which one is the right choice.
I wanted
to make it up to you
with the rest of my life,
but now I'm aware
that I shouldn't have forced you
with my so-called love.
My fate tied me up
to a wheelchair
and I tied you up
to me.
I know you're in pain
and you can't fall asleep,
but I kept lying to myself.
I was wrong.
I was too selfish.
I don't want you
to be with Li Jianjian,
because I don't want
to recall my past.
I want to have a new life.
But seeing you with her
reminds me
that I once abandoned you
and hurt you.
I don't deserve your love.
Yes.
I don't deserve to be your mother.
My love is too selfish.
Now I understand
that you've never belonged to me.
You should live your life
the way you want.
This time,
I really want you
to be happy.
And I'll let go of myself.
I'm leaving.
Please take care of Chengzi.
I love you both.
Please forgive me
and then
forget about me.
♫Darling♫
♫Sometimes♫
♫I feel really exhausted♫
♫And I would♫
♫shed tears♫
♫in loneliness♫
♫This is what growing up is like♫
Mom,
♫We used to rely on each other♫
you're awake.
You were drowned
and there's infection in your lungs,
so you need to stay in hospital for a few days.
Luckily, two men were fishing
at the beach before dawn
and they saved you.
Chengzi was so worried
that she took care of you here for a whole day.
I sent her back for some sleep.
She read your note
and she felt sorry,
saying that she was mean to you,
so
you said nothing about her
in your suicide note.
If you think you've done something wrong,
only by being alive, can you make it up.
If you die,
everything stops.
And those wrong things,
bad things
and painful memories
will be there forever
and they won't get better.
Can they still get better?
I remember when I was little,
I had scabs on the back
and it hurt so much.
You said
the wound will get better
after the pus gets out.
We'll get better.
Look,
what a nice day today!
♫Thinking of the first time that I held your hand♫
♫you held me so tight as if I was everything to you♫
♫One is getting bigger♫
♫while the other is getting smaller♫
♫Time brings us♫
[One Month Later]
♫together in our lives♫
Coming!
Mr. Ling.
So? Have you packed up yet?
Yes.
I came to help.
Thank you.
Mom,
hurry up. Mr. Ling is here!
Coming.
Check it
to see if you've left anything.
It’s all here.
I'll start taking things down now.
OK.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Then I'm leaving now.
OK. OK.
I'm sorry
to have
bothered you with it.
It's no big deal.
Check it
to see if you've left anything.
It’s all here.
Let's go.
I've been waiting for a chance
to apologize to you.
For what?
I answered Ling Xiao's phone
when you called him the other day.
I said
something unpleasant,
so
you committed suicide.
It was not your fault.
I've told you
it was my fault.
Besides,
after Yunyun was born,
you took care of two kids at home
and I was always away on duty.
At that time,
I knew nothing
about PTSD
and I thought
you would get over with it after some time.
Actually, I've really done
so many wrong things.
I'm sorry.
Let's not talk about
those unhappy things.
I've forgotten them.
Good.
I'll settle down in Singapore.
Chengzi likes it
and I'm used to it,
so please
take good care of Ling Xiao.
I'll take good care of him,
because I'm his father.
That's right!
Here it is.
After you go back,
don't spend all your time on playing.
Mom has difficulty in moving,
so help her
with the housework
like cooking.
Besides,
study hard
to get into a good college.
Ms. Chen Ting,
Ziqiu and I put
some Xiamen special local products for you
in the trunk,
and you can send them to your friends
when you go back.
Thank you.
You're welcome. It's what I should have done.
Thank you, too.
Thank you for taking care of Chengzi
during this period of time.
You're welcome.
Chengzi, now you've learnt
how hard the life can be,
so study hard after you go back.
Then we're leaving now.
Study hard
and don't spend all your time on playing.
During the Spring Festival,
Jianjian and I
will go and visit you in Singapore.
OK.
Go.
Ziqiu,
thank you
and I will miss you.
OK.
Come back when you have time.
I'm leaving.
Naughty girl!
Jianjian,
this time,
I'll really leave Ling Xiao to you.
You two take good care of each other.
OK.
Please rest assured.
I'll make him happy.
Ma'am, safe journey!
OK.
Now they've left.
And there's
one hour for you
to put on makeup and get dressed.
We'll set out when you're ready.
That's right!
I should go and ask Tang Can to put makeup on me,
or it'll be too late.
Let's go. Go.
To get a marriage certificate?
Yes.
It's so sudden.
It seems I should prepare
a red envelope.
Of course!
If you're not short of money, prepare a thick red envelope.
If you're short of money,
borrow some money and prepare a thick red envelope.
Are you a moneygrubber?
I spent a lot of money
and invited everyone I know
to watch
your stage debut tomorrow.
Are you moved?
Don't talk about it.
I'm nervous even now.
What if
I fail it?
What if I get replaced
by the alternative?
What if the audience boos me?
I'll boo them back with all my friends and relatives.
Love you, babe.
Look at you.
Who is that?
Mrs. Qi.
Tang Can.
Mrs. Qi, you're here.
Jianjian,
both of you are home.
Let me help you.
It's heavy.
Let me do it.
Where is Mingyue?
She went out.
She doesn't have to go to work today,
does she?
She
went out to buy something.
I've made something delicious
for you.
I didn't bring Shacha sauce this time,
because I remember
that Tang Can is allergic to it, right?
This time, I've made you
sweet crispy peanuts.
Do you like it?
Thank you.
I like it.
You're welcome.
Look how messy it is!
I'll help you
tidy it up.
I really wonder
if you can be a good housewife.
Let me help you.
No need.
Do what you need to do.
We don't have to worry about it now.
Mrs. Qi
is still Mrs. Qi
who despises us.
That's right.
Dad, hurry up!
Bureau of Civil Affairs Bureau will be off work
if you don't hurry up.
Don't rush me.
Right away.
Ms. He Mei bought him
a suit
and he cares so much about his appearance these days.
You're beautiful today.
And you're handsome.
Give me a kiss.
Have a look.
What do you think?
Dad, you look great today!
Ms. He Mei has a great taste.
I feel awkward dressing like this.
It's not awkward.
It looks great on you.
You look so great in it.
Dad,
you really look great today.
Good for you, Dad.
You're having a flash marriage.
Have you been in love for a month?
It's not a flash marriage.
We had a blind date 20 years ago.
OK. Let's go now.
I've put your family register
and ID card in your bag.
They're closer to the bureau
and we should hurry up.
And we'll take a family photo
after you get the certificate.
This is good.
I need some hairspray.
Dad, you look really great now.
Oh, my!
Let's go. Go.
You want to transfer your shop?
Yes.
It has begun
to make a profit,
but I'm
a dessert chef
and I want to do desserts.
After I transfer this shop
to someone else,
I want to open
a dessert shop in the scenic zone
and I want Ms. Luo Hong
to help me choose a location.
Is that OK?
Of course!
I've never expected
that one day
I would take my mom to get married.
My dad will be nice to you
and please be nice to him.
You'll be happy together.
I wish you happiness!
OK.
You two
are too far away from each other.
You're married now. Hug together!
Like this. Like this.
There's no need for that.
Come on!
Man up and hug her!
Hurry up! Hug her!
I'll hug her.
Yes!
Be closer!
Put your arm around her shoulder and look at the camera.
Be closer to each other.
Look at the camera.
Something is missing.
What to do now?
Mom!
You're so beautiful!
This is good.
This one is nice.
Don't let go.
Lean your head over.
My face has got stiff.
Dad,
we are in the photo studio on the second floor.
Just come up.
Yes.
Not bad. Good.
The traffic is so heavy.
I'm late.
Mr. Ling.
Congratulations!
You've finally come.
Come. We were waiting for you to take the family photo.
Yes.
You two get married
and there's no need for me to take the photo with you.
Don't turn us down.
And you're so well dressed
right now.
Besides,
when Jianjian and Ling Xiao get married,
we'll legally become a family.
That's right!
Come and let's take a photo together.
Come! Come!
Stand behind your mom.
Get ready.
OK. Come.
Come and look at it.
Look at the camera here.
We're about to take it.
Get ready!
Come. One.
Two.
Three!