[English subtitles are available]
Go Ahead
Episode 16
Why did you bring him here?
I brough him to have noodles.
You are back.
Good.
Well. Let me introduce him to the two of you.
This is Ran.
Zheng. Zheng.
Jianjian's friend.
You've known each other for years, right?
Yes, yes.
Mr. Li, I'm hungry.
Cook a bowl of seafood noodles for me.
There are no seafood toppings.
Let me cook beef noodles
with some fish balls for you, OK?
Dad, I want them too.
OK. I'll cook two bowls of noodles.
You guys have fun...have fun
Ziqiu, sit opposite.
This place is good.
Sit opposite.
What are you doing?
This is my eldest brother.
This is my second brother.
This is Zheng Shuran, my boyfriend.
So, the three of you grew up together?
Gosh! Li Jianjian,
I actually see your muses.
They are different. They are different.
They cannot be compared with
your muses.
My creation is about the surplus heat of life,
not about the enthusiastic expression of life.
They don't conflict.
The essence is the same.
The more enthusiastic it is,
the sadder and drearier the bottom color is.
I'm good at discovering
the fervor on the surface.
And you can see
the ashes after life is burned at a glance.
Your works
are expressions of good things on the surface,
but there is always
something fragile as if treading on thin ice.
Right. Beauty is fragile.
Do your works
give people such a feeling too?
What are they talking about?
But I'm more inclined to
pursue eternal beauty.
There is nothing
that is eternal.
The ending of all things in the world
is disappearance.
Disappearance is eternal.
But disappearance is not beautiful.
Disappearance is disappearance.
Sorry to disturb.
It seems that
this is not the first time you met.
Right. Actually, this is the second time.
Last time, at the sculpture exhibition,
there was a little misunderstanding between us.
At the time, I heard
someone called her name.
She didn't recognize me.
So,
after meeting Li Jianjian,
you asked her to be your girlfriend?
Yes.
She is interesting
and warm.
I like it a lot.
Thanks.
So what on earth do you like about her?
I should say
I haven't found
anything that I don't like about her.
Neither have I.
I think Shuran is perfect.
We have a lot to talk about.
The noodles taste particularly good, don't they?
Yes.
We're going to have fish.
You arrived just in time.
Mr. Ling.
Jianjian.
Wash hands and eat.
Wash your hands. Come on.
Did you see Zheng get in the car?
Yes, yes.
I told you
that it's good to ask him to stay for supper.
There're so many people at home, so it won't be convenient.
And he won't feel at ease.
I think he is quite at ease.
He ate a large bowl of beef noodles.
That's not enough.
He asked for a portion of fish balls.
The fish balls Dad cooks are tasty.
I think he has bad intentions.
Mr. Ling, decide which side is right.
Her boyfriend
agreed to meet her
in my shop yesterday.
But
on the way,
he stared at a girl's hips
and then went back.
Don't talk nonsense.
Whom did you hear about it from?
She said that.
Don't talk nonsense. You don't understand.
Inspirations are very important for creating works.
It's true that
we don't understand the art of making sculptures.
But Ziqiu is right.
When he sees a beautiful girl, he becomes impulsive.
Besides, he is psychologically immature.
He has graduated from university for a few years,
but still depends on
the living expenses his parents give him.
He has good family conditions.
He treats you
to an ice cream
with the money from his parents.
Do you think that's good?
Well. Well. Stop.
Let's eat.
An artist doesn't need
to make a living?
You have spent
some money on subsidizing your good friend.
Will you subsidize him too?
That will be a bottomless pit that can never be filled.
It is not as serious as you said.
Is his current situation
really good?
Well. Stop!
Let's eat.
OK.
Call him and break up with him.
Are you crazy?
I said break up with him.
Why did you talk to your sister like that?
I ask her to break up with him.
I think you should break up with him too.
Why?
Why do you
interfere in
my life?
Well, Jianjian,
what your two brothers do
is for your own good.
I'm good.
I'm very good.
When they were away,
I was good too.
I have friends.
I have things I like to do.
I'm happy every day.
As soon as you were back,
you had to prove your existence,
didn't you?
You even called the police.
I called you but I couldn't get through.
Moreover, what he said on Weibo
is ambiguous.
You have
greatly affected
my life.
Do you know?
Actually,
I do this for your own good.
Thanks. I really don't need.
You can
just live
your own lives well.
When I have a toothache, I'll see the dentist myself.
All the dentists are good.
When I want to have desserts,
I'll go and buy them in the street.
There are dessert shops everywhere.
The two of you really
don't need to do that to me.
You are not my own brothers.
Actually, there is no
legal assistance relationship between us.
You don't need to
do anything to me.
Understand?
Jianjian, why did you say that?
Since the day you met us again,
you've been holding it back, right?
Finally, you said that.
I didn't want to say that so bluntly.
You forced me.
Ling Xiao, don't take it to heart.
Dad, Mr. Li, you eat.
I'm going back.
Ling Xiao...
Ling Xiao!
Jianjian, what you said
is really hurtful.
You said they are not
your own brothers.
Do you forget
that you've grown up together
since childhood?
Buy one for me.
Your tooth doesn't hurt now?
No. Buy one for me.
No. Go home.
Why don't you buy one for me?
Go home.
This is good. This is with jujube paste.
And this is with honey.
Ling Xiao, buy one for me.
Please.
Just one.
Buy one for me.
Go home!
Will you go or not?
I'll go if you buy one for me.
I won't go.
I'll count from one to three.
If you don't go, I'll leave.
One.
Two.
Three.
Jianjian! Jianjian!
Sir,
did you see
the little girl who was with me
just now?
Jianjian!
Jianjian! Jianjian!
Let go of me!
Jianjian! Jianjian, where are you?
I'm here!
Jianjian!
Jianjian! What are you doing?
Let go of me! Ling Xiao!
Let go!
Let go of my sister!
Let go of me! Let go!
Let go!
Let go of her!
Somebody! Catch the bad guys!
Somebody!
Catch the bad guys!
Don't beat my brother!
Somebody! Catch the bad guys!
Let go!
What are the two of you doing?
Let of the kid!
What's going on? What's going?
Call the police!
Luckily, you are fine.
If anything
happened to you,
how would I live?
Haichao,
you should thank
Ling Xiao and Heping for helping you today.
My son was brave.
Good boy. Awesome! Awesome!
Thank you. Thank you.
Helping, thank you. Thank you.
Haichao, no need to do that.
This is what I should do.
Jianjian.
Here's what I want to do.
Mrs. Qian, be a witness for us today.
Jianjian,
don't call him Mr. Ling again.
He is your godfather now.
Kowtow to your godfather.
Godfather.
Don't. Don't.
Jianjian. Jianjian.
From today on,
you are like my own daughter.
Good.
Ling Xiao
saved your life today
and our family.
He'll be your own brother.
Understand?
Call him brother.
Brother.
Sister.
Well. Well.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
Get up.
Haichao, Heping,
from today on, you two families
become a family.
Can the marriage
between them be arranged?
Right.
They have kowtowed.
This is really good.
Why are you following me?
Sorry.
You are not sorry to me.
You don't need to say sorry to me.
No, I'm really sorry.
I don't know
you dislike us so much.
It's not that I dislike you.
It's just that I actually
live very well now.
After you graduated from
high school
and left with your family,
there was no shadow
left for me.
No.
It's true that because you didn't come back on time,
I was a little angry.
But I understand you.
You don't owe me.
So, you don't need to make up.
What you are doing now
makes me bear a heavy psychological burden.
That's not right at all.
We owe you.
Ziqiu, it's all over.
Do you want to turn me
into the girl who always followed you when we were little?
Even if you are always with me,
I'm in my 20s,
so I can't
be clingy to my brothers every day, right?
Well,
what do you mean?
You...
You don't need us now?
Didn't I make it clear to you?
No. You can be angry.
You can even ignore me.
But
don't say you don't need me.
That's none of my business!
Go back to your own home.
It's the first time I saw Jianjian
was so angry with her two brothers.
You missed once.
Back then, when Ziqiu and Ling Xiao were going to leave,
Jianjian lost her temper.
She went to her grandma's
and was unwilling to come back to see them off.
Ziqiu and Ling Xiao called her,
but she refused to answer the phone.
She had been angry for several months.
But they have long
become reconciled, haven't they?
Look.
How her two brothers care about her after they were back.
But it's Ling Xiao's fault today.
He was too outspoken.
But he is really worried that
Jianjian will be cheated by that boy.
Jianjian is not a little girl now.
They haven't seen each other for so many years.
When he is back,
he still disciplines her as if she were a kid.
Jianjian certainly feels bad.
You are right.
What should we do?
What do you mean?
You won't do anything?
What can I do?
They've grown up
and their own ideas.
They should resolve the internal conflicts
by themselves.
The more you meddle, the more you'll be disliked.
Jianjian is such a big girl now.
It's the first time she has a boyfriend.
You won't care about such a big thing?
I think you take things easy.
You are right.
How about you do something about it?
You are going
to use hyacinth beans
to make braised noodles with hyacinth beans tomorrow, right?
That's none of your business.
Do your job.
No, I...
He says he often moves.
He moves from one place to another
and doesn't know where
his real home is.
If he can be as free
as fish,
he won't need to worry.
The fireworks out of the window are so lively,
but it is cold and lonely in the house.
Let's go.
Let's leave the city.
♫If a heavy rain falls♫
♫Then let me become a sea♫
♫Put on the light you gave♫
Who is that?
He Ziqiu?
I'm here to cook breakfast.
It is too early.
It is still seven o'clock.
I just got up.
Li Jianjian will get up at eight o'clock at earliest.
It is OK.
I'll finish early
and go to the shop to make cakes?
You are so generous that you even bought strawberries.
You can just eat one.
I bought them for Li Jianjian.
What?
You didn't
tell my secret to Ling Xiao, did you?
You want me to tell your feelings for him for free?
No way.
Good. Good.
I want to keep a dubious relationship with him
for a period.
You are having a dubious relationship with him?
Lower your voice.
Don't let out my secret.
I'm cooking.
You are flirting in the early morning?
I won't disturb you.
You got up.
We have bread to eat today.
A big breakfast, isn't it?
My belly aches.
You guys eat.
I've got to go.
It took you so much time to make the breakfast.
Eat before you leave.
No.
I've told He Ziqiu.
They made too much fuss.
Internet romance has been popular for many years.
Ling Xiao and Ziqiu cannot be blamed.
Zheng Shuran is indeed
somewhat weird.
The two of you suddenly
decided to meet.
And you were out of touch.
I was so worried.
I remember, when we were high school students,
Ling Xiao disciplined her very strictly.
Now you developed an internet romance.
No wonder he is worried.
By the way, Li Jianjian,
why did you take him
to see your dad
when it's the first time you met him?
I didn't mean to take him to see my dad.
He knew my dad
is running a noodles restaurant,
and wanted to taste the noodles my dad makes.
That was to meet your dad.
Your said he
agreed to meet you,
but because an inspiration came to him on the way,
so, he went back?
Is there any problem with
your EQs?
Li Jianjian,
you've met each other after developing the internet romance.
How do you feel?
I feel particularly good.
I'm telling you.
We have a lot to talk about.
When you met him,
did your heart flutter?
When you took him to meet your dad, were you nervous?
Didn't you worry that your dad
doesn't like him?
Look. Look.
She is still thinking about it.
I know you surely
don't like him.
If she likes him,
how could she take him to see her dad
when it's the first time they met?
If she likes him, she should have been
extremely nervous.
You are crazy. You learned to develop an internet romance from others.
She can't tell
the differences
between friendship
and love.
I knew she had difficulty
in understanding affections.
In her eyes,
there's nothing but wood.
It's impossible for her to tell them apart.
Yes.
When you're in love,
you can't be so calm.
You should be
thinking about
that person all the time.
Yeah!
Love is supposed
to be burning hot
and passionate.
What nonsense
are you talking about?
Love doesn't have to be burning hot and passionate.
What's wrong with steady love?
My parents
met on a blind date.
When they first met, they felt
good about each other
and then decided to get married.
They had a pretty good life together.
Anyway,
we'd like to
develop our love gradually.
I'm in a bad creative state recently.
It's said that love
can inspire creation.
So you start a relationship
for your creation?
It might bring me some inspiration.
After they moved into the opposite apartment,
our doorbell never stops ringing.
I'll get it.
Good morning.
Morning, Mingyue.
Mom!
What are you waiting for? Give a hand.
It's so heavy.
Mom, why did you come here at such an early morning?
You should have told me.
What if I'm not at home?
It's not 8:00 yet.
You couldn't have got out.
Surprise raid!
My bedroom is a bit messy.
It was so hard to find a place to park the car last time,
so I took a taxi here this time.
You're all here!
Hello!
Mrs. Qi.
Hello.
You're having breakfast.
It looks not bad.
Pretty healthy.
Mom, have you had breakfast?
Yes, I have.
Enjoy yourselves.
Eat, please.
Let's eat.
I bought some imported fruits
for you.
Remember to eat fruits every day.
Last night,
I sauced a large piece of beef tendon.
Doesn't it smell delicious?
I've prepared the sauce
and I'll put it in the fridge.
And this,
the barbecue sauce made by your grandma.
Mom, no!
Tang Can is allergic to that.
So we can't have it here.
No one
is allergic to barbecue sauce.
Tang Can, you must be allergic to something else
that you've had.
Yes.
And this,
fish balls
and I'll put them in your fridge.
I'll put these
two reusable bags
in a closet,
so you can reuse them later to protect the environment,
OK?
OK, Mrs. Qi.
Mom, let me help you.
No need.
Just eat your breakfast
and I'll take care of it.
Mrs. Qi is amazing.
Just as usual.
Girls, hang in there.
We have to
withstand the passionate love
from Mrs. Qi.
Sorry. Sorry.
What are you talking about?
Thank you, Mrs. Qi.
You're welcome.
If you like it,
I will come more often
to bring you something delicious.
Good.
Let's eat.
You should clean
the floor completely bit by bit.
I should come more often.
Are you losing your hairs?
Don't always stay up late even if you want to work hard.
Otherwise, you'll go bald.
You do have a lot of clothes.
Only that part of you
makes you a girl.
But you've grown up.
Why do you still wear pink dress?
Can't you read some fashion magazines
when you have time?
Mom, it was you who bought me
a lot of pink clothes before.
When did I
do that?
When I took you to buy clothes,
you picked
those pink clothes.
Mom,
can't you stop denying me?
I was showing my concern,
and you don't appreciate it.
Mrs. Qi, I can do it myself.
I can do it myself.
No need.
You don't have to be so polite to me.
You lost your mother when you were little
and nobody took care of you.
Mingyue and you are best friends,
so I kind of
take you as my own daughter.
I'm not that pathetic.
My father has been taking good care of me
the whole time.
You poor girl!
You've never enjoyed motherly love
and you don't know that motherly love
is different from fatherly love.
It's OK. I'm here.
OK. Just go out.
Leave it to me.
Well, Tang Can,
you should clean this room
on your own.
I really can't do it
for you.
Mrs. Qi, you don't need
to clean this room.
My room looks messy,
but I know where
all my things are.
After you cleaned it last time,
I couldn't find my things.
Tang Can,
I'm not being wordy.
But you don't make a lot of money.
So don't spend all your money
on clothes and cosmetics.
The best investment
for a girl
is on study.
Mrs. Qi,
I bought these clothes for my job.
What kind of job is that?
Going to a parents' meeting
as someone else's parent
is nothing but lying!
You're so pretty
and you were a child star when you were little,
so why don't you continue
to be an actress?
Mom, let me drive you to work.
No need.
Your car is too crappy.
You're not embarrassed to drive it,
but I'll be embarrassed to take it.
Why didn't you tell me
that you wanted a car?
How about selling it?
And I'll add some money,
so you can buy a better car.
No need. I think that it's fine.
The car you drive
represents yourself.
When you drive a fancy car,
no one dares to look down upon you.
Mom, I want to discuss something with you.
Say it.
I don't think it's good for me
to be a contract worker.
Here is the thing.
There's a great opportunity
at our station.
In the second half of this year,
two young reporters
will be sent to the Beijing Office,
so I want to go to Beijing...
No! Beijing is too far away.
There're too many people and too many cars.
The air over there is not good, either.
You're totally unfamiliar with it.
I don't want you to go there.
No.
A lot of my classmates are there,
and I'll come back in two years.
Think it through.
When you come back from Beijing,
you'll be 27 years old.
And it'll take quite a while
to find a suitable boyfriend.
So when will you get married?
And when will you have a child?
Things like that
will happen when it's time.
So when will it happen?
You have to make a plan.
Tang Can, I'm leaving.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you. I really don't need it!
You just need to
take good care of your lives.
I can go to see a dentist if I have a toothache.
There're a lot of good dentists.
If I want to have some desserts,
I'll go and buy some on the street.
There're a lot of dessert shops on the street.
You two don't have to
do anything for me.
You're not my real brothers!
You're not legally obliged
to take care of me.
And you don't have to
do anything for me,
OK?
Let me have a look.
You have another younger sister?
Give it to me.
Qin Meiyang,
you don't share the same family name.
Hello, this is Ling Heping.
This is Chen Ting.
Chen Ting,
it's been quite a long time.
How are you?
I'm good and everything is good.
Ling Xiao told me
that you were unwell recently.
It's just an old trouble.
I'm fine.
You should pay more attention to your health.
Don't eat cold food.
Stomach bleeding is not a trivial matter.
Thank you.
Is Ling Xiao by your side?
I'm working in the office
and Ling Xiao is in the hospital.
Why did he go to hospital?
Is he sick?
You just won't come back
until the dishes are on the table.
Would you like a bowl
or half a bowl of rice?
No need.
I have no appetite and I don't want to eat.
What happened?
Mr. Li,
I'll get off work if there is nothing else.
OK.
Hang out the sign
of closing.
OK!
Take care!
Now tell me about it.
Today,
Chen Ting called me.
Who?
Ling Xiao's mother.
Are you two still
in touch?
No.
We didn't get in touch after Ling Xiao went to college
in Singapore.
So
I was surprised
when she called me today.
Yes.
I was surprised too.
So why did she call you?
It seems
that she doesn't know
that Ling Xiao has got a job here.
She thinks
that Ling Xiao just came to visit me,
and today
she called me
to ask Ling Xiao
to go back.
Ling Xiao
doesn't tell me anything
about himself!
How could he?
Don't blame him.
You know what Chen Ting
is like.
I knew it.
I knew Chen Ting
wouldn't have just let Xiao
back so easily.
We made mistakes,
but it's our child who is suffering.
It's too late to say this.
Anyway, I think
you should
talk to Ling Xiao
about it.
What should I say?
He doesn't talk with me a lot.
He talks with you.
How about you have a talk with him?
I can talk with him about other things.
But for this problem, as his real dad, you should talk with him.
How could you say that?
Didn't you say
that you were also
his real dad?
I really can't help.
Please have a talk with him.
I want to help but I can't.
It's too salty.
Stop eating it.
What are you doing?
Why didn't you go to bed to sleep?
I wasn't sleeping. I was watching TV.
By the way,
have you talked
to Li Jianjian?
No.
I think you should work
on your temper.
We're her elder brothers,
and we're supposed to be cheeky.
Look at me.
If I hadn't been cheeky when I was little,
I wouldn't have a home.
You know her.
It's quite hard for her
to hold it back for so long.
Don't be mad at her.
After all, it's a fact
that we failed her before.
Why do you wear my clothes?
This is yours?
I thought it was mine.
I have one pretty similar.
Those shoes are also yours?
Do you have foot fungus?
Good.
I was just asking. No offense.
You used to wear mine
when we were little.
You can wear all my shoes,
except the ones
that Li Jianjian sent me back then.
That's my line.
Don't wear that pair of my shoes.
I have barely worn them,
but yours are almost worn out.
Go to bed early.
I'm back.
You bought some fruits again?
Cherries!
Your brother bought them.
Can you believe what this person has done to me?
After attending the parents' meeting,
I took his son out to play.
The game coins cost me a dozen yuan
and I took his son to KFC
which cost me a few dozen yuan.
It's fine if he doesn't want to thank me,
but he gave me a moderate comment!
The reason is that I wasted
his son's time on homework.
How could he do things like this?
He hired you
to attend the parents' meeting,
not to take his son
out to play.
I was being kind.
How could he return my kindness with enmity?
You think you were being kind,
but he thinks
you were making troubles for him.
How could you be so inhuman?
I'm inhuman?
I paid for
half a year's rent
of this apartment!
I'm inhuman?
Is she having her period?
You're awake.
This morning,
Ziqiu came at 6:00
and then left.
He was like a wife
in the old society.
What's going on between you two?
Eat quickly.
You're going to the hospital
to extract the dental nerve today.
You can leave home at 10:30.
After seeing the dentist,
I will go to the studio directly
and I'll be there ahead of you.
OK.
The next time you go to see the dentist,
I will go with you
and your brother can clean my teeth.
We'll see.
I've got to go now. Bye.
Bye.
Hello, this way.
Your brother happens to have
an appointment with someone else right now,
so he asked me to treat you,
saying that as long as the doctors' medical skills are good,
it's all the same to you.
What a petty man!
What?
Nothing.
Thank you.
Did your brother apply
for a college in Singapore
because his mother is in Singapore?
So is he closer to his mother
or his father?
He's close to both of them.
Don't try to cover it for him.
Based on my observation of him,
he's not close to any of them.
But your brother
is good with kids.
When we have
a child patient's appointment,
we let him deal with it.
Only by yesterday,
did I find out
that he had another younger sister in Singapore.
She's much younger than him.
No wonder he's experienced with kids.
Have you ever met his younger sister?
Yes, a couple of times.
Your brother...
Miss Feng,
I have an appointment in a while.
It won't take long extracting a tooth nerve, will it?
No, it won't. It'll be quick.
Come here to take the medicine with me.
He's always like this,
as if everyone is in his debt.
At the last award exhibition,
what impressed me the most
is your work with Miss Li.
Two Boys and A Girl
at the age of 17
symbolizes the lost youth
and Dream Lover
represents growing up.
It's awesome.
I like that piece
of work too.
When that idea
came to me,
I was so excited that I couldn't fall asleep all night long.
Bro,
please come to our studio a lot
in the future.
May I have your WeChat number?
Sure!
He's not like
what I've imagined.
So what did you imagine?
I thought
he should be someone
with long hair,
like a wild punk.
Or someone
in dark style.
But unexpectedly,
he's such a sunny young man.
Does my microblog
give people an impression like that?
No wonder your two brothers
thought I was a dangerous man.
Brothers?
Aren't you the only child in your family?
Yes, I am.
My two brothers
grew up together with me,
but we're not blood related.
They're the prototypes
of the two boys of Two Boys and A Girl.
They were studying abroad
and just came back.
Several days ago,
they knew that Li Jianjian and I were going to meet.
She happened to break her phone
and when her two brothers couldn't get in touch with her,
they were about to call the police.
Call the police? Really?
Do your brothers
have sister complex?
Probably!
No.
When I was little,
some strangers almost took me away
under my brother's eyes,
and the lingering effect is
that he always worries about me
a lot.
Do your two brothers
have other siblings?
Yes.
Then their siblings...
I'm hungry. Are you hungry?
Let's eat together. My treat.
Let's go.
You've never talked
about them before.
That's not important.
What would you like to eat?