=The Soulmate=
=Episode 22=
I know where the blood jade is,
but I demand a person in exchange.
Jiang Junsheng and his men
are hot on my trail now.
If you help me,
I'll give you the blood jade.
It's fair,
right?
I'll give the blood jade to the Marshal.
You'll never get your hands
on this treasure.
See you tomorrow night.
Are you leaving?
Yeah.
I'd like
to have dinner
with you all tomorrow night.
You're my best friend.
You must come, okay?
I'll invite the Marshal.
As for Mr. Gao,
could you pass on the message to him?
Okay, we'll definitely be there.
Great.
That's settled then.
I'll take off now.
Escort her out.
Miss Gu, please follow me.
She's in such a hurry to leave.
Something must be going on.
From the looks of it,
I think
she's most likely the real culprit.
We're just one step away
from solving the case and going home.
Now it all depends on tomorrow night,
whether she'll reveal any flaws.
This time,
we cannot let her get away.
Are all the smuggled items here?
Yes.
Open it.
It really is her.
(Miss Gu.)
Here's what
my master left for you.
It seems like he knew
he would be in trouble.
So he
made all your clothes
for a year in advance.
I've been waiting for you.
What happened?
Don't you know?
How would I know?
I was packing at home.
Come in first.
Marshal, I remember
you used to love this sweet and sour fish.
Have a try
at my cooking.
There are still a few dishes
being cooked in the kitchen.
Despite we have been siblings
in name for years,
we've rarely had the time
to sit down together
for a simple home-cooked meal.
(Tea)
Mengqiu.
You're leaving Rongcheng.
Do you have any lingering wishes?
My wish
is to leave Rongcheng.
Looks like you don't have anyone
to miss in Rongcheng.
They are here.
I heard you're leaving Rongcheng.
We brought you a little gift.
There's no need for a gift.
That's too polite.
Please come in first.
The tea has just been brewed.
Have a taste.
No rush to drink the tea.
Let's open the gift first.
Gifts can wait.
Tea cannot.
Tea isn't good when it's cold.
Thank you all for coming today.
I'll use tea instead of wine.
Cheers to you all.
You all came,
supposedly to bid me farewell.
Yet, none of you wants
to drink a sip of tea.
It seems you have some doubts.
If you still consider me
a friend,
why not openly express your doubts?
Please, Miss Gu.
Clear up our doubts.
Miss Gu, you should
be familiar with these things.
Antique papers?
Over the years,
I've bought dozens of them
to copy the works of famous artists.
I doubt they're just for copying.
They're for forgery, right?
I gave most
of the paintings to Father.
As for what he was doing with them,
I have no knowledge.
You've produced dozens
of ancient paintings over the years.
How could you not know?
Marshal.
You know that.
I did whatever Father
instructed me to do.
That was how
it had always been for us,
wasn't it?
Miss Gu, since you claim to be unaware,
allow me to inform you
about the whereabouts
of those ancient paintings.
Several pieces were used as bonuses
by the Grand Marshal
and given to those
who were involved in the blood jade,
such as Wang Ming.
There were also some forgeries,
unknown
to the Grand Marshal,
placed
in the antique pavilion.
Are you really sure
that all of these are forgeries?
Do you trust me?
Today, you come
to bid me farewell,
but it turns out you're here
to investigate me.
I'm just a weak woman,
coerced by the Grand Marshal
to replicate a few paintings.
Does that make me
an unforgivable criminal?
Miss Gu.
What you'd replicated
wasn't just ancient paintings.
This is what everyone
has been searching for,
the blood jade.
Father, take a look.
It's alike.
It's strikingly alike.
You've handled it very well.
Tell me.
How would you like me to reward you?
You agreed before
to let me leave Rongcheng.
I'd like...
You want to leave?
Sure,
but not now.
Wait a few more years.
You said the same thing last time.
Get out.
This is great.
So this is the thing
that caused the deaths of many.
Is this the blood jade?
How did it end up in my house?
Is it a curse coming for me?
Miss Gu.
Keep going.
You must have felt smug
when you helped the Grand Marshal
create the blood jade, right?
But surprisingly,
the curse you fabricated
could actually kill people,
and it even forced
your only loved one to death.
I was an orphan before I was adopted.
I don't have any loved ones.
Miss Gu.
Do you recognize this piece of cloth?
In Rongcheng Orphanage,
every orphan's clothes
would be sewn with such a piece of cloth
to mark their names.
A few days ago,
I dropped by Rongcheng Orphanage.
The director there still
remembers a smart little girl
from over a decade ago.
(Rongcheng Orphanage)
Gu Mengqiu?
Of course, I remember.
Over a decade ago,
when the explosion in Gunan Mountain
caused a landslide,
she followed the fleeing villagers here.
Qiu was great.
She was fortunate too
to be adopted by the Grand Marshal.
Was she also orphaned
because of the explosion?
After the disaster,
we took in
quite a few babies.
At a young age, Qiu was skillful
and could help
sew the names onto the clothes
of children even younger than her.
Just a moment.
I still have those
stored in the archives.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Finding records from so long ago
must be difficult.
No trouble at all.
You've come at the right time.
A few days ago,
someone else was asking about her too.
That's why I haven't
kept the records away.
Have a look at this piece of cloth.
(Qiu)
(Gu Mengqiu, age 6,
orphaned by Gunan Mountain explosion.)
You mentioned
someone else also inquired recently.
Do you remember who it was?
Yeah.
I know him.
I was quite surprised
when he asked about Qiu.
Stop. Don't say anymore.
The director could only
remember so much,
but I also learned something else.
Apart from me,
there was another person inquiring
about the little girl's whereabouts.
It was Mr. Zhang
from the tailor shop in town.
I told you to stop!
- But he was your...
- No, he wasn't!
♪From the moment you turned to me♪
♪My life shone with a purpose♪
♪Across lakes and oceans♪
♪We race toward love's finale♪
♪We glow and shimmer♪
♪Setting stardust on fire along our way♪
♪I'll embrace you for years to come♪
♪Once lonely, once sorrowful♪
♪When the starlight falls on your hands♪
♪My heart finds strength anew♪
♪How long is this life?♪
♪Is it enough to etch the light
of love in the stars?♪
♪Above the constellations♪
♪We leave our song♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪