=The Soulmate=
=Episode 8=
Miss Yu.
Have you
almost lost your life twice?
Yes.
Once with poisoned wine.
And once in the alleyway ambush.
Do you want to know
who did these
and why?
Today,
I'll tell you right before everyone.
Miss Yu.
I did
both of those things.
And the reason
was because of him.
What nonsense are you talking about?
You must be curious
why I treat you like this.
I'll tell you the truth, Miss Yu.
Before you arrived,
Junsheng and I had a good relationship.
He promised me
that if we worked together
to kill the Grand Marshal,
he would take me away.
But then,
you had to be
around him every day,
making me jealous and annoyed.
Guards.
Take this mad woman away.
What now?
Getting anxious?
You want to attack me
for your master?
You accused me
of planning a crime with you.
What evidence do you have?
No one touches me.
She's going to poison herself.
Mad woman.
Do you think
I only have one poison?
And you want the blood jade?
Let me tell you.
The blood jade curse is real.
Everyone will die.
No one can escape.
Jun, quickly.
Send her to the hospital.
Blood jade curse?
The blood jade curse...
The blood jade curse is real.
It's all nonsense.
There's no such curse.
Governor Cao.
The blood jade treasure
is very dangerous.
Do you still want it?
It's human nature to seek wealth.
I kill in war.
My hands are covered in blood.
Only ghosts fear me.
I fear nothing.
Marshal.
She has vomited the poison.
And they've taken her to the hospital.
This is a private matter
of the Grand Marshal's residence.
The police station
will not intervene.
The police must intervene.
Third Lady's life is still in danger now.
If she dies today,
it'll be a murder case.
Please thoroughly investigate
the Grand Marshal's residence.
To avoid suspicion,
I'll stay elsewhere temporarily.
Marshal.
If you leave, who will take over all the things
at the Grand Marshal's residence?
If you don't mind,
I can.
I promise
not to move a single thing here,
not even a blade of grass.
I'll fulfill my duties faithfully.
As long as I'm here,
the residence will be safe.
Why...
Go.
Have someone bring the keys
and give them to Governor Cao.
Understood.
I'll go with you.
Marshal.
I'm worried about Ms. Hong.
I'll go to the hospital
and check on her.
Sorry for today's trouble, Miss Yu.
I'll come and apologize
in person another day.
Better not.
Your family and I
don't seem to get along well.
Every time I come, there's trouble.
It's better if I don't visit.
What happened today
has left me confused.
Could it be that my guess was right?
My guess was right.
Didn't you see
the Marshal's gaze at her?
Do they
look like
they used to be in love?
And you claimed to be
an expert
in love.
It's quite normal.
Men become cold when they stop loving.
Look at him.
He wanted to kill Lady Yu.
Your theory
is quite rich indeed.
But the person
who killed the Grand Marshal
certainly wasn't Third Lady.
Otherwise, the case would
have been solved by now.
The game would be over.
We should have gone back long ago.
Following your logic,
Jiang Junsheng isn't
the murderer either.
Otherwise, we could have gone back
after catching him.
Also,
what exactly is
the blood jade curse?
It's too terrifying.
They keep mentioning blood jade,
indicating a connection between blood jade
and the Grand Marshal's death.
We must find out
the details of this blood jade.
You don't look
too good.
You shouldn't have gone out today.
You should have rested well instead.
I do need to rest.
But,
my dear junior,
do you want to take care
of this dashing and handsome
good senior of yours?
You seem
quite healthy to me.
Miss, we've got a problem.
Looks like I'll have to trouble you
for a while, Miss Yu.
The "elsewhere" you mentioned is here?
Marshal.
You're not welcome here.
Whether I stay or leave
is Miss Yu's decision.
Gao Han.
Escort the guest.
Okay.
I brought a special gift
for you, Miss Yu.
Marshal.
What...
He's the one who drugged the wine.
One of them served poisoned wine.
The other encouraged you to drink it.
What's going on?
Feng Qianhong wasn't sure
if you'd drink the poisoned wine,
so she needed some assistance.
Third Lady bribed you, right?
Miss.
Please spare us.
Third Lady told me
that the wine was all laxatives.
Huang and I really didn't know
there was poison in the wine.
Please spare us.
You don't need to beg her.
She always hits and scolds you.
There's no way she'll let us off.
It's precisely because you usually
seek death and court danger
that we had the chance
to turn fiction into reality.
You brought this upon yourself.
Who can you blame?
Stop the nonsense.
The fact remains.
If you still don't believe it,
you can search
the maid's room.
You should find
evidence of Third Lady bribing her.
Is that really the case?
I won't pursue it further.
Let them go.
Indulging in evil
only leads to endless trouble.
Xue, go.
Thank you, Miss.
Are you done now?
Marshal, are you leaving on your own,
or shall I escort you out?
Wait a moment.
I have one more gift
to give to Miss Yu.
Take a look inside.
Property deed?
(Property Deed)
(Jiang Junsheng)
Why is your name on it?
This is one of the dowries
prepared by your father.
I didn't want it at the time,
but I've changed my mind now.
Is that so?
Nobody told me about this.
To be precise,
the true owner of this property
is me.
Marshal.
I know you're quite generous.
Can you offer us this house
for two days?
Of course.
But it's not for both of you.
Only you.
That won't do.
Wherever my senior goes, I go.
Wherever he goes, I go.
Fine.
Reserve the room at the end
of the second-floor corridor
for Mr. Gao.
Isn't this bullying?
That's a storeroom.
How can I live there?
Marshal.
We should be fair in our actions.
How about we have...
an arm-wrestling match?
Whoever wins, we'll listen to them.
How about it?
Sure.
Junior, good luck.
Who said I was competing with him?
Senior.
You go.
♪From the moment you turned to me♪
♪My life shone with a purpose♪
♪Across lakes and oceans♪
♪We race toward love's finale♪
♪We glow and shimmer♪
♪Setting stardust on fire along our way♪
♪I'll embrace you for years to come♪
♪Once lonely, once sorrowful♪
♪When the starlight falls on your hands♪
♪My heart finds strength anew♪
♪How long is this life?♪
♪Is it enough to etch the light
of love in the stars?♪
♪Above the constellations♪
♪We leave our song♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪