=The Soulmate=
=Episode 13=
(Firenze Restaurant)
Are you not coming in with me?
I don't think it's appropriate
for me to join in.
Rest assured.
I'm here for you
whenever you need me.
Alright then.
You actually came.
All Jiang Junsheng wanted
was a chance to apologize to Lady Yu.
But when you
entered Lady Yu's body,
she was already poisoned to death.
We all have
to return to our world someday.
And after we leave,
Jiang Junsheng will have
to face the news of Lady Yu's death.
If he doesn't
speak up this time,
it'll probably be a regret
for the rest of his life.
Oh, by the way,
I've ordered some food,
but I'm not sure if you'll like it.
I'm not into fancy food.
I just like some burgers
and fries.
Can you get me some…
Barbecue sauce, please.
Sure thing.
I like dipping my fries
in barbecue sauce.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
I usually do that too.
Then, go ahead.
Back then, it was
just about solving cases
and none of this relationship stuff.
But now we
have to deal
with all this drama.
Wow, look at them
having a blast eating without me.
I should go in
and recharge with Jiang Junsheng.
Wait.
I can't just
barge in while they're having a good time.
Be careful.
Mr. Gao,
it's really you.
What's wrong?
I'm fine. I'm just
dealing with an old issue.
You look pale.
My apartment is nearby.
Why not
come over and rest for a bit?
Thanks for the offer, Miss Gu,
but I'm afraid it might be inconvenient.
Don't worry, Mr. Gao.
Miss Yu is my good friend,
and since you're her senior,
it's only right
that I look out for you.
Alright then,
if you insist.
Thanks, Miss Gu.
This way, please.
Enjoy your tea, Mr. Gao.
How are you feeling, Mr. Gao?
Much better. Thanks.
No problem.
Even if we
were strangers,
I wouldn't just turn a blind eye.
Miss Gu,
this tea smells unique.
It has cloves and ginseng.
Cloves calm the nerves,
while ginseng boosts energy.
Have you been feeling unwell lately?
So you know
about tea, too, Mr. Gao.
This is a special blend of flower tea.
Since the incident
at the Grand Marshal's residence,
I've been restless.
I also have insomnia and headaches.
Actually, I invited you over
to rest at my place today
with an ulterior motive.
I heard from Junsheng
that you're a detective.
Lately, I've seen you
around him quite a bit,
so I'm wondering if there's
any progress in my father's case.
To be honest,
I'm quite scared.
I can't find peace of mind
until the culprit is caught.
So, Miss Gu,
do you think the Grand Marshal's death
was suspicious
and unrelated to the blood jade curse
that has been causing a stir lately?
If ghosts and spirits were real,
how could there still be
so much injustice in the world?
I prefer to believe that someone
is intentionally playing tricks.
Mr. Gao, I put my faith in you
to uncover the truth
about my father's death.
Actually,
from the first time I met you,
I felt
you were different
from others in Rongcheng.
You're righteous and brave…
By the way,
Miss Gu,
your cheongsam
is beautifully tailored.
I came to Rongcheng in a hurry
with just a few clothes,
so I want to get some tailored outfits.
Tailored outfits?
Actually, it's easier
to buy ready-made ones,
but if you prefer custom-made,
I suggest you visit Zhang's Tailor Shop.
This dress I'm wearing
was made there.
Is it the tailor shop that specializes
in making clothes
for Grand Marshal's family?
Mr. Zhang often
brings the latest fabrics to our door.
(Zhang's Tailor Shop?)
(I remember the shop owner,
Zhang Zhiran,)
(was also present at the deaths)
(of Grand Marshal Jin and Cao Liang.)
(He can also freely)
(enter the Grand Marshal's residence.)
You don't like dipping fries
in barbecue sauce,
do you?
I can see the agony
on your face
when you eat it.
Have you
learned my eating habits
from Gao Han?
That meddling detective
has been up to no good behind my back.
When I see him again,
he's in deep trouble.
I'm sorry.
I did
ask Gao Han
for a favor.
Apologize?
Is it about Yan Hekun's matter?
It's not entirely your fault.
I messed up a lot
in the past
and hurt your feelings.
I know
saying sorry doesn't mean much to you.
But still,
I wish you could
give me a chance
to start over with you.
Start over?
What do you mean?
I don't get it.
It's getting late.
I'm heading back.
Wait.
Take this painting. It's for you.
Is this me?
Where did you get it?
I painted it.
Barbecue sauce might not be tasty,
but I enjoyed eating it
because I was with you.
I thought of you
while painting this yesterday,
so I wanted to give it to you.
I've also planted many red poppies
you like at home.
If you…
We don't have a chance to start over.
I have a new name now.
You can call me
"Nan Yu" from now on.
Lady Yu liked Jiang Junsheng,
but Nan Yu was different.
(Nan Yu?)
(Then who does Nan Yu)
(have feelings for?)
The blood jade case is still unsolved.
The murderer is still out there.
I can't let you go back alone.
Does Mr. Gao come here often?
It's my first time here. How about you?
I come here regularly.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Thanks.
♪From the moment you turned to me♪
♪My life shone with a purpose♪
♪Across lakes and oceans♪
♪We race toward love's finale♪
♪We glow and shimmer♪
♪Setting stardust on fire along our way♪
♪I'll embrace you for years to come♪
♪Once lonely, once sorrowful♪
♪When the starlight falls on your hands♪
♪My heart finds strength anew♪
♪How long is this life?♪
♪Is it enough to etch the light
of love in the stars?♪
♪Above the constellations♪
♪We leave our song♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪
♪Be it light-years,
an instant or a thought♪
♪I love u for life♪
♪Because you hold the stars♪