♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
♪A brilliant scenery♪
♪Moonlight spills over
the endless clear sky♪
♪The roar of the heartbeat
leaves a trace behind♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪Fervent, boiling love♪
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
=Be Passionately in Love=
=Episode 5=
(No Feelings for Me at All?)
You're truly blessed.
Hui is a good girl.
Thank you.
Luzhou, you're back.
Let me introduce you.
This is Ms. Xue.
Professor Jiang's wife.
This is Luzhou, my son.
Hello, Ms. Xue.
Hello.
Have a seat.
Sit down.
- Please, have a seat.
- Sit.
She's
Hui.
Professor Jiang mentioned her before.
His daughter.
She's off to Ruicheng University
in a few days.
That way, the two of you can
watch out for each other.
Right, Hui?
Okay.
By the way,
your dad will be at the airport.
Go pick him up, and also drop off Hui.
She's off to Bohui for a movie.
Okay.
Thank you, Ma'am.
You're welcome.
Come, have some fruit.
Feel free.
Dad, I'm washing up.
Up so early?
Didn't you watch
the meteor shower last night?
How did you know?
Did Yingying tell you?
I saw it on your social media.
Right...
Who is Chen Luzhou?
(Oh no, I forgot to block him.)
It's
a friend I recently met.
A guy?
He's good at taking photos.
Why are you asking?
Never mind.
Well...
That Zhou guy
takes quite good pictures.
Pretty good.
If there's nothing else, bye.
Oh right.
There seems to be a typhoon
in a couple of days.
Once finished,
return early.
Bye.
(Zhu Yangqi)
Hello.
Chen Xingqi is unwilling to paint.
Why look for Xu Zhi?
If you can't do it, she can?
Based on my observation,
Chen Xingqi is not afraid of anything,
except for Xu Zhi.
Alright.
I'll ask
will she help Chen Luzhou
with his brother.
Sure.
Eight hundred a day for me.
Alright, that's a deal.
Where has Chen Luzhou gone?
Why isn't he taking his brother?
Chen Luzhou went on a blind date today.
- Blind date?
The car's parked a bit far.
Need to walk a bit.
Hello.
I'll be out soon.
My boyfriend's there.
No need.
Boyfriend?
Don't tell my parents.
We
are planning to go abroad together.
Don't worry. Once we're abroad,
I won't trouble you.
It's not you.
I dislike chatting, not your fault.
It's between my mom and me.
Ms. Lian is quite nice.
She's actually very proud of you.
You might not know,
but she often tells my mom
and others at work
how outstanding
and how hardworking you are.
My mom says she's just tough-talking
but soft-hearted.
In fact, it's obvious.
She cares about you a lot.
From No.1 High School?
With your good grades
and handsome looks,
many girls must like you.
Not really.
How come?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Then you must like someone.
Sort of.
Add me on WeChat.
Let's have dinner abroad.
As a thank you for keeping my secret.
That's your boyfriend?
Hui.
Bye.
Let's go.
Go.
Watch a movie or eat?
- Eat.
- Okay.
I haven't eaten much.
(Xu Zhi is indeed quite pretty.)
But the girls who pursued you before,
were all pretty.
What's different with her
compared to other girls
is that she has a boyfriend.
(Zhu Yangqi, you're completely wrong.)
(I don't like girls
who have boyfriends.)
(I just...)
Can you guess
where Xu Zhi took Chen Xingqi?
Go ahead.
Foot massage parlor.
She said Chen Xingqi's feet
were too smelly.
Chen Xingqi's face turned green.
In your family,
who would dare to openly despise him?
Even Chen Xingqi has a day like this.
I told you before
that if Xu Zhi could be your girlfriend,
then someone could handle Chen Xingqi.
How did your blind date go?
I told you it's not a blind date.
Did you...
Did you tell Xu Zhi
I went on a blind date?
Yes, I did.
What'd she say?
She said you were talking nonsense
about interviews
and blind dates.
And then?
She asked you
do you want Chen Xingqi's business.
If not,
then she'll take over.
Tell her to dream on.
(No feelings for me at all?)
Three.
Three?
What did Chen Luzhou say?
Did he agree I take over?
He said no way.
Stingy.
Six.
Pass.
Zhu Yangqi, are you a pig?
I'm on the same team as you.
Why do you block my cards?
Do you even know how to play?
My cards are good, okay?
Hello.
Welcome.
Two people?
I...
Zhai Xiao.
Okay.
Bad guy.
I'll handle him.
Wait a moment.
Look.
Not bad here.
I was here before.
It's quite nice.
She is...
Chai Jingjing?
No.
That's too bizarre.
This guy needs handling.
Otherwise,
more naive girls will get hurt.
How?
What do we do?
Got it.
We record it and then expose him.
Okay.
Alright.
Thank you.
Stop.
What?
Fur. It must be from the tree.
Receive it.
- Okay.
- You can get her?
I'll send a message to Chai Jingjing
with my secondary account.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Some water.
Okay.
Who is it?
It's nothing.
Please enjoy.
(Chai Jingjing)
Chai Jingjing?
Who's that?
My cousin.
Maybe something's happening at home.
It does seem urgent.
Let me take this call.
Alright.
Okay.
Wait for me for a moment.
Hello, Jingjing.
Let me explain.
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow I'll...
Don't explain, bad guy.
Bad guy, we're done!
Stop it, or I'll call the cops.
Bad guy.
Serves him right.
Ling.
Cai Yingying?
You guys did it?
Yes, it was us. What about it?
Are you clinging to me?
You followed me here.
We're not related.
Why are you so clingy?
Pester you?
Yingying has great eyesight.
It's 5.3.
Let's go out.
What?
What? Starting a fight?
Want to fight?
Do you know that
Xu Zhi's uncle owns this villa.
What good outcome can there be
misbehaving here?
You...
Just wait.
Thank you for the reminder.
I'm not ambitious enough.
I don't know what I want.
But now I'm very sure
what I don't want.
Like you,
a piece of non-recyclable trash.
You all just wait.
Just wait.
It's okay.
High five.
Give it to me.
What have you been busy with lately?
Accompanying Chen Xingqi
to paint at the villa.
Luzhou,
that day, I...
It was my fault.
I was too much.
By the way,
everything is settled at school.
I bought an apartment nearby for you.
Living at home is always
more comfortable than staying in a dorm.
Thanks, Dad.
Let's go.
The weather has been very dry lately.
I made some pear soup.
Look.
How nice it is.
We're back.
You're back.
You must be tired from the trip.
Wash your hands. Ms. Mei made pear soup.
Get me a bowl. I'll go make a call.
Drink later.
Alright.
Luzhou.
Come, have a bowl of pear soup.
Thank you, Ms. Mei.
Come on.
Want a spoon? No?
Wash your hands before you drink it.
Changing your face quickly.
Here's a spoon.
You should be in Sichuan Opera.
No.
Want some?
I'll drink it later.
Drink to dissipate the heat.
What did your dad say to you
along the trip?
He told me
once I get settled at school abroad,
he'll buy me an apartment.
Look.
Your dad cares about you.
Remember
when we traveled to Spain?
You didn't buy the speaker
to buy Xingqi a drawing board.
When your dad heard,
he spent the money for his suit
to buy you the speaker.
I joked,
"You can wear a suit for years,
but will the speaker last that long?
Is it worth it?"
He said it's worth it.
If his son likes it,
that's all that matters.
I know.
I know he's good to me.
I won't let him down.
(Convenience Store)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplify every sound♪
♪Who will visit me♪
♪Treading carefully
into my personal space♪
(Seen my cousin's Chinese exam paper.)
(Use 'not only, but also'
for a sentence.)
(He said,)
("My sister not only loves money,)
(but also has no money.")
(I can't tutor him anymore.)
(On my eighteenth birthday,)
(my dad gave me a watch with cracks.)
(I thought it was
some valuable heirloom.)
(But he said)
(that was the one I broke as a child.)
(Now I'm an adult,
he can collect the debt.)
(Get ready to work.)
Where are you?
Still down here.
Bring some things back when you return.
I'm starving.
Want what?
Some instant noodles.
Don't forget Xingqi's water.
You can choose the rest as you like.
What about Xu Zhi?
You tell him.
Chen Luzhou.
Which Lu is it?
Lu as in dumb.
Alright.
Forget it.
I wanted to bring you
two bottles of juice back.
Lu as in twists
and turns, all roads lead to Rome.
Too late.
Not late. You'll buy them for me.
Dream on.
Hello.
Where are you?
I'm tired of playing cards.
In such a hurry to see me?
Rider, the order is overdue.
Sorry, Ms. Xu.
Don't give a bad review.
Depends on how long I wait.
About half an hour.
Okay.
They're returning to rest.
Meet downstairs
at the restaurant?
Okay.
Hello.
Two of us.
Sorry.
No personal drinks here.
So, should we still drink them?
I won't waste them.
I think there's an AV room nearby.
Lead the way.
Come in.
Sorry about that.
We only have this one left here.
How about it?
No problem. This one is fine.
Okay.
Thank you.
Watch what?
I'm fine. Up to you.
I'll choose.
(Daily Legal Education)
(Power of Law)
(Punish the illegal and warn society.)
(Welcome to Daily Legal Education.)
Thank you.
You're not happy?
No.
Because of the blind date?
Don't listen to Zhu Yangqi's nonsense.
My mom tricked me.
She took me to meet a girl
and asked me to look after her abroad.
But she has a boyfriend.
Why are you saying so much?
I didn't ask.
I don't care.
I just feel that
you look a bit off today.
You need a drink
more than whining.
I'm just asking casually.
No hard feelings.
Go ahead.
Have you thought
about what kind
of guy you want?
No, I'll let fate decide.
But I'm somewhat superficial.
I prefer someone smart,
and also earn money.
Because if they're too dumb,
even if they're very handsome,
I refuse.
I don't like it.
Too exhausting to communicate.
I'm not patient.
How to judge intelligence?
Most people have similar intelligence,
except for a few exceptions.
So, before dating,
would you take someone
to the hospital for an IQ test?
That's why I say I'm superficial.
For now, I can only rely on feelings.
College Entrance Examination
is a divide.
Between high scorers and others,
they naturally part ways.
I'm not talking about you.
You're from No.1 High School.
A lean camel is bigger than a horse.
Planning to date once you're in college?
At fate's will.
Qingyi University is average.
Which school is nice?
Jing and Hua Universities
are both okay.
(So cocky.)
(Hua and Jing Universities?)
(Failed and still thinking this?)
(Really dreaming big
despite being mediocre.)
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I think your idea is quite good.
(Alright.)
(That's all for today's program.)
(Thanks.)
(Morality and Rule of Law)
(See you.)
♪Like a breeze,
drifting through the sky♪
♪It wipes away
the trails of sorrow's sigh♪
Mine is gone.
You're not drinking anymore.
I wanted to drink yours.
♪Waiting for an encounter♪
♪The heartbeat reminds♪
Thank you.
Then I'll leave it to you.
♪Let every chapter of the story align♪
♪Even if it rains on you♪
♪I will always be with you♪
♪Like a rainbow appears♪
♪Our love will last♪
♪Even if it rains on you♪
♪I will always be with you♪
♪I will let you know♪
♪You're the only one♪
What's on your mind?
If the person on the show
hadn't been so worried
about what others thought,
would he have ended up like that?
Everyone has a wall in their heart.
It seems solid,
but it can be broken
by one sentence,
or a moment of collapse.
So, if your wall of heart collapses,
then what will you do?
I'll look into this question
and then get back to you.
Okay.
Typhoon weather is coming.
I'll leave here tomorrow.
Dad is about to switch
to the night shift.
I can't leave my grandma home alone.
I should probably take Chen Xingqi down.
By the way,
I got a job to Linshi today.
Needs a photographer.
How much do you plan to hire me for?
How much are you thinking? Name a price.
Keep it reasonable.
Okay.
Okay, goodnight.
Goodnight.
Dad.
You're back.
Such a feast, do we have guests today?
No guests at all.
Just welcoming you back.
Better be.
Where's Grandma?
She suddenly said
that the city is noisy.
Desires rural living.
I'm telling you.
She just wants to go back
to find her friends there.
I brought back the tea for you.
You really thought.
Wash your hands and eat.
Smells so good.
Go wash your hands.
- Dad.
- Zhi.
Go ahead.
Do you think I have
any changes today?
You changed your hairstyle?
You're much energetic.
That's right.
Then take another look at home.
Any changes?
At home...
It's spotless clean.
Did you hire a maid?
What maid?
Even a maid can't clean
as well as I did.
I did everything up and down by myself.
And then?
Then the hospital said
they want to bond.
This time we'll go to Sanya.
Then I thought
I have vacation.
Why not take your grandma to Beijing?
What's your point?
I hope you
to attend a Beijing college.
Dad.
I already discussed it with Cai.
He also said
with your estimated score,
Qingyi University
is really a compromise.
And your homeroom teacher, Mr. Qu,
specially called to tell me
to be sure to persuade you.
He thinks you're young and outstanding,
and should go out to explore
and see the world.
Don't worry.
When you're not around,
I can
take care of myself very well.
Look how well I've kept the house.
This is my last confidence,
enough until your PhD graduation.
Wait.
Where did you get so much money?
Didn't I tell you?
Mr. Lin, the lottery guy,
owes our family five million.
Alright.
Our family's savings
are more than Grandma's Fun Beans.
Okay?
Okay.
Think about it what I just
told you carefully.
I need to go to the hospital now.
You wash the dishes today.
♪On a midsummer night♪
♪The drowsy streetlights
softly start to mend♪
♪The moonlight
penetrates the tree shades♪
♪Chasing the distance
between you and me♪
♪On the mountaintop
where the shooting stars pass♪
♪The silhouette is frozen in eternity♪
♪Fireworks, cicadas chirping,
heartbeat breathing♪
♪The whole world pauses♪
♪Messages connecting the universe♪
(WeChat Transfer)
(Let's split the movie ticket cost.)
(I can still afford
to treat you to a movie.)
(I can afford to watch a movie too.)
(College in Ruicheng
is sending out admission offers.)
(Make sure to check your email.)
(Watch the meteor shower)
Dad,
Beijing has heating.
An electric blanket?
Are you trying to make me
get heat rash in winter?
How about
I get her to meet you?
You can give her these photos.
Forget it.
So she won't bring up
the money issue again.
Weren't you two doing well
at Fu Yu Villa?
Why
suddenly become distant?
I've been thinking why I like her
these past few days.
Love at first sight?
Maybe.
But I think it's more likely
due to a sense of conquest.
I see.
It's because
she
isn't interested in you.
So, unlike those girls
who admired and pursued you.
Or
you don't believe that she's
only interested in your mom.
I just often don't know
what she's really thinking.
Sometimes I feel it seems like
she's playing dumb.
But sometimes I think
she really hasn't caught on.
Either way,
I'm too passive.
I'm done guessing.
Besides, I'm going abroad soon.
We won't work out.
I think it's enough.
Check for anything
to fix.
Let me see.
Okay.
Let's go with this.
Everything is ready,
we just need a photographer.
Chen Luzhou said what?
He didn't agree or refuse.
He'll check his schedule.
Should we ask him again?
Okay.
Good shot!
(Stay focused. Victory
in the College Entrance Examination!)
(Have you decided about the shop visit?)
(Sorry, I got a rush job.)
(I can't go.)
(There's a job shooting a convoy.
Are you taking it?)
(The price is negotiable.)
(Okay.)
It's for you.
Hello, Senior.
Hello.
Senior Luzhou,
could you sign a message for me?
He's busy.
Then we'll have to find someone else.
(Successful shooting.)
Great Photographer Chen
isn't joining us to make money.
He went back to school
to sign autographs for underclassmen.
Look.
A lark in No.1 High School,
who sings very well.
One grade below.
(Got a message from Senior Luzhou.)
She was on a TV talent show.
Do you think
Chen Luzhou really considers us
as friends or not?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I just feel that
although we know each other,
in the end,
everyone returns to their circles.
Even if that's the case,
it's normal, right?
Anyway, he's going abroad.
After that, we'll rarely interact.
Don't worry.
The world will turn without Chen Luzhou.
Just a photographer.
I can find you someone even more...
Almost the same.
I'll look right now.
Lucy.
Why did he come?
This guy.
Here to find you?
You guys go ahead. I'm leaving.
Why run away, Chen Luzhou?
What's he worth?
That's not you.
If you leave, we're done.
Can you just spare me, okay?
Didn't you say he was sneaky?
I'll just be cautious.
No excuses.
You're just scared
to confront him directly.
Watch out.
Come on, pass it over.
Here!
Nice shot!
Defense!
Nice!
Get the rebound!
Nice shot!
Double dribble?
Stay closer.
There!
Don't let him through.
Lucy.
Are you okay?
Can you do it?
- Are you okay?
- Hurt?
Tan Xu, why did you kick him?
Go!
Come.
Lucy, get up first.
Walk this way.
- Slow down.
Hang in there.
(The Origin of Man)
That's the air conditioner remote.
Look!
On and off.
Messing up the air conditioner.
Come on. Tell me.
What made you unhappy?
Why
are people less happy
as they grow older?
In theory,
it's because you've grown up
and seen more.
Your world's expanded.
What used to thrill you
doesn't anymore.
For example?
For example,
you used to get upset as a child.
I just had to give you candy back then,
and you could be happy all day.
But later on, as you gradually grew up,
one piece of candy was no longer enough.
Then I had to take you
to the amusement park,
buy you beautiful clothes,
and even help you
run for class president.
Was I like this when I was little?
Look,
the video of my dear daughter's
class president election.
I've always kept it on my phone.
I've kept it.
Hello everyone, my name is Xu Zhi.
Napoleon once said that
a soldier who doesn't
want to be a general isn't a good one.
Although I am not as rich as Lin Zixuan,
I'm pretty.
Lin Zixuan's money
won't all be spent on you.
But my beauty is completely unreserved.
You all can see.
I hope all vote for me.
But if I am elected class president,
I hope everyone
can cooperate with me in work.
Don't make this hard for me.
Thank you all.
Okay, keep it for your own viewing.
Just don't spread it around.
In the past, candy could soothe you.
But now, even a mountain of candy
might not make you happy.
I also know
that sooner or later,
I won't be able to cheer you up.
By then, there'll definitely be someone
who can make you happy.
However, I hope
that person can appear later.
Dad, don't worry.
I don't need cheering up now.
I just need to make money.
Make money?
Think about it,
I'm going to study in Beijing.
It will cost more than in Qingyi.
I have to earn some pocket money.
Got time.
I'm going with Cai Yingying
tomorrow to Linshi.
Visit a shop.
Earn some money.
You can make money by visiting shops?
Impressive, right?
Let me check whether
inviting shops is profitable.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Aren't you...
Couldn't sleep last night.
Felt dizzy in the morning.
Took a long time to make soy milk.
Couldn't sleep?
Why?
Something is wrong with Zhi.
What's wrong?
Here's the hospital.
Take her here to check.
The doctor can't help.
Ever since
she came back from Fu Yu Villa,
I've felt something's off.
Last night, she grabbed the AC remote,
and went to watch TV.
In the middle of the night,
she oddly asked me,
"Why are people less happy
as they grow older?"
The whole day she's been
absent-minded.
Do you think
she might be in love?
Impossible.
D-Didn't you ask her?
She mentioned that...
That Xu guy...
No.
Just classmates.
New situation.
N-New situation? What...
Quick, look at the phone.
Look at this.
Take a look.
Look, you see.
Chen Luzhou.
Nice picture.
Just this, you...
I think
you need to check,
or ask the child again.
How do I ask?
She definitely won't tell.
Needs checking.
(Andrology, Treatment Room One)
(1034.)
(Chen Luzhou, consultation room 7.)
It's your turn.
Hello, over here.
Doctor.
Where's the discomfort?
I bumped into someone
while playing ball.
(Chen Luzhou)
Are you Chen Luzhou?
I am Chen Luzhou.
(Everyone has a wall in their heart.)
(It seems solid, but it can be broken)
(by one sentence,)
(or a moment of collapse.)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplifying all the sounds♪
♪Who will visit me♪
♪Treading carefully
into my personal space♪
♪Turning the frozen loneliness♪
♪Into concern and care♪
♪Watching stars rise and fall♪
♪Gently pushing me to tour your world♪
♪Swirling into a vortex♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪The lonely clock♪
♪A relentless pursuit, day and night♪
♪Are we both♪
♪Attracted to each other♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪Just a few more embraces away♪
♪From reaching eternity♪
♪After rushing recklessly♪
♪We approach each other♪
♪Without turning back♪
♪In your eyes, I see myself♪
♪Falling into you♪