♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
♪A brilliant scenery♪
♪Moonlight spills over
the endless clear sky♪
♪The roar of the heartbeat
leaves a trace behind♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪Fervent, boiling love♪
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
=Be Passionately in Love=
=Episode 17=
(Every Step He Takes Is Towards You)
What will you do later?
Homework?
You stay up late every day
for homework?
Every time I tell others
I am from Qingyi,
someone always asks me a question.
Do you know what it is?
"Are you from No.1 High School?"
No.1 High School produces brainiacs.
No.1 High School's students
always emphasize where they're from,
as if
no other school can represent Qingyi.
They easily erase the efforts of others.
So you want to work harder
to let those people realize
their superiority is ridiculous.
Of course.
Capability counts more.
How about we make a bet?
Bet on what?
On who does better in the midterms.
You represent No.1 High School,
and I represent Ruijun School.
I see.
Without getting a result,
you don't plan to date.
Alright.
Dating and kissing are both boring.
Kissing while dating is boring.
Only kissing without dating is fun.
Right?
We have already kissed just now.
I feel
it's just like that.
What do you mean?
What do you think?
It means that kissing without dating
is also boring.
Not dating but doing something else
might be fun.
Don't push it, alright?
Would you like to
plan the next investment fair with me?
Sorry.
I may not be able to.
I have too much homework recently.
With me,
chatting to another boy on WeChat?
You are quite bold.
Come on.
You didn't take him seriously at all.
What are you snorting at?
You little sourpickle.
Yeah, he's a pickle.
And he's boring.
He wanted a proper relationship.
And what happened?
He found out the girl likes excitement.
Right?
He feared
they may break up soon.
Even sending that girl
a WeChat message would take ages.
He feared she'd get bored
if he talked too much
or feel ignored if he talked too little.
All his attention
was put on that girl.
And then?
That girl simply said
he's a sourpickle.
Wouldn't you say he's unlucky?
Do you really think so?
What a poor guy.
If we were like this our whole lives,
wouldn't it be nice?
What's nice about it?
Of course not.
Don't even think about it.
You think a lot, don't you?
But even if we got together
and then broke up, as you said,
you'll get something.
Being the first love ex-boyfriend
to me, Xu Zhi,
would sound cool.
It does sound better than school hunk
or class hunk.
After all, you are
the famously beautiful Xu Zhi
from kindergarten onwards.
Look at you.
If you spoke without snark,
you would have a girlfriend.
I can change now.
It's too late.
Wait to be summoned.
Bye.
Good night.
(Chen Luzhou
Other Stickers)
You look happy.
Got back together with Xu Zhi?
(Timetable for Huaguang University's
School of Architecture's Courses)
(Zhu Yangqi will come soon.)
(Let's go eat pork chop together.)
Long time no see.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You didn't reply to me.
What are you looking at?
Why are you so slow today?
Did you get hurt, huh?
Tan Xu?
Should we call him over then?
We four can make a table.
Don't look for trouble.
Wait.
How is this looking for trouble?
An old classmate has come to Beijing.
Inviting him for a meal is quite normal.
No, not normal at all.
Shouldn't Tan Xu
be repeating the course now?
Why did he come to Beijing?
Why did he come to Huaguang University?
What is the reason?
Isn't the answer obvious?
That is,
he specifically came for Xu Zhi.
Will you order or not?
Yes.
Sorry.
It was abrupt
to suddenly come to see you.
But you're the only friend
I know in Beijing now.
Why did you suddenly come to Beijing?
Retaking the course is harder
than I thought.
So I wanted
to come see my ideal university
to find some motivation.
Your mock exam results aren't good?
Not just that.
They're getting worse and worse.
And I can't focus.
I feel I'm getting further
from my parents' expectations.
It's like I've hit a dead end.
Have you thought about
what you are studying for?
Are you doing it for yourself
or for your parents?
Sometimes, you don't
have to care about what people think.
Just do what you want to do.
He can dream on.
Whether he can get
into Huaguang University
is still uncertain.
Why did he come to Xu Zhi?
To talk big game.
If he really came
to talk big game to Xu Zhi,
I would donate some cilantro to him.
Xu Zhi loves to eat it.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Here is your cold dish.
Thank you.
Where's the vinegar?
Sorry, I'll get it now.
No worries, I'll just dip it in him.
Just joking.
You go get it. Thanks.
Eat.
Thank you.
This trip wasn't in vain.
Keep it up.
By the way,
is Chen Luzhou here too?
Yes, and you know about it too?
After all, he's Chen Luzhou.
(De Sica)
Chen Luzhou,
at a time like this,
you skipped class for a movie?
The exams are coming up.
And this... De Sica?
Can De Sica teach you trigonometry
or solid geometry?
Can De Sica take the exams for you?
Let's make a bet, sir.
Bet on what?
If I get first place
in next month's IMO,
you need to give me
a movie leave next time.
Deal.
First place for a movie leave.
Keep your word.
Alright, I'm off.
See you, Mr. Zhang.
Is it really a deal?
(Actually,
I've always envied Chen Luzhou.)
In him,
you can always see that kind
of relaxed determination.
It's like he can accomplish
everything without effort.
But I can't do that.
I can't
view gains and losses so lightly.
Many people think of Chen Luzhou
as a talented player
who can win first place easily.
But everyone ignores his efforts.
In his senior year,
he would sleep at 3 or 4 AM
and get up at eight for school.
And in senior year,
he solved about 8,000 problems
in science alone.
He got in here by add-on admission.
I know about that.
In many people's eyes,
he could go abroad
and get into Huaguang University
as he wanted.
But they don't know
he switched to his dream major
in his sophomore year.
To catch up with the courses,
he put in a lot of effort.
It's just that he never mentions it.
In this way,
you two are quite similar.
Sir, here is your vinegar.
Thank you.
This vinegar is really strong.
You talk a lot.
You've been
looking handsome lately, Lucy.
Stop flattering me.
Lucy, the truth is,
ever since you came back from Europe,
your fashion sense
has become so debatable.
Can you wear a white shirt,
dude?
You dress so casually every day.
With such a good shape,
not wearing a white shirt
is a total waste.
Why wear a white shirt?
To imitate Tan Xu?
Wearing a shirt alone
is not imitating Tan Xu.
Suits and shirts
are the standard for a cool man.
Right, Mr. Cool?
I wonder if my sense of aesthetics
has been spoiled by you
since I was young.
Now I find the campus hunk
of my school quite average.
I mean it.
Do you know what Luo Dan said?
Luo Dan?
My high school classmate
who got into your art academy.
He said,
"Back in high school,
the campus hunk was Chen Luzhou.
Now in college, the campus hunk
is still Chen Luzhou.
Even my dad has remarried twice.
But the campus hunk hasn't changed."
Then I'll go.
That's more like it.
Don't bottle it up
next time.
Just speak out.
At least,
we can drink it away.
We can drink until morning.
Until morning?
You're that free?
Nothing
is more important than consoling
my lovesick bro,
right?
I really don't want
to go back to my dorm room.
Can I go to your place
and squeeze in?
My dorm bed? Forget it.
I can barely fit myself.
I'll get you a hotel room.
You can stay there.
Sure.
A presidential suite, please.
You're dreaming.
Given my current situation,
if you're really my bro,
you should sleep in a park.
You heartless man.
Fill it up, Chen Luzhou.
Alright.
Fill it up.
Wait,
aren't you my bro?
Of course, I am.
You can't hold your liquor,
weakling.
Yeah, I'm a weakling.
Pour some more.
I'm not even drunk.
Okay, we'll drink next time, alright?
If you're my bro, just sleep well.
(Conman's Quote:
I will always be by your side.)
Chen Luzhou,
can't you see what time it is now?
Why are you still studying?
Is it necessary to be so competitive?
Fine, go ahead and study.
Study to death.
You have class to attend to now?
Today...
Wait, it's Saturday today.
I'm going back to school
to have breakfast with Xu Zhi.
Wait.
Feeling sulky,
yet going to have breakfast with her.
Chen Luzhou, you are hopeless.
(Girls' Dormitory)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplify every sound♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪The lonely clock♪
♪A relentless pursuit, day and night♪
♪Are we both♪
♪Attracted to each other♪
♪Falling into you♪
(Have you gotten up?)
That's all for today's class.
(Architectural Drawing)
If you have more questions,
you can come to me.
(Where are you?
What time is the afternoon game?)
No.
I must change my major next year.
I really can't stand
staying up late every day.
I couldn't help dozing off yesterday
and dreamt that Mr. Hu told me,
"You drew well. Don't ever draw again."
It was so scary.
What's wrong?
Fought with your ex-boyfriend?
No.
What ex-boyfriend?
Gong Zhu,
can you do me a favor?
My high school classmate
is coming this afternoon.
So you can't go to Chen Luzhou's
match today?
Don't worry.
We two will cheer for him for you.
Right?
No.
I'd like you to
show my friend around for me.
Show him around?
I want to watch hot guys
play basketball.
I also want to watch my boyfriend play.
Boyfriend...
Thanks.
- Boyfriend?
Are you two really together?
Xu Zhi?
Go, go!
Come on!
Zhao Tianqi, go!
So cool.
Xu Zhi.
Go, go!
You good? It's hot.
It's boiling hot.
Let's eat ice cream later.
But you were really cool just now.
- Right?
- Yes.
I found it cool too.
Super cool.
Right?
One more game?
Sure.
You're up quite early.
Where is your phone?
In the dorm, charging.
You didn't bring your phone?
You can search.
What time is it?
4:30 PM.
Tell Zhu Yangqi
that we're together
and he can get to me through you.
When Zhu Yangqi contacts you,
you want your phone.
When I contact you,
your phone is charging.
Are you tired of me?
You actually asked that?
You would tire first if we were to.
What's with your mouth?
Got hit while playing.
Can you play basketball?
Not really.
What about shooting?
Not really either.
Let's have a shootout of ten.
If you win,
I'll grant you a request.
Do you want to lose or win?
Of course, I want to win.
I'll spot you four goals.
Ten for me, and six for you.
I advise you to give up.
I won't.
At least make an effort.
Otherwise, it'd make me look easy.
Are you serious?
(Would you like to grab a meal?)
(To thank you in person before I go.)
If you are going to him,
don't come to me again anymore.
I'm done wasting time.
That's it for us.
You saw him yesterday?
Do you really think that way?
I thought you knew me.
Come on.
I admit defeat.
If someone really pursues me,
wouldn't you just cheer them on?
If you truly care about me,
would you do that,
Xu Zhi?
It's okay that you gave him a tour
of the campus.
But you should have told me.
What am I to you?
What do you think you're to me?
Don't you know
I have no feelings for him?
But he cares about you.
He has feelings for you.
Do you know what I would do
if Gu Yan came today?
I would never meet her
without telling you.
Xu Zhi, you're not someone
who can't say no.
You just don't care about my feelings.
If that's the case, forget it.
♪On a midsummer night♪
♪The streetlights gradually awaken♪
♪The moonlight
penetrates the tree shades♪
♪Chasing the distance
between you and me♪
♪On the mountaintop
where the shooting stars pass♪
♪The silhouette is frozen in eternity♪
♪Fireworks, cicadas chirping,
heartbeat breathing♪
♪The whole world pauses♪
♪Messages connecting the universe♪
♪Billions of shooting stars♪
♪Following the path of the galaxy♪
♪Falling into your eyes♪
♪Oh, oh, oh♪
♪Billions of raindrops♪
♪Like the universe's response♪
♪Landing in my heart's depth♪
(I guess you're busy.
So I won't disturb you.)
(I'm going back to Qingyi now.)
(See you next time.)
♪We met across billions of light-years♪
♪Ah, ah, ah♪
(Sunflower)
Xu Zhi.
Here, milk tea.
I can't drink anymore.
Chen Luzhou asked me to bring it to you.
Chen Luzhou?
His captain was handing out milk tea
to the team
and asked him if he wanted some.
He said no at first
but took one in the end.
I have to go.
Finally got through.
I called Chen Luzhou all afternoon.
I almost thought
you two vanished into thin air.
He is playing basketball
and didn't bring his phone.
Okay. I'm glad he's still alive.
Are you busy now?
I'm right beside your school.
If you're free, let's have a meal.
Zhi, let's start eating first
and not wait for him.
I'm starving.
Are you sure?
Who knows when he'll be done?
I'm telling you.
Guys take forever
after playing basketball.
They need to shower, fix their hair,
and get changed.
It takes hours at least.
Let's eat first.
You're here.
So he'll definitely come.
No, he won't.
Is he still being jealous?
Did he tell you?
Yes.
Last night, I drank with him until dawn.
Didn't he go at around 4 AM
to have breakfast with you?
I thought he figured it out himself.
I didn't know.
I didn't know he came to see me.
I stayed up late last night.
So I overslept in the morning.
That's bad.
He was upset
and went to have breakfast with you.
But in the end, he waited all morning
and never saw you.
He must be more upset now.
What should I do?
Zhi, I...
I'm just telling you this.
Don't mention it to him later.
Because I...
I haven't shared these thoughts
with him.
Go ahead.
Chen Luzhou
appears to be carefree,
caring about nothing.
But when it comes to you,
he cares a lot.
He knows
you have no feelings for Tan Xu.
But Tan Xu
spent two years with you.
You studied and progressed together.
While Chen Luzhou
has only known you for a few months.
And most of the time you were apart.
I know.
He has
very high standards for himself.
Whatever it is, he forces himself
to do his best.
Sometimes I even think
he's quite stubborn.
But I know he does that
because he doesn't have
much sense of security.
Actually, as his friends,
we often tease him,
saying he's a mama's boy
or something like that.
But actually
he's never spoiled enough
to act wishfully.
In elementary school,
he ranked top in the class.
But his mom believed
it was nothing to be top in class.
In the middle school entrance exam,
he topped the city.
He listened to his parents
to transfer schools or go abroad.
(He keeps adapting to new environments.)
(Although he went through all this,)
(he never told us.)
(He digested)
(all the bad emotions alone.)
(Actually, in these few months
he disappeared,)
(a lot happened.)
(In Ruicheng, he nearly died.)
(Upon his return,
his parents got a divorce.)
(Although he's said nothing,)
(every step he takes)
(is an effort toward you.)
(I only found out recently as well)
(that the night we had a gathering,)
(he secretly took your black hair tie)
(and has always worn it on his wrist.)
♪The moment I hug you♪
♪Let every chapter of the story align♪
♪Even if it rains on you♪
♪I will always be with you♪
♪Like a rainbow appears♪
♪Our love will last♪
♪Even if it rains on you♪
(You passed the add-on admission.)
♪You're the only one♪
♪When the rain blurs the world♪
♪Parallel distance♪
♪With you♪
♪The splendid, sunny memories♪
♪Mend uneasy dreams♪
(Zhi)
♪Even if it rains on you♪
♪I will always be with you♪
♪Like a rainbow appears♪
♪Our love will last♪
♪Even if it rains on you♪
(Zhu Yangqi, can you do me a favor?)
Even if I die...
Die...
Wait a moment.
Die....
Alright, get off.
Let me.
How did the song go?
Set a pitch.
Even if I die...
Lucy, you're here.
Come on, sit down.
You're late. You have to sing a song.
Come on.
See what song you want.
I'll pass. You guys go ahead.
No.
Just pick one.
Sing one.
No one is singing?
Then I'll sing.
Pick my theme song for me.
Okay.
Applause.
Sing.
♪If a heavy rain falls♪
♪Let me♪
♪Become the ocean♪
♪With all those seemingly constraining♪
♪But actually love-woven♪
♪Waves♪
♪If the heavy rain remains♪
♪Maybe, I'll forget to go home♪
Ask him if he has eaten.
If he hasn't, he can order food here.
Got it.
Lucy,
she wants to know
if her sweetheart has eaten.
You added 'sweetheart', right?
No, I don't have the experience.
I'm not ordering. I'm not hungry.
Lucy said he wants you to feed him.
I can hear you.
♪The sun♪
♪If a heavy rain falls♪
It sounds great.
Yingying, doesn't your school
have a curfew?
I remember it's 0:00.
It does?
Yes.
The school gate is closed at 0:00.
Should I take you back to school?
Sure, let's go.
Let's go. Hurry.
By the way,
this room's available till 6 AM.
Sing well and chat well.
Don't waste it.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Luzhou is so hard to deal with.
I've known Zhi for years.
I've never seen her
be so humble to anyone.
If you put it that way,
Lucy has never been so upset before.
Alright?
He's
been so stifled these past few months.
He can let it out a bit.
Lucy blah blah.
Letting it out is fine,
but there should be a limit.
Right?
I think this time,
Lucy has indeed been a bit dramatic.
When I called you that day
after getting drunk,
did I say anything wrong?
What do you think?
- Water, Lucy.
- I'll go buy some.
Thank you all for watching.
See you next episode.
Thank you, audience, for watching.
(Broadcast Host)
See you in the next episode.
Hello, what's up?
Hello?
Is this the host, the lovely Ms. Cai?
Are you drunk?
Yingying,
do you prefer muscular or skinny men?
Can you at least give me a goal?
Gaining muscle is hard enough.
I also need to lose fat.
I really can't take it anymore.
Stylish Zhu,
you don't need to change.
You're fine as you are now.
Wait.
I can also beatbox. Do you like it?
I'm really sorry
for torturing your ears.
That's it?
Also, I promise
I'll control myself.
No more drunk drama.
You better keep your promise.
I will.
Put it on.
You're in short sleeves.
I'm fine.
I'm all muscles.
Quickly put it on.
Well,
it's late.
Let me take you back.
No, I can take a taxi myself.
No, your school is so far.
It's so late, and you're a girl alone.
I can't let you go alone.
Alright.
♪Both of us lack something♪
♪That's why we instantly become unhappy♪
♪It's hard to be simple,
for there are many burdens♪
♪I'm brave, but I still feel sad♪
♪In life, there are choices♪
♪But wisdom often comes
after the closes♪
♪My emotions are a mess.
My words are harsh♪
♪Communication just falls short♪
♪Perhaps only you understand me♪
♪So you didn't escape♪
♪While crying, you tightly hug me♪
♪Whispering how much you love me♪
♪Only you understand me♪
♪Like a trapped beast♪
♪In skyscrapers, longing for freedom♪
I didn't handle
the matter about Tan Xu well.
I'll drink to apologize.
Enough.
Stop drinking.
I booked a room for Cai Yingying.
Before I could say it,
she left with Zhu Yangqi.
I'll still be charged
if I cancel the room.
Maybe I shouldn't cancel it.
If not canceled, who will sleep there?
I will.
Let's go.
Over there.
Why haven't you gone back yet?
I'll see you to the door.
This is it.
Bye-bye.
What's going on?
♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
Why are you still here?
Don't you want me to stay?
You want to stay so much?
♪The roar of the heartbeat♪
♪Drew a trajectory♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
Yes.
I'd regret if I left like that.
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
♪The endless clear sky
disperses the rainy season♪
♪Taking away all the mud♪
♪Leaving an echo♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
(Although he's said nothing,)
(every step he takes)
(is an effort toward you.)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplifying all the sounds♪
♪Who will visit me♪
♪Treading carefully
into my personal space♪
♪Turning the frozen loneliness♪
♪Into concern and care♪
♪Watching stars rise and fall♪
♪Gently pushing me to tour your world♪
♪Swirling into a vortex♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪The lonely clock♪
♪A relentless pursuit, day and night♪
♪Are we both♪
♪Attracted to each other♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪Just a few more embraces away♪
♪From reaching eternity♪
♪After rushing recklessly♪
♪We approach each other♪
♪Without turning back♪
♪In your eyes, I see myself♪
♪Falling into you♪