♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
♪A brilliant scenery♪
♪Moonlight spills over
the endless clear sky♪
♪The roar of the heartbeat
leaves a trace behind♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪Fervent, boiling love♪
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
=Be Passionately in Love=
=Episode 14=
(The Untouchable Lover)
Luzhou.
Don't you feel
the taste of this place's food
is just average?
Why do so many people still come here?
A movie had some scenes
filmed here before.
What movie?
What is it about?
Want to know?
Another 800?
This time, in euros.
Are you not afraid of draining me?
Getting addicted to extorting me.
You're heartless.
No pay?
Then ask others.
Excuse me.
Kid,
what do you want to know?
I will tell you.
You are also Chinese?
Many Chinese people come here to eat.
Such eye-catching ones are rare.
The brother is handsome.
The younger one is cute.
My cute little brother
has many questions.
Please answer them for him.
Come find me outside later.
I'll be at the door.
Thank you.
What do you want to know?
Don't mind him.
He ended a relationship.
Luzhou, wait for me.
Wait for me.
They told us to go to the Lego store.
Is that okay?
Okay.
It's not that I'm picking on him.
You know, it's rare for us to go out.
Is it so hard to take a picture?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Luzhou has been in a bad mood.
You know that.
What's there to be
in a bad mood about for him?
We are seeing him off to school.
He should be happy.
Always pulling a long face.
All right.
You are his dad.
Can you stop arguing with the child?
Was that an explosion just now?
Someone is injured.
From the restaurant.
Luzhou.
Xingqi.
Wait. Slow down.
Luzhou.
Slow down.
Come on.
Let me see.
Be careful.
Hello.
Hello, Luzhou.
Luzhou, where are you?
How's the situation?
Yes, how is it?
Chen Xingqi is fine.
No, he got hit and injured.
What about you?
How are you? Are you okay?
Hello, Luzhou.
What's wrong?
No sound.
Stay here.
Luzhou.
(Police Line)
(According to reports,)
(a local explosion occurred in Ruicheng)
(on the 17th.)
(Currently, one person
has died and three have been injured.)
(News Report)
(A Chinese national student hurt.)
(After the incident,
the police reached the scene)
(and began their probe.)
(Human causes aren't ruled out.)
Fruit is here.
What are you doing?
(News Report)
Over there.
Xingqi.
Excuse me, they are my sons. My sons.
Hurry up.
Luzhou, are you okay?
Xingqi.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
What hurts?
A bit startled.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
His hand got scratched.
Are you okay, Xingqi?
Here, please.
Xingqi,
are you okay?
It's okay, I'm here.
Are you okay?
To the hospital.
- Okay.
Did you bring the passport?
I-It's in the hotel.
I'll go get it.
Be careful yourself.
Hurry up.
It's okay.
Xingqi, I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
What's wrong, Zhi?
Has Chen Luzhou connected you today?
He hasn't replied to my message all day.
I don't know where he's gone.
What? You want him?
Then I'll hang up.
(Ruicheng Explosion Accident)
Chen Luzhou?
Looking for me?
Why didn't you answer the phone?
I dropped the phone.
I couldn't answer it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Don't worry. I won't die.
I promise you
I'd play the violin for you at 80.
Have you missed me?
You're really bad at this.
You should say it's okay,
when we broke up, you said,
"Xu Zhi, your shoelace is untied."
How arrogant.
Not as arrogant as you.
Then why don't you ask me?
What?
Ask if I've missed you.
Have you?
I'll tell you next time.
Okay.
Xingqi.
Luzhou.
No. Luzhou!
No.
This matter is unacceptable.
No room for discussion.
Such a big matter
is not up to you.
You think it's easy to get in here?
I've put in so much effort.
What exactly are you thinking?
You should also
consider from our perspective,
Luzhou.
No way.
Besides,
the arrangements
are all set.
Now you're not going.
Why?
This is my own decision.
I'm not to discuss with you.
Luzhou.
Nice job raising your son.
Look at him now.
Just perfect.
I'll book the flight ticket.
I can't stay in this place any longer.
What's gotten into you?
He's losing it, you have to too?
Can you calm down?
Calm down.
How can I calm down!
- You...
- Every time I close my eyes,
I see that boy covered in blood
lying in front of me.
He's about the same age as Luzhou.
Who can guarantee
similar situations won't happen again.
What if it's Luzhou?
Just because of an incidental event,
do you need to be so emotional?
If this continues like this,
will he continue his studies?
Luzhou is my son.
His life is more important
than anything.
Let's return
immediately.
Zhi, here's a little fortune pouch
for you.
Good luck always.
You really understand me.
Xu Zhi,
this is a small token for you.
T-This wouldn't be
a promissory note, would it?
How could a promissory note
be this thick? Feel it.
When did you become so generous?
Exactly.
Can't remember?
Isn't this
a promise from when you were 6?
I gave you New Year's money
and you said,
"You give me the money,
but I can't spend it.
My dad takes it all."
I asked you what to do.
You said,
"You save it for me.
When I hit college,
give it all to me."
I'm here to fulfill that today.
As expected of Zhi,
having such a business mind at 6.
Isn't this at least 10,000?
A round number.
See. I told you my lucky bag worked.
Really!
Don't take so much money.
What if she wastes it?
It's for her.
Now that you've grown up,
you get to manage it.
Ignore him.
Yes, I'll use it wisely.
But I have to add.
When you earn money,
first buy clothes and food for your dad.
Boyfriend should come second.
Dad is most important. You know?
He's telling you.
Dad is the most important.
Then I might as well not date
or marry in the future.
Just stay by your side.
Don't find me annoying.
How could you not date?
I'm telling you.
Once you're in college
and enter society,
you'll know.
The most innocent romance
is just in the campus.
You should still
give it a try.
Alright.
Don't chase my boyfriend around
with a knife.
How come?
You'd be better off without Chen Luzhou.
Check it at the Hua University.
What if among ten guys,
nine of them are like him?
Just don't get tired of them.
Okay, I'll take your good words.
Love is love.
If someone bullies you,
remember to tell me immediately.
Okay.
The car is here.
Hurry.
So soon?
Don't miss the train.
- Really.
- Zhi.
Zhi, this time you really have
to take care of yourself.
Wear more when it gets cold.
Mr. Xu, are you finished?
Zhi,
you must take good care of yourself.
Make a video call every day.
Call me daily.
Don't lose weight.
You must stay chubby.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Miss me.
You need to study well.
You've never been away from me
for so long.
Alright.
Don't go.
That's enough.
She'll come back during holidays.
Yes.
Missing the train later would be bad.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Wait for me.
I'll go to Beijing next year.
Alright.
Bye-bye.
(Safe travels.)
♪Don't be afraid,
what you've experienced♪
This is it.
♪You will fulfill the past♪
♪Dream you long for♪
♪Open your arms to embrace the breeze♪
♪Together with you♪
♪Look, this city♪
♪It keeps raining♪
♪Ticking and tattling♪
♪Who is worried♪
♪I believe
you can't find a reason either♪
♪Don't give it an answer♪
♪I'm the same♪
♪Just keep moving forward♪
♪Memories fade♪
♪Yet we are still♪
♪For ages♪
Xu Zhi?
Yes.
Hello, my name is Xu Gongzhu.
Hello.
She is Liu Yisi.
We are the same major.
Do you need help? I'll do it.
Thank you.
No problem.
You're also reading these.
My friend gave them to me.
Everyone who can get into Hua University
is truly extraordinary.
When
school starts,
let's go to the library together.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Hello,
I am your roommate, Du Qilan.
Thank you.
This is for you.
Take some if you like.
Don't be shy with Senior.
Senior?
Yes, she is
a sophomore in philosophy.
I was assigned
with several seniors.
After they graduated,
you all came.
By the way,
there's a mixer.
I signed you all up.
Many seniors will be there.
Don't be late.
Senior.
- Handsome guy.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'll leave first.
Contact me anytime.
Okay, bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
I'm coming. Don't rush me.
Need me?
No need. I can do it myself.
Okay.
(Basic Architectural Design)
(Architectural Design Basics)
(Ancient Architecture,
Tang Dynasty Architecture)
(Architectural Art)
(I changed my number.
Remember to save it.)
(Received.)
(On the first day,)
(how did you all spend it?)
(Making my bed.)
(Did you go to Ruicheng
to change your number, Lucy?)
(Why aren't you talking?)
(You haven't
forgotten us already, have you?)
(Silly boy,)
(do you know)
(what does time difference mean?)
(I'm going to sleep.)
Luzhou.
Mom,
how many days remain?
If this continues,
my hand will swell like a pig's trotter.
The doctor said
you won't need injections
until all your indicators
are completely normal.
They also said I need to rest more.
Don't think about it.
You have to attend art class as usual.
Didn't Dad say I could skip it?
Useless.
I don't care. I just want to rest.
I just want to rest.
I want to eat ice cream.
Remember?
When you were in Ruicheng,
you had a fever and started vomiting.
Still want to eat ice cream?
I don't care. I just want it.
Alright, stop...
Sir, turn right ahead
and stop.
Still macadamia, two scoops?
Right.
Mom,
don't you think
Luzhou is acting weird.
If it were before,
he would take
the opportunity to extort me.
But this time he agreed so quickly.
Your brother treats you well.
Not well?
I still like him the way he was before.
Ever since he came back,
he's not close to us anymore.
(Welcome Party)
Xu Zhi.
Excuse me.
No wonder looking familiar.
It really is you.
Qian's mom always mentions you.
She said you're
the best among Qian's tutors.
Did you come alone?
Xu Zhi.
I'll go over first.
Okay.
Where are the others?
Backstage. Eyeing cute guys.
Next, we have philosophy sophomore,
Jiang Yu,
(Welcome Party and Opening Ceremony)
singing Freedom.
♪Both of us lack something♪
♪That's why we instantly become unhappy♪
♪Simplicity is hard♪
♪There are many burdens♪
♪Though very brave♪
♪I still feel sad♪
♪In life, there are choices♪
♪But wisdom often comes
after the closes♪
♪My emotions are a mess♪
♪My words are harsh♪
♪Communication♪
♪Just falls short♪
♪Maybe only you♪
♪Understand me♪
♪So you didn't escape♪
♪With tears streaming down♪
♪You hold me tight♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪How you love me♪
♪Only you♪
♪Understand me♪
♪Like a trapped beast♪
♪In a skyscraper♪
Isn't he quite handsome?
What?
He's Jiang Yu.
Heartthrob of Humanities.
♪Maybe only you♪
♪Understand me♪
♪So you didn't escape♪
♪With tears streaming down♪
♪You hold me tight♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪How you love me♪
Eat what?
Nothing. I'm dieting.
I want to eat fried chicken.
Sure.
Where's she going?
I don't know.
Junior.
What's wrong?
I've lost one of my earrings.
Let me help you find it.
Junior!
Is it this one?
Thank you.
I almost thought I couldn't find it.
This earring is important to you, right?
That's right.
My name is Jiang Yu,
sophomore from School of Humanities.
My name is Xu Zhi.
Architecture.
How did you know?
When singing,
I noticed you.
Alright.
Xu Zhi.
Li Ke.
You left too quickly.
I forgot to tell you.
I formed a group for Qingyi locals.
We meet occasionally.
I'll add you later.
Sure.
I'm there.
I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
You two are high school classmates?
No, we're both from Qingyi.
Different high schools.
She's a friend of my friend.
Girlfriend?
Sort of an ex-girlfriend.
I'm off now.
(Huaguang University's
Extra Admissions Plan)
(Luzhou, you're about to be outed.)
(There's a charming guy chasing Xu Zhi.)
(You better be careful now.)
(Even though I think you're
more handsome than him.)
(But, maybe Xu Zhi)
(doesn't think so.)
The offer arrived.
You just let him not go.
No further discussion.
Do I not even have the right
to speak about Luzhou?
Because of an accidental incident?
Yes.
I did promise you
to send Luzhou abroad when he turned 18.
But you saw what happened that time.
That young man was covered in blood,
lying in front of us.
He's about the same age as Luzhou.
I can't leave my own son
alone abroad.
Except Ruicheng,
he can go to another country.
Have you
already made up your mind
not to make him to go out at all?
You simply don't trust me.
No matter what I say,
you won't believe it.
Is it that I don't trust you?
From the start,
you lied to me.
How is it my fault then?
This happened more than a decade ago.
You're bringing up the past?
I can stop bringing up past,
but please
fulfill your promise.
I can't fulfill it.
If you insist on forcing Luzhou abroad,
we'll get a divorce.
You want to divorce me?
You better not regret it.
I understand.
So you two
have already discussed this.
I'm the only one left in the dark.
Divorce.
Fine then, divorce it is!
(Friend Reuqest)
(I'm Jiang Yu.)
(Don't lose important things again
next time.)
It's okay. Just a small wound.
Otherwise, tonight,
you go sleep in Xingqi's room.
I'll stay with him.
Are you okay?
Even if I explain many things to you,
you may not necessarily understand.
You will definitely look at us
from your perspective.
All would do so.
We are not the same.
I feel that in this world,
there is no such thing as empathy.
Because there is no one
who can truly understand one another.
Don't make things so complicated.
Have you ever thought
if I leave this family,
there wouldn't be many problems.
Don't think like that.
This matter has nothing to do with you.
It's an issue between
Chen Jishen and me.
Adults will handle adult matters.
But I am also an adult now.
From now on,
about the future,
I'll decide my future.
Go to sleep.
Luzhou.
Are mom and dad really going to divorce?
Who will you stay with then?
I won't stay with anyone.
Then can I stay with you?
Go to sleep.
♪On a midsummer night♪
♪The streetlights gradually awaken♪
♪The moonlight
penetrates the tree shades♪
♪Chasing the distance
between you and me♪
♪On the mountaintop
where the shooting stars pass♪
(Quotes from a liar:
I will always be by your side.)
♪Messages connecting the universe♪
♪Billions of shooting stars♪
(Quotes from a liar:
I will always be by your side.)
♪Ah, ah, ah♪
Xu Zhi, over there.
Okay.
Junior, help Xu Zhi.
Come with me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Do you need any help?
I can manage on my own. Thank you.
Well.
As a newbie in publicity department,
feel free to ask me
if anything's unclear.
Okay.
Senior,
how should we stick it here?
I still need to help over there.
Okay.
Then where should I stick this one?
Senior.
Senior, focus a bit.
Thank you.
Hey, Miss Cai,
you finally have time to care about me.
I started school.
I can't contact you freely, okay?
How have you been?
Did you meet the alternative
Chen Luzhou?
I'm not that free.
At our second canteen,
there's a delicious malatang.
For just over 10 yuan,
you get a full bowl.
Really?
Are you trying to tempt me
to go to Beijing?
You should come quickly.
If you're late,
this title of my bestie
will belong to others.
How dare you!
How has your relationship
with your dad been?
(Join the Chemistry Experiment Club)
To be honest,
I think
since I'm repeating my studies,
I can spend an extra year with him.
It's quite good.
You figured it out so quickly?
Because that day,
I went to the hospital.
Come on. Let's drink.
Mr. Cai,
where did Yingying end up going?
She didn't do well on the exam.
She's at home, repeating her studies.
Repeating studies is so tough.
There's no need for this.
For girls,
it's all the same.
Education just sounds good in theory.
A good husband
matters most, right?
Don't say that.
How can a girl's education
not be important?
(Cai Binhong, Vice Dean)
In the past,
I was too busy with work
to look after her when she was young.
Never mind.
She is not worse than others.
And she's intelligent.
If she works hard,
she can get into the university
she likes.
Moreover, I feel
her future marriage quality
isn't important.
What matters is her happiness.
Isn't it?
Yes.
It's okay to stay single.
That's what I think.
If she does well in the next exam,
she will support me.
In case she doesn't do well,
I will support her for life.
Have some tea.
Okay, come on.
Hearing you say that,
I kind of miss Xu.
Don't worry.
Your dad's cooking is so good.
I'll often go to your house
for a meal on your behalf.
Alright, I won't talk to you for now.
My tasks aren't finished.
Bye-bye.
Are you okay?
It's nothing. Just a slight sprain.
It's not serious.
From the dorm lady.
Who bought them?
She has no idea.
(When he)
(took me to the practice track,)
I didn't get
the apexing right
and crashed.
Luckily, it was not serious.
But I scraped my knee
and got arthritis.
It hurts on rainy days.
It even creaks.
That's why I hate going out
on rainy days.
You listen.
Chen Luzhou.
♪And you always have me♪
♪Don't be afraid,
what you've experienced♪
Where are you going?
♪You will fulfill the past♪
♪Dream you long for♪
♪Open your arms to embrace the breeze♪
♪Together with you♪
♪Look, this city♪
♪It keeps raining♪
♪Ticking and tattling♪
♪Who is worried♪
♪I believe
you can't find a reason either♪
♪Don't give it an answer♪
♪I'm the same♪
♪Just keep moving forward♪
♪Memories fade♪
♪Yet we are still♪
♪For ages♪
(Shy Boy Chen: Just woke up. What's up?)
(Did you bring me medicine?)
(Li Ke: Xu Zhi, did you receive
the medicine for you?)
(I received it.)
(How did you know I was injured?)
(I have informants, you know.)
(I'm really sorry.)
(I don't know it.)
(So I just bought randomly.)
(For sprains, joint pain,
calcium supplements,)
(I got them all.)
(Pick)
(a useful one.)
(Thanks a lot.)
(You're welcome.)
(We're fellow villagers.)
(You are a friend of Luzhou.)
(My duty.)
(Impossible.)
(Chen Luzhou is in Ruicheng.)
(How could he possibly
appear in Beijing?)
(Nothing. I hit the wrong key.)
(Zhi)
(Done. There shouldn't
be any loopholes.)
Thanks.
Why so polite with me?
I just didn't expect you
act like a coward,
sending medicine under my name.
In my opinion,
if you really like,
just go for her boldly.
The far-away love isn't unusual.
You have me as a lookout.
I'm busy.
Talk later. Bye.
(Fighting alone for so many years.
What I want might be a bit greedier.)
(It's passionate and unfaltering love.
It's one of a kind. It must be me.)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplifying all the sounds♪
♪Who will visit me♪
♪Treading carefully
into my personal space♪
♪Turning the frozen loneliness♪
♪Into concern and care♪
♪Watching stars rise and fall♪
♪Gently pushing me to tour your world♪
♪Swirling into a vortex♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪The lonely clock♪
♪A relentless pursuit, day and night♪
♪Are we both♪
♪Attracted to each other♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪Just a few more embraces away♪
♪From reaching eternity♪
♪After rushing recklessly♪
♪We approach each other♪
♪Without turning back♪
♪In your eyes, I see myself♪
♪Falling into you♪