One month ago,
my workplace was insanely exploitive,
so I quit the job
as I was never treated like a human being.
[ Rejection of Employment E-mails ]
Now I have no job.
I can't pay rent or my phone bill.
Even my student loan payments are in trouble.
I just want to disappear.
- Ya-ho!
- Hey!
- Join us!
- It's carefree here!
They look like they're having fun.
That might actually work.
Ah, I got one.
Smile Agency Ltd. Interview Notice
Thank you very much for applying to our company...
Smile Agency Ltd.
I-I'm Kanako Nishino!
I worked at a small ad agency.
I am experienced at sales, admin, errands, cleaning,
and organizing company parties...
Hey.
You do realize we're an assassin agency, right?
Can you even kill someone?
No way! No way! Get otter here!
Wait, an assassin?
You mean, like, an actual killer?
What do you mean?
But it's an agency, right?
Oh...
"Agency" as in killing on behalf of someone?
You did manage to track us down.
So clearly you've got some skills.
What?!
My job hunting was a total disaster.
So I even applied to shady websites?!
No, no, no, no snail way!
I'll turn down. I'm leaving.
President, why are you running an assassin agency?
I finally escaped an exploitive company...
And this is even shadier and not a normal company!
I'm sorry but I have to say no. I'm sorry.
Um, in the end...
Our starting salary is 600 thousand yen.
Working hours are 10 AM to 7 PM and weekends off.
Overtime is, of course, paid.
What?
Full social insurance.
And, of course, pension benefits.
You in?
Wow, it's such a top-tier company.
I'll do it!
Absolutely.
Happy Kanako's Killer Life
Episode 1
This is your entrance test.
Shoot the target with this.
Huh?
Wait, what?
No, no, no, no snail way!
There's no way I can kill someone!
Yeah.
I looked into you.
Kanako Nishino.
Your father died of an illness when you were eight.
Your mother works at a local supermarket in the fried foods section.
You even know that?
After graduating from university,
you got a job at an ad agency.
But you boss there abused you terribly.
And in your third year, you quit.
And your target is your former boss.
What?
You really put up with that for three years?
Apparently, there were others who ended up depressed and killed themselves because of him.
Well, at least quitting was the worst that happened to you.
You've already shot him?
Sorry!
My finger slipped!
I wasn't supposed to shoot yet, was I?
I'll redo it!
Ah, but I already shot him!
Alright, I'll just shoot the one over there!
Not bad.
Alright.
Time for a welcome party.
A welcome party?
No way!
After killing someone,
a welcome party is just insane!
Cheers!
Boss? Boss! A toast!
Ah, let's wait for this.
Cheers!
Boss! Who knew alcohol could taste this good after killing someone?!
Flap meat.
Whoa...
I feel so strangely refreshed!
Excuse me!
Excuse me! I'd like to order!
Yes? Yes?
I'll go buy beer.
I'll buy one.
A beer and premium highball, please!
- Yes!
- Understood.
Rump cap.
Boss!
I'll do my best as an assassin!
The rump cap is so good!
Being an assassin is awesome!
Don't say that out loud.
I will say these...
"I quit."
"I can't be an assassin."
Resignation
Letter
Yesterday, I got carried away and shot my ex-boss, but...
I can't tell my mother I'm a killer.
I'll say, "I quit."
Um...
Uh...
Ah, Boss.
[ Operations Report ]
Boss...
Uh...
This is really hard to say, but...
Was that your first time killing someone?
Yes, Sir.
You're...
...a genius.
Huh?
That's the first time I've ever been praised.
No, no, no, that's bunny ears!
You shouldn't be happy about that!
I killed someone!
You nailed a perfect headshot from that distance.
I did?
Yeah, that was no ordinary feat.
Whaaat?!
Where did you learn to handle a gun?
Online.
Just that? Any other training?
Late-night overtime shifts and heavy workloads?
What about hiding your presence?
Should I not do that?
I was scared of being yelled at so I learned to avoid standing out.
Wow! So that actually came in handy!
Am I suited for this?
Goodbye.
Your work desk is here.
Thank you!
Oh, a cat!
Wow!
Of course.
And here's your first job.
Take him out.
What? He's just a regular young guy.
Should we really kill him?
Even if it's a job, this is...
He has repeatedly raped female college students.
Three victims this year alone.
And his parents keep bailing him out.
Let's kill him!
Wait, hold on...
Do you drink?
A little.
Stab him with a syringe as you pass by.
His heart will stop like he's just fallen asleep.
Don't attract attention.
Hey.
Keep an eye on her.
If things go south, you know what to do.
Wait, at home?
Oh, that's cool.
What about your other sizes?
B-cup.
- We want to test it out ourselves first.
- What?
Are you free tonight?
- Yeah, I'm free.
- Oh, okay.
Alright, see you later tonight.
Yeah.
Later.
- See ya.
- Later.
Bye-bye.
What an idiot!
Seriously, huh?
No, no, no, that's bunny ears!
Killing a young guy with a future...
That's kind of hard to justify.
I mean, I can't kill anyone in the first place!
I can't!
- How about her?
- She's gross!
You responded fast!
She's gross!
What was her name again?
No idea. Gifu?
"Gifu" is easy to remember.
Should I call the Gifu girl?
Only scumbags would judge others by their looks.
Call an ambulance!
Good afternoon.
I just finished work.
See you again tomorrow.
Wow, it really disappears.
Amazing.
Hello?
Oh, hey, Mom.
The package arrived!
They don't sell these here.
How's it going, Kanako? Been busy?
Hmm, it's the usual.
You sound like you're doing well.
Really?
Umm...
Mom...
I changed jobs.
Oh, really?
But you said you liked your old job.
Well, a lot happened.
So today was my first day.
I had to go straight to the field.
The field?
For what?
For the agency's survey.
Did you do it properly?
Yeah, more or less.
It went pretty smoothly.
Maybe an 80 out of 100.
Not bad.
Well, good for you. It went well.
Yeah.
I might be good at this new job.
I see.
That's good.
I'll do my best.
But don't overdo it.
You always push yourself too hard.
I'll be careful.
I'll kill you!
Okay!
Newbie, where did you disappear to yesterday?
Umm...
I went straight home.
Sorry.
But the boss said once I messaged him...
If you get in my way, you're dead.
I'm gonna croak with fear!
Is he your senior?
His name is Sakurai.
He always saying "I'll kill you."
He definitely hates you.
You think so?
He's so scary!
Also, I have no experience doing a surprise attack in the dark.
Newbie.
I'll kill you.
Who is it?
What's going on?! What's going on?!
Oh no!
Stop dragging your feet, or I'll kill you.
Slow, slow, I'm dinosaur slow.
As I thought I'm not cut out for being an assassin.
Yeah...
Someone as useless as me...
Should just live deep in the mountains...
Quietly, without bothering anyone.
That's right...
I won't get in the way anymore.
Poof.
Did she die?
Good work, Sir.
Since when were you there?
Uh, the whole time.
"Stop dragging your feet."
"I'll kill you."
I was here since you said that.
Uh, well...
I was trying not to be a bother.
And since there were a lot of people,
I figured sticking close would cause the least trouble.
So for now...
I stuck close...
Did I piss him off?
I could probably handle them one at a time.
I have to do this properly...
I need to say something...
I feel like I'm gonna croak literally...
Um, Sakurai...
That was amazing earlier.
You kill so smoothly.
Have you been an assassin for a long time?
No, no, that's not what it!
I should change the subject...
So, Sakurai...
Who's your favorite member BLACKPINK?
Rosé?
Hey.
Yes?!
Before, you...
Are they chasing us?!
Deal with them.
Huh?
Show me how it's done.
Did you already shoot?
Ah, sorry!
I'll make sure to aim properly next time.
My former boss always said that I should get things done in three seconds, so I just reacted.
Is she for real...?
I'm sorry.
I accidentally put a hole in it the rear window...
In the gentle sunlight of spring,
Our Failure
I was nestled in your kindness
And I was such a coward, wasn't I?
Good work on the late-night shift.
Sakurai got mad at me...
I'm sorry.
That's just how he is.
He actually think highly of you.
What?! That's surprising!
I put in a little extra for your first paycheck.
From now on, please take care of me
I know I'm like this, but forgive me with a smile
Always cherish me, okay?
Becau...
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much...
...rantee
Kanako Nishino
Non
Sakurai
Taisuke Fujigaya
Voices of the Animals
Asuka Saito
Voice of the Preview
Fumihiko Tachiki
President / Boss
Atsuro Watabe
Next Episode Preview
Was the man Kanako met at the convenience store her father?
And is the man in the subway
a reincarnation of her mother's enemy?
Two people approaches Kanako...
...we might as well call
Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
A mysterious pair.
Plus, a female teacher appraises a hidden treasure!
Next time: The Steamy Kanako Case! The Stray Sniper's Struggle Arc!
Don't miss it!
Shiawase Kanako no Koroshiya Seikatsu (2025) JDrama ep01
Unofficial fan English translations for DMM version - v2025.03.01
TL-Skeweds' translations may contain errors.
If you find any, please point them out as specifically as possible
and suggest how to improve them through our email (tl.skeweds@gmail.com).
There may be improved translations in the future.