(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
You can find your mother.
Have you ever looked
for your biological mother?
Do you want to look for her?
The mother who gave you birth.
I don't even know who my mother is.
How and where
are you going to find her?
What do you think you know about me
to offer to find her?
Are you ridiculing me right now?
- So, do you want to find her?
- No.
Not at all.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Gosh, that man just took off.
I hope it's not broken.
It's fine as long as you're okay.
Stop minding me and go.
Why do you care
if the heater is broken or I'm hurt?
Mind your own business.
You're irritating me.
Do you think I want to mind you?
You keep getting on my mind...
and making me feel concerned.
You're always suffering
like everyone's punching bag,
letting people walk all over you.
How can I turn a blind eye to that?
Is that my fault?
Turn your gaze away and pretend
like you don't hear anything...
no matter what others say to me.
Just treat me like I'm invisible.
Please!
I can't do that!
Do you pity me?
- Because I'm an orphan?
- How can you say that?
Do you pity me
because I don't have a mom...
who'll fight against Ms. Yoon's mom
after getting beaten up by her?
If that isn't the case,
why do you suddenly bring her up?
Did I ever say I wanted to find
my biological mother?
I don't know what she looks like
or what her name is.
I never even thought about
my birth mother to this day.
Who do you think you are to ask
if I want to find her?
No, I...
Do you not want to find her?
Not at all?
No, I don't.
I do not.
Why does he care if I get hurt...
or if I find my mom?
You look hurt.
Where's your mommy?
What's wrong?
It looks hurt. Where's its mommy?
Let's take you to a doctor.
The inflammation looks severe
all over its lungs.
It'd need to be hospitalized
for about a week.
Would it be all right
after treatment?
Of course.
What do you want to call her?
She's a girl.
You should name her.
- Yali?
- "Yali?"
I like it.
Yali.
And the guardian's name?
- Goo Na Ha.
- Hwang Jin Goo.
- Please. Yes.
- No, you can do it.
- It's okay.
- Goodness.
I'll go with Ms. Goo.
- All right.
Hang in there a little more, Yali.
It didn't seem like
she had been weaned off.
How did she end up losing her mommy?
I wonder.
She'll be fine after treatment,
so don't worry too much.
Ha Na, why are you so late?
Why are you here again?
Goodbye.
Okay. Goodbye.
You're still out of your mind.
Why were you with him again
after what Yoon Se Young...
and her mom did?
Is something going on?
No, nothing.
A strong negation equals
a strong affirmation.
You're suspicious.
Don't settle
with Yoon Se Young's mom,
even if she kneels and begs you.
- I already did.
- What?
You took the compensation, right?
- How much did you get?
- I didn't take it.
You're insane.
Why did you settle the case
without any compensation?
Did you really do something wrong?
Is something going on
between you and Hwang...
So, why didn't you take the money?
Then, how will you save
Ji Seok's face?
Yes, I'm home.
She settled?
The chairwoman initiated
a lunch meeting with Ms. Goo...
and Ms. Yoon's mother.
It seemed like she was persuaded
or coerced into settling the case.
What was her term?
It was to appoint Ms. Yoon
to the hotel instead,
and she'd be working
right under you.
Are you sure
you'll be fine working with Ji Seok?
I can't avoid him forever.
It's a great chance to find out
what he's up to.
You finally sound like my daughter.
Make sure you find out about
his relationship with Richard Han...
and what his motivation is...
in joining our business.
Why do you think I'm here?
To get my revenge on you?
It's more like the opposite.
How dare he ban me
from entering the building?
Me, the next chairwoman
of Hyesung Group?
What? You won't let me be
the chairwoman?
Of course,
you're the next chairwoman.
Anyway, why were you at work?
Right. I thought
she took the files to work...
from that safe.
I wanted to take a photo
of the safe in her office.
I'll find a chance to take one.
I can be your friend.
How's my best friend?
Eun Chong? Yes, he's well.
It must be tough to balance
your work and raising your nephew.
Even working mothers
have a tough time raising their own,
and you're doing it for your nephew.
Eun Chong is a smart and good boy,
so it's not too hard.
He brings me lots of happiness.
I heard you had been looking
for Eun Chong's grandmother.
Yes.
But I don't have enough leads,
so it's not too easy.
Do you have some leads?
My friend remembered
a few fragments of memories...
before she passed away.
Such as?
She remembered a wooden swing,
a fireplace, hot chocolate,
and marshmallow.
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Did she mention anything
about her parents?
No, we hoped she'd remember
something about her parents,
but she suddenly passed away.
Wooden swing, fireplace,
hot chocolate, and marshmallow.
Be careful. Watch your clothes.
All right!
Should I get rid of the fireplace
and the wooden swing...
before Goo Ha Na moved in here?
And my family photos.
How did that sick kitten
end up losing its mother?
What happens after you treat her?
What will you do then?
She should be adopted.
I feel bad...
for all humans and animals
that don't have a mother.
Do you pity me?
- Because I'm an orphan?
- How can you say that?
Did I ever say I wanted
to find my biological mother?
Do you not want to find her?
Not at all?
No, I don't.
I do not.
Does she really have zero intention?
Yoon Se Young.
You aren't the only one
who has a mom.
I have a mom too.
Mom!
She even shouted out
that she also had a mom.
Mr. Hwang wasn't the type
who'd talk empty.
I have zero information
about my mother.
What was he thinking
when he said he'd help me find her?
Ha Na, what's wrong
with this fan heater?
It's broken.
Did you not check it
before you picked it up?
- Well...
- Come on.
People shouldn't con each other
in the neighborhood.
I'll report this guy so that
they'll never get to use...
the secondhand marketplace again.
No, that's not it.
I dropped a perfectly good product,
so that happened.
Really? You should've been careful.
Right. I heard you settled the case.
Why did you do that?
You should've put her behind bars.
- You should leave.
- Darn it.
Ms. Goo Ha Na wanted to be
separated from Ms. Yoon at work...
as her term for the settlement.
It'll be hard for you two to work
in the same office when you marry.
Think of this
as moving up her appointment...
- at the hotel.
- Yes, ma'am.
We put an end to the assault case...
after Ms. Goo settled
and Mr. Goo dropped the complaint.
Thank you.
Ms. Yoon will be helpful in turning
the hotel into a global business.
She studied a lot in America
regarding that industry.
I look forward to it.
The Dubai contract
was pushed back by three months,
and so was the second payment...
of the investment.
The tour would proceed as planned
after three months.
I believe
we'll receive the investment...
once what you said happens.
I don't understand the logic...
behind postponing the investment
because of a subsidiary's contract.
I wish to speak to Richard Han.
When is he coming to Korea?
He'll be here soon.
He hasn't given me a date,
but I can't just wait forever.
Let's set a date
for a video conference.
Let's do that.
Will you go after Hyesung Group...
after you put Hyesung Tour down?
Make sure you report
those exact words to the chairwoman.
It'd be fun to discuss that
over the video call.
What will Richard Han say?
In the worst-case scenario,
the investment will fall through.
Then, do that.
You aren't in a situation
to worry about the group.
You lost the contract
with both Hanguk and Hyesung Hotel,
resulting in a stock price decline.
The Dubai contract
almost became your lifeline,
but that was also postponed
by three months.
Hyesung Tour will
switch over to deficit very soon.
We almost went into a deficit...
because of the contract
you called off.
We've maintained our sales,
so we wouldn't go into a deficit...
if you didn't hinder us.
So, it's my fault?
It's kind of confusing.
I thought you'd be competent
as Hyesung Group's possible successor,
but you had trouble
separating work and personal life,
and your personal life
didn't seem too clean, either.
I was also confused.
You continue to provoke
and taunt me,
but it doesn't seem like
it's only because of work.
What is it?
I find you fascinating.
I don't find you fascinating.
You aren't my type.
Head Director Goo, who keeps a good record
in work and personal life,
I'll keep an eye on you
and see if you maintain that.
The second payment
for the investment was postponed?
Mr. Goo was behind
the Dubai project, right?
The circumstances say he's the one,
but there's no evidence.
What great timing.
I'll have to keep an eye on him
as soon as I transfer to the hotel.
He wouldn't give us information
that easily.
I'll do whatever it takes
to find out.
Find a legal way to keep an eye
on Mr. Goo and Richard Han.
Let's make him cut his own throat.
That sounds fun.
- When is my transfer?
- Next week.
Ms. Yoon, you were summoned
by Head Director Goo.
Have a seat.
I called you because you'd start
at the hotel next week.
Yes.
It's your first time at the hotel,
so get used to the basics first.
Secretary Jung will
give you the files.
I plan to use our overseas investors
when it comes to marketing.
If you give me their information...
- Who gave you that idea?
- I came up with it.
You just have to do the tasks
as I tell you.
You don't know what I'll demand.
Why do you want the investors' file?
Tell me whatever you need.
- I'll do anything if it's for work.
- "Anything?"
Did you decide to side with me
instead of Hwang Jin Goo?
Don't be so clingy.
It's not appealing.
You were behind the Dubai project.
Did you think you'd win
by tampering with the investment?
I already won.
If you want to win,
bring evidence instead of feeling me out.
It's not too appealing
when you're clingy with your words.
So, you'll do anything
if it's for work?
Yes, I like that attitude.
I look forward to everything.
Sure. I do, too.
You don't have a lot of stuff.
Here. Those are the rules
for our cohabitation.
Put it up on the wall
and read it morning and night.
All right. Did Eun Chong write this?
I did.
The format
doesn't take away the meaning.
- Sorry?
- Well, it's not the handwriting.
You have to read the rules.
Yes, I see.
Also, there's a bit of draft
in this room,
so I put a fan heater here.
The one who was here before you said
hot air was your skin's worst enemy,
so she always refused to use one.
But you were a bit older,
so I thought the coldness could
make you fall out of your health.
It was my special gesture.
This may look broken,
but it still works fine.
Thank you. I'll put it to good use.
Please ask me anything
if you have any questions.
- Please relax as you unpack.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
He's a bright young man.
Ms. Goo, have you revised
your theme?
Yes, what if we take the photos
they take during this trip...
and turn them
into their younger selves?
The daughter back to her childhood,
and the mother back to her youth.
It'll lower the bar for those...
who don't have photos
from childhood.
Is that possible?
Have you asked the photo crew
for advice?
Yes, they can do that
by using AI technology.
I want to run a sample test
after the president's approval.
Gosh, I love the idea.
How many times have you traveled
with your mom after you grew up?
Often, right?
No, never.
Why not?
You seemed like a good daughter.
Did you propose
the mother-daughter therapy tour,
although you've never traveled
with your mom?
This is a fraud.
Isn't that so, Ms. Yoon?
You all didn't know?
Ms. Goo...
You all should be
more interested in your colleague.
What's wrong?
Did I do something?
No, you didn't.
My mother passed away
when I was in high school.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm not the only one
who doesn't have a mom in this world.
I imagined I still had my mom
while I put this proposal together.
I had fun thinking...
how it would've been great
to do these things with her...
if she were still here.
Yes, your mother's absence could
make you become more innovative.
Keep up the good work, Ms. Goo.
It's Mr. Hwang.
You can get back to work.
We'll cancel the contract
if we do not have guests from Dubai...
even after three months.
Our investment is at stake,
so we're also in a bit of a hurry.
I'll contact you immediately
if anything changes.
Goodbye.
It's a tour
for mothers and daughters.
Can you send me
a tea lesson recommendation?
Goodbye.
Ms. Goo.
Yes, Mr. Hwang.
Will you continue to avoid me?
Do you want me to transfer you
if you feel that uncomfortable?
I didn't avoid you on purpose.
I wanted to focus on work
without anything else on my mind.
The mother-daughter therapy tour
is my first project,
so I want to do a good job.
I imagined I still had my mom
while I put this proposal together.
I had fun thinking...
how it would've been great
to do these things with her...
if she were still here.
- Is there a problem?
- No.
I'm sorry for yesterday.
You were misunderstood
and beaten because of me.
I felt bad because it seemed like
you had to handle every trouble,
so I ended up crossing the line.
It's all right.
I also got overly emotional.
- Excuse me.
- Ms. Goo.
Yes?
I'm not sure
if what I'm doing is right.
But I'd rather do this myself
than make someone else do it.
Ms. Goo, if I can help
with your happiness...
by keeping this secret forever,
then I'll do that.
Please speak.
Do you know
about the DNA registration program?
It's something that families
with missing persons do.
Have you ever done that?
- No.
- You look for Eun Chong's grandma,
but why won't you look
for your biological mother?
It seems like
you're doing this out of pity.
But my foster parents are
my only parents.
I've never thought of my real mom
over the 30 years of my life,
and I never imagined I'd meet her.
I don't even care
if she's alive or dead.
What if
you start considering it now?
Why do you suddenly ask?
Someone is...
looking for you.
Who?
Her foster parents
passed away in a car accident?
Yes, it was handled
as a simple traffic accident.
Then, their business began to fail,
and in the end, it went bankrupt.
- What was the business called?
- Youngshin Distribution.
Any connections with my business?
Who's looking for me?
Someone who may be
your biological mother.
Stop joking.
Who would joke around
about something like this?
Who is this person?
I'll tell you
after you receive a DNA test.
No, tell me now.
To be honest,
I don't get what you mean.
I don't know who my real mom is,
so how do you know her?
Everything is
just a speculation for now.
It must be true.
Why do you speculate
that she's my birth mother?
You should hear it from her.
Do you have memories before seven,
before the children's home?
No.
You were too young,
so you couldn't rely
just on your memories.
That's why she wants
to take a DNA test.
She could be your biological mother.
Then, I'll meet her first.
We'll talk face to face.
After you take the test.
You said I could be her daughter.
Then, I'll meet her
right away and...
Does she not want to meet me?
- It's not that.
- If she wanted a parentage test,
she shouldn't have hidden behind you
and asked me to do it.
She should've come to me
and asked me herself.
If she isn't that desperate,
she probably isn't my mom.
It was quite random of you
to mention my biological mother.
I'll pretend I never heard this.
- What if she is?
- I doubt it.
I lived a perfectly good life
without knowing...
who my biological mom was.
I'll just continue to live this way.
Do you...
- resent your mother?
- I can't do that...
because I don't feel anything
about her.
Please excuse me.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Is there really
something going on between them?
Ji Seok.
Is something going on
between you and Mr. Hwang?
- What?
- Is there something...
between you two,
just as the rumors say?
Nothing is going on.
Then, what happened just now?
Why would the president
have such a serious discussion...
with an employee?
It was about work.
Bye.
She won't do the DNA test? Why not?
She thought you should meet her
if you were her daughter...
instead of hiding behind me
and demanding that she take a test.
She must've been hurt.
I was too rash.
She must've been disconcerted
because this was the first time.
Even animals know
who their mothers are.
Of course, she missed
the mother who gave her birth.
I also want to see Eun Chong
very badly.
How did you end up telling her
about her biological mother?
I also hoped
Ms. Goo could have a mother.
Someone who could take her side
for the rest of her life.
I thought you could be
a mother like that.
Then, have you made your decision?
Yes, I'll take over the process
of turning Ms. Goo...
into your daughter.
I know it won't be easy
and that it'll be dangerous.
Thank you, Jin Goo.
However, I do have one term.
Please keep her safe
no matter what the situation is.
Promise me that
you won't hurt her in any way.
Yes, I promise.
What can I begin with?
Bring the file in.
Yes, Ms. Chairwoman.
This file contains
basic information on Ms. Goo.
Her files in the children's home
were destroyed in a fire,
so I'm missing information
from her childhood.
The file includes
her identification, education,
work history,
and files regarding her career.
Your sister
must've been through a lot.
My heart breaks
whenever I think about her trouble.
I'm sure my sister...
would've won the grand slam
if suffering were a sports event.
She practically raised me,
and she raised him
since when he was one.
Gosh.
Uncle Ji Chang, are you crying?
I'm not crying!
Everything will return to her
as blessings.
Of course.
If you agree, make a toast.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Hey.
Hello.
- Did the move-in go all right?
- Yes.
You haven't had dinner, right?
Please join us.
He treated us
to celebrate his move-in.
You didn't have to.
Thank you.
- Did you eat a lot, Eun Chong?
- Yes.
You should eat, too, Auntie.
Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
How can this happen
all in one person's life?
She went to the children's home
at age seven.
She went through
multiple adoptions and dissolutions.
Then, she was adopted
by Goo Ji Seok's family at ten.
Her foster parents
passed away when she was 18.
After that,
she became the breadwinner.
And now, she's a foster mom.
It's heartbreaking.
The chairwoman will become someone
for her to rely on from now on.
I hope so.
You said her age was the problem.
It's not just her age.
Ms. Goo's father passed away,
but Mr. Yoon simply left home.
She doesn't have any memories
before age seven.
What if we said
her memories were distorted...
and made her believe
the chairwoman's memories...
as the truth?
Memories from that age
tend to be inaccurate,
so she won't be suspicious
even if her memories are distorted.
Can you revise the age
in the news articles...
- regarding Yu Jin's disappearance?
- Yes.
Right. You said the information
she knew about her daughter...
- could be a problem, too.
- Yes.
We must destroy the fireplace...
and the wooden swing.
And all family pictures...
except for the ones
from her infancy.
Mom. Dad.
I wanted to pretend like
I never heard that.
But the words "birth mother"...
seem to be stuck in my head
like leeches and won't let go.
But how did she know about me?
How does she know the president?
Hello. How's your room?
Let me know anytime
if you need anything.
Everything is wonderful,
thanks to your consideration.
How shall I address you?
You can call me Ha Na.
Ha Na.
- Should we sit for a moment?
- Sure.
Our place is a bit rowdy, isn't it?
It's like a real family home.
I like it.
I missed something like this
after living alone for a long time.
I also heard about Eun Chong...
and that you've been
looking for his grandmother.
Yes.
You're young enough
to be my daughter,
but I want to show you my respect.
My brother must've said
so many things.
You look for Eun Chong's grandma,
but why won't you look
for your biological mother?
Is something troubling you?
Well, no.
May I ask about your family?
I had a family.
But she has gone away to a place
where I can't see her anymore.
And there's someone
I can't meet even if I want to.
It looks like
there's someone you want to meet.
Why don't you pluck up your courage?
I should do that
if I didn't want to leave regrets.
But there are many things
I need to figure out first.
But I believe in the saying that
everything is meant to be.
It comforts me to know
that those who must meet...
will end up meeting one day.
I like that saying, too.
It doesn't apply just to romance.
I think everything is like that.
It looks like
we speak the same language.
We do.
(Job Application, Name: Goo Ha Na)
She dropped out of high school
and took the GED exam.
Then, she studied alone,
passed the international tour guide test,
and got a job at a travel agency.
She never took a day off
from her late teens until this day.
Ms. Goo,
what do you have inside you?
What gave you the strength
to hold out to this day...
without anyone to rely on?
A hundred and fifty dollars?
Where do you think you're going?
A hundred and fifty dollars is
almost my day's wage.
You're also responsible,
so please pay half the fine.
I'm really sorry.
So, please correct
just the news article.
I'm the breadwinner of my family,
so I must make money.
She was like family.
Eun Chong had no one in his life,
so naturally, I decided to take him.
My family is what charges my energy.
When I'm with my siblings
and Eun Chong,
I feel full at heart,
even though we're broke...
and don't own a home.
When I was younger,
I always felt empty here,
like the wind blew
through a hole here.
If anyone finds out she isn't
the chairwoman's real daughter,
everyone will be miserable.
It doesn't leave out anyone.
Every single one.
I can't let anyone find out.
Ms. Goo.
Please be happy.
I'll do my best...
to let it happen.
You...
surely deserve...
to be happy.
(Cinderella Game)
Can you find out more
about Richard Han?
He sent his woman as a spy.
Have you heard anything
about Goo Ji Seok in America?
Would my life change in any way...
if I met my real mom now?
You should meet Ms. Goo first.
Please consider Eun Chong.
What are you up to, Yeo Jin?
You must deceive her smoothly.
She would want to meet me right now
if she were my mom.
I truly wish to help you.
Who is she?
Is she someone I know?