(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 49)
Was that not a dream?
Then, back then,
did Ms. Goo and I...
Wait. Hey.
I think the security guard is gone.
- Should we go out?
- Yes.
Then, I'll go first.
Mr. Hwang, you can come out.
- My gosh!
- Who are you?
Please let me go just once.
I had to handle something urgently.
I understand your situation,
but you weren't supposed
to come into the office.
It was just today, sir.
I won't sneak in again.
He's right.
We were done with everything
after tonight. We're about to leave.
Please have some.
I'm so sorry.
We're causing you trouble, right?
All right.
I hope his punishment
is lifted soon.
You two should go.
- Thank you.
Jin Goo had to work in the corridor?
I was already dumbfounded...
about how he was on suspension
after punching someone.
He's in the corridor?
You should've stopped him!
I tried,
but he wouldn't listen to me.
What does he do
sitting out in the corridor?
He was looking for the evidence...
that Mr. Goo postponed
the Dubai contract by three months.
He went home late
doing that yesterday, so again,
he must've been doing that today.
Will you let Jin Goo
get humiliated like this?
First, you should
lift his punishment...
and handle the disposal, too.
If you approve
the disposal of Hyesung Tour,
then I'll stay quiet
about your corporate raiding.
If I had to consider Jin Goo,
I would need to scrap that plan.
But I also can't let him expose
my corporate raids.
Grandma, where's my auntie?
Hey, Eun Chong. You're up.
Do you want to stay with me
until she gets home?
Come here.
Isn't it ridiculous how she cares
much more about him than Yu Jin?
Tell me about it.
I'm sure she has a reason.
- Mr. Han said that?
- Yes.
He said he'd ask someone
in the police,
but it'd take some time, so he asked you
to finalize the sale first.
I'll do that.
It was worth the hard work.
The two must've worked overtime.
Yes, they must've finished putting
the shredded papers together.
(Quick Delivery)
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Chairwoman Shin once collapsed
after receiving a delivery, right?
How do you feel?
I was quite concerned after hearing
about your collapse yesterday.
I'm fine. Goodbye.
That was probably when she found out
about her daughter's death.
You said she wouldn't recover easily
if her daughter had died.
She must've received good news, too.
Something that could offset
her daughter's death.
We're back on ground zero.
What could that be?
If our presumptions are correct,
that must be the reason
Ha Na is her fake daughter now.
She went to a children's home...
the day after she received
that delivery, right?
- Yes.
- Why did she go there?
Ha Na has never heard
of the name Yoon Yu Jin.
What if she used a different name
that wasn't Yoon Yu Jin?
"A different name?"
Cheers.
The file we put together
should be enough...
to get more board members
on your side, right?
There's enough evidence,
so we have a fighting chance.
I should also persuade them
as much as I could.
We looked at it until our eyes
got dry and almost popped out...
and put everything together
with so much effort.
I hope it goes well.
You make that look so delicious.
Come to think of it, we haven't had
a welcome dinner since you started.
Goodness, people don't have
company dinners anymore. I'm fine.
Have some food, too.
Thank you.
Two days ago, you took me home...
after I got drunk, remember?
Right. Why do you suddenly ask
about that day?
By any chance, did...
Well, nothing happened, right?
Wait, does he remember?
Like what?
There was this moment,
and I wasn't sure...
if I was dreaming or if it was real.
Are you okay?
What was this moment
you weren't sure of?
Never mind. Later.
He must be talking about that.
It's not like I can tell him.
Why don't we clink our glasses
instead of clinking our lips?
What am I saying?
I must've gone crazy.
Gosh, I must be drunk.
I began to say total nonsense.
We should go.
So, it wasn't a dream.
What was that smile?
I'm suddenly craving a drink.
- Another bottle of drink, please.
- Sure.
Wait, you weren't supposed to drink.
Your mother told me.
I can take a glass or two of soju.
I deserve
this kind of small happiness.
You were completely knocked out
after half a bottle that day.
Well, that day, it was...
because I wasn't feeling well,
not because I was drunk.
I'm feeling great today, though.
We found the evidence, and...
I just feel great
about everything today.
My dear child, the apple of my eye.
I'll live the rest of my life...
for you.
What is it?
It seemed like Richard Han had
more information than we expected.
He had been digging up
other shell companies...
besides the one Mr. Goo showed you.
And you still don't know
who Richard Han is?
No, and it seemed quite suspicious
that he refused to do a video call.
Did Mr. Hwang say
he found the evidence?
I don't know. Yu Jin isn't home yet.
You should make a decision
by tomorrow.
A heart condition?
It must've been serious.
Well, the chairwoman saved me
from the brink of death.
So, I consider her my second mother.
My mom did such wonderful work.
Your second mother,
who gave you a heart.
Wait, that means
I'm your older sister.
I'm the older brother.
- Why?
- I was born earlier.
- Show me your ID.
- I don't have it.
Also, why do you want to be
my older sister?
Aren't you sick
of having younger brothers?
Wouldn't it be nice to have
an older guy in your life?
"An older guy?"
It'd be nice
to have an older peer in my life.
Then, you can find one.
Right. I should date a guy
who was a year older than me.
You need to find a decent guy,
unlike that man last time...
Hey, don't bring that up again.
I already learned my lesson
deep inside my head...
No, deep inside my heart.
I'm glad.
Right. When I was younger,
this guy I knew said...
he'd get heart surgery, too.
I wonder
if he's living a good life...
after a successful surgery.
He probably is, just like me.
I want to know.
Life happened,
so I had forgotten about him.
If you two were meant to meet,
you would, at least once.
It'd be nice to meet him
at least once.
He shared his luck with me, too.
He was a good kid.
- Was he your first love?
- No.
It was a trivial encounter,
but it was nice.
Let's have one last drink
before we go.
Okay.
- Cheers.
You came just now?
Did you drink?
Yes, I was a bit hungry after work.
- With who?
- Mr. Hwang.
Just the two of you?
Other staff members
couldn't stay late.
All right. You could crave a cool
drink of beer after doing overtime.
How's putting the shredded file
back in one going?
If you were curious,
why didn't you help us out?
Mr. Hwang could've used
lots of help today.
I had a meeting
for the hotel yesterday,
and today, I felt under the weather,
so I came home early to rest.
What if they really put it together?
Bye.
Who were you talking to
about the shredded file?
- What are you talking about?
- You were on the phone...
in the break room, asking
what would happen if we put it together.
Was it about the shredded...
Do you enjoy
eavesdropping on my calls?
I wasn't eavesdropping.
You can't share work things
with random people.
I wasn't talking about
that shredded file or whatever.
Do you come to work
just to slander me?
- What?
- I'm not crazy.
Why would I share such
confidential information with another?
What did Mr. Hwang see in Se Young
that he decided to marry her?
Calm down.
No, that can't happen. Stop.
Then, would it kill me?
Are things not going well at work?
No, I found the evidence,
so everything would go well.
Gosh, I'm so glad.
I believed in you.
And the chairwoman is
on your side, too.
- When do you receive training?
- Next week.
Thanks to you, I took great courage
in the latter years of my life.
That's so wonderful.
Shabu shabu is your favorite dish,
so I know you'll do well.
But you can't overstrain yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll hire some staff,
and I also know
how to look after myself.
All right.
Now, take a good look.
This is the evidence
that you're behind everything.
You're barging in without context.
You canceled the contracts
with our affiliated businesses,
abetted the forgery
of official papers,
and usurped and destroyed
the evidence from Dubai.
I think the story is quite evident.
I commend you for your effort.
And the result
doesn't look so bad, either.
But I'm sorry.
The game has already ended.
- "Ended?"
- Then, please excuse me.
I have to be
at an important meeting.
Stop right there.
I'm not done talking to you!
I'm not done talking to you.
What did you mean,
the game has already ended?
Oh, there's Chairwoman Shin.
Come in, Mr. Goo.
- Mr. Hwang, wait here.
- Ms. Chairwoman.
But I'm sorry.
The game has already ended.
Wait, is the chairwoman giving him
the approval for the disposal?
You cannot go inside.
- Move aside.
- No, Mr. Hwang.
(Signed by: Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin)
President Hwang will
resist furiously.
Move aside!
Mr. Hwang...
Move. Move aside!
Did you just sign
the disposal agreement?
This time, things went
as Richard Han wanted.
But tell him that
it won't be easy next time.
Yes, I'll relay your words to him.
Please excuse me.
Ms. Chairwoman, this isn't right.
I even found evidence
that Mr. Goo was behind this. How...
How can you
suddenly make this decision?
I'm sorry, Jin Goo.
But I made this decision
as Hyesung Group's chairwoman.
I hope you'll understand.
"Understand?"
You need to tell me
the reason first.
Give me a reason
so that I can understand!
(Head Director Goo Ji Seok)
I'll continue to dance
between Ji Seok and Jin Goo...
even after the business gets sold.
I don't know who'll take
Hyesung Group over at the moment.
Did she sign it?
Yes.
Congratulations.
- We're at work.
- You never cared about that.
Shouldn't you worry more
about Hwang Jin Goo right now?
Keep a straight face.
Don't let him catch you.
Do you think he will?
I can't believe it.
It said we've been sold.
It must be true.
We went through so much trouble
to put the shredded file together.
How can this happen?
I'll send my resume
to other travel agencies.
You should start looking, too.
Why don't we wait
until the president gets here?
- Where's Mr. Hwang?
- He's not here.
Is it true
that the business is sold?
I guess so. How can this happen?
- Mr. Hwang.
It seemed like
you all heard the news.
How could our disposal
be decided this quickly?
We even found the evidence.
Have you met with the chairwoman?
I'm so sorry, everyone.
But I will find a measure...
to secure your next position.
Mr. Han, she signed
the disposal agreement.
Good work.
If we take the rest of the shares
other than what the chairwoman has,
that'll give us two more percent
in the entire Hyesung Group.
That'll get our total shares
up to ten percent.
Ms. Goo Ha Na is here.
Yes, sir. Goodbye. Yes.
How did you persuade the chairwoman?
Why did she decide
to sell the business?
Why are you asking me?
You're her daughter.
You can ask her yourself.
I thought it'd be more accurate
to hear it from the man...
who turned the evidence we put
back together into nothing.
Everything was already done.
Why is the reason so important?
I needed to know why it was done.
Only then would our staff
who worked hard...
to stop our business from disposal
feel less wronged!
That's all the more reason
not to come and ask me.
Yes, I did
make your evidence useless.
But Chairwoman Shin
probably has another intention...
for deciding to sell the business.
- What?
- Ask her yourself.
Ask her what weakness I found
that she had to sign the agreement.
But of course, she won't answer.
"Weakness?"
I'm...
here, Mr. Goo.
Wait a moment. I'll be done soon.
Yes, Mr. Goo.
You may leave, Ms. Goo.
What did she say?
Was she mad because of the disposal?
What was that?
They seemed
much closer than I thought.
Did they become friends
while working together?
Why are you asking me?
You're her daughter.
You can ask her yourself.
Fine, I'll ask Mom.
(Chairwoman Shin Yeo Jin)
- Who?
- Ms. Goo Ha Na.
She wants to talk to you
about your decision to sell the business.
Let her in.
I'm keeping
your identity a secret at work.
What if someone saw you here?
I'm sorry.
I felt anxious,
so I came to ask you something.
Ask what?
I wanted to know why you agreed
to sell the business.
Why do you want to know that?
I already talked
to Jin Goo about that.
There was evidence,
but you suddenly decided to sell it.
Mr. Hwang didn't seem
to know the reason,
and Mr. Goo also wouldn't tell me.
I have a good reason
when I don't share something.
In that case, it's a good courtesy
to just let it slide.
I see. Right.
Ask her yourself.
Ask her what weakness I found
that she had to sign the agreement.
Does he really have
something on her?
Do you have any other questions?
What will happen
to the staff members?
They were all anxious
about their employment.
You're rather nosy.
You're my daughter.
You need to look at the big picture.
If you let personal feelings
get the best of you...
and don't know when to step in or not,
then you can't do anything big.
Refrain from visiting my office
in the future.
There are many eyes around.
We should be careful.
- Okay.
- I'll see you at home.
Okay.
Was it such a big mistake...
for a daughter to visit her mom?
What's wrong?
Were you heartbroken
about the disposal?
No.
You don't know the reason yet,
do you?
On the surface, she said
it was because of the investment.
But I think there's another reason.
Do you think someone holds
a weakness against the chairwoman?
"A weakness?"
Did you hear something?
No, I was just wondering.
I went to her office to ask for a reason,
but she got mad at me.
What if someone saw you?
Right?
I can't even call her my mom.
Why did I go there?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I was a little frustrated.
I wanted to speak to her casually,
but she still seemed distant.
I guess things must be
different at work than home.
I understand.
You're in need of customer service.
I think you need that
more than me today.
Why don't I make you
a cup of sweet coffee?
I'll have a cup.
One moment.
I'm sorry.
I made you stay up all night,
but it came down to this.
It wasn't even your fault.
- Have some.
- Thanks.
That's good.
If we can be this sweet...
Well, I meant...
it'd be great if things at work
could be this sweet.
Right. Yes.
That's what I want, too.
Then, let me make you some coffee.
No, I like it best when I make it.
I can't believe this.
What's the genre of this drama?
Total soap opera
around a family affair.
The younger brother sells
his older sister's business?
I've never heard
of anything like this.
I didn't think
Ji Seok could do so much damage.
Gosh, that sociopath.
It's frightening that
he and I share the same DNA.
Anyway, Ha Na won't have a problem
even if that company...
suddenly disappears, right?
Who'll mess
with the chairwoman's daughter?
Ji Seok must've known that
when he did this.
You're right. Innocent citizens
always end up suffering the most.
Right. Is everything going well
before the grand opening?
Of course. I'll probably
rake in money as soon as I open.
Once you do that,
what will you do for me?
- What?
- Well...
Free coupons.
Or you can have a voucher
to get three bestselling fritters.
Forget that.
I'll keep siding with Ha Na.
See you on the day of the opening.
Hey, it's really good, though.
Don't tell Ji Seok!
I was suspicious
of that little kid she brought.
"Little kid?"
I told you that it was odd
how Yeo Jin was all over him.
Why does she care so much
about that completely strange kid?
It does seem odd
for a cold-blooded corporate raider...
to suddenly act like
she's now a humanitarianist.
Find out more about that kid.
How did she end up raising that kid?
And what did his parents do?
I want everything.
One moment.
Hello?
The disposal was finalized?
Did Richard Han...
hold you back
with his corporate raiding scheme?
Nothing good will come out
if those words get out now.
Both Jin Goo
and Se Young have no idea.
You're right.
Then, what will you do with Jin Goo?
He lost his travel agency,
so you should
bring him to the hotel.
You should drive out Mr. Goo
and put Jin Goo in his position.
I can't get rid of Mr. Goo.
Because of your corporate raiding?
Hey, wait.
Maybe Richard Han sent you
those death portrait photos.
Did he spread the rumor
of Yu Jin's death, too?
Goodness, would he start the rumor
on how you found Yu Jin, too?
"The rumor?"
I'm so glad
Yu Jin is a grown-up now.
If she were as young as Eun Chong,
she could've been kidnapped or...
Goodness, Yeo Jin.
I'm just saying.
Who would kidnap
a grown-up like her?
Why did she look so startled
at the word kidnapping?
Was she worried about the boy,
not Goo Ha Na?
Where? Over there?
Where? Let's go.
Your mommy was very pretty.
Auntie Ha Na said
I took after my mommy.
Yes, you did.
What are you doing?
Nothing much.
- Go out and play. Go.
- Okay.
Why did Yeo Jin shudder
at the word kidnapping?
It'd make sense
if she was worried about that kid.
Don't you feel bad that
he doesn't have a mom? Be nicer to him.
Bang Ul, you can't afford
to worry about other people's kids.
Your son became unemployed.
What do you mean?
Why was Jin Goo unemployed?
Hyesung Tour would get sold.
What?
But Jin Goo said he found evidence,
so he'd be fine.
That evidence is useless now.
Yeo Jin reluctantly
had to make that choice,
so keep a straight face
when you're around her.
Oh, no.
It's ridiculous how the fake daughter
came with a kid.
It seems like
the fake daughter is just the front.
That kid seems like the real one.
Should I go through her room?
She still has
that ridiculous thing up there.
That means it must have
something to do with that kid.
She must have something here.
What's with this?
What is this?
What's this photo?
Wait.
She's...
Yu Jin.
By the way, what photo did you lose
to cause such a fuss?
Tell us,
and we can help you find it.
It's a photo of me, my mommy,
and Auntie Ha Na.
Wait.
Then, this was the photo
she had lost?
Could it mean...
that you're Yu Jin's son?
Little Grandma, what are you doing?
(Cinderella Game)
Eun Chong might fall into danger
if the shell companies were exposed.
You were the real one.
You should be careful.
You found your daughter now.
Blackmailing won't work on me.
Everyone will become miserable
if you find out.
Can't you just stop here?
I'll go to the hotel.
I didn't expect him
to volunteer to work for me.
You're nearby?
You're crazy.
What if someone sees you?
Why is she seeing someone else
while dating Mr. Hwang?