(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 64)
Do you have
something to say, Yeo Jin?
- Yes, have a seat.
- Okay.
My priority is
for Eun Chong to find his peace.
Of course.
That was why I thought of a way.
Why don't you two marry...
and adopt Eun Chong?
You want us to adopt him?
That'd be wonderful.
There are no parents...
who'll be better
at taking care of Eun Chong.
- Isn't that so, Se Young?
- Yes.
It also sounds great to me,
Aunt Yeo Jin.
You two will also become
the heirs to Hyesung Group...
after you adopt Eun Chong.
Our priority is to raise Eun Chong
into a wonderful successor.
Jin Goo and Se Young's marriage...
and Eun Chong's adoption.
Everything
worked itself out wonderfully.
Isn't that so, Jin Goo?
Se Young seems happy with this.
What do you think?
I don't want to do this.
Why not?
I cannot marry Se Young.
I'd like to call off the engagement.
Jin Goo.
What is this utter nonsense?
What's the reason?
We...
don't love each other.
You need to talk to me first.
Did you just drop this alone...
without talking to Se Young?
How dare you
call the engagement off?
You two should talk.
He caused enough trouble
with Goo Ha Na all along,
and he now wanted
to call the engagement off?
They absolutely cannot call it off
for Eun Chong's sake.
Of course not.
You won't find a better man than Jin Goo
to be Eun Chong's dad.
You should've talked to me first.
How can you announce this
to the elders without saying a word to me?
I didn't want to share it like this.
The chairwoman told us to marry
and adopt Eun Chong, so...
So what?
You always did everything
as she asked.
That was why you agreed to marry me.
So, just decide...
to adopt Eun Chong
as you always have.
I won't do that anymore.
And I made the decision
to marry you...
regardless
of what the chairwoman wanted.
Back then, I liked you.
Now you don't,
so you're calling it off?
I still like you today,
just as I did back then.
I'll marry you and adopt Eun Chong.
You don't like him.
I understand you want to be his mom
because of Hyesung Group, but...
If you get it, then it's fine.
He began to grow on me,
and I want to raise him
into a solid successor, too.
You didn't even ask
why I was calling the engagement off.
Is this because of Ji Seok?
That's 50 percent.
I don't want to mention him
to the elders.
It'll only embarrass me,
and it won't benefit you, either.
What about the other half?
I'm not sure if I can spend...
the rest of my life with you.
I don't love you.
- But I...
- Don't say that you love me.
Both you and I know that isn't true.
Don't fool yourself, too.
You can't see through my mind.
Isn't it because of Goo Ha Na?
Ha Na is irrelevant
to our broken engagement...
She probably is.
If we break off our engagement,
it's her fault.
So, make a wise decision.
I'm not calling this off.
Not even over my dead body.
- Don't get Ha Na into this.
- I threw down my pride to say this.
You have no right...
to jilt me like this.
You cheated on me with Goo Ji Seok
while we were engaged.
That's more than enough
to break off our engagement,
and I have all the right to do that.
I wasn't cheating.
I told you it was all in the past!
Both you, me, and Goo Ji Seok know
it's not just in the past.
But I don't want the elders to know.
Let's call it off quietly.
I'll kill myself
if you call the engagement off.
I'll kill myself!
Se Young.
What? What happened to her?
Are you all right? What's wrong?
She's bleeding!
She bled?
Is she unwell?
She should see a doctor.
Yes, she'll come downstairs
after changing.
You can drive her, Jin Goo.
No, I'll go with her.
- You can stay home.
- I'll go.
I feel more comfortable with Mom.
Let's go.
Have a seat.
I hope you and Se Young...
will become Eun Chong's mom and dad.
I can be his dad
without marrying her,
but I cannot marry Se Young.
She may not share blood with me,
but she's still my niece.
Se Young and her mom
stayed by my side...
after Yu Jin and my husband
both left this home.
If anyone should become his mom,
it'd have to be Se Young.
Please become his dad
and be my successor.
I probably must've hurt you
in some way,
but you also know
how much I trust and depend on you.
I don't think...
I'll change my mind.
Is it because of Goo Ha Na?
My decision to call this off...
has nothing to do with Ha Na.
(JH Beautiful Women's Clinic)
I thought I was pregnant, too.
You are pregnant.
What are you talking about?
Keep this and show it to Jin Goo.
- What is this?
- The baby in your womb.
You're eight weeks
into the pregnancy.
Mom.
This is the last move you can make
to cling to him.
Vaginal bleeding due to stress?
This was a chance
sent to us by fate.
Do you think he'll believe it?
You stayed the night out last time.
Yes.
He saw you bleeding with his eyes,
so he'd believe you
if you said you were pregnant.
If he doesn't believe you,
we can bribe a doctor...
and take him there with you.
Then, am I now an expectant mother?
Hey, are you all right?
Yeo Jin, we need to celebrate.
Se Young is pregnant.
Really?
Congratulations, Se Young.
Thank you, Aunt Yeo Jin.
Where's Jin Goo?
He's upstairs with Eun Chong.
She'll get to adopt Eun Chong
and have her own child.
We have two occasions to celebrate.
I'll go upstairs
and talk to Jin Goo.
- Okay.
What did the doctor say?
Are you unwell?
No.
You're a dad now, Jin Goo.
- What?
- And I'm a mom.
Wait, are you saying
you're pregnant?
Yes, I'm eight weeks into it.
Are you serious?
Look.
That's your baby in my womb.
I was still in the early stage,
so I should've been careful.
That bleeding
could've led to the worst.
That's our baby.
Are you going to let our child
grow up without a dad?
If you aren't sure if it's yours
because of Ji Seok,
then I'll let you check
after I give birth.
You're really something
for making me say...
something like this.
Come in.
- Did you tell him?
- Yes.
Congratulations, Jin Goo.
This child came to this world
as a blessing,
so you should be grateful.
She's still in the early stages,
so she has to be careful.
Don't give her any stress.
So, don't try to break off...
the engagement again, okay?
How dare a servant like you
try to break off the engagement?
I should be the one
to call this off first.
Breaking it off, my foot.
You're now tied down for life.
Congratulations, Bang Ul.
Both you and I will
become grandmothers.
"Grandmothers?"
Is Se Young pregnant?
Goodness, that's great.
How far along is she?
Eight weeks.
How did you know?
Did she have morning sickness?
She suddenly had vaginal bleeding.
She bled?
Are the baby and Se Young both fine?
Thankfully, yes.
Goodness, why did she bleed?
Is she unwell?
We'll talk in person tomorrow.
Come to our place, okay?
Yes, I'll make some healthy food
for Se Young to eat.
That's our baby.
Are you going to let our child
grow up without a dad?
How did I end up coming here?
I'm going in first.
What do you want?
You're really brazen for a con man.
I heard you were the one
who made Ha Na into a fake daughter.
Wait, why should I be so polite?
You ruined my sister's life.
You were the key instigator.
I'm guessing you're probably here
to apologize to Ha Na.
She doesn't need
something like that.
Don't be seen anywhere
in the 100-meter radius of our home.
Just go
unless you want to fight me, too.
Mr. Hwang is outside.
How's Ha Na?
Get lost!
That's none of your business.
Don't show her your pathetic pity.
I never pitied her.
Then, why did you deceive her?
It was because you pitied her
and thought she was a joke!
That isn't the case.
I knew I did Ha Na
and her siblings wrong.
If you allow me,
I'll repay all of you
for the rest of my life.
Can you make it like
this never happened?
You can't.
Then, don't ever lurk around here.
The day I see you here again is...
the last day you'll breathe.
I must've liked you,
Ha Na.
Se Young cheated on him
with Ji Seok.
I knew something was fishy
between those two.
What? Why did he go after
someone else's woman?
Did I actually hear it?
Or was I dreaming?
You're up, Ha Na.
How do you feel?
I feel better.
Have some porridge
before you take your medicine.
Have a seat.
About Ji Seok and Se Young...
What? How did you know?
I thought I heard
Ji Eun saying that yesterday.
Were they
really in that kind of relationship?
Shocking, isn't it?
Why did he choose to date
someone who'd marry soon?
Did he have
no one better in his life?
Goodness. You should eat.
Ji Seok was Se Young's other man?
I said it was all in the past,
that we broke up two years ago.
Two years ago?
Ji Seok was in America back then.
Did he date her back then?
How did things
get tangled up like this?
Congratulations, Jin Goo.
I'm so happy about this.
It's now considered invaluable
to have a baby before marrying.
I'm so glad.
I'm making chicken and seafood soup
to give to Se Young tomorrow.
- Have some when I'm done.
- I'm fine.
Is something weighing you down?
Did you feel burdened
now that you became a dad?
The child will grow up on their own
after you give birth to them.
And you two have enough money,
so don't worry about it.
I'll get changed.
She's pregnant?
Eun Chong, these days, can you sleep
right away when you lie down?
How have you felt lately?
Do you feel jolly and happy?
Or do you feel sad and angry?
You must feel sad.
Is it because
you cannot see Auntie Ha Na?
How sad are you?
Eun Chong has a reduced appetite
and insomnia,
and he has no interest
in anything right now.
He's suffering from depression.
What can I do
to help him get better?
It'd be best
to let him meet Auntie Ha Na,
the reason for his depression.
I can't do that.
Is there any other way?
He'll undergo play therapy
and art therapy at the same time.
Painting or communicating with animals
will help improve...
his emotional stability.
Goodness.
- Where's Se Young?
- She's in her room.
Hello, Ms. Chairwoman. I'm here.
- Hello.
- Yes, Mom.
- Bang Ul is here.
Okay.
Se Young, Jin Goo's mother is here.
Mother.
You can lie down
if you're too tired.
Goodness, how did you
end up bleeding?
I'm so glad
both you and the baby are fine.
Yes, Mother.
Goodness, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
She was heartbroken
because of Jin Goo.
Both Se Young and I
didn't get any sleep last night.
What about Jin Goo?
Did he do something wrong?
He said...
he wanted to call off
our engagement, Mother.
Calling the engagement off?
You're now pregnant with his child.
What is this nonsense?
Tell me about it.
Se Young fainted
after hearing that yesterday...
and ended up bleeding.
Well, thanks to that,
we found out about her pregnancy.
Why did he want to call it off?
Did you two get into a fight?
No.
He said he didn't love me, Mother.
I feel miserable.
How can he say that to me,
who's pregnant with his child?
Goodness, stop crying.
You'll lose your energy.
You're in the early stages,
so you must be careful.
He's going to be a parent soon.
What's this nonsense about love?
Don't worry about him.
He won't be able to call it off.
What if he stays stubborn?
Mother, I want to give birth to a child
in a happy family...
and raise them well.
He said that when he didn't know
you were pregnant.
He has
a high sense of responsibility.
Just trust me and relax.
I made chicken and seafood soup,
so warm it up and have some.
Yes, Mother.
My goodness.
You must've been heartbroken.
How can he say
he wants to call the engagement off?
Make sure you take charge
and keep him in line.
Se Young is in the early stages,
so she can't be stressed out.
Okay.
And the chairwoman said...
they should adopt Eun Chong
after they get married.
Eun Chong?
If they just adopt Eun Chong,
Jin Goo will be
the next chairman of Hyesung Group.
And the one after him
will be Eun Chong.
So, you need to do your best
to convince him.
If Se Young marries someone else,
that'll be the end
of Jin Goo's success.
If the chairwoman wants that,
then he'll do that.
- Hello.
- It's been a while, Ha Na.
Were you ill?
I caught a cold.
You must've been stressed out.
You dropped a lot of weight.
Hey, Ha Na. You're back.
- Hello, Mr. Yoon.
- Hey.
Anyway, there was a rumor that
the chairwoman found her daughter.
Is that true?
I heard that was a false rumor.
There was already an article
on the suspicion of her death.
What's the fact, then?
It's not like
she has multiple daughters.
Is Mr. Hwang here?
He's out on business,
so he isn't in the office.
I see.
(Letter of Resignation)
I heard you skipped work.
Are you unwell?
Didn't you choke me
and tell me to die?
You should be grateful
that I let you live.
Did you call to check
if I were dead?
Don't be mad.
I wasn't in my right mind.
What are you up to?
Don't you need me?
I need you.
I have to stay low
until I get married.
Don't even call me.
Why are you
so adamant about your marriage?
Hyesung Group
doesn't belong to Hwang Jin Goo.
My aunt told me to marry him
and adopt Eun Chong.
It wouldn't be so bad
to take it over in that way.
It'll be fun to control things
behind the scenes.
I'll call you back.
Yes?
- May I come in?
- Sure.
Do you feel better?
You should've gotten more rest.
Why are you here already?
I resigned.
I'm glad.
You kept working and working
without ever taking any time off.
You should rest for a while.
Are you dating Yoon Se Young?
- Eun Chong.
- Ms. Bang Ul.
Have you been well, Eun Chong?
I heard you were sick.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Grandma,
I don't have the cold anymore,
so may I go play with Yali?
He'll undergo play therapy
and art therapy at the same time.
Painting or communicating
with animals will help improve...
his emotional stability.
But Ms. Sim, you must be busy.
I'm fine...
as long as he has your permission.
- You can go, Eun Chong.
- Okay.
I apologize
that Jin Goo caused trouble.
He can't call the engagement off.
I'll talk to him
and make sure he understands.
Okay.
Hwang Jin Goo, that punk, came back?
Chairwoman Shin should apologize,
but she wouldn't come.
Only that punk I don't want to see
comes by every day.
Are they kidding me?
I think it's our turn.
We'll barge in if she won't come.
Yes, let's teach her a lesson
and show what happens...
if she messes with our family.
Get up.
Let's go.
- Who is it?
- We're Goo Ha Na's siblings.
What the heck?
What do you want?
We're here to see the chairwoman.
Goodness.
Who is it?
Goo Ha Na's younger siblings.
Let them in.
What brings you here?
Don't you know?
How will you compensate
for ruining my sister's life?
She can't eat or sleep.
She's practically dead.
You need to apologize sincerely...
to my sister.
Have a seat before you talk.
You need to return
kindness with kindness,
not with evil!
Did you have any idea
how she raised Eun Chong?
She raised him
with so much love since infancy...
after he was
left alone in this world.
And she went through so much
trying to find his grandmother.
How can you do this as a human?
Ms. Goo persistently declined
any compensation.
I had been thinking about a way.
I'm glad you're here.
- You need to apologize first!
- Hey.
What kind of compensation
are we talking about?
I can offer her money
or real estate.
Tell me what you want.
First, apologize to her.
Then, you can compensate.
All right. Come inside.
Yali!
You're going to be Jin Goo's son?
Then, you're my grandson.
Ms. Bang Ul, can you do me a favor?
What is it?
Can I go to Auntie Ha Na's place?
I want to see her.
Really?
But the chairwoman can't find out.
Can we keep it a secret?
"A secret?"
I came today...
to say my goodbyes.
What? Did you get a new job
while you took some time off?
No, I'm going to rest.
Wait, why are you suddenly quitting?
Are you seriously unwell?
No.
Thank you very much for everything.
Wait, you can't just leave
without a farewell party.
It's such a shame.
Let's schedule something
and meet up.
You've done well, Ha Na.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hello?
- Eun Chong.
- Auntie Ha Na.
Whose phone are you calling from?
Ms. Bang Ul's phone.
You're going to come to my place
with Ms. Bang Ul?
I'm at work right now,
so I'll be there soon.
Okay. Please wait for me.
Do you feel okay?
I feel too sick to eat anything.
But still, you should eat something.
I'm better off without eating.
I'll end up vomiting anyway.
That must be hard.
Will you really
call our engagement off?
I'll tell you
after I sort out my thoughts.
Our baby can hear everything.
Let's talk later.
Bye.
(Travel Service Department
General Manager Hwang Jin Goo)
(Letter of Resignation,
Name: Goo Ha Na)
Mr. Yoon, when did Ms. Goo come by?
She just left
about five minutes ago.
Five minutes?
You must've missed
your auntie so much...
if you ended up becoming depressed.
I get to meet
both Yali and Auntie Ha Na today.
It's the best day ever.
It is.
(Chairwoman Shin)
Why is the chairwoman calling me?
I probably shouldn't pick up.
The person you have reached...
I thought of going
to Ms. Sim's restaurant for dinner,
but she wouldn't pick up.
What if she took Eun Chong
and went to Goo Ha Na's place?
That's nonsense.
He was already in that neighborhood,
so he probably asked her.
Tell Ms. Jang to get the car ready.
Are you going to go?
Why is it so hard to grab a taxi?
This is bad.
- Hop in, Ha Na.
- It's okay.
I won't say anything.
You must be in a hurry, so hop in.
- Where is she right now?
- She's almost here.
What do you want to do with her?
I want to give her a big hug.
Goodness. Do you love her that much?
- Yes!
- My gosh.
Auntie!
Goodness. Ms. Chairwoman.
Why are you here?
You can't come here after saying
you wanted to see the cat.
- Let's go.
- I don't want to.
I want to see Auntie Ha Na
before I leave.
She's almost here.
Can you just let him see her
while he's already here?
- Get him in the car.
- Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Eun Chong.
My goodness.
My gosh.
- My gosh, Eun Chong.
- Ms. Bang Ul!
My goodness. Why...
Eun Chong!
Auntie Ha Na?
- You can't go.
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Eun Chong, no.
- Eun Chong.
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Eun Chong!
- Oh, no.
- Auntie Ha Na!
Auntie Ha Na!
- Auntie Ha Na.
- Eun Chong. No.
- Please open the door.
- Let me out!
Open the door.
You can't go.
- Go.
- Eun Chong, I'm right here.
- Please open the door.
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Go.
No. Eun Chong!
Eun Chong!
- Eun Chong!
- Auntie Ha Na!
Auntie Ha Na!
Eun Chong! Please don't go!
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Eun Chong!
Eun Chong!
Auntie Ha Na!
- Auntie Ha Na!
- Eun Chong!
(Cinderella Game)
Since when did you dare to defy me?
You're calling the engagement off
after getting your fiancée pregnant?
I'll take responsibility
for the baby.
Why don't you marry me
and adopt Eun Chong?
Depression?
How will you take responsibility
for my sister's life?
How is his grandmother
worse than us?
I need to bring Eun Chong home.
I got the evidence that
she forcefully took him in her car.
The police?
He was never diagnosed
with depression. He's healthy.
Eun Chong!
Drag her out.