(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 96)
Wait, aren't you Detective Cho?
- Who are you?
- We met at the casino in Gangwon.
Wait a moment.
Here's my business card.
Detective Cho?
What's going on?
Hey, let go of me. Let go.
What is this? Darn it.
Let go of me.
I'm a detective.
Who are you two?
The police will be here soon.
You have the right
to consult an attorney.
Are you two...
detectives?
- No. We're...
- law-abiding citizens.
Darn it.
Hey.
You're bleeding.
I'll put ointment on it later.
You should
call the chairwoman first.
Okay.
You must be Detective Cho Byung Jin.
Yes, I am. Who are...
I'm the mother to Yoon Yu Jin,
the woman who died...
in a hit-and-run accident
seven years ago.
I'm Yu Jin's dad.
A hit-and-run accident?
Yoon who?
Myung Ji made you stage
Yu Jin's hit-and-run accident...
Yeo Jin.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Myung Ji and I are old friends,
but I never took a penny from her.
On top of that, I have no idea
what hit-and-run accident this is.
Bring my daughter back.
Who do you think you people are
to do that to her?
What's wrong with you?
I'll make sure I find evidence...
and lock you
and Myung Ji up in prison.
You hid yourself well
for the last seven years.
But you can't do that anymore.
When will the investigation begin?
My daughter, whom you allegedly
don't know, is named Yoon Yu Jin.
We'll meet again very soon.
You got arrested?
Someone must've found out
we were meeting there.
So, Sung Ho and Yeo Jin
came to see you?
The couple came together
and even grabbed me by the collar.
They asked
if I took money from you...
and acted as a broker
for the accident.
And what did you say?
I acted like I didn't know anything,
so don't worry.
There's no evidence
for the hit-and-run accident,
so they'll take you in
for accepting bribes.
They'll detain you
to begin investigating the accident.
Yes, so find an attorney for me
as soon as possible.
I won't share your name,
so don't worry about that.
Okay.
Hey, Attorney Kim.
I need you to go
to the police station now.
Detective Cho
and the driver must know each other.
Why don't we conduct
a confrontational questioning?
That's a great idea.
He keeps refusing to see us.
Will he agree to do that?
Mr. Yoon kept sending him food...
and wrote him many letters,
so shouldn't he meet him?
He's completely under
Myung Ji's grip.
Were you hurt?
Yes, right. One moment, please.
You got hurt trying to save me.
Didn't we have great teamwork?
Except that you got hurt.
It's a glorious wound for me.
Did that hurt?
It was cold.
Something like that can't hurt me.
No way. I'm sure it stings.
I'm glad it wasn't any worse.
All my pain goes away...
when you touch it.
Then, I'll keep my hands on you.
We should be together...
until the end of time.
Until the end of time.
You're fine, right?
Mr. Yoon.
Yes?
You can meet him.
- Please follow me.
- Did he agree to see me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
I have nothing to say.
Please stop sending me letters.
I came to say that.
Then,
please hear me out.
I can't bring back my late daughter.
But help us bring her justice...
and let her bereaved family...
say goodbye to her in peace.
There is...
nothing I can do.
He's my daughter's son.
This child is now eight years old.
You took his mother away from him.
I'm not asking for anything much.
Just testify the name of the person
who told you to cause the accident.
You must know who Choi Myung Ji is.
- I don't.
- And Detective Cho Byung Jin.
I don't.
Detective Cho...
was arrested
and put under interrogation.
Even if you hold out,
it'll be the end of you
as soon as he talks.
You have a daughter, too.
You needed money because of her.
Would your daughter be happy
that you did something like this?
You can't undo
the crime you've committed.
But you can be forgiven.
Please help me.
Just testify that
Choi Myung Ji was behind this.
Then, I will...
forgive you and help you.
Did you meet him? What's he like?
He was an ordinary man.
How did he end up
doing something like this?
It had to be money.
What else would it be?
- Will he help us?
- Not yet.
But I thought meeting him was
a huge success today.
I'll do whatever it takes
to persuade him.
Our best move is to make the driver
put pressure on Detective Cho...
and then let him spill the beans
on Myung Ji.
We have to get the two
in a confrontational questioning.
Okay.
I'll try to let that happen, too.
They'll try to persuade those two.
Do not let them conduct...
- a confrontational questioning.
- No, ma'am.
Let Detective Cho know...
that he'll be dismissed or suspended
for accepting bribes,
but if he's charged
with murder instigation,
his life will be ruined altogether
whenever you meet him.
Tell him
not to worry about his family.
Yes, ma'am.
I just received an update...
that the hit-and-run driver
agreed to meet Mr. Yoon.
What?
He held out well to this day.
Why did he suddenly do this?
He can't begin to meet them.
Ban him from accepting visitors
starting tomorrow.
Find a way to send the hit-and-run driver
to another detention center.
The hit-and-run driver?
The one who hit Yu Jin?
What are you up to?
Please excuse me.
- Sure. Good work, Attorney Kim.
- Yes, ma'am.
I heard something
about the hit-and-run driver.
What was that about?
What hit-and-run driver?
I was discussing your embezzlement.
She was talking
about the hit-and-run driver.
Did she really do that to Yu Jin,
just as Aunt Yeo Jin said?
Was I sued for embezzlement?
Not yet.
Why hasn't Yeo Jin sued me yet?
I find that suspicious, too.
And I returned the million dollars,
so don't worry.
- Where are you going?
- I'm meeting my blind date.
You made a wise decision.
If he says something about
the article on your embezzlement,
tell him everything was fabricated,
that we're the victims.
I'll manage.
Since when did you manage anything?
It's belated, but I'll do it now.
And smile, will you?
Your life isn't over
just because you're fired.
You can get married
and become an even bigger success.
Goodness.
Do you not mind even
if my mom and I are both criminals?
There's only a hair of difference...
between what's illegal, expedient,
or legal when you run a business.
You were unlucky, so you got caught.
How generous.
An embezzlement charge is
not even a problem.
But there was talk
about how you two were behind...
the accident that killed
Chairwoman Shin's late daughter.
You two didn't do that, did you?
What's with that serious face?
I was just checking.
Honestly speaking,
my parents were against you.
You've been in too many scandals,
so the whole nation knew about you.
But I told them
that I wanted to marry you, so...
- Let's get married.
- Really?
I know you have
lots of women in your life.
- Them? It's...
- I don't care.
You can date them.
I also know that you gamble.
Keep doing it. It's not my money.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
You're almost too chill.
I heard about your family, too.
Your mom has
complicated money problems,
and you've separated
from Chairwoman Shin, too.
I don't care.
My family has more money.
Just let us never worry about money.
That's all I want.
That's a given.
Let's marry within three months.
Three months? I'm down.
We seem to speak the same language.
I'll need more money
to keep Detective Cho...
and the driver's mouths shut.
I should sell off this house
as soon as possible.
Or should I use that money...
to hire someone and kill the driver?
Ms. Choi.
Yes? I want to sell the place
as soon as I can.
The faster, the better.
Many people will come and see it
when I tell them...
that it used to belong
to Hyesung's chairwoman.
No, just show it to people
who actually want to buy it.
It's not an attraction.
- Okay. Please excuse me, then.
- Goodbye.
- You're back already?
- Are you selling the house?
It's a hassle to start a renovation,
so we'll sell it
and move somewhere else.
How did it go?
I'll marry him.
Really?
Use this chance
to leave your mother...
and live on your own.
Everyone is once a rando.
Even if I pick and choose,
men are all the same.
So? Will you marry him?
Yes, Ji Seok.
I'll marry him.
(Chairman Goo Ji Seok)
You'll abandon me now that
you got a good use of me?
I helped you take this position,
Ji Seok!
Did you really rat me out?
That's enough.
It's all your fault.
She got fired...
and cut ties with her mom.
She must be having a rough time.
You should stay seated.
I'm perfectly capable of moving,
so I should help out.
I need to earn my keep, too.
I'll go over to your place
to grab Eun Chong's toys.
Are you sure you can go alone?
I'll go with Jin Goo.
Hey, stop making such a fuss.
Come and eat.
Eun Chong, how many times
do I have to say no...
to the pot lid alarm?
It wasn't a pot lid today.
You must've acted
as your uncle's alarm very often.
Yes, he was
Uncle Ji Chang's alarm clock.
- I'll use a recorder tomorrow.
- No way.
Yesterday, I saw you making
only shrieking sounds on it.
Then, I'll practice some more
before I use it to wake you up.
I'll set an alarm
and wake myself up,
so just eat your food.
- Come here.
- Stop it.
Cut it out.
I set up a meeting on the weekend
to meet the man's family. Okay?
You can manage this.
It's not like
you're walking into your death.
Jin Goo must've felt like this...
when he had to marry me.
Don't think like that.
You should look forward
to living a good life with him.
And go on a few dates, too.
Is that the realtor?
I came to get Eun Chong's toys.
Did you take off the cameras, too?
I'm doing what I want with my home.
Is there a problem?
Take your stuff and go.
Yes, Jae Jun.
I heard our families were meeting
on the weekend to discuss our marriage.
We can meet
at the Western cuisine restaurant...
at the Hyesung Hotel.
Yes.
Se Young is marrying...
the son of a rich family.
- Let's go upstairs.
- Okay.
- Hello. Feel free to look around.
- Sure.
The place looks great.
Why are you selling?
I'm sick of the place.
You took good care of it,
although it hasn't been renovated
in a while.
Yes, once you buy it,
you can turn the place inside out.
Are you selling this house?
Mind your own business and leave.
She put the house out on sale?
She knows I gave birth to Yu Jin
and raised her there,
so she's trying to mess with me.
Did you apply for an injunction
to prohibit disposition?
Yes, it'll take some more time
until the decision is made.
I'll try to stop
the house from selling.
Please don't worry about it.
That impudent woman.
Se Young is getting married?
Who told you that?
I heard it at her place.
She was on the phone with the guy,
saying they'd meet on the weekend...
at the Western cuisine restaurant
at the Hyesung Hotel on the weekend.
You didn't know?
No.
How is marrying this easy?
It's like she went out to shop.
I heard you were getting married.
Yes.
With who?
- You saw him.
- That blind date?
Do you know what he's like?
A rich womanizer...
who likes to gamble.
Why are you suddenly marrying
a man like that?
- Did your mom make you do this?
- Yes.
I'll grant her one last wish...
and escape from her grasp.
I don't want to be
miserable anymore.
You said you'd rebel against her.
I am rebelling.
I won't see her anymore
as soon as I marry him.
I wasn't picky about anything.
All I wanted was money.
Then, things became very simple.
Love? I don't need that.
Don't do it.
Who do you think you are?
It's not like you'll marry me.
You don't want me,
but you also don't want
others to have me?
Do you think marriage will
help you escape from your mom?
How are you going to do that
by giving up on yourself?
Go abroad to study instead.
Don't say it like you care.
If you think about it,
you're the meanest one.
Do you know how miserable I feel?
You took advantage of me,
then abandoned me.
But my mom will never leave me.
Well, she'll only sell me off.
Yes.
Both your mom and I
gave you a hard time.
Why are you adding to this?
It's your life.
You should reconsider.
I'll live a good life
as if I'm rubbing it in your face.
Are you marrying him
to rub it in my face?
I have no idea.
I felt like
I should at least get married.
If life gets too tough,
I'll just divorce him.
It's appalling
to see you seem concerned.
Don't ever call me again.
You and I are over.
If I ask you to be with me,
will you say yes?
Why?
Are you going to marry me?
- It's already too late.
- Why?
Marrying someone my mom wants is...
one last present I can give her.
The driver wanted to meet you?
Yes, I'm on my way to see him.
Do you want to come?
Of course, I'll go.
Call me when you're nearby.
Is something going on?
The driver reached out to Sung Ho
and said he wanted to meet.
Really?
That sounds like good news.
I'm sure it is.
Thank you.
I came with my wife.
I'm sorry.
It seemed like
you had something to say.
Why did you want to see me?
Why did you do that?
Why did you do that
to my poor daughter?
If I can,
I want to break this window...
and take your life, too.
But I changed my mind.
Please help us.
You're the only one
who can bring justice to my daughter.
I've committed
my share of sins in my life.
When I was the perpetrator,
I thought money was
the only thing victims wanted.
But now that I've become the victim,
I realized what I wanted was...
a heartfelt apology, not money.
If you truly wish
to apologize to us,
then help us bring justice
to our daughter's death.
Please.
We won't ask for more.
Can you just do that one thing?
Please think of our grandson.
You also have a child of your own.
At least tell the police that
there was someone behind this.
Then, I can forgive you
for everything.
I will.
I'll request
confrontational questioning...
with Detective Cho.
- Really?
I'm not sure if he'll say yes.
Tell the detective that
Detective Cho made you do it.
Then, you'd be able
to make him move.
Okay.
Thank you.
Can they arrest the instigator...
after the confrontational questioning?
The chance goes up.
I hope it happens.
Do you know who's behind everything?
No.
Goodness.
Why would any human
in their right mind...
make someone do that
just to harm another?
I wonder.
Anyway, whoever is behind this is...
probably someone
who knows the chairwoman's daughter.
Who could it be?
The couple went to see him together?
I told you
to ban him from seeing anyone!
What did Detective Cho say?
He won't agree to do
the confrontational questioning,
so he told you to trust him
and not to worry.
Of course, he'll say no.
But the detective
may put them up for this.
If the driver says...
Detective Cho was behind it,
Cho will begin to feel
great pressure.
I'll meet with Cho
after I meet my future in-laws.
Tell him to refuse the questioning
until he sees me.
If I ask you to be with me,
will you say yes?
You'll meet your in-laws soon.
Why don't you go to a spa
and get a facial?
Don't act too servile...
in front of his family
when you meet them.
If you do, I'll feel like
you're really selling me off.
I never act too servile.
Hello? I'm Choi Myung Ji.
The police station?
What does this concern?
Did Detective Cho spill everything?
The embezzlement?
I'm not free on the weekend.
I'll be at the police station
on Monday.
Goodbye.
- Did they sue me?
- Yes.
I was called as a testifier...
to confirm a few things.
I can't believe we're tasting
the same black tea...
as the British royals in our house.
It feels like a dream.
Gosh. It's just bitter.
I prefer this.
Me, too.
It's probably not easy
for younger people to enjoy.
I like it.
I have the most luxurious taste
in this family.
You're only saying that
because it's expensive.
It's nice to be here
with my grandma, aunts, and uncle.
It's a shame that
Chairman Goo isn't here.
He can join us next time.
Please give me a chance.
Nothing I do will be enough
to pay everything back...
but allow me
to return your kindness.
And of course,
for everything I did wrong, too.
Okay, then.
Please punish Choi Myung Ji first.
It all depends
on the confrontational questioning.
We'll be able to get her
if the two men meet.
Really?
- You have our support.
- Yes.
It won't happen
if one person declines,
so it's not easy.
I was also worried that
the driver might change his mind.
I have a feeling that
it'll all go well.
I'll take your word for it.
- Yeo Jin.
- Mr. Yoon.
What brings you here without a call?
Is something going on?
Detective Cho and the driver
finally met.
They did?
Did they do the questioning?
This is great news.
(Chairman Goo Ji Seok)
She was on the phone with the guy,
saying they'd meet on the weekend...
at the Western cuisine restaurant
at the Hyesung Hotel on the weekend.
Let me see you.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Anyway, is your husband
running late?
He's abroad on a business trip,
so he can't come today.
Did he have to leave in a hurry?
It was already scheduled.
Golf is more important to him
than meeting the in-laws.
Hey.
I heard you were fired
and now have become unemployed.
Good. You can focus on
assisting my son.
Yes, right.
I'll teach her well.
Please be kind to her.
Who is it?
Does Ms. Choi Myung Ji live here?
We're the police.
Are you Ms. Choi?
She doesn't live here.
This was her legal address.
If you want to find her,
go to the Western cuisine restaurant
at the Hyesung Hotel.
You look quite worried
for a young woman.
Is it because
you went through a lot,
including the canceled marriage
and your dismissal?
I like her vibe.
Sure.
Come in.
Excuse me.
We're from Yongju Police Station.
Which one of you is
Ms. Choi Myung Ji?
That's me.
You're here
because of the embezzlement, right?
Let's talk outside.
You're under arrest without a warrant
for murder instigation.
What? What did you say?
What are you doing?
You're arrested without a warrant...
due to the possibility
of evidence destruction and flight.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it. What are you doing?
I didn't do it.
Se Young, I didn't do it.
Myung Ji,
your fall and destruction
will begin now.
No!
It wasn't me. Let go of me. Let go.
Se Young, it wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
No. I didn't do it.
It wasn't me! No!
(Cinderella Game)
I never gave out such an order!
- Murder instigation?
- It's not true!
You've killed someone, too. Right?
Are you sure you didn't do it, Mom?
It's all my fault.
Myung Ji deceived us since that day.
I'm so scared and frightened.
I saw her at the police station.
Something didn't feel right.
I want to make a decision...
for the first and the last time.
Se Young!
I need to look for Se Young.