(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were
filmed under production guidelines.)
(Episode 15)
Yu Jin. My baby.
- Mommy.
- My baby.
How did you get here?
You kept praying, right?
So, I came to see you.
Come here, my baby.
Yu Jin.
My baby. Pumpkin.
Yu Jin?
Pumpkin!
Yu Jin.
Yu Jin, where are you, my baby?
Come to Mommy.
Don't go, Yu Jin.
Yu Jin!
You kept praying, right?
So, I came to see you.
You came to see me
because I kept praying?
You will...
come to see me, right?
She has a sad story
of losing her only daughter...
a long time ago.
Bang Ul, can you make us some tea?
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
- Is the chairwoman at work?
- She's leaving in the afternoon.
So, she'll have lunch
before she leaves.
I know everyone at her office,
but I haven't seen you before.
I heard the head director's
older sister recently started.
Is that you?
Yes.
Please do your best for Ms. Yoon.
She needs help
from her junior staff.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Here.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Have some.
- Yes.
I don't know
how this will come across,
but Mr. Goo has
practically stolen...
President Hwang's position.
I heard he canceled
the contract with the hotel, too.
Why would your younger brother
do that to your workplace?
Are you two on bad terms?
No.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing for you to apologize.
Don't mention that
I said something like this,
but put in a good word to him.
Or you can tip me off quietly
if you know anything.
No?
All right. You can finish your tea.
You can grab a cab.
Goodness, no.
It's all right. I have cab fare.
You came here on business,
so your travel should be covered.
Otherwise, I heard
it could be seen as a power trip.
Hello, Ms. Jang?
Have you heard anything from him?
I had a hunch
I'd have an update on Yu Jin.
Please look into it.
Hey, was someone here?
One of Se Young's juniors.
She left a file.
- Would you like something, ma'am?
- No.
I dozed off and dreamed of Yu Jin.
Did you have the same dream again?
This time, it was different.
She'd always cry
and go further away,
but this time,
she showed me a huge smile.
My goodness.
That was a wonderful dream.
Yes, Yeo Jin.
It must be a good sign.
I've never had
such a long dream about her.
And she has never smiled before.
There must be great news ahead.
Should I find a good fortuneteller?
I wanted to turn the fireplace back
to how it looked before.
The fireplace? All of a sudden? Why?
I'll clean it up, Ms. Chairwoman.
Yes, you should make it look clean.
We boarded up the fireplace long ago
ever since Yu Jin had disappeared.
Why did she give me so much money?
Gosh, what do I do?
It'll be weird to go back
and return it to her.
Where's Ms. Goo?
I sent her on a work task.
It's odd to say this
without her here,
but Ms. Goo is the exclusive guide
for guests from Dubai.
She already has experience,
and she has done good work
during the Hyesung Hotel incident.
Please show her your support.
I'm going to Hanguk Hotel.
Have a great day, everyone.
- See you.
How can she be the exclusive guide?
Do you think
it's because of Director Goo?
He messed with our business.
Why would he give her a chance?
It's such a mystery.
Does she have a bigger connection
than Director Goo?
She must have
the most fascinating connections.
- Ms. Yoon, are you okay with her?
- Why would I be okay?
Stop chatting and get to work.
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh, hello, Mr. Hwang.
Where have you been?
Whose clothes is that?
It's for Ms. Yoon, isn't it?
As I mentioned before,
turn down these personal errands.
You'll be busy soon.
Okay.
As you know, we're having guests
from Dubai starting next month.
You'll be the exclusive guide.
You should put together
a program proposal.
Really?
So, why me?
What's so bad about you?
- Do you not feel confident?
- Goodness, no.
I'll do a great job.
That's good, then.
Thank you.
All right!
I brought your coat, Ms. Yoon.
Excuse me, Ms. Yoon.
Please return this to your mother.
- What's this?
- Your mother gave it for a cab,
but it was too much,
so I thought I should return it.
Do I have to run your errands?
You should've said no to my mom
if you didn't want it.
Why did you bring it here
and ask me to return it?
Why?
Were you going to keep it
if the amount was decent?
But did you get scared
when you saw too much inside?
Is that why you are
making my mom look weird?
What? No.
- Then, I'll return it myself...
- Forget it.
(Team Leader Yoon Se Young)
What's this?
Why was this stained?
What? Where?
Right here. Can't you see?
I think...
the fabric is supposed to be...
Get your hands off.
Why? Were you offended?
No.
Mr. Hwang said I was the exclusive guide
for Dubai guests.
If she finds that awful,
then it must be true.
You must pay us three times as much
as compensation for breaking terms.
If you tell me who your investor is,
then we will
adjust the compensation.
Mr. Hwang, just accept the trend.
We will pay the compensation,
so stop nitpicking.
You're a reasonable man.
- "Reasonable?"
- It's reasonable to follow trends.
It's always reasonable
to follow the trend.
No, in these times,
we must be especially vigilant.
Hyesung Tour was
intentionally attacked,
so I must know the reason
not to suffer twice.
I heard the investor was American.
Was the investor a Korean-American?
I don't know.
Do you know Richard Han?
It looks like
President Hwang is suspecting us...
as Hanguk Hotel's investors.
If he already mentioned my name,
they'll just have
to find the evidence.
It won't be easy
Why don't you rush
the Dubai project?
Hanguk Hotel and Hyesung Hotel...
What's next? The Dubai deal?
It'll take a while
to develop the Dubai project.
- Why?
- Hwang Jin Goo got ahead of me.
I'll begin by canceling contracts
for restaurants and rental cars.
President Hwang must be
an unexpected challenge.
And Chairwoman Shin seems to be
looking for her lost daughter.
She has been quiet
for a while, hasn't she?
Why has she resumed the search?
There are no known reasons.
She must've wanted to find her
as her parent.
We'll talk in person soon.
Yes, I wish to meet you soon, sir.
An envelope with money went missing?
I put it in the drawer,
but it's not there.
Who was in the office during lunch?
We went out to eat together
and came back together.
Was Ms. Goo here?
I wonder.
I didn't see her at the restaurant.
Ms. Goo, where have you been?
I went to the archives
to find books on Dubai.
Soo Jung, Jin Kyung,
go through her drawers.
Yes.
- Go.
- What's wrong?
Why are you going through my drawer?
Only you saw me putting
this envelope into my drawer.
Is that the envelope?
There it is.
Did you give it back as a show,
then decide to steal it?
What? No.
Wait, why was this in my bag?
I don't know what this is about.
Then what? Did someone else
put this in your bag?
- Gosh, is there a CCTV here?
- No.
You knew it wasn't around
when you stole it.
No, I really didn't steal it.
I told you
about three strikes, didn't I?
I got you the third time.
Leave right now.
What's going on?
- How much?
- It was 500 dollars.
I found it in her bag,
yet she denied it.
She's so brazen.
If she said she didn't do it,
then it must be true.
Why would she confess
that she was the thief?
The money was in her bag.
Why do you keep doing this?
You're always on her side.
I wasn't taking her side.
I'd say the same for anyone else.
What if someone else
put that in her bag?
That's absurd.
We cannot ignore that possibility.
Make sure you handle it cautiously.
We keep losing our hotel contracts,
so don't let our staff lose spirits.
And make sure
we don't let the word go out.
My auntie needs to repay her debt.
"Debt?" How much is it?
And why are you paying it off?
I just need 10 50-cent coins.
I wanted to check the CCTV
in the corridor to see...
who went into the office at lunch.
- The Tour Planning Team?
- Yes.
- So, between 12:30 p.m. to 1 p.m.?
The CCTV in the corridor
was turned off at that hour.
It was turned off? Why?
Was there an update
or maintenance scheduled?
I don't see any notice
for that time period.
Then, could someone have...
turned it off
and back on intentionally?
Who knows?
There is a bit of chance.
Who could be?
Only Ms. Yoon and I saw her...
put the envelope into her drawer.
I told you not to call me.
I'm guessing
no one is bothering you these days.
No one, my foot.
So? Do you need me?
I'll ask if I need your help.
- Don't get ahead of yourself.
- Right.
It's already been six years.
Don't you think
I did such a neat job?
Neat, my foot.
You've been haunting me for years.
I'll wait for your call.
Good grief.
Ji Eun, there was a theft
at Hyesung Tour.
Someone stole
from Ms. Yoon Se Young.
What? Who was this brave brat?
How did you know it was a woman?
Someone who pulled strings
to get her job.
If she didn't get the job fairly,
she should at least do her job well.
Hyesung Tour?
- What's her name?
- No idea.
I heard she was a tour guide...
who started days ago.
Darn it.
The person you have reached is...
Why won't you pick up?
Why did you have to go
to your nephew's kindergarten?
You don't have to answer me
if it's private.
My nephew took up jobs
trying to help me.
To pay your debt back?
How did you know?
I ran into him in the alley.
And I got a flyer, too.
He cared so much about his auntie.
I should be a better aunt.
And I paid off my debt.
- You did?
- Yes.
Actually, I met my ex-boyfriend
on that day...
to pay him back.
I ended up sharing too much.
This is embarrassing.
Well, people sometimes go into debt.
I caused
too many commotions, haven't I?
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
You first met me
when I took up an illegal gig,
so I could understand the suspicion.
You said you'd never do that again.
I trust my staff members,
and that includes you.
So, make sure
you prove your innocence.
Don't take the false blame
over just 500 dollars.
Thank you for giving me your trust.
Is there a way
to prove your innocence?
Not yet.
Yes, something was weird
with the CCTV in the corridor.
- Why?
- I think someone turned it off...
just during lunch on purpose.
- "On purpose?"
- Yes.
The security office said turning it off
in a certain range of time...
usually happens
under maintenance notices.
But there were no notices,
and the reason was unknown.
They'll look into it
and get back to me.
Let me know when you hear back.
Yes, sir.
He's been searching through villages
near the sea where she went missing.
A few years ago,
a young woman and a kid...
came by looking
for someone like Yu Jin.
He left his contact there,
so he'd look into it and call back.
If that young woman knows Yu Jin,
all I have to do is
find her contact.
I'm home, Aunt Yeo Jin.
Hey, you're home.
You lit the fireplace.
I wanted to use it this winter.
Why is she
suddenly lighting the fireplace?
Because of that dream
she had of Yu Jin?
Who knows?
Leave her alone.
It's not a big deal.
How did it go with the envelope?
I made her look like a thief.
I found fault with her,
so she'd be fired very soon.
I considered reporting her
for taking a bribe.
Good. Great job.
No one could find out
you were behind this, right?
She wants to prove her innocence,
but there's no way.
Can you think of a way?
We can't let her get kicked out
by taking false blame as a thief.
She's getting bashed into pieces
for pulling strings and stealing.
She was framed.
Otherwise, why would it
show up in her bag?
And the envelope was
from Yoon Se Young's mother.
"Yoon Se Young's mother?"
- She staged this.
- "Staged?"
Why would she do that?
I should've returned it
when she gave it to me.
Why did I bring it to the office?
Who could it be?
It was a relief
that Mr. Hwang believed me.
Make sure you prove your innocence.
Don't take the false blame
over just 500 dollars.
How did he know it was 500 dollars?
Did Ms. Yoon tell him?
- Then, I'll return it myself...
- Forget it.
She didn't even open it...
when she stashed it in her drawer.
What's with that serious face?
- Are you imagining something?
- What? No.
Eun Chong, did you prepare
everything for tomorrow?
Yes, I have to bring...
Mommy's cell phone tomorrow.
What? Why?
It's a secret right now.
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Gosh. Why would a kid like you
keep secrets?
What could it be?
My gosh.
Get in!
Hello, Mr. Hwang.
I'll just take the bus.
Hop in. We're losing time.
Thank you.
We actually ran into each other
as neighbors.
Did you get some sleep?
I didn't think so.
I didn't sleep too well.
- May I ask you something?
- Sure.
How did you know it was 500 dollars?
Ms. Yoon said so. Why?
I was wondering
if words got around everywhere.
- I need to take this.
- Sure.
Hey, what's up?
Ha Na, the envelope thing
could've been staged by Yoon Se Young.
- What do you mean?
- Don't you know what it means?
Does she hate you?
Is there a reason
why she needs to frame you?
I don't know.
How did you come up with that idea?
- Ji Seok did.
- Ji Seok?
He wouldn't tell me why,
but he was sure
Yoon Se Young staged this.
Gosh, how am I going to get her?
Why would Ji Seok think so?
That's enough.
What's enough?
Your immature and crude play.
Are you dreaming?
You aren't fully awake yet.
How will you handle this later?
You were worried about me?
How despicable.
Yes.
That's how you should respond.
You'll become
the main hero of this play.
Wait, you aren't the main hero.
You're the biggest villain.
So, people can get better
at talking nonsense.
Speak for yourself.
You seem like a real heiress
after acting like one for a while.
- Has the real heiress died?
- You're crazy.
- Ji Seok.
- If you quit when I told you to,
you wouldn't be in this situation.
What?
Ms. Yoon, why is my desk outside?
You're no longer with Hyesong Tour
as of yesterday. You didn't know?
I never resigned.
You've been struck out.
Does Hyesung Tour have
a strikeout policy?
I thought you weren't allowed
to fire employees recklessly.
So, you'll bring the law into this?
I can call the police.
Let's handle the theft first.
Beat it.
I don't want to see you around here.
The CCTV in the corridor...
could've been tampered with
just during lunchtime.
What? Says who?
I confirmed it
with the security office.
They'll find the reason
and give me an answer,
so I will leave on my own...
if I turn out to be the perpetrator.
Why is the desk out there?
- She must've been fired.
- I think so.
Be quiet.
- Hello.
Why did you say
the camera was tampered with?
That woman kept prying,
so he must've told her
what was in the manual.
Did you destroy everything
that could be used as evidence?
Call me immediately
if anything happens.
Hanguk Hotel's investor is
also Richard Han?
Yes, I don't have hard evidence yet,
but circumstantial evidence
seems to point to him.
If that is true,
what do you think he's after?
I need to know what he's like
to give you an answer.
- When is he coming?
- The end of this month.
Let's schedule a meeting
as soon as he arrives.
Yes, ma'am.
(Missing Persons Unit)
What's wrong?
It's the Missing Persons Unit.
You should pick up.
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
A missing person you found
seemed to be my Yu Jin?
Yes, if she's in her thirties,
that's about Yu Jin's age.
Where is she right now?
She doesn't remember?
How's her condition?
Do you have a picture of her?
I should run a parentage test first.
Yes.
All right. Thank you.
Are you all right?
You should have this.
So, the DNA sample was a match...
with a missing person
who could be Yu Jin, right?
Yes.
Yes, there was a chance
our DNA could match.
Congratulations, Chairwoman Shin.
This was the first time
you had a DNA match.
I'm so happy for you.
This isn't a dream, is it?
Can I really believe this, Jin Goo?
No, it's not a dream.
You can believe it.
So, what did they say?
Yes, they asked me...
to take a new DNA sample
and send it to the police station.
Call Dr. Hong.
Let me do it right away.
Yes, I'll escort you there.
Don't let anyone find out
until I have the final result.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's take your sample.
Okay.
You're all done.
I'm Lee Eun Chong,
and my most cherished item is...
this cell phone.
This phone has...
videos of me and my mommy,
who's in paradise.
My mommy, who's in paradise,
passed away in a car accident
when I was one.
I cannot see her,
but I can still see her
and listen to her voice...
on this phone,
so this is my most cherished item.
But someone who is
the dearest to me is...
my auntie, Auntie Ha Na!
Okay.
I'm the dearest person to you,
Eun Chong,
so I won't let people
treat me unfairly.
I'll make sure I clear my name.
Yu Jin.
Was that why
you came to see me in my dream?
We will meet again. We will.
I'm home, Aunt Yeo Jin.
Were you looking at Yu Jin's photos?
Get changed and come downstairs...
- for a cup of tea.
- Okay.
The police station called me.
- With an update on Yu Jin?
- Yes.
This missing person they found
had a DNA match with me.
She's about the same age, too.
Oh, my. Was it Yu Jin?
My goodness.
Congratulations, Yeo Jin.
Se Young, this is big news.
We found Yu Jin.
Really, Aunt Yeo Jin?
You found Yu Jin?
I have to wait for the DNA test.
If your DNAs match,
it must be 100 percent certain.
When will they have the result?
I told them to do it
as quickly as possible.
It'll come out within the week.
The wait still seems too long.
Can't they rush it?
My heart is racing.
I've already waited 20 years,
so a few days wasn't a problem.
Yes, you're right.
It's just a few days.
Do you like that one?
Here.
Eun Chong, you were
also so adorable back then.
Do I look like my mommy?
Yes, of course.
Your sparkly eyes, defined nose,
cute lips,
and you're brave like her, too.
You're just like her.
Go to sleep if you're sleepy.
Let's go to sleep.
All right.
Your mommy helped
prove my innocence...
when people framed me as a thief
at the children's home.
What would your mommy have done...
if she were still with us?
Keep it quiet
until we have the result.
- Of course.
- Yes.
Have some.
What's wrong?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I was a little excited
to hear about Yu Jin.
Do you like that one?
This one, too.
I have to find
Eun Chong's grandmother, too.
But I'm getting no matches
with his DNA,
and there are no leads.
Fireplace. Wooden swing.
Hot chocolate. Marshmallow.
Can I really find her
with these leads?
If you hadn't
gotten into that accident,
would we have found his grandmother?
Du Na, tell me.
Who were you with...
just before your death?
I'm dying to see her.
But of course, not as much as you.
Thank you.
(Cinderella Game)
I can't believe it. I'm scared.
Yu Jin will never show up.
Let's get moving.
We should cut it down
when we have a chance.
I'll offer a deal
that is hard to turn down.
I never stole
that envelope with money.
I don't know anything.
Please help vindicate Ms. Goo Ha Na.
Shouldn't you focus more
on the bet you have going with me?
There's a criminal here
at Hyesung Tour's office,
so arrest her immediately.
What are you doing?
Someone like you
can't win against me.